Okay, okay, all right. Did you tweet? I'm about to. Okay, I'm waiting for the retweet potential. It's right there?
It's very it's very boring. It's just a basic boring tweet. Yeah, but like I I would have to write my own. All right, so
Hey
What's up, everybody? How's everybody doing?
Welcome to Elden Ring Co-op. Which one of us will become the Elden Lord? Only one of us can. All right
Uh, I got everything going. Let's open this up. All right. Are we good? I think we're good
All right. So we here are two. I know there's no intro. I know I know I get we were so late
I just do that. Well, you need a little bit of intro. All right. Here's a little bit of an intro for you
There might be some people that you know, check the bars like I don't even know what this is. What are they doing?
Right. Okay. So we have installed your mic is weird. Oh
No, it's not one guy. I mean my mic is weird. Who said that?
Oh, it's a one. Okay. Why how is it possible that I could read that? All right
Anyways, so we have installed right now. We have the seamless co-op mod
Which means that we can both be in the game. We don't have to do any signs or soap stone things
We're just in the game together permanently
We also have randomizer on all the randomized enemies that we don't know what they are
We have no idea nice McDonald's voice time that person over a day
All of all of the items are randomized and all of the monsters are randomized and I believe even between us
We might have different random seeds for items
So what you pick up is going to be different than what I pick up
And the way the randomizer worked from the last time I used it is like every time you pick up like the basic
Roa berry, uh, that item is always a different item
It's not a different item every time you pick one of them up like a roa berry could be
Sledgehammer really you'll just constantly be picking up sledgehammer. Yeah. Yeah, I'm me strong by the way
This is me strong. I told you I promised a me strong playthrough and this is what it is
Uh, this is me smart inspired by blanca. If I roll you guys make lightning you do. Oh, all right
You guys ready? Are we wait make sure everyone is everybody here. Are you present?
There's a couple people missing stirs is it stir is quiet. Hold on. I'll fix it. I'll fix it stir
You're a little quiet. Let me turn you up. Okay. I'll talk a little louder
You don't have to do it. I got you say can you say you're like your abc's real quick?
a b c d e f g
h i j k l m n o p
I have a friend who can't recite the criken can't recite the alphabet
Did you get louder like how are you not louder for me right now? Um, I don't know. This is very bizarre
I'm turning you up in discord, but you're not being turned up at all to me. Uh
Pump up the volume pump it up pump up the volume
Okay, I turned you up as high as I could possibly turn you up. I think it's you you think it's me
All right, is that is that better because I don't know what's going on with what's wrong with it
Say your abc's one more time a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z
I don't know what's wrong with you. What's wrong with me if I mess up like better. All right. All right, let's go. Okay
My apologies will come later. Oh, that's right
You have to go and look at a full apology like dude
Do you want to fight the boss or do you want to like I need like full attention to explain the like 10 step
Program of how i've ruined your day and like how we're never gonna talk again
No, all right
Let's let's fight dracula and then we'll talk about it. All right elden ring co-op with randomizers
I hope you remember the buttons because we kept drinking elixirs every time we went to go open a door
I remember hey, can we be the tutorial? No, you think we can be the tutorial boss. He's taking like no damage
Get good first person to die here. Um has to I don't know something funny
All right, you're gonna better queue up something funny
Get a first person to die something funny they have to do. Oh you have to do something funny
I've never been funny ever
You're supposed to be high right now
You don't know anything
I'm kidding. I'm
Don't please wait. Is that why you like you left the room before we started you go do like edibles?
No weird. No, are you like a delinquent streamer now? Are you like no hell what happened? I'm so concerned
What happens fond in the tutorial instantly died and now i'm watching your character with no health float
Just float just not moving float
Because i'm at a loading screen. Oh, yeah
All right. All right. So here's what we're gonna do. Uh, we're just gonna I mean
Maybe this is why they wait. No, no, no, this is normal. This is normal. This happens. This is normal
We this is this is fine. We just have to read just restart. This is fine. I'm i'm you're gonna touch a shrine or
I'm I think we have to restart
No, go through the tutorial and rest at one of the bonfires. Yes. Okay. All right. All right. All right
We'll just just let everybody just chill out. We're good. Well, everyone just chill up chill out. Everything's fine
All right, we're just gonna exit. Okay. Yeah, there is always league of legends to
If this doesn't work, i'm not playing league of legends. Okay. All right. So just open the game up
That's not there's no problems at all. Like there's not a problem
Just the more that we focus on the negativity the more that it's going to cause a problem
So just open it back up get to a spot before you're closing the game
I I was stuck. Oh, i'm stuck too. Yeah, just I would just restart it get out to that first bonfire
The one with um, you know when you see like the big open area just relax
Yeah, I I had been told that you you had to get to the first bonfire and now I see why
Okay. All right. Just that's all right
Okay
Everything is good to go. I'm just opening it again. Relax. I know a lot of people are like oh my god
Not like this. Everything's everything's going exactly that is not like this right that all that's all over we've all
Okay
so originally we were going to start when my food got here and I finished eating because we didn't want to get interrupted right and
Then my my food delivery man texted me saying hold on. I need to restart my car
Uh, because I because he was parked at the food place for like an hour
So that that was that's part one of why it was definitely my fault. My food was about an hour and 15 minutes late
Okay, and then also I tried to make everything easier for jerma and like tried to set some of this stuff up yesterday
And like I I was a little confused
I was like i'm gonna send you these files
And like everything that I did and everything I told him to do was wrong until at the very end
We were just like fine. Let's do it like just go through the steps
Just follow these steps and then everything worked but I I tried like three different ways
To give him
You were trying you were trying to make it so easy
Yeah, so easy and it ended up being so difficult. I made everything significantly harder
Okay
So I think i'm ready
I think i'm ready to you at that first like the one before you open the door before the the first bonfire that you can
Actually touch right? Yeah, um in the basement at the bonfire with the knife. I'm gonna turn you up a little bit more
Because it's people are saying you're still a little quiet
I can turn myself up a bit as well. Does that help talk say some stuff a b c d e f g h i j k elemental p
Is that better? We're good to go. All right. Is that good? Way better. Perfect. All right. Cool. All right. All right
Yeah, okay. Oh, yeah
All right, i'm coming in. Are you ready? I'm ready. I hope so you're at that first site of grace. I am turning this on
I'm I'm at the first site of grace. Yes. Oh, you can't see i'll turn it on. I'm
I can't contain it. I'm so excited. What the fuck was that noise? What?
It sounded like someone did a drive-by on you
What like I thought I just heard like a machine gun firing
No
All right. I'm that sounds like a bird in your room. Can you pick up this item? There's an item here
What is it? So is something weird? Oh dude
Why did I get so much stuff?
Sacred relic sword ash of wood. Did you get all these things?
I got I got a ripple blade and a smithing stone dude. I got all right
Our items are not the same by the way, but I got a lot of cool stuff. I can't even use it
Yeah, I can't equip it because we're
Well, whatever we have randomized loot does that cares? Yeah, it's gonna be a rough start before we can you know
Get something we can actually use that's an end game weapon. That's an end game boss weapon
Yeah, all right. The the big kicker is is this thing out here the same for both of us, right?
Well, the tutorial guy was already the same. So I think that's settled. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, come back here
Okay, let's do a bit. No, no, no
I'm just saying like it's been a while since I played this remember the first time you opened this door
You went like this. Did you do this? I did I was like, holy shit
You know what? I the first thing I did is I walked out here
I saw the night and I said wow i've seen I haven't seen anything in this game other than a whole bunch of streamers
Waste their time fighting this for three hours at the start of their streams
I'm not gonna bore you guys with that and i'm gonna walk by it
That's what I did
David you're the type of player that like opens the wikipedia page the second you install. I don't I didn't no
I just that was the only thing I knew is that I didn't want to fight that enemy for like two hours
There's always one dark souls enemy in the beginning that it was like oh I can beat it
And then they can't fucking beat it and they can't own up to that. They you didn't beat it, right?
How long did you fight it? Who is this by the way? Is this still the same character? Uh,
Yes, but I think they're what they're wearing is randomized. So they look different. Okay. Did you touch this touch it?
Let's take a let's take a little nap
All right. So by the way, keep in mind if either one of us sits at a bonfire it resets the whole game
So we have to be we have to okay. What's that? That's uh tree spirit, right? Yeah. Okay. So
All right. What do you want to do?
um
Well, I I think I mean I know exactly what we should do but I want to leave it to you
So we don't have another terraria moment. I mean the I don't think there is a terraria moment. What's what do you what's this?
Ooh, what's it? Oh, that's not that's normal. Yeah. No, that was different for me. I mean we we have to go get the horse, right?
Oh something was different. Yeah, so okay the first thing you do you got to run up to the church and rest there
Yes, and then you run to the other bonfire and then you get the horse
But like I don't I see it like I already feel like i'm dragging you. No, no, no, that's what I would have done
Okay, well I need you to say what you're gonna do and then like I want to be like you're the strong one
And I trust you so you should do magic then you should be like a magic user
I should be like the two-handed weapon user. Yeah, like ideally if I if I can find magic also, uh
Everything the merchant sells should also be randomized really. Oh a golden rune. Oh
Yeah, finding what's up, uh, like hero runes that you can pop in the early game are pretty funny. Look at that
I have a I have a tunic. Damn it. Okay. What do you got? Yeah, this is
Shit kindred of wrought ashes. I don't even know what the hell I want to do
Yeah, and one of the settings that I had enabled should exist. Um
The notes that they sell I think are hints to key items in case we can't find one
You can buy the notes from them and they'll be like, hey
Did you know that like the great rune is actually here take the giant's flame? I wouldn't screw up your game
What where oh you rest it the npc disappeared when you rushed it I was like, oh no
I'm super paranoid that like something else. I know but whatever
Look, it's it's a bunch of fucking mods. It's there's gonna be problems, right?
Okay
Well, then we gotta go up the road to the next bonfire so we can get our horse and also
Pick up any items we find so it's every single enemy is randomized
So that means that the random kind of tarnished that are walking around could just be like millennia. I believe so. Yeah
And they should be scary if they're if it is a boss, it's scaled down. This is still just a goat
This is the stuff. Wait, there's a hand they are scaled. All right, that's funny great dragonfly head. It's stupid
All right
I think the goats and stuff might not be randomized because they need to be
I don't know. I just all the animals aren't they're like not enemies. I don't know put it on
I don't think i've ever even seen that enemy in the game
All right, so we need to go wait. I can't open my map
Uh, because there's enemies targeting us that that flower is trying to kill us. Are you serious? All right. Well, it's scaled, right?
Yeah, they still take a million hits
I forgot I forgot. It's all right. Well, we'll we'll get there just stand on the poison. It doesn't matter. Just kill it
Are you dead? I thought it killed you in one hit. That scream made me think I was dead
Oh stagga stagga
I didn't know you could stagger the plants
Jesus christ
Okay, so what do we get for that?
Slumbering egg and an octopus. Oh free. I got trash. Let's get the bonfire in here
Oh, yeah, so we can be unpoisoned and we'll go the other way. Do you think we'll beat the first boss?
Uh, I mean the first boss
Could just be like a bandit. That's very true
Why are you still poisoned? Uh, i'm not you look you to me. You look like you're poisoned as well
Okay, let's just run we gotta get we gotta go get our dog
Somebody said we might have to restart the game one more time after this cutscene. Okay, somebody said stinky
Yeah, you just have like the sims
Uh, like hygiene is zero right now. Well, it's kind of what it's like. All right, let's see what happens
Hmm. Are you just gonna skip this? Yeah, I skipped it. You're sitting on the ground stinking for me
Okay, I'm I'm talking
except
Oh, I didn't even I didn't even get to talk to her. Oh you didn't no
You see me walking around? Yeah, you're just kind of walking around. All right. What happens if you sit down?
I mean I did I got the cutscene, but I didn't get to talk to her afterwards
Oh, there is the talk to millennia option
I'd like to an auto trigger. How do we make it so we don't smell?
I kind of like the stink. I kind of feel at home. Okay
I don't want to look at that the whole time. We play I bet you if you die, it'll be gone, baby
I mean you're stinking for me, but i'm okay with that. I don't mind it's not a big deal
How do I how do I get to that? There it is. No, don't do that. I wonder okay
All right commander. What do we do now? All right now open world. We can go anywhere get on your horse
I forgot how to do that too. I gotta equip it. All right, so we need to like level up
Let's clear out and we need to find some items. How wait, how do you?
Jesus how do you bookmark? Okay, so hit start just the regular start menu you go use your d-pad to go all the way to the right
This is where I put it is over in that pouch menu
You hit y to switch and then you hold y to get to that sub menu. That's how I do it
I'm remembering that's the last see I've uh, yeah, we've all played this game, but it was like three years ago
Let's feel like a while doesn't it? All right. So what's in the box for you? Oh, you don't stink anymore. Oh good
God's skin peeler got a perfume bottle. Do all this shit just takes I don't that thing's not bad, isn't it?
That thing's like really good
I need 17 strength and 22 dexterity
Oh, we need to establish a rule right now because we're finding different items
Are we allowed to drop items for the other person?
Like if I find a two-hander and you're like, oh dude, I want that right. Uh, what do you guys think?
I would say no unless a lot of essential
Uh, let's get a pull up. I think because i'm seeing if it's very it's very mixed. It's no. Yes. No, no
No, yes. Yes. Yes. I don't know. No. No. No. Yeah. Yeah
In the meantime found items. All right, let's click we have a problem. This person has a bunch of runes
I thought they're supposed to scale. I thought the enemy's scaled. I mean they do but
What why is it so much health? What's the ash of war with this thing? Our weapons just suck like i'm on a dagger
That's true. I'm gonna die
You know
Well, I can't believe that I can't believe we're already fighting the first boss
I mean this this sort of is if you think about it
It really is
He's just so fast
All right. What do you actually want to play as because we need to figure this out. I gotta find something. I I wouldn't play magic
Skip it around
This looks so weird. You're kind of like boarding around a little. All right
We got it
Ooh
They didn't drop anything me strong the priest. I feel like you're just you're getting things
Yeah, my game's really fun. Yours doesn't sound very fun
My i've started on not fun mode. I have enough to level up. We should probably do that
Well, you're gonna respawn that fucking boss enemy
Yeah, but I mean we need to level up. We're let's clear. Let's clear this area
I think I actually have the stone shard starting item to open up the door and we can try and get random items
I think this map item is also probably random. Oh, this is okay. I'm gonna pick up this map item
Okay, it is a map. All right, I got it
You dead? Oh it dead
Uh, wait, one of the god skin bosses is right here. So, uh, I don't know what what we need to do
Should we run or should we fight it? I am still naked with a dagger
But but I I can take it. I am a cleric
I have no flasks. I'm the smartest caveman. All right, i'm going back and sitting at the bonfire. Are you coming? Sure
This is aggroed onto us right now. Well, then do it what happened to you?
Nothing happened to me, but everything reset. All right. What do we this is important?
Give him your armor. Well, he has to ask nicely for it. It was the pole
Uh, overwhelmingly. Yes to share items. Yeah
That honestly surprises me. I mean I think I have to do strength to make this bearable
Well, I mean we can also just drop like end game boss weapons
Okay, do you yeah, do you want your gear here? How do I how do you drop something here? Now follow me?
Okay, this is my i'm my one directive. Okay, this is just following me. I'm gonna follow on your horse
Let's go. We ride watch out for the jelly, you know, all the like, uh,
The graves. Yeah that have a whole bunch of pickable like runes that are like there's like 10 runes on a whole bunch of
Well market great. We need to market. We gotta play. I'm not I kind of remember how to get there
But I don't remember where it is on the map. You sound like a dad like oh, yeah. I know I know where it is
Do you yeah, of course I do. I don't know where it is. But I know like the general here
I don't want a map. Hey, watch out for this giant rolling ball. You don't want to get you don't
Get squished by the ball
I think we should look at the map who needs a map. I don't want him. I I don't know how to look at the
Watch this
I do
I mean i'm in combat. I know you know what they look like on the map. They're like the little
Rectangles, I mean i'm pretty sure I know where i'm going
Do you?
Yeah, let's get this bonfire. Ooh
I am without maiden
Okay setting down
Do we what about the painting? Oh, I got death root from the dude. It's a random item
I got an ancient dragon smithing stone
All right. I'm still falling. You seem to know where you're going. I'm lost
You really are aren't you tell me the truth. No, it's no it's this way
Tell me the truth
I'm not lost if I were lost i'd say so because I wouldn't want to like
Derail any further than I have today. No, okay. You're right. You got it
No, you had it right. Yeah right here right here. So let's uh, just loot loot up
This feels like cheating. I like it
Okay smithing stones eclipse shotle
shuttle
royal knight armor
Golden anchor nine big anchor weapon. Yeah, i'm gonna build a level up like 30 times
Blasphemous claw. I don't even remember what that is. It's like a throwable. What I have a legendary over there. Whatever it is
Tonic of forgetfulness. Yeah, I didn't I got the anchor if you want it remembrance of the dragon lord. Wait, hold on
This is oh, this is the remembrance
Oh
That's a lot of souls dude, i'm gonna be like level 50 right now
We're gonna stomp through this game. Do you want did you get any actual armor?
I don't even know what this item is either actually. Uh, no, I still have no armor. How do I drop something?
I man, you know, I the poll said yes, but my my heart is still saying no your heart says no, okay. Yeah
I thought I was naked. I thought this dick was right there
I was like, oh my god. Oh god. Don't look don't look. Oh, that reminds me of a story
I was uh, I was getting the mods yesterday
So I was looking through the elden ring mod nexus
And I was just scrolling down to see other popular mods if there's anything else we could do
Oh, no, and then one came up and I was like, that's weird
Better nude model what objectively makes a nude model better than the other nude model and I clicked to open it
And then my wife walked in the room behind me and was like, what is that?
Somebody said don't scroll on nexus mods. Yeah, seriously popular mods you scroll down once and it's like
Do you want the naked?
Um doll the purple blue doll girl
Oh, we can also do that because it's night time if we go back to that bonfire
I forget how that works. You like rested it and she's like, oh
Oh, and you need that for the spirit things, but I imagine we're not summoning because we're already two people
All right. We've gone. Let's let's teleport back to
that church church of
Ella, right because then we'll probably get the cutscene we can i'm gonna love love like 30 times
Oh, it's a vote to warp. Oh, yeah, she was totally nude
But also she's a doll. It doesn't make sense warping takes forever for the non-host by the way. Okay, that's all right
Yeah, i'm already talking to her don't forget your helmet
I think she'll also give you a random item. She gave me a fire of blossoms
Now it is thine to do as thou wishest. All right. I have the spirit calling bell and a death root
I she's not even here, but I don't think it really matters. All right. I'm gonna level up like 15 to 30 times
Okay, i'm going to get one level. I can't level level three
It really looks like your dick's out dude, I know
But you didn't get any runes
No, how come i'm getting so many of these and you're not getting any well. I got I got this weapon
Both of me I get you want to you want to go up to the little startling zone cave with the mini boss in it
It's right here. Yeah, hold on. Let me talk to millennia blade of mikala
Is this light but now you can see the razor
Cool. All right
I'm ready. Can I equip that weapon? No, no, I need decks. What how much decks do I need 22? No
No, I just want like a big fucking cartoon hammer. I don't want any of this here here here, dude
There's the one thing i'm gonna drop my heart still tells me no
But i've got something because you just want to be like fully geared instantly
I know i'm just no I don't is is it discard to place on the ground, right? Nope. No, I deleted it
Okay, you deleted it. Oh, wait, hold on a second. Hold on a second. Hold on. Let me do this
What else do you have
I'm gonna be fucking unstoppable
Let's go 32 points in strength
You've got a full set of gear six out
What what level are you? Um
Jesus
Dude 32 points in strength. I'm gonna one hit kill everything. We're gonna beat this game. We're gonna win
I'm telling you we're gonna beat the game
well
It's all right. You just like hang out and like tell funny stories and i'll like be fine
You say that but like let's go down here have the final boss of this area be like, I don't know maleketh or something weird
Wait rest at the at this side of grace
Just in case you don't have it. Well, just in case you die
Uh, well, then you can respawn at the stake. Oh, no, you know, you can't you cannot not in seamless co-op
They removed that really I thought we had the options when we tested it earlier didn't read the patch notes
Dude, don't you wish you could like just walking down here
Don't you wish you could delete your fucking memory and play elden ring again
You have no vigor and you've ruined the scaling whatever what's the shit? Oh, what's that?
Actually, it's not that good
Actually pretty good actually pretty good help help help i'm coming
defend defend
Hey, that guy would have killed me. Thank you
Okay, two butterflies
I I am legit finding bird feathers and eggs
I got talisman. Oh nice, dude. I got something cool
Isn't it funny that the one thing I did find I was going to give to you the long sword
He's gonna play easy mode
Hey
When you take you take it if you can get it, right?
I'm sorry, but if I get like one of the late game remembrances in the first five seconds, i'm gonna do it
Hands off. What the fuck?
We don't have a lantern by the way. Yeah, I know
Well, i'm ready. Did you get this item? What do you actually want to do magic because I just got stuff
I could do magic
I I don't want you to drop it for me
I I would love to get to the end of the game and like you're
In full golden armor and I still haven't gotten like a shirt like we can we can handle all your fat rolling. Whatever it is
Unstoppable. Oh, it's cracked. All right. So what this is the first little mini boss, right?
Yeah, okay
All right. Oh, it's actually this actually is actually really bad
Is that uh, it's actually kind of an inappropriate room
I gotta remember how this how this fight works. I hope you deal damage because I don't
You're doing fine. All right, back it up back it up ugly. Look at me. I tried to pull it didn't work
I don't think we're gonna do this
I he one shot me he dead. It looked like he was attacking you and he spun all the way around
All right, are you spectating me?
Yeah, you got this dude. You're unbeatable
I've heard you're unbeatable find out what I dodged it
I feel like you're you're actually doing less damage than I was I am because you haven't gotten a weapon
Oh
Fuck fuck
Fuck
I thought he was me strong, but he was me weak
Okay, so what's happening? My somebody said I fucked up the whole my whole character. Do you think we can do it?
I think we can do it
Uh, it's it's doable. It's a little rough for me because I i'm level three and I have no vigor or armor
Let's go we can do it. Okay
One more try one more try
Let's just run downstairs because these items are gonna be the same. Oh, that's right
Well, actually if we kill if we kill people they might be different, right?
All right, this idiot is over here. I'm just going down. Yes, technically if they drop different stuff
All right, i'm going in
What technicality? Okay, i'm coming
You doomed him by over leveling oh because the creature is scaling to you wait why
Because because the random enemies do scale. I don't know. I don't know your chat. I think they might just be saying words
I don't think your character's bricked
um
I think you're doing great. Okay. Well just you've
Let's go
Hey guys
Let's game. Yes. That's what i'm saying
Being extra careful
Because he might just fucking 180 degree spin and aggro at me
I'm cutting off his tail, dude
Oh
Oh shit
Oh, come on really doing a row. Yeah
Yo, he he's just spamming that move. He's new with this
He's just spamming
Uh-oh
Like that lingering hitbox cheater cheater spammer
Are you gonna do the crawl again?
Don't get too greedy you just got so greedy and it's making me I try I know I've mistimed my dodge. I'm sorry
What what did he swing at?
I don't know. The room is very small for this character
I'm distracting right now. You just get the hits in
I'm telling you he's looking at you and I think he's attacking you and he does a full spin on me
All right. Well, hold on. Let's see if I can do this. I can't take like one hit
My mimic tears got this
I dodged that's what i'm saying
Actually, I remember there being like an actual delay on dodge rolls in this game
No, that's not the problem, madam
He's won. He's won
Does this boss have two phases? I hope not a different one
Oh, he pulled. Okay
fucking
No, I got I got so screwed there. He did the fire thing in a bit too many times. I I had it I had it
Like what can we go get some items?
Yeah
A little bit. I had it too. Okay. I'm following you
All right, let's get let's do
Get on the horse
And let's get to
Let's go clear
What the fuck was that? All right
So we need to get out of here. Let's move like over here. Let's just go down here clear this out
Isn't there there's a chest down here, isn't there? Yeah, we can get that. Yeah, let's let's just play
Get it. Let's just play
All right guys
Today we're doing our just play of elden ring. Mm-hmm. Uh, here's here's the room
Watch out. Yeah, watch out. Watch out. We got
Yeah, I know so funny. This is literally my least favorite item in any from software games. It's like this this frost
But I don't know what happened to my body. My mind just went somewhere. I don't know what i'm i'm
What happened to my mind dead body? Oh shit
He's in the game dude don't die dude don't die i'll take the hits
I'm shooting at me. All right, we have to pull this thing out. Let's pull this guy out
You're gonna die
I got him. Oh nice
All right, hopefully you get something out of this
Why is there like another guy here?
But she fell off the I killed the wolf but not the girl. Is this an npc? Oh, no, no. Okay
I got some thin beast bones
Yep. All right, let's go downstairs. This is gonna be a big item
I hope for your sake. I hope for my sake too
I'll just leave them. What are you doing? I'm trying to do backstab
That's what we should be doing man. We should be trading off backstabs. I can't really backstab the wolf
All right, let's see
I'm gonna let you open it because I feel like you deserve it
Golden lune
Wet stone knife. What is that? Yeah, that's for uh, that was for the upgrading your weapons. You need the
I think that's always there
What did you get a golden moon?
three eight hundred soul point
important v
I mean v
Vv important v important. What's vv?
Vv important. What are you talking? Who is saying this to you? Somebody said vv important and they tagged me
Okay. Well, let's get the chest in the back here. I don't know if you want to fight the godskin noble
He's probably not that tough. I feel like the godskin noble would be harder than the worm
Yeah, he should be scaled as a normal enemy hp not boss hp. Oh, okay smithing. So I have a lot of smithing stones
Yeah, just do all right. Let's see if it's let's see if it's scaled. Uh, no
It is not
Okay
Well, we're already doing it. So you want to just run get them. I actually think we can get them
Okay, well, I don't have any healing left
Oh
And if you can still I think we can get them you think so?
Yeah, i'm dead. I'm not
This is this would actually be ridiculously easy if one of us did have magic to just stand around and be the asshole
That throws magic at him god. Oh, oh good luck. You're
There's no hope for you. I'm alive
It didn't kill me. I'm alive level fucking 25. Oh god. Damn it. Don't
Thrust weapons, I hate these things. Yeah, i'll give you i'll give you the anchor
No, I'll wait
I can't I can't reach him and you got you
wrought essence
hopelessness
Wait, why did I get that?
Wait, what's going on? Sometimes an enemy might fall off the map or something. Maybe you just I don't know i'm dead shit
My actual souls that I need to be one tenth the level of you
Oh, I also did get an item for dying wrought essence. Wait, this this thing reduces your mind. Can I delete this?
Reduces maximum health it's part of the mod sit at a grace to delete it
What? Yeah, I got a weird item that what's the point if it resets because if you die you're out of grace
Oh, I don't understand bird. It's balancing for seamless co-op
Oh, I can I get it. So if you die
And I try to come back to help you
And it reduces your to make us so we can't just like jeez stuff
I see well, I don't think we should do that. Anyway, no, we're gonna try to do this as legit as we can
Okay, I want to go grab my uh
My runes
And then we can go and go anywhere just pick a direction and we're going to go off into the sunset
All right. Well the logical direction is to go just towards um
Margot yeah market search of the elden ring
Why is that logical because that's the first area to go to is it though? Yeah
What about the castle to the south? I mean we could
Yeah, we could do that
Okay
Is that illogical?
I'm just trying to remember the thing you just said of hey, where are we going is you should pick where we go
And then now you're like trying to make me decide somewhere else. Let's tell me where let's go. I'm following you
Okay, you are the commander. I am your
hairy
Companion. All right. Um, let's go. Let's go. We'll go so are you sure about that?
You didn't want to go to a market
No, I don't think I actually don't think we're ready for that if that's another hard boss before I can't do it
I'll make sure you get this
Oh, I see what what's going on?
I mean is that when you act when you touch the bonfire to get it
I auto sit at it because you've already touched it. So I think you getting the bonfire gets it for both of us
Oh, I just realized that I they I get what people mean now by how I just ruined everything for my character by just
Spamming everything to strength. Um, I need 3200 runes to level up now and that's not going to happen for like an hour
I see
NPC. Oh, it's the
the
Clothing guy. What's his name walk or something? Where is he? He's right here golden rune eight
I've got a pretty fat level up there
I I don't think I ever helped this guy or came here and got him one time ever
Really? He's cool. He's got a cool story. Let me guess how his story ends. How do you think it ends?
Oh, well, it's an elden ring npc he dies
Oh, wait, he just gave me something sick. Wait, what he gave me throwing daggers
Uh this npc spoiler alert for those that didn't play. Um, he does not die if you you know, he can die
right like every npc can but
There's there's a scenario where he doesn't well
Let's cut his head off because instead of a like a ball bearing he'll drop something else a bell a bell ball
I think that in elden ring there's very few things that I mean
This is like the npc that you do not hurt out of all of them. You sure about that? I am like
As a general elden ring community, I think this guy is protected forever. Like you don't hurt this guy ever, right?
Okay, where are we going boss? All right
Okay, I just was making sure you understood that before you uh, i'm not hurting him. I he's i'm not doing anything
Don't kill him. Please we we can go do his quest if you want
You never did any of this do what did you just like run through the game as fast as you could?
He's the guy that gives you the needle right? Yeah, the sewing needle. Yeah. No, I just I think I just
Happen to miss him. If I break this do you get why does this guy have so much health?
Are you gonna you get that?
Yeah, okay, because this is a misbegotten and he's pretty late game
Not really
Late-ish right? Isn't this this is the farmazula people, isn't it?
uh
No, I thought this was the castle more
Misbegotten but they might be in both areas
Huh? No, this is early game drop a staff you coward
He's more castle
Uh beast blood. Oh, I thought that was millennia. It's like a shit
That enemy does suck though. It I they're one of my like least favorite enemies
Well one on one if you beat this enemy first try i'll give you 100. By the way, you can't take any damage
Why you just add shit as I run in?
I I can't even get near the guy. I'll take it
Oh sneaky. All right, i'll do it now
Oh now now i'll do it
I've got the rot
and now
Rot i'm actually scarlet rotting and dying. I need to get to a bonfire. Yeah, this item might be something good
I'm dying dude, dude. I'm dying
Dude, i'm dying. Well, just go just go to a bonfire. Um, I can hang out dude. I'm dying
All right, I don't think i'm gonna make it dude. I'm dying dude. I'm not gonna teleport to the bonfire. Why are you running?
Ah, i'm roleplaying
you
Idiot does that mean what happens now?
Do I have to die too? No, I think I can just rest you rest and then come back. Okay
Oh, yeah, you did around you. Yeah, you did. Okay. I think it's different though. Maybe not. Oh, no. No. Whoa, I didn't
Okay, that was weird
That guy shouldn't respawn though because he's
Whatever it is
Whatever you did. I see you going around but you're not on a horse. Okay, let's just run by these guys
Oh, this is like a crab this reminds me of like the dark souls, too
Uh, but when they recreate what was it called scholar of the first sin?
Yeah, like I guess we'll put a crab and um, one of those casters. It doesn't just call it the first sin
Yeah, you're riding around on nothing too
That looks so scary. It looks like a horror movie
What is going on over there? What's happening over here?
Is this kind of lagging giant fighting somebody or is he trying to fight us? I think he's trying to fight us but can't get out
There's like giant bugs in here
Okay, I think that's a bad idea. So we shouldn't go that way unless you think we can cheese this
I don't think we can I think he's cheesing us by being in there
Yeah, he's yeah, this is a strategy
There is the basement down here as well
What about the loot? All right, get the loot golden. Oh shit. I got good shit. I got good shit
I got some real good. I got grumble gauntlets. What is the grumble gauntlet? All right
grumble
Grumble gauntlets is what it was. All right coming down. I'm down here. This is a boss. This is a boss down here though
I don't know where you went. He's still chasing me. Did you go down the hole? I went down the hole. Yeah
Oh i'm coming. We can definitely cheese this by the way. There's no way you can fit down here
Go in the hole. Hold on. I need a second. I I found like some high level runes and uh a good sword
I got the fuck golden epitaph
Was this one of the ones that shoots like magic?
Or this was the holy one
Oh crucible gauntlets. I thought it said I don't know why it looked like grumble like crumble a grumble. All right, you ready?
Uh, oh, I don't want to lose my souls here, but okay. I believe in us. There's no way we're losing
Just don't even come in then
I'm coming in. It's a mad soldier dude. We're fine. It's crazy. He's fucking gone nuts. He's gone bad
All right, good. So what is in here?
That guy was that guy was fucked up
That's not bad runes
Oh, that's right
Uh, they sell stuff though, right? Because their shop will be random
I have the lowest amount of intelligence. Yeah, we have the lowest amount of intelligence you could possibly have in the game
Can you even talk to her?
Yeah
Okay, uh, there's still sorceries, but are these different?
I feel like these are the same
Nah, she's selling garbage for me
Here i'm about to level up
But actually might be able to do it. All right, so uh chat help me out here somebody was saying
I can't believe you did that. So how do I fix this points and decks, right?
Uh, the glintstone blades are intelligence scaling stuff, right?
I don't want to do like full-on caster and cheese enemies, but I I could go like glintstone blade
and all that stuff
yeah
Yeah, glintstone is uh is intelligent. Just do health
Only until you figure it out
I've vigor 17 intelligence 16. I mean I have 32 strength. So I just have to figure out the hell i'm doing
Dude, you are clapped for the rest of the game. We can find the uh, the respect things
I think I have to live with this
I just kind of got excited
And just put every point in it. I think we're out. Look that was that was fun. We're good
Actually, a faith could be fun and I already found the weapon like a faith weapon. Hmm
Oh god
Why is this aggro range so huge?
I want to see this convoy and all of the random enemies in it walking together
I want to see the fucking parade of every enemy in elden ring. That's true
Uh, he's still behind us. I don't
Yep
What is this?
Um a lobster
Wait, what is that?
Why is it like a lobster tree?
I don't know. I'm not messing with a lobster. Yeah, we got way too much stuff following us
Imagine you get to the final fight and it's like you have to become an elden lord and you go into the arena and it's a lobster
That would be awesome. No one would have ever beat this game
Huge hand huge hand and it's very fast
Look at how fast that is anime in the game. No. Oh my god. We are disagree so much. I hate those things
Those things are stupid like design wise the type of enemy that they are
I like the hand
All right, but design resting design wise
Playing against it like actually the actual mechanics the thing has fighting it. Not great
Okay, just saying if you're gonna be like, oh, I love it
No, I love like it punching me
Turning into a fist and like ramming me wherever I am
I didn't over here. Okay, i'm following you smithing stone. All right, so let's take a look
We're trying to get to this tower over here. So let's just keep going. I wonder those boss, um the jails
We should try to do those. Um, but we could get some we get some pretty lucky shit here
Maybe all right. This is just a vr chat lobby
Like this is not
Elevator. Oh shit. All right, go go go keep going
Plus two
Where are you?
I'm behind you
Somebody said they I think that's alexander. Is it really?
What? Hey
Stop don't do that
I killed the dog
With the holy blade of the emperor. All right, so let's see what's in here
Who knows dude, it might be mad soldier too. I hope it's mad soldier. All right be on your toes could be anyone. Oh up here
What is it?
It's just a regular ass guy
No, this guy is one of the most fucked up people
And I got insta comboed
Because when he jumps up you get like sunlocked
Should I try should I try to fight him?
Yeah, what are you gonna do? What else are you gonna do?
I don't think he's got that much health, but this enemy sucks
Shit. Oh, I think he just looks weird because the npcs have random items
I fucking hate i'm gonna go bare hands. I'm gonna use my bare hands. I hate this thing so much
I hate frost items in all these games. I'm just using my bare hands. I I think
A steak. Oh, oh, yeah, I can give you a weapon. I think I found some other stuff. You're that desperate. No, i'm just mad
Okay, he's just mad. I don't want to fight that guy. He doesn't have that much health. We can kill him
Let me see. Why are you playing this shit again?
What this is like one of the best games ever like made?
This game's fun what come on I think we can do it
Okay. Yeah, I wasn't ready
He caught me off guard. I wasn't ready. Make sure you get your souls
You had me. All right. Don't just go right up. He's gonna do the thing. He's gonna kill you in one hit
It's just just there you go. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. He's gonna turn to you. I'm gonna do the same thing
Get him turn around you got this guy
This is so unfair
back on the ground
Uh-oh
Uh-oh, he did a weird move
I feel like we invaded some poor player
Just like and we're just fucking with him
He keeps trying to do that same move
You can't cast spells man. We're in your face
He's just if I get it off if I just get it off both these motherfuckers are dead
Go up. Oh shit. I'm gonna die
All right. We're good. We got him
Honestly
He got outplayed. Yeah, he did
royal house scroll
Oh, come on a scroll
I got a fireproof liver
I forget what all that stuff even does I assume fire resistance i'm not gonna I don't want to cast spells
Well, I gave souls. We're still leveling, you know early game. That's true
All right, so we did that let's mark it on the map so we don't forget
I'm gonna say uh, the sword is it was completed
Okay, do you see that or do you have to do it on your own? I don't see it
All right, we're gonna trust you. You're the wayfinder. Okay, we can keep going down and you want to just keep going down across the bridge
i'm following you
Yeah, but i'm gonna be going like roleplay speed on my horse
We can do roleplay speed
That's fine. I'm gonna follow you. Yeah. All right. He's getting back to the road
Kind of looks like you're kind of looks like you're speeding up there. This is this is what you would be going if you were
When i'm not going full blast
I don't know about that
Let's cross the bridge. Oh, hold on item up here. Ooh
Oh, it looked like a purple item from way back there
fire grease
smithing stone
I hope the next item you find is a spear
Sorry, but yeah, that'd be kind of that would be humorous. It'd be comical
All right. Let's go. Yeah, i'm on team comedy
Yeah, I mean if you're playing randomizer
You kind of have to be on team comedy
Uh item here. Ooh
What is that thing?
That thing is this thing is like one of the best items in the whole game. I think isn't it dragon crest shield talisman plus two
That's pretty good nice
Yeah, I haven't found a article of clothing
No, you haven't
Are we going down?
I was gonna go across the bridge
This death drop here or no. Yeah, if you jump down through the wind you won't take damage. Oh, it's all right
You're good. All right, let's go the wind
Uh, oh that dragonfly ant
Is arming the ballista?
Wait, is it really?
Oh, I thought it was I got a spell I got gravity well, it was a bug well manning the ballista
E d. Yeah, what the fuck? Oh one of oh god. I'm sorry for aggroing you. Okay, good
Okay, it was one of the like the bomb birds. These enemies are lazy
I think they just have a line of sight that we're just breaking. What is on this? What is on her head? What is this?
Oh, okay. I thought I was like why is what's like on her head? You can't say that
I thought it was like I think I thought she was a different character actually does look like she's wearing like a flower pot
Uh, should we kill her to save the trouble of someone else having to do it?
Um, i'm not gonna make any decisions on npc killings looks like you already did
You basically you decide it by not deciding. I hope she kills you doesn't deal damage though
I'm not your father. I got I got a helmet it was worth it. I got her helmet
She dropped it. I got a mask
finally
Cool. It is I sir knight. Somebody said fuck you, sir
Jerma just watched I can't hit you. I can't stop you. There's no friendly fire
Yeah, but you didn't tell me to stop. Um
item
Yep, that would have been a laugh out loud comedy moment, but I I had to get away from it
Isn't there an item here? There is oh
Oh, it's over though. I there's no we don't lose no
I literally just got rivers of blood right now noise
Uh nice, uh, like, uh, I don't I just I just got teach
Are you fighting everything? I just ran up ahead. No, so I think something died
Yeah, but I can't you
I can't use rivers of blood right? That's like that's lame. Isn't it? You can use whatever you want
but
I mean like I physically can't because I have 32 points in strength because I freaked out and pressed the button
Yeah, I don't think you can
All right. So down here we need to find wisdom map fragment down here
I've got the academy key. This guy's selling the academy key
So i'm gonna buy that
Haven't enough to level up. Oh shit, and he's got smithing stone ones, which is very good
When I finally get an item, so should I put any points? I feel like I need to put points in dexterity
What if I what did I do? No only vigor. Okay. All right, do not level decks
under any circumstance
Okay
Steve bell bearing you can just take it from him. He's selling a sacred tier
Okay, I need to buy that
Yeah, he sold really good stuff for me
And I got the academy glint stone so we can actually go do the thing where you can respect if you absolutely needed to we can
Go to lucaria
I think it'll be all right as long as I get like a big super heavy weapon soon. I'll be fine
Okay, let's uh, i'm gonna rest did you add a charge to your flask in the very beginning?
No, well, I would do it because you picked golden seed didn't you I didn't I picked uh
Stone key, why would you pick stone key over golden seed?
Uh, just to make you mad to anger you and you feel the wall between your brain and your skull
No, oh you thought I was asking you that no, I was reading that out loud. I know but i'm still confused
No matter no matter where that sentence came from. It's confusing. Yeah, it is isn't it so much shit
I'm like, it's so overwhelming when you there's so many things to see did I not? Yeah, I did. Okay. I'm ready
I'm gonna start rp'ing. Oh wait. Yeah. No, no, let's wait till night time
For the cavalry. I'm curious. I assume you like just can do it and it overrides my game find out
Until nightfall hit it
Uh, I don't think it did it. I don't think it did it. I'm the host. Maybe I gotta do it
Uh, you also sit down while i'm doing it. I don't know i'm sitting
Uh that seemed to have worked. Yeah, uh chat my chat says host can do it. All right, so where's the night cavalry?
Well, doesn't this area so I have one of those birds that jumps down at night. I think it does
Oh, wait, it's just it's just the night cavalry. Okay
Did this get rolled into just being the regular enemy that's supposed to be here different night cavalry?
I don't know like i'm not doing damage
Seems to be very tough. Oh, you're not on your horse
I'm like not hurting him. He's also really I
We're all right. I think you're hitting his horse
Yeah, we're you're hurting his horse. Definitely
Ouch, ah that lock on game. So, uh, do you want to leave so bad?
Battles, huh? I was just thinking like I don't know if there is an elden ring to the horse battles
Sticking with this. I mean we kind of we're here and we're already hurting him
All right, we'll just get off the horses then and let's fight him one on one two v two
Dude, my camera keeps unlocking him and it's it's rough
Ow, ow am I dead? I think you're okay. I just hit the jump button instead
Where is he going? I don't know. He's running. Uh-huh
I remember the first time I fought one of these and you like feel so proud you get him off the horse and he
Instantly just summons the horse again. Yeah
Dude, I want to target him not the horse
Why can I not target him?
All right, have you given up?
I don't want to say yes because I know you're gonna be like see I I wanted to give up a while ago
There's no see there's like a there's a let's go. All right, get on your horse and let's get out of here
Jeremy you have to hit him until he dies
I
I don't
I don't think you he's still behind us
Make sure you get the map fragment. It's my second ancient dragon smithing stone
There's a bug with the mod. If you fight on horseback, the lock-on will stop working. Oh
That is what's happening to me. I was wondering why it was so weird
All right, where are you heading?
I don't know. I was just looking around. I like forgot. There was this whole beach over here because I think there's nothing on it
Let's go to the beach
When are you gonna do a screaming stream?
I did one like a year or two ago
I just turned the uh the stream on I just sit there and I just go like
And and like it's the stream's only like
15 minutes that I can't really do for that long
You just screamed
Yeah, I just kind of scream and then to get a breather take a sip of water scream again
And then it's like my throat kind of hurts. I have to stop
That's cool. I like that
What is the it's like this headless person?
Oh, there's something really good here. I don't know what it is, but I hope it's
I'm glad we came down here
Great ghost glove ward. That's the highest love ward in the game. Isn't it? I don't know. Yeah it is
Okay
That was cool. Now, let's let's check out this area
with a swamp
What that call wait? I was expecting the giant to be shooting the crossbows out of us, but he's like
a bumblebee
Dude, I don't know what happened or what's wrong, but my pants and underwear are like stuck adhered to my legs and ass
I don't know. This is weird. I don't understand why oh to have clothing
First world problems there buddy
This has never happened before. I don't know why this is happening. This is weird. Oh in real life
What did you think of your pants? I thought I don't know your clothes are sticking to you
It's not even that hot
Have you worn have you like I don't know. Did you bathe in something sticky?
Did you do like an applesauce bath? Isn't there like a place to jump off in the middle or is that a different place?
Uh in dark souls 2
Uh, there is a giant up there that you have a cool item. That's a cool item
Yeah, I got the
the dragonfly something from astel
I got a
blade's head
Okay, what do you want to do here?
um
I can't believe you're still with the spear
I know
Let's just let's just aggro believe throw shit
These enemies actually kind of suck
I don't know. There's a couple dogs
dog dog rat dog
Cat dog
I I thought I couldn't target it for a second scarlet rot scarlet super i'm scared of dog
Go out on the road or back in the town all because I could have put in cat dog down
You good guys
All right, you're back good wonder if there's any good loot in here. Oh, yeah, I am
Any secrets in here? Oh, I got leggings
Wait
I don't want to wear pants. Oh, well, I want to wear leggings
Oh, I got the gross
Messer, what is this?
Gross messer. Can I use this?
How can I not put this on?
Why can I not use this?
I can't even equip this in two hands
Oh my god, give me a break. Why are things up? That thing's a gross messer
Who handing only works for strength?
Did you do that?
Yeah, your character's got so much cooler than mine in like 15 minutes. I have I got one sword
Yeah, and it's uh, that's the bug weapon. That's the one of the coolest swords. I was I was about to use that in my um
first playthrough
He's jealous
Fucking level 30 character over here. Ooh, look at this
Just mad. He put it all into strength
I got a bow
Is there a boss in here? There is isn't there?
I don't think I don't even remember ever coming up this way. This is um
Isn't don't know that there's a guy at the top right? He's like me. I am the leader of this place
Have you seen my daughter? I got a knight rider glaive. I got a glass you want another thrusting weapon
That guy didn't even move
He was in prison
It's got yeah
I in all of my playthroughs
I never came up here and was always wondering where this guy was and I always missed this
You didn't ever come over here. I don't know how there's just it's a big game and some things you miss
You know that gives me so much confidence that this game really is as good as it is because
You saying that how many times did you play through the game at least a few times, right?
A lot. Yeah, so a lot. That's really cool. The fact that you just haven't even seen this place
Yeah, every time I did a new playthrough. I was like, I never saw this before
I missed this on my first one. Uh, we have uh
Over there should be careful. I don't I don't like this situation. This actually is not good
Why did you aggro everything
What are you doing? Why did you ever the whole top? This is my fault
They weren't already walking over to us. We do we could have killed a few of them
Oh my god. Thank goodness. I can fix this character
Oh my god, there are enemies stir must have done this
I think you can only hurt these guys with blunt weapons, by the way
Oh
Uh, you can backstab her but yeah, you might need a blunt weapon
Um, we're gonna die here. We just need to go. Okay, follow me
Where did you go? I don't follow me. Actually, it's better do
I followed you and i'm out of hell. No, no, no, no, because they're back. Oh, uh,
That's a gigantic centipede monster thing over there. Uh, this is bad. They're casting us
They're casting us
Oh my god, what the f don't go that way don't go that way this I got caught
I'm dead
Like I said, i've never been up there ever well, um stir there's not that's not what's up there
I know but like I don't even where we're going you ran into a dead end. You should know that's a dead end
You're a master of this game, right?
Okay, we're just gonna get back up. Did you rest again to get rid of your whatever they gave you an idea
Fix your character. All right, hold on. I know i'm not gonna do that yet because I feel like it's gonna scale all the enemies
How how would you fix it because I have a golden rune plus 10
And i'm about to level up like five ten more times. Oh, no, i'm pretty sure you can use that
I think they're still leveled by the zone that they're in. I was I was saying dumb things before
Oh, I thought this is way more than it is. There's a boss at this castle andy
Uh, yeah, we saw it. It was astel. I think because uh that was spamming at us. No, that's my sword
Why are you a dog?
I thought you hate it when people were wolves
What? All right. Wait, wait, wait, we need to figure out where where's the progress route to get up to the top
You go to the other side of this and you go upright. Yeah, okay. All right, let's not not up the pile
We can just let's kill these uh, somebody said that was so funny. Mine's too. Yeah, if I get poisoned i'm gonna be so mad
There's so much poison dust
Did he heal?
Why is this guy not dying?
Yeah, then you can just run along the side ignore blob. That's funny. You got the sleeping rock there
This is normally a sleepy guy there
smithing stone
We're getting a lot of those
Oh, it's a mog like enemy
These guys are actually horrible. Aren't they?
Oh, no, no. No, I know. I thought it was a bog like it's not
Do I hate those guys too with the bow?
Well, they can shoot you from across the whole game, right? Those things. Yeah, they're so annoying. Don't look up
Please be respectful. I I can't guys. What is he talking about eyes forward?
I thought you meant that there was like a something very scary like a monster or something. No
It was my bare body that cannot find clothing
All right. We need to be careful here because there is a gigantic giant up here
Item up here too
That's so scary. I don't think we're going to be able to get to that part. Uh, they're kind of right in the way
Oh, I didn't see the gigantic astle in the sky. You didn't see that. That's what was killed
That's what that's the first time i've noticed it
What?
It is shoot. Oh, yeah, that that's what I was saying
I think this is a run scenario
Oh god
Okay, let's uh, let's pull aggro pull him back. Okay, we can kill this giant
Okay, this is a run angle. Yeah, this is a run now. Why are you why are we fighting this?
This is a run scenario. It always was
And you left me with the fucking guy with the battle act
There's a bar feeder on me
Is there i'm learning the names?
All right, hide hide for a second
This thing is invincible we're in so much trouble, uh, we gotta go down here, right?
Yeah. All right. Let's reset them
All right
Reset
Okay progress
All right. Everything's good to go
Sounds good
Where are you? I went down the rocks
Oh, yeah. Oh, there is a boss down at the beach right with the uh, yeah the misbegon
Whoops. I I really did that
I really did this I did this to myself and there's a fucking brutal enemy down there
Uh, there is that there's a mogul like down here
This is a run angle. Uh, i'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna do it, right?
That just happened
Where the hell are you?
Something in my nose. I went down. I did that I went the right way
Okay, well i'm further ahead
The right way isn't this an npc bridge?
Wait, how come I can't tell this isn't this isn't this the guy?
Run saved you got a larval tear
Oh god, okay. Wait
um
Where you're all the way down, right? I jumped off the side of the bridge to get on the roof
Uh
Oh, okay. You're right there
Um, I want to go up that ladder and get the item that's up there though
Okay, I already jumped down you can do that if you want i'll wait. I was in a bit of a panic
Oh goodness
I'm rooting for you
Okay, I thought what he came whatever that ladder is pretty hard to get up do I laugh like a cartoon character
Do you laugh?
um
Sometimes uh, did you respawn? I did
Oh, you didn't want to spectate me
No, why would I want to spectate you? I'm i'm coming because I could just go up here and get the bonfire up here
And then we could have
I thought it was like an honor system where if one person dies
That my game just lagged for a second
Come on, you see you're all the way down, right? I'm resetting the enemies. Yeah
That's a bear. What?
Why is it? Well, I thought wait, all right
Okay, I got a crustacean amulet or something
I don't think the bear can get out of this door. All right, this is an opportunity for us to kill this
I nuked him. Nice. That thing is so good. It really is. I should have used it in my playthrough
Get off my friend
This is his bear is in the way
Are you ever gonna play elden ring?
um, no
Absolutely not. I was thinking about it the other day during my scream, uh stream
I was sitting there going
What the fuck am I doing man? Like why am I doing this?
I'm like trying so hard to be funny and shit and like I could just be playing elden ring
Like I think I was like this eighth or ninth scream and i'm just like this is i'm trying way too hard
Wait, did you really do a scream stream?
No
You thought that was real something i'm missing here
Squad move up. All right, let's go
dagger
And a cookbook lame
Do it like you fucking mean it
That you ever go back here to the secret cave
secret cave
There's just I guess it's not really a cave but back here
Is there something back here? I think usually there's something there's something relevant back here like a weird sword or something
really
Yeah
I don't think i've ever been back here
like a
million
squid back here
That's cool. I didn't get anything good, but cool
All right. I got
Uh, I think i'm all right. This is the slowest enemy i've ever seen
And you're waiting. Uh, yeah, but
I hope the uh, the boat enemies summon like random
dudes and not just the same skeletons
I would imagine it's probably
Something different
All right. What do you think we're gonna get in here?
um
I think we're gonna get a uh
We call them by the way, I think that you upgrade your elixir with
oh
Crystal tears, I can't believe how fucking cool. This is right like I
I wish this was just in the game normally
Yeah, this is so much better. This is a million times better
Did you ever play neo 2 and does anyone know if that actually even has multiplayer because i've been wanting to oh god
It's an actual boss
This is a bad place to fight this too
37 damage. Oh no
Shit wait, I might just walk off the edge. Is that possible?
um
I don't think so
We really deal no damage to every boss we fought
Oh my god
Of course, it's not going to go anywhere else. There's nowhere else for it to teleport to
I even dodged too
It's so awkward. All right, it's gonna spawn literally right here
again one more
um
That actually might be a strategy here
It's way to put the teleport and whale on it. Yeah
It would be so funny if it just fell in the ocean
Oh
Looks like it was possible
There's so many look at all these fucking random animals
Jump on you. Oh my god, but oh, please don't kill me
I'm dead
This is uh, totally doable if you want to wait, uh an hour. I'm willing to wait as long as it takes me to do it
Yeah, that's that's all right
Let him cook. I'm letting him he he has the whole kitchen to himself right now
I really don't want to be in this kitchen for this long
Like I should be getting paid overtime
Yeah, but you'll have the achievement or you know on stream you beat this
alone
You know what you should do is go stand at the very edge where the world stops and try to get him to jump
And land over the edge of the world
I don't a lot of the bosses will avoid it
I feel like i'm gonna walk off by accident
Okay, here it is
Okay
This is menacing
Uh, uh, yeah, he's he's not gonna
No
He's gonna slide me off
Oh, hold on
Oh, please
No, he's like clipping. Yeah
in the air
Yeah halfway
You're a medulla line of cheetos
Please
If you would if you could do that for me, please. Oh man
After gamer session
What's that person even talking about? I what is this what just happened?
It oh, yeah, it heals it heals what it kills all of the animals in the area and heals off of them
What the fuck?
And all of the animals are in a pile. So I think it just hits all of them
Yeah, every single animal in that actual boss's encounter room are spread out over the course of like a mile
Okay, so uh, let's vote to i'm gonna like teleport out of here. So all right, we know that's there
Can we at least get the item that's up there?
Up where with the mog like enemy is blocking the way
Uh, we would have to go back a bonfire
We would oh we would okay, so we gotta go to the that's one behind the castle, right?
How do I vote?
You just pick it
Like pick the same one as you. Yeah, I think we probably both do it like in the same. Yeah
Go to caitlin
I feel like we need to get through limb grave before we decide to go to k. Uh caitlin. Are you here?
Yeah, oh
Oh, yeah loads longer
Okay, so we need to
Is this I think it's a chest up there, right?
Uh, there's usually a good item up there. It's not guaranteed that there will be
Oh, let's try
You know what? I would want to do if I was calling the shots you you absolutely can call a shot if you want
You know the chest that makes you go to bed and teleport you
to the crystal mine
I would go there
We can do that
Especially because when you run around the mine you just like smithing stones or something else
And you can run around the swamp and pick up a whole bunch of items there
What happened to the mog like enemy that was here?
I don't know what a mog like is. Is it a new genre of game?
I mean, I feel like you you know, you know and like you're not like part of our secret club
So kind of have to figure it out
All right, you can you can join secret club if you do this secret secret club handshake. Don't look up. Okay, you ready?
It's put your hand out
You shake hands you go like this you go like this you part the hair twice
You nod you nod you nod elbow elbow elbow to elbow elbow to elbow finger finger gun
Okay, and then kiss
Okay, a mog this item is worth it for you a mog like enemy is
It just is I don't know. It's a stupid
This fire grease. It wasn't worth it
Um, it's just those big burly guys that kind of look like mog. They're like the blood enemies big ones an omen
Yeah, a mogan mogman mogman omen an omen enemy
An omen mogman. They're like the blood omen enemies. They have that we called them mog likes because I thought people
There's a whole thing. You're gonna have to go read like where we going first step starting. Uh bonfire first step
Why do you want to go all the way back here?
You don't want to explore the other stuff on the peninsula. I told you where I wanted to go. Follow me
Okay, delete your way markers. I'll keep them because I like to remember where I was. All right, follow you
Oh, we should see where the dragon is
I wanted to go into down into that area where that's the teleport chest. Okay, lindell soldier
I'm ignoring him
So do you want to see who the dragon is?
It looks like it's a dragon. Uh, it's the way worst dragon
Isn't that uh surrounded by a whole bunch of like goons in his vr chat lobby as you put it
But we're not going we're not doing that. I want to go in the hole
This dude's spawn in with a ballista
Yeah, it's uh, it's four to sex. Yeah, okay straight down this hole. There's a lot of shitty enemies here. I hope you uh,
I wish you the best
I'm down and there's and there's a lot of enemies down here and he's blowing a trumpet
uh
They're gonna
Oh my god. Wait, I need to how do I say I need to sit in the mist. I can't get in there
All right, I can't get in the mist
Good luck. Oh my god, please barf trigger. Don't kill me. All right. I made it. What do we got? Is that hold on?
I may have actually just been
Shit
I can't use it
You ready?
I'm as ready as i'm ever gonna be
Yeah, I don't I don't care what enemies generate in this area. There's no way it could be worse than what it actually is
That's true. That's so true. It actually made the area way easier. Okay. This is the one that has the
Uh elevator that goes up and down and you can jump off in the middle
Okay, we're gonna run around the swamp grab some stuff. Oh i'm hitting this first try
Never mind
All the invisible thing
Yeah, this one's annoying
dung beetles
Well, you just gotta stand in one spot. I'm not doing it. I'll do it. Yeah, I gotta stand in the right spot right here
ow
Um, this is not a place for us to be standing in one spot
You'll be all right
And I look forward to being able to let's go
I want to get this thing
It's gonna be like a fucking dung. It's gonna be
All right, i'm on the horse what did you want you wanted to run around here and pick stuff up? Yeah, follow me item
Oh quick get us out of here
Thanks. Oh millennia wants to talk to me for some reason but also
What I don't know. Does that yeah, she wants to talk to me, too. Hello
Forgive me
I'm here to vac ban both of you fuck fuck
Oh my
Okay, i'm dead. I couldn't even talk to her. She took me to the um, no she didn't I thought she was taking me to the round table
I don't know who is doing that. Oh, it's this
There's a flower thing up there
You can't even get to that
Okay, let me get the rod off me
Yes, go to the round table hold before this thing kills me
Oh, I didn't go god. Damn it
Oh, you didn't go
No, i'm
We're not you don't want to do don't we have to don't okay. I was gonna here
Let's finish what we came here for follow me. Okay into the swamp
Okay. Oh, it's a giant beetle
Do you don't want to kill this puppy as like a this thing's probably like candy in it and shit
All right, i'm just gonna follow you i'm following you. You you are the quarterback right now
You brought the splat
I you oh my god
Turn around turn around turn around what do you turn around?
Don't go in there. I made a wrong turn
I'm gonna get this fucking thing and we're gonna get the item that's inside of it
There's a stone sword key. What did you get?
Uh golden rune three. Where did you go?
I went I went back down because that's a boss arena with a dragon in it. Yeah
I'm getting rid of these things
All right. So what is your
Why are you here? What was your plan here? You want to just run around?
No, there's like, uh the city over here has a whole bunch of items in it. We just got invaded
It is one of those ulcerated tree spirits up there. We're not getting up there
It is no way this is
This is not happening man. This is worse than I thought it would be because of all the fucking gigantic enemies out here
It's not like slow swamp enemies anymore. It's everything you don't want. Okay
I got one of the uh
I will meet you at the round table hold. Yeah, i'll see you at the round table
Okay, i'm gonna see if I can grab some shit. Somebody said comic con
Also all the people you can buy stuff from at the round table
Gives a lot of item options
All right, are we going to the round table hold or what?
Yeah, go
No, i'm saying like this is taking a while and i'm saying yeah go
Are you there now? No, but I can join you. I think we have to do the vote teleport, right?
Um, no, i'm i'm there
Okay, this was not worth it in my mind. It really is comic con usually running through here
you can grab a bunch of good stuff, but now it's all like flowers and and useless nothing and
God to your enemies
What somebody got hurt who just got hurt? I just heard somebody go like
Gideon looks fucking ridiculous
It's a different guy gideon looks like he's playing world of warcraft with a bunch of like level 25 greens
That's where I came out of right?
Yeah, I think it would be better to run along inside the mine than come out here
Okay, i'm just gonna come to you
This is corin yeah
He still kind of looks like thematically accurate doesn't he where'd he go?
Oh you respawn them. I wonder what you sell aspect of the crucible horns
Oh, oh, yeah, you can't do it from this very one bonfire
Did you say that you were gonna do magic because bordasaxe's lightning spear is on this guy. Uh, I mean that's that's faith, right?
It's faith, but this is arguably one of the best. Um, isn't this one of the best weapons in the game?
This is like one of the best a spells in the game. Isn't it pretty good. I don't want to
Do shit that cheesy
I just I don't want the situation where one guy's like taking aggro while i'm throwing projectiles
I can't wait to see the blacksmith. Wow, what an absolute gigachad and a game full of randomization
He doesn't give a shit. He's just wearing the same clothes weird
Wait, you're just wearing corin's outfit with horns on greetings. Great. I am fear circumscript
Perhaps you might share with me doing so and you do you think it's where I come from that your disdain is but should come pain
This game is so good
Are you here?
Not yet. I had to go to a different bonafire and I haven't gotten the one yet
I thought there was one where I am and there is not
it was like
These like this, uh, uh, this I can't even describe this
It makes me laugh every time I see it though
Oh
Got the middle finger filet. Oh, I caught you not doing the pose
Oh shit, you missed your acting cue. Can I use any of this? I don't think so
Insane weapon. What the fuck
Yeah, but I can't I don't have enough decks to put it on the key
I mean the key this is
Did you on purpose make the worst build?
No, I just freaked out and put every point in strength because I thought it was like holy shit
Well, look at this academy key
I already got one. Yeah, I already got one. I just saved money
I can't touch this
Oh, okay. You do that every time what put every single point in strength. No, I didn't I played I played like a
I played like an int dex character warp to the round table to hold
Um, I guess i'll agree because I think we both have to
I thought you were already there
I am but I think I have to like accept it for you to be here too. Maybe because i'm already here
Now it put you standing next to me and I didn't teleport
You look at 10 year old at subway who realizes he can ask for unlimited cheese. I probably have to leave
Yeah, let's uh do teleport back to the first bonfire. Yep first
Wait, well you can get unlimited cheese
You know now, okay, so now
If you say go to the round table hole do we both get to go?
I already did. Oh you did. Okay. I think it's cute the round table hold. I think is
fucked up for multiplayer here
I wonder if we can both do it again
Okay, i'm gonna do it. I already voted. Okay
You voted to warp to the round table hold. I guess it does work. Yeah, there you are. Cool
I am milania blade of mikala. Did you see uh, get in I just got here
Oh, I thought you said you were already here. No, I haven't been here yet. I gave this guy a death root
I had found one of those it doesn't have any clothes. Okay, that was weird. I thought I didn't have any pants on
We got mogue
Oh, yeah, go rank you look stupid
Fuck you
Uh, I forgot what's the difference between arcane and intellect? Like what does arcane scale was that like the bleed stuff arcane is blood
Arcane is also like its own weird thing with luck and stuff, right?
Yes
Yeah arcane is bleed blood. Yeah arcane is luck and bleed
Oh, they there's some dragon spells that scale with um arcane as well. You have the ripple blade that scales on it status build up
The npcs all have different outfits for stir. Oh because the items are randomized. That's right
Yeah, is this what gideon's face looks like underneath the helmet or is that randomized to bloodhound step?
They're selling me bloodhound step, but i'm poor so gideon has long white hair interesting
They have faces
I've seen the dung. Um the dung eater's face
He must be new here i'm just call me he's just like kind of like a looks like a peasant or something
Or just like a regular costume
Oh, do you want to jump down here and fight the yeah, let's do it. Yeah, let's see what's down here
I'm coming not there yet. I wonder if it's the same npc
Okay. Oh, okay
Is it different? I think I think it's different
Then it's frost attacks, right?
And she's like frost out me
Oh my god
They got randomized gear
Do not let her do that dragon move. That's the fucking blood scythe
i'm gonna
Fucking blood blood blood blood blood
What just happened she just freaked out
I respond
Oh, you can come back down here then can't you even with the reduced health and stuff?
Yeah, but i'd rather watch
Oh and it's weird. She's I can't even see her
Did I not kill her in case it messes up your game not killer you got this how long does that last?
Don't you do that?
What happened that was?
She has more than one dragon move apparently
She has all the
Super crazy. All right, let's go kill this motherfucker outplayed. I'm using a big long extra long toothpick right now
What? Watch out for the dragon
I have one shot me I think because I still had the debuff. I think we have the debuff. Yeah
It was our crush
ah
Now you should go talk to the two fingers
I hope the two fingers is
Like a I don't know like a rat or something
The grand rat
I know you're gonna do the dragon thing again
Where are you?
I went and got the item
It's an item. Oh there is there is
Oh nice
I have like dude, what the fuck so many debuffs
This is stupid. It's so fucking wide
I'm out. I'm out of here the fun. Hey fun fact, dude
The weapon you have that toothpick weapon is one of the top 10 worst items in the game
Okay, we're gonna do what you wanted to do from the beginning and see how fate would have gone. We're gonna go up to
Morgoth no, you want you want this fight rest at the grace?
Wipe that debuff
And get down there and we're gonna beat this lady
Okay
Easy. See I was only I was only dying because I had like four debuffs and I don't know how I got them
You're supposed to be like the gamer and like you're good at stuff. I'm still naked
You're like 20 levels 30 levels higher than me
Oh, no
It's not
Eat this
Why are we not doing that this strategy?
Because he rolls
Get ready get it get it get it get it
All the npc fighters in this game. We need to just do that too
he rolls
And what happened there?
Dude, he almost fucking double killed us you I can't get I can't get a solid backstab
All right, just keep the distraction up
Yeah, just do just do that. Just do that just run away and cast that spell and then he turns on me and i'm so slow
How was that not a backstab after I hit him? He turned damn it
How many estus is uh, is it two or three?
um
What was that weird shit? I would have had the backstab. How many of those does this person have?
That has to be the last one. I don't I think this
I think the other equipment
That she has is a
Like 10 estus flasks
Nice yeah, don't do it. Don't do it. I'm so scared of the fire
I
Okay, all right, you're gonna also die there you got this dude
All right, but just you should maybe you should be alive. So i'm alive
They're invisible to me. Oh my god. It's over. We're gonna lose
I can't see them
What did you do? What did you do? I respond him. What do you mean you respond? How did you do that?
I came down here and they're invisible to me and then they invaded again
Oh my god, dude, are you kidding me?
It's because you weighed it I
you
You hesitate it
I wanted you to get the item if I die if you die
Just rest rest of the other round. I'm just gonna die then we're not messing this up again. Okay, we're good
You got to read chat between attempts big guy
You sounded like a train whistle
All right. What do we need?
Upgrade the shirt
I don't want to upgrade the toothpick because I don't know if we're gonna get enough smithing stones to even complete anything
What's going on down there?
I don't know you seem
What the fuck just happened?
She was waiting for us, man. She was waiting for us. I don't see her
I resummoned her the whole this whole thing might be fucked now
Do we have to resummon her again you landed on the ground? I didn't even see the fire that killed you
Are there two of them down there?
No, but I think it's desync
Can we leave at least like if you want to fight this we can leave and come back because something is fucked up
All right, we keep hold on
I'm gonna die
Die save i'm dead
All right, too bad on my screen you jumped off landed on the ground
There was nothing there and then you just died on fire just traveled to and from the round table
Okay, let's just all right. You know what? Let's just leave we're gonna leave. I want to fight margott. Okay, let's go
Gate front and let's just run to margott front and
Yo, right
We never you know, we never even did
The lizard in the cave. We have made no progress. I leveled up 30 times. I have not all right
Things are good
Everything should we make sure you don't have that
debuff still
Yo, actually hold on rest at the grace because I have two of them hold hold hold i'm about to crack that
I'm i'm cracking the case. What do you mean? I actually can upgrade to plus five on a weapon. I have the whole
Chain she's asking me about torrent again
Now she wants me to go around I was already at round table. He broke it
Why does he still have this? All right, so we debated if we were gonna trade like trade weapons
Uh, and we came to the agreement that my game crashed
Oh, I would imagine something weird has been has been going on because once we went down. Yeah. All right
Let's just reset it you restart. I um, I crashed so I need to relaunch. All right, let's just reset it reset it
Just trade weapons. Yeah, but so it's like should we not I think it might be more interesting if we don't we don't trade
I just that was very weird. I went all the way back here. Oh, you know what?
I think I got teleported out of the game. I'm just gonna restart the game. It's probably for the best, right?
Okay. Yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna go to round table. I have like a long sword. I can upgrade to five up to you
Yeah, I think it's more fun this way
Look if it gets to a point where we can't make any progress then whatever I I don't think that'll happen
Did you?
Did you exit the whole game or did you just restart like the my my game crashed? Oh, okay
I think I don't I think I finally got the millennia go to round table hold and it was like super confused because I'd already been
There. All right. So should I try to join you? Uh
Go to a bonfire and see if uh, you can talk to millennia before you rejoin me
Actually, i'm gonna go to round table
I cannot and then invite you because my game still feels like it's being a little weird
I feel like i'm okay
I go to gate front. Let's see
Okay, then later I could um, I could just upgrade this weapon to uh,
Give it a in in ashes of war when I find it if I upgrade a long sword
I no longer have millennia here. So, okay, give me one minute, sir
I didn't quit out of the whole game. I just kind of reset this. Okay, sir kind of thing
So I think we're okay. I don't have any I don't have any runes to do it
I got a different talisman though. Now. I definitely keep that on
We also I think it's always in the same spot
We have to go get the like crystal elixir thing that you get for free at some point at the church
Did you buy that sacred tear that was on that vendor? I don't think I ever saw one that was you ours are different
Oh, that's right. It is different. I'm just gonna go grab whatever this uh, are you ready for me to join your game?
No, i'm upgrading my weapon. You have a plus five long sword. I'm back sniff sniff you died so many times
Can I put I could put glintstone pebble on it? I'm not doing it bloodhound step long sword
Yeah, I got a little excited I got like 20 000 runes
I came into i'm gonna go to the gate house and set up the thing to invite you
Okay, i'm right there gate front. I brought like five dolls to the casino
And hit like a 50 000 jackpot and then put 50 000 on red and lost it all like I just freaked out
I was just like let's go and I put everything into one spot and I just fucked everything up
My world is open to wanderers. There's level two decks. I'm just gonna put two points in decks. I know everyone's gonna be like
It's that's gonna be fine. Don't worry. I'm using it. Does your character have a thong on? I don't think so
Okay, seems to be back to normal. Nice. How's the game audio everybody? Is it audio is good?
Are we in a good spot? I don't know what that is. But what's happening? Why are you why are you sitting here?
I'm I took my horse up all the way up the road. Oh you okay
You were just frozen for me for a sec. I figure we just do stuff up in this direction
There's a couple of the there's like a jail we can try those aren't dogs
I love that golden seed was actually a golden seed. Is that not random?
Um
It should be it might not be but pretty lucky if that's the case. It's not random
Yeah, I like actually deal damage now. I'm ready for the real market. I need to all right
So you want to go beat the you want to go do the worm?
Oh, we can do that if you feel like that you're confident that we could do. Yeah
I I feel confident I can kill it
I mean I can kill it and you can say that we can kill it that we can kill it that we as a team
okay, just a little bit like you kind of
It's like
Don't we have to send? Um send her back to the round table
Yeah, if you're kind of like a simp like that
She gave me a twig grove side cave. That is where is that one?
Where's the grove side cave?
That's the one with the beast in it above the starting area
There it is
Please do a grover voice
That's me grover
I fucking hate that. I'm so pissed off
That was so cringy and i'm so annoyed with myself that I just listened to you. I don't know who grover is
I wanted it. It's just like my body just decides to do that
Like hey do do an impression of peter griffin. Yeah, it should be peter griffin. It's like shut up
Shut up jump jump monkey
Dude, I swear to god. I saw your ass poking out the back of your flaps. All right, let's play
Don't let the intrusive thoughts in
All right ready gamers
This is do or die
Watch out watch out watch out
Oh, that's cheap. That's that's unfortunate
He zoned us
Oh my god, I can't even see anything
You're okay kind of you're it's happening again
That was not fair. Can you do any other move?
No, don't do that
I rolled I was mid-roll. This guy is cheating so hard
We're doing fine
Oh
Big deal big deal. Oh, come on. Come on
Why can't we get it? It's because it's better that you didn't because he would have had iframes for me
I
He just woke up and started fucking throwing up in the corner. You got this i'll be right
You got this
Why would you do that? I'm like concentrating don't just scream
You got it. You're trying to make us lose
No mistakes now look what you've done. Look what you've done and now i'm distracted and now we're talking
Dodging watch out watch out we lose here. It's your fault. I'm just saying
I'm doing a scream stream
Don't get hit
Shut your mouth, please. All right scream. All right, let's do it
Yes, finally
Finally a weapon you want the wheel dude. I don't think I need the wheel considering that the gargoyles
It's a faith weapon. Oh, yeah, it's a pretty good sword or axe weapon. It is if I had a 22 faith
Uh, you need to bonfire. I I won't respawn. I need to bonfire. Yeah, like i'm not respawning
Oh, i'm just gonna go back to the entrance. Is there anything else in here? Uh, no, what did you get?
Uh use this wheel the pizza cutter two-hander
uh
My game is really freaking out that you teleport it. I rested at the graces that help you
Uh says you died
Yeah
Now i'm respawning there you are. All right, so
Here so I discard
Use the wheel. All right. I'm i'm taking all right. We're allowed three trades. I'm taking one of those trades
I want the wheel
That's a nice rule
There you go. Yeah, it's pretty sick
But I think i'm really like i'm think i'm really feeling the spear right now
Just feeling i'm feeling the spear for another like at least 20 minutes or I put it on all right
How much decks do I actually need? All right the next hopefully i'm gonna wish for like a bunch of good runes
All right. Where are we teleporting to though? Because we?
Uh up to morgue. Yeah, let's go for it morgue it
Yeah, i'm gonna be your squire the whole game the way i'm dressed. Did you do the shack?
Yeah, my game I can't get off the map. I'm like frozen. Did that help? No, i'm stuck on the map and I can hear you walking around
Yeah, I just sat at the bonfire. It said warp to storm hills. Uh shack bailed. Oh, I I did it again
I voted again. I think here we go. Okay, good seamless. The axe is just the weapon art for faith. Can I actually use it?
Um, I have a weapon art
I can give you as well if you want if you can I don't even think you can change it on that weapon
I have like earthbreaker
After war I wonder if this works
Find out it wouldn't have the x on it though would it?
I wouldn't
Uh, yeah, it's the axe. I don't think this is gonna work. Let's try it
Oh, oh
Oh
Actually, no, we're good. We're good. We're good. This actually works
This is doing this is okay
Doing more than before my little glint stone pebble on this long sword
It does the same amount of damage from before if I hit something like 10 times
All right mount up
Yeah, I was doing 71 damage before now. I'm doing 91. It has to be something right
I'm doing like 250
You got you got to get like the the
tier one somber stone
Somebody said no, dude, that sphere is really just that bad. What the hell is behind us? Okay, we're good
This is our uh, come back arc. I think so
I think we finally got like the critical mass of items the critical mass
Oh, do not aggro
That fucking thing. Oh shit. It's the scion thing
Oh, it's coming after me. I'm just gonna go up into the tunnel
Which is going we're just running by
Yeah, okay kill this guy in one hit
Yeah
Can you do a marge simpson for me?
Homer it's me marge
Oh, I don't think that we um, we can't afford that bard. Sorry
Thank you
He just does it he just he just fucking does it. Okay, let's go fight marge. Is the cutscene gonna be different?
I hope so. I hope it's like a bug
If it's the same i'm skipping
Is it but if a rat it's him is it skip skip?
Oh, we just fought you what I don't want to fight you again
Oh my god, hold on i'm dead i'm fat rolling right now because the stupid axe
what
What happened to you?
I jumped over the lava, but it's just it's just doing the walk back and forth
Mocking us makar the fell omen. Why does it have that title?
It has the fell omen title
Oh, good luck. You're gonna take it all day
Still says the line
Oh, man
Back to limb grave
This is the two-phase version the one that stands up. Oh, this is gonna be awful
We got this just just fix your fat rolling get naked with me
Me strong remember me strong
Okay, let's go that that last one was a test
How tarnished looks like you may be in search of the elden ring
Oh, yeah, you can't do that
This is gonna absolutely screw us
God damn it. That's why I didn't want to be back. That's why I didn't want to be over there
Whoa, please don't kill me
I forget if this is like sakiro and you can jump when he does that attack. Don't don't get the parry. Don't get the parry
Oh, no, no, no, no, don't go off
Uh-oh, he's standing up. I don't remember this move said very well
And i'm out of healing potions. It's a lot of really long wind-ups
What the fuck is happening?
Good question
Oh shit
Oh the iframes you're right careful
Sorry, I probably scared you
I was running away
What the heck dodge this?
We gotta get under him again. I shouldn't have run away
Big swing who wants me but you can have me
He's coming from me now watch out for the ninja turtle's leg
I'm trying to get this done
Oh my god
There it is kick his ass kick his ass I got the iframes stab at the end
Okay. All right. All right, back it up. Don't be crazy
I waited so long for the rule too. I felt like I timed it perfectly what that's fucked up
What?
That's fucked up in two ways
How did he hit his bowl? I was behind I was back where his tail was that's called cheating
Oh, that sucks. It's all right
How come you didn't grab your runes? I was focused
Shit. All right. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it
We got it. I could feel that coming the whole that whole wind-up. I was like, I can't believe we're about to lose like this
Boy, I lost the runes. Wait, what?
Oh, whoops. Sorry. Okay. I'll get him back
I don't even know what hit me
Well on him
stamina
Careful, I thought you went off the edge for a second
How did that miss? I can't go over there
Oh my
Goodness, dude. No, I died. I I heard the dialogue start and I thought he was gonna phase transition
But then he did one more attack
I feel like I should just jump off the edge. I don't think i'm doing this with two health potions
Uh-oh
Yeah, there's no way I was gonna do that other one. He hates hitting the boss
This is the one I cannot believe we did not be I gotta get over that
Okay, if you need a second to rethink your life choices
Uh
Yeah, if you need a flower or a rock i've got it by the way
That was a really weird path that he took. I was so that was
Okay, and we're stuck in the we're stuck in between that shit. Don't let it get to you
We go again
I
Dude I came in coming in here so confident and it's just weird shit
I'm dead. No, you're not you're fine. And that doesn't that
Uh that right of passing skill
Why have not must truly be in thy veins?
Somebody said have him drop the anchor for you, but that's two out of three items to trade just do it laughing my ass off
All right, this is okay focus confidence patience
Pulling it back chaos is a ladder bro. What are you doing?
Dude, I don't know. I'm sorry. I just give me the just give me the thing. Give me the fucking weapon
Do you want me you want me to jump off?
I just I don't know. I got locked in. I got locked in and I just
Give me the anchor. I don't have the anchor
What do you mean?
I deleted the anchor remember? No when I first tried to drop you the anchor. I discarded it instead of dropped it. Oh
That's right. Otherwise, I have a knight rider halberd
I don't think that's it
Can I use that thing?
Uh, it's strength and dex how much dex?
um
Oh, no zero attributes required put it on the ground
Shit, how do I do this again?
Try the pizza cutter. I need more dex for that
There you go. I'm pretty sure that's a good weapon too. Oh my god. Thank goodness. Let me see
That's your that's your number two out of three
Oh, I just threw up. All right, this is the no, this is perfect. Yes. All right, we're good
Two out of three trades. I know
Pulling it back pulling it back
And it hits you with the back swing
I even was like calling like I know what's going on
Pulling it back. I dodged through it. I apparently not
I think you're a little early
I fucked it that one
One shot me
I've been hit by it before
I just jump off
Up to you. Okay, it's good. He's got a time
This game sucks, dude. No, this is not the real game. You probably haven't have you ever seen this before
This is not how the game is what we're saying. No one's jumping off this time. No escapes back to the war
Back to the wall. They aren't a war fight strong
never surrender
Legolas the inside of my nose is so itchy. Wait, do we have
No, okay. Somebody said make sure you don't have the debuff that we have to clear. All right, we're good
No, do you have any like resins you can put on your axe like a lightning resin or something?
Before you walk in fire grease. Hold on. Let me I'm gonna put some of this shit on my bar
I'm gonna use every single one of these
All right. What is it? What is it?
blood
rot
poison
Fire against the fire magma rod i'm gonna boil i'm gonna do i'm gonna do blood
What?
Take your time
No need no need to rush in there
We're gonna get the blood filled up man
Yeah, well, it's this boss. You can't
That's true
Come on really doing it again. Yeah
I dodged into him doing it and that hit me and almost knocked me off the mat. Uh-oh
I got this dude. Don't just like take a break
Watch that. Hi. Oh my god, dude. Look at stir. Just doing so good stir soloing the boss
Get your head of stir solo botch get your chat. Is that is this upsetting you?
It's supposed to be me doing that
You're doing you haven't been hit in
30 straight seconds stir is better than you and stir combined
Don't laugh at that. Don't laugh at that. That's not funny. That's it's not very funny
It's not funny
It is though
No, it's not
liability pov
Hey, uh if you don't
What happened there got hit by the tail the first time
Oh god
He fucking held it forever
Fucking held in ring bosses, dude
Oh
Uh-oh
Uh, I think something's wrong
What the music's still playing and i'm still spectating you
He's still in there
Take me rest. There we go fix it. I think it did
Still hear me. Yeah, I hear you you were cutting out a lot though
Um, how about now we good?
Yeah, you sound good now. I see better. Are we good? It says you left. I probably just have to reconnect
All right. Hi, that was weird
Okay, yeah that boss fight just like broke my computer
You still have the thing down, right?
I don't know says I might have to put it down again. You probably do
I'm in the boss fight though
Why are you fighting the boss alone?
Okay, i'm jumping off. I'm gonna put it down. Why are you fighting the boss alone? You're doing your content without me
I didn't I didn't know how long you were gonna be disconnected. So I was just doing something
Yeah, i'm ready
I have used my tiny great pot to allow new wonders to walk into my world
I am joining
You are joining another player. I am the chosen one
I will become elden lord
I might have to restart my game. Let me reset the game. Okay
Oh
That's fine. It's fine. You need it. You need it like a break
The game was you know, it's getting to your man
Let's try it. No. Oh you said he you need to use the separation mist
Do I because it already said you left
Oh
Whoa, okay. I am i'm in your world. You're not in a session now. Okay, let's see if that does it
What am I doing that? Do you put one down right? There's already one down
There should be yes. Okay. Let's see. I just restarted the game
No
Did I reset the game?
Like should I exit exit exit? Let me see if this works
Stirr has to restart. Oh, you have to restart. I think he needs to use it. So you have to do the separation mist
They said just waiting for instructions
I'm doing i'm finding i'm doing i'm finding i'm finding i'm finding i'm finding i'm finding it. Where is it?
It's like a big it's like it looks like a moon. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
You lost 10 000 viewers. Yeah, it's all right
A thick mist envelops my world and I am now alone and I look like a pikachu or something
I don't know why that made my hair weirder way to change the way you looked
Yeah, my all of my like bodily hair became like paint. Okay, now i'm opening my world
To watchers once more uh wanderers not watchers
Okay, and now you're trying to join me joining now
Yeah, I lost 10 000 fucking viewers
So happy they're never coming back
like next stream
They're they're like, uh, nah, that was it
So everyone that is coming back
Yeah, they're not they're gonna miss this shit. That's on them
I hate when that hits you and you're like dodging it
I don't want to be in this corner
Yeah, that's bad
You're in that corner. You're in that corner
It'll be fine. Mm. I don't like you being over there. It's too close to the
What's he gonna do hit me?
Stir, I don't like this
I'm farming him dude
I'm backing up now. You're in the corner now. It's not me
Oh, yep
Where am I? Oh you got good backing up. I don't watch out fire behind you
Thank you for the heads up
He's gonna pull it back and it has a hitbox the size of the earth
Gonna stand up in a second. Oh, yeah
He's been in this corner this entire time
Oh fucking ninja turtle
Big swing you've gotten used to that timing after dying twice. Mm-hmm
No, he got you he fucking stepped on me, dude
We can't do it dude
It's like if we miss time that one time we die. I think when we see him go for it
We need to just run away
Like not even roll just like walk away
I'm gonna upgrade my weapon
Do you have the upgrades for it? I think I have I should hey remember, uh, you only need to use one
Stone per upgrade. Oh, all right. Let's i'm gonna go upgrade this a couple times
Wait, what? Oh, that's right. You you you cheated. I forgot I cheated
Didn't you she said like shouldn't it be like one two then five then ten then ten or something it goes like one three six
One three six one three six. I'm pretty sure or like one two three four
Yeah
but um
I played randomizer before and like I said, it took me like eight hours of walking around looking for smithing stone threes and it wasn't fun
oh, it was just like
extremely tedious
uh
Did you go back to the hole? No, did you you're still standing here? I tried to warp to it. I voted to warp there
Even just one or two times my game crashed
No
Yeah, something about round table hold is not great. Maybe we need to go to that other blacksmith and get that waypoint
Yeah, who's uh not yeah. Oh, yeah in the first church you can blacksmith there. We should do that
Can you do everything there? Like can you uh, you can just do everything doesn't matter. Yeah, we'll start doing that then
I think that one has a limit and then you need to find the giant blacksmith
If you wanted to do everything without going to hold how much is it to upgrade this shit?
The church has a limit of up only up to plus three. Can I sell?
Can I sell too?
You know also if you want to go to that first mine
I don't think it will be smithing stuff
But there's still like a ton of items to pick up in those mines the blacksmith can sell
Oh, I thought it was not the blacksmith but the blacksmith didn't let you do it. I swear. I i'll get it
Right. It's been a while since I've played elden ring
690 that's a weird number. Yeah, that's my graphics card. How many what's going on right now?
All right, so boom i'm gonna upgrade this
Once because I don't think I can afford anything else. Don't have any just random stupid items. I can just get rid of
I don't like this
828 what I can't warp. All right. I this thing is pretty good now
Okay, I believe in us. I'm gonna put my thing down push your thing down. You sold the rivers of blood your problem
That's what I should i'm pretty sure also you can sell uh the grave wards for quite a bit
Which I should do just level this is my first stream. What emotes should I use?
Uh, you probably should use um, okay. Yes
I am ready to join you
Join me do it. It's all on you
I will say for how crazy and broken and buggy this could really be
this
Works pretty smoothly
This is actually remarkable that we've only had a couple of small bug like crashes in three hours playing this
All right. This is the one
That's so much damage
Come on, bro. I'm dead. I slid all the way off
I'm supposed to see how much damage I do
100 that's better
What was it?
It was like 90 like 70
Hey, don't worry. I got this
Watch this
Oh, I do germa is so much better than germa and stir. I check this up
I mean
I will have to bow to you for all eternity. Really if you beat him right now. Are you serious?
Yeah
I even have a fun story if you wanted after this, okay related to that
Honestly, also, I feel like we would have done this if either of us had like plus one s this
Sorry, bro. Did your game crash? Mine just did mine did not
Uh, I crashed
The ai took over I mean you did say that this wasn't as buggy as it could be a second ago
So you were asking for it
Yeah, but kind of like, you know what happens in life or death when somebody drops out of the game like the ai took over
That's what you were just watching. We doing this or what? We did it first try. Oh, I thought you actually okay
Yeah, we're doing that we're doing it just first try how what the
Heck what the why is this health gone?
Dude, i'm fucking rolling by it
This the salamander crawl i'll say uh, worst monster move in all dark souls games
No, it is not
Not even close
What's worse than this the bed of chaos?
The bed of chaos swipe move is worse than this by far
I don't remember that
No way. This is not even close
dude
Dude, I haven't gotten to participate yet
And i'm out of flasks
Fuck but you're out of flasks right now
Yeah, I i take so much fucking damage
I I could sense you're tilted right now and it's like fucking up my game
Well, this whole fight I believed and then you come in and then he walks
He walks away from you then he walks away from you and then he walks away from you
And then he does all of your health and damage from walking away from you
Okay, um
We should
One more try and then we'll go explore
Germa has six flasks
Yeah, do you yeah, are you for real?
Where are you?
I have three flasks. How many mana flasks do you have? I had one because I was actually using glintstone pebble. Why did
What you using glintstone pebble right now? I was
I'm gonna take it off. I mean i'll be i'm seeing a lot of omega lows, but we're dying in one hit doesn't matter
You hey you I have six flasks. That's true, but we're dying in one hit from that move
skill issue
silence
About to go full gamer mode dog. Yo
Oh want to walk away real quick?
That's the worst fucking move in any dark so i'm telling you i'm telling you no it is not
The worst move in all of dark souls. You know, let's just be let's just focus. Okay. You know what I
Just dodge it dude
Just dodge it. Why are you not dodging it? You got here in my
Why why can't you dodge that move?
If that moves on a problem, why don't you just walk?
Just spam it three times and put fucking lava on every square inch of the map and push you off with it
We're fighting this boss
In the area where he's not supposed to be right now
That's the issue. All right, relax. We're good. We're good. We're gonna get in there
We beat him the first try with by the way
I was using a weapon that was only doing like 60 damage to swing when we beat him last time
Okay, let's do it again. You finally got six upgraded flasks. It's not the problem. That's not the problem
That's not the problem. I feel like we would have won if I had fucking six flasks
I don't think so. You've died in one hit by that move each time
See look, we're good. Good. Just relax
No him walking away from you good. You're good. We're not good
Here he comes again. I'm just gonna like afk because that's that's all
That's all I got. I'm just gonna afk over here
You why you're not afking? You're fine. I was while he was running around
All right. This is a good start
We're good. Oh my god, dude
Nice aim not you him. All right, easy
I the greed was kind of strong there. The greed was a little strong
the
You should have ran away from him
When he faced transitions you can hit him for free
There was no greed then he just did that one attack and I mistimed it and then I died
What you did? No, but I'm
When he says the words and he puts he always puts lava on his sword
The fuck I'd watched you respawn in you need to rest
at the bonfire
You're a coward. We're not cowards. Why?
That was a good attempt though. This is just how you this is hey, this is randomizer. What's the what's the worst boss moves?
What's your your least favorite? You were saying some boss. I don't really remember it
uh
All of radan's entire move set every single one
Every single move radan does
Okay, and and that's that's one through ten and then everything else is like 11 to 12 13
Yeah, what comes that like we're just gonna pretend that boss doesn't exist. Okay
um
I feel like you have to I'd have to like refresh my memory
But I feel like a lot of stuff in dark souls 2 was unbelievably annoying
It is what it's usually like the setup of things and not one individual move
stuck on a fucking tree
He just hit me with the butt of his thingy
We're good
Where did he go?
Where is he?
What he deleted me? I thought he was still doing the other side
You may need to restart the game. Yeah, i'm out of the fight and respawn me. I'm not spectating you
Okay, so now i'm coming back
Okay, I want to go let's go through like the first
And we'll come back. We just need like a 10 minute away from here
We're gonna go where the dragon is in the beginning go back to the first step. We're gonna go into the fucking the upgrade mine
Okay, so you want to go to?
First step the first step
Okay. Yeah, so we'll we'll come back. We'll be fine
There's no sense in getting upset by this
I am
So happy to be playing games
My good friend exactly. There's no what's the point of getting upset about this?
It's a tricky game
Game's tricky. It's hard
So you're asking about why I have so many flasks did you not pick up the golden seed at that
The places where you could we walked by two of them
Uh, they were not golden seeds. They weren't I thought people said that wait did
that
It is
I don't know. Maybe your seed
There is a setting so that you can always have those be golden seeds
And your seed is uh, we're going around
You don't want to fight this right now, I don't want to I don't want to talk about it. I just want to go
You know diggy diggy hole
Or like a shirt of some kind. I would like a plus one to my flask
So I don't have to use like three flasks every one time I get hit
Yeah
All right. People normally suck this bad at this
Yeah, usually worse. It's usually it this that's that's why people you know, that's why people play these games
It's because it's usually
Usually it takes a mugger
There's fucking fruits growing out of the wall. I was gonna say I picked up like a mushroom
I miss dark and darker. Did you play that?
I did a little bit. Is it good? I only played like the first beta and it was actually a lot of fun
It looks really cool
Definitely wish it had a little bit more to it, but it was great
Hopefully when they actually come out in beta
It will be a lot more right?
Yeah, like it's still like another like year of development or at least
Okay, there's a boss down here too. Isn't there should be there's always a boss in the mines. You should do a backflip
No, i'm good. Watch out pot friend actually is
ow
stone sword key
Wait a minute
I'm waiting
I that I think I might that thing actually might be amazing
great omen killer cleaver
uh
Decent I think the axe that you have would do better if you could use it really I believe so
Uh, where did where are you?
Uh, we go back to elevator and there's a this one has the jump off point. All right
Facing forward. Yeah, i'm definitely gonna put at least two three points
I gotta I gotta put at least like 14 other way other way. What do you want?
What do you mean other way? Oh, I thought you know because you're facing the other direction
Okay, so if this is a magma worm in this boss door, i'm going i'm gonna go buy a lottery ticket today
I I would do the opposite of buy a lottery ticket because i'm fucking sick of him
Ooh
Whatever is let him stay there
Okay
Okay, can we peek in there? I hope it's another mad soldier
Love that boss
Is it a magma worm?
Oh god
Oh, this is bad. We're not gonna be able to beat this
No, we like don't even have a blunt weapon to hit it with
Let's we can do some damage
What the fuck what? Okay. What i've been grabbed. I am being grabbed. I am
Being grabbed
When he grabbed you my game just froze
Holy shit, that's fast. I thought it was slower than that
Oh my god, give me away from the fucking door
I actually don't know this boss's move set at all. I I never fought it
I've tried to fight it once. I was like, I don't like this and then I never did it
I mean you're really kind of supposed to fight this boss with the horse
Yeah, he's hard to chase down. Oh my god. He just moves around so erratically
This this is definitely a horse. This is a this is a horse fight. It really is
I don't know what that is
It's called it you get on the horse and don't get hit by it
Every swing you fucking hop
I he's
Run run run run run run just sprint trying
trying
But I got like staggered by every single hit
You got this
No, I do not he's got this
Dude every one of his moves. It's like i'm going to the river and then i'm
Stake of maricop you're supposed to be on the horse for this fight
No, there there definitely is one of these that is in a mine
But I don't know if the movesets are the same. I can't remember. We got it. Are we uh sprinting are we fighting?
Let's go you fight one in the seletano. Really?
Yeah
I do think it's like um
Significantly weaker than the main one
It's okay. We're ready. We were refreshed on the move set. We're good to go
Okay, I should get a shield at some point. There were people selling them in the round table the crash hold
Lower health lesson the horse one has way more magic shit. Yeah
You gotta be fucking kidding me. How did I not?
Just when did they stop?
Dude
Everything he does is just like staggered
Oh
That's not good for you
All right, I hit the thing by accident. I was way off of it. That's all right
What is it what
I just keep hearing you scream
I've been perma combo for like the last minute. All right, we're gonna say sorry. Sorry
What the fuck just happened?
Dude, that shit threw me off big time
Oh, hey, he runs like four times. Okay, you got this man
What are you talking about?
Little fucking mr. Six flask over here. Stop it. This is not the time to make this joke
Stop
You're gonna make me lose
Ooh
I got I got a shield. I got millennia's armor. Cool. Woof. All right
Well, we got literally no help at all. That does not do anything for either one of us
We are still at the same exact place we were before fighting the worm. Um, so cool. Well, you got some souls
That's true. Need you to rest. Oh, okay. Where's the where's the bonfire?
Is it not just right here? It's at the bottom of the elevator, bro. I almost just walked off to get there, bro
Let's go to where the uh elixir is good idea
And then I also gave that guy the the grave root so we can go to uh, talk to beast boy
I think he gives you an item. You know what I mean? The teleporter that's sitting in the bush. Oh
That's right next to the where we're going. Anyway, ooh
Yeah, you like that. Can you just repeat everything you just said? I wasn't listening. Um
I don't know where the church is where you get the elixir. You remember where it is. I can't find it on the map
You're talking about you talk about the the the drink where oh you can do like a damage mitigation or you know, explode yourself
Yeah, where is that? It's not here, right? It's like, uh
Let's uh teleport to artist shack. I think you have that I was gonna say I think it's over here east of the lake
East side of limb grave artist. Can you can we vote? Can we vote? I just tried to do it
I think this would do hit lb. I think that should accept it immediately. Can I not teleport because i'm inside the cave?
Uh, let's just get out of the yeah, maybe should I get out of the cave?
I mean I spawned like at the bottom of it. Oh, maybe i'm gonna get out you have to leave
You think yourself an elden lord you are nothing underneath my boots which boss says that um, what just happened?
Did you are you teleporting teleporting to the start of the dungeon from the bottom of the dungeon i'm i'm outside right now
Okay, i'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming
Or artist shack unless you want to try this dragon
The big one over here the scary one. Yeah, I mean do you want to just die for a joke?
Okay, let's go do a joke. I I believe he should have really low health scaling because he's like a loser, right?
I mean, I maybe it sounds like accurate as long as like we don't get aggro'd by his whole like crew
I mean, he's sitting on top of it. Well, he's gone. We beat him. It was easy. He's gonna fly in I just
Yeah, I don't even know where i'm going
No, yeah, you gotta get off the horse that one shot me there man. I mean, it's definitely doable
It just you just lay down
Uh where he's back. All right, are you uh, just respawning or should I just die?
I just respawn
Do you want to fight him or do you want to um?
Something does not look right
Let's just get out of here gets we go this way he thinks you get the map fragment down here, too
Okay, you were just flying through the air. Look like you were on a broomstick. So you want to go
Okay, there's uh
Yeah, you marked it. Oh, no, I I see it on the map. I'm going to it. Okay, that's just straight this way
Oh, here's kenneth height. I want to see what he's wearing
A little bit of a little little fashionista there, huh? He got the latest fall trend. Yeah, she looks all right. He looks all right
smithing stone one flask of wondrous busy
Kill him. No
I'm not wow. You want me to kill kenneth height?
he's
One spoiler alert spoiler alert spoilers for this is the spoiler of the entire game
Kenneth height is one of the only npcs that lives through the whole game
I mean like pretty he's pretty fucking sick. Don't you think?
Not in my game
Because you probably backstabbed him for fun
Well, didn't his like quest line not finish when the game came out?
I think that's why he stayed alive because they didn't finish his like whole arc. Oh, well, that's also why I killed him
You coming down here? Yeah, I didn't want to die a bunch of places to fall. I want to pete real quick
Uh spoiler is over. Yes
Okay, stop acting weird. It's not fun
It is here. You're right for a second. I thought I wasn't gonna be there. Do we even have anything?
The only thing I have I guess i'll put it on
Do I have any of the items that should be on this menu here?
They miss old germa old germa was weirder than this one. What if anything?
I've dialed back how fucking weird of a person I am
Wait, what we're dialing back how weird we are. Somebody said stop being weird. I was like, what do you mean?
we're super normal
we're going in the
the stargate
Kenneth pike
Oh
tree
Grant me sucker
Oh tree that really is bugleberry. Oh tree the fuck there's a boat here. He's sucker please
Yeah, it is. You're right. Oh, yeah
You're giving death root
Yeah
Feed it me it me strong feed it me feed me more
Okay, I got like not much. Whoa, what did I get?
Oh, wow, do you ever got something cool again? I did I got a golden run
um
I think the scaling probably makes this boat have a lot of health. Oh, wait the boat's out here
Yeah
black blade mariner
But this guy sucks though, it shouldn't be too bad
Holy shit. Never mind
He's gonna aggro some like crazy enemy. That's probably near here
What the fuck?
What just happened to you?
I got crushed
Weird I didn't see anything hit you. You just died
It summons the gigantic skeleton hands
Yeah
Yeah, so this is the hard one that has way too much health
I tried to revive you did it work? Yep. Come back
All right, let's let's go down this road because there's also one of those trees and if you're actually getting golden seeds from them
Then there should be another golden seed here for you
um
Where are you talking about straight down the road?
Straight down the road
Where are you? Did you respawn at the where we were just fighting that guy? No
Oh
Uh, that was up here, right? He's still yeah, the beast will sanctum. I think you have to vote for it
How do I do the quick vote?
Left bumper I think
It's not it's guard
Can you do it now?
No, i'm in combat the viewers are all coming back
Oh shit, they are. What's up?
Yo, what up? What up gamers? Uh, let's go somewhere different
Go somewhere different. Okay. Well, I don't know if you want to go back to fighting market
I think I think we should
There's like a million different catacombs we can do but okay. Here's what we're gonna do
Let's go get the map fragment here
So let's teleport to the mist wood outskirts right in the middle. Let's get the map fragment
Okay, get the map fragment
Take off my runes
Oh shit, I need to go get my runes from the stupid. Yeah
My money were there
3000 dude, you're like level 40 3000 runes isn't a lot. Yeah, okay. Who cares? Let's go. I can't get you on the horse
I can't get on my horse
move
move legs
Okay
Looks like i'm just walking. Oh, I found dragon fire
And if I find like a somber stone one, I think I can like fully upgrade a weapon
You got any somber stone ones?
I think I actually do
I have two somber stone ones you can have them. Yo, come here. This is the play
It's gonna take me a minute because my horse doesn't work. Oh, no, I would only get a plus two
It's not that important are these random
so
You need that stone
Now let's go down here because there's a bajillion items as you just run along the river, right?
Oh, wait, this is yeah, this is underground when you go
Like all the this is where that boss was supposed to be right the uh, the elk or whatever it is
Yeah
Somewhere way down here after you light all the bonfire thingies
so um
Little tail because we're on the long elevator yesterday
I went out with a bunch of people and we went to a place around here called pinballs
I don't know if it's a texas thing
That's like, you know pinball arcade has a whole bunch like the goofy arcade stuff here
And it had one of those punch machines where like the the punch thing comes down and you punch it
You get like a score for how hard you hit it. Yeah
So like everyone in the whole group like 12 people we're all doing it. We're having a good time
There was like, oh shit like oh you did better. Oh, like I did better and then like this dude comes over
Super drunk is like yeah, I I do like mma dude like hey guys. What's up?
This is my name. How's it going?
And he like did it to like show off in front of everyone
And apparently like later I saw him all night
like he was watching people drunk like just sitting in a chair that could have view of that anytime anyone went over there he like
Asserted himself and like his whole identity was punching this thing
Uh, it was really weird and then I went and I beat his punch
Oh, no
So he came back up to me later and was like, oh, yeah, dude
Oh, yeah
like like telling me like all this like martial arts stuff and like
Trying to like I don't know like the weirdest down speak to me of like yeah
You got this is how you actually you got to do it. Like this is a proper punch
You learn this, you know doing mma for like five years, man
And you just you what what was your score, uh
900 something yeah, I was gonna say I can get that fucking thing to 900
I could tell you I could like show you how to do it
If uh, if we if you and I get there like if we're at a thing
I could probably teach you like the right way to do it because I can do probably like nine
50 or so I notoriously know how to do that very well. I could show you what's the proper technique
Are you are you being that guy to me right now?
Because him his buddy and like their girlfriends were sitting in a table and any like I don't know
I felt like I wish I was his girlfriend to just understand how weird he was being anytime anyone went over to this thing
This guy's waiting for this tube with the ballista is like dude. You're not gonna shoot. What are you shooting at?
Hey, remember pick up all these items got a couple warming. Oh, there's that
Oh, this is a legendary item
Oh
Yep, I just got another remembrance. You didn't yeah, i'm aware that I didn't i'm aware that you're getting really good shit all the time
I
Know this is so itchy today. Why get off me? That's a cool move. Why haven't I been doing this?
Does this turn into anything else? I found five bolts. I have raw meat dumpling raw meat dumpling
Oh
Are you serious?
Fucking starlight kid the best spell in the game poison darts
All right, I got cloves
I'm dead
I got combo. Yeah, I was so excited
How long we've been playing we're playing? Uh
All right, 30 minutes well four hours. That's my I got a shirt
I'll fucking go
Do I need to yeah you coming back or do I need to reset it?
I reset it so I lose the debuff and they're all going to be around you again
I just want to run
I thought you could horse down here. Holy shit. You weren't kidding. They actually are all back right now in front of me
Yeah, I told you yeah, you're gonna die. I am not
I've
You're gonna die. I am not gonna die. You're gonna die
No, i'm not i'm not going to die
Watch out. I'm not gonna die
Assassin's gambit. I don't know. What is that?
Is that like the the chess show?
It's like stab someone and like does like the quirky smile into the camera
What are you talking about?
The assassin's gambit. Yeah, I planned that murder
Still didn't die
Okay. Hey. Hey. Hey, where are you?
I'm gonna make this ball fall down. You want to fight this ball on top of the statue? Sure went all the way up
You went all the way up
How'd you wait? How'd you get up there again?
Are you gonna go all the way around and like do some jumps and there's a couple items along the way?
I got a whip
The horned whip
Yeah this way
Show me did you still did you want this many stone?
Uh, no, i'm good
Close part two
How did I get scarlet raw? What did I just what happened to me?
Maybe one of the ants
Weird. All right. So where do I go from here?
um
Well, hold up. Hold on. Hold up. Let's get the shit from there's a bunch of items over here. I got a legendary
finally
lion great bow
smithing stone five actually that was uh, I need that as well and I can go to like the seven
I got a whip and trousers
Dude things are coming together for me
Okay, come this way
Kill this fucking dude. I have scarlet rod. I'm dead
I'm lagging too. I you keep teleporting around
I'm dead. I'm poisoned. I'm dead
Are you dead for real for real? No, I'm like dead dead. Is it respawning you?
um
I think so. Yeah, you l2 multiple times. I will
Oh, I am so far away now
What?
Oh no
I'm fuming
why
I'm gonna die too because i'm poisoned what's going on
What his I thought that was you who the fuck is that? I don't know somebody I can hear somebody on my screen
It's like a naked dude where you died that looked kind of like you with a sword
I still can't use the horse. We're gonna have to reset probably
Hold on. I think when I get to the bonfire I can we can resolve this
Okay, I vote it to travel if you can
Uh, I I don't have that bonfire
You know, that's why you spawn so far away. You never touched it
Yeah
Well, I didn't have the horse and it was irritating me and you started talking about some guy punching stuff and you punching him or something
You punch the thing
Yeah punch the thing
And then the guy came over and told me he can punch things better
I'm right there
Wait, you forgot to put the map underground. Oh that wait. Wait. Wait, there is true, right?
Oh, that is true. Okay, I can I can travel there. I forgot that that existed. Can you um warp with me?
So I can just get down there
I want to figure out what this left bumper thing is. It doesn't
Do anything because you and the horse died simultaneously to the skeleton reset
Okay, so where's that thing?
You start with it was like a cool jump to get jump. Okay horse up. I don't have a horse
Do I need it?
Why don't you have a horse because it glitched out at me and the horse died at the exact same time in the same frame
So it broke my game
one use
Can I make the jump aside?
Uh, I actually don't think you can do this without it. Yeah, we'll do something else then we're good. Yeah
I mean should I
You're you coming?
Yeah, it just takes me an extra second
You look kind of cool now
Yeah, like i've got like a shirt I can wear
Man, i'm so fast on this little donkey. How many hours do I spend in a tanning bed a week?
I I have a story
so
before like pax east
2014 or 2015 or something. There's like almost 10 years ago now. I
You know as a gamer right and it's like as a gamer
I didn't really go out that much during the summer at one at this point
I was like doing youtube videos and all this stuff, right?
So I was really pale
And I was like, oh there's gonna be a bunch of youtubers and there's other people there a bunch of people in the industry
So I I didn't want to be freaking pale
so I went to a tanning salon
and I went one time and the people behind the counter were just like
You know, this is not really gonna do anything and i'm like, yeah
But like even if it does something at all just a little so I get like a little bit of color
It didn't do I don't think it really did anything
I just went into tanning bed for like 30 or 40 minutes do anything if you do it once you have
Apparently you have to do it like at least a couple of times
Otherwise, it's like it doesn't it doesn't really do much
So I went to a tanning salon hound's fang
Ooh
You want one of those wanted your third trade?
Every time an item comes up. No, i'm good
So I I went to a tanning bed one time
And it was I don't know. This is weird. I didn't like it. Did you just sit there?
And it's like and the whole time i'm sitting there thinking
I don't this is probably like bad
You're just laying there like real like
I don't actually need this but I so badly just didn't want to I like I feel like
I don't know like oh i'm gonna be going in like this like people I may be meeting up with are talking to people
Oh, wait, what if I do like a meetup?
I wanted I don't know. I would like oh hey, man, I get a lot of sun. I'm everything's good on this end
it'd be funnier if like
it worked too well and you had like the
I was just like circle art things and
Yeah
Like super burnt and like you very obviously you have just you were just in a tanning
You look weird like I don't I don't get those things. That's that is the whole thing is weird to me
Why didn't you just go outside?
Because it was it wasn't I couldn't get sun
It was like I don't know what pax it was it was like pax east or pax prime
It was one of them it wasn't in like the summer
Yeah, pax pax east was always like really shitty weather winter. It was like february march or sunday, right?
Yeah, it was like may march, but it was still
We do the weather
I i'm so jealous of you being able to be on a horse like even with you resting
You're not getting your horse back. I don't think so. I know where's the bonfire up here. Did we get it?
Where are you? Why did you want to tan in winter?
I didn't want to tan. I just wanted to look
Like oh man, yeah, I go outside. I've i've gotten a little bit of sun
i'm healthy
dude
Trying to show off somebody said I haven't actually rested at a bonfire in like a half an hour really
Yeah, it's you definitely don't have your horse and you just need to rest at a bonfire
I thought there was one over here or is it in the next area right here? I think take a seat
I'm pretty sure I already did this take a seat. I did it already call your horse. Nope
What is it's like summoning it but not
I think i'm seeing it and then it disappears. Do you want to load a different zone or something?
Um, I think it's just bugged. Uh, we could you want to just read?
Want me to just leave come back or something?
I'll just disconnect and come back. I just mean like teleport to a new area
I I mean I have teleported a couple. Yeah, I I guess you could
I'm just running around picking up items here
What's going on? Oh, they're going
Come back and
Okay
Let me make sure this worked
Yeah, we haven't even taken a break. Have we we haven't like really walked away for any like any amount of time. Have we?
I did a pp
Okay, that fixed it
It did fix it. It was a big pp
Yo, what?
Okay, I figured if you join my world, do you just appear where I am?
That's a good question. Let's find out can you put down a thing?
Jesus thing a thing
Oh my
Is your thing doesn't matter if your thing's down where doesn't matter where I think it is already active because of before
Uh, let's see if it works. I may need to do the disconnect thing
Yeah, I got the horse back
although
New problem
I cannot I cannot join your world. Okay. Let me
Reset it
You get all your wisdom teeth taken out
I'll make sure you down again. Make sure you're just chilling out
What why are you asking about wisdom teeth?
I'm just talking to somebody
Oh, okay
I'm like i'm here
Okay, i'm back and I have
my horse
Where are you going? What the fuck you're like glitching everywhere
All right, let's continue
I don't see where you're like something's weird. Yeah
Oh, I got a glenstone staff if you want it
I think it doesn't like this area very much
You know what? I will take the glenstone staff as one of my one things
That's a lot of runes. I think you've synced up. I see you moving around now. I should just buy this just to have it
Oh golden seed
Fuck you
I have not found one talisman slots. This i'm getting great rolls. I don't like this. I don't like this germa guy
Let me just go ahead and make sure I can purchase some more of this
This guy's got really good stuff for me
Do you want the glenstone stuff? Yeah
Uh, how do I drop it?
Uh, you go into your inventory not your equipment you find it and you do leave on it not discard discarding. It's bad leaving. It's good
I have the rotten crystal staff and I have the carrion glenstone stuff
Uh carrion glenstone
There you go. Should I buy this too?
You're a plate for sona 3 for fuck's sake
Uh this iron wet blade
This thing is probably
Yeah, my guy, I don't know your guy sounds like he's fucking loaded my guy's got arrows
Uh arrows a pulley crossbow a cookbook a cookbook and a cookbook
You're getting really bad rolls you really are
Oh, no, i'm miss begum
Oh, he's gonna kill i roll. Yeah, he killed me. He insta fucking killed me
Do you want me to die too or are you?
Um, I think we should go back to market
Okay, we've been we've been goofing around. I found a lot of items
I'm ready
Yeah, I am gonna just this is what the people need
Um, all right, where are we going?
Forget how to uh change the map. Okay. Um
I feel like I just shouldn't stand here anymore
Okay. Oh boy
Uh, you're gonna have to give me one second while I get away from all this
Okay, where are we going?
Market let's go for it
Um
Do it I did it there theater kid
Sorry, I got the werewolf gun on my screen
That was kind of scary to just see you hanging. I thought you killed yourself. Okay
Wait, okay before we do anything. I have another
Golden seed I have seven flasks dude. You only have three
I've got four now because I switched the one mana
But yeah pretty much it's time to do this
No more messing around. This is the one we are we're ready. We're prepared. We're fresh. We've leveled up
It's coming back. It's coming back
And he hit me on the opposite side of him. Don't it's just once you start complaining. That's when you lose your gamer skills
Something's wrong with them. Something is wrong with this guy
Nice nice
It's good to go
Okay
Get behind him
As he starts putting a lot on his blade. We can just keep hitting him
But don't be too cocky about it. Here he comes
Hey, yeah, just run away from the big slam
Dude, bro. My game is having problems
He's gonna slap
Dude, he keeps freezing
This is the run dude. I'm going to heck. Yes
Oh heck. Yes
Watch that cockiness
Oh god
Watch that watch it watch it
All right, easy easy
I'm going easy
He's probably gonna do the spin
Is this easy mode?
That's it. Yes
We got through the uh, we got through the wall
I you're gonna be really mad about this, but I just got another golden seed
I got two golden seeds and the halic tree left medallion. Oh, okay
So i'm caught up
catching up two seeds
Nice
That feels pretty good. And that's how you have twins
All right points. I need points in endurance. Why did I do this?
Decks, I think I need to do it. I think I have to two decks just do at least two decks
Okay
No, you know what? I can fix this right now
I'm gonna fix it right now
I have 40 000 souls now. Let's fix this
You fucking piece of shit
All right, I feel like i'm getting so many just like a handouts from the game
all right
Okay, this is big this fixes it
i'm thinking
like
15 12
or like 14
16 12 14
Like this are we okay? Is this gonna be all right?
Sure, whatever
all strength fuck it
16 12 14
Is 12 decks enough? I don't think it is. I'm an idiot
Leave decks at 12 leave decks at 12. That's enough. That's enough. That's enough
You're an idiot. Why?
I want to go to round table to upgrade my sword. I thought I couldn't do it as much but I can upgrade it like a lot more
12 is good, dude, dude 18 decks, please 14. I don't know
Check the weapons
Hold on. This is this is really important because i'm gonna be i'm not gonna be able to level up for like another
Four or five hours stir. I need to get this right
You're just gonna find like 10 more remembrances
You say that now but look at what you've had to deal with
Yeah, but that's me
I can use this
I can use this right now
This needs faith, but that doesn't matter. I can use this
This thing's pretty beefy
Use the pizza cutter
pizza cutter pizza cutter
18 ducks
Use the pizza cutter. All right, we need a poll because i'm sorry i'm gonna be like waste a bunch of time here
Do you want me to put enough points into decks to use the pizza cutter?
Because this is yeah, this is the decision we have to make
You're asking me
I mean you can contribute if you want
Oh, well, I don't care
But I wonder if they even shoot if there's
Pizza cutter sucks. It's dog shit. It's so bad. All right, I
What a bad idea
What do you want to do? I'll tell you what I want to do
Can we go do this at round table? Hold?
Yes
Did you say to go?
I did and then it says you already voted to warp here
You voted my map is frozen until like the timer runs out
Okay, it says it failed
Okay, don't do it again. Okay. I'm not doing it for me to do it might be like a weird host thing
All right
That's not
That's not a big majority
to vote it
That's not
That's 53. That's not that oh shit
but
on guard
Someone's in the round table. What's going on? This looks a little different man. Why does it look so different?
Actually, I have 40. I don't even have a weapon equipped. I have 40 000 souls right now. Please kill him
Bro, i'm trying. Thank god. I was about to shit my pants. Can we get a weapon? Can we get something?
Satisfaction, I thought you got his arm
Oh, it's over. It's over here. It's over here where he was standing
Good stuff. No one is standing anywhere where he used to be standing
No, my round table hold is empty. Oh minus two. The blacksmith is not there. You're not here. No npcs are here
Yeah, mine is gone, too
Okay. Now can we like teleport maybe we can do it now?
Yeah
this
Looks yes. I got an item
I do not nobody's in here. Uh, i'm not there's nobody here. Okay. Well you were just leveling right?
I just want to I need to blacksmith real quick. Yeah, I you you I
No blacksmith isn't here weird. Okay, so let's teleport out. Should we try again?
Uh omen killer is a mog type weapon. I think i'm going omen killer
I know that it was 53 but you're forgetting about the streamer vote. My vote is worth 5 and i'm going with the mog type weapon
I think
Our games are not synced
Yeah, i'm gonna dismiss i'm gonna like yeah, just use the get out of my world. Yeah, i'll use it right now
I almost feel like it'd be easier to like
Dismiss you from the world and then do round table hold we probably yeah, let's do that
I feel like we spend so much time trying to get there that we could have already just done it
So just do your thing and then when we're done upgrading then we'll be back up first chance we get we gotta find the uh,
The other blacksmith that we can use so we can avoid this as well
Yeah, I am playing as me strong. That's true. I can't go against the me strong
Uh build what does omen killer use in need?
Well, you have smithing stone too
Uh, I probably let's see I do
I have two smithing stone twos
Oh, well, you're probably gonna need them unless you're using a somber stone thing. Uh
What is that? What is the omen killer? Oh, this thing is pretty cool. I like it
This uses regular smithing stone. So I need it. Okay. Well, this causes blood loss. It does
Strength infuse it
Do I have that yet?
Uh, I don't really have um, I forgot. How do you sell things?
blacksmith
Blacksmith has a cell tab
All right. That being said let's go ahead and do this
Because I I need it so bad, right? I got i've got dex 12 dexterity. This is good
I gotta get my my vigor up and my endurance
Okay
much better
So
Now this is faith scaling
When are you gonna when's your guilty gear tournament?
Don't you they're asking you that?
Uh, I think they're just saying words directed at you in hopes that you'll read them
Oh, that's right. You can do that, right? Okay. I forgot you could do that
150 41 130 61
All right. I am now prepared. I'm completely ready. Can I level up one more time?
Okay, I thought I had more stuff than I thought I had but I didn't have the things I thought I had
I'm just selling the rune arc. I don't care
Go ahead and do that
Why not?
Actually, I thought there were a thousand not 200
Okay, where are we gonna meet up?
Uh, wherever you feel like uh, we can do the rest of the castle that we just unlocked. Let's do that
Oh, and I need to reinvent you to my world. So i'm gonna go back to
market
and invite
My seal is down. Uh, we could make sure you use the humanity before you try and reconnect
And i'm standing exactly over here if you can see find my son
Sell the pizza cutter. I might have sellers remorse if I do that
I need to make sure
7800 come on. I'm almost ready
We should pee too. We should like go to the bathroom. I have not I did pee you can get you can do whatever you want
okay, you know I
I peed
Peed for like three minutes straight
Uh, but there are also a lot of items here like at the gate castle
Yeah
Uh, and they're all scattered on the floor and you can just open up the main gate because there's no one manning the ballistas
That's pretty good. All right. I'm gonna take a quick pee break. I will be right back
Um, give me like two minutes. I might refill this drink to this water. I might get some more water
There was tea in here earlier, but i'm gonna replace it with water. I'll be right back. Oh, are you hello?
Oh my god, i'm, sorry everybody. Are you hello? Are you?
Hello, are you?
That was that was okay. All right. If we good you ready to get this. Uh, yeah
Uh, yeah, I think yeah, i'm i'm i've got my sign up. I'm just waiting for you to join
Uh, can you use an afigi? Shut the f**k up. Remember just ate a fistful of edibles. I did not
All right. So I got my new weapon. What is the actual what is that? Oh wait, that's pretty cool
Looks like a holy buff. Yeah, I have all right attack power with successive attacks. He's fully ready
All right, let's go. Where are you? Oh, there are so many items here
Are we going right front door? Yeah
Did you grab all this shit?
I don't know if you want to go around and just do the other stuff and pick up items as well
We can do that. We should probably i'm more used to that route. Yeah, I got golden
Kill him kill him
Oh kill him. No, i'm kidding. Don't you should because he steals souls from you. What?
Yeah
Did you get his ball bearing?
Which is good if you take that to the you know, the the shop ladies the maidens
Then his shop is still randomized at them, but you do miss out on
The what is it the last smithing stone available?
I don't know if that was a good idea
It was a great idea
What last smithing stone his store has the last like dragon smithing stone in it at the end of the game
His shit's all randomized. Yeah, but I mean in like the regular playthrough not in this one. Okay
I'm just saying that's is this a regular playthrough right now? No, i'm gonna saying in jet and regular playthrough. You don't
He stays around. Well, well actually like for real right now, dude, you're not gonna make it to the end game
We might not but whatever smithing stone three
No, demi human mobs
What?
This thing's pretty good
Reeves
Epic that guy was strong. So wait, sorry is this cutscene up here gonna screw everything up?
um
Decent odds wait, no, no, no, we killed him
Yeah
We also killed him
He can't close us in the
He's a mean guy. He'll never become elden lord. I mean if he just ran up there after everything died
It's like put the crown on or whatever it work. I got explosives
Yo, I am getting the smithing stones
This is i'm ramping
Can you get out of the way?
I think uh me we might need a
We might need a full reset soon
Because every like 30 seconds, you're kind of just teleporting
oh
He's strong be strong watch out misbegotten, uh, he's kind of stuck up there
See what happens watch out watch out
Uh talisman pouch. What is that again? Is that for more?
room more talismans
Yes
Crystal spear. I kind of like that
Yo
actual
intelligence man
Yeah, maybe
Cool. I like my character now what changed?
uh
Put on regular just slacks and like a cool cape and a wolf head. Oh, okay. That's all it took
A nice pair of slacks. We got a raid. Oh, a raid did come in
from snaps cube
Welcome everybody playing
Elden ring
co-op seamless co-op mod
I don't know why I just swallowed weird
Human body is a wonder. It's been pretty good so far. I'll say it's been
When we first were talking about doing this, I was actually
Pretty scared that this was going to be every five minutes. We were going to crash or oh I desync
Oh reset it. This has been pretty great. I'd say he fell except for that right there, but that was it happens sometimes
It's okay
You fell is everyone falling just just
I'm working through something right now. I got oh I can upgrade my sword a lot
smithing stone two times three
You're getting a lot of those. I'm not getting any
Yeah, i'm i'm I think I could hit like plus 15 right now if I go upgrade. Did you just do you know the button?
Oh god
Oh god, what is that?
I forgot. There's an enemy that like jump scares you there and it's a fucking bear
There
I pressed it. I swear to god
I
I pressed it. I'm why you would not do that three times
Yeah, gameplay on my stream. No, no, no, no, no, no, I pressed it
All right, dude
Where are you?
Behind you you gotta do another jump
Ah, you think you're so funny think about it until the very end
I could I could just I could get them. I could get them real good here. Holy shit a bear is up here
What the heck?
Nice reaction. That was a good react
One of the one of the best all-time reacts. This actually is a pretty hard spot in the regular game. Yeah in the lore the
Halberd the kind of winged knight that's up there is actually really annoying. I just got some pants for real
I'm not even joking. I've got pants
Well, that's a way easier enemy to deal with
There's a hole there if you wanted
If you need like a joke, i'm fine
Yeah, I we we probably I don't know when you want to do it but
You you are we are have we our connection together is not fantastic right now
Uh, let's end here and I can go upgrade my sword. I'll kick you out
Okay, kick me out and like i'm like reset like the game game. You know what I mean reset the game game
We set the game game
You look golden and crispy you why do you look deep fried?
You've been in a tanning booth
All right, you kicked me out, right?
Yeah, i'm gonna like
Quit and reset i'm gonna like actually restart the whole game like to desktop
I suggest you do it too
I feel like we haven't had a refresh in a little while you're calling for a full refresh
I am calling for a full refresh. Okay, i'm back dude
Um gamer mode was just fucking activated, dude
My long sword went from five to plus 14
Official gamer
Wait, I can still go further. I just don't have the souls
uh
We might have a problem
What's the problem? I can't open the game anymore. What is what is it saying?
Because I just activated game remote. I don't know if you heard
um
Maybe time for a full reset
Yeah
Well, let me do this again and make sure this is not going to be a problem. Okay, we're okay
Oh, thank god. All right for a second
I got like a hard crash with like the with the red stop sign and the white x in the middle and it was like
Blah blah blah blah a bunch of bullshit. I was like this is bad. So we're good. Did you do a uh reset?
Yeah
He's you're lying. I you know, you didn't okay doing a full reset. I got my I got my sword to plus 16 germo
I'm very excited to use it
Um, i'm gonna do a raid with you
Yeah, like like a wow raid not like a
twitch raid
People make fun of me for doing wow references. I hope they do it to you too
I have I I don't know anything about wow. I was doing that for you. Oh, okay. Thanks
Uh, I am gonna go back to oh, yeah. Remember you need to launch with the the dot back
Yeah, that's why you were getting errors. Uh, I think I did it right. So we're going to the rampart tower, right? I am ready
Hopefully a full reset will fix the teleporting problem because you were kind of just
I want to say every 30 seconds or so every every enemy and you would freeze and then 10 five seconds later
It'd be like everything would just kind of catch up. Hope this fixes it. So how are you how you feel?
Are you good? How do I feel? I feel great
I feel like i'm like i'm at the top of my class like i'm getting straight a's but I just put down my uh
My thing you can join i'm talking about like playing this and streaming this you you're good to go
Keep going right i'm i'm I just got the plus 16. All right, I want to hit some things with my new sword
I'm i'm i'm down to stay here for a little while too. This was just checking in
I just want to hit something with my sword. We're good. Let's go. Oh my god
I think I know about that too. I'm the one that came up with that
You actually are the originator. You don't think I know that skip. This is a good guy over here
Hey, hey you isn't this a really scary big like bird enemy?
Yeah
The awful like we made this game, but we also didn't want you to enjoy it bird enemy dude. Look at this damage
What's so is that just a regular? Oh my god
That actually was a lot
How much was that?
Uh, it was 570
What?
Oh, I definitely have to put that on
All right. That's perfect
Don't worry stand behind me. I've never even seen this. Does this have any attributes on it?
No, it's goofy
Insane drip you're looking fresh. I look like i'm belong in a katamari game. Nice line. Nice line
There's been a lot of bugs
But you have like an antecedent
One shot. All right. Now we definitely are going to be able to beat this whole game, right? Like if that's the case
I ascend it. This is glint stone pebble people you just killed that I hate him
Watch out dragons ahead
flag
In my first playthrough, I was looking at my menu and that
Swept down like that and I thought it was a dragon tail and I screamed
That's pretty crazy. I've never noticed it
Oh shit, we got a bow boy. Keep it down. That actually is one of the harder ones, isn't it?
Honestly, you should just
You're doing 600 plus damage. Yeah
Oh my goodness. I'm so glad I didn't get hit by that
I thought I had another weapon in my other hand
Whirl. Oh flame
Oh, he's too short. He's too short
You gotta fight him
All my swings just went over his head. I got him
Cool. This is a fun game
Should I play this game normally? I haven't this is the first time i've really played it. Is this like a yeah
Um, I actually wouldn't really recommend it alone. It's like too hard and like I don't it's not even like fun
Are there this exhausting are there this many enemies that are spawned in and stuff or is it like are they how does it work normally?
Uh, this is about the same like really
It's just the co-op thing. Yeah
Like a lot of a lot of this you're thinking that but a lot of the spawns in this game don't really make any sense
Like they put crabs next to like sorcerers and stuff. It's kind of just spam enemies. You should rest
I'm uh, i'm trying to make you remember when we played terraria together
I'm I know I remember I brought it up earlier and um
Again, everyone i'd like to apologize for like making germa play a great game and having a fun time with him
I'd like to sincerely just say i'm sorry
There was a lot of minus twos that just didn't even understand what was going on right there
For those of you that don't know stir and I played terraria together and it was me just watching him play with like a thousand mods
And i've never played terraria before and I was just like is this game like fun normally and he's like, yeah
Yeah, but like don't worry. Just come over here. Yeah, take take all these items. Nothing wrong. Just watching
All you guys are just watching. Hey, I had a good time. It was fun
I remember
It really was so funny because I remember it's half the time. I would just be like hey i'd be up in the base
And you'd be down
Adventuring somewhere just collecting ore like the one specific ore that you needed
and
whoa
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I think that just both get a great drop. Yeah, I think that's
I got a fantastic drop doing that. Oh, it's one of those omens. Hold on
From where though? Is it an omen? No
All the way up there ignore him. Yeah, yeah that guy we killed earlier, but he respawned
Let's just get this bonfire
And then go up the other way
I think this thing is really really good
Oh my goodness
50 strength, I could almost do that. What about the int? I can respec when we do the um
Academy. Yeah, we already have the key. Yeah good for now. No me strong doesn't have intelligence
Ooh, I like that
I like your outfit
There we go. I was waiting. Okay. Yeah, that's my good drop. You're just missing the default green tunic
Well, i'm kind of like an epic bar face the glint stone pebbler
We're we're at godric. Aren't we?
Yeah, he's like right through here
magic missile magic missile
Secure that for you secure that kill but my game keeps lagging
Are you on are you on the wi-fi?
Yeah, but it's a good wi-fi router. I have like five to ten megabytes down. No. Oh the oh the giga mat
the bamco giga mat
I just don't think that I think this mod does not like um the bigger open areas
It does uh, like when we load a new zone. Sometimes it freezes and wiggles
It hasn't been that bad for me
Cool, but I don't need it
Oh, what'd you get?
mushroom arms
Oh
Can't really see him
No, i'm not on the wi-fi
It's an item over here. What is it? I am going to one shot godric
I hope you do this
Well godric is going to be a dog
Uh, we're aggroing like every single thing here
It's probably not a good idea
oh
I've run out of magics
Oh these fuckers. He almost got me
Got a larval tear I have one too. So that's awesome
Oh, okay. I thought you were looking for one. Yeah, I got one. I actually got one really early
It was like
I want to say the first like half hour we were playing first hour
Okay
Candle stand i'm getting a lot of random weapons now
Yeah, I think we're pretty set to just do content
Oh painting
Morgan's cursed sword rate mace. Is that should I use that?
Oh, yeah, some blood weapon. Fuck that. How did I just break that myself?
I don't know you can power stance then
This thing gave me three awesome items. I prefer the mace
another one
gargoyles greataxe
Another one that might be better than what I have right now
Have you have you plus one a single weapon? Yeah, i'm holding right now. You should do a weld
You want me to do a weld do a weld huge weapons. I think dual welding is
Definitely dangerous, especially if you don't have a mask for it if you want you do jump attacks. They're really strong
Oh my god, that seems amazing
I'm actually gonna do this for a minute. Oh
Little gross boy
Didn't even see that until it started moving. Oh, we got one of like I hate these enemies
Oh, there's been a lot of I hate these enemies thrown out there today
This is a real
One takes the cake. Uh, this is bad. This is actually not good
This is gonna be harder than the boss it probably right now and i'm getting killed by a fucking one singular gargoyle
Good luck
I love this slap
Oh my fucker fucking fucks. What the fuck? What was that? I think it was one of the enemies
Are you okay?
Yeah, i'm good. Yeah, watch out. There's like this one gargoyle up there. You're not gonna want to fight that guy
Okay
It might have even been this one. He's killing me again
Oh shit with the dog
Here a whimper i'm doing all strength and endurance and i'm gonna do dual weld
This he's sitting up on this stupid fence post thing and I can't hit him fight the other stuff
Dude, this is a shit show of an uh, and this is this is
I don't think we can walk by here
I don't need to you don't run up there. Don't start hitting the things sitting on the spike
We got a dual weld
Okay, hold on minus five thousand souls, by the way, what do you mean me or who me?
I'm still alive still. Okay, kill this girl girl
one at a time
Okay, I can magic bolt the the ass sitter
And I don't know what is shooting that like giant blob of poison. I have no idea
This other thing the guy with the crown
I don't think we can fight this
We can it's just
We gotta like one v one and not be like perma staggered when he comes out here or two v one
Because i'm always fighting some other shit while you're fighting it
Oh, it's him doing that
Oh my god, look at the surface area. The surface area is insane
And it made me realize there's a good item back here. Well, uh, I don't want to reset this but i'm poisoned
Hopefully how long do not we're good
there
You are
Okay, bye
You good. Oh, you got the finger. I got the finger
Well, I think I know what?
Has to happen now, right?
I I don't know what needs to happen. This is the weapon i'm using
All right. I mean i'm pretty settled in what I got. I'm i'm comfortable
Can I do a well, um, it didn't look like I could swing both
Is it like a joke that how you pronounce that is that like a running gag or is it real? What do you mean?
Dual weld dual welding dual will do wielding
do welding
Bam
Did I kill it?
Yeah
Dual wheel dual wielding
You almost sound like when you say it that way that you're trying to do like the ubu duo wielding
This is what it sucks
The finger this thing's dumb. It didn't even hurt anything
Actually, it's kind of good. Never mind
Okay, changed your tune pretty quick there buddy. Do
Welding
Duo wounding
All right. Are we ready?
Uh, no, let's go up the stairs the other direction and and get those items and just look what's up there
Do a wee bit of a rest
Uh, let me put a point into what do you think strength? Of course wait endurance
I love how this greatly increases your maximum fp and it is
as much
I don't think they can even cast one spill
It's because it's percent based
Yeah
It's really not I need to like upgrade it
Upgrading things is pretty good
You know, what's really actually good about this is you don't get staggered if you take damage while you do it
Oh, is it one of those those are really good. It seems pretty good. Okay, where did you go?
Bro, are you on the wi-fi? I went back down to the bonfire. Oh and I rest it
oh
All right
I don't look funny enough. Can you can you step up your comedy right now?
I haven't laughed in like an hour. I know like what the fuck dude. I think this is pretty good actually
I you feel like I like your face
I miss my face. I only wore this for you
Do you want it? I'm not going you think i'm gonna try to
Pretend to be one of the most celebrated people on planet earth. No, there's only one bar
I'm actually kind of offended that you did that
Did what?
You know, nobody can be barf drinker besides barf drinker. Okay. Well, i'm no longer barf drinker
I apologize. I thought you'd think it was like funny and we'd have like a ha you're barf. Sorry
I don't I didn't see what it was
Uh, are we skipping or we uh, we uh story watchers. We are
Skipping skipping
Can't skip it. Oh, it's god free the grafted. Oh shit
This might not be that bad though. This was one of the dumber ones
Oh my god, dude, just stand there and cast
glint stone
glintstone pebble
i'm out
Shit
I'm gonna die
All right, I gotta stop using the comedy move
See stop
What he's actually teleporting that's what i'm saying
Finger him. Wait, wait, wait. Let me get the last hit
Finger him. What the fuck dude? What what what?
What I got four golden seeds
What are you kidding me?
What did you get? I got a heater shield and
I didn't I didn't even care. It was so I didn't even I didn't even
You got well, at least you got cool stuff
Yeah, I don't know if I would be betting against us right now. He has an absolutely jacked up
Glint stone. Why are you doing that much damage? I don't understand. How are you doing that? Um
Because it is a weapon art
It's not the actual spell and then the weapon art spells are tied to the upgrade level of your weapon and my weapons plus 16
magic glint stone pebble sword
Jesus like if it was an actual glint stone pebble spell it wouldn't be doing that much. Okay
Let's uh, let's go find some bosses. Hold on
I can level up one more time
I got 20 vigor. I I can do um, just dumping the strength now. I think that's the plan
Plus 10 finger would be sick. Maybe i'll do it. Uh, do you need any smithing stones?
I I have quite a lot of sombers you'll probably get you up to like a
Does this use? Uh, yeah, what does this use? Is it somber or is it regular?
I don't know. This thing's kind of a piece of shit though
Strength d dex d and 20. I mean 50. I mean this thing kind of sucks
I know i'm so indecisive. I have to pick something usually again
I think we actually switch personalities because usually this would be me I picked up a default long sword and was like that's that's the one
What about this thing though?
I expected that if we played together you'd be using a whip. So this is uh an upgrade really
Yeah, okay
I will keep the finger for a comedy weapon, but i'm going to probably upgrade the ruins great sword
I think that's the plan. Okay in the meantime, let me put the actual thing that I had. Yeah, it's just for now
Nobody here sitting sitting that no one's here sitting the chair. Oh my god. Don't don't get out of that chair
You haven't earned it. I did sit in it. You lagged because you're on a fucking 28k modem. I'm on a 45 180
Forget where you go here. Okay, you still haven't landed
He's okay. That was funny. I got my rivers of blood
But i'm more of a default long sword kind of guy
It's weird. I mean, I I know I know you pretty well at this point
But it is kind of interesting that we're playing randomizer and you're like, yeah, i'll take just the regular long sword
I haven't really found anything else that like made sense
I did want to be a spellcaster. We haven't found anything. I got a crystal spear, but they kind of suck man
There is I I didn't want to over complicate it even more
But I think there's an option in the randomizer that when you find an item it also has like a random ash of war
and they can be um
Get like some really weird combination items. This is the guy that
I I know I have to tell you like you this is that guy, right? I yes it is you say so
Give me some runes, please donate 10 runes. Sure
Yes
Oh ancient death rancor kill him take a path to the graveyard
I just realized that this is not the outfit he's supposed to have on
Bubble people I think we can just go straight to uh ray lucaria because we have the keys
Yeah, we do
Pretty far away though. No, you like go down this hill and then you're out into the lake
Hmm. What's on your food?
Uh radar what what should I get?
What should I do what's on my food radar for your radar? Yeah, like what what are you thinking?
What am I thinking that you should eat?
Not necessarily. Yeah
now
Well, if you don't want to hear it
You I don't know lasagna. I that's that's not
Oh, hey mcdonald's or like a pizza or like making
I'm not gonna make a fucking lasagna
Not right now
Actually
That sounds pretty good
That's a that takes a lot of time
It does it takes a very long time
Uh, you're gonna let's just you're gonna keep riding kill this thing
I'm not killing it
So were you gonna upgrade that because again like I I might actually have all the way to plus 10 somber smithing stones
Maybe I haven't decided yet
But I somebody said you can't drop
stones
Really? I don't know if they're lying enough
You can't apparently you cannot drop, uh smithing stones on the ground
Although this is not in the right spot now it is
I'll just keep them for when I find something
This is my favorite part of the randomizer so far is opening up these merchant loot boxes
It's got a lantern for me. Thank god. Yeah
But I can't afford it
I think stone one i'll take it
Uh glenstone craftsman's cookbook. Do you want this? Well, the cookbooks I think are also random
Why is this so expensive?
Actually, that's something we probably should have been checking. I forget how the cooking even works. Wait a minute
This is I can buy this is an unlimited amount of these boiled crab. I can buy
It's about 20 of them. Um, okay. I'm gonna mark this because
you know the boiled crab boiled crab boiled crab
is
Uh greatly boost physical damage negation for a time
These are apparently really really hard to come by
And they're 250 and i'm i'm gonna buy like 500 of them. Sounds like cheating
It is
I guess I'd take the bell, right? Okay. All right. Um, where to um straight to lucaria
The pokemon I think that's his name
Isn't there a uh a map um, um, he's hitting me he's hitting me even stop hitting me. I can't help you
I'm fine
I still don't have a plus one to my flask
What happened? That was really weird. Okay. I'm all right
The bonfire
Yeah, this one's fake. This one's actually fake. This one doesn't work. This one's not real
They should have added mimic graces that yeah, they like attack you and shit
Isn't um this this portal if you go in here teleports you all the way up to the door. There's a different one
I don't remember. Oh legendary
lord armor
Yeah travel go in there
Yeah
Oh god, where are we going? He doesn't even talk to me anymore
What did you go on the portal? Yep. Okay
Man i'm getting the good good stuff
I'm gonna be elden lord
You probably are and it's annoying because look at how cool you look and how much powerful you are than me
We kind of match now. How do I not have a key didn't we both? Oh wait, maybe we I can't use it
Maybe we bought the fake one
Because there's there's two keys do I need one too
No, but there's two lucaria keys one that you give to the guy for a quest and one that you use for yourself
It's the fucking not. Yeah
It's the one that he gets
Okay, and maybe uh, maybe we can go where the dragon is and see if that
Oh that actually might be a much easier boss
Yeah, we're jumping off. Uh, be careful. I've died here. I died here probably 30 times
Okay, well i'll watch you go first. Yeah, you're gonna die dude. Holy shit. That's where you do it
See trust me. Maybe art. I died so many times jumping off of that edge
Just being ridiculed and laughed at by everybody watching for days. I just had a flashback
I remember watching your initial elden ring playthrough in the area near here at the castle church where you have to find the three turtles
It was the closest i've ever come to just ending it all. Where's the dragon?
But also I agree. I fucking hate that place. Isn't the dragon right here? Uh
I don't know. I thought the dragon distracted everything looks the same. I think it's up a bit further
Is it further up? Oh spinning stone?
Uh, there's there's a something boss enemy out here. Where are you? Oh shit. We lost each other
We're good
Yeah, I would avoid the the super slug boss
What is that? Is that a oh, it's a tree spirit
Is that just a regular enemy or is that supposed to be the dragon because the the key is behind the dragon?
That's a regular enemy
The dragon's in like the alcove
dude, he is
Moving his hips in all sorts of ways
He is just
He's so he won't leave he won't stop his aggro range is insane
Do you want to kill him? Let's do it. Let's teach him a lesson
Okay
Um, let's find the dragon. We actually demolished him
Yeah, let me look at the map. Oh, I didn't get wait. I thought I picked up the map
Come on snail shoot that ballista. That's okay. I love that. I'm gonna shoot his blister and I'm gonna get them
Oh, no, wait, I don't have any hands. How am I supposed to do this?
Don't kill him. He's a character. I made he's he's like a I gave him a voice
That means he's he gets to live you were the one hitting him. I didn't mean to yeah, let's go
Uh, I think we're on the wrong side
um
We're gonna go like up here like this way, right? Yeah, it's up here
Pfft
We're gonna soft lock our game if you give one of the bosses a voice
Uh-oh
So don't do that. Isn't it right up here?
Where where is it?
We need the map in this direction
Get out of the way. Yeah, it's up here
All right. What is it? I hope it's
I hope it's really easy
Oh, wait, I think I saw
Oh, it was a dragon. It's a dragon. What?
But then it wasn't a dragon but now it is a dragon wait, why is it it's a dragon it's a different dragon lame
Wait, it's not
It's not a dragon
That was the fucking scariest thing i've ever seen in my life that was the scariest thing that's ever happened to me
It was like a 3d movie dude was coming out of the screen my like chest hurts. It actually was a 3d movie. Oh my god
I guess it was a dragon
Shit
Uh, are there two of them now?
No, I think it's just the one
Oh, he hurt his ankle
Watch out
He's gonna breathe the fire
This was not a glint stone dragon
He has a fucking billion health
I think this is the starting area first dragon you would normally fight
Why wouldn't gonna despawn?
No, it's not
Why you gotta be so negative?
And why are you not on the horse?
Are you trying to die?
I don't like fighting him on the horse
I get on the horse like when he moves
Trying to die
Hey
ready
Whack
He went way shorter than I thought
What the hell did I do that for?
It's a good thing we didn't aggro him into that like other boss enemy
No
He did
Does he get his health back? I don't think he does unless the co-op mod broke it
He does not
That can just happen
Oh my you gotta be fucking kidding me
Good luck
I've died to that enough times
Oh, I'm just gonna fly away again
Are you trying to duck behind them?
That was so funny
That should have worked and if it did you would have gotten a stamp of approval
That's so awesome
It was actually worth a try. You're right. Come on
Every cartoon i've ever watched
Means that should have worked
That's gonna get me isn't it?
He needs to stop
Glintstone dragon agil. Yeah, i'm gonna get hit he took one damage
I think it's because I was mid jump
Agil
Oh
Oh my god
He just just just
Lacerated your throat
Who's it?
Yeah, I would have had the health if this game allowed for rp and I could have hid behind that stump
That's too bad that that didn't work aim for the head genius. It's i'm not playing
We were spectating him playing
That wasn't me
Wait, are you talking about me? But I am a genius. Thank you
Okay, so
The key was behind him and I got more like golden seeds. There's a lot of good items behind him
Let's do that at least get the key
Don't hit his legs
Hey, I play my game the way you you play yours, you know, you play you know what I mean?
I'll play my game the way I want
Oh, it is the first dragon. That's why it's doing the intro
Oh agil
Agil
I don't know if people know this but his head's actually up in the air and it's not on the ground at all times. You can't
Always hit his head
Because it's raised above the ground
A lot of the time well, you don't know anything
What did you just do to my fucking best friend trying to get him right in the face that move sucks that move sucks bad
uh
Coward
Coward before me
Is that a world of warcraft reference?
Is that what Illidan says?
That was not as deep as I wanted it to be
I let me try that one more time
Coward before me way better and a thousand times better than the first one
That is not that was what you were supposed to hear
But instead you heard something else
Okay, what is it? What's the reference old timer? I don't know. It was an orc
But it is world of warcraft
maybe
I I don't
The first one was the first one was cookie monster
What the hell was that move?
Oh god
We're almost got it almost got it almost got it
There's something in my face
Don't breathe fire this way don't breathe don't breathe fire this way. That's the slam
Oh, that was a good hit
I knew he was I was fucking greedy. I was like i'm just gonna hit him the one time
And germa's also gonna be dealing damage
There's no way he's gonna get another attack off
Hey noticed uh
You were kind of like looking at me and my buddy over here. I think you like fucking such hot shit
Thanks for help fighting the dragon
Dick
I did nothing
He's watched
That that's
the dragon trainer
Dude, that was his dragon
And why wouldn't he be over here going like no, what have you done to my dragon?
because he's actually
kind of relieved
Because his dad was a dragon trainer
And he didn't really ever want the job
But there's someone's gotta take care of it
How many of you guys here like hate my guts?
Why what?
I keep doing like these like stupid voices
All right, where we going i'm dead right now
So I need a rest you're kind of in control of the whole the whole situation and you're just killing the mana
dumb beetle
Do you need more mana? No, we're ready to do it dude. I can't vote i'm fucking dead
So I have to run all the way back here
I guess it's so far
If we're saying there was the lb, there's no lb
Oh, you have to run all the way over there. Oh, come on guys
It's not even a good impression of me I would have laughed if it was good
It wasn't you you think everything's about you
That way that wasn't you doing what I was just doing
It was me doing what you were doing, but it wasn't me being you
Okay, let's go up to lucario now that we have the actual key. I'm very confused of what you just said
Let's do it. What's this pole?
I walked in the castle already
Why would you do that now? I don't even have control of the character. I turned into an npc
Yeah, I might have fucked things up really think through you stop rushing. What the hell. How big is that hand back there?
There's a hand that big in this game
You've never seen that
No, it's a secret boss
I actually do mean that it actually is like a secret boss funny thing a tidbit about this actual secret boss in the game. It drops
Nothing. There's no reason to kill it. It doesn't do anything normally. Um,
I it's in there's like a some overpass where it's kind of hanging
It doesn't it's it's like a useless enemy to kill. I forget where it is
It's like a narrow
Place and it's like an overpass and it drops down in the mountains
Yeah, I remember when it when I finding it was like holy shit. Oh my god and then killing it
It was it didn't not even like a butterfly nothing. It has no loot table. Wow, stand up fix your posture for god's sakes
I'm tired 19 percent of you are hate watching me right now. Oh shit
Say something say something that they'll hate. No, I don't want to do that. That's what they're here for
How could it be only 19? That sounds pretty that sounds pretty low
Oh god
This guy has a lot of help I got you I got you. Oh you okay. What?
I think you're underestimating how strong this guy is. He's pretty strong. I don't see
He's pretty strong
Oh, what the fuck I was trying to match it I came like lagged
Where are you? I died. I'm coming back. Oh, oh you didn't like spectate. No, I just did didn't give me the option to
Okay. Am I waiting for you?
You have an e-buff. Oh, whatever. We'll be fine. He has like 700 damage glen stone. We're fine
It's like a bonfire up here
Seeing this place for the first time from the outside was awesome. This guy had me huge blood-borne vibes
Okay, I think I am I am now the decent like are you some weird shit?
Okay, what's in here seems better now?
um
This is a classic run through this room and pretend it doesn't exist. I don't even care what the enemies are. Okay
and let's rest
Oh, why do you still have 18 000 viewers? I don't know
Yeah, I think I think I did leave like 17 000 souls at the dragon boss
It gave it to me after I died so I thought I would respond with them because the weird co-op stuff
I think I gotta go back
Yeah, I got we gotta go. I gotta go pick this. Yeah, they're gonna go pick this up
Yeah, there were 18 000 souls in the ground. That's you had that that's a lot
Yeah, it's a lot. So i'm voting
I'm asking kindly once again if we're
to the temple quarter, um
Where is that just south of us?
Oh, oh, oh, oh I see what you mean. I didn't I I thought for a second
I thought you're talking about the dragon area. Oh, yeah the dragon area. I don't know why this is called like temple
There's no temple you got what you needed
Yeah, let me go back to uh
Church of the cuckoo. Are you insecure right now? No, i'm just chilling. I'm having fun. Don't worry about me. I'm good
What do you what would you be insecure about the cookie monster voice that I did like 10 minutes ago? Oh
You did do a you did do a pretty weird marge like three hours ago as well. That was actually good though
That's the difference
I don't care if a voice if a voice sucks
And it's stupid and it's like cringy that a human would do it in front of like a stadium full of people
That's fine. As long as it was good
You cannot go back and tell me wait
what
Is it like I don't know by definition if it was cringy then it also wasn't good. No
It was it was an almost flawless marge simpson
But that was like kind of cringy to do that. Don't you think?
Uh, no
Oh, all right, then there's no argument here
Yeah, i'm just gonna let that guy we're just gonna like oh it's mambo
Yeah, mambo number five
Everybody loves mambo. I thought that was a giant sheep. I'm tanking it. I'm tanking it. I'm tanking it
um
Will you one of us is falling off this?
I'm tanking this i'm tanking that was so sad
Thank you. I'm tanking it. I'm tanking it
I'm taking it out mambo
I hate I don't want to kill mambo, but we kind of have to
Why is ever why why does every creature have a name?
uh
when you played
Through the first time what did you use for a spirit summon?
mimic tier
Yes, I ruined my first playthrough
that's oh
Look, it's not that that's not a big deal
I didn't use the spirit summon all game until I found that and then my chat was like
I was like what?
I watched my mimic tier kill morgot without me even playing the game and then I kind of felt like oh, this is not
I remember do you guys remember that it was like wow morgot. Oh my god
This is so epic and he just killed him without even playing and it felt really I was like, oh, I didn't even really do anything
I
I can't remember there was like one boss that I let my mimic tier fight on their own
And I was like, I don't even feel bad about that. I didn't feel like fighting this boss
Well, the reason why I say that is because the snake that enemy we just fought is what is going on
What is this guy doing? It's super frozen. Do you think i'm getting what you were talking about before?
Uh, I upgraded that snake that with the fire whip to plus 10. That's what I used the whole game
His name was mambo
I also ignored I completely ignored the mechanic
That's a big bird
What would you say is uh?
Did you hate elden beast like everybody else did
um
Kind of yeah, I don't know this very many people that oh my god. Okay. Hold on. This thing could kill us both
Uh, this thing has so much health
I think we just run. Yeah, we have to run I think
Don't go over there. What use the you can't move
Oh my god
Help i'm just i'm going across the bridge man. I don't want to sing you i'm asking god
get shit
I'm telling you just come across the bridge. We don't have to fucking kill this thing
Oh, okay. All right. All right
I'm fine
This is so stressful
Why is this guy disappearing with magic? Did you see what what?
I didn't see
Where did this come from help?
Are you still alive?
Yeah, how did you live through that I don't understand I I stood back and watched nothing aggro'd to me
Uh, but what are you doing?
Uh, should I rest?
Wait, where's the bonfire? Oh, do you want me to reset it?
uh
Sure, I think we need to do like a legit reset because it's desyncing a lot. I
Don't close the game yet because my I have 20 000 souls that are on the ground out there
Oh, okay
All right, all right this guy this guy is fucking crazy man. Well, just ignore just ignore him. Okay. All right
Oh, it's the teleporting glintstone guys. Is that what you meant? He actually teleports
Oh gosh, do I am I gonna get those?
Here you
You can go around the side my game crashed. Oh, thank god is beck
There's still dude. There's still an angry dude down here
Okay, I am now ready to sever the connection
We got let's get the next bonfire
Uh, okay. I'm gonna follow your lead
Okay
Yeah, we're desyncing so hard
Watch it. We're gonna just jump and run
my god
Don't drop those souls. I'm not i'm holding them
Excuse me
What don't you what's happening? Okay
Sir, I need you to communicate with me clearly. Why would you am I should I go up there with you? Yeah, that's where my next bonfire is
Don't follow me. Did you forget everything? No, I I remember but he's just moving so fast. He's moving too quickly
Oh, sorry. I'll slow down. I'll wear some heavy armor
All right. So do you want to actually do like a reset? Yeah, I'm gonna do like a quit the main menu and we'll restart
You know, I don't think we need to restart the whole game. No, I don't think so
Like I have to banish you
Yeah, leave us alone
What is doing that?
And then I banished you
I hope you spent your souls
I did but I um, am I gonna get those back?
This eighty six hundred they're gonna be right here, right? Yeah. Sure. Yeah, they're okay. We're good
You look like you're in a painting
Cool. I am ready whenever you are in fact
I'm just gonna get out of the way because this thing's gonna keep doing that isn't it?
Yeah, I put my thing down. I'm gonna try and kill it in the real world, which is my world
Do something funny. I'm falling asleep
Did you just not see the the insanity of the last five minutes
Maybe if you're falling asleep, you should go to sleep and actually get a good tonight. Good night. Good night. Rest
I feel like I feel like we screamed at least five or six times each
What why are you asleep?
I'm really used to the screaming by now. So it's not that big of a deal
Don't do that though
Oh, that was the wake-up call
Get in here. There's a chest back here. You're running away wrong way
You're kind of just freaking out dude. I'm fine
Don't you want the sick loot? Sure. I got immutable shield
A little bit of witchcraft the first stone sword key. I found the whole game pretty cool
And you get the chest
This chest right there. Yeah
golden rune
Pretty cool. Have a pizza
party
Have a piece I could go for a pizza
Hmm somber ancient dragon smoothing stone. We actually just did that
There's a lot of hidden walls here well
now
The game really begins because I just got horror loser remembrance. This is like a hundred thousand souls. Nice find. That's a good find
That's a pretty good find. That's also a good find but it's faith, isn't it?
Stupid bubble thing
But that's just not good
Get the axe
Get the axe get the axe don't do the remembrance
Is the axe good? I don't remember it. I feel like the weapon art was kind of lame on it
Maybe it scales really well
All right, it's this one here, right
It's the one that has no books, right?
I don't know. I think this is another one of those things that maybe only ever did one time. Yeah, it's over
This place is wacky
It's like three or four ways to go in secret walls
Ooh, I think that's all right
Then come over here the items you get from the boss souls are also randomized. Oh, that's all right
Well, i'm just gonna break it then just put strength true
Okay, cool. And by the way, um
Interesting to note nothing up here, but uh jump over here
Take a look at that
Mm-hmm
And I think there's another thing we can do here any secrets in here. Uh, no down another one
Any secrets in here? Yes. Whoa
Oh, you were actually fighting something. Mm-hmm
This is the big thing here and I think this is one of the best scaling staff in the game, right?
Um, there's one of those witches in here
This thing actually is gonna this thing hurts a lot from what I remember
It's got one eight feet
Yeah, i've never come down here. Really?
I think I remember
Trying to find this one. So I don't think I uh, I did the whole floor thing that you just did
I think I found the first secret door. That's also really good the magma sword
It's faith
Sure, maybe I should do faith. I don't know but this thing is the the sword. Yeah
That thing is really good
I get to be the magma worm
I have a lot of souls to lose. So let's beat her first try
This is going to be a really easy boss
How is this going to work with the bubble stuff?
What it's not that's not him this isn't a
This is an imposter why is he wearing this default?
He's just he's just a guy
He's in like a ray of lucaria with like the stone helmet thing
He's just a normal guy
Oh, no, this is where this is not. Um, this is the dog
Usually yeah
He healed
He cheated
Next time him
Oh be careful my friend
And nothing left in that flask
Okay, we got him
Gideon off near of radigan
He couldn't pick a character either I don't know
What everything I guess i'll be sir gideon off near of radigan the brave the wise actually
Yeah, do I go full on just absolute insane mode here? What is absolute insane mode?
Could you break that down for people who are unfamiliar? It is me doing the horror loot remembrance and getting like 120 000 souls
You should go super hard here
No mercy
That's it
Wait, I thought it was way more than that. Isn't that one of the last bosses in the whole game?
Yeah, I thought it was like 100k. How much how much did you get 30k?
That might be scaled then is it scaled? Okay. Well because yeah, here should be like 80
It's 80k
For elden 30k though. All right, whatever
What a useless amount of knowledge that i've held in the back of my brain for like a year to be like yeah
I think horror lose is 80 000
And apparently be right and I use this
This thing is crazy
Oh, you got the fucking sexy girl hat. Yep. Sorry. I have it. She's not even real
It's starting to look more and more like the character. I actually played the game with
Oh, is the ball still here? I wonder if the ball is something else. I challenge you to combat. It's an interesting group
Now i'm now i'm fucking
Stand back. I've got the new fall season
um
Will you this is wait, this is a sheep here
Yeah, usually I think there's like bunny rabbits, but the the normal
Enemies are replaced
You know what i'm saying, you know, you know, like i'm not gonna finish the sentence. Yeah, I know exactly what you mean. It's an arm
troll knight sword
I like that weapon
But I probably don't have the strength to use it
Probably not. So do you want to go walk around and get all the wacky shit here or do you want to just kill?
Uh ray lucario and get out of here
um
This area is so big. I just want to kill
uh lucario
Do you want to check back here real quick? It's just a sprint. Why is one of those usually a bunch of items?
The mosquito is biting me
Oh shit, I got the sacramental bud
I got regular club
Anything else back here?
Uh, there's one item around the back
And we got a a tree over here
stop
a little bit of a ritual pot
Oh, I thought there could only be one barf. Oh
What happened to that?
I just wanted to see what it looked like
Okay
I'm putting on this thing again
Yeah
Okay, i'm just going
You're a fraud
me
No, i'm just gonna come out of nowhere and call me a fraud
You're a fraud. You know that
Well, i've got an epic loot here. I gotta get that one
um
Thank god I wasn't
Okay, the ball's still here. What does starlight shards even do? I forget which way it goes at the end
same
Mm-hmm. I've never gone down that way. I died. Why can I see everything?
Uh, oh because you reset it. You want to wait for you?
Yeah
Be careful
I I have to go down to the bottom. There's an item dude
It's a purple
I thought that was gonna kill you
me too
The the guy with the hat
Where does this teleporter take you? I forget
Um, I also forget
What do you mean you forgot? This is it's not like this is like a 200 hour game with
Thousands of locations and and and potentially millions of different things to see
It might take you inside volcano near the volcano manor. I think so
Or I think that one takes you somewhere stupid but there is one in like those locked rooms that takes you to
There we have like a car we have literally I actually have a comedy guy
He doesn't have a weapon. He just has the shield the weapon is a shield weapon. No, wait, he's he's got pyromancy
Killing me with comedy
Oh my god, that hurt a lot
Where did this person come from?
I don't know. Why don't you ask them? I got moon veil
I used that for a while
Uh, i've actually never used it. I would be curious to try it. It's really fun because i'm intelligent
You can uh, let's just make sure we don't get jumped on here. This is one of those awful enemies, isn't it?
No
It was one of the sad pathetic losers
Uh, everybody is gonna hate you for using it because it's like it was like the broken meta weapon
But it's actually very fun to use the weapon arts are awesome
I really like do like the crescent moon slash thingy. Yeah, i'm not gonna use it unless I can upgrade it but
I'll keep it in mind
I mean hasn't this game have like a whole bunch of balance passes. Is it still like oh you gotta get moon veil
I think they nerfed it, but
It doesn't matter
I'm really low on uh healing
For this this is a good idea. Should we?
I mean
We don't know what boss it even is I keep like we get here and it's like oh, yeah
You gotta get ready for the I don't uh
This is where the game we're not gonna be able to beat this. Do you see what's up there?
No, I didn't you didn't see what was up there. I didn't see I didn't see
This is actually impossible
Good luck
This room is so small
Doesn't he do a foot?
Yeah, he fills the whole room dude. This is this is not going to be possible
This is not completable
All right, we're gonna have to figure out
We're just gonna need to scale so much we can kill him like yeah, yes him. Yep
We actually might be okay as long as it doesn't do that more than like four or five times
I have no healing so next one i'm dead. Oh boy
How did you not die?
I don't know
Hey
There's a lot of the optional shit like this where you had to do a lot like go through some weird amount of effort
To fight this boss. Yeah, I also another one. I never fought him
I feel like you missed a pretty large amount of the optional stuff in the game
The game's just that fucking big though. I really didn't
I keep saying. Oh, yeah, I never seen this but like
What do you want from me?
Who what?
You lagged on my screen
He like jumped backwards and his hand
Sliding me backwards hurt me
interesting thought from somebody in chat though is
This is phase one. We have to fight a different boss after this. I think i'm pretty sure that's not sure
There was an option in the randomizer for multi-phase bosses to like switch creatures between phases
Uh, hey, i'm i'm for it. Do you want to go again? It wasn't that bad. No, it wasn't that bad, but I
Um, can I can you I need to do more damage that big explosion because we can't avoid it
but maybe if you get like a
lightning resist shield I have
Uh
I have the crucible shield but it's gonna be so heavy. I don't think this even work
I can drop a shield for you with 34 lightning is
Like this thing says more. Okay, then i've i've just got a little baby light shields
Yeah, we can try that
He didn't have a lot of health and he doesn't that boss normally like
Teleport around in the sky
We might get in trouble there. We'll see
Uh
The one issue is I feel like i'm not doing very much damage with this. I need to upgrade it
Whatever. Fuck it. Let's go. We could uh quickly before we do the boss go to eg
And unlock that blacksmith like we've been talking about because we can just ride the horse straight up there now
Let's try it one or two more times. This is uh, this is one of the fun walkbacks. Yes it is
One of the most one of the most walkbacks of all dark souls
And we should probably get rid of the the bowl
I called it a bowl and i'm mad. We should probably get rid of the bowl. Oh the the bowl are you're teleporting around
Wait, okay. That was not fucking fair
That was not fair
That was not fair. I'm gonna die to random enemies. I just reset them. Yeah, forget where you even go to destroy the bowl
You gotta go up
Is uh outside this ladder I think it's actually out where that border is
I also think there's a shortcut on this side so you don't have to go that way, but it's still pretty long
There go 9 000 souls wonderful. What are you fighting out here?
little baby
Yeah, i've used like half of my flasks already. Well, let's we gotta do it then we have to beat it
I'm down to three
Okay, more like placid who sucks
Oh my goodness
Are you gonna do it? I'm so paranoid
Is it okay actually was not that bad if you if you tank it with the shield?
Yeah, that was pretty good. What's wrong with him? Uh, he's staggered. I'm stunning stabbing his face
face stabbed
um
What are you doing to teleport? Yeah, is this where he does the flying thing?
Oh my god, he's in the walls dude, this is gonna be impossible
He's in he goes in the walls
You're still yeah, your damage is really bad. It's terrible
How upgraded is that weapon plus one man? It's things a piece of fucking shit. This thing's a piece of shit
Upgrade a weapon
I am plus 16
What?
Hold on saying you what you're plus 16
Yes, how did you do that? How did you not hear me saying this two hours ago?
Like four or five times you're a plus 16 on you i'm plus one i'm plus
How do you have that many things? Wait a minute
Upgrade it only costs one per upgrade right back
That's why I wanted to go to the blacksmith. Don't go to the round table
We teleport to uh
Temple quarter again, and then we just got to go north for a while. That was shocking
I'm shocked that you're at plus 16. I don't know why it's shocking
I am shocked. I'm shocked to learn how little you listen to me. He said it like 50 times
I thought you were talking about your glint stone thing was like super powerful somehow because of a
Some reason asked me why it was so strong and I says because my weapon is plus 16
And it's a weapon art
Oh, I you only said that once and I didn't listen to you
You asked who asked
Hey, hey who asked am I right guys?
I asked I care
A plus one weapon a face movie. No controller plugged in
That's so fucking stupid. I cannot believe that
I forgot how this works. Do we go underneath the thing like we just keep going under here
Or do we have to go up to the left for eg?
The thing is I was like so indecisive that I wouldn't oh, I don't want to upgrade that because I don't know. I'm not sure
Up up into the left
up and to the left a little bit of a bonfire here for any bonfire enjoyers coming up on our
Left-hand side if you look out the passenger side window
Well, but to be really fair though
You did go from like doing nothing to like millions of damage like 30 minutes ago 40 minutes
Yeah, because I got very excited and I told you I went from plus five to plus 16
So it's not like this has been going on for the last six and a half hours
This is just you know, like 30 40 minutes ago you got omega juiced up you got absolutely juiced up this happened
Like shortly after market before we did the castle it is
Yeah, because after we beat market there was a whole bunch of smithing stones on the floor for me in the front of the castle
You got absolutely powered up
Really? Yeah
Well, it's not that long
Yeah, I bet you thought it would take longer for me to surpass you kid
Just wait till I get this thing to plus 16. Oh all of a sudden you're gonna be freaking out
Okay, where are we going? Because this bear hurts
Keep running north
Have you played?
You didn't know where you didn't know where we were going until chat told you five seconds ago. I knew
I figured it out. What?
It's a chest over there. Hey, remember when you want to see that
every enemy
every random ass enemy
When uh when elven ring was new after my first playthrough and there were some mods I used one that was uh, I don't know
What's hitting me?
There was one where the enemy aggro range was basically infinite
So like you'd spawn into a zone and every single enemy that has loaded in would run at you
Uh good times
This is pretty good times
So where exactly are we going from where you are right now?
um
Like from where you are currently right now
I believe you just hold left and then you go through some ruins and then eg's on the left. Okay
I feel like I already went kind of far though
You you did you have gone kind of far
I don't think I passed it though
No, yeah, I don't think you've been going that far
I definitely don't think you've passed it. Yeah. No, it's it's right up here. Yeah
Oh, you made it
What are you doing?
um
You were running in place like 100 feet in the air on my screen that whole time
I have no idea where you are. I'm just following the marker. No
Because the marker was pointing me to you in the air
Hey, there you are
You know, they took that sound from vega from uh street fighter. He makes that sound they did it first
um
I think something's wrong with my game
Okay. Well, let's just get to this thing
It's right up here friend
Can you hear the sound of my voice friend? I all right
Can you just tell me north east south or west from where we just continue going north?
This game sucks. This game sucks. This game sucks. This game sucks. Well, how did you die?
This game sucks. What did you do? What what did he do my my horse?
He didn't jump it got like stuck on a rock for a second and it didn't jump
I can't believe that grr rr martin would fucking do that. Like really man
Okay. Hi. There you are. I can finally see you now
Oh, I know where to go now. Okay. Now I I remember now you feel like it's an illusory wall. You have to hit this
Yeah
Yeah, if you're lame you hit the wall
You got my ten souls. Yeah, cool kids do it the other way
Okay
So I need to make a decision here and the decision is i'm gonna upgrade a bunch of shit
He's not here. There he is. He's he's loading in
Okay
Hi, what do I want?
Hey, by the way, just a quick question
Yeah
On my game, it is not one smithing stone to upgrade something
It I need not I need I need four
To keep going. I think you have the like cool cheat game. I don't
Oh
It was it was it's part of the randomizer and my thought because I gave you the overall seed and you copied all my stuff
That you would also have that but I think that makes sense because you actually don't have my seed
So so something happened. It's all the way wait somber. I think it's somber not regular
I think somber is always one like in in the normal game
Somber can't be plus 16. So everyone was making fun of me and it turns out that I I because I was like
Yeah, yeah somber weapons go up to plus 10
Yeah, so when I was doing the upgrades it was like, oh I need four more stones
I'm sitting here going what is people talking about? I had it right. I'm not the idiot. I
I'm looking at what I got on my screen. It wasn't my fault
So give me all your stones then wait, you can't so I need a somber weapon because we'll get
Your weapon and I can upgrade it. Oh, that's right. We can do that. Uh here do this one
I want to use this for a little while. I don't have a somber one
So if you have a plus one, I I can take yours all the way to plus seven
Okay, hold on I can do
I can take this to plus three
four
Okay, I need you can do it from five to seven, right? Yeah. Okay, wait after
No, please not the joke weapon. Well, hey take two take
No, it's fine. It's fine. I'm gonna I'll upgrade this one too. We're doing the finger
You're gonna do the finger. But yeah, i'm gonna do them both. Okay, he's gonna do the finger
I'm gonna do with them both. Is everybody really gonna be mad at me about this? I've been doing like
60 damage for the last two hours. It's gonna be better. I deleted it by accident
I need that back actually so you need to figure that out
I don't have the souls to upgrade if you have like runes you can drop. It's like a thousand per upgrade
Just give it back bro. Just give it back bro. Come on, bro
Yeah, but this is not like diablo 2. I can't drop rune. I can't drop gold on the ground
You can drop runes what right you can just discard like a stack of runes where wait, can you actually do that though?
Pretty sure yes, you can how this is like diablo
You just discard the runes just like you do with the weapon you have to do with your inventory
Not your equipment. Oh, just not not discard leave do not discard them. I need 1200 rune to get seven
Where is this?
Where is it in the item menu? I don't know this item menu was like gigantic golden runes
Oh, okay. I okay, I don't think this is gonna get you there. I didn't think you could drop those
I didn't know I didn't think you could drop those. I thought there's like a bound
That was 400. I don't think I had enough if we could sell stuff here. I could do it, but I don't think he sells
Oh, yeah, I can't I can't plus seven then that's look i'm gonna be doing
Like 500 more damage than I was before. It's fine. We're good. Give it to me. Yeah plus six is pretty big for somber
It's on the ground. It's not did you delete it? No, it's on the ground. I put it put it right here
I can still pick it up again. Okay. Hold on. Let me sit down. You can't pick it up because you upgraded it
What what do you mean now? What hold on? It's too high. What does that mean? He's not plus. What does this mean?
I got a plus one omen killer still
Fucked. Oh, okay. You can't drop that for me. We were trying to tell you we were warning you
You've never had a plus six so you can't just try to play this game with my friend
Fucking miyazaki
When can I hold this? Can I I can't do you see the item I dropped on the ground? I can see that. Yes
Okay, that's a that's a plus two. Okay, I need intelligence first. How much do I need? That's a plus three
That's a plus four. Yep. Well people were telling us we couldn't drop that shit. Wait, I thought we couldn't why is everybody making things up to us?
The only reason we did it that way
Wait, what?
Okay. All right. All right, and so
Here's a uh, here's a maybe you can't see that one. Maybe that one's too high
That one's a plus seven. I got that six, but what do I need to upgrade something else that I can actually use
I need 16 intelligence. So what is somber in my fucking inventory that I can equip dude?
We're just we're destroying the economy. Wait finger
He has the finger and I can't get it back room. All right
I'm just gonna do like the gargoyle axe or something or the omen cleaver gargoyle axe is good
Well, either those but it's regular smithing stones gargoyle
Yeah, can I hold this hold what the gargoyle? Okay, but this is not this is regular smithing stone though
I need four. I mean, please the sword will work. This i'm not sure that it will upgrade the runes great sword
Yeah, I know but I need intelligence
I can't this whole thing got fucked up because you took the fucking finger from me and I can't get it back
What they're saying is is that if you upgrade that sword
Then I can drop the finger and you'll be able to see it because you have an item that's upgraded to six
Okay, all right, so upgrade this stupid sword
What's what I need runes or or I have a bloodhounds fang
Or rivers of blood that I can give you or that you can do it to the moon veil
Because I might actually upgrade that anyway. All right, but I I have I I have I need like 15 000 souls
Okay, that should be enough I I need like 15 000 souls to upgrade this to plus seven
Oh, it's way too much. And what would you like to go do? I'm freaking out dude, dude
I I don't know. I don't have a weapon anymore. I think you only need like
6000 where you just go sell some shit. I don't know. I'm selling literally everything I fucking have
I thought I thought I just almost killed him. We just run up into that castle and kill lice. All right
Go that boss go fight this come on keep playing and save up everything. We're fine
Blame blame the
The fact that we didn't know that how how are we supposed to know that was going to happen because of the the strict
Online integrity of the elden ring game where you definitely can't just download a soul level
200 character and then play online
We can't drop shit. We didn't know we could probably kill this boss
I think we can easily demolish this boss and make it look like children. We're supposed to play this game
I actually don't do terrible damage with this. This area is also
I it might be lower level. I can't remember. Jesus. Oh carrion regal scepter
Oh, I thought that was a sword but also a captain staff this guy like extra big
I feel like they're not normally this big. Oh, you didn't find the secret extra egg boss egg bubble boss
You didn't find the bubble butt boss. Oh, looks like you don't know that his bubble butt can fucking crush your fucking jaw
Dude, i'm so fucked up right now
I'm just like, oh, there's so many emotions doing too much stimulation
There's way too much stimulation right now. First of all, get this off. So lance. All right. What do you think this? Oh my god
Nice damage, dude. Maybe you should upgrade your weapon. Oh my goodness
Oh, that was actually pretty cool. I didn't know that that was cool. All right getting there spam jump. It's heavy swings
What uh guys, uh, what do you want me to do? I need to get I I get it by any means necessary
Don't let them get to you they're they're see they're making fun of you for using something
That's actually good in the game to dissuade you from doing it
So that they can make fun of you when you do something also less efficient. It's gonna just keep happening
They're in your head, man
Sir, I haven't been live this whole time. I don't even know what you're talking about
Then who have you been talking to who's he talking to? I just i'm just having fun with my friend
I told you I didn't feel that good and I wasn't streaming today
That makes me feel worse that you weren't listening to me earlier because I know that's so much worse
That is like a thousand times worse
Now, this is what his full attention is where you're going. You're doing role play. You're doing like some some clergy
Everyone part of it. No, just pick the item that's here
Oh, wow lightning great bolts
Oh, wow, like hear ye hear ye
That but the joke was that i'm not doing a bit. I just wanted you to get the item
You'll get them you don't belong here now
Let's just run through all this
Yeah
I'm surprised. These are all actually ghost mode. I know it's weird
What what happened this fucking goblin goon?
One shot me
Just some regular dude
Oh, I think I have uh, I might have um
Here i'm resetting it. Hello
I might have had a
What uh that I might have the debuffs
Oh my god
Oh, and you had i'm just running to you
um
You just spawned everybody on me too. Yeah, that's fine because you're really powerful and you're capable
Like I just launched a nuke
The way we're even supposed to be going
I think we've dropped down. Don't we?
Do we just do we go drop down somewhere?
I don't remember. I thought you like you come out this way
Then it summons things then you go back and it opens up a different area or
I don't know. It's been a long. It's been like a year. I don't I think we actually oh, oh, but wait, wait, wait
Over here
I think that's different. That's where you get the like the super omega laser beam sword
I wonder what's here then. Oh my god. What a completely missed. What a jump
I didn't even jump forward. I did like the tiniest smallest hop i've ever seen
Yeah, that was a complete whiff
I think over here. No, I just want to go up to uh
Lycia what was that dude?
Oh my god. Okay. This is
There's a dragon over here a big one
Not a small dragon
Yeah, we just went the wrong way. There's a different path up here
This is where the sword of uh knight and flame is right? Yeah
You might need to go back to the bonfire
um, okay
Are you did you spawn or are you not spawned? I I ran up to where we should have ran already
Uh
I think i'm going the right way, aren't I? I think this is the right way. Wait, isn't this I think i'm going the right way
You're going the right way. I think i'm going the right way. No, this is i'm going the right. No, you're going the wrong way
No, i'm going the right way
I'm 100 going the right way. You're going the wrong way
You're on the wrong way
I'm in a bonfire right now. Where are you?
Like a new bonfire you haven't been to but I don't think that I can warp you here because you haven't been here
Am I not going the right way?
You're not going the right way. We don't wait because you come up this way and then
Because we were in here
And then out here
Okay, I was going the right way
Yeah, then over here
I mean I have
I was no idea where you are. I was going the right way
I don't think
That's true
Yes, I know. I'm I I promise you i'm going the right way
Do I have to like look at your stream to see what the oh you aren't you are going the right way and
I i've been telling you I was going the right way
It took a long way to get to the right way
It may have been the long way, but it was a correct way. Is there another bonfire up here? Yeah
That that fucking bowl's wearing your head down dude. It actually is I need to take it off
This is how my mom and dad argue on road trips guy showing off with his mom and dad
Cool, I got I got miniature ronnie and the finger slayer blade
Really isn't that aren't those both the same quest?
I think they are
This weapon is so dumb. It's just like that
It's like just a wall. It's like a piece of a wall. It's like the chair of a it's a leg of a chair
This is an expensive chair, which is a big big hand
Nice swing loser
Big hand is a big hand is here big hand
There's an archer big hand is more important than archer, isn't it?
What if the archer hits you and the big hand's coming for you?
Big hand is more dangerous than the archer archer. You can easily dodge
But the archer hits you and stuns you and then you get hit by the big hand. Yeah. Well if you get hit
Big bear don't go left
Which way?
This is a mobile game ad
Which way do you pick? Oh, I don't know. Maybe i'll go this way. They always pick the shittiest way
Yeah, oh I got sword dance
dance
I've heard what this was
But okay. No, I know. I think I know but I don't know that's up and the boss is literally right here
Yeah, I know but I thought there was like a shortcut you open there
Okay, you ready to fight mad soldier? I'm ready to fight. Uh
magma worm three
Get up
My game is lagging so bad
Oh my god, she's raining people on us
um
When do we get to fight her?
They're beating me by making me run out of stamina
all right, this actually we gotta be don't be so cocky here because
They're just dive bombing
ow
Hey, you gotta dodge that
Oh because we have to kill the ones with the
the oro
I'm sorry my bloodlust
Sorry
I love the dive the design of this fight. This is amazing. This should have been the real fight. This should have been the actual fight
Watch out for the explosive
Watch out explosives inbound
Be it right now. Here's where this gets really wacky. There's not a part two to this, right?
I have no idea
I hope not
Okay, when does she land?
No, stop it. Stop it anakin. You're killing younglings
What's going on? I don't know. I was like waiting to see if like
She's not spawning the ones we need to kill
I I think oh no, she broke right?
Yeah, she broke
There's so much shit in the way
Oh my goodness. I hope I hope I don't die here. There's no way I die this there's no way I die
It would be so shameful this book won't stop hitting me
What a shameful boss
I think her strategy is just trying to make you feel bad. I think the one we have to kill is up there
No, all right. We're good
Pray for no face too. Seriously
Thank god, yeah
Got talisman pouch. I have I have like four talismans
Pouches, but only one talisman
Yeah, we need more pouches
No the other way I saw the other way the other way that I like I only how many do you have?
How many do you have stop dude, please stop?
This is not good
I don't know if there's an item back here
Nope, do you want to go visit pidea? Do you like pidea?
Um
What okay, so
Next step
Um, I promise next up
Yeah
I think we go back down that uh that other way and we drop down and then you go into the church again
And you talk to pidea and use a merchant. Uh, I need to upgrade this weapon. I need to actually go do that
Do you have enough souls? You should have enough. So I I definitely do at this point. Yeah
So we need to go back making me stand up. I don't know. I just want to level
Like forcing me to stand up. It's weird come this way. I need to I want to level this up. No come this way
We're already here. It's like two seconds. Okay. All right. All right. I'm here two seconds
I forgot to blink. You haven't blinked in the last hour. It feels like it. Can you do that with your souls?
Oh, that's where all the pots are
Wow
And not pots this time though
Oh my god
Gloves ready up. Nice
sleep tight
baby
What the fuck?
sleep tight
I'm somewhat lost and confused. I thought this was something very different. We we keep going down and then you end up jumping to that thing
Okay, yeah, would he get away from me? I'm so I don't want to jump with these
He's gonna attack me
And keep going. Oh my god. It's the he turned into the boy
I didn't know I didn't care about that one. I didn't give it a voice. Oh shit. I'm getting out of here
Is that the meme?
Has he turned into a titan?
Is that what I would say if I were like funny?
What would someone funny say? You need to apologize for that
No, you need to apologize because that's
I didn't know he could do that
We came all the way this way for like one item
What is that usually?
I think that is
Usually it is um
Okay, i'm i'm i'm gonna die if I go down there so i'm not going to
Okay, let's um, let's I can't teleport because this fucking titan over here
Won't stop. Yeah. Well, there's like a chimera fighting me now like we really shouldn't have done that
I don't know why if all I do should have just left
I really was hoping we could like go to different areas
I think we can I think you can just go somewhere else
I mean whenever we waypoint travel here i'm resetting so we can travel. Yeah
Where do you want to go? Oh you wanted to go upgrade. Yes, I do
That would be nice
Leave aaron in 2021. We need a new meme funeral
Oh, I forgot about that
They haven't even finished that show yet. How can the meme be dead before the show is over?
The problem with the show is they keep doing
final season
attack on titan last season part two
part three aaron's final moments part one
All right. I i'm picking this thing. I'm doing this. We're gonna upgrade this thing all the way
Okay, I need 30. I need one smithing stone five. Do you have one?
No, I have a four and a seven i'm the weird one i want to make sure everyone knows that
We've got a four and then a seven and then like an ancient
dragon one
That's good enough
Okay, what what is yours upgraded to can I like drop your finger on the ground for you?
This is plus five at this point plus four
You're just making up numbers
Okay, you want to go back to ray of lucaria with like a wait. We did that right?
No, we didn't the way to do syrax that's gonna be interesting
But yes, okay. What do I need to upgrade one more time? I gotta have hold on
Should I just put points into intelligence or no?
Level in yeah, I can respect in a minute. Okay, let's go. We need to go to
Which one is it?
it is
Without the map. It's kind of hard to see. All right. Where we going church of the cuckoo or what is uh debate parlor?
It's worth it for the sword
Yeah, i'll be able to do a full respect after this. This is perfect. No amount of intelligence will fix your brain
Actually, I think a lot of intelligence would fix my brain because i'd be smarter stir
Can we get a la la, please? A lot of people are asking for it a la la. Yes a la la
Like the guy from uh better call sol. Yes. I don't think I can do that
I feel like you probably could was it la la or la lo? I think it was la la. I'm dude, dude
You don't think you could do it. I don't know what you're asking for to do an impression
Is that what is that what you were actually asking for because I feel like I went way off
No, I was asking for you to do an impression of love la la
Can you give an example? Yes, like hold on. I just don't want to get hit
Just say la la
No, that's no I
la la
I don't know
What am I a part of right now?
Never mind
Why is it never mind now?
I've I was busy doing something. There's a secret down there. It's not from
Breaking bad
Okay, I thought you guys were linking I was asking you for lines
That this character says
I can't remember
Can you just tell a joke already la la
there
Okay, and what is that?
I don't really even know dude like
there comes
Block it tank it block block it tanking
You can't even see where his body is
And he can't it seems like he can't see us either because he doesn't really actually attack you
No, not really
dude
What the fuck
I can't believe placidusex is the queen of the full moon
I still have not got an estus upgrade
Okay, I sure hope he's aggro'd to you because i'm just rolling
at random intervals
I think he's on you
He is
He does not like you
He just wants to kill you so bad
I have no more healing
This is fucking terrible
There's nothing I could do there
I didn't even realize he was I I don't know you're you're naked
ow
Dude, his ass is so big. I
Okay. Well, at least you didn't have to do with the infinite flicker strike teleportation. I'm inside the wall
ability
There's no way I beat this
Here we go
dodge it
I just did
I don't know that you dodged it or that he spawned in a situation where he couldn't swing at you
I just dodged it right there
Just dodged it right there again
Yeah, I don't know about that
I think this he has a second phase
Just like rinala. I don't think the random enemies
properly trigger second phases
Where is he?
He's coming
Or not. I think he's stuck in the wall
Die come on die die die die die. He fell out of the world. Come on die
He literally fell all the way down
Come on really
Yo, I can't imagine fighting like radon in this room
No
Like what if he actually got to do his meteor?
Where would you go?
dead
Use your magical potion
So what's the plan you want to go for it again? Um, I think if I can
Survive the teleportation phase it could be better
Can you drop golden seeds?
because if you can can I just
I had you
No, you can't
Wait, can you?
Hmm. I think I can
No, I need the what is the flask upgrade one?
sacred tear like
That's what I need
Yeah, I only have one of those
It's actually really bad when you need to drink twice to feel your health. Yeah, it's yeah
I'm drinking like three or four times right now
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Take 10 of these
Put it on your bar
Okay, that negates like a ton of damage like almost all physical damage or something
How do how long they last? I don't know but you have 10 of them
And if we need more I know where they are. It only blocks physical damage, but that's a big deal
All right. So before we go in the store
Fucking snap into a slim gym, right?
Oh my god
I what I rolled
Here it is again. Really? That's unfair. Can you jump over this?
I doubt it. Nope. He's cheesing us this time. We're actually not in a terrible position
Okay, i'm eating another
Where is he? All right. He's in this chandelier
The chandelier he's a bookcase now
Oh shit
No, not no, dude. Come on. What was that? That was horseshit. That actually was stupid
That same that yeah
You're not in a bad spot. You're all right. You know, do you still?
I have no more healing
Better than last time
You can hear him
That's what yeah, it happened to me last time I thought he died that would have been awesome
Hey, it's still winnable. Yeah, it's true
I don't know what he's doing. Uh, no you're dead
No, you're all right
I thought he was doing the thing in the ground
Yeah, I was trying to like look up to see what movie was even doing. I think I waste a lot of time doing it
I think we can do it. Yeah, I think you got like you shouldn't have died that early
Yeah, sorry there bud
But like like I think you shouldn't have died there if you watch the vaude he I got hit by a swipe
And then he started doing the breath immediately directly pinpointing my exact location that I was standing right there and hit me directly
Right before I even iframes to kick down. Yeah, but like I feel like I feel like you shouldn't have died there
I really you shouldn't have died there either. You still did. Yeah. Well, I feel like you should have been there to help
I was died
Dermott's a good point. Hey
Hey, I got a feeling this is the one I had that feeling too
but I don't know we've been married for a while now and
We can um
I'm trying to think is it where's the ball? I'm at the elevator
weird
All right. Let's focus on surviving
and focus on
thriving being
Good. All right. Okay surviving and being good is our strat
Eat your thing. Hey, don't forget who got those by the way
I'm not completely useless
The trade merchant. All right, no more fucking around. Let's go
This is the real one
Stop fucking around. I didn't even see where he swung dude
There's no way to see it
That's unfortunate. We're good. He's doing it again. He is
Who knows what he's doing?
Can't see his body
What was I supposed to do there was nothing I could do there
I've got four flasks this time
What i'll be honest, I don't even know what hit you
Like the attack was over and I did like so much damage
He's just he just fills the whole arena
I mean to be fair
This is one of the last bosses of elden ring
so
Is there anywhere else we can go?
There's tons of places we can go
Is just he just fills the whole arena with that yellow shit. Honestly, you could do this. I think we could
Just the problem is just that yellow flame if you're in the wrong spot you're dead
I think i'm just gonna let him kill me here and we give it one more try one more college try
It's hard to know what is the wrong spot too because he's so big
I think with your like it if you were just here
The extra amount of dps he'd be dead. Yeah, I i'm telling you I got I got completely screwed over twice in a row
Let's go. Let's fucking get this boy
We can do it. Okay
So
It is winnable it's very winnable what if you were good at the game
Um, I don't know
No, i'm not going on another i'm not no i'm not going on. No
We're not no i'm having this we're just i'm just walked off the edge
This time I hope I do not get
double
Double hit by that yellow flame. That's what happened last time
It's like it's it was still a little faint whisper of that shit that hit me twice
No, I don't get hit but at once if you fall on the ground from flame
I don't know if you know, but don't start rolling just like lay on the ground. Thank you. Thank you that
I don't it really is that sarcastic? No, no, no, i'm dead serious
I did I actually did not think about that. That's true
You you get a lot more eye frames if you lay on the ground
A lot of dragons will like put you on the ground if you panic and get up it it hits you instantly again
I you know, i'm not even kidding. I did not know that
Okay, let's go
I'm so not sure no, I I swear I promise I promise
My game lagged like yeah, like okay my game froze
And then I fell on the ground from the fire. Yeah, and it like it kept a buffered roll and I stood up into the fire again
Uh, I probably should just die here shouldn't I?
We were doing really good. We were doing all right
I got through his health pretty quickly
Yeah, you actually do a lot of damage compared to what i've been doing. I mean i don't
I think you could beat him
Does he know about the dodge button? He's trying to get me to growl at you and i'm not gonna do it
He did it he's mad more mad than I am
Stop. Oh, do you not like that? Does that make you like uncomfortable? Can auto hear me is auto uncomfortable?
Are you just like not like?
People
Let's go. Yeah, this one's winnable. Is your monitor turned on? Oh my god
What the fuck?
Your mom was turned on last night
chatter
because of me
I yeah, what the heck stop
rude
All right. So here's the deal
If we don't beat him this time, we're gonna go fight another couple of bosses
Okay
Okay. Yeah, there's like a million catacombs we can go down into there's tons of stuff
We don't have to fight like the last like top three top five last bosses in the whole game
We we we can come back
Eat your slim jim
What the fuck are you doing a game?
Probably fine
Fucking slay queen
I'm gonna slay this queen
Here comes the thingy
Yeah, we can be hitting him during that we got time. I am terrified of that
I'll be honest
Watch out. He's doing that spraying that shit over here
What the fuck are you talking? Okay, stop being a weirdo
Yeah, i've gone through a lot of flasks this place
I prefer phase two at this point. I don't know. We're not we're doing okay. Everything's fine
That was a quick transition though from
What I think he hit the wall?
Oh, you're in trouble. He's doing that stupid shit over there. I'm good
You're in trouble. Um, no, no, i'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine
Playing it safe. Yeah me too
And until he like just hops
Changes his angle and lights the whole room on fire
He can do it
Where the fuck were they?
Maybe all right. Where do you want to go? The guy's in the wall. I can't see where the fuck he is
Do you want to go again? You want to prove the haters wrong?
No, I don't you want to tell them this is a ridiculous boss fight in this tiny supper one more
All right one more and actually I think it might be better. I have like
Somebody's lightning liver. Somebody's got it right. I want to just respec and if we beat him that means I get to respec
Yeah, I just want that that sweet spot
I think i'm gonna go on like uh
Use left trigger. I don't think I I don't have enough intelligence to do it
I don't think I can even do that move
Don't you need it? Hold on. Oh, I don't like what do you mean? You're too dumb to press left trigger. That's true
Do a fully charged heavy
I think it's not gonna do that much more damage
All right, let's go
It'll do extra damage, but I have to hold it much longer. I'll try it. See
Watch out for that fire. You might do it usually does it like right now comes this bullshit
Yeah, i'm like basically out of flasks
already
Jesus
It's just so hard to see what his body's doing
Jesus it's like i'm it's like i'm hitting a mountain
All right
Pull up swings. Pull up. Pull up
He's going to second phase. All right, weird weird eat another one of your uh, uh, uh, you know my goober berries. Yes
spread out too
Okay, we're good. We're good different. Just just have everybody chill out
Oh, no
You gotta be shitting me. I dodged right through it. This was the one
Yeah
What that was weird? I don't know what just happened, but he's over here
Bro, what?
Are you doing over here man?
What?
Dude, you got so much surface area here. Look at this. So he's gonna pick the same three spots
I'm so lucky that didn't hit me. All right, here comes the area of back bullshit
Where'd he go?
He's gonna drop it on me
I hope where did he go?
Oh, he's teleporting
Yeah, the claw into the flame
What the fuck is he doing right now, man? He's doing laser beam. He hit him
Fucking clown box
I
I thought you would have had him there too if that didn't hit you but like who can tell what?
Oh, you need to rest at the bonfire. I'm still in the fight
What that was so unfair?
What happened? What did he just what did he do?
What did he just?
Happened
Uh, what happened? He's not playing fair
He's a weapon you have stats for
Uh, I had it a store currently owns it. He
The store has it in his inventory
The issue is not the damage you're doing more damage than me
the issue is
Sometimes uses flame attacks. So what why did I then you die? Okay, so he did a flame attack
And then it was over and then I died. Was that the laser?
That's the one where he goes super psycho mode and does lasers in like 400 million directions. Oh my god
We both got yeah
Oh, can we do a warming stone?
Somebody said two hand the shield. That's not a bad idea. That might actually work
I wonder no don't potion why because we can put a warming stone down before we go in
All right, we can just chill out we can talk about
I can't I I thought he was dead too. I thought his move was over
I don't even know what I got hit by don't go in he was near a pillar his laser explodes on contact with ground
You stood near his head
Which was near the pillar and the
The laser beam exploded the pillar. Oh, that's so sad
That's so sad
Shots four and five clearly missed
I'm gonna drop a warming stone during like the phase transition as well
I didn't mean to do that. I'm just so shooken up right now
Sorry, we'll get a writer
You gotta seriously dude
I'm dead
I got trapped
I got trapped. He did it twice in the same area
I need you to focus up, dude
The guild needs this
Okay, you have no idea how hard I was just holding it not just getting wicked pissed
Okay, we're good. I'm so glad you said that because that was really funny and it just like
The fact that the guild needs me right now is that's so funny I was about to be like the fuck do you know
You're gonna do like a noise like that. No one's gonna know what it means. But like you would know
Okay, it's a combination of being in the right place
Not being too greedy
Uh getting good rng on the moves. I mean the area is tiny. There's not a whole lot of wiggle room
I forget how you even double hand your your shield on your offhand
Uh, I can but uh, I was just told that that does not help
Oh, okay
From what I was told could be wrong. Let's try it again
I'm only gonna use the clam powder the clam chowder in the second phase
I used all mine
Oh, I felt like six
Really?
Yeah
That's the claw fire
And
There's nowhere to go
No
No, no
Nice nice. He's staggered. Ooh
All right, dropping a warming stone in the center. Yep. He's going up easy easy careful
All right smelling warming stone in the center. I had no idea where he was. He says all right fire incoming
you
Can't be serious. All right. It's all right. Sorry you got he killed me instantly with the laser
Yeah, I like saw you die in one shot. You got it. You got it. Come on for the guild. Where the fuck is he?
Okay, I couldn't even hit him
I thought he was doing the fire after the swings. I started trying to run. I know there was like a return swing
Okay, so the lightning once he's in when he's in phase two do not be in front of him for any reason
He does that laser light show and it instantly kills you
That's what killed you the other time and it goes on for a really long time
That's unfortunate. I'm out of warming stones, too. I think they helped a lot. I don't know if you have any
Uh, let me check. I don't think I do though. We could that was so close. I think we can do it warming stones
I don't think I have any
No, I don't think so
I might have I mean buff on
Shit, I don't know how I would check we could take rune arcs. Couldn't we I do have a debuff on?
Fuck I had a reduced attack debuff
Apparently the warming stones heal the bots. Oh do they?
That's so funny
Oh, all right. I mean that was that was pretty good. That was pretty good. This is tough. This is not easy
This is tricky
Your weapon is a stagger do jump attacks
I mean I do it just it's hard to get in there, but I I do
Oh my god. Okay. I am
I want to see if we can I forget if there's a shortcut over here because I need to rest the bonfire get rid of my
debuff
What you have a debuff right now or no, you didn't yeah
I think during that fight I had a reduced attack debuff the whole time really
Well, let's just let's do this. Let's go up and take care of this shit
What is going on?
Because of the weird way that like last time I died and you had to reset it and then I resp I don't know
Uh, what's gonna happen or how long I had it. Let's turn the stupid ball off
Well, we can just do this shortcut for now on
I'm getting rid of that ball. Well, I'm saying the shortcut ignores the ball. Oh, never mind. There's a giant dog up here
I don't care about that anymore
I'm gonna go rest. I'll be back
Shortcut is literally going to be worse. Apparently why?
Uh, it seems a lot better because of the random enemies that are there
They're not like super threatening the way they normally are. Where did you go all the way back? Yeah, I rested
It's usually worse
Yeah, because they usually spam like homing magic at you. But right now it's like
Undead that are just like kind of looking at me. I just ran right by everyone. There's no problem
It's way easier
Uh, and then we then we don't need to deal with the ball. Let me actually
I I have six flasks. I need to get my field back up
Okay, I should
Man, I forgot but I should take my mana flask off
Because i'm not really casting mat. Jesus. Fuck that was longer ranged. I thought i'm just I don't I'm just going
I don't even care. I'm just gonna go back
I could beat this boss by myself
Are you you respawned at the bonfire, right?
I'm i'm killing myself and i'm gonna i'm gonna come back with you
So that I can reset my flask like one extra flask would help a lot. Yeah
um
We've gotten him two or three times down to like
less than five percent
When are you gonna play the great ace attorney games?
My uncle doesn't care because he doesn't know who you are, but I do
Uh, what does your uncle have to do with any of that? That's
I don't I don't expect your uncle to know who I am. I'll play it
Yeah, but he's gonna play jade cocoon first
I actually need to find that game
Are you guys just hoping that the second boss is gonna be easier when you kill this one?
I don't think there is one
There wasn't a phase two for rayo lucario
Would it be a phase two for this? Well, I mean that boss doesn't usually have phase two the base boss
But I still don't do like it doesn't matter. We're gonna win right now. I don't want to hear anyone say
It does nothing matters. We're about to win right now. So like doesn't even matter what you're saying, you know, that's a good point
Because we are the hey bod watchers. This is the one skip to here
Because it does just a bad start like I just got screwed
Again again just really poor really just bad fucking start overall bad
It was just a bad start overall. It was a bad start overall. I could feel it the second we walked through the door
Okay
The vibe was off. It was the vibe was so wrong. It was off completely
It's just like I would I would do a move and he would time it perfectly to put something on the ground that
You know what? I mean? It was just the vibe was just the vibes were off on that
The fight always starts off three lightnings
Be aware be aware. I know but the just do the vibe
I'm not disagreeing with you. The vibe was off dude
If I just had like glint stone omega kamehameha and then I could fucking kamehameha him and then hit the gritty
Hit the gritty
Yeah
Okay, come on. He doesn't know we can do it
We have been playing for eight hours. I mean that doesn't have it might be hitting game or fatigue. It's possible
Yeah for like old people
Well, I I we could be hitting game or fatigue
For old people
You didn't even eat
Do I need to yeah
No fasting it keeps your mind present like i'm i'm on the hunt for some food and that food is pasadousis axes
What is this character's name?
Me strong. No, no, no the boss we're fighting get it right and spell it correctly and i'll give you 100 dollars
pass
Placid do sex. Okay. Now now now do it for me do what for you? I don't know either
It's like placid oxics
I think I could have done it if we took a moment, but I want to fucking fight this thing
Can you be like focused you like dodge a little red lightning that's about to come down?
Not take any like greed swings and like die in the first fucking phase. I didn't
You show me what your made up for the guild
You got double hit by the fire guy, but I did I didn't know but you don't understand. I didn't jump
I didn't get up. I did what you said
Seems like I only got hit once
What even just I hit my head on the fucking treasure box. I'm just relaxed
guild needs you
Fucking only fighter that's online at this time
You don't understand. I got so screwed
I mean like just run away
If you're worried you're gonna get hit you can also always like you you actually can't go anywhere when he does that. Oh my god
Did I do it?
Yeah
I didn't
I thought you're gonna yell at me and say don't do it
So I tried to predict I was on the ground the whole time. I tried. No, no, we're good. We're good. Everything's fine
We're good. We did a lot of damage
Everyone's screaming at me. You don't understand the last few times. It's like we're good
Oh dodged
like a mouse
Okay focus
You gotta focus
That was so stupid
Bringing it back
You can't even see when the rocks come out. It's such what's manure
Oh my i'm just getting infinite combo
beam
It's a good thing. I'd use three flasks for that
Okay, it's getting close to beam health like don't don't get beamed. I'm gonna try as hard as I can to not get beamed
Do we even know do we even know?
Do we even know
What lies beyond in the infinite void?
He's beaming into the wall. Now's our opportunity
That was such a huge rng player right there. Come on. Come on. Come on. Kill him. Kill him. Come on like a boss, man
Like a fucking boss
Oh, thank all right. No phase two. No phase two. No phase two
Oh, I skipped I don't
All right, we got it we got it we got it
Sucks it's the easiest boss of the fucking whole game. Just relax. Just take your time. Look at that damage. Look at that
Stop don't laugh. Don't laugh
What you're gonna get me going don't
Are you i'm alive stay alive stay alive, dude, if you have to just warming stone back there do it
I don't have any I was my low hp every once in a while
I'm gonna hit one time and then run away to take out girl fucker
That one didn't count
Oh, this weapon is fucking slow as shit
With my sword alone. I was having a hard time getting a single hit in well that was um, that was interesting
This is easy like a boss
Oh, I feel like I could have done that too. It's just it's been so long since seeing that second phase
I got fucking one shot by the bow
That thing is always so hard for me to dodge like in the beginning of radon's fight
And he's like i'm gonna shoot one really slow missile at you across the map
I always miss time it the bow my weakness you gotta go forward. You gotta dodge forward
Only go forward. So you like make sense only dodge forward if you dodge back left or right you'll get hit by it every time
especially
okay, so um
Respawn and then go up the shortcut. I don't know why we went ball away. I don't know
I think I didn't remove my buff either. I don't know if I have one nice bald spot where
Where shouldn't have one because we both like did actual real dying. So I have a question is that always going to be uh,
Yeah
Do I have grease my check you still i'm gonna use grease
But uh, actually chat i'm using an intellect sword and it scales with arcane magic and you can't put grease on magic swords
Your vibes are off bro. When's the last time you guys hit the no. No, no someone's saying your vibes are off man
When was the last time you hit the splinky? You know, that's true. I feel better. I feel a lot better
We crushed placid axe
Flaccid man, I feel actually I feel pretty good now. What's your what's that thing's weapon art that you said you can't use
I think it's a big like earthquake. It's a big like purple earthquake
All right. Let's try it again
All right vibes are better. I feel pretty good vibes have been returned
Yo, we're just chilling
We are super
duper gamers
Just vibing out
I hurt a little bit
And no stamp you've just a bad start just a bad. No, it really was though. Like I was fine
It's just I ran out of fucking stamina and then he hit me like with his elbow
Bro hit me with his fucking elbow. Like I was fine
wrong vibe
Like I don't know. He he like he turned
and
Can we get a priest for the rez crouch into r1?
What the hell is this move?
What is this weird ass move?
Yeah, that's what cheaters use
It's so good
All right for a second. I thought this was you they they did nerf it at some point
so I don't uh the door this this fucking asshole piece of
Scum was blocking the door. I couldn't go through
The vibe was off. Make sure you rest the debuff
The vibes are fine. It's just just blocking the door
Peter griffin here. I wish you luck with the boss fight
Thanks peter
you forgot um
Family guy is sponsored in pot by
That means you're not the real peter griffin. That's how I know
All right. I'm gonna i'm gonna let's give this one more try and then
We're double bossing and I have like a plus five weapon that I can't even equip correctly
It's plus four
We are double bossing right now
That's true
Vibe check vibe check don't get locked in the corner. Be careful. Hold on. Take your time run away from the lightning
I'm not quite sure about that vibe here right now. Let me see give me a minute
Like in you're like in the fight vibes are on
Already vibes are off
Already i'm getting out of the corner
No
There's nowhere to go. You just die
Vibes were off that one. All right, if you get hit by that fire, you just die. I got hit by it
How come I got up slower than you?
The vibes were fucking terrible
kill me
I walked into it
Dude, but I can't even see what this motherfucker is doing for a move. It's like
That's been this entire fight. All right
Relax relax relax
And vibes is just killing me right?
kill me
How are you alive and you're trying to die?
I was trying a bit. I thought it was funny
I just like shook. I just shook my whole room
All right. I am doing a veto
Vibe stamp right now
Can we please do one where you don't die in like the first 10 seconds? No, the vibes are off
Okay, I legitimately think we have it if you can just like just here's what we're gonna do. Here's the strat
We're gonna run in we're gonna go up for the first 20 seconds of the boss fight
I don't want you to hit hit the boss more than one time and then just like walk away
Yeah, but I got the fucking strike twice in a row. Yeah, like do like a jump attack. Did I like shrink?
Why is this like so huge?
I'm gonna try that strategy the crouch into swing
See if it works
Is that the the heavy poke?
Yeah, like this thing
I wonder if it's behind you behind you behind you behind you he's dead. Yeah first playthrough. No spoilers, please never seen this boss
What turning animation did like a full s this worth of damage?
Okay, here we go
What the fuck is that bullshit?
I I was like so bright. Oh, wow. What a clean dodge. Oh totally boom. You're dead
Like a fucking hour later
We're gonna beat this whole thing right now watch
Not even a fucking scratch. I'm fine
Okay
That this is uh, this is way too hard for what we have right now. Let's go
I think it'll be really funny. Let's like do like a catacombs
We're gonna get to the end boss and it's gonna be like so just a guy named like charles
And we could feel good about that. I need you to rest. I'm like locked in the boss room
I need to get enough intelligence to use this weapon correctly or take the finger out of your inventory
I can't do that for you. I need to do it. I need you to do that. I need to take my finger out of your
You know, I need that it's a plus seven
Yeah
Yeah, it is it is it is like okay, like a 30 probably damage increase definitely know what?
um
So let's go to it. Let's go to one of the catacombs. Where's a good one something quick something easy
I forget where they are. I mean probably go to the artist shack and there's one around there
I forget exactly where the starting I think there is one like down here like over here. Hey, can you freak out?
No, I could also just go to that urn tree
Like like anywhere we can we can go anywhere and do anything this whole wide open world is open to us
Somebody said why do you get redder every time you die? I wonder why that is
Why would somebody get red? I just keep getting redder apparently
I know you're changing the hue on your camera
Okay, we're gonna relax going up let's just go do a dungeon go clear a boss go get me
You know another few smithing stones and all that stuff and we'll be good to go
Okay, where exactly?
I
I think there's one there's one here right like in the middle of the lake or like at the end of the lake
There's one here. Uh
Come this way
And I also down there is the the first boater
Mariner I think is relic right here. I haven't been looking at the mod chat at all. I'm sorry
I don't know. Is there anything important in here?
Lol. Yeah, we realized
I thought I did
Uh, did you go down?
Yeah, this is the pat. No, there's like a big bear in this cave. Usually
Smith and stone seven. I could probably actually upgrade my weapon quite a bit too
Like already with the stuff that I have
I just need ruins and I just need
another somber stone
I wish I could
this whole thing
Just got so twisted up
Because I put 30 points in strength because I had a fucking meltdown
I was
So excited to get that and I just used it all and it was just it was really fun. It was really exciting
I mean
It was very exciting
A lot of people would have done the same
Right now this is up to kayla dude. I'm so lost. I forget all the beginning like many areas
Um there we could also go back to castle more and fight that boss. We could probably kill it easily now
Come over here
It was the the deer. Where are you?
Uh, are you?
And there's some water village. There's a place to go down. I think this is just a boss right in here
Just uh, oh, yeah, this is where the mariner would be and then I think there also is a basement
There's a there's the gargoyle out here. I wish we could like ping
You're like I I see him. Okay, let's go get him by the gargoyle. All right
Let's go for it. It's dangerous. Get out of here tibia kindred
Uh, oh, uh, we have a bird
Oh my god, dude
Let's hear this fucking giant crow
I'm gonna pull the crow back here. He just got in the bus
You don't you dare kill me. Don't you dare kill me?
Okay, he's dead
Am I playing co-op right now? I had dude one of those giant crows came over
I that would have been the end of this whole run if I didn't kill that
Wow, he he led the target
Why can't we just kill him?
Okay
Epic, okay
Now let's go down and see what's in there. Where is it over here? Right?
I forget. I am for random items. Yeah
I think it's over here
On the other side, I think you forgot already
Yeah, I don't mean like this whole place. Look, I'm right here identical. The whole thing looks identical
Why you'd really diss the elden ring art team like that?
And it's like a little like a sugar cube on the ground to go in you thought it was coming
Getting cookbooks
Yeah, that was kind of not worth it
Well, it was content complete it progress
I didn't want to even kill that deer, but I had to
Let's go all the way down castle moore
Yeah, I need a sacred tier yesterday. I really do that would be like the number one
Best thing did you uh teleport castle mooring, right?
Um beside the rampart goal all the way at the bottom
Oh, right, right, right
um
Yeah, people thought I was gonna growl. That's why I did them. I'm gonna growl
Do you like beans and hot dogs? Yeah, that sounds amazing, dude that
It actually is really good
Okay, I haven't had one in a while. I think I got some some
Something like that. This is gonna kill me. Did you ever get that lasagna?
Uh, you're gonna get a lasagna earlier. No, no, no
No beans and hot dogs is great
Perfect. All right. We should definitely be able to do this now
Oh, come on. Really?
You're being quinge
Don't do it. Oh, he respawns here
Or not
Uh-oh
Uh, is that actual I think he's gonna actual spawn. Is he gonna suck them all up or what?
No
All right. He sucked them all up. Do they respawn? I don't think so, right?
He might have a move that spawns them
Yeah, they spawned again
I thought you died right there as I go shit. Oh my goodness. Where's the edge?
What does he will he stop doing this move?
Oh my god, it's hurting us
Yeah, it also sucks you
All right, that's it
What we didn't kill?
What is he doing?
Okay, we're good
Memory stone and a golden seed. I got a sacred tear. Thank goodness jealous. I'm jealous
Hey, i'm leaving the stream open because i'm going to bed, but please don't scream or growl or anything
I'm not gonna I was just earlier. I was just joking around about it
Okay, that's good
Can we go back to um
Blacksmith so I can upgrade because I think I need do I have the amount of stones I need?
You were missing a five
Yeah
No, I need a five still
I wonder if anybody sells them
Left side of this island. We haven't even gotten to I know there's a bunch of
Catacombs urd tree and all the shit out there. It's just always annoying because there's like one bridge
But we can go up to
Castlemore and rampart and go west
um
I'm
We also haven't we haven't done any of the urd trees. Yeah, that's what I mean
Yeah, so there's a lot of shit we haven't done
Instead we're in fucking ray lucario fighting placidusax. Let's do the urd tree over here. Let's see what you said
And then are you how are you feeling are you all right? I feel like I should probably honestly I was up
Until five a.m. Last night. So like i'm i'm a little bit goofed
um
I do I do have to however wake up and go to the gym tomorrow
But like who cares?
Am I right?
I mean am I right we can always just like I don't take a day take a day or two and come back on like monday
Or it's a tuesday or something
And I thought we're gonna play tomorrow
Yeah, but if it's like you're up too late and you want to go to the gym and stuff
I like have to go early no matter what. Oh, it's not it's not a it's not a whole thing. Okay
I rescheduled the gymming already
Uh, I definitely want to eat food though
So whatever like a boss or two. Yeah, I don't know set like a milestone and then we'll stop and we can play tomorrow
Let's fight a boss
get some
You know ruins
Because it has been eight and a half hours and i'm hungry. This is uh
The demi god, I don't know if you count that is that does this count? Yeah
this counts
What time do you want to start tomorrow?
What is this counts?
Um, are you sure it's kind of like five bosses in here
No, man
Actually, I guess because bosses can I was thinking that it would be an actual a boss but it doesn't necessarily have to be a boss
All right, the the it's the bear. Yeah, the rune bear is a boss shit down
Is it I think the rune bear is technically a boss, right?
I didn't think so
That's i'm a human. I'm playing with you. I was trying to hit you
Okay, what's the deal?
It's a little weirdo following you
pops barrier
Thanks, pop
This one doesn't count germa
All right, fine. There's not even a fog gate
It's patchwork a boss
Does that count?
I mean
Now isn't there a way to go down here though?
Yeah, no, there's like a chest but it's in a weird like hidden spot
There's actually wait, hold on
There's like we're surrounded by caves right now there's like a lot we can do
not
There's a cave up here
time zones, uh pacific
That's probably really late for a lot of you guys
I was back down probably really late for you. What time is it for you red? It's late for you, isn't it? Um
Holy shit, it's late. That's what i'm saying. That's what i've been trying to say dude
You won't just pull the plug now and just come back. No, there's one there's a cave around here, dude
I know it
You're gonna miss your gym appointment
I'm not I was gonna be up late anyway
Okay
When you get up really groggy tomorrow and you don't get like a good pump on
You're gonna remember that's fine. I wasn't gonna get a good one anyway
Why not? I don't know. Uh, I gotta fight a boss. I have to fight a boss dude
Where the hell are the caves around here?
I mean, it's hard to look at the map because we can't let's let's jump up the the air beam the air pilot
Jump up jump
Okay across the bridge
right
No other way
Wait, yeah across the bridge across the bridge again
Sir, i'm hungry
Shush. I know where i'm going. I know where I am now. We're right next to one somebody said
Do you really know where you're going? I know where i'm going. I'm not just trolling you
Get the church waypoint and then you go like down the hill and there's a swampy ass
Oh my god, I got another sacred tier
That's huge
I got a kukri
My flask actually now will be pretty good. I think
It's been a little while. That's cool. I should hold on. Can I level up 13? Hold on
13 what? Yeah
What the hell are you asking me?
What is i'm asking you on a date to go to this fucking like we have to it's late
But I have we have to kill a boss first
Like do an encounter we have to do an encounter. Let's go straight up to the urn tree
Okay
That was the goal from the beginning
Yeah, well, uh, we'll be back tomorrow
So I did I did you say a time tomorrow? I don't remember. Was it same time or later?
I'll i'll be around like all morning
So you want to start early message me?
Uh, no, I mean like same time you said like one year time
Hey, look what boss it is
That's pretty fitting get to fight another one. What is the odds of this actually happening?
What is the odds of this shit?
What's this weird seed?
another magma worm
Yeah, i'm just gonna stay on the horse horse. Yeah
Okay, this one does a super spin this one actually has a lot of health
What this motherfucker jumps
Yeah, where is this guy normally found?
Yo dorix. I've never heard of this guy
Theodorix
Is he the one that's all the way in the ice area all the way in that one corner?
He's in the volcano
So I can't imagine the volcano. Oh spinning around like that. I think he is in the volcano
I haven't been able to get over near him
He also has phase two
Done still like a fucking monster hunter like we're just like hunt the same monster all stream
Oh, I come on dude, like i'm so close to my like dragon plate armor. We're doing like one more magma worm
All right. Nice
Only 3,600 but whatever
Letter to patches and ronin's armor
Okay, let's teleport back to the church. I want to see one thing and then it's done
the church
Yeah, that we just came from church of pilgrimage right above us
All right
so we'll do
What one o'clock two two o'clock tomorrow pacific?
One or two i'll be around just message me
I don't know if you want to make like a solid schedule so people know but like well
We don't we're not gonna we're not gonna run into the technical bullshit. So let's start at one
Okay, I will be back probably by
Let me think i'll be back two hours before that. That's fine
Yeah, I um
Yeah, we started one that we can it won't be too late if we go a long time
Cool
I forgot how you use the cookbooks was the thing I wanted to look at
I thought you did that at I think I think you just have them now
If you because it's crafting shit
So we never got the crafting thing to do any crafting. Oh, yeah, you need an item to craft. Yeah
Okay. Well, yeah, because I think the crafting things that you craft are also randomized
You would like spend a whole bunch of weird stuff to get weird thing and i've got a lot of weird stuff
Anyway, yeah, that was good. Good fun. Good night. I think we'll I mean, I don't know if we'll beat it tomorrow
But I think we'll probably get the least past very lucaria and it threw um, we made some pretty good progress
Look at we look at how long look at this. We did pretty good. I banish you
Yeah, we'll start at one
The hardest part is always an elden ring like gearing up in the beginning. Well, I mean randomizer doesn't make it any easier
Yeah, I mean there's like the tricks you could do where you go kill the giant dragon and you know
Wow, I got all those souls and everyone like claps. Yeah, I'd rather that i'd rather just suck
absolute asshole at the game and
Mess up two or three builds in a row and I think it's more fun that way. That's what i'm saying
Anyway, i'll see you i'll see you tomorrow. See you tomorrow. Bye stir. Bye and
Goodbye to all of you kind of a meaty one today. I don't know if we're gonna do
A I can't tell you this is gonna be a nine-hour stream tomorrow, but we'll play it
We'll go for a little while as long as we can. Thanks for watching everybody. We'll see you tomorrow
I'm very very hungry and i'm very tired. I'm kind of kind of uh
Zonked out right now, but that was a lot of fun. I was scared that it wasn't gonna work that well
But it actually works very very well. Appreciate you hanging out very very late for a lot of you. I am going to
Eat food and go right to bed
All right
First order of business tomorrow when the stream starts is I have to do I need to find a smithing stone five
And I gotta put points into intelligence. That's what we're doing. You needed a typing test. Oh, that's right
I'll bring it up tomorrow to him. Elden Ring is always a blast even though it's kind of a frustrating mess sometimes
But it's always fun
There was two or three potential growl attempts and I stopped them and you saw my face
I looked over and I put a stop to it. Nah, I'll uh, i'll see you tomorrow. Good night everybody. Take care of yourselves drink a
I can't even talk. It's just a glass of water. Call your mother. You know the deal. See you guys later