Uh, this is, uh, this is the game. It's not quite ready to start yet. Um, this is a game where you play, you run an item store, and you have to sell and trade products, and over the course of that time try to make as much money as possible to, um, I have no idea what this is.
I was told that this is a fun game. I can't skip this. Why can I no longer skip this?
Oh, hi, there we go. Hey everybody! Uh, hold on, I'm not ready yet. Just pretend I wasn't here. Okay, that's better. I actually did not mean to show you that, but I did.
Accident? No, I don't- why is this popping up? This is all- my stream deck is so wrong right now.
I better not fuck around with this, because if I turn the camera on, it's gonna be embarrassing. So, I'm just gonna do it by hand, manually.
Alright. Yeah, we're gonna play, uh, Recettear, and Item Shops Tales is something that people thought I would like.
It's about trading stocks, and, um, going on adventures with your friends, and you know how I love the markets.
Did I say it? Wait a minute, did I say it? What are you linking me? What is this?
What the fuck is this?
What- what is this? That's a real ad. No, it's not. Somebody- one of you, like, meme aficionados doctored that shit. That's real.
Let me say it again, hold on. I'm- no, stop- this is so loud! Where is it? Why do I have a porn ad?
Somebody link it.
What is this implying? Is this implying that I'm chatting with this girl, or is she watching me?
Am I the porn, or are they the porn? I don't understand. Why this clip? Where did you get this gift from?
I'm the chatter? Turn this off.
I gotta- hold on, this is important. Why? Where did you find this?
Acting like he doesn't know.
What?
Alright, well that's fucking weird. I don't know what webs- don't go to this website, because they're probably just gonna, like, take your data.
I would be careful of that, like, data bait, so I don't know what that is. I don't endorse that website. I'm not part of that website.
Make sure you don't have your credit card on a notepad on your computer if you click on that link, okay?
Anyways, that's fucking odd, but- and of all the things, that's like- why wouldn't you take- I'm laughing!
I'm, like, laughing at that person. You don't, like, laugh at porn. You don't know- what? Is it porn, or is it just, like, a chat with me thing?
What do you mean you don't? That's so fucking funny.
What do I even do about that, though? That's the thing, right?
What the fuck am I supposed to do about that? Go get a lawyer?
Oh, hey, yes, this is Dick and Dick Associates. Hey, yeah, it's me, German985. Just put a call in. Somebody's using my face in a porn ad.
Do you know what company it is? I have no idea. They might be overseas.
Do you have any idea who it is?
No, I have absolutely no clue. Somebody linked it to me in chat.
Okay, um, you know, you're probably better off just- I gotta take another call.
You wanna sue him? Yeah!
Give me the person's name, where they're located, and what the business or country is located in.
Can't give you any of that. They're using my likeness to sell chatting software.
Unbelievable. It's me, like, of all the videos to pull.
Why wouldn't you pull one of me talking as if I was talking to you guys?
You know, like we sit here with the face cam on and I just talk?
Why would you take the one of me laughing at a baby running into a wall over and over again?
I've talked to the camera like a thousand times before.
I don't- whatever. We sit here.
An item shop's tail. This is what we're doing today.
Hope you had a good Fourth of July. Those of you that celebrated.
We don't need to hear the theme song again.
Alright, so this should be fun. It's a game about buying stocks.
I'm like stuck on repeat right now.
New game. Here we go. Can I skip all this?
Are you guys gonna be mad if I skip the whole thing?
Oh, for the love of- she's still asleep. No. No, yes. Don't skip it. Skip it.
Why is this Sesame Street music?
Alright, I- I'm gonna just- we're gonna do it normally.
I'm not gonna skip. That was a pretty good fucking fat cloud.
Does she really not understand how important today is?
I'm in bed? Why am I under the covers like that?
Merple. Can't eat another bite. That's my name. My name is Resetti.
Resiti. Is it Reset?
But I can always find room for yummy candy.
Mimble-werble.
I've heard of like, mmm, or like, er, or, uh, Mimble-werble.
Oh, I'm so tired this morning. Mimble-werble.
Wake up, please. Is that me?
Whoa, whoa, what is it?
Oh, Tier. Good- good morning.
We do not have time for good morning, Resetti.
Are you planning on spending the rest of your life dreaming of sweets?
Today is the day we set for opening the store. I'm so- I'm way too excited for this.
Uh, we did? Oh, yeah, we did.
Merde.
Zero F all the-
Listen, go wash your face and make yourself presentable.
And then join me downstairs in the storefront.
Okay, I'll be right down.
Hey, sorry, I kept you waiting.
Okay, Tier, let's open the shop right now.
Capitalism ho.
Patience, Resetti. It is a virtue you will need.
We need to take care of a few matters before we open officially.
Everybody settle down for a second, because this game is like actually fun, I've heard.
Well, I somehow doubt that a store without anything to sell is going to attract all that much business.
Oh. Oh, yeah, we don't have anything to sell.
So, what do we do?
To start with, we need to establish a stock of items for the store.
If we have nothing to sell, we cannot claim to be much of a shop.
That's true. Hmm, so where should we go to get stocked up?
Let's go get like, liquor.
The best way, I think, would be to visit either the town market or the merchant's guild.
We need to give our regards to the head of the guild regardless.
So that should probably be our first stop.
Constant capitalism.
Oh, that's the place to run by that old guy, right?
We got an old guy. Can't let you do the old guy voice.
You know it's coming. I can't wait to do it.
The guild operates as a wholesaler for local merchants.
So if we stop by, we can purchase an initial stock.
It would not hurt Grover.
Give up, give our polite regards to the guild chief either.
Especially since the guild is the organization that allows us to operate here in the first place.
Why does everybody have a guild?
Monster Ranch here, we gotta, there's a guild.
The rest of the tier, guild.
Who cares about the guild?
Okay, got it. Then let's go right now.
Hold on, that person's like, why is that person floating off the ground?
When you want to leave the shop, head to the front door currently located in the upper right hand corner of the store.
But I wanted to leave through the window like an action hero.
To infinity.
And beyond. They didn't want to get in trouble for that apparently.
Why?
Brassetti!
Okay, fine.
Oh, it's because it actually is, it's like a fairy or something.
Alright, so here's my store.
So we have to leave.
You didn't think there was going to be any action in this game.
You didn't think there was going to be any fucking running T-poses in this game, did you?
I know it's the easiest thing I could, alright, there's a lot to do here.
Alright, so we need to go to the merchant's guild.
This action will not take any time.
We have 1,000 picks.
Pictures of what?
Here comes the old guy.
A girl and a fairy, you two, yes, you're Brassetti and that Lone Shark.
I get to do an old person voice. I get to do an old man voice.
Well, that is not, well, an incorrect assessment.
Could I ask that you refrain from calling me Lone Shark?
That's right, mister.
She and I are partners, don't be mean.
Forgive me, forgive me, partners it is.
So, how are the preparations for running that shop coming along?
Quite well, thank you.
In fact, we plan on opening today, so we stopped by in order to show our gratitude for your help.
Very good, you two know what you want.
If you have any problems, let me know, I'll be glad to help.
We appreciate your kindness, thank you.
I wish you a starting monster.
He'll grow up to be big and strong.
We appreciate your kindness, thank you, bye.
Not a problem at all, what are we going to buy from here?
So you came straight here to pick up some merchandise, right?
Well, up to the counter then, let's get you two sorted.
Are those two cigars on him? What is that?
He's got two cigar holders?
What's on his chest there?
Are those clothespins? I'm not sure what those are.
Those are pens, those are fat fucking pens.
Those are extra large Sharpies.
Those are not pens.
Is that first time?
Alright, I gotta pay attention to this.
Our funds are limited, so do not go completely overboard.
I recommend purchasing no more than ten items.
Buy, sell, talk.
Alright, so we need to stock up.
A worn out dented chipped sword.
Still better than going into the wild bare handed though.
140.
A standard lightweight long sword.
Perfect for novices learning the art of swordplay.
It's 840 bucks.
Alright, I just gotta...
Oh shit, there's more.
We have one item.
I didn't know there was more bars.
Hold on, how much are these?
I recommend ten items.
Oh.
Why can't I just lie about what the sword is?
That's how capitalism works.
I'm just gonna make up a story about why this thing is worth so much money.
Rusty dagger.
I can't even...
We can have two items. Leather gloves.
Wait, hold on, clothes.
Can I sell anything?
Sell it back to him?
Hey, we're running our item store here.
360.
This guy probably thinks we're like fucking morons.
What is the guild? What can I do here?
About merchant levels.
Merchant level is, well, your ability as a merchant.
As it goes up, you'll figure out how to redecorate or even expand your store.
Heck, you might even be able to convince me to let you have a look at some of our more premium items.
So they got drugs behind the counter.
You don't put your hands up and say premium with your fingers like that.
Unless it's something fucking illegal.
So...
How do you raise your level? Simple. Buy, sell, trade.
This is an art and you learn by doing.
If there's anything you don't know, just ask.
Okay.
Let's go sell it.
Let's go sell that sword.
Aw, but unknown items.
Now if you go dungeon diving, you'll find a lot of stuff which you won't be able to identify at first.
In particular, I'll bet my hat, you'll find a lot of what are commonly called mystery ingredients by the adventurers.
You can go dungeon diving.
At first you'll probably be tearing your hair out over all the junk you keep finding in those places.
But as your merchant level goes up, you'll be able to sort out the stuff you find and pick the best materials and whatnot from the lot.
Oh, and if you manage to get out of these death traps safely, you'll have time to identify everything safely.
That means you won't know what you're carrying till you leave.
Huh, that's interesting.
Alright, well let's go. Let's get out of here.
I got my merchandise.
Right then, will that be all?
Yep, this is perfect.
We shall return when our stocks run low again.
Haha, I'm looking forward to it.
Here, a little something extra as a start-up gift.
Bread from the ground.
Half of a donut. Walnut bread, thanks a bunch.
Alright little lady, give them your all.
Capitalism, ho.
Well, Adam Sandler would be proud of us at any rate.
Alright, we're gonna go back to recetteer.
Very well, it's time to give you a crash course on the basics of running an item shop.
I am so excited and I don't know why.
I was supposed to just relax today.
Okay, what do I do first?
First, we need to put some items on display.
We do not have our goods out for people to see.
We can hardly expect the customers to buy them after all.
Just need to get near these counters.
Just so, once you know where you wish to place something,
choose what you wish to place in that spot by pressing the primary button.
Primary button?
You will understand when you try it, trust me.
Now remember, what you place will affect how people perceive the store.
So think carefully before you place something.
Okay, why not line up what we purchased on one of the counters?
Okay, so I have longsword and clothes.
Longsword has to be right here.
Base price, 1200 bucks.
That's the item that people are gonna be coming in.
And that's the one that lags your game.
Alright, then how about maybe in the back wall here?
Do it by the window.
No, I don't want to sell the bread.
I'm already getting talked to.
May I speak with you a moment?
What is it? What?
Those counters by the window, items you place there are visible to anyone passing by on the street.
As such, putting eye-catching items, the sort of thing that makes you think,
I want to buy this more than anything, on those counters is a core principle of running a shop.
In a very real way, those counters are the face of the shop.
And what is placed there greatly affects interest in our business.
So choose what to place there very, very carefully.
Wow, I never thought about like that before.
Hokkai, I'll be careful.
So then, how do I pick it up?
I'm gonna put, oh, she likes the sword.
Look, you can use that sword to cut that bread.
I got it up here.
I'll put the clothes over here.
This is a window.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You probably shouldn't cough near the bread.
I mean, you can, but we're gonna have to put a mask on you.
Are you sure it doesn't look dumb?
Do not worry, everything looks good. Enough for a first attack.
Now I need to teach you how to actually sell things.
Please go sit at the counter.
Oh, you're talking to me. You're talking about me.
Here they come.
Well, then the items are in place and now you need to learn how to actually sell things to people without embarrassing yourself.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Super Mario 3D World!
Alright, right.
Actually, sell things.
Hokkai, oh!
So to start with, I will lecture on the actual process of selling an item we have displayed.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
I can't pay attention.
Alright.
if the students do not listen they do not get any credit right right right now then when a customer
enters be sure to greet them with a nice big welcome uh welcome greeting the customer helps
them feel comfortable and relaxed while in the store their comfort is fundamental to our business
remember that as we continue now a typical customer will find an item they want on our
display and then they will come over to the counter to pay for it let me demonstrate could
i get this please um um um i don't know let me think about that i i i'm a store and i have things
that people pay me to give them i don't know what they want will be in the target window
you will also be able to see the name and the base price pay close attention to that base price
also if you press button three you can view expanded it well i don't what's that on
xbox consult the custom dot exe program included with resit here if you wish to check or alter
your button configuration wait button three custom dot exe focus your life is hard enough to
control as it is uh okay now the next you must decide what price you wish to offer
in general you want to try and name a price higher than the base try naming a price if
you will uh let's see you likely notice that the base price serves as your default
to raise your offer press up press up okay is this an android learning how to do things as a
pro i don't understand that's not gonna happen all right let's do uh 116 percent of base price
is that gonna work a fair price oh what oh oh shit i get how do i get this off um
i can't put that on zero there we are i got i gotta get it i'll only need just one person
to buy that and i'll be good okay i'm gonna say uh 1350 very good that is how you adjust
your offer this might be obvious if a customer is satisfied with your offer it is a sale and
you get a little bit of experience along with the money if your price is too high however
a customer can simply walk out learning to determine the proper price there lies the
challenge now if a customer disagrees with the price but not so much that they want to
storm out then you can negotiate remember what i said about comfort earlier and that is the
key here offer price but do not make it so outrageous that the customer feels you were not
acting in good faith 112 is fine so if they disagree but stay offer them a new price
ideally you will lower your offer a little and they will take it and give you a sale
some customers may just be trying to sniff out a better price when they're really willing to
pay your initial price however whether or not you risk testing that possibility is up to you
how long can you well that depends on how long can you keep haggling depends
on how regular a customer the person in the question is as we're starting out you will not
be able to haggle for very long but after customers begin to trust us a little you
can haggle for a longer period of time well time to put the theory into practice um okay
why isn't why why aren't you the boss and you the fairy if i'm the manager i come in and
i switch them i say you put the wings on and you go stand behind that counter this is like
fucking stupid uh juno upset i'll just give 10 community subs thank you thanks with the 10
community subs much love to you uh could i get this please oh okay i pick a price right needs
to be higher than the base uh up button uh customer will likely buy immediately knife the
fine art of haggling theoretically what you wish to do is lower your price slowly but as
i mentioned there is a limit how long you can haggle the idea is to deduce a customer's
desired price and go from there you say deduce the desired price but how do i the large number
of stores sell at about 30 over base price 30 it is not a hard and fast rule but people
will usually accept that price level usually if you can manage to go over that you will make
a lot of money but you do not want to risk driving away a customer right then so as a
customer i am haggling could you make it a little bit cheaper okay oh shit you want it cheap by
one cent all right here we go if you can sell me an item you'll be ready for what lies ahead
this is the true mentor and student come here hey so what's what's what's uh what's that like
the famous one like sell me this he likes to sell me this uh sell me this pen right
doesn't somebody do that yeah and send a movie or something all right let's begin
hello welcome to press it here i would like to buy this please steal i don't have one of those
well what happens now is sorry you have to go this is a you have to go to target because
they're all out at walmart so you have to go down the street sorry all right so how about
30 right let's be i'm not doing that number let's do like 41 50 hmm could you a little
lower perhaps yeah i guess so i you know i like you you're you're smart you're fun you're cool
you're coming here all the time and you know you're not you're you always got like good
coffee where you are yeah yeah that's a little bit lower i don't think so i don't think so i'm
doing you a favor here you know how rare these steel swords are you know how hard it is
to get these i had to go dungeon dumpster diving to find this all right all right you
know i like you i like you you know how stupid this is can we just take a quick break to just
talk about how dumb this shit is this is what happens everywhere why can't you just
sell me a product that is like what why do we have to do this did you do the shit when
you buy a car too how much is your car uh twenty thousand dollars no it isn't how much
is the car for real uh it's actually uh actually seventeen thousand dollars no it's not what's
the actual what do you what do you want from that car you know fifteen thousand is what
we want to sell this car for okay cool can i have the car for fifteen thousand
well i mean i mean well i don't think so you see because the car costs like nine
thousand dollars to make and why do we do this just sell it i lost why do we do this
to ourselves there's no reason to do this okay you know what i like you we're gonna start at 3800
so he's oh he's a ceasar communist no no i know i'm just saying i want to buy a product
if you want to sell me a product put a fucking price tag on it and sell it to me
why do we have to have like a like a three and a half hour long back and forth
where you tell me your life story so i pay more money for the car than it actually is
just put there's a price tag on the car there's a price tag on the car why not just have no price
tag and just say hey come on in and let's chat why is there a price on the car oh i did it
cut his mic no if a car is fifteen thousand dollars and you want to sell it for fifteen
thousand dollars and you have a price tag on the car for fifteen thousand dollars
that's what the car should be you shouldn't put a fake price tag on the car until the
customer comes in and says well that's fucked up i know i know i know it's wicked fucked up
it's actually 12 have a good day what oh we're gonna do it okay i would like this please all
right sure thing 30 we did 3800 last time let's do 39 let's be let's get daring here little
lower a little lower okay this is my final offer i sold yeah i sold a steel sword for
3750 picks if you want to practice again let me know anytime we're in the show okay i did it
and that is essentially how it goes you're quite good for someone who has
never done this before and has asked so many questions and was essentially just
parroting every sentence i said and not really learning anything we still have a
little bit of time left today so let us go ahead and open the store proper if anyone
comes in simply handle them in the same way that we just practice whoa are you sure it'll be okay
do not worry as the saying goes salesmanship is more of an art than it is a science
we're just fucking around all the time it's not about selling products it's just it's an
art now give me a paintbrush it looks like fucking make money now then i'll open us up
going instead of the comment oh here we go oh welcome looking for something looking for
something specific this please bread 100 bucks oh well
there's a bread shortage uh in uh in uh texas right now so you know i mean
we get our bread from massachusetts so this doesn't affect us at all
thank you glee i sold walnut bread for a one one zero what a scam
congratulations you did well i i scammed that lady i me rissetta i i scammed that fucking old
lady oh my just don't i i did it i i'm so happy i did it i did it i took something
from somewhere for way less money and put it in front of somebody else and lied to them
and doubled my money i tell you actually did it papa i did it i i don't i look i'm not against
capitalism i got i i trade goddamn stocks and crypto currency do you think i'm against
capitalism no i'm against fucking buck bullshit capitalism crypto hey we don't make fun of
crypto here crypto is you're describing like the bullshit no i'm not look if somebody wants
to buy whatever that i'm i am just as an outside perspective i'm just making statements that's it
i'm not saying we gotta do this i'm just i'm just making statements it's been three months
since papa left i don't get why he suddenly said i'm gonna go be a hero and then took off
without saying when he'd be back i really hope he's okay i'm getting lonely what the
fuck is going on right now well i shouldn't worry too much about him the best thing about
him is how tough he is he'll be okay is it dad is that burp papa wouldn't knock who is that
who is it there's nobody there wait what's at my feet here good evening um you are mademoiselle
reset lemongrass uh miss fairy pardon me but i am the one asking the questions
again you are reseti lemongrass um yes i'm reset my name is tier i'm an agent of the
term finance company finance company i'm here to collect payment on the loan paid out to your
father here is the contract and my identification um loan repayment uh in plainter terms i'm here
to get our money back and another thing about loans let's talk about fucking loans and how
they if you are incapable of facilitating repayment this house will be seized as
collateral in order to pay the loan i tell you this this person doesn't even know anything
facilitating collateral huh seize what
papa is he's not here yes i see that now uh monsieur lemongrass disappeared following a
fracas atop the local volcano so we assumed he might have returned here even if he has not
however the contract covers this eventuality covers this quite as the some i'm not gonna
read her lines anymore quite as the sole remaining member of his household we shall
require that you pay his debts in his stead i barely have enough money to live by myself
naturally we're not demanding it all be repaid at once there's still a small amount of
time before any payment is due therefore am i gonna get sold off in parts to distant foreign
lands to repay papa's debts i wonder if i can survive with only two internal organs
maybe if i eat a lot of spinach that can replace my blood
all right i'm sorry guys but she's pretty dumb you know like we've seen a lot of
sentence repeating thinking if you eat spinach it's gonna replace blood like you i mean come on
ahem please listen to me for a moment i have no clue where you're getting these
ludicrous ideas from but i would never do such a thing quite the opposite in fact
i was sent here to ensure that you wouldn't have to resort to such well absurd methods
to pay us back instead let me give you a different solution work for us for the rest of
your life 10 to 12 hours a day paying slowly back until you're 80 i've been sent to support
you to the fullest of my ability so that you may repay the debt via labor wait what but i've
never worked a single day in my life experience is no bearing no no work experience all that
matters is whether or not you are willing to work uh that was not the kind of response
that i would have assumed would happen from that why would you just go oh if you do not wish
to work then that is that the house is mine and i will have to ask you to leave the premises
as the saying goes those who do not work do not eat so miss lemongrass which will it be
work or the house yes remember happy gilmore his grandfather built that fucking house with
his bare hands and then that dickhead comes along that golf pro trying to like buy it
spoilers by the way for happy gilmore what can i even do i already have an idea this is the
backstory the city is an adventuring hub in addition this house faces out onto one of the
main city lanes therefore i propose converting this house into a store i would be like take
the fucking house you like cold-hearted piece of shit so you already own the store it did
just take the house well we won't take your house we'll just turn it into our house but
you can still sleep here just just squish the fairy yeah dude like come on i can't turn the
webcam on but i kind of have to just listen to sasame street music for a second this is
important all right so yeah what what what's stopping you from going from doing something
like this you know she's saying all these things like oh yeah we're gonna like own your
house and oh yeah your father is a fucking adventurer just like yeah oh yeah go ahead
tell me follow us what got you she's not that small how do you know she'd survive
did i lose my why did i lose this i was only gone for a little while to do market research
where could she have gone i'm like sleeping under the covers like fucking sad all i did
was threaten to take away everything she ever knew and loved asking her to turn the house
into an item shop was foolish even if it was to repay the debt the poor girl must be terribly
confused and on top of that her father is probably uh oh wait what's going on why is
the house being filled with like yayness it's done hey tier look it's done what is that
oh it's our shop sign of course doesn't it look cool but but it's on the ground oh of
course it's on the ground isn't that interesting how it's on the ground what what would be under
the ground here what are you what are you doing oh you know it's your grave you can't be a shop
without one of these you know yes well it's quite made well made he he said oh by the way
before i started uh i need to make this really clear before the stream started i was in chat
we were just talking and like talking about stuff and having fun and chilling and stuff
i wrote ha ha ha and everybody mocked me for doing it and i realized that you i can no longer
write like he he or like ha ha in text anymore because it's seen as like weird ironic fake
like laughing i can't run you cannot write ha ha ha ever again you have to do an emote now
it's seen as like a kappa ha ha ha oh yeah funny right no no i actually thought that was
funny well do the right emote then be that as it may while the sign is nice i am is there a
problem well the name you're quite sure that you have thought that through well we're partners
right you said so so put reset and tear together and reset here isn't it neat well that is to
say the sentiment is commendable but it's the two of us opening the store so the name should
reflect that right you don't like it really it's not that but well
okay your risk of tear that's awful why would you put tear it you know there's no reason for
that mispronounced it even slightly and reket tear racket racketeer this job is going to be
even more absurdly difficult than i originally suspected i fear and so a fairy suddenly
entered my life one thing was for sure this sure wasn't going to be dull how is it possible
to sleep this much each day how tear let's do the very best we can reset wake up please
what who's on first that's a boomer joke that's a super boomer joke that's so boomer that's
such a boomer joke that shits in black and white that's how old that joke is i just think
it's funny the clock does not have a good morning hand wait didn't we already do this
you're the proprietor of an item shop you must learn to be responsible and not sleep the day
away right right right right okay well why in the name of heaven are you smiling so much the
smile you have while sleeping is just getting bigger no no reason i just think i saw something
nice in my dreams here let's give it our all well if you really are dedicated to making
this work wash yourself and meet me downstairs will do can i play can i fucking play
so i have an item shop and stuff and it's all cool and awesome so uh what do i do now
that's up to your judgment if you sit at the counter we can open immediately
or we can reorganize the shop or we could even go search for new stock
around town or elsewhere yikes that's a ton of options how do i choose
it is as i said earlier running a place like this is more of an art than it is something
you can simply follow a map through simply pick something we will deal with what comes
okay welcome to recetteer all right i have 130 bucks how long is the day day two
how much money do i have not enough i need to sell this thing i gotta sell the sword
let's do it open the store wait hold on town square pub chapel adventurers guild
i mean it's blinking this shit's blinking hey what's this place this is the adventurers
guild the guild manages expeditions to the various untamed wilderness areas there have
been ruins in the city the area is commonly referred to as dungeons without approval
adventurers cannot visit dungeons you have to get approved ah we can't just go into the
dungeon to pick up everything now why what the heck we could get a ton of profit and shit
it's still a very good idea great many people evade that you can go into the dungeon and
get stuff and collect it and sell it but you have to identify it we must first hire an
adventurer can i just pick anybody the truth of the matter is a bit more complicated even
if you pay them few adventures are willing to risk their lives simply for the benefit
of a complete stranger mostly they turn away people when they don't know but yes
get to know a few adventures and build up a certain level of trust with them
if all goes well they will give you a symbol of their guild membership this usually takes the
form of a card with that in hand we can bring an adventurer with us so it's like they're
inviting us to a dinner party no you're going into a dungeon where you might both die see
attempting to rip you limb for i said i said it first but the analogy does work somewhere
right so first i need to meet adventurer where do you meet adventurers at the bar
after all we run an item shop we should get a few coming in as clients on a fairly
regular basis all right we're gonna sell that sword to somebody let's go get a dinner invitation
indeed just be careful that reset is not on the menu huh is something wrong well that guy
over there listen to me if i can't work i can't get the money and if i can't get the money
i can't get the items and if i can't get the items apparently i can't work
heaven if i had a few things i could at least visit the hall of trials
oh i wonder what's going on he seems to be a rookie adventurer complaining about his inability
to complete the required guild test oh test it is guild test the guild hardly allows anyone
off the street you can only work officially with the guild after passing tears and items up
owners hardly the only every episode of every single one of these i've ever watched i have an
idea sorry i do believe we have found our first adventurer wait what do you mean by uh tier
weight oh son of a i burn what cash i had just getting to the city if i can't get into the
guild i don't know what i'll even do for dinner money now i'm hungry great
excuse me pardon me a moment are you there adventurer with the seedy look who you calling
seedy well you two would be uh we're a pair of merchants who happen to be passing
merchants oh you heard me talking sorry but i'm way too broke and seedy to buy anything
believe me i could tell about your seedy nature that you're attempting to sell you
anything would be a colossal waste of time now come on tier stop with the seedy already he
isn't a plant minus two by the way so are you two going to prune me or what here would
you like it if we came with you to the hall of trials if you require equipment or items
we can provide them i'd call you a pair of angels then but why business naturally we help you pass
the trial you provide us with your card oh i get it we help mr swordsman clear the dungeon
and then he gives us his card a sign of our eternal friendship very dumb uh eternal friendship
is rather irrelevant in this case but it does work out neatly for all of us what do you say
i see you guys are pretty new at all this too huh oh that was i i did that one pretty i
phoned that part that was a phoned in line i'll offer mr swordsman yes or no yes
that wasn't me i swear that was in the game all right then heck i got nothing to lose while
aside from my precious life anyway yayifications glad to meet you too uh i'm reset nice to meet
you what's your name um what's louis call me louis louis the swordsman good to meet you
yes yes now then we will begin all the preparations for a dungeon visit
is he gonna die including a visit to the central market to pick up food and other
restorative items we'll then return here for you when we are ready right i'll be waiting here
all right so now we have to go to the we have to go get food um the apple is a bit sour
so it's best used in jam or a pie um he's a too much money i can buy bread this town
staple snack walnuts soft dough and a bit of sugar make it perfect i guess i'm gonna buy
two breads one bread can i can i like chase down the lady i sold the bread to all right
will he live off of one bread he's got a worn sword leather armor wooden shield old muffler
why does he have a muffler on uses sore okay leave leave level one swordsman louis pick the
items you wish to bring with you and finish like the depart option you got one bread let's go the
hall of trials so this is the dungeon just so welcome to the jungle as they say and another
hour long tutorial on how to control in combat i'm not a monster slayer i'm scared the two of
us are perfectly safe there's a protective field around the two of us to the monsters
we may as well be invisible so why are you on screen you could have just not put them on screen
you could have just sent this guy down louis perfectly safe too then no no not quite actually
uh well louis is uh you know louis could see some problems in the next few minutes
we don't have to worry but this is accomplished by making us virtually
intangible to everything inside this place we can directly manipulate nothing
we can't collect things why are we in here that's why our adventurer remains outside the field
so this guy picks up stuff should i venture be injured we can place him in the field
and retreat since we must carry him back however we can take very little else with us
one item at most so even if we run into trouble we don't lose everything but wait
i thought you said we can't yes i will elaborate further if need be later i'm not
going to press that button we can bring as much as our bags will allow us to carry if we get out
safely cool wait as much as our bags will allow well you have bags too yep yep the adventurers
focus on adventuring while we keep track of what to loot you got it cool k o day let's get
karate equip items in bag
all right i just used sp slime
is this money where are these items this would be more tolerable if you muted
why would i mute this something in here oh crafter's knife that'll beat me a pretty penny i think
is it goo what is it can i pick it up slime fluid missed i got it i got it
oh he's dead is there a dodge roll if there's a dodge roll that's gonna be
okay she just gets like upset every time he gets a hit i just hear like oh no
uh-oh there's a trap that was a crit this crits in this game pretty cool
so does he level up down here
term of the crits yes oh sure i don't know if i want to stand on this
not yet is there a run or a sprint or a dash
i don't think so chest how much do i have room in our bags do we have
summer sandals i don't gonna be able to sell this stuff and then i'm gonna be oh this is how
it begins
get 11 sp level three
oh they get this brand of traps all right let's keep going go to the next floor yes
okay all right red slimes they're more aggressive
this is gonna get so hard i can't like this is gonna be the hardest fucking game ever
ladle a back scratcher i'm gonna sell that for like five grand
it's like the mines and stardew yeah that's what this reminds me of
how do i look at my backpack is there a way to see my in my backpack i don't think so
i don't have a way to look at my in my sack
why would they just be rocks i don't have like a dodge roll
no i don't want to do this this probably with all kinds of like treasures
he's gonna die to the rocks i don't think i don't think it's possible for me to die down here
oh what's that walnut bread times two well i'm glad i did this because i'm gonna have
a ton of inventory for the store
oh there's a trap
more bread yeah i can sell it
yeah how do you take it i don't know what you said new enemy type
is it a bad guy i don't know i mean that doesn't look like a bad guy iron armband
is this for the playstation 1 but it's it's a cute game we're not done yet i i look
this looks like it could be interesting i promise to skip 60 of all dialogue from here on out
no in the sea of nose i see in all capitals thank god all right i'm gonna be careful
it's going off like
computer how many floors are there
i can't wait to like sell all this guy's stuff give it to us we'll hold it for safe keeping
oh thanks guys what an idiot
oh that felt kind of good it felt good that was fun he doesn't get anything you commission
him to go down i'm gonna translate i think this is the last floor is it
we'll be careful was i right i think i'm right that's pretty close i think
this is not what happened anybody here speak japanese two candies
combat's kind of fun i can see okay this is this game is gonna be fun
if this gets really hard
it's a playstation 1 enemy it's all right
i might have to make the game full screen though because it's really kind of chugged down
here for some reason oh was it pendant souvenir charm i'm gonna make like five grand
ten grand all right be careful
apple thank you for being the canary to tell me when to leave no no no not yet not yet not yet
oh you got
watch that side overestimating value this game's downfall
i do like the weird 2d 3d isometric it looks weird
but it works somehow
get the item hold on wait wait wait wait what do we get item where get item where is it i don't
see anything no i'm gonna get like the sonic the hedgehog shoe sure i already have a ton of
those already
all right not a trap i knew it was gonna be a trap oh shit i don't have any
i don't have enough sp to do that move and i was timing it
oh is he gonna die in the tutorial unidentified item goldfish yeah i'm gonna
have to make this full screen unfortunately oh longbow
i'm good i got full health again
so what's what's max level that a dungeon adventurer can be
oh can't carry anymore i want that how do i can i like what the hell is going on
items walnut bread slime fluid why can't i think they can only be in stacks of three
no what why are these stacked oh it's plus three it's plus four so get rid of the shitty one
i'm getting rid of this one
all right i gotta leave the dungeon i'm out of space
come on group up group up group up
please be nice his eyes are worn from six decades of games
stun lock both of them that was pretty good all right so group up group up
can i get them all in a circle here around me
no there no no
eat bread i'll eat bread and if i need it that's probably health
all right let's get out of here you found a game that i'm good at
what i mean what i mean i found a game that i'm good at this is just like the beginning
he thinks it's health well why would it's food oh this is this is did i did i do it i didn't i
did i did i i did it i've cleared the hall of trials oh sweet mystery of life now you'll
give me money way to go louis reset tear this is all thanks to you guys this is all well
and good but there's a treasure chest just beyond it behooves us to investigate thoroughly
tear you really do like going for the money don't you what i do not suppose such foolishness
there's no need to treat me like a flying ball of breed hey hey hey now i love me some
treasure too don't worry tear i'll feel you on this really you two completely misunderstand me
it's gonna be trapped so the contents of the chest give me just a second here hey it's
classified redacted documents wow so this is an adventurous guild card
here take one like we promised oh yeah thanks while you did promise to give us your card
eventually we're not so crass as to demand your very first card you really should think
about who you want to give your first no here take it please i'd love to thanks louis
awesome i can't wait to adventure with you two some more really now young people are so annoying
with their social engagements hey tier what's this thing that just showed up
oh yes that that's a refrigerator is a door you can you go through it and it'll take you back
to town you cleared the dungeon and they show up when you clear a dungeon they appear every
five levels so you can leave got it don't we have to start all the way at the beginning
not at all you can always head back to the floor that had a door on it in fact if you do not use
a door you do have to restart okay that's good to know so if you find a door always use it
returning home takes time furthermore leaving ends the current contract with our companion
and we would have to rehire him or choose a new one if there is something specific in a
dungeon that you desire you can simply ignore the doors and press onward so it is stardew
game came out in like 2006 all righty then i think we have to go home now
quite so just to be sure in the future please try to avoid referring to this as going home
because it's not your house you're really gonna pull that on me right now you're going to like
passive aggressively tell me that it's not my house now you're gonna do that that's
unbelievable that's i mean that's actually unbelievable turns out it was just a movie
yata means clear all right cool 20 out of 20 what does rearrange mean oh show the cool stuff
first 1400 base 1400 base 650 this is gonna be sick a couple of birds nests all right now
let's get this shit loaded up here we go let's get some cool stuff in the window
get the crafter's knife in there get the long bow in there iron armband in the window
let's put let's get let's get the charms and um chocolate a simple chocolate bar made with
a cocoa base 500 bucks 1100 that's like the finest chocolate in the fucking world
all right close we get these off replace these with the sandals
i guess you can just keep them up this is the clothes shop store
all right uh what does it take atmosphere what was that just a store atmosphere okay
i'm ready to make some money store atmosphere oh here we go it's her
store atmosphere wait why is this like a political spectrum store atmosphere according
to tier light dark gaudy plane well we're very much on the right side here
do we want to be light and gaudy or do we want to be dark and plain or do we want to be
plain and light so we're very plain merchant level i can see level one starting level
of customers yeah can take orders more items all right this we're just starting
i'm ready to open the store wait isn't it like nighttime what time is it
oh we got a lot of customers
whoa hold on wait yeah you over set bring this up please
wouldn't shield it so you 650 all right hold on everybody slow down here
yeah get away from there don't touch that i need to get some security cameras
i'm sticking to my guns on this no way all right like bring it up again i like you
hey there's no beating you said yeah i'll take that price
got it gee i sold our armband for 700 bucks anybody else welcome
oh can i purchase this from you 1400 should we just fuck this guy uh 1800
right then i'd call that a fair deal thanks that's a lot anybody what can i get you
you have one of these that's a lucky day for both of us then
yeah it sure is 2000 that's it that's a long bow that's rare no no no no no no 1900
1850 it well i feel like i'm playing the prices 1800 got it the money just flows
oh it's me again um could i also have this long sword 1700 1650 take it or leave it
i just made a lot of money you did well you look tired profits
imagine selling shit in real life if it was this easy all right so i sold
oh yeah i saw that bread earlier too profits plus 5000 store score difference
look fuck it we're just gonna buy more we're just gonna open the shop again
now i'm no longer an adventurer store i'm like an ice cream and candy store
what's wrong concerning the debt i have a suggestion concerning it's free how much do i owe you
paying it all back at once is wholly beyond your means how do you know that small weekly payments
wholly beyond oh this is now that this is this is where i this is where we have to see all this
bullshit oh you made six thousand dollars well hold on here's the 2000 for the taxes of
course take taxes out first now you're at 4000 oh you have like a couple of credit cards
you have a couple of um small loans that's another like fucking uh 1500 2000 let's take
that away from you too you know you sold that's your money but it's not anymore
if it leaves you with like a 1200 bucks you get a car payment too it makes you pay that car down
you're a thousand how much does it eat food i would pay for groceries for the you're talking
about like four five six hundred bucks a month all right now you're down to like 300 bucks well
you want to buy you want to buy anything else for you sorry get lost i just want to go to
disney okay i want to go to disney with my family and it's like four grand stop taxing me
stop putting me in debt stop over pricing your shit i just want to go to disney that's all i care
about all i wanted was a pepsi libertarian you never told me how big papa's debt is exactly
that's because you would faint if you found out for now it's a secret so you like predatory
lended my father stop taxing me stop putting my family in debt let me let me let me prosper
for god sakes hire a good lawyer oh i can't wait to hire a good lawyer what's that like seven grand
stop taxing me stop putting me in debt stop making me get a lawyer every three months
actual anger as the store begins to build up steam we will increase payment size
ten thousand dollars the repayment date nearest to the current date how much of that is interest
how much of that am i paying down to principal you fucking floating motherfucker
how much of that is interest the amount do will be displayed on the calendar in the main menu please
be sure to check it regular what if i don't can i just not pay karate i'll keep an eye on it
i can't wait to get bills in the mail all right let's wait do i have anything else i put
up here oh slimes slime plus three uh let's do get some look we got slime slime next to the
bread probably not a good idea but we got slime we got bread here we go open it up
i have now a candy store oh slime fluid plus three oh i'll take this
write that i'd call that a fair deal thank you somebody buy the chocolate it's expensive
oh this will do souvenir charm can you sell it for just a little less all right there
i'm old and i think that 399 is the same thing as 400 because i've been conditioned to think that
for some reason 99 of some sense means it's way less thank you have a good day
oh it's me again you know how much for this piece of clothing it's a little too expensive
for me 99 cents that's a fair deal for me thank you oh it's me again i don't you have such
good prices at your store how much is this bread oh it's 99 cents i'll take it looking for
something i want this oh right i should have done 199 i was scamming myself uh well
well young lady that'll be um well could you make it a little cheaper this is getting dumb
that's getting like trouble because i was like selling like something too expensive to like
child wait she wasn't buying like a knife right what was she buying was that a plant
bread bread okay i know she wasn't buying like a sword or anything well then you seem to
have developed a basic understanding of how to sell things to people and not drive them
to burn the shop in anger yepperoni yepperoni
why does it what i feel like my mother just texted me back yes being a truly great store
owner involves more than selling things however there are there are times when people will want
to sell items to you really i suspect we'll begin to get such offers very soon
but i already buy stuff from the guild and the market so why should i worry about buying
stuff from the customers there's one major difference between a guild or a market purchase
and a purchase from an individual individuals do not have set prices in other words you can
scam them as you do while you're selling haggled down oh so i can get stuff really cheap but
that seems like it'd be pretty hard fundamentally buying and selling are not that different
the customer shows you an item they wish to sell and then you set a price and perhaps
negotiate obviously you wish to pay less than the base price of the item okay so buy
high and sell low that sounds like what i do on markets all the time just so that is the very
core of a successful business now then shall we practice the fundamental procedure is the same
as when selling okay welcome to recetteer uh would you buy this from me hmm let me
need to name a price 1096 at this level there will not be much profit when we resell
go somewhat lower really all right this this is like a knockoff at this point eight percent of
base price 826 excellent this is a good price level now then let us practice haggling over
the price it's the same now that you have offered a price you believe to be fair adjust
your offer until you agree to sell to you could you offer me a little more i think it's
worth a lot 50 and 70 percent of the base is a good target you will gain an item to sell without
giving up too much money let's go welcome uh what would you be willing to pay for this
i forgot everything you told me pay twice 150 thank you welcome two thousand dollars for a
baked yam uh bring that down 900 you're really easy to buy from i could say whatever i want
you just removed 65 percent of all value all right do i have what what items do i have
the apple on there i want this to be a food based restaurant all right and then
back scratch is going to go up here right here get rid of that get this other bullshit over
here all right let's do it again one two three open the store welcome can i help you with
anything i remember you this is a present from mommy it's a present you know it's a present for
mom this is getting dumb she's smart though that's oh it's me again i'm really easy to sell to
need to help the old pension you see what can i get for this
ah bread sucks i mean you won't i got plenty of bread 40 she's about right yeah
yeah yeah change that seems perfectly normal i read that online therefore it's real bye
oh i got wall a walnut bread welcome i sold it to him i thought he was selling it to me
he was but no he was buying like i was so he was selling that to he was selling that to me
so i bought it for 40 right wait wait wait wait what are you guys talking about
i bought that from him for 40 he that i had that right what are you talking about why is
everybody like attacking me right now i picked this up a while nosing around a cave can i sell
it see he wants to sell it to me for 2300 get out of here man i would i want to pay
1300 for this less than that i want to i want to lie to his face 43 percent of base price
see don't think didn't think i'd get that good price
he's dumb i can sell that for like 3000 i was looking for this okay we're looking for this so
let's go uh 170 this guy's really really really gullible could you take it down just
a little bit sure that's unreasonable hi what can i get for you you have it yay
please i just want to buy my mother a present okay now you know i'm full of shit so i can't
i can't you know i'm full of shit so let's go 105 i'm a good shopper right oh you little
shit i knew what you were doing and you know that i respect you for that i respect you for
doing that to me can i help you any chance i could get you to buy this little lady
oh it's a yam it's a really expensive yam oh you're old hold on give me one second let me pick this
up uh this is a rock it's a rock yes it's a rock this is only this is worth nothing oh sorry
thank you bye you can have it i'd like this 100 120 that seems fair holy cow it's late
times seem to fly by today speaking of time i plan on doing some mild schedule management
for you from now on to ensure you're working in an effective manner to pay back the debt
what are you talking about i've broken up the day into four time periods morning afternoon
evening and night what you can do and how much you can do depends on the time of day
hey yeah the clock's been broken up into four areas think of each part as a slice of time
a slice like pie yeah okay i thought i would be able to keep your attention if i made it
rather similar to some sort of sweet food so this is the morning slice the afternoon i'm
getting hungry so this four sections of the day you can only act between morning and night
yes when night ends you need to go to bed trying to run a shop while sleep deprived is
unpleasant so i'll close up when it gets late so you essentially have two options for each slice
you can open the store for a time or go about town on business you can't do both at once so
decide in advance what you need to do to be clear opening the shop will consume a slice
and returning to the store after going out regardless of what you actually did
will also consume a slice but what if i go to like the plaza and then the chapel
slice slice you can get around town easily enough to avoid consuming a slice with each move
only when you return to the store will the clock advance a slice so in that case i should do a
lot when i leave the shop yes that's a good attitude to take now there's another vital element
leaving town all together visiting a dungeon will consume two slices no matter what that takes
that long so if i go in the morning and i'll get back in the evening that's precisely how it works
thus you can only leave for a dungeon at an early point in the day if it is night or you
have done something else that evening you cannot go because if i did go i'd get back
real late right exactly not only would you annoy your adventurer companions with staying
out so late you would also be dead on your feet the next day after returning
man this is a lot to wrap my head around you guys ever watch uh training videos company training
videos i'm getting that vibe right now this is go watch go watch the pizza hut training video
i watch it all the time we're making it great i'm not kidding i like lie in bed and watch
training videos i don't know they're like soothing to me i don't know why that's sad
what do you mean that's sad i'll have my ipad and like kim will be next to me and will it be
like okay good but good night go to i'm going to bed we'll be like on our devices and i'll
load up the wendy's training video it's like 45 minutes long and i just watch it it's it's
like an infomercial before you know it you will be thinking about it naturally you guys yeah
don't you don't you put the sauce in the middle and you go out you leave about a half
an inch on the edge you don't put the sauce all the way to the edge of the pizza
and you want to line the toppings up with the sauce never to go over that edge of the pizza
especially when making a pan pizza well it helps that you will always be able to see how much
time a particular action will consume simply pay attention to the clock i want to make sure
weigh out all your cheese and stuff and you do a top cheese as well the dough master in
the morning will give you uh and if there's any bubbles or it doesn't look very good
report it to the dough master and use another one i will be glad to go over it as often as
you need i don't think i need to go over i'm actually a dough master so you know what i'm
talking about all right so i got like i can open the store one more time look at this shit baked
yam let's get the let's get our food here beef bowl uh let's put nothing here i'm gonna
back scratcher should go over this way put the sandals
is
and i want the fish up there too
back scratcher goes down here these are gonna sell for thousands of dollars
he's like old guy's gonna come in the store and buy the yam for three times as much as he
sells it to you for hey there mommy asked me to sell this unthankful statue
i can't i can't uh i gotta i gotta do decent prices with her excuse me how much is this yam
a tight balance sheet this month this is precious but i think i can sell it
it's bread don't kid yourself it ain't worth that much is it really worth so little
hmm
oh really thanks it's you again this is a present for daddy as long as i can get a little bit of
money come up with the yam old man looking for something special oh i've been thinking
about getting one of these for a while now one goldfish graham cracker now these are
expensive 1500 customer service seems to be a lost art these days that's fine thank you
now thank you anybody else you have one of these it's a lucky day for both of us didn't
you just sell this to me all right so you lost a hundred bucks you lost well you lost a full
dollar oh yeah excuse me miss i would like to ask you if i could buy this please sir would do
weren't you in here yesterday yesterday i don't know what you're talking about i don't i haven't
been here oh that'll do thank you what a scam all right i can't help but notice what you just
did to that old man i'm reporting you i'm reporting you to osha hey could i purchase
this yeah you sure can 350 gee i sold an apple so this do you think i could turn it into a bit
of coin so you're selling me this candy okay i mean like maybe got it i almost have ten thousand
dollars you seem more or less used to the basics of running a shop there's one of the
matter however you cannot always be certain that a customer will know what they want when
come in what are you talking about they may come in thinking oh what should i make for dinner
what would be a good weapon and so forth they will not be quite sure exactly what they wish
to purchase when they come through our door in such a case we must provide them with advice
to help them decide wait wait how could i do that many customers will simply give up if they
do not find something suitable for their needs on our counters others whoever will realize
that we may have reserved stock and we would require as to whether or not we have something
they seek that's when you may suggest an item you think they would like
okay you'll impress them if you know what they want and you'll cause them to return
no pressure then okay let's practice kk welcome i would like a sword please so anything is okay
as long as it's a sword ultimately you must pick something the person would like by the
way if i may give you a little advice if you sell weapons and armor to your adventurer friends
they will equip the items you sell them meaning of course that if you sell items to them then
we do not need to lend them any items at the start of a dungeon and we'll be able to bring
back more items for our own use even if an adventurer must retreat while in a dungeon
the equipment is not lost since it's in their possession so we're just going to
scam all the whole way we're doing like meta scamming so we want to sell to our
adventurer friends even if you must undersell it to them well we don't have to do that don't worry
accessories work the same way so think carefully about who you sell what to
and what effect it may have on their performance so that guy came in and he bought
the armband so if i get any cool armor or weapons only sell it to the adventurers
you can see what that person currently has and see if it's better than that's cool
all right let's go i'd like a sword please i got one for you here it's a steel sword yes excellent
the rest is like a normal sale hello i'd be like a weapon however however what some
sell windbreaker how about something like this oh this is lovely how much is it
could you go a little lower excellent price thank you this is a ponzi scheme
i'd like a weapon however here how about this long sword oh that's lovely how much is it
yeah speaking of debt so today's the third i have one two three four five i have to pay
ten thousand dollars on the eighth that's all my money i mean can i start burying cash in the
backyard good thing i fucking did that holy shit that would have been horrible i got crashed
all right so it's night time can't open the store oh yeah actually i kind of could
let's put like candy up here no i want to sell i want to sell this
oh here we go i don't suppose you have a scarf
shit uh do you want to back scratch you
how much for this candy 380 i can't ask you to go any lower right no you can't except you can
this is for sale right eight oh thousand bucks i knew i was gonna sell those i want to
sell the beef bowl damn it good night good night 4600 bucks in profit
yeah that guy doesn't know how to negotiate i don't some people don't like negotiating
i'm not i don't really like it some people you know if somebody says oh that's uh
but here's the problem with negotiating you this is why like that this world is so fucking
dumb okay you can't like go into a macy's and negotiate the price of a pair of pants
you can't walk up to the fucking counter at macy's with like a fair pair of fucking jeans
uh this this says 80 i want to pay 60 uh sir what the fuck are you talking about
security we have like a fucking weirdo at the front desk but you can do that with
other forms of property why you can negotiate some places but other places you
you'll get like arrested if you try to tell them you're gonna pay 50 dollars for the 80 dollar
jeans you can do that with a house but not a pair of sandals that's what i'm saying
negotiation is such a strange thing i can't like negotiate with the guy at the bar how
much the drink is all right i want to go buy some stuff i have a lot of money yeah that's
a 750 for the bud light uh i mean what you meant to say was five dollars uh can we get
this fucking guy out of here and then you like cut to you getting like thrown out onto
the street all right let's go to the market hmm tree seed necklace cloth cape wait hold on
this is a lot of money but i could just sell a bunch of cloth old muffler he already has this
one i don't even want that on the store powerful ring unthankful statue medicine
i'm gonna get a bunch of capes yeah all right guys i'm going all in on capes
i'm gonna feed the cape store what do you mean rip what i get i can't negotiate with this person
you understand even in the same town it's not consistent okay all right let's go let me look
what's in the chapel say terry you came from a finance company right what on earth yes that's
right i work for term e finance i got what do you mean i don't have enough time to do this
you're employed by them right what's it like no that's not quite accurate i was contracted to
term me through another organization thus i'm not really an employee per se so you just
contracted i'm surprised you seem so it's not that surprising almost all fairies in human
society belong to a fairy specific contract agency there are of course a few free agent
fairies out there as well and so that's how it works oh yeah it's like a baseball team
yes i have to tell the truth it can be difficult for fairies to find employment in human
society so the agencies were founded an age ago in order to help facilitate fairy livelihoods
that's amazing quite we just had that conversation in the church what was the
point of doing that in the church all right what town square i love being able to relax
in the plaza like this you never seem to have trouble relaxing even when we are not
in the plaza i can i try sometimes i can do it that that like drop water droplet like what
can you guys do that if you like uh tap the side of your cheek and go like what
i used to be able to do it i can't do it anymore uh well it's healthy right
what a waste of time let's go to the pool uh this is closed uh let's just let's go let's
go let's sell the cakes for fucking a ton of money look we got bibs and we got beef beef and
bibs that's a cool restaurant name where you can just be as sloppy as you fucking want don't take
nobody take that that's mine bibs and beef where the whole counter it's all sloppy like fucking
sloppy joe sandwiches and wicked gross like pulled pork you eat with your hands and the
whole table is covered with a sheet and you get a big bib nobody that's mine bankrupt what
are you talking about you know how much it costs to make a sloppy joe you talk about
like capitalism a sloppy joe takes like 48 cents to make you can sell for like seven dollars
all right that looks good by the way just want to be sure everyone is aware that i said that on
stream and it's gonna be time stamped it is july 6th 2019 i am doing a verbal document
here a verbal out loud document that i i'm a verbal out loud patent of bibs and beef a
store where your restaurant where you eat food with a bib and you can eat like sloppy joes
and shit and my grandchild's been pestering me to get a hat i don't have hats so well do you want
like a bird's nest hat just like dunk it on his head what are you doing i'm gonna beef some bib
motherfucker i don't have i don't have that you don't have any i'm terrible how can you be
terrible at not having inventory shit i'm looking for some chocolate and of course you're
selling this when i'm near broke he is okay does it get like the five percent adventurer friend
discount no that's i was looking to sell that all right somebody buy a cloak there it is no
ha ha never thought i'd find one of these dropped it by five cents somebody buy those
cloaks i spent a lot of money on these why does nobody want this somebody doesn't want a
cape buy it they're really nice oh hello i would like this cape my daughter-in-law asked me to
pick this up that's too much there you go you invested in capes right before the great cape
crash do i have a weapon i don't backscratcher is not a weapon shit do i have no talent
hey i could use a weapon well you don't have it you don't have it why do you say it twice
well you don't have it you don't have it well do i have to pay the debt back
i got plenty of time i'm looking for a treasure that's a treasure the ultimate in
treasures sir may divert your attention over here to the backscratcher all those hard to
reach places i know sometimes at work i've seen you do the bear up against your furnace
and move back and forth scratching your back on the hard iron not anymore sir
it is worth a lot don't have enough money on hand it's a pretty good lie what
that was only 125 negative 2100 negative 2100 how i didn't where's the negative
time of the capes shit that's right okay i'm gonna go buy a sword what how much money do i have
no you don't fuck it uh let's go warren sword level six louis let's go here we go jade way
which one jade way hall of trials jade way floor one to five wait hall of trials
jade way equip items in the bag yes
okay here we go i wish you would just say that
okay we got unidentified ingredient
oh hold on those bees those little bugs i think are bad
treasure ingredient come on something cool unthankful statue things dumb
um
it's a mimic no not yet not yet there's probably something down here
lots of unidentified items so how do i identify the items again
i just have to leave with them right
huh
you do it with your butt i mean a laugh face i see
oh i just made it snow i mean it's slippery holy shit snow
it's the ice level in mario again yeah yeah yeah yeah news sp consumption has been halved
is a good thing or a bad thing
all right i want to get a good sword and sell it to him because this guy's sword sucks
how am i ever gonna fight like the dragon that's at the end if i'm gonna have a warren
sword i mean like you got it you still gotta pay for it but i'm gonna give it to him
imminent crash incoming imminent crash
yeah he's gonna put more points into strength yeah but i'm not in control of that
he's in control of his own build
i have nothing to do with it
common shield oh i'll be selling that to you don't think that's kind of sad though
he's doing all this work and he picks up a shield wow that's way better than what i have
i have to buy this from the person that's standing cowering behind
if i have a lot of swords who rule why do we pretend kings hold all the power souvenir charm
double swing unidentified ingredient what's my highest stat in real life um i can chug wicked fast
chan to tweet a boy yo
watch out shark fins a plus two shark bin
what can i do faster drink or pee uh there is a limit to how fast you can pee
so i don't know what you're talking about got another cape yeah it's a good day for a cape
four three two what's my highest stat in real life my ability to take
bullshit you know what i mean
what's my highest stat in real life my ability to like give no fucks
come here what what just happened
oh
what's my element of fire i'm like really unpredictable and fucking uncontrollable
you can't minus two because of the spam filter
that means it's happening so often that you can't even type it you're being like fenced
it's you're being like fenced in you can't do it no that doesn't mean everybody do it
that's not fair that delete that that's not fair
you can't carry anymore oh i'm gonna use something what does slime do can you eat the
slime eat the bread we're almost done almost at the bottom of this tutorial too
comedy meter is crashing yeah you guys are deliberately crashing
everyone's deliberately that's why it's it can't be used as a real barometer just open it
huh you guys are the you you guys are the guys that go to the movie you've seen three times
already and react the whole time and like talk shit about all the scenes that are about to
pop up to your friends and everybody around you can hear you there's nothing there's
nothing worth you've already seen it you don't have to do the minus two shit again
i need to get rid of stuff the slimes the slimes don't do anything
i don't think i want to do it anymore i want the slimes to be gone oh my god comet shield cape
the statues are dumb too oh oh but by the way everybody did anybody see on the front page of
reddit the other day i can't you couldn't write this shit they had the differences
between jelly jello and jam it was fucking everywhere and i was right everyone was talking
about this and i was right everybody talked so much shit about everything i was saying and then
it turns out what do you know the guy with the plus 10 intelligence you wonder what static was
jelly is gelatin i can't even fucking believe it i'll i got i got everyone was no that's
actually not what it is i got a hat i saw that i was laughing my ass off
i was just lying down just like you gotta be kidding me why would that be there but i'm so glad
because i've i've been absolved of all the things everyone thought it was so stupid and
there it is the explanation for what all of them are oh bomb
damn it i can't carry anymore what if i get rid of the unthinkable statue whatever it is
scared of it they're only worth 140 dollars i think i bread can sell for more than that
i'm not the original poster i've just i i agree with the post
was this a melon what's this crap these shrooms are crap this walnut bread is is crap
just eat it orange
pick me up that all right that's good uh fifth floor is the end of this one
although i think i can go up but whatever oh the crown slime lord of slime this is a boss
yeah watch it one damage i haven't hurt this thing this is gonna kill me
uh-oh
22 oh shit you okay you gotta break them up i get it break them up
yeah
earth real challenge two don't get greedy only two swings
jump again i can do three he's gonna die to the easiest boss just don't say that
then it becomes a reality nice
oh and you made it no uh chest i'm not gonna die slime wheel yeah nice okay
no i got a lot of stuff so let's go down
yeah i got a lot this the 1200 what else do i get these shark fins are worth a lot
powerful anti-venom slime fluid slime fluid furball powerful anti-venom wool hat insect trap
stuff kind of sucks but let's go to the pub what is it say tier is alcohol yummy
i've only tried it once before myself really wow you're so grown up i hated it it stank of
barrels typically most alcoholic beverages are left to age in barrels that's not true so the
drink had a strong wooden smell and it was not dissimilar to attempting to drink a tree
that's not true okay that doesn't sound yummy at all to be honest the popularity
of the substance baffles me it always sells well so stalking it is always a good way to make some
money but but barrels barrels that's a pretty good joke we can go to the market we can go uh
let's go so how do i get alcohol let's head back here because i want to set up my shop
again here we go let's do shark fin where's my shark fins excuse me get out of my way
okay i also want to get rid of the uh get the arm band up there no no that thing's terrible
i need to sell these capes i'm gonna keep the shield take a shot for every drink you sell
it's not it's not that kind of night all right what else do i got more capes no let's
take take them off i don't let's only have two because nothing people will think
they're oversupplied and be like why are these not selling uh let's put the anti-venom
out here too insect trap anti-venom chocolate bar 700 bucks for an orange
all right i get to put in the shield why not you're thinking too hard for an anime game
what this is for sale right yep 600 bucks you put the food next to insect repellent
okay but it's wrapped up i could use some food really well i got news for you i got an orange
here beef bowl i've been trying to sell this for a while good choice 3000 bucks this guy
doesn't fuck around so i'm gonna go one oh one oh four wow that's kind of ridiculous
that guy seriously that was very very reasonable this is for sale right yes it is
can you take it down a little bit thank you
you're trying to mega scam him oh here we go now he's selling some food i can ah it's
only been touched by four or five different people at this point
so
i just sell it at value nobody can afford this lower it under charge this guy 20 2400 come on
okay i got plus 900 i'm fine i'm gonna have to sell the thing at cost nobody wants it it's
too expensive nobody wants it nobody wants that stupid thing got a weapon nope i don't
i bought it for a thousand yeah but i wanted to maximize my profit
this will do 550 750 650 good deal all right i have enough money to pay my debt
excuse me miss i just got stung by a scorpion outside can you help me my daughter-in-law asked
me to pick this up 12 000 should we just try to do it for 150 yes just to hear i'm too scared
i need the money okay how we doing how many days do i got i got two days i need a little
bit more money i need to sell this fucking beef somebody buy this and no one's buying
any capes either i need a weapon all right let me go get a weapon i still have plenty of time
uh the market right no no it's like the adventurer's guild right or the merchant's
guild there we go worn sword is all i he only has daggers i could get a dagger
crafter's knife staff magician's staff maybe get a longbow spears oh iron spear
yeah i'm gonna get an iron spear and armor iron armor all right get this shit out of here
get the spear in the window get the armor in the window keep the beef there keep the shark fin
there move this arm band get this nobody wants this so many of these dumb cave what was
i thinking all right let's go put the beef ball on the floor the wife's been up in my
shorts about getting a weapon really well how about an iron spear perfect don't have the money
on you 2000 no no no no like 1999 there it is what no matter how you slice it that's unreasonable
you back the wife's been up my shorts about getting so oh by the way i forgot
i just told you to fuck off and left the store but oh shit i have i gotta buy food
uh this is the only store and i really didn't feel like putting in the gps like the nearest
grocery store like eight miles away uh you got any food oh my god i have to sell this at a
loss nobody wants this nobody has any money to buy that people what's going on do you have a
book i don't have any books go to the library hey hey this item is for sale right oh defense
33 to 36 it is for sale and just for you i'll make sure to give you a good price on it
and now you're gonna be wearing it oh and this will do what are you gonna use that for
grandpa always has a lot of money oh there we go yeah i'm a loaded fucking millionaire
i just felt like owning this and potentially throwing it out of my window on random stuff
thank you grandpa always has money i was gonna sit oh by the way uh i need bread too remember
that guy that came in here talked shit about food well that's all right i'll buy what he was
gonna get hey grandpa thanks for being a good customer take care of you take care of the
customers that take care of you that's how they get you they they throw in the the thing
that's free that is meaningless you want to buy the vacuum cleaner the four five hundred
dollar vacuum cleaner oh but yes wait we'll throw in a new shower head rack absolutely free
that thing's fucking stupid that's gonna just be in your closet you're not gonna use it
i just did that with the bread all right what uh it's too late to do anything else so
i think i'm ready for bed no i still got time you do one more let's go
reset i'll take this common shield right that i'd call that a failure thanks
wait i know i don't i i want to i just sold it to the other guy got any weapons nope sorry i
just lost my last weapon good night good night 4500 in profit exceeded expectation
so when do i have to pay tomorrow is the debt i hadn't paid 10 000
i need to go get another weapon uh how about a magician staff laundry pole
that's i don't i mean at that point you just start punching people
shield maybe buy another common shield common shield and a crafter's knife
and let's get a magician staff anything else to talk about no get the cheap items no you buy
huge and you sell huge i'm gonna put i'm gonna put the magician staff out i need to get rid
of this beef obviously i'm gonna sell this at like a 50% base loss i don't even care
would you mind telling me this just get rid of it i don't want it i spent a thousand
dollars on it i got a 500 dollar profit i don't care i was looking for this
135 a little bit less i i could crafter's knife hi there what can i get you
oh wooden armband so this is the legendary reset sell me this don't you already have
one of these here you already have one
oh insect trap i've never sold an insect trap before let's just do a reasonable 150
derma you suck i just sold three items in a row but more than i paid for them what are you
talking about i did very good right there that was very well done 1400 14 000
get one of these dumb capes there's already a cape up here
how much is this stuff worth put the anti-venom up there it sells people usually buy it
shield in there too it's super new charm
just put the capes everywhere i don't care anymore i love these capes
oh i don't suppose you have a piece of armor oh but i do my friend 36 to 40 15 so i
that's a good one yes it is all right so how much money do you have how much did i buy this
for i bought this for like 900 to say the thousand this guy's broke all right i bought
up a 900 or 1200 oh god damn it but this is i'm left i'm this is the armor that i'm gonna be
using i make out there it's fine it's i i i sold it at a loss but i get to use the armor
don't worry i'll make it all back my grandpa's fucking trillion dollar estate
would you mind selling me this weird fucked up item that i could just put on a shelf
in a bathroom somewhere thank you hey i'm back again i'm thinking about getting a shield too
i'm thinking of throwing the spear out the window you know the one i just bought from you
and then going down my elevator and running out the front door and blocking it with the
shield i mean i i've lived like 600 stories after i think it's possible and i'm gonna make
a youtube video on it and do a slow motion that sounds like a really cool video idea
now that's too expected oh that's fine this is a present from mommy this girl is hard to
sell to let's just go with like let's go with like 103 i'm seeing pretty good on money
i don't know i can do the one more run on the store here furball
um kind of running out items i have so many capes i'm never selling those capes i'm gonna hold
those capes to zero what the garbage wait hold on how are we doing like politically here
all right keep that there let's get the capes look okay here's here's the thing
you want to know my strategy right now here's the strategy there's only capes in the store so
you have to buy one if that's the only thing right i was walking by and i noticed
you had the wife asked me to get some food perfect bread seems about right
any capes um you don't have some food do you you need more food
uh did you eat it before you left oh i screwed it up again oh boy
i was supposed to bring that food back to the wife and i ate it before i left the store
i wouldn't have any food all right time to pay the debt i have enough
should i just like tie the capes together and sell it as a parachute
i mean look if you want to be a good entrepreneur and a good business man
business woman you you adapt those are all two thousand dollars each no capes are boring but
if you tie them together and you make a giant parachute for 10 grand all of a sudden it's
really interesting uh incidentally you are aware that today is the first day of collections
hey what as in pay up or we take your house let's see i have a calendar that i can check
when i'm on a break don't i or in the main menu i bet you yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i knew it was the
day the amount is scheduled to increase every week what what what kind of interest rate do i
have an a scaling interest rate isn't that illegal i have a completely always never-ending
scaling upwards interest rate what the fuck is up with that all right we got capes here
here got it i heard and there was potentially parachutes here is that possible to see them
thank you see my twin brother came in there told me that there were parachutes available
i want one too because that fucking asshole we're like the twix brothers
when he does something cool i do it even cooler he's gonna jump off his roof with this
so i'm gonna do that too that's a good deal oh i thought they were gonna buy you another cape
all right i need to uh i don't have my inventory i have i get the magician staff let's get it
up here all right now i'm just gonna dump this stuff this stuff sucks i'm not gonna buy any
more capes i just look it's debt day hey we're back it's just right i tell you like a whole
family of fucking old twix people i want one too thank you hey some of my brothers came in here
but what they don't understand is i'm the fucking evil one they're all buying capes i'm
gonna buy the staff and right before they all jump off i'm gonna delete with a magical spell
their capes off their backs and they just hit the ground and then i will own the whole old
fucking twix family factory beef bowl oh do you want to sell this my how much what i don't want
that how do i not pay for this i don't it's i don't want this i don't want this it doesn't
sell yeah i'll do it i'll do it for a thousand it yes it's that cheap look i'll
throw in five cents did i just get fucking scammed i think i did i think i just got
scammed i shouldn't have done that i don't want the beef bowl i got let me hold on let's get it up
there chestnuts get the anti-venom up there i got a lot of i'm doing good on money put the shrooms
up here can i upgrade my uh store hey it's me again what else what else do you want me to say
as the fucking old guy what else is there to do hey let me tell you i need some bread for
my twin twix brothers bald if i want some food what would be good
i hear me out on this guys she i sold she i i bought it for a one thousand five one
that take profits when you can i don't know what your goal here was okay
okay six hundred sounds good
thousand dollars in profit just have to sell to the old man you gotta sell to the old man that
has like 10 kilos of gold in his house he just takes a razor and just shaves the top every
day and buys it every once all right i think it's time for bed it's a plus four slime
i'm out of inventory so all we got is you know hold on let's go get a drink
what is it why are adventurers in the pub so often do they all like alcohol that much
well adventurers certainly do enjoy their liquid pleasure but a pub like this also handles
quests for adventures really many of the people here are looking for work isn't that kind of
stuff handled by the adventurers guild the guild does also handle some quests but remember you can
only hire a guild adventurer officially if you possess the guild card of that person assuming
they have one at all therefore places like this tend to offer a different kind of quest
more daily run-of-the-mill business if you will clients do not pay as much as guild
sponsored ones but this sort of place is also far friendlier to rookies however if the
request is too simple or moronic it is likely that no one will even attempt to do it
look the requests are posted up there on the wall let us have a look shall we
let's see please find my lost kitty can i hire someone to stand in a ticket line for me
please kill 10 crows around the garbage dump green item offered can one of you hot studs
wow there's quite a variety well it's true that they are often used as glorified handymen
in a way this sort of thing is a sign of how much adventurers have blended into daily city
life in this city that's true hey actually we should do this quest i mean i'd love to help
someone find their kitty uh no i'm afraid we cannot well anyone can post a request only those
registered with the adventurers guild can legally take on such requests so i'm afraid
we cannot do anything listed here that's a bummer so why do we keep coming here why not
even like old enough to go in here how do we keep getting in the front door
i heard the door open who is it oh it's two children two children well whatever i'm just
gonna go back to cleaning my glass save i'll save oh ten thousand dollars in profit
no my money my money where's my money going ten thousand dollars in debt has been repaid so
this is the payment for the week let me see congratulations well done 30 percent of your
money is now gone i did it i did it i did i did it i worked really hard to delete 35 percent
of my money i doubt i did it so this is it that insolent little plebeian shop which is
for the focus of so much rumor my my my it's so common so dirty so dull how does that little
pro get people to come in i wonder well no matter this is the perfect opportunity
to show that little shrew and this whole city what a truly elegant shop is like
we all get ferries oh you know you don't own that store yet right it belongs to your
parents silence you insolent fairy it'll be mine eventually that's practically the same thing
oh a little shop wrist sit here your day's a number let's see it i'm gonna i'm gonna go
pee wait and i told you to address me as young mistress day nine all right whoa whoa whoa hey
wait what is that something's alive in there colonel my genius astounds even me sometimes
the best way to learn about your foe is direct infiltration after all that's an amazon
box and with strategic espionage ability such as this i can't fail who's under that box
um who's that the interior decoration is as seedy and plebeian as the outside
which means their selection of items will see astounding what could it be what sort of thing
could that filthy little pearl sell perhaps some kind of black and white animal the
ownership of which violates international treaties zebra perhaps the most delicious
apples this side of mar de blanc perhaps one of those books father says i'm too young to read
oh be quiet whoever you are oh i've been found out
could you grab that box kind of looks weird
well then uh oh oh oh oh oh oh honestly i shouldn't be surprised by this
i should have expected a foe as canny as you to break through my otherwise
impenetrable stealth techniques okay this confirms it you are indeed worthy of being
my rival rival oh sorry sorry let me redo that again oh i have failed to introduce myself of
course i am the owner of the monolithic item store chain big bash tim allen
well to be specific i'm the owner's only child and inheritor alouette is my name remember it
i won't everyone around you around me calls me young mistress alouette but you oh my rival
shall have the privilege of calling me lady alouette tim alouette a big bash it is a
massive store chain with a capital stock value of 15 billion picks and a yearly gross profit of
500 billion oh that's a lot i heard the commotion and came to see what was happening but
why are the two of you discussing big bash i'm not really sure interesting you also have a
fairy huh prime alouette prime it's how we get our boxes really it's an amazon thing
yeah yeah what's up oh oh mistress i see your attempt at infiltration failed
but what are you talking about their superior detection ability simply caught me off guard
and overwhelm my cardboard that's all that's a fairy dang this one sure is sharp you got a
problem with that kid i mean you hang out with one too so what's the big deal
hey call me prime you could say i'm alure the mistress's guardian
well i'm resetting this is tier it's nice to meet you yeah real pleasure to meet you too
bookworm dork geek nerd dork are you by chance referring to me
like there's anyone else here i'd call that well the pleasure are all mine then
all right mistress we've introduced ourselves to how about we head on home what are you talking
about i haven't finished introducing half of the fantabalistic amazing incredibleness that is
alouette inheritor of big bash if we stick around for that we'll be here all week come
on now we're going home reset listen and listen well enjoy your happy carefree days as
long as you can but when i am through with you yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah see you guys around
she's doing these little like see what do you think that was all about she's still here that
was not dissimilar to meeting a hurricane in human form no now she's gone all right time to
time to save and time to pee i'll be right back enjoy the music how are you doing so we
got next we've got thirty thousand dollars as you can see here well more than a week
how was the pee the pee was good i just grabbed a little soda all right i need to do some more
adventuring i gotta get this guy a better sword though yeah this inventory is terrible
let me go back here where is her uh store gonna be buy give me like steel sword this
thing is he uses i'm getting it pretty wand bows composite bow practice lance i think i'm just gonna
buy a bunch of equipment and let him have it for very very cheap he has the armor he's got
iron armor he's got iron armband and wooden armband he doesn't have a shield though big
shield he has the hat maybe he could use a helm all right let me i don't want to spend
that much money i'm gonna buy another long sword uh i'm gonna buy i still have a staff
you going into the red no i'll be fine oh he's the girl the little girl wow is that a laugh
or is that a cry hey what's wrong my dolly oh the shoulder has been ripped this is my
favorite anyway can you give that to me for a second okay uh let me see i have a little
thread and a needle in my apron pocket here and loop loop uh don't poke myself hey and done how
does that look you you fixed her yay thank you so much lady you're welcome uh that'll be 60
dollars for materials and 20 dollars for labor and if you don't pay it then i'm coming after
you and your whole family okay then see you in court you're good at sign crafting but you're
fairly deft handed needlework too how about you tier i bet you sew a lot of stuff
uh there is no time for dawdling where to next we're gonna get like some weird exposition here
there's gonna be an entire she would chat go where's the chat did i accidentally close
the chat window i think i did well i'm stupid hey there you guys are hi i got you back
all right i guess fairies aren't very good at using big needles huh
um i don't think so i guess not all right let's go put this inventory up keep the cloak let's get
the steel sword no no no no no long sword and that was the uh i don't know i already i sold
the magician's um catalyst device i need more stuff i need more stuff uh let's go with
tre- tree seed necklace i'll take two of them
adventurer's cape that's an even better that's an even cooler cape
oh this ring's power enhances the wearer's willpower allowing them to shrug off physical
blows thankful wait unthankful statue un and a thankful statue unthankful what somebody
wanted a book too right all right watermelons and let's get a few cherries okay i got
great inventory now by the way i don't even want this shit anymore i don't want it on this i
don't want it on the shelf now i got good inventory let me let me get rid of this other crap
by the way i need to do a dungeon run i will i will all right we got let's get what do
we want in the window let's get the necklace in the window let's get the adventurer's cape
in the window 5200 fucking bucks thankful statue back scratcher a couple of books
no i want the books over here no the books can be over here i want the food on the left
okay then insect wrap food get the watermelon and the cherries
i think that's pretty good although maybe i want the thankful statue up here
i think that's fine let's go let's make some money
i've been looking for one of these cherry 1100 profit welcome long sword
those don't come cheap pretty good deal thank you those are hard to get
piece of armor you already have armor he's wearing iron armor right now
okay wait cape is armor no no it's not cape's not armor is armor is iron armor
leather armor i mean in incomplete yes in literal terms you'd be correct but not in
the literal sense of this game you want the necklace thousand bucks should i just go
absolutely fucking crazy and just see if i can get 2000
i started ridiculous and brought it down to an even more ridiculous than it because that was the
first number was fake he got your bluff call when she died my grandmother told me to sell
this off if i ever got into trouble okay so uh i'll give it to you for 900
your grandmother left you a candy apple that's not that's not a great inheritance my husband
had this hidden in his den i'll give you i'll give you 500 bucks for it
six six fifties all i'm willing to part with here no it's not worth talking to you either i
can't sell those would you sell this to me finally the cape all the capes are gone
i did it i made like 100 of my money back with all those capes everybody told me i was
dumb you gotta do the long con okay what else do i have anymore candy apple up there i want
this steel sword i really really really want to give that i want him to buy it
have fun with the thirty thousand dollar payment yeah it's like next week
i got plenty of time you want the unthankful statue 135
up candy apple you know what i thought about it i really want it back
in the green i'm probably going to be in the green for the day all right here we go
i really don't want to sell this but i don't want to buy this oh we both can agree on that
oh that's pretty good deal 50 off the necklace
it's a bit expensive yeah you're right 125 1250
week
everybody else
cherries 1200 just a little bit less 1179 what am i saying chewy minus 60 it's all right i but
i have that i spent like 16 or 17 thousand dollars news the price of candy has increased
the price of candy do i have candy oh that was a news flash important events are reported for
everyone in the city it's the twix brothers their stunt was a success all right uh that one
was a sudden jump in candy prices you're buying or selling candy pay close attention
sudden scarcity has driven the price of candy up in general that means that prices will
roughly double because like all the twix guys did the stunt yeah and the guy with the magic
wand i'm telling you he deleted all their capes finally my friend candy that sell for 300 may
now sell for 600 i'll buy all the candy in the city and keep it for myself maybe i'll share
or sell a little but it is candy ahem no prices will stabilize after some time
nobody can say for how long for once however you have hit upon a good point while it can be hard
to predict price fluctuations if you keep a fairly wide variety of stock handy it's possible
to take advantage of a situation like this and make money you can also try to take the
advantage of the situation after news comes in of course but it's harder to really make
a profit that way it's complicated i'm hungry it's really not that hard of a concept to
understand ah the news again watch carefully this information could be vital louis the swordsman
bounced check at local cafe now on the lamb louis doesn't have any money that's vital news
imagine if you turned on the news and they just talked about how
some random person couldn't pay for something i'll tell you though if that's your news
things are probably going pretty well wherever you are free louis oh wait wait wait come here
store atmosphere uh-oh we're getting we're getting a little bit more further to the
to the left side here merchant level uh i can get more item more items at level four
uh level five is what was it come here
okay fusion rank one at this level you may fuse items what do i have any candy
no no candy here no i put the watermelon up there should i just stockpile cherries
something new i somebody's gonna buy this like fucking five thousand dollar statue
put it up there instead of the steel all right let's go
bread i came and did not i came here to sell this did he say sell or buy yeah what should i pay
okay i don't want the bread is there like a just decline 2900 2600
somebody take that statue looking for something do you have some food i do i have
you what you're kind of a pain in the ass to sell to though cherry
uh louis uh louis you don't have any money it is louis though should i help louis out
all right louis i'm gonna help you out here
oh
louis my dungeon guy i have to take care of the dungeon guy
all right i need to go speaking of dungeon i need to do it now i think i'm just gonna
give him the sword if he's too stupid to try to get it from me you're aiding a known
criminal pick the items you wish to bring with you um can i just take the sword will he
equip it how do i equip this he'll just do it okay all right louis let's go jade way we're
gonna go down floor six to ten so you got it on right yeah he's got the steel he's got all
right now that was three thousand dollars louis you better put it to good use and can you
learn something else besides regular swing this thing actually does a shitload of damage
don't fuck this up louis
i need treasure louis find it no i don't want that mushroom suck i've gotten to the point
in ow i've gotten to the point in diablo 2 where i don't even pick up any blues or
gray or white i don't pick any of those up anymore if it's not yellow letters on the
ground i'm just going to run over it well i was just not paying attention
these little rabbits are so annoying just put them up against the wall
next slide please oh we've dropped in frame whoa whoa who's that who's this this person's
hmm hello oh yes can i help you i think that might be my line are you looking for something
i'd be happy to help if you are
i'm lost can you perhaps tell me where i am let's give her wrong directions where you are
and here that could be a problem these dungeons alter their shape when a person
enters i'm afraid that giving you your precise current location is not possible
oh i've entered a dungeon then how surprising what how can you i was just on my way home from
hmm wow in some ways i'm kind of in awe how in the name of heaven do you get so lost as to
end up in a dungeon how indeed i too am at a loss well bye given how lost you seem to be
i hope the trees don't start shaking what should i do now though to begin with i would recommend
searching for a floor of the dungeon with a large red door that will allow you to
exit the dungeon really why thank you miss fairy you are very kind be careful farewell
well that was unexpected i hope she gets home okay she's gone
well what did you leave back here did you even open this up
a rotten carrot a shell necklace is it a ghost i don't think it's is it a ghost
whatever i don't need it i got thrown rocks
no it's a bomb
come on louis what's that unidentified cool one chain what's that mean what does that mean
you didn't get hit once
so floor 10 i think we're gonna end up right one damage please
another necklace
uh don't want it i don't care about the play-doh looking thing
still alive what is it oh another bomb well they get hurt by that
the blast radius no of course not
what's that is that a lizard on a stick charred lizard what the hell
this is fluffy i got room for it
oh eat lizard eat lizard i'll eat the lizard if i need to i don't need to do now
the bees drop good shit new skill uh what the fuck just happened did twitch was it twitch
that was weird did twitch just go down because i was still in the chat room
my internet wasn't like out that was weird because i was still seeing everybody's in the chat
well um welcome back hey welcome to a new stream did anybody else turn off
did any other like other streamers turn off
no just us well don't ask me what the hell that was because everything was it was fine
there was like no problems at all
some other people did too
well if we're good we're good right what is that egg toast i i'm not even kidding around
that's like one of my favorite breakfasts in the world i'm not gonna sell that
i'm gonna keep that for dentist bib french toast is better don't you're gonna make me
actually upset french toast is not better than dropped egg on top i'm it's it's not
it is oh my god it's not it's not at all it is so much worse i don't know why everybody
wants to make what's what's with the sweetness stuff the breakfast cereal i understand i don't
want like this sweetness no i want like savory bacon crunchy salty dipping your bread and soggy
soaking it up with eggs and then frying it on the skillet and adding a bunch of
powdered sugar and syrup on it i'm not a fan i'm gonna get by every single one of these
uh no i'm kidding french toast is actually really good french toast is really good um if it's made
uh with enough backtracking you know with french toast is made with enough unpopular
opinions to then backtrack um well i'm getting a lot of um getting a lot of random items
this goodie level 11 backpedaling backtracking what did i say backtracking
close it up
come here you stupid golfer
that felt good eat lizard no what did i just teleport down where did i go
i'm i want to see what the boss is i'm looking forward to the boss don't pick up slimes
they're not even worth picking up oh what's that
i wonder how many floors are down here i missed a shark fin oh shit did i i'll get it i'll get
it don't worry got it where was it up here i can wrap around what is it over here
where's over
one frame are we getting oofed i don't know that's weird there's the shark fin hey i'll take it
the screen's frozen but i can hear him hello usually i can tell when it's a cox problem
because my all my internet will get fucked up i'll look over and chat won't even be working
so maybe this is like a twitch ingest server problem i don't know
if it is it is if it isn't it isn't floor 10 time for a boss twitch is having indigestion
yeah it's a giant rat with a crowbar okay i gotta be careful because it looks like he
this is such an awesome created character i feel like this is a wrestling character
oh that hurt i'm gonna have to eat the lizard soon holy shit he's
what is he doing what did he just do is he what does he just eat something
oh he's eating the mushrooms and falling down don't let him eat the red ones that's probably
health right if i were a video game the purple ones would be the poisonous ones
oh let's see if that theory's correct nice crit double crit triple crit that's pretty damn good
not dead oh no that was his last breath he set up to fall back down
all right what did i get anything even worth taking here ingredients
agree i got some i got some unidentified stuff and some things
let's see what we got charred lizard furball insect trap chocolate bar egg toast
shark fin so what the hell was it was it a bunch of insect traps
furball cha what was it slime raincoat these items are terrible it looks like nobody's here
that bar is really not very good then all right down for bed
holy shit they would take 20 subs men of character are currently seeking out rusty daggers
help conserve water turn that faucet off when brushing your teeth rusty dagger i i can get a
rusty dagger buy rusty dagger how much is it just should i buy like a few of them all right
fusion the product that this fusion will be a mystery until you attempt it so rank fusion
resolve rank one dagger rank one staff magician staff easy rank one what rank one bracelet
i need five insect traps rank one necklace should i go for it takes a lizard in the shell
i'm gonna do it a necklace with a magical blue stone who knows what a stone this could do for
you ten thousand four hundred dollars holy shit uh but cyanide zero gave 20 community subs
thank you so much for the huge amount of subs that is a shit load so hold on long
sword and i don't i don't okay i don't have all the ingredients for these what do i know how to do
insect trap an iron armband is the one that i can do and it's a bracelet i need five insect
traps and an armband let's get it five insect traps you got those here you got iron armbands
here i know you do don't you yes you do how many you got let's just get one and then
i have to go to the market food medicines flooring wallpaper carpets what the fuck is
all this should get more daggers this is stupid i'll get five more should i sell this thing for
like 15 000 holy shit i can sell this thing for like 20 000 get that no get it in the
window egg toast is mine all right let's go
what do you need i'd like some food please i got something for you i got uh
625 lower no i can't go lower only sell the necklace to the old man
let's hope that's what he wants i'd like a rusty dagger please i want food take candy instead
somebody buy that necklace i don't even want you to have this because
i have to use that i don't use a rusty dagger why is he even buying this somebody
buy somebody buy the necklace put a raincoat up there no um put that necklace up there too
well yeah why would i put the cheaper necklace next to the more expensive necklace
is it really that expensive madness hey are you sure all right 130
i can't buy that price have i ran grandpa dry already take a look at that necklace come on
this guy just takes anything i tell him so i'm back over the right somebody buy it
get the daggers out there nobody wants nobody wants a back scratcher nobody wants a book
they just want the daggers take them all right sell
me i would like a dagger 500 i need to try to go higher on that dude
i need some food i can help you out there
140 fork it over 650
no i'm not gonna sell the egg that's mine
okay you want clothes all right here 110 just get it out of my store
all daggers are going for 500 are you not even trying to make money
yes i am what do you mean i'm not even trying he's i'm gonna make it to the end of the week
all right the price of shields has decreased today's saucepan index 20 shields
oh you better believe i'm going to buy a bunch of shields right now oh look at this
wouldn't you i'm gonna buy like common shield like all right i'm good shield speculation
yes no something's wrong with louis i think louis may have gotten hit in the head too
hard down the dungeon let's go ask why do i get the feeling that i would much rather
not get involved louis hello oh receipt receipt like a store receipt oh receipt
tear what's up what are you doing wandering around here oh well i got hungry so i decided
to take a look and see if i could find some edible grasses or herbs or something eating
grass i don't have any money or anything and i keep bouncing checks so i read on the internet
that you could eat grass and it was a super food i'm not so sure which of these are edible
you see louis if you eat that you'll blow up your stomach that's funny it is they taste best
if you clean them now the plants with the soft leaves at the east end of the plaza those
taste the best you should try them i eat grass too why do you know so much about this
thanks a ton receipt i owe you again no problem remember to wash what you find
why do i feel as though that is the least of his concerns chapel adventures guild no not yet
not yet i need to make i gotta make some money oh fuck no shields at price it down
the prices are down i'm gonna wait i'm gonna hold those until i gotta make a big sale here
let's see if we can get away with uh 525
all right 500 500 don't 500 sell higher they won't i can't oh this is important
6 000 6 000 no no like 5800 yes no not higher i need to make this money
if he walks away i don't pay my debt and i lose the game is this really for sale yes
it is 500 bucks oh shut up i got this like mooch s friend the price of daggers has decreased
the price of candy has normalized sell sell sell but no take them off the market
i'm gonna go get it no i can't buy any more things i know i can't buy any i have three days
to make like ten thousand dollars we gotta go into the dungeon or something we gotta go
to the dungeon i really don't want to lose it but i have to sell the egg toast
come on in there it is shark fin come on grandpa 2600 a little bit lower 20 24
or for 2450 good sale a lot of people in here
why do i always want stuff like this when i'm broke i don't know but you're obviously not
going to pay me what i want for it so you might that's the same one when she died my
grandmother told me to sell this off if i ever got into trouble it's the it's the my grandma
died please take a food item from me look all the best i can do is fucking full 100 man i don't
want it do you have a bracelet i don't have a bracelet i just sold it to this stupid
motherfucker that has three of them come on come on little lady you got a hat i don't think i
have a hat either i don't have a hat fuck i need five grand statue i think this might sell
how much i don't want your gross food holy shit he actually did it would you take this
i don't want it why i have three days to pay off my debt and i'm taking on more
the price of long swords has decreased the rusty daggers boom has ended beware of theft
while in the market do i have long swords sell this i have to i louis needs this
i gotta get rid of this food shark fin shark fin no one's buying this people buy the shark fins
no one's buying the necklace either let's go
and of course you're selling this when i'm broke you can't afford this louis so stop
coming in here that's all right that's more than i i got it i got what i needed that's it
he's eating luxury food well he's buying shark fin he's buying he's buying like foie gras
the price of weapons has decreased the price of shields has normalized hold on wait
so swords i need to go buy some more swords let's get the shields up there big shield
i am now a shield establishment all right let's go go buy that book
not yet i don't have any bracelets no i'm sorry get lost i'm not no i'm not going to
buy anything else bingo shields 1500 all right yam i just need to get rid of it i don't care 110
percent good one more big sale and it's it i got oh damn 48 defense you need this
i did it and he has it now
oh
mom asked me to sell this housewives with new money management skills are on a precious metals
bender the price of daggers has normalized several incidents with fake high-class
restaurants have left diners uncertain buy gold i don't have i don't have any gold
let's get a book out there too
it's beef time yeah i got good food here change walls thin layers of lacquer painted a top one
another for a smooth finish the beauty is in the color blending did i do it that's what i
currently own get rid of the shield inventory you still want to break i don't have any
bracelets you come in every day i'd like a hat i don't have hats either
i thought you didn't have any money invest in hats and bracelets
oh we're gonna get rid of our last cape 2500 finally took a few months but i got rid of all
capes i got some left over here do you have a book it's called it's an errand
i i do have a book i'll take that 700 bucks
she's not gonna do it did you have a book yeah we have one um just give her the book
two days give me a bracelet merchant skilled bracelet although they're like look at these
look at how cheap these swords are look at all these cheap how cheap all this is
oh how much do i have left not enough i have enough for sturdy glove all right bracelet
okay stop a hat i need a hat sure but don't listen keep buying the sky is the limit if
you don't give a shit well i need to pay thirty thousand dollars in two days the price
of heavy armor has decreased oh don't keep doing this the price of swords has normalized
i told you i should have done what i did i told you wait what oh because all weapons prices are
done still worth it it's still worth it i'm not gonna sell it all right i got what everybody
needs let's go put let's get a raincoat over here holy shit you actually want this
you want the thankful statue fifty let's let's try to get something let's try to get six
grand for this cut the loss into five grand i think five thousand fifty five hundred
fifty two hundred is probably safer fifty one ninety nine yes that was a big that's a big one
oh this month is tight but i really want that shield you have a better shield
what's he doing with all this stuff i guess if you're gonna pay me for it then i'll take
it fine you have one of these it's a lucky day for both of us egg toast it's gonna take
a lot for me to part with the egg toast you're killing me got everybody wants the
egg toast it's good shit cherries cherries sell very easily at 1200 all right time for bed
that's 13 600
food is decreased weapons have normalized good let's get some swords out here
anything else i need up here i'm gonna keep one of these sturdy gloves
not bad i could buy food but when it's when's judgment day tomorrow
oh me thank you miss me improve the story down i'm gonna go buy cooler stuff
all right sturdy glove
now he's got a better glove
how much is that dagger 500 what do you need you have a bracelet i do have a bracelet
it's spiked armband you can backhand somebody with this thing that'll be 1300
oh that'll be uh-oh 1200 uh-oh for has increased the value of things boom has ended
armor do i have armor price oh robes i don't care about that little girl anymore
let's get armor this is all this is armor go all right i'm gonna go buy just the
shittiest bracelet i can find give me a bracelet am i actually gonna go to the store
and buy a more an expensive bracelet to buy why would i do that no i'm not gonna do that
big sis wait you walk so fast tier is something wrong i know it's nothing
you're looking at those sisters hey tier how do you think people see us
how do do you think we look like sisters given that i'm a fairy i rather doubt that
oh right still if we did i'd be kind of happy well since i'm bigger i'd be the big
sister right your logic as always is breathtaking yeah i guess you would be the big sister
but that'd be really nice too right sis i'm gonna sell my shares in this company i think
i'm out of here you're breathtaking hey wait for me what's going on in the market oh hi
how are you out shopping oh hello yes i was just looking for some ingredients for lunch
it's such a selection though i can't make up my mind it's kind of amazing isn't it you
can turn one thing into a lot of dishes or a lot of things into one dish it's sort of like magic
the way cooking changes stuff i never thought about that way you're adorable speaking of
culinary magic have you ever heard of the legendary chef legendary who's it apparently
there is a chef who takes the worst ingredients and turns them into food that can delight anyone
you know things like slime liver salad skeleton bones souffle jello volcano crab cakes things like
that that's amazing i guess i have to wonder if it's actually edible though
food is cheap right is the great is the great candy price increase of uh look at this this
is cheap shit right now watermelons this is so cheap i'm stocking up how much do i have
40 000 i don't think i can this is rent money no it's not all right let's go it's 30 000 i'm
good it's not gonna rot that's not how this game works we're open for business
oh you want the armband yeah prices are skyrocketing on those
1500 oh i like a raincoat that'll be 500 okay that was 166 percent
you want the store the steel sword make it a lot of good sales here
do i have a scarf i don't have a scarf i could have sold the 200 percent what the fuck
you want the magic wand that'll be that'll be 4500 bucks
all right you got me 4200 i made it all back shields has increased yes more shields
look what i got i have shields quite a bit of this is not going to sell no one's gonna buy
this
no don't sell man put the long sword out there i hate the voice should i want to turn the voice down
oh
i don't have a scarf back to bed shield oh boy what's that 750 dollars please
oh wow that you can that's insane are you serious
that is the definition of a sucker that a more than 200 percent increase
i got 42 grand price of heavy armor has increased
food is normalized so we can put some food out there
let's get uh what should i get out there candy apple
candy apple with the shield
uh we're gonna buy this hat yeah for 650 bucks
oh my god okay you gotta follow those trends
that was a joke right yeah it was i was just kidding it's actually 200
i'd like a trap that's not a treasure oh that's not classified as a treasure
damn it not what i wanted jesus settle down long swords has decreased
armor is normalized all right we'll get this out of here let's get some candy apple out here
fish cherry candy apple all right i want to bow i want to make the store cooler
what do i go for this carpets the most basic of carpets and the standard by which all of
us are judged green carpet the carpet is soft counters wooden counter legendary counter
lineup items use it as a desk even hide things in certain compartments legendary wallpaper
starry wallpaper a romantic wallpaper that simulates a starry sky enjoy that feeling of
a vacation yeah resort i want the resort wallpaper stone floor tile floor brick floor
uh tile very easy to clean very popular with city dwellers and shopkeepers tiles okay what's
that i got money i'm good i got money it's 30 000 i got 39 so let's get oh i can't hold on
change the wall resort oh cool how do i change the ground is there how do i change the tile
hey but that's much cooler people are gonna like this now what do you think
you lack should i put the tiles up there to sell legendary counter for sale green carpet for sale
let's go you need a hat i don't have any i can't ask for something you don't have after all
it's true do i really have no talent no you have plenty of talent don't
candy apple those things i don't think i've ever put an offer in for a candy apple and
people haven't taken it i thought that was the tile it's like why that's not even for sale
is that even out anywhere how does he know i have this i got a food up maybe
go lower 800 food prices are up are they really not i can't buy to sell this
790 even stuff like this sells what was that what was like a backhanded insult
i feel like this guy's think i can get away with it yes daggers has decreased
and shields has normalized wasn't i supposed to pay my debt today oh it is it's the end of the
day okay excuse me i should i can still sell the shield this is fine all right last little
bit before the end of the day here candy apple let's be let's be really really rude
about this 150 just a little less so you know i could probably get away with one like one like
45 you think damn it i found a i found a ham sandwich out in the trash is where you found
this i found a ham sandwich do you want to buy it from me this is expensive um a thousand
thousand come on i kind of want the sandwich 1500
it's a wild ham sandwich do you have any food
yes i do i have a 3400 dollar ham sandwich yes instant profit feels pretty good
want this shield 1600 a little lower you're right i could do 145 50
one more this is nice yes it is less i can't bet you know what i got it for so cheap
2400 almost level seven come on level seven i did it anybody else candy apple
that's too it that's apparently that's way too expensive we'll do
1999 this is something my grandmother treasured this guy was the same yam i do keep getting yammed
nice why is everybody's grandma in the game so lame it's a good question
i have to be careful here now because over the course of the next week this is probably
going to be 60 to 70 thousand dollars this is the payment for the week congratulations well done i
have officially received your payment for this week let us continue to work hard next week
i did it all right 50 grand 60 grand probably maybe 70 grand total all right gonna work hard
today too capitalism ho what's that girl doing outside the shop she's out just kind
of staring into the shop and she has a tattoo on her head okay does she want to come inside maybe
or are windows that gripping well smile receipt come on smile look friendly i just imagine a
forced teeth smile okay what should i do here call police please tell me you have not reached
the point where your face is frozen in a vapid smile for all eternity there's a girl
curious about the inside and she's looking scanning the items yeah we got a neighborhood
watch down here i'll just come and arrest you the shop so i try to give her my best come in
and buy lots of stuff smile she's not there anymore citizens of rest so i am terrifying you
say really terrifying is that smile you think yeah you're a terror can we just stop staring
at each other what did i do wrong now given how well you're doing i think it's time i
explained how to take an order in advance customers have simply put purchasing items
from us immediately with an advanced order however a customer will let us know what they
want and return in a set number of days to pick up the items obviously not every customer
will want to do this but if a customer tells you that they want something in so many days
it's an advanced order okay so i have to make sure i have it here it's pre-orders if they
simply wanted the items now they would purchase the items now the date is based on what is
convenient for the customer not you so if they want an item and say three days you must give
it to them then and remember we must be open to actually sell an item to someone so make
sure the store is open that day or we cannot fill the order okay it's too complex no i get
i understand this works people use advanced orders to purchase multiple items at once
it is an excellent chance to sell many items in one go try to fill as many as you can see
she said it was complicated i said it was fun all right let's go let's get rid of this actually
no i'm gonna hold on to the food there's gonna be a food surge i just know it somebody will
buy this fucking dumb necklace eventually get it in the window so how much am i how much do i owe
80 000 next week i knew it was gonna be hovering around there somewhere
there's a lot that is a lot okay i'm gonna i think i'm gonna go adventure
i think it's time to go down steel sword anything else i can take here
uh i could take some just the bread just in case you need i need to eat it
that's good so now we're gonna go to floor 11 to 15 so what's other equip items yes
so i'm looking for the
play-doh snake things i need like five of those play-doh green play-doh snake thingies
what what all right i just noticed somebody linked the total and immediately a bunch of
manipulators just did i didn't even do anything see that manipulation in real time that's market
manipulation you motherfuckers can go into jail for that this game is pretty fun i like this game
do i get to have anybody else besides louis tell me if i miss any items no go back around
this way
i mean i guess you know i i could just go down as fast as i possibly can
to try boots leather boots
don't be so stupid here
okay i thought that was an npc
oops can i block is there a way to hold the shield up i guess not
you have to parry well that would be shocking oh you auto block from the front okay that's
good enough
stupid rocks
uh kind of an odd random encounter yeah that was that actually you're right that was a sharp
nato all right don't get sloppy here because i don't have a way to heal i have to level up
the heal or eat the bread and i brought one bread all right i'm gonna have to eat it
no i i think i could probably level up before that
more bread really no play-doh snake things
uh
can i buy those from anybody
fish wheel it's not fish wheel what is everything that i i get hit by or die to have to be a
wheel
yes yes yes yes mushroom wheel whatever you say i'll take all your words for it
but at least a wheel something good no that shit sucks i think i'm just gonna throw
those in the trash i'm just gonna sell them and merchant not even on my in my store
stuff not even worth picking up
windbreaker
no i don't pick that up i don't pick up the shitty toupee
damn it
all right candy i'll take it all right i got hit by fish wheel but he died to fish wheel
make fun of him instead
mom's making cookies for the best yeah the best ice cream i've ever had
yeah mom's making cookies from basket robbins is the best thing i've ever eaten in my whole life
that tweet kept me up all night why because my one real tweet in three or four months is a
shit post it kept me up at night
explain it what's there to explain there's nothing i don't have to explain anything
just know that the ice cream mom's making cookies from basket robbins this is all you
need to know is without question the best ice cream i have ever had in my life i couldn't
stop that one i tried i couldn't i could i could i could i tried to put my hand up to mute but i
couldn't i'm excuse me do that i'm sorry did i miss something up here greedy goblin streamer
sells out to ice cream company eat mom's making cookies ice find a basket robbins and go eat
there go have the mom's making cookies ice cream and come back and talk to me
tell me that i was wrong i want you to i want you to prove me wrong i want you to go there
i want you to have it and then i want you to tell me that i was wrong i'm ready to debate
you i'm ready to hear it it's i'm just telling you i got destroyed in this debate
we've even started debating i haven't debated anybody on this hold on hold on this is a
tricky poll here there's one other ice cream that i think i've ever had that reaction to
and i don't agree with it anymore my opinion has changed um the birthday cake ice cream from
cold stone used to be it was just i couldn't handle it it was too good i need to get rid
of some stuff hold on but i my tastes have changed i don't believe that anymore
it's like too sweet it's too much for me now
uh
lemon basil ice cream is also that's very good too but i wouldn't call that the best ice
cream i've ever had in my life i would call that a very substantially good ice cream
all right 14 almost at 15 getting there
can't care anymore it's not worth is it worth throwing something else away from candy
yeah moose tracks no moose track moose track doesn't have shit on mom's making cookies
and i know i know that that might be your favorite moose tracks might be your favorite
but that means you haven't had mom's making cookies that's what it means that's all right i
know that that's i know that's what happened uh half baked used to be my favorite ice cream
from ben and jerry's i was so uninformed
mom's making cookies is cookies inside of a cookie dough flavored ice cream with
cookie dough chunks inside of it as well it is a cookie dough flavored ice cream
do you understand you need to think about this you have to understand this
yeah
i don't know how they did it i don't know how they do it i don't know what kind of i don't know
what kind of like flavor chemical they put into this i don't know but it's insanely good
so much so that i bought like the i bought like the three pound tub of it yes i did
i didn't just go there and have it i went there and had it and freaked out and said i
want to buy like the four pound tub prove it okay yeah i i can actually prove that
like i bought i bought like the tub
i'm not gonna no no no more food shit no i'm not doing any more food streams
no no i'm not doing food no food shit
go back for the yam hold on can i just throw this away
i can't throw his stuff away throw this away eat the bread pick up the cherry
and pick up the yam get rid of that stupid windbreaker
what's wrong with the windbreaker don't they sell sell him a better sword he won't buy a
better sword he keeps coming in getting wristbands oh it's a helmet it's wooden
we're almost 15 floors down and you're gonna give me a wooden helmet
oh
no i don't want the toupee
mom's making cookies the name sucks it should look like it's making cookies all right you have
me there mom's making cookies with you know making cookies not making it's mom's making
cookies no just making just making cookies
see that's people see the name and they go all right that sounds like
shit that's a gimmick damn it i was trying to go this way i missed twice
can i review it i've already just i just reviewed it i just told you it's the best
ice cream i've ever had and i told you what was in it what else is for me to review
do it while eating it you're i already know what it tastes like uh oh this is the lowest floor of
the dungeon not precisely while we cannot currently proceed any further i strongly
suspect that we can go even deeper next time am i getting hard locked out because i was doing
too well the dungeons change shape every time someone enters them some theorize that they
adapt the strength of those who enter that is what happened and refer to it as the living
dungeon phenomenon okay so what's in the chest i wonder if the dungeon gets bored if it's alone
so that would make the people who are foolish enough to enter a place like this to play things
of the underworld hey i see i like the way you'd think girl who's there it's me no it's
it's me even names charms the lady thief thief thief so your treasure is valuables and
assorted shiny bits i'll be taking them if you please we won't let you always the way
well then in that case looks like it's time to cut some fools
oh shit this guy sucks why do we have to bring like the jobber
okay you see can i eat oh yes i can can
good thing i can estus
oh oh oh you're getting mortal combated now sweep the leg
and a crit to end it what's that there's a heart scarf right there oh frigging fragging
ow yosemite sam there are only two characters in the history of all media that have done
uh friggin fraggin and that is yosemite sam and uh what's earl from home alone what's his name
joe pesci not earl what's his name joe pesci harry that's right harry from home alone and
yosemite sam are the only two people that are allowed to do that miss are you okay i'm
mortally wounded i can see the far shore i can see oh i'm kidding if you get this worried about
every burke who tries to slit your throat and take your lucre oh friggin fraggin fraggin
friggin fraggin racha fragile racha fragile fragile friggin fraggin hey you really are
hurt here take this wound ointment what the did you have that on you this entire time
sorry you two appear oddballs you know that believe me she's the only one only round strange
object currently present please do not assume that both of us are nearly so foolish really seems
to me like the two two make a good pair well then young ladies i should scamper it since i've
been beaten like a mutt enjoy your treasure you earned it wait i'm receipt and this is
we live at 222 we have an item shop at the top of the hill in town called receipt here
you should stop by i should huh i'll keep that in mind see you kids later goodbye char yeah see
you kids later bunch of like little dumb girls by the way i'm 12 you're nine i'm so old okay
goodbye the lady thief huh she was kind of cool hey are you jealous absolutely not oh she's so
cool hand knit muffler oh i gotta get in there we turn around he's like bleeding out
i did everything i could to protect everybody uh let's get rid of the bunch of the raincoat
should i throw the raincoat away what's the cheapest thing i have here it's either the
raincoat i need the insect trap with the candy just eat the candy
oh a pot very odd vase nice let's get out of here i might put one three thousand dollars all
right very cool let's go back to the shop uh i have to pee again so we're gonna do another
go pee scenario because i'm drinking soda speaking of home alone i'm the kid in home
alone that drinks the soda and pisses the bed i'll be right back where are we at we are
somebody said this is i'm getting an animal crossing vibe from this uh i agree except we're
playing as the bad guy in animal crossing all right uh what do i got clear p yeah like
two clear i gotta slow down what i want to do wooden helm
whoa three thousand bucks leather boots get those up there too very
twenty one thousand dollars um i got a lot of expensive stuff i'm gonna dump all this other
crap though the bat wings are worth some money how many insect traps do i need i need five right
store atmosphere whoa we somehow got down into the dark and in the middle
thank you classy banana for the 10 community subs subs coming in hot i can't even touch them
they're too hot they just came out of the oven thank you classy banana no orders but thanks a
lot appreciate it never mind uh can i change the walls direct me to see my hold on merchant
level level seven chain all right here we go i gotta be level eight and level nine to change
the floors oh my god um so there's a lot to do in this game it seems uh germa wide about
the clown car five community subs thank you and soft 33 10 community subs thank you to the
both of you for your amazing contributions thank you subs rolling in you oh it's her
not bad this is a pretty nice looking place um oh it's the let's her it's the lady i forgot about
you you're not gonna steal shit all right you know is it really so kosher for an employee
to give a customer a face like that thought a smile was the basis for customer satisfaction
oh for a normal customer that's completely true for someone who openly attempted to murder
us however this is the only face i have to show well it looks like she's got a different
idea um we're doing this in the middle of all the customers oh yay charm welcome i'm so glad
you came yeah well i kept wondering about this place nice store you have here thank you make
yourself at home receipt see i see all too clearly thank you that receipts a good girl
nice trusting honest don't you agree of course i do you don't need to tell me that
who gives a shit about any of this are you gonna buy something or not you annoying motherfucker i
guess not thanks for wasting a full hour of my time i got customers sprawled through this
whole place and one of them wants 21 cents 31 cents and leave now you want a helmet
oh that's a little too much i'm not gonna no i'm not gonna sell this to you for
yeah please don't i gotta eat you know
oh i'm gonna start with five grand
now i'll bring it down to four thousand forty two hundred oh look who it is
is how much for this well for you that's 2000 less than what i thought i have to pay what
could have sold for more it's this lady it pains me to part with this but for your sake
i'll sell it to you i don't i don't want your dumb like cotton candy filled crouton please
i i pretty much took that for free my grandchild's been pestering me to get a
treasure where's it now 21 000 um 30 000 i could probably get 30 000 is that too much
how about 20 like 25 25 000 i don't have that kind of money shit 22 000 20 000 18
i mean where how when am i gonna sell this 22 no no no no what do you mean no don't sell low
but i wouldn't be able to sell this 20 i'm gonna say 22 no he's not gonna buy it i'm gonna sell
that thing for like 15 grand sorry i still made some money let's get let's get the
windbreaker out there
welcome what can i we're getting all these other characters now
yeah that girl who's hanging out near the windows early staying glassed yayness
i'm glad you came in what can i get you arma oh is that your name so is that like miss
arma like a last name or miss arma negative arma so you're saying just call me arma then
affirmative well i'm receipt nice to meet you arma receipt yep state the purpose of this
facility the purpose of uh okay to start with i'm sorry i blacked out there for a minute
how long is it have i still here how long was i out for um so you buy and sell items here
a material distribution center understood unity precision i'm the best car in heartstone
uh material uh yeah okay so what do you want i am taking this object then
geek wait no you can't just take things what are you doing get back here
there is a problem well if you want to have something uh distributed you got to pay me
money money term unidentified elaborate i need to explain money yikes i better start all over
then so uh how do i explain what money is well the money we use is referred to as pics oh
um i'm i'm i don't know what's going i think i have to go to a doctor
i don't that's not normal right that shouldn't be happening uh money money yeah okay do you
have a car do you have a car i think this is not normal oh this is happening more than
i thought it was gonna happen understood i currently lack money and am therefore unable
to perform shopping come back sometime that was exhausting i hope she does come back
who the fuck are you oh oh yeah that's a other fairy how much is this selling for how about a
good 550 i don't care what you think or smell is that really that much money
like a bandit bye bandit hey you know auto's name was going to be bandit i'd like this
you're back all right this the last time i did five grand it came down let's do four grand
or 3,800 38 36 37 38 what this is like a rare fucking item this is a rare dungeon item
this lady's too cheap 33 i didn't get scammed
how much of the cherries they're all the cherries they're 1,100
welcome this place all fish is 1,200
be back i would like some food i just sold you some but you know
we got baked yams candy uh let's go with the baked yams
how's that absolutely how about uh it's 20 2,200 to baked yams
that's a pretty good couple of sales
i need 80,000 bucks
what's up scam the yam scam scam yam
oh price of shields i think i have a few of those left don't i did i sell all the shields
shit hey hey hey come on in welcome to receipt here oh this place isn't nearly as nice as i
thought it would be can these people really get me what i need excuse me well i've got no choice
god keeps riding forward you there go fetch the owner of this place i have business with him
the owner well you're looking at her what can i do for you surely you're joking don't waste
my time girl hot no really i'm the owner can i help you uh sir you dare make a fool out
of me you must think i'm just some idiot kid no i uh you expect me to believe someone as short
as you owns this establishment stop playing with me and bring me the new owner now
shut up i am the owner really what in the world is going on here why are you shouting
at a customer dear listen he's being oh murder some kind of problem i assume
a fairy interesting not what i expected pardon physically slight and at a disadvantage against
larger creatures but innately talented at administration and management quite possibly
the only non-human race to easily adapt to human culture by utilizing their unique talent
in other words you you must be the proprietor madame fairy good day i apologize for having to
raise my voice at your servant oh well i don't hang on just a second it's a pleasure to meet
you madame fairy kai you is my name and i am a magician by trade and i need to place an
order for some regents an item order oh very well what can i get you i require three items
specifically a charred lizard a batwing and slime litter i only need one of each there's no need
for a precise deadline but obviously the sooner you can provide them the better it will be for
everyone can i assume you'll take the order naturally we shall obtain what you need as soon
as we can marvelous well then if you'll excuse me uh you know i uh yes you look look don't
cause your boss trouble all right pretending to be the owner like that will only make you look
foolish what i am the owner now there there is no need to get angry about this simple mistake
nothing more if it's so simple then why do you look so happy about it you clearly
misunderstand me yes clearly i haven't i gotta take them with that stuff off the shelf
all right you want the fish 13 on it thank you thank you uh thank you thank you oh hi welcome
i'll lower myself to buying something from you a hat i just like swing a piece of plywood out
you know how hard it is to swing a giant piece of plywood i don't have that sorry
oh i'll take a beat bowl 2400 it's not easy to swing a giant
huge piece of plywood it takes a lot of strength they do they do that shit like crossfit they
pick up like big plywood sheets and like swing them against the air resistance
this is desire you don't eat food oh look hey the robot doesn't the robot doesn't know shit
yeah it's 30 000 30 000 oh okay i bought the beef for 2400 no i didn't
you bought the beef bowl not for 2400 what i didn't buy it for 2400
oh yes yeah that that strange robot lady just touched may i own it now
any chance i could get you to buy this from me oh chocolate 20x a bracelet i don't have a
bracelet sorry go home again i scanned myself twice i just bought that for 200 bucks i know i
just bought that for way less i may have fucked up the first one hey could i purchase this yes
you can for 2400 bucks how's the item business treating you receipt i think i can give you a
hand on that score how much for this uh that's the cloth robe we'll do 1200 okay should i just
overcharge the hell out of this person hold on wait wait wait wait own it now robot lady just
touched right own it now right whatever okay so i i made it back oh we're going 300 on this
one a thousand dollars it's that much it's you know it's nine it's it's 900 ding ding ding
ding ding ding i still lost money no i didn't i got still up i've been looking for a candy apple how
much should i buy it for how much should you take it for i redeemed myself yes i did i have to make
80k i got plenty of time what the heck too much 1800 take it away get out of here don't come back
a person won't buy anything just leave there are signs of a boom in long swords among
men who know quality the price have what that anyways um so let's put long swords out
i want to wait wait wait wait this is important um i need to see my open order
so kayu wants charred liver bat wings and slime liver so i need a bat wing take one of
these off i don't want to get rid of all my food food's gonna bloom here soon i know it
give me something else up there and let's just get rid of this inventory and then go sell
i mean go buy stuff you know what i'm trying to say mommy asked me to sell this
go away oh hi please produce a piece of armor raincoat will you take a raincoat
um
all right
i'll get it why is everybody freaking out everybody's freaking out i didn't do anything
i didn't i didn't do anything i could probably do it too that's too expensive 1300 you can't afford
it i know i could do it really well no no no no no no sell me this no take the other one
take the better one shit whatever
there's no reason to be mad i did okay when i when i went like everyone was just like
a wave of just upset people were just fucking flowing i just bought the can well i'm being
distracted by people screaming at me i hope he comes in and buys all right i need to go to
these stores i'm gonna get the thief's knife price is currently down and i'm gonna get the
crafter's knife parade armor oh i can't do shields parade helm no mark it back here let
me put this on no shit whatever do the voice right now no i think that's like an 80 20
percentage of people that want me to not do it the price of accessories has decreased
the price of daggers has normalized good we're fake items and scams all right there we go we
can put the thief's knife up here let's get rid of these rusty daggers and let's do some
fish uh chocolate no the beef what about accessories hold on a minute here this is
cheaper isn't it what's the price cut on that 14 900 get that out of here
is the vase an accessory it's a treasure all right let's go wait don't ignore us jeremy
got a piece of armor um i did i did but not anymore goodbye
oh i can't do it guys so i'm gonna i'm gonna lose people
oh already five okay four thousand i probably do 4200 four thousand is probably safe here
welcome do you have some food yes we do you want an orange
well then that was at base value any chance i could get you to buy this
i don't want to buy any more bread 30 cents is it really that yes 30 cents
my daughter-in-law asked me to pick this up she sure did 750 700 take it a little bit
thank you little lady i'd like to get two treasures if i come to pick them up in two days
will you have them yep you're gonna you didn't say the price it's gonna be like
40 000 worth of stuff very odd vase 21 000 and an unthankful statue
what the hell is this bill you didn't specify how expensive no one's gonna be able to
afford any of this shit adventurers guild is closed oh wait a minute i could buy a couple
i'm gonna buy this yeah these are cheap right now oh these are cheap healing ring
purity ring honest honest to god sometimes i'm telling you guys sometimes you have to
fucking go nuts because i'm gonna sell this shit and i'm gonna make back like fucking
50 60 000 when those prices normalize but what about your credit score i'll be fine
how many days do i have one two three i've got like four days oh shit okay i need to have
80 000 i can do it i can do it i can do it you're actually fucking dead no i'm not
it's not i'm not dead i'm gonna everything's gonna be fine time to replace your blood with
spinach everything's gonna be fine do you see this shit 10 fucking grand eight grand seven
grand six grand it's gonna be just fine let's sell our food baked yams candy apples and all
this shit i'm ready let's go sell the vase no one's gonna buy it and i could take this shit
to the market and sell it at an extreme loss the vase is for the old man yeah
okay here we go let's be reasonable with this 2000 a bit expensive 1800 here we go
string it together okay that'll be 1700 bucks is it that much 1600 for you
oh
how you doing bingo cherries uh sell this if i get into trouble can i just do zero i don't
want to buy anything can you get me two pieces of armor i'll come get them in three days
i can do i'm gonna go buy it from him i'm gonna re-gift all right here's the yam
2400 this is just what i was looking for yes it is 2400 leveled up okay i'm everything's fine
negative 13 000 but that's because i bought a lot of this shit and watch this we're gonna
get a price skyrocket here comes the news the price of armor has increased shit i was
gonna go buy armor he just he just fucked me so bad he just completely fucked me over
he knew i was gonna do that he knows me too well i have to go adventure but i need to sell
stuff you can still buy it so glad i got those floors and carpets it's not dire yet
oh it's not hold on change flooring oh take a look at that now we've got a store
it's not dire it's only dire when i don't it's not dire yet it's not dire i still have plenty
of time i have today tomorrow the next day and the next day this time once these prices
normalize here i'm gonna make a ton of money i may even try no that's for grandpa these are
for grandpa by the way when is he when is his order tomorrow old man two treasures so tomorrow
the old man's month because one of the two treasures all right now i gotta go i wonder
if it's worth try go adventure sell one more food the bat wing i gotta get i gotta get the
bat wing up there adventure adventure adventure adventure adventure a means adventure right
sell an adventure you got it let's go
can i help you i am procuring this item right then get this sorted please two grand there
ah this will do 2500 come on pull back to back need to help your old pension you see what
can i get for this i don't want to buy things right now but i'll give you 300 for it a little
more pretend all right miss capitalist in two days i want you to get two food stuffs for me
i can do that i have two things of food do you have a bracelet no i got rings shit
i really don't want to sell this but i really don't want to buy this 500
eh 650 and that's it
this is game stop game stop values i'd like some food please all right grandpa's got a
lot of money so i'm gonna give him a baking that sounds good 2500 i don't have that kind
of money shit 2200 25 000 time to adventure
didn't you buy that yam for 2400 what's going on in the town square what the
how peculiar there's something shining in the fountain basin oh yeah the coins in the fountain
wow there's a lot of coins in there can we reach in and scoop them up why are there
coins in a public water display you never had the urge to toss a coin into a fountain and make a
wish just looking at the fountain kind of makes me want to can i make the natural assumption
that you have been so abysmally foolish in the past is to actually throw perfectly valid
money into this fountain maybe once or twice worth rice oh i haven't done it in forever
though really i certainly hope not cool all right larry you got a lot of expensive
shit on you should i give him a ring no he's a mine uh let's bring the walnut bread and uh a
cherry no the orange it's cheaper give him the book a slapstick comedy about 200 warriors saving
a village this is humor no this is 1600 bucks boss rush wait what boss rush all right let's
go so it's three bosses back to back
come on shrink
he shrunk even more oh shit i took damage
damn it i'm gonna be fine don't worry does it give me any items
yeah we'll eat that no snack snack on a mushroom please
yeah it's jimmy tootie unless it is like jimmy tootie eat something
right in the back why is it not hurting him
why is it not hurting him there it is you gotta get him right this side
he did it he did it he did it he did it he did it he did the thing he did it
nothing else here huh and versus charm
all right slow down slow down
got the counter attack just bait in the turn easy
easy so i just did it what do i get for this that's it i just wasted like six hours of the
day for this i didn't get anything not a chest not a that was actually two slices of time
and it's over day's over all right it is very it's imperative that i can put those
treasures up here news the price of long swords has decreased the swords boom has end
fuck i'm just i have two days where's grandpa today old man two treasures
shit these are still down i'm gonna give him the unthankful statue in a very odd phase
go buy an expensive treasure i can't is that that's not a good idea
that's not a good idea is it i'm gonna i have to sell them 10 like 23 this is like this is how i do
it let me save the game first just in case something catastrophic happens what you want i'm
good hold it hold everything hold everything no i can't hold everything i've got to get rid
of something i got five of these necklaces burn the shop down for insurance i need 60 grand
i it's yeah hold on i need to make sure i need to see something here is there an oh shit so
there is okay there is a oh my god look at this i mean there is a a fuck you scenario
and i think i'll be able to do it i can't buy any shit why did i not have armor oh little
receipt working hard i hope are you out of town on a walk that i am i make a habit of getting
out of the house on days like this walking in the sun like this is good for the soul
clear days do feel nice you stay indoors during periods of an inclement weather then
i know sun's good for the soul but rain hardens the body
sides it's nice to see the city looking different on a rainy day so then you just
go for a walk every day yeah well i guess if you gotta be sure about it i do he how on
earth do you find that funny what's the point of this stuff here we are in the chapel again
when i was little i used to come here a lot actually really i must admit you do not strike
me as the pious type when you came to the chapel you'd get a stamp on a little card
with enough stamps you get a piece of candy so your primary motivation was the candy not the
fake yep oh my goodness by previous judgment hit the sweet spot it seems so just don't
click on these is essentially what i'm getting in from this all right here we go i need
what do i need to do here i have to liquidate some shit
i need some liquidation diffusion do i do i have anything to rank one staff i need a magic
staff about five bat wings i don't have enough to do that i need to five insect traps and one
arm bed only hit three i need a charred lizard i don't have that it's over it's not over
watch what i hold on there's another thing of lore here
i have to have a big lunch time to dig it's many i can i had to buy oh i didn't know the rings
were gonna be on this like super downward trend but the last like five days i thought
i was gonna be able to buy them in like a day or two later start to sell them they're
still down it's been like six days wolf wolf are you hungry too huh you look pretty lean
i'll give you half of it hey don't wolf it down wolf wolf wolf murph tasty isn't it i spent
a long time picking it out i hope you like it am i feeding the dog grass louis really kind
isn't he to be honest i thought he and the dog would end up fighting for the food
that'd be sad all right i gotta start to make moves here i need this fucking money
i need it i have to sell and this is way more than what i bought it for
wait until tomorrow that's why i have to sell these
i don't have any armor unless like hey is a necklace armor is a ring armor technically
okay here we go i went and bought this but i know one uses it will you take it no
i don't want it i don't want it do you have the treasures oh i do i got your back scratcher
and a 22 000 vase yes oh shit okay hold on hold on this is important
30 can i get i need to get 25 000 right now i just screamed so loud i'm really sorry no it
can't be 30 it's gonna be too much i have to i have to this has to happen it has to be like
20 or like 22 i'm gonna 20 i have to i it's i lose if i don't get at least 10 to 20 grand
22 got it all right i'm fine everything's good it was 22 000 now it's everything's fine
never go i had to i had to do that i desire a book i got a book
book
i'm good no they don't buy it for the base price remember i did that before and the guy told me
to fuck myself no 20 they don't have that much money yeah i by the way i found that vase
i didn't buy that vase that was pure that was pure profit we found this when cleaning
the cellar is it worth anything it's worth zero you found bread in the cellar i in fact i'm
insulted that you would come here and try to sell this to me i bought the fish mother fuck
this is what my decisions are my decisions all right leave my decisions alone that's you
you're in the store arguing with me while i'm trying to have customers come in imagine you went
into a store and you saw that somebody sold something for cheaper and you were like wow you're
stupid for selling that cheaper by the way do you have any do you have any candy apples oh
fuck i just like dropped something i want some food hold on candy apple no no no this girl never
ever buys anything for more than like two or three hundred bucks take some chocolate
that's you're not gonna buy it i knew it i knew it 500 get out of here
50 000 i'm good i need 30 000 more dollars we've got two days i got plenty of stuff wait a
minute hold on two pieces of armor and two food stuffs i need two armors like can i just put
two raincoats in here i'm just gonna put two pieces of clothes in here two raincoats does
it have to be armor it doesn't matter look 420 840 dollars okay i'm gonna sell to him for
a thousand i don't give a shit what's done is done evening receipt out for an evening stroll a bit
late isn't it it is a bit late i guess what are you up to sir oh stargazing i just tried to press
escape but didn't work well stargazing is pleasant enough but do you mind the cold you
will not be very romantic if you come with the flu good advice bye good night 24 grand come
on i'm gonna get there stargazing with you know his five rusty knives the chilly season is here
those sensitive to cold should bundle up the price of accessories has normalized i live for
this let's go welcome to murph good day have you completed my order yet
no well you see uh what you still don't have it i should have known this place would be
unreliable oh but well nothing for it and to be fair some of those items are up there
the slime livers from normal slimes are too small for starters i need something from one
that's bigger bat wings shouldn't be too hard if you hunt the eyeball bats though
i've always heard that gnolls and giant mice are fond of charred lizards
no the dog like creatures never seen one throws rocks punches real hard the manuals of beasts and
monsters name those creatures as gnolls oh i see i didn't know well among adventurers it's
common knowledge more to the point however while i did not set a deadline i'm not the
immortal kind of wizard not yet anyway i'd really like for you boss to get the regents as soon as
she can please let her know i'm getting a little impatient worst part of it i assume
you have my food stuffs i do let's do expensive shit so let's do candy apple and a fish so
that's 16 26 2700 higher idiot higher idiot what do you mean higher idiot more than 133
percent pieces of armor okay okay that's what you're looking for i see very good choice what
the fuck is wrong with people what do you have a hat i don't have hats somebody buying
accessory i'm done i'm gonna do orders somebody buy something can i get some food oh my fucking
god sure here have something cheap because you don't have any money how about a piece of bread
that'll be uh 120 dollars that's a little too much just fucking take it get out here
just take it a cheap welcome two weapons required in three days can you provide
yes somebody buy something oh no the price of weapons has increased
i have somebody has to buy these nobody wants the fucking rings shit come on just open the
store and somebody buy it no i don't want any more of this no hey good day it's me did you
my order he comes gonna come in every day i don't have time for this just go i'll i'll
do it just welcome i need two food stuffs if i return three days oh my god nobody wants
anything now they want things after i crumble under debt i've been wanting a fish
she's always complaining that i don't charge enough
oh i don't want any bread i don't want any bread
somebody please buy an accessory looking for an accessory
uh no mom wants everyone wants to sell shit to me nobody wants to buy anything
no i don't have a book i have a lot of accessories i'm so close i'm so close somebody buy a ring
old man help me out here
oh shit reopen the store now
there it is there it is okay so everybody slow down everybody shut up everybody quiet
quiet everybody quiet someone's gonna buy the necklace i know how weird that would look in
the store if somebody's like hey can i buy this shut up everybody hey someone's gonna buy
this shut the fuck up everybody back there he's gonna actually buy hey what do you need sir
this is too important 16 i'm not doing 120 18 17 17 uh i need this money right now
100 178 17 800 so i find myself with a sudden need for two weapons and i need them in two days
sure why does the rich girl keep coming in and buying like bread
no she wants me to buy her bread i need more
so close hi there i was tidying up and found old bread
yeah would you like to store my old shit in your house oh my god please just
okay it's a necklace would you sell this to me yes i would
anybody else cherry i'll take a cherry's actually sell pretty well i'll do 40
44 percent of base price i'll do 55 percent you take come on people buy that
no put the necklace up there
uh put the end even up there too and the cherry wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait what the hell do people want in three days two okay somebody
wants two food and i need a bunch of weapons so i need i got plenty of food
i'll get there
1200 almost at 80 grand the next one's gonna be like 150 000 dollars here we are
you want the ring 10 grand no no no no 96 90 9200
8580 75 7600 is that too low but i didn't i would still make a profit on it i bought it
for like 3000 yeah no it's worth it that's worth it it it really is i think it was a
fireworks i didn't get scammed i bought that ring for like 3900 bucks that was a profit no
matter how you swing it and it guarantees i'll have a little bit of money tomorrow
when my grandmother died okay i really don't mean like anything but why does your
your grandmother seems to keep dying is this the same i i he keeps coming and says hey my
grandmother just died and she left me this beef bowl and i just want to get rid of it
if it's possible his grandmother dies like every day what is your toll in filthy lucre
yeah you can have the 13th day the day is saved i am procuring this chocolate bar
item exceeds allowable price variance
yeah i sold the chocolate bar sick got a weapon oh i sure do you get the last rusty dagger
here 250 get out of here candy apple but do you think i could sell it i do
candy apples do pretty well i'll give it to you 700
plus 40 000 profit i have enough to pay the debt and what time is it
oh i've been streaming this for six hours holy shit the price of precious metals has decreased
why do i buy gold all right so we're playing this tomorrow too i kind of want to keep going
this game's fun we'll go for a little bit longer i'm not done yet but uh we're doing
this tomorrow so all right um i i need to somebody said give her the batwing already
i will i will display the batwing save the game uh the top one's fine
the deck is due today food stuffs what's coming up food stuffs right
by tomorrow i need two weapons i gotta get four weapons actually
shit weapons are expensive i mean i could just do two shitty swords what do you think just
actually four shitty swords just wait till tomorrow one step i need five batwing i think
i gotta go back in the dungeon eventually here too these things sell for a ton all right let's
pay the debt the price of heavy armor has increased and the cold weather gear boom has
ended i don't think i have any armor um i'm gonna go let's go dungeon now i don't need to
take anything with me but i'm out of this is really the only two places i can do i have to
do floor 11 to 15 i wasted a slice fuck you're right i need items
damn it right there it is there's a floating eye holy fuck what just happened
i need to find not bat wings i need the silly i need two more of those who drops the little
putty snake stuff these guys no i have to watch the events to unlock new characters and maps
i've been doing that and all they do is just run into people and say hey
what are you doing outside looking outside cool it's fun to be outside yes it is
that's been the last like five events
i don't need that but it is fun to be outside you're right it is batwing
it's not what i need though these guys supposed to drop shit right
oh what is what's that red oil
cap now
chestnut don't need it but this is an item collection run i've been about leave without
items nothing come on
come on there it is got it charred lizard that is a 14 000 necklace right beautiful
the rabbits drop anything i don't think they do
too
slime livers right the liver only drops from the boss slime really seems kind of odd
mushroom just take it he literally explained this i mean if but if you think that i was
paying attention to 40 even if the dialogue on the screen i really just wasn't and i i'm
assuming the majority of everybody here can say the same cursor on the screen i don't where
where there's no cursor on the screen why it's not not it's not good to lie
where's my fucking mouse it's under the desk that was what fell down earlier i got it i got
i saw it just cover it with your own mouse that's you know that's a 500 iq play
get them all
bugs damn it they usually drop the um thing i'm looking for
now nobody wants a common wooden shield nobody wants that
yeah 16
those sell for a lot
so is it it's a percentage chance to just drop from the slime boss so i need to just
do the slime boss over and over again is this monster hunter
oh that's a nice helmet warrior's helmet
bring back the cursor it's not coming back hey i'll come back tomorrow when i play this tomorrow
you'll see it i'm kind of addicted to this game it's such a simple concept but it's it's
fun
nice to get all the bugs yes all right i need one more of these
one more of those things and i can cry i confuse the uh
try moonlighter it's similar i gotta go to a surprise party you gotta stream it again
after tomorrow we'll see if i'm still addicted and i'm still having fun i don't know we'll
just do it again moonlighter is kind of bad says lucretius look what do you it's bad
oh did you just start fighting it's a good game what's wrong with it
this is the only thing we play now special inkwell i'm getting some treasures here
but that's just like your opinion man well it's not my opinion i haven't played it
it could be great could be bad could be awful could be fun i don't know
forget about the mushrooms although i don't know dude i might need them
eventually or something up to make a fusion i don't know
oh
in the top recedar stream worldwide it's probably because i'm the only
recedar stream worldwide that's probably what's going on
moonlighter has a much less impressive haggle system and the combat is a lot more repetitive
unfortunately i'd say the game is much more this game is much more fleshed out
really come on give me one more one more so we can see it ah come on
do the anime voice no it's too late like two or three hours ago when i was like
screaming maybe i would have done it
yeah
shit can i eat the chestnut these things a stupid throne boy those things are expensive
sandals if you do the anime voice i will use my sub
ah
he's it's greed no i haven't done it yet have you noticed
i didn't immediately i'm contemplating that right now
i'm thinking about it but i haven't done it yet he's doing pre-sell out i haven't no i
haven't done anything hold on not yet there's probably a chest back here
here give me another one of those things that i need i need one more of those little snake things
they drop from the bees
no i'm not gonna do it it's water shroom now get rid of this shroom i need to open the
chest what's that it's an old muffler it's even worse oh look at this
oh look at this look at me
i can't i can't have me like that if you don't do it i will be unhappy but i will
continue to watch the stream did i get it i got it i got it i can craft that item
uh i i i don't know i have to get i got i gotta get an easy one what did you drop unknown
get rid of this other fucking shroom
what's that what's this shit there's too many cool things wooden shield stupid get rid of it
no what's less than that i have too much nice stuff the muffler get rid of that
yeah honey i'll buy a thousand dollars in bits if you do the voice you're not gonna do that
i can guarantee that's not gonna happen and i don't want you to do that let me save you some
money if i throw away the shield candy apples worth no i don't want to do that because now
here's the thing now there's pressure on that person if i do it oh fuck i didn't really want
to do this and you don't have to do it and i don't want you to do it fine fine don't buy that money
do not buy that money there it is i did it it's done now you can move on
done okay that's it we win what do you mean we win
i don't want a thousand dollars don't give it to me
oh yeah we did it guys we did it streams over i'm leaving no i tell it i'm telling you i only did
that just because nobody would ever stop you know you've been here for long enough that would
never stop i would have to hear that every day like 10 streams from now 35 year old man
pretends to be nine year old japanese girl to protect to to make 12 year old chat happy
no i mean that is kind of what happened but you guys aren't 12 you guys are like 36
which makes that even worse by the way 34 year old man pretends to be nine year old to appease
25 to 30 plus year old chat that's even worse that's fucking weird so i'm 22 that's weird i'm
19 18 19 19 26 20 25 19 19 21 35 year old man pretends to be nine year old to get a thousand
dollars that's more accurate but it's not accurate because i didn't get a thousand
and i do not want a thousand dollars honey is 2300 bucks i had to do it i had to do it and you know
i did i sometimes the hardest choices require strongest of wheels imagine people is voice
cracked in the fucking movie people would have laughed i need to open this get rid of the
hat open the box what is it chest piece i'll take it now i'll do elmo i'll do elmo for free
i i love i'll do elmo for free
mr noodle we're speaking japanese today mr noodle and he knocked it out of the park he got both
things done and that's the way the stream ends end of the stream voice
i could do the whole elmo song right now but i don't like it you after you do elmo for
more than three or four seconds your brain starts to go shut up elmo your brain starts to say
may i shouldn't be doing this any longer after like 10 seconds it's like it's probably time
to stop doing this i think that just gave me a nosebleed no it's all right just a bloody
booger it's fine why do i hear the end music this this why is that on i don't know oh
treasure trash all right let's craft some items that's the cheapest thing i got i need that though
crusader bone thanks for five community subs thank you appreciate it uh probably the
the wooden shit no what do i get rid of here anti-venom plus two is the other anti-venom
just scared of one of them it's just a little whatever is that cheaper than this
that's all we care about is money so yeah it's thrown away
you have a million anti-venom yeah but i might need it for uh some kind of thing all right we're
good back to town fusion and money we go to the book fusion time here we go
bracelet needs an iron iron armband so let's get it iron armband fusion so this is going
to be a bracelet insect trap and an iron iron armband here's your thousand bits now
squeal like an anime girl for my amusement i was a thousand dollars and a thousand bits
you're off by a little what am i gonna get maiden's bracelet plus 11 plus 11
1800 bucks that's it that's some bullshit oh i need a cape cloth cape i just need to buy one
cloth cape and then there was something else i can make not the glove staff yeah okay i need
two more bat wings all right let me let me do the cloth robe which one was it i don't i don't
remember i don't remember what which one was it i don't remember cloth cape i don't think i buy
that can i buy that here i need cape cape that's right i can't buy what market's closed what
about the pub looks like nobody's here uh i think it's time for bed time to do the debt
i'm going to go to the market eighty thousand dollars watch it be deleted from my bank account
game sucks well done work hard next week no no no you already did it already made my money
oh sinister objects are increasing in popularity with men chapel masters worried
sinister items what is a sinister item 2600 bucks plus 11 all right uh i need to buy the cape
cape cape cape cape cape cape cape cape cloth cape fusion rank one cape there it is
boom that's holy shit romantics cape ten thousand five hundred dollars
cape with a daring pleasing vine like pattern just looking at it inspires longing in the heart
its base price is ten thousand five hundred bucks all right anything else town square
let's do an event snippet hey what's wrong i dropped my hairpin it's real important too
oh don't cry i'll help you find it yeah just leave it to me despite how she may look tier is
a master at finding things pardon she can get into every nook and cranny and find anything
oh really thank you glad we could find it thank you wow tier your black is cold
why did it have to be in a drain of all places hey you did great and we can use
you to warm the store now no you're gonna take a shower because there's food in that
store i don't want you near my merchandise covered in shit wash go to take a shower
wash and sanitize your hands all right how much do i oh that's a lot of money that's
two hundred thousand dollars in a week i thought it was gonna be like 160
well should be an interesting scenario tomorrow when we continue i'm gonna call it here
it's a perfect little time to stop six and a half hours will take us to about seven i will see you
guys tomorrow we'll we're just gonna pick up right where we left off i'm having a lot of fun
with it the game's a lot of fun game is saved game is good so let's see if we can keep it
going i am saying turn i'm not gonna touch anything else yet no say i'm good yeah 621
that looks good what time same time somewhere between like three o'clock pacific three to
four pm pacific check your local listings did i miss the carnival stream you did not don't worry
that's not going to happen for at least a month or two so don't worry i thought this was a
house flipper stream he said by the end of the summer um do you know what months the summer
is august september the end of like middle of september that's um summer september is
not summer um the first and second week of september is still in summertime um it ends on
it ends on september 23rd i just want to make sure we're aware summer ends on monday september
23rd we're in the northern hemisphere that's where i live anyways chat just got googled
but all things considered here thank you everybody for watching uh by the way we didn't
really touch much upon this i kind of just embarrassingly glazed over it i'm part of a
porn ad so that's uh or a like a chat with your crush porn advertisement thing that's kind
of interesting we didn't really touch the bonnet that much wait yeah i know that people
weren't here for this this is really weird they used a face cam of me and like a weird
fucking like sidebar ad i can't believe that's real is it actually real yeah someone's gonna
link it so i'm not gonna show it on stream because i don't want to like accidentally
advertise a company that i not only have nothing to do with but who have like taken my likeness and
put it somewhere that i did not give permission to so yeah hey guys look at the website
anyways that is gonna be the end of the stream i'll see you guys tomorrow
let's do the bits and subs of course let's go back a little while ago here we had
demons v for the 25 dollars thank you demons actually demons v gave 32 dollars here
and they say thank you for the stream i've had five operations this year and i'm in a lot of pain
and your stream helps distract me i'm really sorry to hear that hopefully you have a swift
recovery here whatever you're going through whatever you had to have done but thank you
so much for the 25 bucks 30 bucks 32 bucks and then they said also please yell less and
make fewer loud noises well i don't i may not have done that that's your best quality no
come on i do i really have to go to bed tonight thinking that my best quality is
loud noises imagine like you're in the shower you shape when you're here my best quality
is loud noises no i'm more than that right thank you though for the 32 bucks
uh thank you jedi master for the five dollars somebody make a death grips remix with a slice
sound bite you know the song i'm not aware of the song but whoever i don't know thank you
for the five bucks uh the best striped sweater thanks for the ten dollars hey germa couldn't
watch your stream today but i just wanted to drop it and say thank you you're one of the
most creative funny dedicated content creators i've come across and i always counted your
stream to lift my mood and turn my day around you've helped me so much through this
through some rough times recently and i'm so grateful to have found your streams and youtube
videos thank you for all the laughs and i hope you have a good stream and good rest of your
night sorry you couldn't stick around uh today but you dropping in and giving me 10 dollars and
saying a ton of incredibly nice things about me so thank you for that and i'm happy
that you're happy here thank you so much for the 10 bucks that was the best striped sweater
glad to be around here do you plan on streaming cb what is this what is that
i didn't complete it cold brew cold do i plan on streaming me drinking a seed a cold brew
coffee i i have yeah um i have a i had a cold brew this morning and it was delicious
right off the fucking shield come on you can do better than that thank you zake for the
hi it's me your kid soccer coach really what happened can you pick him up from practice
it's been days and he's really hungry i know that you're really busy watching these asian
cartoons but i'll have to contact child protective services if you don't feed them
thank you smelly boy for the 250 the billion the billion old man that has to be in the
next rumble a billion dollar old man with the twix brothers uh thank you demons v again
for five dollars do the long tongue to them do the long tongue to them to to what
does a long like go like like sticky tongue oh in the porn in the ad i'm not doing an ad no no
no no no thank you for the five dollars i'm not going to stick my tongue out on camera
you could give me 500 million dollars and i wouldn't do it i mean okay i would do it
for 500 million dollars literally every single person in for the rest of my entire lineage
would be taken care of for me to stick my fucking tongue out on camera that's worth it
worth it uh thank you to oh my god taeyeon for the 250 a while ago you talked about
sardines i went out and got some and they were pretty meh you got any other boomer food
suggestions well hold on a minute here this is important did you get the boneless skinless
sardines by the way there's only one brand you should be purchasing and that's king oscar
king oscar boneless and seedless seed boneless and skinless sardines in oil boneless and
skinless sardines in oil king oscar they come in a tin you fold them back put them on smash
them up put them on a little bit of toast maybe add a little bit of mayonnaise to that
or a tomato on top you may have you may have not have eaten them correctly king oscar
they're the best i don't look i don't do sponsorships i just tell you the truth
about what i believe king oscar sardines are the best baskin robin's mom's cookies ice cream
is the best you don't have to pay me to say that i'm just i'm telling you a fact
king oscar doesn't have to come here and give me a thousand dollars to do an anime
voice i'm just gonna speak facts why would he sponsor after 2 000 people just left anyway
well this is the end of the spring if i had a sponsorship i would have been probably required
to do it peak viewership anyways sardines are really good another boomer food that you should
try uh let me think about this it's just food it's not boomer food canned fish is really
good for you and it's really tastes good as long as you do it right canned tuna canned
sardines anchovies they are good if you can just get over it how weird and strange and
gross television has told you they are you're gonna enjoy them canned tuna is great did it try
pasta with uh pasta casserole uh what uh pasta with tuna no tuna casserole and pasta casserole
i'm a fucking idiot tuna casserole is a really good boomer food look it up but thank you for
the 250 hope you can retry sardines when you get the right brand snooze and cough
thanks for the 250 hey germ i'm really looking forward to today's stream i haven't checked what
you're playing yet mainly because i can always trust you to choose a fun game and thanks to
your no anime game policy we don't have to watch stuff like that either i'm so proud of you
that you never break your policy that is what makes you so great and unique in my eyes
germa you're the best you never disappoint never that said i'm gonna open the stream
now i'm really excited you never fail us when did i ever say a no anime game policy
i've never had a no anime game policy before i said i watch one anime a year this is not an anime
i did not say that somebody can go find that if they really want to i never said there is a
no anime game policy on this stream was that some way for me to deflect not having to play
doki doki literature club because i got asked that every single day every moment of every
stream i think play doki doki literature club may have been in this chat more than germa moon
or more than half of my emotes for a period there i had to deflect it somehow you're an actual
liar i've already told everybody here that 90 80 to 90 percent of everything i say in this
stream is not real and i always clarify when things are real like for instance
baskin robbins ice cream is the best that ice cream mom's cookies i said before this is one
of the 10 things that i say on stream that's real and then i continue to say that sometimes
it's too easy sometimes it's too easy guys come on but thank you snooze and copter for the
five dollars they say dot dot dot dot after writing all that so i don't think they were
uh they may have been a little disappointed chocolate fudge brownie is the best ice cream
get wrecked jupiter face let's ban this guy real quick oh how do i turn off um
hold on actually just did that what was his name did i even do the right person
how do you untie about somebody all right there we go there we go i got they say wow
you banned someone from pointing out the truth i already i unbanned him i had banned
it wasn't even banned i do it was a small time out of 10 minutes but if you're going to say
something so so awful like chocolate fudge brownies better than moms making cookies
i feel like you've gotta go for at least enough for me to not have to look at it
anyways anyways anyways thank you to uh abomination zero for the five dollars thank
you for another great night jeremy you've done so much for me and i'd really like to start
streaming myself make it look like so much fun how the hell do you do it by having fun
it's important if you cannot reliably enjoy yourself on stream then it's kind of hard for
other people too as well except when you play mario maker it's one exception but uh good luck
to you i wish you the best i've been watching since 2011 so you've been doing something right
um i don't know if that's just up to you though you know if you've been watching for that long
then i hope you do think i'm doing something right but there i mean there are plenty of people
that have watched in come and gone and and that's fine too there may be people that
have come to this channel and said i don't really like this and left you kind of just
have to find the community that speaks to you you know i don't really like this
no i can't like time that i'm not going to do that this streamer only makes loud noises
it's been seven hours okay i probably made like 12 loud noises so it was like 18 to 20 seconds
of loud noises in seven hours that is less than like a quarter of a percent of loud noise time
on screen so come on give me a little bit of a slack here a wiki this thanks for the 15
dollars at german 985 i'd like to buy one of your rings please i usually sell them for 1500 so
thank you for the 15 bucks thank you thank you thank you one of my rings lacronda gave 35
dollars no message just 35 bucks thank you lacronda really appreciate that it's a lot
of money just to give so thank you i think that was when i did the uh elmo anime thing
combined them both but thank you so much for the 35 dollars it's a lot of money
wavelet thanks for the 420 diger but deska i think that's what i was trying to say
and then oh my god teyon 250 daijo budesca what does that mean what is daijo budesco what's it
mean it means good night y'all no why did that's not what it means it means are you okay
okay all right are you okay are you okay crusader bone gave five community subs let's make sure we
touch on that and also speaking of subs here comes the credits by the way this should be a new
screen here and a couple of new things to listen to music wise while blordow continues to
chip away at all the new stuff i'll probably implementing that over the next couple of streams
it might take um like into next week but you should see it really soon and the credits
are gonna roll right now thank you to everybody that subs to this channel thanks everybody
all of you means a lot everybody and we are gonna have unfortunately there were a lot more
subs than what you're seeing on screen right now but because the stream cut off in half
three two or three hours ago i believe we may have lost the first two or three hours of
people that have subscribed in the first couple hours so i'm sorry to say that because technically
a new stream had to start because i'm not even sure that was a cox thing i think that was a
twitch thing but regardless thank you everybody for something there's a lot of you old bits
got deleted uh they no they shouldn't they're here i got them here yeah they should be fine
this because i had this window open the whole time let me see how long ago
because i have all the bits here from five six hours ago you see unless they're uh are they
up here my message was like 10 minutes into the stream uh i don't see it here
huh i don't see it here at all let me check this one germa mustard psych
uh that's strange how it didn't go through though because everything else is here
oh yeah it looks like uh soul harv as well for 250 thank you soul harv earlier i guess the first
like couple of bits got cut off for some weird reason uh did you know and it's uh the first few
bits here are talking about the porn joke a real screenshot from the uh porn ad which i'm
not going to show on stream but thank you soul heart thank you origin hi germa this bit is is
this donation is cursed after you finish reading this you'll be turned into an evie
still here dan man me thanks for the four dollars nile aurion thanks for the three dollars
it's not a porn ad it's just you having a conversation with a lovely lady that isn't kim
oh i didn't have that conversation uh tabarin thanks for the five bucks you know fail to
make me smile and laugh i love you thank you tabarin for the five bucks thank you thank you
man boy for the 250 not that i'm complaining but i thought you didn't play anime games i guess
you really are a weeb this is not even an anime game i mean it's an anime it's this is not like
a tv show it's an item capitalist store it's a game you make look you could make these you
can make like kermit the frog and big bird the two characters and it's what i would still
play it hey i don't i don't even like care if it's like anime characters i don't give a
shit about all that is the game fun and is there cool fun concepts the main characters squeeze
every five all right i'll turn off the squeak i'll turn i'll turn it down uh thank you burger
b for the ten dollars burger b thank you ten bucks from burger b uh k zero legacy thanks
for the five bucks love you man thanks for the lulls and the plus twos you got it thank you
thank you volemy for the 30 dollars ah yes the wonders of capitalism where an eight-year-old
is pressed into indentured servitude to pay her father's debts i hope you're happy journal
it could be burt they could be big bird and kermit the frog and i'd still play it and
it would it would it could be sesame street teaches capitalism and i'd play it thank you
for the 30 bucks though thank you s10 w update for the two dollars and 50 cents hey again jeremy
aka germa985 now the host of the stream and owner of the channel germa985 just doing my
timely donation here to tell you that i wish you the best and good luck with life see ya
see see you too thanks for the 250 thanks for the um i was gonna say thanks for the
update your name is update thanks it still works and then 21 thanks for the three bucks
hey everybody germa here with another team fortune two gameplay commentary tonight we're
gonna be playing as them or whatever who cares and that's gonna wrap up the video thank you
all so much for watching and of course take care everybody i don't think i made that video
but well that's fine and then fast forwarding up here we had a clueless sniper for 250 can
you do a b anime voice there's no way that's gonna happen i don't think i could
no that's i maybe tomorrow ask me again tomorrow thank you for the 250 alicia
alicia music thanks for the 10 bucks 10 dollars from alicia music hey germa was
watching the green screen encore stream last week and i couldn't help but put some germa
easter eggs into a music video i made you do not need to watch the whole thing but at
one minute and 27 seconds you're driving in the bright window when it is centered
and at 157 you're climbing the tree on the right and also there are brown notes why are
they brown notes well hold on here let's see here here's the video let's let's get this
let's see if we can find this here so i had 127 hold on that is not this that's not this
person's song that's still the sasame street music from the game that's not their song
somebody already had a sour please ready to go and they're like oh shit wait this is
not the right one i gotta hold let me mute this oh this is not their song all right
get your sour please is ready so we're going to 127 that's not me right all right 127
where is it 127 how do you do frame by frame on youtube what is what you're driving in the
bright window where back hold on get this on hd 360 p i don't see anything enhance it is
it right there is that me is that me the person walking by is it this right here that
like weird ghost person you missed it that's not me where's the other one 157 you're climbing
the tree center on the bright window this is all right that there i am i thought it was
bullshit for a minute i'm like what the hell is this this is like a wild goose chase all
right and then again why am i talking like i'm picking this up and it's heavy okay and then
at 157 you're climbing the tree i didn't where is it i didn't see it 157 you're climbing the
tree 156 156 157 climbing the tree i don't see a tree should be climbing the tree on the right
let me see it i don't see it we're looking for a ghost i don't see anything am i in there
turn on the click map i it's not even on hold on let me get closer is that me in there i
think that's me yeah that's me right there i'm doing i'm hanging on the links that you went
to like blend me into the tree that's me right no that's not me yes it is all right anyways that
was uh called where's waldo thank you uh aliceye or ala alicia i if you'd like to do your own
hunting it's there i linked it before check it out and there's also a brown note but i don't
want to hear the brown note i'm gonna shit my pants uh ok rollo thanks for the 10 dollars
ok rollo thanks for always making me smile germy i was diagnosed with depression earlier this year
so school has been uh tough but despite these struggles i can always rely on you to raise my
spirits in a matter of the day sincerely thank you for your dedication and your love germa
heart germa heart germa heart i'm really sorry to hear that ok rollo keep pressing forward
take care of yourself and hopefully school gets better thank you for being part of this
community hope things start looking up thank you so much for your 10 dollars join the
discord too tons of great people there if you haven't already so we can shout the discord out
if we can it's a great little spot it's public thank you so much and take care of yourself
thank you we also had 10 dollars from nautilus i accidentally put the dollar sign on the 1000
and i feel really bad so here's 1000 bits anyway i accidentally put the dollar sign on
what's that smell guilt bits well it's plastic right squeal vessel no thank you for the 10
dollars told you it wasn't necessary but thank you for the 1000 bits regardless thank you
you see 4g thanks for the 250 big dip in smooth recovery this is today that's not a that's not
a that's that's just simply it that's a little just small sell-off let's take a look let's get
this on the screen all right so what's what happened here let's see um first of all what
happened was i could tell you exactly this was this was gamed and i said it i said out
loud something about like everyone's gaming me and doing minus twos and then everybody just
jumped on the bandwagon and dumped the comedy stock down to zero and then look at that
immediate turnaround you know we call that in the industry we call that a bear trap
so sorry guys it looks pretty rigged that's a stay that's a squad that's a steady comedy
level nice meme lines i just i want something to do like technical analysis to these charts
somehow i think that'd be really funny put a bunch of ta like technical analysis on what's
gonna happen but no that's fine thank you for that c4g forodian weapon thanks for the three
bucks happy saturday germa hart by the way your elmo anime voice was the highlight of my night
have a good one thank you forodian thanks for the three bucks you have a good one as well
you have a good one snooze and copter thanks for the 250 hey you know i'm joking right i
enjoy all your streams especially when you're having fun or in a good mood i got the pink
bad pink bit badge now by the way uh how many bits is that i don't know it's okay if you call
me a call me snooze by the way we've known each other long enough no need to be formal
no i know you just i know you're just kidding i was too that's the thing about this train
we can go back and forth and kid we can just kid around uh there's origian again for the
250 talking about the cursed message i'm gonna be turned into an evie when i'm done
saying this uh what's dragon cute what's dragon cute mean what is that dragon cute have fun
i don't know what that means why the fuck are you serious why what is that
audio warning for the first sound what it's supposed to be evie it's supposed to be evie
what's this first fucking sound listen what the fuck is that that was so loud i mean i turn
my uh audio pumping through obs is um my audio pumping through obs is dropped by 50
right now so thank god it is because that my head hurts my like ears and head hurt right
now my ears hurt i was wondering why it took so long for the thing to play it takes like
eight full seconds then blows your ears out anyways um thank you for the 250
app key thanks for the three bucks dr clay thanks for the five bucks i didn't see you but
i saw a face in a tree i don't see it don't see it somebody just came in with a raid
right next to the right dave raid just gave an answer dave dave dave raid unfortunately dave
thank you dave cap for the raid um but i'm literally about to turn the stream off so
hopefully you had fun on your stream whatever it was thank you dave cap for the raid welcome
everybody uh we're about to hit the on the pause button for until tomorrow but welcome
regardless and have a great night have a wonderful rest of your night i see i want to
hold on let me zoom in here i see like a weird muppet face in the tree i don't see um me though
i don't see me in here anyways snooze thanks for the 250 right at the very end
i know you were kidding and he says as if i wouldn't know actually by the way snoozing
is better well that i just changed it i just changed it uh you were close but we're not that
close okay have a good night for real i thought you i just thought about how far
you've come and that's awesome thank you thank you snoozing did he make the 80k or did we
lose oh i made the 80k i made it just in time the next leg is 200 000 we'll see if i can do
it tomorrow take care everybody see you soon tomorrow around three to four p.m pacific
much love to you more receipt here coming up shortly have a great night