Hello, my wonderful friends. Good afternoon. Hope you're having a good day. I'm just hanging out. I'm just having a good time.
There we go. Hey, why don't we change some music? Yeah, let's change the music a little bit today.
Those of you that weren't out here a couple days ago. This is the intro song to Monster Rancher 4. I don't know why.
What if this was just my intro?
Stream's starting soon, guys. See you in a minute. I can kind of do it again. I thought my cough was kind of back. Remember I couldn't do that last week?
Hey, that's what you've been hearing. That's been the intro to Monster Rancher 4. We're going to continue where we left off.
We had three wonderful little babies that are starting to grow up into adults. And they're probably going to die really soon, so don't get too attached.
But yeah, I was out last night. I took Kim out. It was her birthday weekend, so we went out. It was her birthday weekend.
We ended up being able to take the same amount of time off because she works too. So we ended up being able to go out last night.
It was really fun. It was great. But the only problem is I have made my sickness come back. I'm coughing again, which sucks because I was just over it.
Well, what can you do? But I think I just caused it to come back for a minute.
I don't know. Something's going on. Something is going around. I probably got sick with something else. I'd be so pissed.
Sick forever. I just keep getting a different strand of the cold.
Anyways, let's go right where we left off. Welcome, everybody.
I've been sick since I swallowed the semen. I'm like, I know. That's fucked up.
I'm going to have to go to the doctor and be like, why have I been sick for like three weeks?
I never get sick like this. You guys know that. Maybe like once or twice, maybe once a year, I will get sick like this.
Like sort of like coughing and no, never. I have a bunch of other problems, but I never get sick.
It was your first winter in Vegas. That's true. It was the Mike and the raw pizza. Raw pizza.
As is Vroomer. I catch everybody up that wasn't paying attention last time.
Maybe you fell asleep because of a retarded sleeper. Or maybe you were just not here.
These are our three monsters. We have Wally, Roberto, and Vroomer.
Vroomer is the best currently, but I think Roberto is going to be passing him very soon.
But Wally I think is on their way out. They're not very good. They're causing problems.
This thing sucks. I'll be honest. But its cute factor brings it to like an eight.
So its usefulness is like a four. But look at that dance.
We can try fusing Wally with somebody. How about this? This is what we're going to do.
We're going to say goodbye to Wally, but we're not going to say bye.
We're not going to say bye. We're going to say hello to their fresh DNA.
And we're going to fuse them with somebody else. Because we're going to put some more CDs in.
Give him...I'm a monster.
Let me...alright, here's what's going to happen.
Let me see...no, no, no, don't do that.
Let's take a look at the calendar. I didn't win in the D rank. I got cheesed by the enemy.
They resurrected twice. But I think you unlock more monsters when somebody gets up here.
So we were almost here, but I got screwed.
So unfortunately we got to go back and do that again.
That was kind of an annoying moment, but whatever.
For the time being, I think it's time.
It's time to freeze Wally.
We're going to have them forever.
Everyone's going to be very upset about this.
Just wait longer.
I kind of want to put in some more CDs.
Let's be honest here.
I want to see a couple more CDs worth of monsters.
And Wally's just the weakest link out of the three of them. That's just the way it is.
High King Milk, 10 community subs.
What is it with Monster Rancher 4 and community subs right off the bat? 10.
Thank you, High King Milk.
His intelligence is so high, but he just don't...
Let me take a look at this.
So this is 216, 199, 200.
But better moves.
This is 242, 139, 182.
Alright, maybe not.
Maybe if I just increase his accuracy, he'll be good.
Roberto just doesn't have high stats, but the moves, they hit so often and they're so good.
Maybe Vroomer. Vroomer sucks.
No, I've said that about all three of them. They're all good.
Look, Vroomer is almost a year and three months old.
And Roberto is about to pass them.
You understand?
D, he's not even one.
It might be time to put Vroomer on ice.
Alright, I'm going to give it a couple more weeks.
If Vroomer and Wally can prove in the next two or three weeks of training that they're worth keeping around, then I'll keep them.
I'm telling you, one or two of them are gone.
We can even combine them.
I could combine Vroomer with Roberto or Wally.
Alright, what have we got for schedule?
You know what? Fuck it.
I'm going to combine the two of them.
Let's go.
Roberto is our ranked player.
We're just going to mess with DNA now.
Look, the game is saved, so if this sucks, I'll just save this comment.
Goodbye, Vroomer.
See, he's happy.
Alright, now let's retire Wally and we're going to fuse them together.
We're going to get a nut on a wheel.
How do you guys not think that's cool?
I do.
It's cool, man.
You're going to get a pinwheel.
Alright, here we go.
Combine.
Let's see.
We still have these idiots here.
Alright, Vroomer and Wally.
What happens?
Skunk Roller and Suzurecho.
Sprite.
The base stats are not really that good.
Skunk Roller.
Wind Lore, Backspin.
It's just a wheel.
Attack and...
These both sound like Twitch emotes.
Let's do it.
Let's see what happens.
I'll save scumming.
Okay, well Vroomer just consumed.
That's just Vroomer.
It was unfrozen and ate the walnut and then just walked out.
No.
Vroomer and...
Okay, what about High Intelligence?
What about Wonka and Wally?
Mush Tan.
Pumpkey Plant.
Pumpkey Plant has actually pretty high...
Actually, Mush Tan does too.
Look at the health on Mush Tan.
That's not bad base stats.
Mush Tan.
Let's see, what do you look at?
It's a plant, right?
No.
We've seen it already.
I don't want this.
Oh my god.
I kind of have to keep this one.
How about Wally Wonka?
No.
Let's do Shroomer.
We already had a Shroomer.
How about like Prove It To Me?
Yeah, that's a good name.
Prove It To Me.
Come on.
Prove it to me.
That's worse than hashtag V.
Yeah, I know how to spell prove it, guys.
Look, it needs to fit in this tiny amount of characters that can fit here.
Prove it to me.
Prove to me.
No, that sucks.
That's worse than what I did.
Prover.
Let's see if they can prove it.
Let's get a couple of discs in here.
High base stats, though.
All right, Prover.
I need to go back.
We got Roberto.
Shrine.
Let's get some more discs in here.
Roberto is going to climb the ranks real fast, so don't worry about losing progress there.
All you really need is just one.
Create.
All right, from a saucer.
What's going in?
I've got Dark Souls.
I don't even own Dark Souls.
The actual physical copy.
I don't think I own any of them.
How about Dynamite Cop?
Or Space Channel 5 is down here, too.
Let's put in Dynamite Cop.
Here, I'll prove it.
Hey, don't worry, I'll be a Prover.
How do I look today?
Probably bad.
No, not that bad.
Here, Dynamite Cop for the Dreamcast.
Going to insert CD into the disc tray.
After this, I'll put Red Box in after this.
It's going to be a Shroomer.
If it is, then I'm just going to accept fate and just wait until we unlock more.
And you get some really good McDonald's M hair today.
But I should just spray paint.
Or what's the spray color?
My hair?
Yellow in the front there.
All right, here we go.
Oh, by the way, I have something to talk about.
I got approval from somebody at Twitch.
The Scratch Ticket charity stream is going to happen.
Probably in the next couple days.
For the deaths in Sekiro.
Oh my fucking God, it's fate.
I'm just going to play.
Should I just take them both?
Let's try a different one.
Let's try Space Channel.
Give me a break.
Is it because they're Dreamcast and all Dreamcast games are the same game?
Well, this is not even a Dreamcast game, so that's fine.
Space Channel 5, this is the bootleg one, isn't it?
So, you know what I mean?
This is the bootleg one.
This is not even a Sega Dreamcast game.
This is somebody like burnt this on their fucking Windows 2000 computer.
Something.
Something that's not the mushroom guy.
I would be, it's going to be the mushroom, it's going to be Dreamcast.
Because all the Dreamcast games have the same internal seed or something.
I'm going to have to grab other disks that are not Dreamcast.
Okay.
Dreamcast used proprietary code.
So maybe it is.
Maybe they can't, maybe you can't pull data from Dreamcast.
Okay, come on.
The fungus is a catch-all for any disk that's too new.
I'm going to have to get some old shit.
I got some old shit here.
It's a meat rumor.
We just replaced this one.
We just replaced the rumor with meat rumor.
It's just Cheeto dusted rumor.
We already talked about this.
Upgraded.
No.
No, no, no.
I'm putting in Redbox.
Redbox is about to go in.
And then, like somebody said, you might as well just grind up to rank A.
I got a really good monster to grind up to rank A.
We're just going to just, we're steamrolling all the competitions.
Let's get this here.
Too new?
We'll just use standard DVDs and CDs and PS1, PS2 disks.
Copy protection doesn't affect those.
Interesting.
But here is, here's Redbox.
It's a great CD.
Redbox guy, come on.
Give us something here.
This is a regular, just CD, DVD.
It's not like a protected code from Dreamcast.
Watch like Vinnie come in here and goes, oh, actually, we use like the protected code, man.
You're going to get a fucking shroomer.
What is it?
Something cool. Come on.
To get a monster with higher stats, the two monsters you're combining need to be friends.
What?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
To get a monster with better, with higher stats, the two monsters you're combining need to be friends.
You can see how good of friends they are by going into the Breeder tab and going to the last page.
What?
How can you be friends when you're frozen and dead?
I don't know how that works.
KD, five community subs.
Thank you, KD.
Welcome back.
KD, give him more subs.
Thank you so much, KD.
Now we got a robo bunny.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're taking this monster home.
We got a farm full of robots.
It's a X bunny.
No.
Bunny.
The energizer rabbit.
Did the energizer rabbit have a name?
I like energizer.
It was bunny. No, it was not.
Five more community subs from KD.
Thank you, KD.
Again, ten now.
How about a, how about vroomer?
How about, how about energizer?
Like this.
The energizer.
Energize sleep.
All right, energize.
He's a little sleepy.
All right, let's go to the ranch.
We got some new stuff.
It's time.
So here are the two.
We got energize prover and Roberto.
Roberto is, sole purpose is to grind tournaments.
These two are going to just relax.
I don't care.
They're not joining any tournaments.
Let me take a little bit.
Let's just hold that thought.
Yeah, you guys just rest and eat and just go to training.
You are going to grind tournaments.
In each rank unlocks more monster fusion types.
So after D, new races unlock is possible on the discs you put in.
All right, cool.
So let's, it's going to grind up tournaments.
When's the next one?
More community subs from KD.
My God.
Thank you, KD.
For your, every five minutes.
Is it the tournament today?
Let's go.
Join it, Roberto.
He's ready.
Just crush the competition.
He's so good.
And you guys, who gives a shit?
You can just do whatever you want.
No, automatic for technique.
I mean you, automatic for speed.
Yeah, who cares?
They're just DNA.
Roberto is going to do life training today.
It's a little quiet.
Nine health from Roberto.
That's good.
Kill or be killed?
You're doing just good.
Let's give you some food.
Because we have to just grind tournaments.
Oh shit, I'm out of food.
You can use squid today.
I'll go buy some food tomorrow.
Let's see how funny.
Okay, depending on how funny and cute they are.
You're a lot bigger than I thought you were.
I hate this thing so much.
I really hope that that stupid mushroom is not the most powerful thing we have.
We all love him.
No, you don't.
I can't wait to see in the chat in an hour or two.
Burn him.
Just eat him.
Ice him.
Kill that fucking stupid thing.
It's going to be everywhere.
It's the dumbest monster that we've ever seen.
And there's going to be an argument in chat.
I don't know why you guys think that.
Like why do you think that?
Like that person's name.
Like are you stupid?
I saw, I see that you've only been a follower of the channel for like two months.
I was here when Beanbag Sonic was created.
You don't know shit, idiot.
And then that person's going to be like, fuck you man.
It's going to cause problems.
Don't do that.
All right, what do you got?
Nothing.
I don't even need to look at the stats.
Roberto is too good.
I see you've only been a follower for two months.
I was here when Beanbag Sonic was created.
Look at that thing.
It really is cooking.
It's all right.
It's a little rusty.
This is such a high hit for someone.
I just need to do three of these and we can get the secret.
Guy versus Ghassan.
Ghassan wins.
And then the championship is against Ghassan.
This is one of those big rocks.
Lots of life.
Pretty good defense.
Just kind of have to knock it hit.
That'll be good.
Guy Ghassan was a French revolutionary, I think.
Guy Ghassan.
Monster.
Bingo.
And then we can go with a shoulder tackle.
This, if you don't think we're going to grind up the tournaments and win them.
With Roberto.
It was a long shot with Rumor because Rumor didn't have very good accuracy.
I should win all these up to like rank C or B.
One final tip from the Monster Rancher expert.
The good trick is to get the house that allows you to have four monsters have three you don't care about doing exploring.
And one you use to get your rank up.
All right.
Well, I already meeting you halfway there because I already don't care about the other two.
So I'm already getting to that point.
I miss Wally, but you gotta move on.
All right.
So let's go to the calendar.
The next tournament here is for Roberto.
Sign you up for that one.
Just do any every single one I can do in a row.
That's at least ranked D.
Now the other two are going to just go for go on a walk.
Let me take a look at this.
So you let me do.
Why don't you just do intelligence.
Just make it at least look like you're trying.
And then speed.
I don't have to think of speed accuracy.
What did you have Roberto?
You can sleep now.
You're good.
I think you can do life again, right?
Yeah, life blade then rest.
I think I should maybe I should bring them all exploring because Roberto's almost level five.
I need food.
I'll go to town this week because he does that with his ears.
Weirdly enough.
Yeah, you are tired.
You're tired. I don't want to bring you.
Oh, I hate you so much.
Burn it, burn it, burn it, burn it, burn it.
I'm turning the page with his face.
I need food.
I would like to buy.
I got lots of money.
Let's get some like 10 potatoes because I always use them.
Let's get like five bananas.
Maybe a couple of squids.
Beef is too expensive.
Squid.
I'll get like three squids for Roberto.
And.
I feel like I said I have so much stuff to sell, but I don't know the hell it does.
Like Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
These battle cards.
What are these even for?
Silver coin, amethyst.
Hey, where's the monster rancher expert?
You still here?
What are these for?
Yes, I am. All right. What what are these for?
Should I just sell all this expensive stuff?
Luxuries?
It's for fusions later on.
Okay, so don't use them.
Ooh.
All right. Don't use these either.
I'm not going to use them. I'm going to hold on.
I hate forever so much.
I'm whimpering right now.
Don't worry.
We'll only walk the plank in like a few days.
Some of those will relieve stress.
Okay, the way we raise Roberto from this point on will determine the difference between victory and defeat.
Roberto is now no longer a baby.
Rest.
And then you got a sandbag.
Let me take an actual look here.
220 power.
Accuracy could use a little work and so could speed.
Accuracy and speed.
Although his moves are so accurate anyways.
All right. What does it say? Your favorite food?
His moves.
Traits, super weapon.
Record.
Temper, cool, size, normal. Likes, reference.
Doesn't like to sleep.
What do you mean likes to be referenced?
Why would you not like to sleep?
That's kind of strange.
You have to rest though.
Do you have to rest?
Maybe he doesn't have to sleep.
Okay, well.
All right.
What about these other two?
Let's make sure they're at least doing something.
Let's do automatic.
Ah, fuck me.
I didn't mean to press X.
Let me go talk to him.
He likes references.
I have those.
Item, reference.
Items of knowledge.
Here.
I just have to show it to him and he likes it.
Is he holding it?
Ah.
He doesn't even read it.
He just looks at it and goes, yes.
He's happy.
That's my favorite book.
As you know, I'm building an underdog story here.
Let's take, let's get them.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's still do the caves.
Try to level up again.
Bring him up.
Kill the shroom.
No, I want to progress in the cave.
Because he's almost level five.
This will at least get him maybe into the move or another trade maybe.
That'd be good.
Oh yeah, right.
I have to turn this down every time I come in here.
Give shroom a chance to let him prove himself.
Nah.
It's going to end up as a scenario where he accidentally comes.
Roberto's going to get hurt.
And shroom is going to have to come off the bench.
It's going to be the last person.
I'm going to be the coach sitting there staring into the audience.
Being like, is there anybody in here that I can throw?
Any of you?
I'm looking for my star quarterback got hurt.
And no one's going to raise their hands.
And I'm going to have to go to the bench and there's going to be the shroom.
And I'm going to, I'm going to wince and go.
Get in there.
He's going to be like, oh, okay.
It's going to be a very, very defining moment of his character.
He's going to get in.
He's going to get the ball.
And it's going to be, here we go with like five seconds left.
One, two, three.
And he's going to go back.
It's going to be in slow motion.
And here comes like somebody on the left.
Oh, it's a blitz.
It's an all out blitz.
And as his sweats coming down his head, he's got to prove that one fucking point away from a win.
Literally, he rears back to throw.
And the cuts to the coach.
Can't believe it.
Oh, did I make the right decision?
Somebody comes he didn't see from his right.
He grabs him by the arm, tackles and rips his arm off.
And he just looks over and starts screaming at his arm.
That's now just a socket.
Countdown goes down to zero.
You lose the game.
You didn't go fast enough.
Roll the credits.
And as the credits are rolling, like he's getting put on a stretcher.
And like the coach is seen.
Was betting on the other team.
It's like, what the fuck is that?
Hold on.
What's going on over there?
He's playing with the other coach.
He put him in.
Okay, that's weird.
The credits keep going down.
After like another 30 seconds of credits, there's a school board meeting.
For like the college.
And they're shutting down the sports program.
Not enough money came in this year because of that horrible loss for the college.
That's not how school funding works.
If you lose a monster football tournament.
Oh, I got another one of these.
You need a psychopath so you can take all the glory yourself.
Now you're thinking, now you're thinking with portals.
These monsters are so easy to cut through.
All right, five, what do we get?
That's it?
I don't think you get anything for level five.
Not even flex tape.
Please no portal spoilers.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Most of the items you find in this dungeon, you give to your monsters.
Later on, items need to be appraised.
Then used in fusions.
That mist, how?
You need to milk rumor before he died.
No.
You can't do that in this game.
I just want to get him to level five but it seems like he didn't get anything.
Why do I keep, I don't know guys.
I wish I could tell you why I read those.
It just kind of is there.
As a one hit kill.
I just, I look over and I see it and it's just, oh okay.
One guy.
Read the good boy messages for once.
All right.
I'm no longer going to read those messages that come up about like milking people.
So don't even try.
I really love your stuff by the way, have you?
Pretty good try.
Damn, okay.
97 damage.
Do you like the TV show The Venture Brothers?
Yeah, it's a good show.
It was fun, funny.
Didn't they bring it back for like a special season or something?
Or is it actually back now forever?
They're still making episodes.
It never ended.
Didn't it go on like a hiatus for six years or something?
More than that.
It was a long time ago.
Nobody stands a chance.
152 damage.
I just, I don't belong here.
Almost level six though.
All right, can anybody help me with the...
Hasn't every Adult Swim show been canceled at some point?
Yeah.
Adult Swim is such a weird network.
Because they just like kind of throw spaghetti into the ceiling.
And then sometimes a piece will stick.
All right, what about the other monsters?
Roberto can't help you, but what about the other ones?
Can the bunny do something here?
What about Prover?
But I think some of my, probably some of my favorite shows,
at least back when I watched TV every day were on Adult Swim,
there were some really good shows.
I have like four of those.
I hate Prover so much.
Don't you understand?
Well, just wait for the football game.
Please, no.
That was too dark.
Get in there.
Really? You're a little bunny rabbit and you can't go in a little bunny rabbit hole.
Wait, we have to see the animation.
What happened?
Did you hear that?
You have the least offensive walk.
Sound and animation.
Offensive, yeah, like offensive to my ears.
660 points.
There are too many bats.
Yeah, there are.
Languages are so weird.
There are.
I just said the same word.
English is so hard to understand.
Oh, they're over there.
What did you say?
Let's see what the bunny can do.
One damage.
Wait, what's this? Is this a scream?
This is a scream.
This is bunny Pogchamp.
You guys want to be able to enable Pog?
There it is.
I can't even go.
Back up and do it.
I can't move back to have me back it up.
Here we go.
It's called Muhaha.
Muhaha.
What?
Oh, this is.
How much damage?
Weak.
What about, let's bring in the plant.
Prove it.
You got Pecking and Joseph Pollen.
Joseph Pollen.
Pretty sick move.
Sorry, I just screamed at you.
Golden Foot.
Sniper.
Probably better for the Pollen attack.
Well, he does have high intelligence, so that helps.
Another sword.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Bunny's traits are.
Power moves that use the feet and do just damage, but it's harder to dodge.
And the traits for Prover are.
Magic Lore.
Ups magic power and lets you add a magic to skill.
I still don't know what that means.
And then Sniper and Pheromone.
Increase power moves that use charm.
It's like a charm enemies.
What do you guys think is the hardest English sentence to remotely understand for someone that does not speak it?
It's got to be something with the words that sound exactly the same, but mean different things.
Follow German985 on Twitch is the hardest thing to understand.
Buffalo?
What do you mean, Buffalo?
That's the hardest word to understand?
He doesn't know.
No, I don't.
I don't know what that means.
Well, don't let him die.
Pull him out quick.
Pull him out.
Bring in Roberto.
I don't want anybody dying.
Wikipedia.
There's a Wikipedia article for the word Buffalo.
It's like eight times.
It's a grammatically correct sentence in American English, often presented as an example of how homonyms and homophones can be used to create complicated linguistic constructs through lexical ambiguity.
It has been discussed in literature in various forms when it appeared in Beyond Language Adventures in Word and Thought.
The sentence employs three distinct meanings of the word Buffalo as a proper noun to refer to a specific place named Buffalo, the city of Buffalo, New York, as a verb meaning to bully, harass, or intimidate, as a noun to refer to the animal more easily decoded, though semantically equivalent would be bison from buffalo.
That other bison from buffalo bully themselves, bully bison from buffalo.
But that's not.
All right, I'm done.
I'm not, I don't want to read that anymore.
But that's not a sentence.
turn slash nice but about I mean it is a sentence but those are just words you
just it's just Buffalo Buffalo Buffalo it's a noun verb in an adjective that's
a stupid Buffalo Buffalo Buffalo Buffalo Buffalo
yeah but you don't say Buffalo from Buffalo that's right you say Buffalo
Buffalo how late to my how late am I to the party here
word bump any word is weird when you say it let's say pick a word okay I'm gonna
use the word mosquito okay when you say a word that many times you think about a
word that many times it becomes so strange mosquito mosquito mosquito
mosquito mosquito that doesn't sound right now the speed is too much just
instantly please this is like probably there's like 2,700 people here I bet you
anything 2,000 of you want me to stop this conversation and 400 of you just
said the same word like ten times and went what the fuck James well John had
had had had had had had had had but nobody talks like that you know he
actually speaks the way that is written semantic say see say semantic
satiation if that's not like a real sentence but that's not you wouldn't
have a conversation like that with somebody if somebody was talking like
that on the subway you'd move two seats to the right you'd be like I don't know
this person's fucking kind of crazy John had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had had you'd be
like move down a few seats it's a hundred percent grammatically perfect
and that's the point you're missing the point don't hurt yourself trying to
no I get it I know it's like a complete grammatical sentence but I'm talking
about if somebody was learning English you wouldn't a difficult sentence for
them to understand would not be John had had had had had had had had had had had
had had had had had had had right I'm talking about like a sentence that you
would see in like everyday life that's not a goalpost move that's like that's
not and nobody has that conversation final guts this topics fucking sucks is
it not really it's not really a topic as much as it's a question but can be
understood through I'm not reading it I'm not gonna read it no I've already
read two of them Buffalo had had had had Buffalo had Chad what what is this
that's it I beat it so I got a new move for I was almost gonna say Chad let's
take a look there's a calm turn slash life damage a cut into is also a this
takes 30 guts this takes 20 so a little bit more to use it accuracy see
accuracy ease more accurate mid-range so it's it's kind of better than cutting
too it just takes more to use but that's fine I'd rather use that to be honest
does the same amount of damage and hits more often but just time it better with
the guts then you get something else to somebody else somebody get something
else all right you like golden sword and honey you don't like honey toast you
like sleep and you don't like to fight I told you this is the worst let's see it
I told you an hour from now I want to see the people that are writing ice him
right here it is told you this is gonna happen okay let's take a look at the
schedule sandbag I'm gonna change this because I wanted to do accuracy it's
pretty low tub target tub you only you just sleep no you have such good stats
read the book and then in the tub no likely and then you sandbag and target
all right get to work Roberto that was really good
prover is those awful I like to sleep and I don't like to do any fighting or
anything and you guys want me to keep looking you look at it I don't even care
he went to the Buffalo Wikipedia page and he's trying to learn English and now
he just brain doesn't work function anymore what does he like what do
mushrooms even eat potatoes I don't even know what would you even eat what was
he just say did that use an energy did that use an action what what happened
hey why don't you eat the thing that looks like you but isn't you it's a
completely different animal what a weird fucked up world we live in I guess you
like that little bunnies like carrots what am I stupid yeah have a squid did
that was I mean I don't like it I mean what what what does the third swing from
Legend of Zelda noise mean I don't know all right let's go Roberto has to do
what tournaments Roberto no that's a gamer fact that only a real gamer would
know I know I'm a real gamer so Roberto has tournament next week so let's do
yeah rest up that tournament in fact let's switch this around rest now and
do tub today the tournament so you're nice and fresh I'm gonna do target you
do life blade before not bad for success that's another plus six for prover but
this does look pretty funny though this is so look at the look at this bad gym
form I swear to God I've seen people at the gym do this when I used to work out
all the time it's like dude what the fuck even exercise you trying to do
you get some old like 60 year old man come over and do this exact thing this
doesn't do anything what are you working out yeah you know just my back lies
chest and legs have you ever read anything about how to do correctly do an
exercise no I just pick up things and move them do you want me to show you how
to do something no no I can do it and then that person would not show up two
three straight weeks in a row and you'd see him again it turns out that they
hurt themselves yeah I don't know what happened I tweaked my neck somehow when
I was working out I'm just getting old German is the jock that no one likes
what are you talking about okay wait that did just come off like really
really really like mean and elitist it's just sir you want to like help you out
there let me know I'm gonna show you how to do it I can do it you're gonna get
hurt okay fine see you later and I got the two two ear pods in blasting music
how do people even talk like that I have an actual question for those of you
watching when there are ear pods in your ears and I can hear every single word
and it's so loud and you're having a direct perfect conversation with me how
is it possible how do you talk when I do that I'm gonna show you guys what
happens okay we're gonna do a real experiment on spring I'm going to blast
a hill I'm gonna give you a gym song ready what that what is it called hold
on give me the gym song the gym song that everybody in the gym listens to I
know what it is god damn it oh oh come on I it's in the tip of my tongue no no
no it's not like one of those jokey meme ones it's like it's a fallout boy song
what is it called hold on where is it where is it where is it fall fall out
boy famous single I don't know the name of the song what is their most famous
song I don't I don't know what it is but I know what it sounds like what is it
called not the brown note I want to do an experiment is this it centuries hold
on I'm gonna play this like two seconds don't forget about the bond this is it
this is it this is the one that you hear okay so here's the experiment you ready
so I'm gonna try to talk to you guys I'm gonna be the guy at the gym that talks
to you this is gonna be as loud as I can make this and we'll see how hard it is
to speak here we go the thing is you have to be able to hear this you will
you will I'm at the gym you'll hear it hey bro what's going on man you need
some help with the with the bench you let me get over there and what are you
doing 200 pounds 220 yeah that's what I thought you're strong guy yeah yeah I
read that book too that's a good book I can't do it more than five seconds you
see what I'm talking about how do you talk with like this I can't fucking do
it anymore I fucking can't know it like that all right I'll try I'll do it I
swear to God I'll do it this loudest my computer can go warning the real proud
oh I'm gonna die is this gonna kill me hey it's a dating sim yeah try to like
get the jock to like you let's see yeah here you go guys use your attempt dating
sim try to get the jock to like you this has a warning on it you can't even hear
this no you can't hear that it needs to be louder this hurts my head ten hours
of the brown noise why is it not playing that just that just fucking caused me
anguish no you guys can't even hear that it's not loud enough that just like
maybe fucking cough um the fear noise no I don't I'm not doing that let me try
this okay this is this is an acting class you want to learn how to act and
you want to learn how to compose yourself during a scene they should do
this in workshops I should run a workshop and do this you're an actor
the scene is you're a jock in the gym trying to talk to somebody doing with
weights all right it's desync it shouldn't be no it's not desync this should
be synced up fine is it shouldn't be do you think this is on 650 this is should
be on 650 too yeah it's on 650 still no I think you guys need to refresh okay
here we go the video is behind I got an idea there you go all right here we go
acting class the guy at the gym comes up to you he's got earphones in he's
talking that's fucking impossible it's so loud you don't understand that it
sounds okay you can hear it kind of but to me that is the loudest fucking sound
I've ever heard in my entire life why would somebody be listening to this at
the gym this is what's in your earphones I can't do this kids you it's a bad
actor I'm not a bad actor can we hear it you got you can't hear this it's so
fucking loud here we go hey man you uh hey man you uh I noticed I will do this
until the fucking stream ends I don't care it's it's not the fact that it's
fucking somebody shitting their pants it's so loud that it scares you hey bro
notice that you were you have trouble with weights I fucking hate this but I
have to do it boogers are gonna come flying out of my nose god damn it hey
bro I I was just I was noticing that you had some you were doing 220 on the on
the bench that man I'll take care of that you know you need a spotter yeah
you're here alone you need a spotter to help you here that counted that counts
that has to count hey man hey man I'm just I was I was noticing you were on
the bench here and you doing like 220 you don't have a spotter it's weird
usually you come with a spotter to the gym bro yeah I can I can help you do
that I can I can get on the I can help I can get on there with you we can do it
together at the same time actually that's how I spot I usually I just move
to the left and the person on the bench also is we do it together at the same
time I don't even know if you guys could hear that but I tried try another scene
I just the reason why this is funny to me is I imagine somebody in the gym with
a playlist with this shit on their playlist why would you have this on a
playlist this is something that you listen to you are fucked you are fucked
up screaming and like people farting why would this person have this and you're
not even embarrassed I don't care I tell people to watch you for good content and
this is what you do to me both at the same time in different tabs oh you're
killing you're gonna kill me I won't be able to do it guys that's not gonna
happen all right I'm gonna try this one time and we're gonna do this one fucking
final time hey what are you listening to man oh you know I got fallout boy on
here oh scream and fart compilation at the same time how loud of these that's
pretty fucking loud no no no I'm fucking crying god damn it you're killing me huh
it's just a play like I keep going over over and over again the guy with the
fucking tank top and he's jacked he's got like fucking oil all over him he's
got like super spray tan he says she's like throwing weights around and you
like you he walks by you and you're just like kind of doing whatever and he's
really loud and that's what you hear really fucking loud he's like what's
fucking wrong with that guy Jesus nice monster rancher stream oh why am I I was
laughing too hard too fast I don't even know what prompted this that's in
fucking sane what what happened to this stream can we go back to
finish the skin it's the fact that and it was like the the Wilhelm scream they're
like it's from every weird video game at the same time this is harder than
secure oh it is it's not even the fact that it's like funny because it's like
oh somebody farting oh harder than secure is a hard thing this is like the
hard thing challenge no that's it I can't go back oh I can't go back I look
like a bully from the Disney original channel movie I was about I was about
turn of the acting again and be like hey shut up bro they always have that tongue
like that you want you want to be like a Disney Channel bully I'll give you the
quick this is acting tips remember this is an acting stream now say a sentence
and then slowly smile and bite down on the edges of your tongue and then walk
that every time if you want to be like a character that's like an asshole yeah I
mean you lifted those weights pretty shittily for a weakling you know
I mean bite like that what happened my stream I didn't why did that happen what
that wasn't supposed to happen no I'm going back to playing Monster
Rancher we I don't remember what we were doing it's time to play the game I
don't know how long I've been doing this for but it's been way too long oh my god
this is this is the scream thing let me see no no no dude I swear to God you
just I just cried on stream you could take a clip of this like right here
just watch this why is this so sad to this person what like weird fucked up
place is this well like no no I don't want this look at this forget about
this part here because this is where I start to lose it but look at this right
here
three hours with your eyes I'm gonna take a break I'll be right back this is the
worst thing I just got up and moved around and like got I go and pee Kim is
in the bathroom and I'm just peeing she hears piss going into the toilet right
you know what that sounds like and then it would stop because I was laughing so
like I cook it was like she's closing me up bang piss comes up real fast like
after I can get a breath and stop just like you know get over it right she
goes wow that's a vicious pee I have to start laughing again I'm broken I have
to have to sit here and relax I really do why was Kim listen because she was
like the way that the bathroom is set up is there's the bathroom and then there's
a door to the toilet so it's like this tiny little airplane bathroom that's
inside of a bathroom it's kind of weird there's a door to the toilet but then
there's an actual like bathroom with like a sink and shit there's like a stall
in the bathroom I have one of those see somebody knows what I'm talking about
how did we get there because the mushroom was doing a weird workout that
I made fun of the workout and then I got into how people blast music in their
ears and it's hard to talk and then people at the gym do that and it's like
funny and then I don't know they got somehow from there but we are going to
try to just get composed here and continue to play this game I I am I am
I'm mentally drained but I just get a break for a minute I don't even know how
long that went on for but here is a monster rancher for here it is let's go
ahead and continue what we were doing what's the link this is like okay new
format oh my special boy is graduating college oh what a beautiful what a
beautiful beautiful day it is for my boy that's like your dad that's like dad is
happy with text next to it and maybe an image that comes after it or before dad
is so happy he's crying do what you will that's a wedding dad right there
that is a first dance wedding dad hair too somehow like my hair got all fucked
up in the back all right what were we doing my boy there's another one is
another one is another one this is a good one I'll cap this one for you all
right now that's my boy what about this one you could use this in a lot of
different formats couldn't you I don't know why I'm giving you guys so much
fire here but hold on look at this this is important oh fuck my hand I'm sorry
this is fucking embarrassing but I don't care whatever there's so many fucked up
dumb images of me on the internet like whatever I'll give you this one myself
okay this is called half that was happy sad no this is sad dad this you actually
could be used I'll put it on screen we'll break down the differences here so
hold on let's see my boy wait so let's get this one with the other one why can
I click this all right so here we go it's gonna be called my boy let's put
these next to each other so you can see what I'm talking about one of these is
you know my boy I'm so happy and the other one is oh no I don't know about
this I mean they both could be rims and chin what what do you mean oh you mean
there you like okay
yeah look at this though get in real close here like this is real look at
right here that's actual real emotion in those eyes there's pain there's
happiness the suffering raw emotion there's more of these no I gotta move
on we can't this is not even a picture I don't understand you just took come on
you this is not even about you doctored this image all right is that like is
that what I think I look like when I look in the mirror you know I mean I'm
looking at a mirror in a dream remember I told you don't look at a mirror when
you're in a dream this is what you'll see you'll see like a goofy claymation
version of yourself if you look at a mirror while you're dreaming you look
like a bird which one looks worse though let's let's be honest where is it I
actually think that the other one might look better you deliberately fucked with
this and I think the picture on the left is uglier than the one on the right I
mean the one on the right is like more handsome this is ridiculous okay I'm
done you look like an orc oh when is the self-conscious hour gonna be over I'm
just kidding all right I have to move on we have to go no more no more we've
spent our time we've had our fun I need to train monsters in this game on the
X out of the window that says screaming compilation that'd be good the one with
my hands and look at my long my fingernails all right let's go all right
that's the last one I promise I'll keep this one for a little while how did you
take an image of me crying and do this look at the hair though all right let's
go uncanny Valley yeah that's that's like somebody inputted me into a program
and computer generated me if anybody still gives a shit about German 985 in
a hundred years they'll have a computer that will get but that's gonna be in the
corner all right I have to change this now because this is not gonna be sync
it up anymore there we go
big tube face who didn't have a competition today I don't think they
did today no tomorrow there is one Roberto is in it let's go no no I look
just maybe into like a Dark Souls NPC looks like I look a hundred years old
this is like expectation versus reality right this is my current but current
we'll do current mood current mood all right there's enough of this no more no
more of these this is not even my face this is a different person's face whose
face is this okay either that's not my face this person does not exist calm
right this looks like my brother okay all right I'm done this is like
evolution but like what do I do I like evolve into this thing something the
forbidden one not putting that one on this is all right hold on we start here
I don't know is this like this is like okay this one here's the start this is
where I like devolve into like the computer generated person and then I
turn into this you guys are so quick with this shit it's fucking hilarious
okay I this is too much fun that is real this is what's really going to
happen I want you to remember this I will look like this exactly it's gonna
be completely the same oh fuck wrong thing this doesn't work like this I got
it hold on almost there is the evolution this evolution of my boy yeah so all
right you got this is what like dad okay I got it this is what dad looked like
when he was in college and then dad you know met your mother and then they had
children and this is like you about my boys are growing up there they are my
boys and girls are both growing up getting older riding the bike for the
first time changing diapers move on to here he proposed he proposed to her my
back hurts I can't really mow the lawn anymore I might actually get I'm gonna
get to see my grandson and my granddaughter get married I can't believe
here's the day of the wedding they got married they actually did and all the
work I've put in over the decades of time finally gonna see my son and my
daughter no no no like they have two kids and they both marry different
people guys no these have to be flipped because this is like young this is like
16 year old this is like dad in college this is dad when he's a teenager I think
okay schedule I'm fucking believable so we need to rest every Roberto has a
tournament today rest rest we're good everyone's gonna gonna feed everybody
that's good plus almost nine defense from Roberto it's funny because the
title of this dream is splicing DNA on the ranch and that's kind of what we
were just we're doing with me so we got a tournament today cool okay
tournament today okay sorry I had to take a second today's the day for
Roberto I gotta feed Roberto food squid you like squid don't you I'm gonna move
this I'm you can't continue like nothing happened look that was the
intermission the stream goes on that was like the episode 2 of stream Monster
Rancher stream to speed the rabbit potato that was an exhausting intermission
yeah there's all of it how many do you have German thick that's not part of the
family that what if I just filled out every one of my last emotes lots with
those what dog shit what a terrible channel this would be imagine if like
half of my emotes were just all those images all right Roberto let's stomp it
mean the planets that put the planets at least have like a transparency
background it's not just clips of my foam in the
background that was something else all right Roberto versus Fiddler let's take
a look at the enemy here it's gonna be with one hit kill or two hit kill
why like stunk fucking hurts yeah that's audio foam yeah that's the new
move turn slash it's really good he's so good he's really so good he's got BBS
colors of course he's good no we're gonna just win instantly could it be
sweet Ryan definitely I think so key ready one two three he's too good that
move is so good it's just it is a one hit kill on 90% of everybody we got to
get him up quick before he dies I'm gonna just do tournaments with Roberto
get him to like rank B and a this thing is terrible just kill it whoa how do you
get one of these how do you get one of the big dogs I would love one of these
big dogs risk of rain two is out yeah I think actually I think me and it's out
because I'm gonna play that one in a couple days looks fun it is an a rank
unlock cool 1500 gold eight more fame Roberto getting popular it's very good
cool peaceful Haley five community subs from peaceful Haley thank you Haley five
community subs thank you that means a lot thanks all thank you so much
oh there's another image if people want me to click on I guess I guess I'll do
it let's just be the beard I don't look like here what car what like cartoon
character or actor is this Juno upset oh thanks to the five community subs you
look like Arthur Morgan no I was gonna say David Spade but Juno upset oh thanks
to the five community subs thank you oh god that one with like my eyebrows up my
let's get you intelligence training are you tired now you get and let's get you
some acts yeah accuracy training and then you sandbag training and then rest
and then light blade twice sounds good and then I'm also gonna make sure you
sign up for the next possible tournament which is where's it this one right here
Roberto get it and then the official tournament is the next two days afterwards
uh I can't like play when shit like this is in the chat you know how difficult
it is for me to like focus on this video game when this is in the chat over and
over again what image is this and why is it still in the background no let's go
all right he signed up for it his training is gonna be yeah so he's going
today all of them are doing something not bad everybody's pretty good how are
you doing you got tournament you need to eat tired praise you're doing great you're
actually doing a great job and I'll feed you too because you're hungry give a
squid gotta feed the robot yeah for some reason you're gonna sleep before the
tournament and you need to eat too I'll give you a squid lively and you are
tired though so to bed is this better than Monster Rancher 2 ah that's it's
hard to say so he's gonna rest today they both I like Monster Rancher 2's
minigame system better because this is kind of just numbers on the screen
whereas you got to actually see the fun little animation play out and and
although they were they were repetitive it was still fun to see them all right
we can buy something maybe here what will you do I can I buy a bigger house
like blade tub trampoline target book sandbag what am I missing trampoline
target I have no I have it all how do I buy a bigger house praise anything
customize is there a way I can custom I can buy a bigger house I do have to win
more tournaments it's another corn emote what am I missing another yeah there's
like 10 or 12 corn emotes flying around can't really do anything
all right calendar we've got another tournament here almost ready to get out
of D rank and to see rank hopefully you can do some some accuracy training you
can do some more like we need some more help on you who cares rest and then your
tournament sounds good begin well that's terrible some people have all
their whole channels emotes corn related how the hell would you do that
that's almost as dumb as having him be completely planet related like every
emotes a planet just like a royalty-free NASA image with like your face on it
from like a picture you took at Blizzcon like four and a half years ago I mean
you can eat too I know you don't like bananas but do you know do you like
bananas let me see get Roberto in their steam role another time yeah steam roll
another competition and then we can finally climb out of this dumb rank
German says he won't read gross messages but spends an hour crying at a fart joke
it wasn't the fact that it was a fart it was the fact that it was loud and it was
the whole scenario it wasn't just the fart that I thought was funny it was the
entire bowl soup it wasn't just the carrots it was the lentils it was the
kale it was the broth the whole bowl soup was hilarious to me
Freudian weapon thanks for 10 bucks no 10 bucks 10 community subs not 10 bucks
that's way more than $10 Freudian coming in 10 community subs thanks for 10
bucks thank you Freudian 10 community subs rolling it did I just described
farts like a bowl soup no I described the whole scenario as many ingredients
into why I thought that was that funny German is a mature streamer that's I'm
not gonna it's all right by the way this is a fluffy dog rumor that's actually
pretty cool turnslash and just wait bingo Roberto
maybe I should just build up I think I'm just gonna oh okay for Roberto now I'm
just gonna build accuracy and power and just try to beat the complete glass
cannon where you have you just have really high chance to hit and just try
to kill things in one or two hits preferably one hit opponent quit afraid
of Roberto holiday versus they're all the same monster I got this in the back
I still have this corn on my monitor gets out of here every time I close a
window there's another fucked up image that I have to see I have like 10 tabs
open that's it one almost one hit it's okay what is a higher hit percent chance
slash does well I missed the kick no that's not good no that's not good at
all all right back it up getting close now closer closer closer closer
all right that's why I got to build up accuracy and power you run into a
scenario where I'm just gonna burn through guts and lose what I get the
money yeah the dashing is what did it but I just didn't want to get in range I
got a peach cool Roberto getting pretty popular almost 50 so then let's take a
look at the calendar you got official tournament here or Roberto let's get him in
tip-top shape we have two cycles to work with today let me see 228 power I
got to get that accuracy up German a lot about Minecraft VR thanks to five
community subs more community subs rolling in thank you guys more community
sub drops you guys are very generous thank you accuracy and speed are
probably what I need to do accuracy speed and power so let's take this get
life out of here accuracy speed let's do accuracy twice and then we'll rest before
the tournament he's tired he's tired we'll do we'll rest now and then we'll
do two days of accuracy training that should be good what about you guys you
let's get you into yeah let me just even look up you guys are just useless so who
cares your life your intelligence a great power act but you're not gonna be
doing back accuracy and defense probably important let's just do accuracy and
intelligence then or this is good intelligence like over 200 or defense
I'm gonna say defense defense book is fine and then what about you kind of
balanced all the way around except your health is terrible uh I'm gonna say
health and speed or health and accuracy let's just do health a couple times what
does intelligence improve it improves magic damage any move that is a green
move not a yellow move yellow is based on power green is based on intelligence
so it makes you do more damage with your green based intelligence based moves
and I believe it also increases your defense to those moves as well at least
I think that's what it was like in the second game yeah it's like magic resist
because defense does not help with magic damage I don't think I think that's good
you just need health right health and health
your health is terrible all right good night not reasoned by very much
tired you can rest tomorrow frustrated oh no wait how are you doing lively good
have a potato what flavor mushroom is that lemon lime that's a sprite flavored
mushroom oh sorry a surge flavored mushroom it's probably more accurate so
the tournaments tomorrow right here so I got a couple of days you killed Wally
no I had to I had to do it all right you're frustrated so you don't do anything
today rest and then book you are tired so rest and then like blade you are
going to target training and then maybe target training again go for it that was
really good plus 12 into accuracy and we doing it tomorrow as well good work
anybody else need anything I think everyone's asleep yeah you're good next
day next week competition is one more day nobody can join this one so I can't
do it this will hopefully get us to see I really hope so because that'd be the
first time we've been able to do it I'm getting carried by Roberto oh yeah
absolutely so you can probably do this training and be fine yeah and I'll just
feed you you'll be fine you're lively okay not bad please don't be tired nice
okay good have some good food we're gonna give you a oh I wonder if I should
give him an energy bar no this is too expensive maybe I'll just give it to
him so I can guarantee myself yeah I'm gonna give it to him take this and get
us into rank C he's good Roberto's gonna get addicted to energy bars fuse him
before he dies his genes are too good to lose I'll make sure all right we got a
bullshit ending on the last time we did this by Calabrino last standing like
three times my stats are really really good I have amazing moves this is just
high intelligence watch out for the int attacks I gave myself some more
accuracy this should help a lot he's already starting up good block get in
there get in there don't let him do anything
all right all right I'm gonna stick with this just a regular slash does so
much damage just twice if you can start it off with that turn slash move the
jumping one then you're good to go but if you don't get it first I'm not gonna
do it again because it takes 30 guts not a good idea Roberto currently is
probably gonna live to three and a half years old energy bars boosts and remove
some of the remaining time alive yeah that's good to know so energy bars
actually take years off of their life
state pretty much balanced across the board except no power and no defense
really stay away from the intelligence moves from what it seems and go bye stay
in close see you guys at rank C cuz that's definitely where we're gonna be
at the end of this and I'll see you at rank B not long after probably
most I've not seen so far since playing very many high-power enemies everyone's
building intelligence for some reason very few high-power enemies all right
that's all right not good good final guts all right that's annoying
that's also annoying not good thank God final guts is the worst
oh is there a way that I wonder there's a move you can get where you just turn
off their final guts I wonder if there's a stay dead move it always ends in
Calabrino so I just have to beat everybody here all right here we go high
power of high life decent speed this is gonna be hard I get it I'm okay I'm not
gonna do I'm only gonna do slash here because it's the highest accuracy that
I have he'll dodge everything just getting close that's not a good start
that's a really bad start just don't even give him a chance again 78% chance
to hit this got only one more two more fights Roberto versus Calarino round two
have you improved at all high intelligence low power high health so
just watch out for the intelligence moves and try to just burn down I'm only
gonna go for slashes here I already saw that dialogue I already read it in a
funny voice didn't I all right monitor guts get in close and slash good block
84% chance to hit this perfect do it again 83% goodbye that was we didn't get
that was such bullshit last time I did this was two final guts going up to
rank C Roberto really is just extraordinarily powerful that's why I
want to try to just grind to rank a so we can unlock some more monsters how
could I lose to this kid this is just unbelievable whoo two grand of a squid
Roberto you've done it you brought us into a new ring congratulations Fane I
had no idea you'd come so far I mean no sorry what it's all right see oh no that
was me talking it's all right see so I can't even believe that myself I mean
shoot after I was kicked out of Elvis school I thought that I'd lost my last
chance there are always chances people just overlook them Rio you've really
made a wonderful ranch Fane you look after this ranch in Rio too yes sir leave
it to me cheers oh you really did it you're all I thought you'd be now you've
got to sit your sides higher next stop the competition ruin the Femba hotspot
the kingdom capital Roy win yeah we can do it I needed to know why I had this
power and who I was here at the ranch I've been gradually putting the pieces
together I won't deny my identity anymore I'm not afraid of the truth hey
real I'll find my own path as the true Rio the truth is it what do you mean the
true Rio good job you deserve rest rest and then let's work on that accuracy
say maybe I'll take them into a can I go anywhere new now that I'm rank C
anything to a different so here we go to this nothing at all until here which
obviously you're gonna sign up for it it's a long time yeah can I can I do
something else because that was the cave I don't maybe I unlocked a new place
we'll find out anyways resting book sandbag and everyone's hungry I need to
go to town you can't go to town right this second go to town yeah and I saw
that go to town when you can you can upgrade the house in the new day yeah I
saw I saw it I saw it I saw it I saw it I saw it a little hungry potato I don't
want potato well sure if I have a banana then frustrated lively okay here you can
too buffalo buffalo buffalo there you go energize frustrated hey man I see you
dead lifting was that 250 without a spotter only the caves all right I need
to buy food or somebody you said go to town shrine association item association
what can I do for you today shrine so what will it be a praise now just a
moment you don't have a saucer stone whatever whatever you old fuck what
what what wasn't that bad Oh Fane look at that visitors from the ocean what from
the ocean what do you mean Rio oh that looks like a monster on its own like
giant turtle aha so this is that ranch I've been hearing about the Hoyt who
are you ah yes the name's gun wheel I'm a proud man of the sea the Hoyt what do
you need excuse me Paul told me about the young band of travelers heading
across the city of the capital and notice that you were doing a 200 pounds
spotter think about coming in here helping you out be careful and maybe if
you scoot over but such marvelous young people can't do without boat so I
rushed over here to offer you my trusted sardine you see ahoy you mean this boat
we couldn't no no no don't be silly except my old partner the sardine will
once again sail the seas with the youthful hopes of riding upon it it's
just marvelous don't you think ahoy uh yeah I guess you're right well then it's
settled you take good care of my little sardine now head south young folks ahoy
he's gone and what was up with that fellow it was really strange I don't know
how he was able to talk to us so clearly with all the screaming farts in his
ears it gave us a nice boat why would this guy just give us a boat what a
stupid guy didn't even ask for like money all right I'm gonna assume that
means I can I can probably go somewhere else now we'll try that but first wait
a minute feed your guild members in stream legends why is nightbot saying
that is nightbot playing stream legends what the hell anyways so let's just
keep building look let me see what I actually want to do with you let's get a
good training regimen accuracy and speed with some power sprinkled in in
between so we'll go to the speed speed accuracy speed power speed all I have is
the high jump mmm I think I'm gonna get the buck
maybe I'll just stick with power and accuracy then accuracy accuracy power
power accuracy power rest accuracy accuracy accuracy power no rest power
so we got power accuracy power rests accuracy accuracy rest power fuck it's
sick who cares just do automatic with these idiots speed and then we're gonna
auto do technique go for it and he's a little higher than that I don't have to
do it again though have a squid let's take them to the new zone rostrated
you'll be fine have a banana now have a potato getting like stream legends
exploits in the chat look just be happy okay feed us I will I did that the end
of the stream Honda Honda Toyota Toyota Toyota Honda Toyota Honda up down
Toyota Toyota Toyota Toyota now I wish I could play that game for real lively
everyone's good let's see if we can do something new here for the adventure
adventure toggle caves what I have a boat now why can I do anything left right
left right Toyota Toyota Toyota Honda okay we get everyone scheduled calendar
let's take a look at a calendar that's a long ways away good gain and accuracy
good you're just doing fine good okay lively lively sleepy sleepy just keep
the training up pretty good gains all around whoa hello we're good well the
whole thing just fucking died there for a second we're good the internet like
just exploded for a second but I think we're okay oh it hasn't turned off it's
probably going through a rough patch like it does sometimes tired you need to
rest well I have more references here look at this don't you like this and I'm
gonna feed you to potato Roberto wants pork pork where do I get pork from pork
is not beef I want pork can I go get it oh wait a minute new town city of
academia and cultural known for its coliseum library and monster studies
whoever well let's go here you get yeah I know you wait but where do you get it
in the game the capital brilliant it's even bigger than I imagined look at
that fame it says ruin rookie club wow a new competition well let's go have a
look while the scale of things is totally different and it's pretty cool
oh shut up uh there's like a million people in this crowd huh is that you
thing Graham why are you here nice to see you what the heck are you doing here
I can't believe you quitting school all of a sudden and all that now here's
something you won't believe I became a breeder here in ruin I was doing this
thing I kind of screwed up this competition that's why I'm here wow you
became a win ruin breeder right after graduating Elvis school you dummy
there's only one real ace who graduated from Elvis school and it's her look up
on the stage you take a good look at the champion breeder what Philia you
from our same class she's the top ranked Fimber rookie and she's cute too
she's earned instant popularity she's really incredible Wow everybody's
working so hard I can't wait to battle with everybody oh I'll go to the
Association and ask if I can enter the competition welcome to Fimber I'm the
receptionist Pierre hello Pierre we're here to first your appointment name
please what we just came from toggle we don't have an appointment well that's a
no good I'm sorry we can't see you today what first fill out in this form
and then this form and this don't forget to dot your eyes and cross your teeth
whoo-hoo come visit us again next week I don't know why I had it is no way we
just came to see if we could enter the room competition now listen here this is
the Fimber headquarters we can't have people coming in without appointments now
you come again next week and we'll answer any little question that you have
but for now well the exit is over there it's nothing like the toggle monster
Association shoot we'll just have to come back next week softlock softlock
softlocked softlocked softlocked oh I was gonna do it right before coming here
but the I got distracted oh no I was gonna do it right before coming here but
I got distracted by the other town and now the game's softlocked itself thank
fucking God get me back quick oh my goodness that would have been such a
horrendous end to the stream because of what am I gonna go back and do three
hours worth of Monster Ranger again get me back there quick that was I didn't
save one time this whole entire stream look at that that's the walnut is still
in here guys that was before I even froze walnut and from her
shit that would have been so bad that was this entire stream almost three
hours all right let's see how I fare in C rank we got a couple more three or four
more weeks what are you doing you're resting today yes you're very tired you
deserve it target training twice and then we'd be
sandbag training after a rest that's good pretty good recovery why did I
freeze rumor because we got to the realization that Roberto was the only
one that was gonna take us through to a higher rank so then we made these two
assholes that were just kind of funny characters to be side content comic
relief characters for the main character who is this one and so far I think it's
worked out pretty well you almost gave me a heart attack with that softlock I
almost had a heart attack in the chair here playing the game we went in almost
softlocked or hard I would be a hard lock at that point we can do anybody
frustrated here just be happy what would you have done if it had actually
crashed I'm gonna be real with you guys I am having a lot of fun playing this
and this is like you know the second stream we've done of this game and I'm
having a good time but that would be so devastating to me that I would probably
just put in mr. mosquito and maybe I would do off-stream I would just grind
up and do it again you need to eat okay you should probably eat too you don't
want potatoes though here have a peach this is like shaped like you you
probably like it you loved it but adventure is still a toggle
caves all right let me go back to town and actually inquire about tournaments
and stuff maybe that's why there's not an official tournament let's see so it
appears that you attended Elvis school but later dropped out meaning that you
don't have an official breeder license then you can't enter the competition
what but I entered the toggle competition just fine according to your
toggle registration you entered with a recommendation hmm well for local
competition recommendations from a respected member of the community is
acceptable but we can't have just anybody entering the top level
competition hmm but fame is the toggle champion then it shouldn't be a problem
for him to get a real license now if you would kindly shuffle over to the exit
all right we need a license shoot we came all this way for nothing what's
with that I can't believe this I go out on the road for a bit and that little
brat philia goes and turns into a star what a cruel world TT and she's in a
very bad mood huh it's you the ones from toggle this is too much I'm going
home this instant move it or lose it grandma yeah she hit her head on the
fucking ground are you all right she had to hit her head on the ground what's
gotten into her oh oh no she's hurt her bad we better see her home took you a
long time to fall down but you okay you sure are sweet I forgot to introduce
myself I'm more it to me I don't deserve such kind help from strangers thank you
so much for playing in my game don't mention it are you going to be okay oh of
course oh you just stay still do you have any medicine oh please don't worry
about me I'll just be fine my daughter's coming home soon and I'm oh that would
have been embarrassing good thing I didn't do it I'm whole me I did it
anyways well speak of the devil Oh visitors oh hey yeah that's how it
happened they brought me home what a coincidence that this is that thing that
you're always telling me about grandma don't embarrass me but boy oh boy it's
been a long time huh fain ever since that one fateful day yeah now I work on a
ranch and toggle but I'm not an official breeder yet on a ranch that's
great I was really worried that you would give up on becoming a breeder all
together well for a while there I almost did but I'm okay now thanks for crying
um Philly uh could I ask you something it's about your grandmother she's doing
a lot worse than I expected she's what yeah grandma's been very weak lately
normal medicine hardly helps her anymore if only I had some healing mushrooms to
make medicine from but they are rare in these parts healing mushrooms and toggle
really often I can go search for them really gee thanks sorry okay so we're
gonna get healing mushrooms in the cave what about the library hello and welcome
to our library how can I help you talk this is the largest library in these
parts and it's open every day of the year how many time how can I help you
look monster mysteries the Elvis school
oh monster this Lee is known for its long monster lifespan currently people
are investigating whether this is because of the warm and comfortable
climate you can't read the rest who cares somebody else to read the
screenshot it some short books two pages is that a book or is that a Jehovah's
Witness pamphlet I think there's more information on those item shop welcome
what you're gonna do let's see what you got pork you probably have pork here
you don't need chocolate no you don't have any pork got carrots though I'll
take a few of these watermelon mango banana mushroom potato I need I have like
two actually two ladies chocolate chocolate egg let's get like two of
these mango let's get like five days and then you have scream this is the scream
the mochi's expression changes from different bit this is this is a famous
painting Ruby and this five thousand dollars for Ruby two thousand ten bone
I'll buy a couple I'll buy a bone it's like ten cents we can go back to the
ranch now I got enough items it's a human bone I got a pee damn it really
hadn't even been three hours and I have to the second time I had to pee pee
break unfortunately scene a minute hey I'm gonna meet for a second cuz I just
got I just got a soda and I have a soda on screen I want you guys to be able to
hear this though I mean this is like the beginning of every single movie you go
to this is the sound you hear usually plays like some upbeat music like
please turn your phone off enjoy the movie you don't hear that you guys
don't hear this how did you hear the oh it's because that this is still on oh
god damn it I poured the soda over the ice and it did the like fuck it who
cares fucking old man we care we care I'm glad you guys do thanks for care
because I had the audio still on for here this is interesting this is an
orange vanilla coke it's strange yeah it's all right it's not bad you know
this kind of tastes like it's tastes like what do they call it like the
graveyard sludge when you go and you hold the button down across the whole
entire fountain you go to like orange soda sprite coke cherry coke what's that
called that's what this tastes like swamp water there you go yeah I mean
that's not a bad thing if you want if you want to drink some swamp water see
birthday today happy birthday napalm hope you have a good one everybody say
happy birthday right now to that person all right it was gonna do training right
nice level 9 accuracy that's what I'm fucking talking about you're okay you're
frustrated you're both frustrated look at the focus on you that's bad you're
gonna settle down now you're okay about you okay okay okay okay frustrated
scold him no they're doing fine all right everyone's all right proceed to
the weekend which will take us we have to do the caves to when is that
competition it's soon isn't it yeah so we'll do this and then we'll go explore
the cave look for the healing mushroom and bring it to the lady how sick is
this lady because we're not gonna be back with this mushroom for like three
or four months that's just kind of trying to figure this out is that this
can take us at least six to seven weeks to come back with this all right rest
target get that accuracy up yes tired you get to rest and then I'm gonna give
you some food here too a good one one that you really like a mango that was a
that was a good one hungry hungry I think they're both sleeping yeah no
shit hey wake up you're in trouble god damn it just getting April fools here's
a carrot after this first competition for rank C we'll try schedule you are
yep you're on everything's fine with you everything's fine with you you are
resting today and then you do power training and then it's first ever
attempt at a rank C tournament pretty good gains you need to eat mango you
guys like fruits right does everybody like fruits yeah McDonald's fries cure
baldness am I is this a stream that I did like two years ago we already talked
about this this is which this was a huge point of contention two years ago when
we talked about it's not true this is the day of yes so he's lively sandbag
training will be fine give us more power before we first go into rank C I'll give
him some food too come on big gains big gains nice you are not focused I gotta
get you focused what do you like yeah I'm gonna give you something to like get
you back on track likes the sword I could show you the sword but I feel like
that's really as a waste yeah the sword guy you think would like the sword but
he likes books instead he's more into books okay where's the all right you
guys are fine rank C first battle this is $3,000 and you get a fish see if I'm
gonna get my ass kicked here with Roberto stupid questions what's Munkah
s Munkah s is the oh what what the fuck is that face
lock rim let's see how good you guys are pretty good 275 speed 200 intelligence
188 attack power no fucking come on I was trying to say like go back he's now
he's fighting for himself I was trying to go back like no go back but it's give
commands I wanted to look at my stats in comparison hopefully good luck that was
the right start come on one hit you're good you're all right without me yeah
you're fine without me good again final guts who cares it's the most bolster
hit him again don't let this person do final guts and come back please do
anything and fucking win please what are you doing why even have that as an
option just stood around and then died you've run out of gas okay well all
right this is Valens I have to win everything now high intelligence high
accuracy let's just end it not gonna live a lens pretty cool design that's a
dog with a gigantic binocular in his head one single binocular it's like a
sniper scope that was a wow 70% chance didn't hit it holy shit easy slow down
sorry not that much damage went for it I'm gonna wait for my guts to build up
he's bullish just hang on hang out I'm gonna get this kick take less than
slash more than slash single one more he's out of guts that hurt but he's out
of guts it's not good got it so okay everybody has lost one match that means
it's anybody's game Vinette 225 intelligence actually pretty good across
the board revenge of the walnut that is just Wally the same exact kind that's
how you that's what I want to see right off the bat almost 200 damage instantly
killed that's why we built so much power go back to it more power more accuracy I
want to build do that every time and you guys were telling me that I shouldn't
have frozen one three thousand gold in a fish
okay good work calendar we've got another one of these so I'll sign up for
Berto and then hopefully let me see here so that's this one then so let's see
that's also the same one in February March Jesus May where's there an
official tournament there is no official time really
oh it's cuz I have to get the license I gotta get the license so how much time
is between there so we got let's take them to the caves and find that healing
mushroom hopefully then that we can get a license handed to us and then there'll
be an official tournament hopefully soon after these ones here already signed up
for this one all right let's go let's take a look we got sandbag now rest and
then we'll do two sandbags and then rest that's fine that's good you're on
automatic anyways automatic for speed for technique who's hungry the fish is
going to you know who I keep trying to give prover a potato and they never
wanted you think I would have figured that out by now no not yet feed us you
guys fine all right now you're good sandbag sandbag level 14 power I want
him to have over 300 attack power sleeping you need to eat yeah I was
Roberto still alive he's not that old he's not even like a year or two old now
I'll give you a fish you're probably gonna love it rare in the seas of Togo
the nice monster tree here feed your guild members how long do they live for
between I believe between three and five years depending on how you treat them
how tired they are how your training goes right it's between like three and
five three and six years you got another tournament here at the sandbag rest
target that sounds good he's killing it right now did I superglue Wally's mouth
shut no I just froze him he needs to rest come here one more day how are
things doing go ahead take a look around what will you do still don't have
I don't have another level up for these like sandbag hanging punching bag or
something or weightlifting it has to be a third or fourth level why would you
stop a little too if I need to find an item or something I'm gonna find those
tablets right Twitch streamers stroking his ego it's towards stroking his ego
I go I don't know what you mean by that Lego my ego rest and then target make
him feed you guys all right you know what here listen everybody relax open up
your open stream legends if you want it I'm gonna I'm caving here I do this at
the end of the stream usually extensions stream well we got it open
ready three two one there you go I wasn't making it up look bro I fucking
love Monster Rancher well so don't we here we love this franchise here what
you gonna give what you gonna give us a follow yes and I mean every all three
thousand nine ninety eight people here now he's good competition two no what is
it oh it's next week right it's this next week okay you are lively but a
little hungry you'll be good after this and then your tournament comes up this
will put a bit around nice plus 13 Roberto has had at least five to six in
a row more than ten steps all right let's give him some food let's praise him
too you're doing great you're gonna carry us all the way to be and see an a
rank feed you a potato I don't have I don't know if you like carrots do you
like carrots you do this all right Roberto get in there three thousand
bucks and it's a fish ever so closer to potentially ranking up to be ranked
Roberto versus Boonin Boonin Boonin has nearly 200 in every step which is
really good lots of moves hard skin this might be challenging I was a 300
attack power though speed and intelligence are so bad I don't know if
that's that's gonna be bad thing for me almost 300 attack horrible cockroach
dog let's go you know what's gonna happen here right off the bat nice got it
getting close slash came over you don't have a chance I can't fuck around in
these because once you get to like C and B you can die in one or two hits so I
have to make it count I can get one shot by some of these people all right this
is Tilden Tilden one why that's why my defense is so bad to 202 power it's just
gonna come down to who gets who hits first essentially all right I have better
accuracy don't I oh you got it first sorry I'll answer right here fuck not
good do it again come on don't lose this here come on don't lose it got it nice
all right now get him a slash quick again 70% all right I was pretty risky
that's it do pont I guess no I can lose this here if I
listed du pont how did you lose so many that insane accuracy insane speed and
high and terrible health though that's probably 125 health do you pond this
should be one hit see if I can get it so good I just build power and accuracy
and I can just always open with that move and win that strategy might not
work getting into rank B and rank a but at least I'll get there
Alberto is almost too famous almost 100 fame all right so now we're gonna save
the game rest up a little and then go in the cave
schedule so we've got everyone's tired let's just have this be a day of rest
for everybody and then you're going full-on sandbag sandbag accuracy
accuracy
all right everybody go to bed food has to go around here it's very hungry
yeah these guys are just bait to go do the adventure mode
all right I'm out of food hates carrots hates potatoes hates carrots hates
but I can't know I'm sorry I think it's time for you to go into the fucking yeah
I'm sorry you you you suck you're too hard to deal with we'll get a new
monster you're fine you're good to go Roberto hates Jeremy I remember that
that was so fun all right weekend activities let's go find the mushroom
crush it right now not yet so you're trying to healing mushroom I want
Roberto to get all the experience here did you beat Sekiro actually I did not
I got to the chained ogre and lost a hundred and forty five times and
decided the games probably wasn't for me so I just moved on it was so good it
really is these enemies are nothing now well energized leveled up to level 3
hard head and on show okay can I do anything with this Roberto's almost
level six or seven hopefully he gets something else
come on mushroom all right maybe another couple random encounters so Roberto can
level up have you beaten ender dragon in minecraft yet no but what happened was I
actually I got to a point in minecraft I started it and found out the game just
kind of wasn't for me I got to a creeper and it exploded and I died to a creeper
like ten times in a row and I was like I just don't think I can it's the games
are for me so stop playing that's actually true is it though almost level
seven come on did you ever beat Saxton Hale in team fortress 2 well no because
I opened up TF2 for the first time and I'm I'm of the opinion that a first
person shooter should not have somebody that can kill you instantly from behind
so I got back stabbed and I was like what this is not even a fucking first
person shooter and I got like irritated so the games just kind of off of me
hundred and seventy seven damage can I go to a different cave did you ever
graduate from high school well now what happened was I got to high school and
it was in ninth grade and I've just I couldn't do it the geometry was way too
hard so I just said like yeah fuck it is kind of not for me so I just didn't do
it I stopped high school you know just nothing level seven nothing at level
seven why really at that's kind of dumb it's like a long time to get there you
can dodge one you can dodge two but you can't dodge three you're dead yeah I
gotta get to a new zone this experience is not good enough for Roberto uh explore
everything I feel like I have to find the mushroom I feel like is it a cut
scene thing or could I have missed it here I was watching a different streamer
last night and somebody asked in Chad if they died to pinwheel if you even if
you die to pinwheel that's all right that's not even a big deal why is that
some super unforgivable sin if you die to pinwheel in Dark Souls what if you
happen to have like an itchy ass when you go into the encounter I don't know
maybe you put your controller down because you didn't the cutscene came up
and you went to go grab like a snack or cheese it's or something maybe you just
got unlucky and you just got hit I don't know it's not such a good deal they
didn't even have a chance it's not like losing to the divine dragon Roberto can't
help you investigate this any I don't this part I don't understand this who
can help me investigate these things do you have to be like a water monster or
something I'm just gonna let Prover get hit in the head in this next encounter
mushroom where's a mushroom Prover can't help you with that I don't think anybody
can what about Roberto Roberto can't help you with that Prover is the
healings room what oh look how good you are actually kind of good he's got very
high intelligence and it's poison got a teddy bear the bunny can't fit in there
I don't think mushroom obtained silver coin yeah we tried to put put the bunny
in there last time nobody can do anything with that can you give the
teddy bear to my little brother no it's mine you see those video clips of the
baseball home runs where this is some buddy sitting next to a little kid and
the big home run Wow and the guy or girl whatever reaches over like the kid
and grabs the home run and cheers and doesn't give it to the kid that's what I
do isn't that part of a Will Ferrell movie probably yeah soon I caught it I
caught the ball I caught the ball I did I did it no no you cannot have the
ball no it's my ball no probably something like that yeah you probably
root for the Red Sox so it makes sense all sports fans of the same sports fans
as Jerry Seinfeld once said you're rooting for laundry god damn it I should
be trying to level them up anyways no of course you want to support your team
right I like the Red Sox because they grew up in the area and they had a
stadium it's fun to go to games and hey this is the team where I live I think
wrestling is wrestling now I don't think is cooler but the idea of wrestling is
cooler I think because it's a theater show where they actually like to hurt
each other kind of and there's like like a big in baseball if they were like
dramatic story arcs where you know at one point the center fielder got like
kidnapped or something and an old guy with like a vase came out and halfway
through the fourth inning like resurrected the center fielder or
something I imagine there was like the wacky bullshit from wrestling in
baseball and football yeah turns out I don't know what happened the entire
outfield is not here we haven't seen the entire outfield in two straight days but
they're gonna play the game anyways and it's just the infield and they there's
like fly balls going over their heads and shit and then finally after like four
of like a five maybe six innings it cuts to backstage of the outfielders coming
into the stadium they're getting into the outfielders here they are they made
into the stadium and then a car drives and runs two of them over the car who
is that it's like the manager of the other team oh my god oh that's Bill
Broski the third base coach for the Orioles and then the one outfielder has
to play every position imagine if the wrestling weird shit was in other sports
instead of the pitcher walking from the bullpen they like how do you like an
elaborate entrance he like comes up from the ground and this like fire around the
mound like gangrel used to do back in the attitude error he drinks from a
goblet of blood that's a gangrel used to do that where the hell is this
mushroom and all of them instead of special moves they had special they'd
know they still had their finishing moves but it was weird pitches and wacky
baseball like batting stances and you knew when he did the weird fucked up
stance it was his finishing move and you might hit a home run here the pitcher
changes their windup to be their finishing move wind up and it's like
here it is the quirky ball this is just making the Mario games real life as of
what it is Mario Baseball is just what I'm describing Mario Super Slugger but
wouldn't that be fun scream it scream what baseball somebody asked earlier
what's with all the violent sports references what what are you talking
about yeah they'd have like weird special
abilities like I know like we're talking about Mario sluggers but imagine if
somebody was like this really like decrepit small old man came up to the
mound it's like oh here it is this is old man yeah people I don't know what
I couldn't I couldn't think of a name he comes up and he gets to the mound and
everyone's like oh wait that's who this guy sucks like who's this guy's terrible
and he pulls up well you know everyone knows of course old man people's got the
cannon he sucks himself but he's got a great item he gets on the mound and he
loads the baseball into the cannon and it's like shoots into the catcher's
minute like 7,000 miles per hour the catcher would have to just get out of
the way no the catcher gets a special item too that's why you have these two
guys work together one of your catchers has like a metal plate for a catcher's
minute and he does like a wicked comedy stance when he loads the thing and does
the lights the fuse he likes if using that jumps back and goes puts his
fingers both fingers in his ears and crouches down everyone screams old man
no no no he's just he just screams crouches down it's gotta be a loud one
Mario Kart double-dash but with WWE wrestlers didn't they do that already
energize obtains cave search really doesn't move to have to learn yeah they
already did that yeah i streamed that game i forgot that's true i that was as
well that was a stream on this channel i genuinely thought that you made the
gnome video for a while what i did too i no i didn't uh 10 community subs just
came in from pin man thank you for the 10 community stuff big sub drop thank
you that was quick i think i'll probably get to level 8 after this one maybe i'll
learn something new something at level 8 a new trait new passive there it is
Roberto mastered midair midair midair is that his finisher
mid holy shit life damage s accuracy a this is what i'm using now what is this
is short range takes almost my entire guts meter takes 50 guts so it has to go
in this short range slot but holy crap that's i have to put it i'm gonna
replace kick we're gonna try this out i'm actually i'm gonna do this too i'm
gonna put charge down here i'm gonna put turn slash here i'm gonna put regular
slash here and then midair here
let's see what this does it says the highest damage you can possibly have for
a move in the game and one of the highest accuracy ratings let's see how it
is midair wow uh oh i don't know if uh i don't know if it's possible for me to
lose i think i will take this character to s or at least a ranking and wipe the
floor with everyone because that move potentially will doesn't matter even a
high health pool it's over 200 220 250 health is a lot of health that's an
instant kill move and it's one of the most accurate in the game rose perfume
it's pronounced midair not midair but don't tell me but don't let me tell you
how to live your life midare midare midair midair midoria
prover flower dance is this it oh sick yeah sick yeah sick dude dude sick yeah
yeah sick yeah put in a little too much the mushrooms were somewhere around here
what is it i hear the voice of a monster it's saying be gone from my territory
something's headed this way watch out
blobster oh something's coming it's the blobster let's kill him in one hit he dodged it he dodged
the midair not this one all right let's clean it up with a swing all right you two guts relax
see you later blobster oh i get it he's a lobster wow good thing i did that with
roberto i was level nine well that was a real tough one not really oh look fain over there the
mushroom i feel like i just did that on stream i feel like i just like activated one of my scenes
can't believe you remembered this yeah if i see something once i rarely forget it
that's why when i picked up the gaia stone and saw the vision i felt like i'd seen it before
let's go home we've got to give this to maro yes that's right joke incoming no not really
february week four week four
let's go give it tomorrow save the game what's versus data i think that means you can bring
monsters to your friend's house approver on ice not until i get to rank b with roberto
well you know what fuck it let's do it now actually i want to do the let's see what we
got for training here we wanted power and accuracy with roberto it's plenty of power
that move is going to be incredible and then under incredible undodgeable
and i will win the entire video game with roberto
but undoing couple undodgeable hey these guys are gonna be dna food oh hungry right
um oh you don't like any food i have to go to the town you can eat in a minute you're fine
you're all right i gotta buy some food
who cares if it's going into the freezer anyways that's true
let's go give the healing mushroom we found some healing mushrooms here they are
thanks so much fein i'll make some medicine from the right away
you're too kind fein my back feels just great i have something to give you today here you are
it's gonna be a license a letter from mr carnab what you mean the femba president carnab
precisely carnab is an old friend of mine i told him about you really let's see it's gonna be a
license dear fein i heard about you from maro and you sound like a truly admirable lad
and an excellent fighter if anybody deserves a breeder's license it's you but the real world
is not a simple place so listen to my proposal first i ask of you a favor have you heard of the
kalaragi jungle well it's a very odd place the jungle is littered with these gadget thingies
well more like junk and i want to investigate them would you please retrieve the junk then
if you pass a little test i'll give you your license what do you think hey hard to believe
he's a high ranking association member teehee well how about it fein are you ready to take
on the challenge of course explore the jungle and pick up the junk
oh uh guys i was never soft-locked i had to press x
so apparently there's that
need food all right we want i need more carrots
five of them everybody wants potatoes anymore mangoes everybody likes mangoes get tennies
library who cares all right now we have to do more jungle exploring with a new adventure
unlocked probably gonna be harder it's all right so this is fein's ranch hmm okay here i go
hello there what are you doing here oh uh well i wanted to thank you for the other day so
shoot you don't have to thank us no i do and about the battles in ruin you better learn new
battle techniques if you don't learn counters you'll have a hard time i wanted to warn you
counters what kind of ability is that time to learn a counter the counter when an opponent
attacks hold the l2 button then push the button you think they used i'll use an x button move
uh so i have to guess what button they're pressing but what do you mean x yeah but you can also change
skills by pushing different buttons try performing a skill with the o button yes with the o button
you perform a skill precisely damage is lowered but you may contact more often next try performing
a skill with the square button to perform a skill with force what how did we not hear know this
before why is the tutorial for this yeah why is it halfway through the game it's not halfway
through the game so circle is force does a lot of damage x button yeah that's what i've been doing
this whole time what does that do i've been doing every single move with x that's a no okay normally
try using the x again to perform a skill
so i have to guess at what button they press and okay thanks well fooey you get away from him girl
huh tt you came all this way geez lay off and go home
you sure are charming you must think you're king of the world today i'll show you who's a real boss
around here get your pesky assistant and prepare yourselves oh boy well okay let's make it a tag
battle let's see what you got tag battle that mechanic is the whole reason i dislike this game
i've had so many victories snatched away in s rank because of that oh all right we're going
up against your garbage and calorino okay time to learn about tag battles first the tag how to
switch monsters i've done before try this l1 l1 tag out now you've switched in tag battles you
were able to use partnership powers take a deep breath stay still and wait team up there now your
partnership power is charged now you can carry out a chase attack while your partnership power
is rising the skill panel turns red select the panel and use a skill after you perform a skill
the standby partner will do a chase attack so that all right so you have to have the team up
did we even we didn't even play why you you have the nerve to use combinations on me
this is just the pits i'm going home counters and tag moves this is so cool thanks philia
not at all i'm glad you like them well see you around fain best of luck i can't wait to use
those on you because you're going to be the champion of the next area and i'm going to use
tag maneuvers on you and you're going to be like i can't believe i told you that i told you those
things all right so we can do let me see no official tournaments so i i'm gonna i'm gonna
just go to the jungle everybody let's feed and what do we got for schedules who's tired
everyone's all right
book high jump and sandbag and then we can feed everybody and then do the jungle
or we go i don't think both of these guys just suck should we should just make them
dna if we can try to get some new monsters yeah sorry roger oh i don't think he knew that i was
just a mushroom this whole time stan stan i can't believe you didn't see through my disguise
and you maybe both people suck uh i want to go to town
have some fish we could do some combinations but where i could put some discs in look at how
hungry you are well it's you just are they friends they might not be friends to combine
what is it what's this link that is a long messy link not a virus it's not that messy
that crying face is gonna follow me forever let's see lawful good neutral good chaotic good
lawful neutral true neutral chaotic neutral neutral evil lawful evil uh chaotic neutral and
chaotic evil are the same image except in chaotic evil there's a little bit of gray hair dusting
just having more gray hair makes me eviler yes apparently there's gray hair in all of them
the fuck there is no there's not i don't have gray hair all right should we go to the haba
select the monster to be retired
look at that 303 power energize sucks 160 160 not good enough 241 and 212 really isn't bad
but you just you just aren't very good freeze roberto or no balls why would i ever do that
i've ranked up to another rank let's see if we can get some new monsters i got a bunch of
playstation 1 games over there and some playstation 2 we'll try some of those
create i would like to use a saucer stone all right let me grab hold on let me grab
some of those other discs over here stuntman alias the ring stuntman again the jackass game
let's put in let's put in the ring put in the fallout boy cd i don't own i don't own a fallout
boy cd there you go for proof he could be putting anything in there he could be putting the same
thing in there he's just like he's just acting on stream i mean i'm a fucking damn good actor
this is the ring burn the brown note onto a cd and then play that and do that i don't even have
i don't even have a burnable cd i don't have to burn okay i have a question those of you that
i don't have a cdr or anything but i have a question is it possible for me to burn over this
this is just a disc right can i just delete this and burn over it there's no way oh well
it's read only read only memory so this is from the ring thank you for waiting
no shroom no shroom no shroom and no rumor either
well let's put alias in here this is playstation 2 i think it actually might be the dreamcast
curse yeah it's just dreamcast i don't i didn't want to believe it but now i do alias something
give me a new seed let's see something awesome something that i'll be proud to level up after
this we'll do jackass the game um all right what the hell is this it's a skull flower
not a mushroom let's i'll take a look at it it's the mushroom but it's dead
the unprover unprover doomer i like the unprover i don't think it'll fit though
so
now it doesn't fit
unprover
i can do the actual word but i can't do two o's the way that you want unprover i can do unprover
the unprover unprover isn't a word yeah i know unprover try another stone this is jackass what
does that word mean that means that you are um if you're a prover that means you're proving
something no fuck it whatever so an unprover uh this is that's weird to understand explain i
know what it means but i can't explain what it means does that make sense it means that you are
supposed to be somebody that can prove things but you're not being able to prove anything
you're a disprover but you're unproving things it's i i can't explain it you guys know what i mean
so debunk no no but he's the prover that's his name his name is the prover the unprover
at that i mean we're not using that's not the terminology like proving something
it's his actual name he's the prover guys it's a proverb thank you
you guys are hilarious all right jackass the game see we can get unfunny unsubbed oh my god
oh my oh i wasn't even in frame i got a dragon that is from jackass the playstation 2 video game
is the wow okay well i know who we're gonna be playing with freeze him no thank you take this
monster home uh-huh damn it i can't do roid spiro stevo i can do spire how do you pronounce it
spiroid spiroid that's pretty good
spiroids all right there we go spiroid that sounds like an illness oh yeah i got spiroids
and add a heart at the end no remove the s spiroid yes we're gonna take this monster back now
okay hurry up i need to see the stats the base stats here combine spiroid and roberto to make
god wow you're fucking huge all right let's see come on uh 163 intelligence base why is everybody
laughing that base intellect level nine 163 base intellect don't he's bad okay yes it's all right
though is the unprover better 153 what about the moves fire fire and bite and then power moves
with the tail d bite what is d bite all right what about you unprover what do you got i kind
of like unprover let me see again what do you have the moves uh this is pecking and pollen
kind of like the other one but much better base stats yeah they're not going to hand us a god
character that's true he's good 163 base stats at just being born is really actually pretty good
147 power 163 and just mash intellect and um accuracy and can be used for a fusion later as
well this is true all right um let's get them in let's get them into the uh let's go intellect
and uh accuracy oh maybe i'll just hammer accuracy for a little while let's hammer accuracy
and then uh rest we'll bring up uh intelligence book gonna be a smart dragon
again rest and we'll go to
more accuracy and we'll take a look at it after that all right you on the other hand
what do you need uh defense and intelligence maybe you kind of need a lot of things intelligence
and accuracy defense and speed maybe defense in life i'm gonna say defense in life for now
okay and then we'll take a look at it afterwards there will be the book it's an int now you on the
other hand you're doing just fine but you also need to rest here and then we'll do power let's
take a look here we go that's a lot for being zero years old unprover didn't do very well what
does this dragon like to eat good job save i'll save i'll save i'll save i'll save i'll save
it's the skull and you're doing fine too all right proceed the weekend activities let's
should i just take them yeah let's just take them out to the jungle i have Roberto Roberto
can just carry everybody free experience free exp i mean maybe Roberto should just go
i'll save yeah save first okay Roberto's so much better than everyone else yeah but he's also a
lot older think of it this way if i do three or four weeks of intelligence with the dragon
there'll be over 200 intelligence that's pretty great actually all right target sandbag and
lifeblade game is saved and we'll take everybody into the jungle after this i'll tell you though
he's got really really good stat uh stat adding usually it takes him to like at least six months
before they start getting that much so he'll be really good stat adding okay what does he eat
though are you gonna be mad if i give you like a carrot is that thank you or is that no thank you
okay you're doing just fine i think you eat uh you eat mangoes and shit i can't believe we
got a dragon out of jackass okay uh i think it's time let's say good job to you too
so proceed to the weekend head to the jungle and let's continue because i want to be able to do
higher ranks bring everybody it's just free experience for the other two because they're
not going to take any damage well at least i hope not jungle so we're just supposed to explore this
and find the junk right uh you currently have unlocked dragon and robot you can get a cool
robot dragon or bone dragon or shroom dragon and the the i want to have right now is part naga so
it likes fish okay good to know let's see what happens uh well that's it even in the next area
he's too good he might be too good level nine obtained wind lure i don't know what that means
let's find out so there's a fish type that's funny what is wind war
ups wind and fire power and lets you add a wind power to skill you still don't get how that works
you combine Roberto and the dragon and get a metal dragon that would be crazy well i got an
intelligence stone whatever that means help for your information yeah i know i know i've read it
the first time that's so good i'm gonna play with a spiroid for a little bit try to get him some
levels am i using square i'm just using x at the moment that system's kind of weird forward i bring
up the dragon what the hell are you guys doing over here now you know but you know the car when
you're driving the car you know there's a i know the gas pedal but there's also a brake
you've not maybe you might well put your foot on the brake and just gently put your foot on it and
press it a little uh-huh and do a drift hey as long as you start to slow down a little
come on where's the stuff this stuff here can i touch anything with the bushes or anything no
i want to see what the fire looks like what is that thing spiroids let's see fire that is such
a weird monster seriously holy shit this thing's amazing real shit just got real probably should
try to counter that that was awesome so you gotta do those quick and guess it correctly so you have
a one in three chance to get that right and you have to do it fast got him the anime move
hard skin and detail level up a couple more times see if i can get another move or two there
it doesn't very much help but Roberto carry um can somebody dig
can spyroid dig actually no you have to learn it don't you yeah something you learn by leveling up
burn that's big let's go big on it power move real i don't know what that even means
he blocked it blocked it again he's bullish uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh he's gotta hit it here
uh-oh i missed well jackass dragon oh well how are you still here well he was just bullish half
the time nice dodge he's that counter now you're dead lower lifespan well he shouldn't have missed
four of the moves i tried well what does bullish even mean like stupid it means stubborn
well don't be so stubborn otherwise it's gonna get you killed he learned he'll figure it out
he's just a baby i know what bullish means bullish in like a stock market term is not
what they mean in this game it's like a financial term that they're not like oh things are looking
bullish not this again i didn't say it i didn't bring it up i tried to fight to stop it from
happening nothing how can i cross this oh almost got the teenage mutant ninja turtles
boss character ah this thing almost level 10 so it's not this way wherever this random junk
that this guy wants is not here this would be level 10 hopefully we get something good at level
10 actually countered it unbelievable dude all right so it's just turned this is this just turned
into a guessing game yes really oh come on if you don't try to counter you can still block it
welcome to the reason why i said go back to two well we're already this invested
magic lore for Roberto unprover obtained sniper Roberto mastered air shot and unprover has slap
now air shot what is air shot air shot accuracy a so it's an intelligence move was it like a
moonlit sword move that's a lot of guts damage i think that's the highest guts damage thing i have
yep so this is a far range i can put it pretty much anywhere
so my intelligence is terrible though and i also got the magic lore helps magic power
uh what about the other unprover got pecking slap
slap is a accuracy much better accuracy but does barely any damage uh this is kind of just uh
light move to maybe get one last tap in for them to guess and uh block it
all right let me find this thing great now the other baby is gonna die no he's not check it
no if he gets hit once Roberto's coming well Roberto's coming Roberto we'll get it
let's try it air shot that's pretty cool if you know if you have to zone somebody up oh fuck
don't let that happen i could get out of here they're almost dead this is bad i don't want to
lose any more health i hope it's in this box they're not prepared for this yet oh shit oh no
all right i need to get to the menu i need to sort first before this happens
put Roberto up front because otherwise he's gonna get hit and die item do i have anything
thing no oh use when combining to regenerate a monster with higher intelligence that's pretty
cool all right please be in here toy junk get me out of here before somebody dies
fuck this is bad let's just hope for no random battle this is it right look at this huge area
that's good obtain a speed stone oh my god this is so huge no don't do this got it come on
oh you piece of shit no no no no no no no block it no he's my health is fine how do i get the full
health from can you do something please oh my god are you serious he's so strong i can't do any
fucking moves kill him oh uh jexie toop uh thank you jexie tup for the 50 bucks 5 000 bits just
came in right now thank you for 50 dollars jexie tup oh god this is bad and jexie tup you say i
hear you used to be a substitute teacher do you have any stories or is that just a rumor thanks
for the laughs you're pretty good hey thank you um i've told a few stories before there's one time
where i just had a british accent the whole time i just pretended like i was just british that was
it i used to draw shit on the board i used to draw puzzles on the board to have people try to solve
they would call the uh they were called what's it's that's a friends episode i got dirt search so now
i can search the dirt on the ground but i need to activate this but yeah i i did do substitute
teaching what grade did you teach i was a professor in college uh what's up rayo this is the same as
the stone in the cave this is the gaia stone my old friend can you hear me the same voice that
i heard back in the cave destroyed and battled my soul fled into a stone even without corporal
forum i am here to help you just who are you i offer you support and guidance to help you keep
the world from once again falling to darkness close your eyes gaze upon the fate that must be
prevented uh what is it rio this rock it's uh i mean it's nothing sorry let's go thank god
those are all in-game sounds yeah let's get some good sound effects
so now i should be able to go get my license let's go to the association we saved it though
uh so let's see let's go to the schedule i don't know the calendar
Roberto needs to do one more tournament
so this one here until they're able to try to rank up to b
so let me see what i got here schedule let's do some more you should rest you should rest
you should do target practice yes and then rest and then we'll go back to the association
uh food let's give you a give me a mango i like you because you eat all the food i give you
you don't complain about eating a potato or a mango you don't have one specific food that
you'd like to eat all right association time it's because robots don't have taste buds
did i not complete the task hello welcome to our library y'all gonna help
um the guy sent me the letter and i did it i don't understand
um give me some
do you sell fish for any meat how do you not sell meat
um
i don't understand the next part of this i didn't get the junk oh guys i gotta pee again
i don't understand why are you taking a bunch of liquid
it's already signed up
yeah i'm trying to pee again i sometimes this just happens sometimes okay i will stream
for eight to ten hours sometimes and pee once and then i will stream
we'll be going for five hours and pee like four times i don't get it it's another vicious pee
no i hey i've been to the doctor i've had like tons of blood work done and tons of examinations
done over the last few months i my my blood is clean my body is apparently clean i pee tested
too i peed into the jar everything seems to be normal i think it's just when i drink like certain
coffee i don't know i break all right that should be the last time i have to pee before calling it
a night oh also i do want to make this uh aware to all of you uh the schedule i don't have a
schedule but i'm gonna be jumping all over the place here sorry there's been like one day off
one day on one day off one day on two days off one day on one day off uh but tomorrow there's
no stream tomorrow i was gonna go two or three days in a row but we're just gonna move that
forward and i'm gonna end up going thursday friday saturday there's just been like some
obligations that i've had to do so uh sorry it's been like one day on one day off one day on one
day off but i am gonna lock in uh there's quite a bit to do the amount the stream's still going
on i'm not stopping now this might be you know an end of the stream voice but it's not um i have i
told you twitch has approved of my scratch off stream so that's gonna happen risk of rain with
italics maybe more monster rancher 4 some more vr maybe and something else very special something
very very special will also be happening uh during that period of three streams in a row late april
fools no no no no a lot of you already know what it is but it looks really really fucking cool so
nothing tomorrow but we're gonna go like i said friday saturday sunday not labo no something way
more special than just playing labo clown car but let's keep going i just want to make sure
people wear that that those are not gonna be anything tomorrow we're gonna come back on
thursday and i will do it i will do three days in a row after um things kind of keep coming up that
i have to take care of they fall at the time periods where it just makes it so i can't stream
but let's go let's continue for like another couple hours we've got
all right i need to go find the junk he's already signed up for this one what have we got how old
is roberto because this is roberto is a year and a half almost roberto is a year and a half
he's only we gotta get him up there now so much power some let's get over 200 accuracy
and then i'm gonna move into once he gets over like 220 accuracy i think we'll split it between
power and speed or power in life power indeed probably power in life maybe a little bit of
defense so he's resting today he's gonna do get that yeah we'll do two let's get the rest of the
accuracy out of the way try to get like 220 240
and then power power and we'll take a look after that you on the other hand you're doing book book
rest yeah intelligence tub tub rest all right okay sounds good hydrate i'm drinking right now
i'm currently consuming a beverage right this second fine you're fine you're okay here
have a carrot is it water it is the it is the coca cola that i've been drinking for the last
two hours and on my last break not the one you just where i just peed but the one like from
two hours ago i did drink a full glass of water before i came back up here he's lying no that's
not a lie that's for real everybody's working today there we go two more accuracy and we should
be good to go with accuracy until probably rank like a i would assume to give you some food good
job first of all and carry please die already Roberto why are you saying that really ban that
guy a dragon that eats carrots i need to get meat almost there to do potentially the official cup
is to go get the junk i'm sure everybody has something to do today yeah no you don't need to
rest back to the book then rest you no don't rest you're fine target target target you
uh just do sandbag sandbag sandbag rest pretty good hey that's not bad it's pretty good
it's pretty good pretty good pretty good all right you now need to press
i swear these little flower guys eat more than anybody else
the mushrooms and the flowers eat way more you you you eat more food than the dragon does
how makes no sense all right now everybody seems to be this is a day of rest
rest rest rest anybody feeling down everybody good lively let's give you something to eat too
a mango this time this is like a little snack okay you're good lively lively and you're all good
a little bit more training
so let's get you into the accuracy right but i want to do one more
let's get you into the book again and then you into the light blade
pretty great gains Roberto should be fine now for accuracy for a while he's probably over to 22 30
and let's also good work
okay everybody's all right what we got for competitions something's coming up right
yeah cup of more weeks Roberto has this that'll give him enough to actually compete
and bring him up to here to be so let's see let's block out the week here so we got let's do
a sandbag and then maybe a rest here yeah let's say sandbag and then rest he should be good to go
and then we'll from there going forward we're going to do power and life or power and defense
you need some more accuracy yes you do and health is fine for both of you good for
all right you can relax now what's with the gross plant get rumor back
um i really hate to tell you this but rumor is rumor is dead i'm sorry
here have a potato you liked it no he didn't like it he was he was pissed off at that
all right you got a tournament tomorrow so it should have been you it should have been you
instead yeah who's gonna raise them who's gonna play i will me maybe i will so this is today
rest today target and you can rest today too and then do life bad plus four only what's up with
that oh you're tired all right you're yeah uh i'm sorry but roberto is the last one i have to win
don't feed your monster potatoes it's the worst food in the whole game even if the monster likes
it well i actually haven't been i truly have not been i've been given to mangoes and carrots and
bananas all right shouldn't be too much of a problem everybody in c rank seems to be just
across the board 180 190 on every step we saw that weird monster with 482 intelligence that time
made no sense
i'll just bully you forever i want to spray that flower with roundup oh my god easy
he already is dark dead how do you kill which that is already dead
my power with fire that's not a good start
all right look at that damage look at that damage he's unstoppable unbeatable immutable
unbelievable irreplaceable irredeemable undeniable this is versus push
oh 232 with insane accuracy just kill it fast kill it fast aesthetic that's not good
again quick thank god that yeah nice game mechanic that actually sucks i can't fucking
wait for Roberto to win again jesus christ that arrogant fuck thinks he's so fucking tough
of picking on unprepared ai's what a load of shit what's the point of having attorney
if we know what the results will be all right out of any coffee pasta just coffee paste
bullshit my favorite it really is the one about my mom bought me a laptop for my birthday and it's
heating up my laptop and just burning my legs that's i that's actually a funny thing
coffee pasta's like all right here it comes but that's actually kind of funny i don't want i don't
have to get no isn't it like it it's burning my legs it hurts and shit i thought that was that's
what it was yeah that's that's it my legs starting to somebody has the right one all right put it in
emote only i fucked it all up that was my fault i'm like encouraging spam emote only for like five
minutes target training rest yeah you've died life blade target no no i don't think i need this
anymore let me get a good look 342 power i'm gonna say life the speed is so bad life and defense
maybe or just life just stack health get it up to 200 you can rest here you rest you you you hate me
right now yeah get the get the tub pretty good health increase sick let's get that over 200
fish there we go eat this you you deserve it you earned it okay what about the dinosaur
how you doing you doing good proceed i think it's time now to try to find that junk because
Roberto's ready
how tired is everybody uh maybe i'll wait i'll wait till like the next day
hello how are things need anything today go ahead take a look around
not really unless you have something new do you have anything new
get the same shit what about i have those stones right no
no well see you later everyone's all right yeah it's probably it's time maybe you should rest
and then we'll go because i want to be able to make sure i steam roll it yeah rest today
open the book up with the tub and they'll be okay they don't doesn't matter anyways
then i can feed everybody and go on the adventure good increase i played a lot of monster rancher
too when i was 10 but then one of my monsters died of old age and i cried and i quit playing
forever that's sad but you know life life is a circle you know you have some mango
everyone's good let's find the junk in the jungle let's bring everybody let's just farm experience
for these two start exploring so i didn't do this last time somehow i found the end
but i need to find the junk
i guess time is cubic no time is a circle the earth is a circle the snake eating itself
the oreboreus is a circle pizza is a circle your brain is a circle your head is a circle
the pills i just took that make me think this strangely shaped like a circle everything just
circle man the casino chips they're a circle the earth is a circle the moon is a circle the sun is
a circle 87 chance to hit now i think that's fine final guts it up now don't do drugs it's
fucking bad for you don't be crazy don't be an idiot tylenol okay i'm gonna list you the drugs
that are okay tylenol that's all
level 11 what do i get genius he's now a genius this one you thought Roberto couldn't get any
better genius increases intelligence attacks but strength attacks damage easily what can i turn
this off i don't know what does this mean but strength attacks damage easily i get hurt more
by strength that's terrible oh somebody can dig right who can dig straight down
uh unprover right i think so investigate it unprover couldn't find anything what good
are you gonna give me here man come on
this game looks like a fake game that an extra would be playing in a movie uh spyroid obtained
big lung i got toy glasses
it's very funny
is it a trait big lung increases power of moves that expel breath so fire
a fake game that the extra is playing in the movie somewhere in the background
you don't even get a chance sit down germa subs you are a germa sub all right junk
junk yes obtained junk toy that's it right that's what he wanted is germa sub to germa yes but
germa is sub to germa because germa is germa is germa so therefore it just gets a badge next to
their name i thought that was a monster i just get a sub to my own channel but it's not i don't
have to pay for it it's just there i didn't do anything i just have it wait was there something
over here that i just walked by no imagine subbing to germa see to that the person just said that
and they're not subscribed so they can say that i mean it's rude exceptionally rude but we're not
going to talk about that we're just talking about facts i don't know the toy is not the junk that i
need did you wave your hands and fingers across while you said that in a kind british accent
and with their twinkle sounds made and my eyes kind of glazed over
that is what i'm looking for where is this thing star wars is too old kids don't get that reference
what one just came out like a year ago that was the biggest hit 334
all right unprover leveled up flower dance didn't oh no that was the mushroom why are
mushrooms just flowers in this game i don't bunny anymore do i no we iced the bunny
and apparently no apparently you can't cut for this with your sword somehow like digimon world
that is digimon world is that like an mmo the massive multiplayer game or something
this should even exist in this game please have this be it that's a document 10
it's a playstation 1 game it's like this but you explore a world with your monster rancher friend
i can't progress anymore i have to go all the way around it's one of my favorite games
i'll check it out am i looking for the mushrooms now i'm looking for this
specific junk that this guy wants so i can participate in the city tournament
digimon world is amazing but you hatch eggs it's like this and you get to watch your monsters poop
everywhere i love how that's a selling point that's perfect for you you definitely won't check it out
by the way well why wouldn't i just because i check it out doesn't mean i'm gonna play it
i'm gonna check it out that means i'm gonna open up a tab type in digimon world watch like a trailer
look up reviews and then decide you know what that sounds good feels so good when you insta kill
the fart streamer is judging a poop game we already talked about that why that wasn't the
reason why i thought that was so funny you're putting words in my ears that's fine yes words
in my ears you're currently putting words into my ears and i don't not like them i don't like
hearing them great wing probably trait great wing our moves that use the wings you guys don't have
the twitch integration uh better twitch.tv notification sound thing every time a line
of chat comes i can hear you guys because i want to make sure i know when a chat message comes
through every time almost level six for unprover i really don't know what this is
it's causing me anguish yeah i get an email every time there's a chat message twitch sends
me a notification it's hard though i mean i'd like to know exactly when in the time the date
stamped when i get a chat message in my chat room but it can be hard because you know my bank
statements are on that same email so uh credit card like it's all there so i have to like skim
through like once every couple months and i'm really trying to see like bank like info i have
to sift through like 800 to 900 000 emails unprover mastered helicopter somebody said you know you can
just search emails what is the search box i don't have i just i just killed a fucking new
anime i didn't see what it was because i've been one hitting everything i don't know what that
monster was golden foot and flutter can i walk forward five feet without this happening
i mean i guess i was farming experience everyone write messages with the word bank so he can't
find them
if only that were real bang yeah i'll just search the word bank and i'll find it
search result turned up 41 000 entries the place to dig you suck unprover two in a row
important info please open give me the junk oh come on can i even do this
is this something i can physically do all the way down is that a timer uh it's an energy meter
i have to get out of here before they get sizzled we're really remotely close to it
i can help you out with your emails just give me the password in the email okay
i appreciate that really you'll help me that's really thoughtful of you do you need anything
else is that all you need there it is jungler d it's like a velociraptor face but a pd piranha
as well fire lore for roberto gust i'm getting a lot of um intelligence moves for roberto now
i want your neopets account i need those worth any money there ain't much left is there a neopet
that this many years later is actually worth more than a couple hundred bucks hey this is
city bank just want to let you know that we lost your money what what the fuck are you talking
what do you mean city bank how's my money gone what the fuck i gotta look into this
so city bank just like gave me a notification right here i was it was in chat i don't understand
that's weird that it would come up in twitch chat it had like a username too it was weird
let me just check no my money's still in it let me just make sure that the ball i have two accounts
of the city bank let's see eleven dollars and four dollars in that statement all right no that's good
no it's maybe it did get wiped what are you spending all your money on
where is this stupid item why is this part of the game gated i just want to take him to a tournament
all right third time's charm is your last chance if you don't get this i'm actually going to freeze
you nice knowing you fifty thousand dollars has been transferred to stir you did not complete this
transaction please contact city bank customer service um that's no that's real that's weird
that's in twitch chat that's real okay i don't know what that's weird that pops up here though
keen fang trample machine gun machine let me see what that looks like
so let's see machine gun critical hit rate is a all right maybe i'm not going to put you into
the friar lady again all right machine gun is long range so it takes 40 guts to do that
accuracy is terrible the dance flower dance it's a charm all right well let's uh get dirt search
already keen fang of course that's what it means uh you got something new too you got trample
uh this is really good tons of guts damage massive crit rating tons of damage
actual to health and not terrible accuracy takes 34 guts to do is it long range
uh this is my flutter is a super accurate move i'm not sure what this it might be a status effect
we also have detail trample uh detail
i guess i could put it on the last row flutter is a slow that's cool
what's the best breakfast food whoa this is your animal you got jigglypuff
we stole all your money well that would be impossible considering i don't have any money
every set that i make i buy gold bars and i scrape the gold into small baggies you just take a knife
and you scrape scrape scrape filings off into ziploc bags and i've stored them all over the world
only i know where they are everywhere in fact i i've done it so many times that i had originally
a treasure map that i was going to leave but over time i did it so often that the map got so confusing
that i don't even know where they are there was circles and x's and i had a globe and it's been
done eight nine thousand twelve hundred times i only know where two of them are and one of them's
under my bed but it's only like four dollars worth of gold the other one is under a tree
i buried it under a tree and it sucks because this is like probably 15 it's probably 15 bucks
worth of gold under that tree but i i know i can bring it in like the general area of the general
forest of what tree it was but i couldn't point at which one it was i was quick fucked up for
some reason like i i i ubered here i just ubered to the forest nice story now shut up and keep
playing hey you shut up and keep playing we got a boss coming okay fine pass the controller here
take it let me talk about my gold filings while you beat the boss in one hit there's a lot of
help oh fuck i'm gonna die this is baby grute hey shut up do die you shut up employing the use of
eighth grade at the lunch table insults that's you know that's how you know it's going real well
uh stray monster left something behind it's gonna be the junk yes wonder what it is well whatever
let's hurry and take this to the monster associate okay we're finally gonna get our license
took long enough all right
let me save the game that took over 30 minutes took longer than that
we got a game wall put in front of us to go walk around in circles to find this junk
i think now i can get this done let me see
i'm really tired you are you rest
you rest too you can do target no you do something else
life maybe i don't need any more accuracy it's perfect that's better uh you hungry
i'm hungry not particularly all right let's go to the town see if i can actually do this
yes association and oh are you fain who i've been hearing about and is that little rio
oh the explorer we met in the cave could you be mr karnab by any chance oh my so it was you well
with that aside let's see what you've got for me you've done an excellent job like true master
explorers well thank you but we really need it is a reader's license oh yes yes yes yes yes that's
right but i must have you take a little test first oh my god come on out yes what is it yes
uh what i called you here for is could you please fight fain why is he so red if you can beat the
best young star then nobody can argue that he doesn't deserve a license he wants me and her
to fight an all-or-nothing single match with philia i'm you want to fight her hardly seems like a
little test but i accept the challenge yes okay show me what you got fain this is gonna be easy
i'll take the license now please thank you can i have it now or is there gonna be a fourth test
or quest i have to go in before i can continue to play the game now there's no question i present
you with a license and rank c reader status from this day you are an official fimb of breeder
congrats now you can enter the real competition yes i can thanks rio now i can enter the same
competition as graham and philia philia ever since fain left school for such a reason
i never never thought i'd have a chance to fight you again i'm so glad philia thank you next we
meet in the official competition where i will want to kill you monster again and this time
it'll be even more embarrassing because there are going to be three people watching this is
going to be 300 000 people watching good luck why was i kicked out of school i wonder if philia
knows the reason all right let's enter that tournament with roberto
hello there fan congratulations i heard you earned your breeder certification
thanks it wouldn't have happened without you caesar i didn't do much you earned this by your
own accord i just provided an opportunity for you well now that you're an official breeder
i'll be sure to ask for your help and you too rio yes father with that in mind i figure it's
about time you expanded the ranch a bit told you to come by next week coming by again expanding
can't wait till next week so we're gonna get a bigger ranch read chat members
we can now enter the competition
why did i read that it was weird all right um let's see when is the official competition
it's coming up right i don't need to do this one i already did it so we're gonna this is four
thousand dollars a cake i think we'll be ready let's get some more life life twice rest and then
maybe let's see 342 power which is unmatched probably need a little bit more life and maybe
some more defense because i yeah i need more defense because i just got that stupid trait
that makes me take more damage from power attacks so defense and life let's just do life now
life rest life defense
probably defense probably rest well let's see this might be a little too much
target and then that's fine book and then we'll just see what it looks like i feel like i have
some speed otherwise a cc train is gonna hit you hard yeah that's true what is the speed
is pretty bad isn't it
i need more food too i will get that after the end of this
don't have any more food that you can eat um six mangoes so i got a little bit fine you're fine
you also need mango no wrong person come here i feel like very slowly without paying attention
he's getting really really really insane stats let me look he's coming along 200 intelligence
i need way more health and accuracy though is the act okay that might look bad at first glance
here but remember the accuracy was below 60 or something it was horrible he looks pretty good
too my intelligence i wish i could just skip tournaments because these guys have to fight
down at the e-rank but maybe not maybe i'll just keep them for exploring and just not even have
him just be the tournament one because it almost feels like that's too much to do
they're going for like three hours how's Roberto he's been pretty good
so you actually sell meat it's very expensive but you still sell it
beef 500 that's so much squid let's get a bunch of these and did i say that correctly that's
eating screws why would i feed screws to my animals
it seems kind of insane i'm gonna buy a couple of beefs just for the purpose of making sure
people are taken care of but get some more bananas
feed it to the robot should feed it up the robot a screw
oh robots don't eat screws they might okay here i am again long time no see and feign how do
you manage to make so much progress in such a short while very loud laugh i'm nothing compared
to you you you've even got the talk down buddy well then we're going to get this done in the
jiffy just like last time we're doing this in one week all right boys thank you you okay so that
gives us another session here you can do this one more time and then rest here so let's do
like play again rest and then you need to let's do book again no let's do target target book and then
rest you need to do book
probably rest all right reberto is probably gonna just i'm gonna do speed now
i gotta put the trampoline back here though that's what speed is he's tired now
what disc did that dragon come from it came from jackass the video game for playstation 2
all right relax now this should be the end of the week let's see what happens
that just about wraps things up what do you think does this suit your tastes
view is really nice okay next is the house and hut like before tell me where you want me to put
them i gotta figure yard now back here great house
nice
okay and then a great hut
nice no no no i want okay i gotta put some more shit here
i'm gonna put i have the sandbag already out here i need the trampoline
let's move some of this stuff out of the way let's get this over here is the tub
is the life blade all the ones that are small go in the same spot here you turn this way
another single right which one of these is single this is
this that something else can go here
monster
sandbag book target what am i missing
that's it right yeah that's everything
all right five monsters can live in the hut oh god five more jesus or a five total
this is gonna get overwhelming here all right rest tub right when is the official tournament
the next week is everybody tired right now
uh rest for everybody rest rest rest and we'll take a look tomorrow see if i can pull him out
of this and get to b rank before the stream comes to a close here six hours into this
hopefully i can get him i probably i'm gonna do speed so many managements good luck feeding
all of them yeah i wish i could hire somebody to come feed them and do you know i wish i
could have somebody feed them no i don't give him beef he's not hungry he's hungry enough for
like a mango i feel like i'm gonna accidentally neglect at least two or three of the monsters
that are here i'm already having trouble dealing with these two or three
here have a squid disc time before i call it yeah i'll uh i'll after i do this next
tournament we'll see if we can get something else because that means i would have unlocked
another set of monsters right getting to b rank all right let's go well i have to you have to get
to b rank that's another thing tub he's um he'll be fine nice okay decent defense now he's doing
okay let's praise him and then go win imagine having to make five individual training schedules
and make sure all your monsters participate in tournaments that's a little too much
thanks for the stream thanks for watching no problem okay weekend oh no no no not yet
yeah you're fine all right c cup official c cup moving on to nearly the end of the cups here
i'm almost gonna be in b and there's a the final is this the fight that is your key to success
reverto versus ropez pretty strong intelligence but not even close to matching my sheer just
absolute dominating step hope my advice wasn't annoying no not at all these games are really
strange and they have a lot of weird particular things so that's fine i'm just kidding around
when i go back and forth about you know saying random things about the game and i'm just messing
around i don't think i said anything that but hopefully you don't feel that way here we go
you know how it's gonna end good start you want to back it up fine air shot i'll take it
i can't wait for him to win again dodongo versus sherry bundy versus alaman
dodongo versus ropez ropez looks like you're not gonna win this all right sherry
you got sherry is pretty scary my intelligence is so low and smoke bomb crescent lightning meteor
i cannot get hit by one of those up i'll die in one hit
again quick thank god you just gotta go in you gotta do the front flip move into the slash
okay reverto versus alaman not that scary but is not gonna miss and dodge a lot of shit
i'm not gonna go in uh with the typical guaranteed victory button i need something
that's gonna hit that's 55 70 here we go that's my way no see i guess that one right
didn't get that one it's a lot of damage it's a lot of overkill but i did it all right bundy
and dodongo are the ones to worry about these are the ones that are winning no sherry wins
so dodongo and alaman let's see dodongo is one of those huge rock monsters
that might be bad for me because all i have a power moves that are really any good decent but
high health how does counter work uh you can either press x square or circle to do a move
x is standard square is power and circle is i believe a better chance to hit like lighter
so when they do a move i have to just guess which one they're doing there's no indicator of which
it is i have to just do a one out of three chance to get it and if i miss it then i get hit but if
i counter it i actually the move doesn't work and i hit them that's not good bad start
holy shit that was okay i pressed square on that that was a power move so dodongo is the only thing
if dodongo loses here to bundy then i automatically will win the tournament
that ain't gonna happen though god damn it well let's see 336 power 355 health 272 defense
oh boy this is gonna be bad low intelligence but so do i i don't my intelligence moves aren't good
enough to do my speed is awful too this guy's just a better version of me i have to work i'm
gonna try to counter why you punks you've come out of your hole have you i've been waiting for you
i couldn't beat you at school but with my new dodongo i'm unbeatable besides i want to impress
phillias so i mean no forget what i just said i won't pull any punches this time it really is
just me but stronger i have a little bit more power but he's way more health i have to rely on
getting a good counter let's try it start like maybe i could just bully him knock it knock it
oh boy i have to hit him hit him with something come on again hailberry do it oh again do it
yes oh my god
see i'm telling you it's gonna be the big guys that do one single move that lands b rank 4000
gold and a cake you are almost as famous as you can ever possibly be he's an anime protagonist
it's not fair he never loses congratulations on your victory nice fighting now do you have a
moment to speak with me sure what is it your victory proves that you too are top class breeders
and your search in the jungle has proved that you are excellent investigators
and so i have a very important favor that i'd like to ask of you sounds awfully important yes
well we at femba sent an investigation team out to the jungle but they haven't returned
are they lost we don't know with some breeders who have gone exploring have not come back as well
and so i wish to rely on you with your skills find out what's going on in there
understood excellent you're a great help i'm just not going in there you deserve a rest
let's see here b rank now it's just to get real
five thousand dollars melons salmon all right let's see let's try it this is the real deal
this is the one thing this is a real game no mistakes allowed up here so Roberto's gonna try
it let's save the game
so that last encounter was a little bit of a wake-up call that i need much more power
and more defense because if i'm gonna trade blows then i better have at least two to 220
something plus 250 defense because at this point he's got another probably year plus of life
and i think it's time that we get to like 450 power and actually just try to one hit kill our
way to the top because spreading out here to intelligence and speed and i think we just have
to do like 400 power and just do the one hit kill move i'm gonna get to 400 power
and see where i'm at after that
that sandbag
no no no rest right you just you just want a tournament sandbag
uh let's see sandbag again put a rest in there
target that's fine uh you can do
you can do the speed nice can i get the new equipment yet uh i think i think that guy has
to show up he shows up like once every uh once every few months right once a month
you need to eat you need to eat too do you know you're fine did i save yeah i saved i got a
save point uh here's a banana okay i just want to see just how dangerous everybody is here
i can join no this is group battle oh you gotta be kidding me tag battle
i have to get somebody else leveled up and ranked up i can't just do it with can i enter this with
one person i really wish i didn't have to because i'll tell you here's a complaint about monster
ranch before at this point do do i really need to beat three of these to do an official tournament
like one of these you know i mean i shouldn't be able to go to one of these like that i should
be able to i feel like that's added shit for no reason because i'm just gonna go through here
because my stats are so high i'm just gonna wipe the floor with everybody here with the dragon
okay if you fuse roberto the fusion will keep its rank that's actually really good to know
well it's not that i want to cheat with the wolf i just i really don't want to do three
cloth league tournaments to do the actual tournament
all right what do we got all right let's get some training done 12 more power slowly climbing away
over 400 let's give you some more meat and i got some squid here what about the cake
from the finest bakery it tastes as good as it looks no you get that's a that's a really special
thing okay have a squid good where's the other guy all right always hungry
fusing a b tier with an e tier is probably not going to be as good as if you fuse it with
something else so this is kind of how the game works i guess is so you get this guy
up to like b rank he's gonna die right so in another year he's dead before he dies
you freeze him and then you level up somebody else and get them to like cb rank fuse them together
and then start that person over with insane stats and then they can just grind up to
s rank that's how it works right for the most part but then this game they have to be friends
so how does that even work didn't didn't somebody say that they have to be friends with each other
so can i freeze him and just keep him here let me take a look monster like bonding right
i mean reverto is really bonded with me but how do i make him friends with somebody else
they have to like work together or something
data school land fame raised after i how have i raised seven flowers competitions one affinity
so good friend friend they're friends great friend i gotta get the dragon up
the dragon i don't the dragon just has to be leveled up and
fused together in the time that he still has left yeah after you fuse them they become
inseparable that's true let's keep moving having five monsters on a farm should be priority number
one i guess that because then they can all be friends i guess
yeah all right let's i got up to b rank i think that i'm gonna call it here well not yet i'm
gonna make two more monsters get them on the farm save it and then we'll call it there so this
should take us another like probably 30 minutes or so let's get some new monsters let's see how
it's gonna look does it matter what town i go to well or what shrine i go to i just don't know
that there is no shrine there is there all right i do have some more of these discs up here so
which ones did i not use create from a saucer all right let's put in i put it was a jackass
was the last one who's next we got i put in stuntman this is stuntman ignition i still have
to play this one for the playstation 3 uh simpsons hit and run i do have it i can put it in but we'll
do this first put in the matrix you get a unique monster i don't have a physical dvd of the matrix
here this is stuntman ignition okay please insert the monster rancher disc something unique we have
we did unlock two or three new breeds so let's see what we get he doesn't have the matrix no
i don't ape escape i don't have that either i faked it what do you mean fake it it's a pumpkin
flower it's just a jack-o-lantern so many plants i don't want this no throw it away
we're gonna try i'll put in simpsons hit and run let me get it first it's over here somewhere
whoa whoa i almost just ripped up the cord all right what the hell even is simpsons hit and run
good luck finding that in here i have to like reorganize this whole thing oh good luck this
whole this whole closet needs to be completely reorganized all right i got lifeline the stupid
voice activation game there's so many discs in here there's so many trades that this total
distortion i'll try that we'll put in lifeline i gotta clean that closet out show it i'll show
it after this just make sure you know i'm not cheating there's a buzz sound did i fuck it up
i did rip it out hold on how did this even happen what on earth did i do um did i fix it
did i make it worse still crusty okay well this is uh from lifeline let's see what we get
i need two more things to just stand there and become friends with each other
is one of the power puff girls which one is this one blossom
like that bloomer no it's not like a possum all the thing is though listen it kind of looks like
a possum i think it works it's blossom the possum it does not actually if i do bloomer that's just
like the meme on the channel it's not even a flower guys bloomus i'm going with the original one
bloomus no blossom it's the power puff girl blossom again we'll do it again this time
we'll put in i'll try total distortion on this game see what we get thank you for not making
another boomer joke no i'm not gonna we've we've already overstayed the welcome with
boomers broomer shroomer boomer bloomer doomer this is total distortion prove it's prover a boomer
joke no it's close though let's see all right rolling the dice on this one because whatever
it is i want i think would where to go with the disc just go i think it's like 70 bucks don't lose
45 dollars at least didn't fake it something we haven't seen yet not in the flower or mushroom
or rumor something we haven't seen oh give me a fucking break
uh so this we're gonna do the we're gonna put in the regular stuntman this is stuntman one not
stuntman ignition what do we get from ignition when is stuntman coming i have to just get it
please do urban chaos didn't i already do urban chaos our ads on some random shitty ad popped
up out of nowhere that shouldn't be happening pre-rolls i cannot turn off but you should not
be getting an ad during the stream ever that should never happen if you got like a pop-up
ad i think that may be coming from somewhere else yeah pre-rolls like when you open up the stream
you'll get an ad but during the stream you should never see an ad i don't run them i don't think
i've ran an ad on this channel in three and a half years run one right now
i don't even know how how do you even run an ad is it on the dashboard i have not ran an ad
in like fucking four years on this channel do it now um we'll be right back did it work
did you is anybody getting an ad hey welcome back uh thanks for checking out the ad break
try running another no i'm not just gonna run fucking ads everybody will leave if i start
running ads they're usually five times louder than the stream people are just gonna leave
i'm not gonna do that again i can't i can't run it i just tried to click it again
i just got like yelled at by twitch because you can't run after i can only run that every eight
minutes somebody just gave 50 bucks why did i get another fucking mushroom this is so annoying
uh am scoots thanks for 50 bucks run a ad thank you for 50 dollars but i i don't i don't i'm not
gonna run ads i can only run an ad break one okay hold on how long can you make an ad break
why would you ever do this okay guys there's a slider here i i can run ads for three straight
fucking minutes are you trying to make people leave your channel no way anybody does this all
right guys like yeah that it's been like 10 minutes i'm gonna run three straight minutes of ads
does anybody actually use that maybe for like turn i guess like tournaments do that or i'm gonna
unsub all right i'm gonna i'm gonna i'll no i'm gonna kill my channel three minutes of ads
no fuck okay i got it this is this is that game 25 to life also playstation 2 hopefully we can
can we get out of this rut of seeing the same shit over and over again do it now i can't do it
now i can only run a break every eight minutes run a three minute ad block all right no no shroom
it's not a fake disc it's right here well that's how we do it that is a stone beetle that's a very
cool monster yes i'll take this one
ad block or ad rock
and every time he shows up every time he lands a move i run an ad
and twitch channel i swear to god
there it is the sound is decent like in the game the audio that shouldn't be
every win with ad rock run a three minute ad i mean we actually do joke around about this but
there are there's okay let's just put it this way there's probably a bunch of people here
that are just hanging out and watching you just maybe just sitting there just chilling oh this
is a monster at your four stream i'll just turn this one on you know what i mean this is fun that
sounds fun you're not chatting you're just kind of hanging out yeah if you get three straight minutes
of ads you're going to leave you're gonna go okay this is uh he's doing like a joke thing
and like yeah hey everyone's in on it this is like kind of funny but like fuck three minutes of ads
like i'm gonna leave nobody wants that nobody wants to see that we need a timer until the next
all right well i did say that that was going to be it we've been going just about seven hours i'm
going to call it here it would be funny at first and then after the third or fourth time would be
like i'm sick of hearing the same loud totino's pizza roll ad over and over again oh i do want
to see their stats that was just an ad no it wasn't that was me telling you that not to watch
look at how many people are here all right let's see what are the base stats on blossom not bad
almost 150 speed 140 intelligence that rock is 147 power pretty terrible actually besides the power
let me get the moves scissors and whirlwind lots of guts damage what about blossom
so scratch and hawaiian and a for guts damage hawaiian okay what about traits sweet voice
increase power boobs that use the voice add rock sounds like malware it probably is but that's
gonna be it guys here's the plan i'm gonna tell you the plan there's a possibility here so we got
a lot of random things that are going to be happening over the next few days
monster rancher 4 a yay or an a from monster rancher 4 continuing this i still fun we got a
yay thing probably i think people are having fun people enjoying this i am we have our dream team
here let me save it i think it's fun yeah i'm having a great time i feel like i'm gonna get
really irritated at the countering system but you know it's fine you're asking the people that stuck
around for seven hours yeah the best people to ask but even though this is that yeah fuck
it i'll do it that sounds fun we'll do it again but in between the next stream is probably not
going to be monster range for there's the scratch ticket stream for sekiro that's going to take me
at least like an hour or two to scratch those i already got confirmation with twitch that that
should be fine you don't know what that what's happening there for every time i died in sekiro
i'm buying that amount monetarily in scratch tickets so whether it's a bunch of ten dollar
five dollar equaling two hundred and twenty one dollars i'm going to scratch all those tickets
on stream and whatever happens through those tickets is going to go right to charity if i
don't win anything if it's zero i'm going to donate two hundred and twenty one dollars
to that charity anyways so winner lose that was something that why wait why 221 i died 221 times
in sekiro and said that i was going to get a scratch ticket for every death even if it's a
million dollars yes if i hit a million dollars on one of these scratch tickets the charity is
getting a million dollars that's just going to happen why did you die that much all right whatever
it's gonna be funny when you only donate six dollars because you only win six dollars but that
i just told you i'm going regardless of anything i'm going to donate at least 221 dollars like if i
scratch up like hundreds of dollars worth of tickets you win like eight bucks all right
eight dollars is going here no it would be so it would be dumb but that's the plan that's
including revives now they they kept track there was a the actual deaths i think please
do a three minute ad i would love to see some products to buy
uh so the charity that i'm going to choose i have not decided yet uh i have narrowed it down to a
few what about taxes okay so that's whatever i can so okay let's say i on stream hit like
this is not this is probably not going to happen but like if i win like 50 grand on a scratch
ticket on stream i i don't know how taxes work with that i don't know this is a question for
my cpa because if i win 50 grand on a scratch ticket a bunch of that's taxed so then i would
have to pay taxes on that but i would give it to be given it to charity but charity is deductible
from taxes but was that with that count as income i would be getting 50 grand of income and writing
off 50 grand of income how does that work i'm gonna okay i'm gonna i gotta call my cpa about
this he's gonna think i'm fucking insane hey so i have a question for you if i buy
200 dollars worth of scratch tickets and i win 50 grand and give 50 grand of charity what happens
to my income he's probably gonna go what the fuck are you talking about he's probably gonna
hang up on me he's watching now no do that voice on the phone hey i got a question for you
all right that's it let's get out of here thanks for hanging out everybody i'll see you guys in a
couple days i'll see you on thursday so this i depending on what happens italics and i were
going to play risk of rain two together we're thinking about doing that monster rancher four
has to continue sakiro scratch off to charity stream has to do has to be there and then something
else and i mean well look i'll just say i'll just tell you what it is i'm gonna play the uh the germa
game on stream it's coming out real soon prepare for that it's gonna be it's gonna be real soon
on pc yep on pc does that include ads no risk of rain two is very very good
yeah so but we'll jumble it around but that's what you can expect over this next uh week or so
general roll the ads oh okay i'll do the three minutes of ads at the end of the stream before i
leave because i want everyone that does not want to see three minutes of ads to have an opportunity
to just leave so we're gonna do the bits let's go back uh about seven plus hours ago just about
seven hours ago to the beginning and it was lazy luke thanks for the 250 lazy luke they say germa
heart it's all thank you for the 250 thank you also to uh tingy for the 250 if you do have the
scratch ticket stream sometime this week and please be on the weekend i don't want to miss
it due to work it'll probably end up being let me just try to think this through here
so nothing tomorrow on wednesday and then thursday friday saturday all right i would probably do
saturday might be a really weird stream because saturday might turn out to be
the sakiro scratch off and the germa slot game stream because i feel like that would be a whole
stream worth of stuff to do because i feel like the scratching the tickets is going to take probably
like an hour plus and then that a game is going to take a couple hours probably or an hour plus
i feel like that makes sense to have those be on the same day you know one can kind of prelude to
the other sounds like a plan and then that makes thursday and friday monster rancher 4 will come
back if not thursday then friday and if me and italics play risk of rain then we'll continue
monster rancher 4 on friday so you can probably assume risk of rain 2 monster rancher 4 and the
weird like irl gambling stream somehow sounds good so expect that on saturday you did spend
six hours trying to build a bird house that's true was that six hours is gambling against the
tos now i actually i talked to two twitch staff about this and as long as gambling is legal in
your area in your state it's fine i mean especially considering that whatever money i would win
would just be going to charity there's i mean guys i live in las vegas is gambling legal in nevada
let me check let me ask one of the 300 casinos that are within a 15 mile radius of where i'm
standing right now do i still have the bird house uh i don't think i do i may have i may have thrown
that away i think i had like no actually you know i just i think it is still down downstairs
i think it's still there but thank you tingy probably see you on saturday for that thank you
heretic for the five dollars jeremy you've been consistently enjoyable to watch and listen to
since day one never stopped being you much love well thank you that means a lot that
if you think i'm that consistently fun to listen to because i think about that a lot and i think
about all the things people say about this channel and i got i like want i like want you to keep
having fun here i want you to keep enjoying these streams i think about especially in the shower
i'll just be like what's what's going on today what's going on this week let's do something fun
what is that though is that going to be fun i'm glad you guys are enjoying it because i'm enjoying
it too uh joules thanks for the 250 hey compact child of Thanos tickets for avengers endgame are
on sale will you be watching it opening week with a crowd of people in imax would you prefer watching
it a little later when things simmer down in the theaters watching either way has its benefits but
i just want to know how you like to watch your movies i like to watch my movies in an empty
theater because anytime i go to a movie that's packed it's always been one of those scenarios
where every possible moment for somebody to scream yeah oh whoa what the whoa like spider-man shows
up for the first time and it's like the spider spider-man whoo it's like we all know he's in the
fucking movie i know spider-man's in the movie you know spider-man's in the movie why do we all
have to cheer when spider-man shows up in the movie you saw the trailer spider-man's in this movie
iron man does like a big blast out of his hands everybody screams it's like he didn't do anything
they should really only fill half the theater for the real experience well for me a little bit
because uh because of they want to make sure that there's not enough not a lot of noise in the
theater you know what i mean i see what exactly what you mean by that because you just because
it could get loud in the theater and you should be like easier to hear and stuff that's why i know
exactly what you're talking about thank you people clap during the theater what are you clapping for
they can't hear you danos is coming in for the big punch oh iron man spins around and like knocks
him out nice nice job tony tony i love you one time that happened i stood up and i pointed up
at the like five people stood up clapping and like screaming i saw somebody was on their phone i
heard like a fucking phone ring and turn your phone off too by the way don't bring your phone
into the movie i don't understand everybody knows not to be on your phone in the movie theater and
everybody gets angry at other people for being on the phone yet you will open up your phone and look
at it and then somebody five seats down is mad that you're opening up your phone and that person
also gets pissed off when other people use their phone and then they open up their phone it's a
cycle it's a vicious circle of everyone using their phones and being mad at other people for
using their phones just don't do it anyways this is all happening loud noises fucking
3g data flying around it was pissing me off so i point i got up and i stood up i pointed at the
projector the guy that was running the projector i said pause it pause the movie for a minute
and he was like well he couldn't hear me people were just screaming and laughing and clapping at
tony stark i was like pause the put the movie on pause and he like and it was just sitting there
frozen i said put the house lights on and they he turned them on and i went and then everybody
just uh whoa okay i went i did my my teacher move everybody shut up i said listen we all want to
enjoy this movie some of you have your kids here some of you were here with your you know your
boyfriends and your girlfriends or whoever everyone just wants to have a good time here
if we could please just relax and enjoy the film the thing we all we all had to pay the same amount
of money to get in here and people looked around for a second and in about five seconds after it
got real quiet and i got hit in the face with a package of mike and ikes and it broke my notes
and everyone started laughing and at the same time all these assholes pulled their phones out
that well none of them were turned off and i could hear the collective iphone take a picture sound
and i heard like a crash up where the projector was like the guy with the projectors laughing so
hard he was cracking up so hard he fucking fell down and knocked the canister over long story short
everybody got a refund i didn't go to the next showing though it was like 20 minutes later let
me give you a long just a tl tl d e too long didn't ear put your phones away enjoy the movie
you can like look you can lean over and like whisper hey well that was wicked fucked up i
can't believe dude he just like bended time with his hands yeah that's fine be good be nice in the
theater everybody had to pay the same amount of money don't throw mike and ikes in anybody it's
not funny i'm serious don't do that it's just fucked up just buy the movie when it comes out
but i'll give it up for i like going with a smaller uh slightly empty theater because
it makes me feel like the movie's from me it's kind of weird but it's true but thank you
jewels for the 250 i'm looking forward to uh avengers uh avengers avengers end game should
be good chunky bologna thanks for the 10 bucks the hardest sentence to understand is you telling
someone where to park a car l u l what are you reading i don't care thanks for the 10 bucks
though ferodian weapon thanks for the 250 yes i need help with the bench oh oh right i forgot
that happened what a fucking disaster thank you for the 250 ferodian sad vega thanks for the 250
i'm laughing so hard and crying at work just watching you try to listen to the brown noise
and then talk to us you're a mad fan that went really off the rails completely there was no
stopping that train and i realized it pretty much halfway through it jess you got it thanks for the
250 they said you're a gift to the world i don't know about that but thank you for the kind words
in the 250 he wants to go to an empty theater because he didn't want to be laughed at for
dressing up his Thanos all right i like i go into the movie theater dressed up it's like you're
really like a big fan and it's great but don't you think you should go dressed up to a place
where it's not like pitch black the only people that can see you in your darth vader costume
as a guy serving the popcorn like you you come into the theater and like your full darth vader
costume and nobody can see you and how uncomfortable is it to be in full costume and sit in one of those
seats not very many people do that imagine how hot you would get in like the darth vader costume
sitting in a theater with 300 people if you do that i hope you enjoy it i just hope that you're
out there before the movie starts like posing and like doing like fake like lightsaber poses
and like taking pictures with people darth vader is from star wars not avengers you show up at a
darth vader costume for the avengers movie and you're like oh fuck i forgot this is the wrong
movie i thought this is episode eight the most ambitious crossover oh god that from yenwen look
at that that looks like the 3d mapping of a character in a video game like they scanned my
face that's insanely good but thank you
thank you silver flame for the 250 i remember when you got drunk labo and got so many sweet
donation messages some guy even gave a thousand dollars you got emotional but didn't cry but you
play farting and screaming noises at once and suddenly water works that's different though
when when i like laugh and my brain gets on overdrive and i start like laughing and
can't control it like that's an automatic body response to like stress that's like body stress
what what a crappy video what video what what is this that's not what my hair looks like
that's not what my hair looks like you fucked this up on purpose that is not what my hair looks
like spider man 3 peter parker
there's a whole album with faces oh my god
what on earth is happening on this channel
we we've seen all these pretty much some of these are just the same ones we've already seen
but just the smudge tool from photoshop used a little bit more
oh oh i can't even look at
oh that's too much man
man i'm gonna die
jesus thank you silver flame for the 250 though sawdust bunnies thanks to 250 they say haha
thank you sad vega for the 250 germa i had a call come in for work when you started playing the
farts and screams i was crying tears of laughter i had to take a few seconds to compose myself and
and mute the stream oh lord it's a miracle i made it through that call
i'm sorry hopefully you didn't hopefully you were able to compose yourself thank you though
thank you door cube for the 250 oh my god that's the hardest i've ever laughed in a long fucking
time and it was the kind of laugh where you run out of air and have to take a huge breath i'm
still recovering thank you thank you e half note for the five bucks thank thank you for making us
all cry about farts thank you for the five dollars thank you drummage drummage door for the five
dollars imagine the embarrassment getting tinnitus from farts thanks for the laugh best laugh i've
had in years it was wild thank you guy at the gym dark soul 9669 thanks for the 15 dollars
have these bits i had tears running down my face and i sweat through all my fucking clothes thank
you thank thank you for the 15 dollars and the incredibly nice thing to say thank you i'm glad
you had fun and then uh also from door cube thanks for the 250 look at my beautiful boy
and it's that image right here it says when you think your dad's crying because he finally got
to see his beautiful boy get married but he's really just listening to farts and screams way
too loud through his ear pods a hot guy might thank you for the 30 dollars 30 bucks you're making
the next sims family album what that cry face man is so fucked up there are things that you never
want like okay as you never want to be on camera crying right nobody like a picture you want to be
smiling or composed that's so fucked up like just make this an evo i'm gonna have to but hot guy of
mine thank you so much for the 30 dollars something or other thanks for the 250 don't cry
because it's over smile because it happened thank you core monster thanks with five bucks
jerma age 54 pondering the marriages of his child that looks like a that looks like a
portrait of like a president oh my god that's so fucking funny thank you core monster
peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hey jeremy wish i could give more gift subs but i'm planning a
trip to texas it's probably not a good idea hope all is well have a good night jerma and chat
thank you for the 250 and thank you for the gift subs as well hopefully you have a fun
time in texas whenever you go and thank you so much for the 250 frody and weapon thanks with
10 bucks here's that 10 dollars you thought i gave earlier seriously though tonight's stream
has been hilarious and uplifting especially after having a shit day at work thanks for being here
and chat too absolutely thank you frody and for the 10 bucks glad that this stream and this
community can make your day a little better thank you peaceful hailey again thanks for 260 here
peaceful hailey and here are some more bits because i want my 5000 bit badge i can't imagine
donating to any other streamer i can't imagine anybody donating to me in the first place but
people do and it's it's i can't fucking believe it thank you guys you guys are awesome thank you
for the support thank you peaceful hailey for the 260 thank you it's time for slime for the five
dollars guys the secret to grinding xp and stream legends super fast is to repeatedly redo the first
level of the raid over and over since it's much faster than doing the rest of the levels and gives
the same amount of xp and gold here my iq there you go you're giving away the secrets redo the
boss battle not the first level well we got a problem here between people fighting on how to
do stream legends thank you though it's time for slime for the five bucks door cube thanks for the
250 door cube i know this is kind of tuber bait but you should try doing a stream of improv scenes
with a speech jammer i'm pretty sure you wouldn't even need any extra programs you just need to
play your mic audio from the stream back into your headphones i don't know i don't know if i
could do that i've tried doing stuff like that before and i can't even speak guys i can't wear
two headphones because i can't talk i don't know if i'd be able to do a whole stream like that maybe
like a 10 to 15 minute segment but thank you door cube internet Jorge thanks for the 15 dollars
15 bucks you almost gave me a heart attack with the soft lock yeah it was uh you just have to
press x i thought the cd wasn't being read for somehow but thankfully that didn't happen and we
keep our progress that's good thank you for the 15 bucks it's a lot of money appreciate it
uh hamburg leo thank you hamburg leo for the 10 bucks jerma i haven't had a chance to watch many
of your streams but i've seen most of the stuff on your youtube accounts i want to say thank you for
all your hard work it's an inspiration to see someone care so much about what they do and then
i want to add that your content always makes me laugh despite myself and has brought me laughter
when i most needed it thank you so much for all you've done and keep up the amazing work
thank you so much i'm ecstatic that people can get enjoyment fun relief friends community here
it's i mean that's amazing that's more than anything i could ever ask for ever so thank you
for that this one's freaking me out actually no it's not no it's staying no this one's awful
put on this one no this one no this one no this one yeah now it's fine that's better
but thank you hamburg leo for the 10 bucks means a lot chunky baloney 10 dollars from chunky baloney
here's a donation in honor of that guy's birthday happy birthday hey happy birthday that guy
whoever you were happy birthday and thank you chunky baloney for the 10 dollars thousand bits
thank you thank you mief pleable for the 250 holy shit germa what the hell that fart scream
gym guy was so funny i decided to try listening to it myself i laughed so hard i threw up on my
desk i was throwing up so hard i couldn't take my earbuds out so it just kept playing the only time
i ever laughed this hard was seeing comedian martin short being played as a human bagpipe
well played what fan with family guy family guy joke thank you me appreciate it hey dr clay
thanks for the 250 they say i had to do this it's a media file use item on what is a video
hold on a second what the hell would i just save this to it's like a movie all right hold on where
does this save to now save it to the desktop no save it to the desktop save it to the desktop
come on there we go let's watch this i like why can i not hear this i all i can hear is the music
from monster rancher there we go and now i can hear this right one two three play
i can't hear this wait what just happened oh okay there we go
that's pretty good i'm i did not plan that just kind of happened but that was dr clay thank you
dr clay for the 250 and that video germa lied about minecraft vr thanks for the 250 enable pog
you coward i can't i have to do i can't do it internet whore hey 15 more dollars here 15 bucks
boomer streamer actually makes a funny joke for once i take a lot of pride in the things that i
say and the jokes that i come up with the story about how i've shaved the gold off and hide it
and people told me to shut the fuck up and play the game because it was a bad joke and wasn't
funny i take pride in that in that routine that i did thank you for the 15 dollars i really
appreciate that that's a lot of money you give them a lot of money today tar alecron thanks for
three bucks hey germa i donated some bits last stream but didn't realize you raised the minimum
donating again to re-ask the question you missed on last time due to your greed anyways i just
wanted to know what's up with your closet man why is it so messy just shut the door maybe here's
a clip i did we just talked about this hey bro what's going on man you need some help with the
with the bench you know they give up there and what are you doing 200 pounds 220 yeah that's
what i thought you're strong guy yeah yeah i read that book too that's a good book what what would
we read that book the closet okay there's two tripods in the closet and a pillow here look
we'll we'll we'll we'll break this down hey bro what's going on man okay you need some help with
the closet with the bench that's a tripod a tripod a pillow and then a bunch of electronics
220 yeah that's what i thought you're strong guy yeah yeah i read that book too that's a good book
look at how hard this is doing look at this i can't do it more than five seconds it's so hard to do
that the pillows from the death count downstream probably now there's a trash bag on the ground
too did you guys see that there's a bag of trash behind me but it's not actually filled with trash
i don't think you guys saw it maybe you did there's no trash in there it's it's filled with stuff
i use it as a storage thing to help move things around and well now we know it's there but thank
you tar alacran appreciate it flank tank thanks it's free bucks flank tank i just finished
watching you secure of odds and at the end you said every other game will be easy and i said oh
yeah go beat neo on stream at least before neo 2 secure secure is harder than neo i mean just
as i said i'm gonna say that secure is harder game than you because i beat it and i played it
so therefore it's it's harder because i played it no i didn't like neo i wasn't a fan of neo
couldn't get into it i really tried i really could not do it i just didn't want to and i i
talked to i did this i told the story before even after the drunk shit-faced whiskey stream
where i played neo and embarrassed myself i went back months later and just tried on my own time
to play neo and i didn't want to play it i didn't like it sorry just the truth i can see how people
enjoy it but i didn't not for me that siege thanks for the 10 bucks they say bamboozled
oh whatever what do you mean what do i do but thank you that siege for the 10 bucks
baited something that siege again thanks for four dollars and 20 cents no message is 420 i think
that was the attack power we were trying to go over 400 thank you though thank you all mew for
the three bucks hey germa i love it when i get the make i want to i love it when i get to make the
live stream especially when i've got a plumber in my house fixing our hot water he said there
was an issue with the the heater almost he tried that okay if you didn't put the dash between the
b and the h i would have said it you dashed it though but thank you all mew for the three bucks
something order thanks for the 250 i was digging through some files and found a cover for a
children's book joke i was thinking about doing but ended up scrapping it do i dare put this link
in chat because it's just a gnome i mean this is a gnome just want to warn you before you click it
just for those of you that were wondering thank you something or other for the 250 and the gnome
children's book smelly boy thanks for the 250 i still cannot believe the farting and screaming
incident neither can i and i forgot i almost forgot what happened thank you peek a banana for
the five dollars thanks for the stream i can't wait to see those lottery scratchers hope you
win big for charity that'd be pretty awesome see what i get hey garfield the monday killer thanks
to the 250 here's an ad germ buy the new garf book it's got tons of funny comics for don't read
garfield it's the worst comic i'm germa and if you buy garfield comics i'm going to be real mad and
tell mom thanks for the ad germa i really miss rumors since he was your goofer what's a germa
stream without a good goof now it's just zombie plant boring dragon and rock ant uh blossom at
least is cute but now we don't get a fun goofy monster you got to recruit a goofy garfield's
telling you goof it up will do is that english yes it was when are you going to play monster
rancher 4 today two days ago and like two or three days from now come on oh you did the smiley face
ah that's the new kappa i forgot thank you to clements clement clevich the clements grumble
for the 10 bucks i haven't laughed i laughed the hardest i've laughed in years during the
intermission today thanks for the years of great streams you mentioned before you used to play
diablo 2 for hours would you ever consider playing it or something like it on stream
i don't i don't think so the last game that i played that was a isometric rpg like that was
grim don and i played it through the third act it was before it was all done and i never went
back and finished it but i don't think i would stream a game like that a game like that is
probably something i would do just for to kind of chill out and just open my mouth and play a game
maybe for a chill stream it would make sense but not something that's in the pipeline or anything
yeah the intermission today was uh kind of threw the whole thing off for a while but it was still
fun glad you enjoyed it thank you for the 10 dollars juno upset oh thanks for the 250 the
farting and screaming bit made an otherwise mediocre day into an amazing one you really are
gift to the world thank you i'm honored and happy that a just a mediocre day can be turned
into something that you remember it had a lot of fun that means a lot so humble well i'm too i'm
look look look look as i try as hard as i can to stay as grounded as i can as a person you know
what i mean i never want to get an ego large enough where i don't give a shit or i think i'm
master not that that ever would happen but i like to keep myself fairly with my ear and head to the
ground yeah not i don't have that tagline that's not my tagline somebody already has the master
of comedy tagline it's not me but i do appreciate it i really do but thank you juno upset oh for the
250 farting and crying what yeah people and i have people have no idea you guys are going to be making
references over the next few weeks about this and there's going to be people that had nothing to do
with that weren't here at all and they're gonna be at least mildly confused as to what the fuck
we're talking about but it's all good too bad uh thank you the same the same oh so the samos for
the 10 bucks thank you the 10 dollars hey jerma thanks for the streams and all the fun times you
share with your community since your youtube days to now you've never failed to make me laugh thanks
for everything and all the great times also for a game recommendation consider escape from monkey
island thank you once again and i intend to be a viewer for as long as i possibly can i will
i'm glad to have you for as long as you want to be here thank you much love to you and escape from
monkey island that's the point and click game right what i was going to do batch these all up
because i was going to try to do a week pretty much like three or four streams in a week where
i played a bunch of these do like a point and click week or something oh right people don't
even know the stream is over whoops that's i forgot about that this just says i'm playing
monster rancher and there's like two fucking weirdos on the screen there that's better yeah
he just came to the uh that was wondering i saw i i did see quite a few people saying like what
the fuck's going on in here i was like wait what do you mean what's going on and the stream is like
over what no you know oh right god that was what was on the screen tingy thank you for the 250 i'm
glad i have enough bits for this last message because it's very important why is the foam
padding on your door in the shape of a penis it isn't it's a minecraft creeper uh what's going
on there but thank you for the 250 let's roll the credits all the subs all the new subs all
the community subs thank you everybody let's blast them out on screen here they come thank you
everybody and yes i'm going to run three minutes of ads i'm going to make sure everyone's well
aware that that's going to happen uh deus morte thanks for the 250 hey jerma purchased the
300 version of adobe photoshop to make this hope it was worth it it's just it's just
it's the crying face with my hair as a mustache ads not yet the stream's not over watch me doing
this be like incredibly lucrative 300 joke you want to put it on stream all right i'll put it
on stream all right so when we come back you have to tell me what you got for ads i want to know if
you get the same ad like five times in a row so the subs don't get ads what's the difference
between a hippo and a zippo one is really heavy the other is a little lighter nice very nice good
work turned off my ad blocker let's go i can't believe there are people that are excited to get
blasted with three minutes of ads subs don't get ads right hold on let me change that real quick
okay no i'm kidding incognito mode to get ads what give us ads i don't i don't even know how
to turn that on i have no idea how to i don't think i can fix that let's see hold on i got
no no no no no guys something like that that's gonna take like 36 hours for that to go through
that's not gonna be that's gonna take some processing time for like twitch to do that
i don't think that's gonna work better get started all right here you go you ready
i unsubbed to get ads oh my god don't even don't even tell me i'm gonna get like a mass exodus of
subs all right here come three minutes of ads and we're gonna stay here i want you to tell me how
what happened all right three minutes okay i'm gonna give fair warning to everybody here this
is happening now if you don't want to see this bullshit then you absolutely completely totally
understandably can leave just thank you see you in a couple days take care of yourself see you
soon those of you that want to be experimented on for some reason ready get the popcorn here
comes three minutes is it working i don't even want to stay live for three what happens if i turn
the stream off i have to be i have to stay live for three more minutes what happens if i turn off
the stream right now do they still get them they still play pizza hot oh pizza hot amazon prime
with commercial fortnight oh my god this is so funny everybody's so excited about this that was
not three minutes it's still going you should you should be still getting red sox championship
video ad nice there's still apparently 106 seconds of ads still going maybe i broke it
it's still going version two no it shouldn't be over already well somebody okay somebody got two
identical division ads in a row good that's good i got hellboy and samsung why are we treating this
like surprise eggs what'd you get in yours i got hellboy verizon and my time at porsche hellboy
this still going people watching in about 27 seconds we're gonna get a rush of people that
just got out why are they tiered that seems weird probably you know it's probably based by country
too maybe you don't get ads or you only get one or two from a certain country all right three
seconds two one here they come how was it how'd you guys do everybody should be out now i got
fortnight more i know oh yeah you can still chat during ads i forgot it doesn't like turn you off
why would it hey frostro thanks for the five dollars thanks for being the safest place on
the internet for my mental health thank you for the five bucks thanks for sticking around
we're glad to have you thank you weekend ad stream so would twitch just pull my stream and ban me
if i just had like a if i just came back here every three minutes no every it's every eight
minutes so if i turned on my stream and it was just a webcam and it was me just sitting there
and i ran three minutes of ads and then i came back i just like played with my phone for 10
minutes and then ran ads again if i ran like 40 minutes of ads on like an eight hour stream
would i get would that be a problem i mean it would kill i would kill my channel but i just sit
there for like eight minutes run three minutes sit there for eight minutes run three minutes
chat wants to give you free money by ads he's contemplating it no i mean if like if if you
guys really want me to do this at the end of the streams right i'm not going to do it every time
like right at the very end when like never during a stream i don't know if i would ever do it my
mic's muted oh please end of the stream joke we'll see i don't know we'll see
i don't want to like turn you guys into like money printers for the last five minutes of a stream
like sit there and watch five minutes of ads have people in chat make fake ad videos and play one
the only way i would ever do that is if it was actually at the end of all the bits
all the sub credits just literally the very end before the stream turns off
is the only time i would ever do that but that's gonna be it i'll see you guys in a couple days
hey skelly uh skelly boner thanks for the five dollars hey jeremy i took the day off for stress
and depression reasons and this absolutely made my day what a wonderful stream thank you for the
five dollars skelly hopefully on your day off kid relax a little thank you for sticking around here
glad as a community we can keep the company make you laugh thank you use ads as a means to punish
chat i don't know about that but that's my time i'll see you guys soon a couple days we'll take
a crack at the probably the risk of rain 2 stuff with italics probably have a great rest of your
night with it i missed somebody's bits who's but statements oh juno upsetto thank you for the 250
juno upsetto right at the very end here and they say oh it's taken over there's no escape you better
get moving ready to not ready or not get ready what is that except from the oh it's probably
from one of the ads take care guys see you in a couple days for probably risk of rain 2
and then we'll return to monster rancher to continue this and then we will do the
scratch off stream and the germa slot video game see you soon take care and goodbye