He's not dead. He's absolutely still alive, and he's probably gonna try to bitch-tape me, so I better be careful.
I'm laughing outside your spawn door. Yeah. Jesus Christ. That's a spy. So is this. I know you're back here. I know you're right. I'm not. You're not getting by me.
I am certain you are standing right in this corner. Yep. I knew it. I can't believe he just died. I can't believe that. I cannot believe that. I can't believe we're being spawn camped either. I just can't believe this.
I'll get behind him. What is going on over there? And there's a pyro. I'm so dead. Nope. Not quite. Nice. Nice job. God. In heaven.
Hallowed be thy name, thy... God, you just ruined my joke, man.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven. Give us this day our daily pyro's bread, and dress us up for trespassers, for we have no trespassers among us.
Deliver us from evil and beyond and however else it goes. Amen. I want to get at least like at least two or three kills in a row. There's a heavy right there. He's our heavy. That's good. Mini sentry.
I'm not going to get myself killed by that. We got a sniper on the side there. I just got a... Here we go. Just chill out back here. Wait for some sorry son of a bitch to come out this door. No, they're all going straight.
Somebody come out this door. Anyone. Anybody come out this side door. I'm literally standing right here. You're looking at me right now. Get behind the first point and kill a bunch of people like this sniper. This sniper, I have to get this sniper.
He's not paying attention. He's like shooting down this hallway. There's no... He's dead because he got killed by this sniper that was down there. Okay. Well, plan ruined. Plan B. Go to their spawn and swing at some random person like this guy. Oh my God.
And he was over hill too. So I don't even... He was six foot two and what do you know? He was pulling his pants since he was two. He's a wrench man. He was 20 feet tall and had a ball. He swung his wrench down like them all. You know, he was a wrench man.
He was 10 feet. Why is he always a certain height in every country song or every like ballad song? Why are they always like a certain height? Oh, he was six feet tall. Who cares? Who cares if he was like two feet tall? Who cares? Who cares about this?
Don't worry, I got this. Don't worry about a thing. I'm in pursuit. I'm in scout pursuit right now. He's not going to get... Yes. You see? You see what happens when you mess with the wrench man? See, I was going to do the same thing. You got a bloody lip. Hold on, please stand still so I can see that like butt lip you got. Come here. Come here, please. I just want to look at your like busted ass lip for a second. Forget the head on approach. I need to try to get behind literally everybody. I'm going around, not going that way. Screw that. We're going
all the way back to their spot. That's the only conceivable way I see that this is really possible is to try to get behind everybody. Don't show yourself to anyone. Right here. This is the spot I'm talking about. Someone's going to walk over here. You got to be fucking kidding me. What is this guy doing there? What is that guy doing there? That guy being in like the weirdest wrong spot possible just got me killed because I'm in the weirdest wrong spot possible. You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Are you going to try to get our intelligence? Is that what you're going to try to do? Oh, you think you're going to get the intelligence? That didn't kill him. Oh, that did. That did. Why am I getting achievements for this? I got like some type of journey to an achievement by doing that. I don't know how. Anybody in here? Yeah, there is. Are there any people who's down here? It's heavy. Just got to be careful. Just got to be careful. Yes. You too. No, you're
not a spy. I thought you were a spy for a second. It's all about defending the intelligence as the wrench in here. Another pyro. If you're going to do the NG wrench technique, then just be careful of pyro's. Pyro's. Did I say pyro? Oh my God. You got to move that gear up. You got to move that gear up. I want to. Oh, oh. Where'd he go? Two pyro's. And a spy and a spy.
And a spy and a spy. No, that didn't kill me. The sentry didn't kill me. Oh, I am so fucked right now. Yes. Oh my God. Oh my God. This guy. This engineer around the corner. Let's go. No, no, no, no, no. You come to me. I'm not. You're not going to bait me around the corner to get killed by the sentry.
Shit. Come on. God damn it. This guy is really good. I can't move. If I move around. There's nothing I could do there. The sentry would have killed me because he's got a sentry on like the mountaintop. Mountain. It's a house. What?