No, no, it's not live. It's not like that. I'm testing some software upgrades and OBS just went live
This is not half up to this. Sorry. We're not starting for like another four hours
Hey guys, so we're playing we're going hi good good afternoon. He's definitely live. Yeah, I am today
First let me make a tweet because how am I supposed to stream without a tweet call this one? I
spy
Mansion, I spy it doesn't matter. What's the title? Do I have a shitty title? No, it's pretty good
But I don't have a Twitter. How will I know?
Just open up Twitter right now and go to twitter.com slash German on a five
You'll find me and then you can see what the streams happening
All right. I this is how you can tell how fucking dumb I am while I was talking I typed into my Twitter
WWW dot slash German nine eight five not even like a twitch. Hey, you know, they're getting rid of URLs
You know that right? That's the thing in like five to ten years guys. It's not gonna be
WWW.twitch.tv
It's gonna type in twitch URLs are going away
Really? Yeah, like a little early
What do I have for my uh?
What do I have for my head like dishwasher repairman window between three and four Pacific?
That's sometimes between two and four. Sometimes they come early
How's the search bar gonna work?
That's a question for a scientist and I am NOT a scientist I'm a tuber and a streamer
so today
we're going to play a
Requested game it is called I spy and the
spooky mansion deluxe
Should be fun. It is a hidden object game. This idea came about
during 700,000 games
We played a hidden object game and people were like
Oh, you know what a great hidden object game is that you should just unironically do a real stream on is I spy
Here we are. I spy mountain blade
Yeah, if you didn't watch the mountain blade stream last night just it was a great stream. I had a lot of fun
Just don't watch past like six and a half hours
Because I this is weird bug on twitch
Where I think there's like a bug inside that the browser where like, you know
You know, you the computer will crash if you watch past six and a half hours. I
Heard I've done it's only on that it's only on that one vaude. I don't know why like I think there's some kind of bug
You can't watch it past six hours something like that
But anyways, let's get started here. That sounds I'm just kidding. It's not real
I had a fucking meltdown after like six and a half hours and I like I like called out chat
It was messy. But you know, I'm not perfect, you know, I'll be the first to tell you that
But we talk we talked it out we we hashed it out everything's all good
But I'm ready give people a little a few moments to trickle in here. Our marriage is saved
First chat experience. No, no, no, no, no. No. Here we go. How do I press this button? Which one is it?
Oh, right. I have to capture my whole desktop
So hopefully there's no like fucking probably there's no like bad folders on here
Like what's what's up? What could be on that folder is tax documents. No, I'm like serious like that. Hopefully that's not there
Like did recently do that. That's ten community subs from Maddie numbers
Thank you for the ten community subs
Welcome everybody. So this is I spy
this game is very old and
I don't know first of all
I skipped the opening cutscene because I had to make sure I could capture the game and
What you missed here a really really whimsical scenario is scenario
I got in door and
Closed boom and there's no handle here. I can't open a door with no handle
See
So I have to finish the puzzle and we've got some canes here and
Here's how you start the game. I'm gonna click the secret message behind the picture frame
Now this is a celebrated game and a celebrated franchise in a celebrated genre that doesn't exist anymore
Well, it does
This is probably at least four or five companies that try to scam your grandmother into buying these
But you know, I think it's a genre that could use some revitalization secret message
It's all the countries in Europe
Here yet to earn puzzle pieces you have to go solve the I spy riddles and play the games that I've
Okay, then come back here and put your pieces in place
It's uh, it's it's Europe. It's it's it's it's Africa
In the bathroom and by the sink there's a riddle for you to solve I think
Okay, go in the bathroom
So we're gonna we'll just go left to right, you know, I'm not gonna go right to left. What is this a manga?
Let's go to the bathroom
Okay
So in the bathroom by the sink is riddle. Mmm. Oh, there's a mouse here
Mouse secret mouse click
That has to be something weird, right? This is an old game. They hid stuff like under the umbrella dog cane
regular cane
golf club
Candy cane. I don't know. How do I go anywhere? How do I leave? Oh
Oh
Like that. Okay. Hold on. There's a cat all the stairs
Cat doesn't do anything. This is one of those singing basses, right?
Cat cat yeah cat mouse
squeaky floorboard
Where's the bathroom?
This is like the dining room. What's under there?
Here's a riddle for you to solve on one listen to it
Then hunt for the items the riddle asks for on this screen. I spy a fork face a tongue
Two nails a face on a coin and three lizard tails, okay spider a screw
two sticks for a drum a
spoonful of bugs and yum. Yum. Yeah, is that me?
Is that my reflection me leaning over the table just peering down? Oh a puzzle. That's my face
Okay a spice by a fork face
Got it. Yum. What a tongue. Okay. This is the spider. Yum. Yum
So that wasn't a four. Okay. I spy a fork face a tongue
two nails a face on a coin a
spider a screw
This is a little yum
Okay, there's one yum
Yum. Yum
spider
All right. How many yums do I have to click three?
Somebody told me that they remember playing this game
Between they only had 15 minutes at the library and they like kept playing this
It's the only time they ever were able to play the game. That's a saw no screw. Is that a screw?
Oh the lizard three lizard tails
We have to watch the cutting for every one
Two lizard tails. No, that's a snake tail. That's not correct
Well, there's another lizard. Can I move it? No
Face on a coin. All right, where's the tongue?
So where's the fork face
Two sticks for a drum. I see the third lizard. Oh, do you well that you need that? I need the lizard tail
Where the two?
Fucking hailing right now outside one nail
Got it three lizard tails. All right, so what's that? I got two I got one yum
Me too money two nails
No, this is a childhood classic guys. Come on. I told you this is this one
This was you know, this was more highly requested than warband. Can you believe that?
Yeah, I got that yum
Yum. Yum. I need two nails. There it is
Two nails, I literally can't believe that well believe it
Get a screw in the yum. Yum. Yum was the screw the screw
There's an ear. I spy a fork face
Where the hell's a fork face? I'm not even gonna tell anybody it's active
That's a face. Oh, it is a face
He's cheating. No, we're playing this together
Fork face. Oh, there is a yum right there. You're right
I
Need a screw there's an eye right there
Screw I win
See that's me
Actually is me
So we got the dead we got the dinner table one done, let's go put this back in
Pick up your piece. Oh, I didn't listen to the rest of the instructions pick up your piece
Okay with a blue green. All right, I need more
What were you guys getting the who from behind the mirror
to Jerry
You talking about
Are you actually talking about the sound when I go back
That can't be what you mean to Jerry. That's my name
That's short for your Jeremiah
No, the puzzle piece has a gnome on it. Oh a thumb a four
I'm not getting no chat help this time. There's four right here. Oh
For okay, where's the thumb?
Of no help from chat get it, right
It knows my name. I know right
By the way getting this game. I had to purchase this game from I'm you know
I'm gonna say because I didn't get this game from like Amazon. So I don't want to give like advertisements
two keys with three holes
Legally, no, I bought this very legally like I bought this game to legally this one with three holes
One key with three holes. So where's the other one? I needed with three holes. There it is
Ladybug with a ladybug guys help me out here. I don't know what this ladybug is
Oh, by the way, I want to give buddy a little bit of a rundown here. Excuse me. Excuse me. I
Bought a vibe. I did it. I finally did it. I purchased a vibe. It'll be here in two days
There's a shitload of things. We're gonna play this coming week. Oh
By the way, it's space channel part one got that one, too
Oh, by the way some more PlayStation 2 stuff. Oh and by the way
Ordered a PlayStation 3 exclusive game. Will you take pictures of safari animals? Oh, by the way first VR game
Gonna play his mind show. Oh, by the way, that's all I got for now. He's stalling
No, I buy the vibe was a long time coming closed door the number nine twice
No, the hits keep on coming. Oh, by the way gonna play the sims for first person also
Oh, by the way, the ASMR stream is happening in probably like a few weeks. Oh, by the way
All right, let me let me like focus on my fucking children's library game. Where's the ladybug? There it is
Don't give away too much. No, that's just those are just a few by the ways
You don't know fucking half the shit I'm doing over the summer
You are gonna get by the Wade all the way to space come like fucking August
To die number buddy the number not a peanut a penny this the penny
By the way, he he ha ha
That guy gets it a penny. All right, where's a peanut? Where's the peanut?
You need to turn the difficulty up
The number nine twice where is nine nine, that's nine right there on the sham
What's this closed door
Holy shit, that's so odd. That's oddly specific. I'm gonna fuck this up
That's really cool for like a fourth grade game. I like it a lot actually and the peanut people could be anywhere
Where's the peanut don't help me? I don't want any help
Don't help me. No, no, that's like a fucking banana. Oh
There it is. Okay. I didn't know if they meant like a shelled elephant peanut from the circus or if they meant an actual
like de-shelled peanut
Guys I just want to make sure everyone's very clear about this. This is like a 30 to 40 hour experience and
There are 14 houses to go through so strap buckle it in
Okay, where's this gonna go right here? Okay, I
Could actually beat this on string. I am aren't I?
All right, we found is like the the seller two hooks
ghost a star a wooden handle a bug in a jar a
Bone that's stone six numbers in line two pairs of goggles and a warning sign
All right. Well, there's the goggles
There's one pair of goggles. I need where the second pair of goggles be
Bone that's stone
Two pairs of goggles a pick a ghost six numbers in a line
Where's this? Oh, there it is. I got it. What about the
What about the the die? What are these called?
the
Roblox, what are we do with the roblox bone that's stone two hooks two hooks and warning sign
Ghost a ghost everybody see a ghost. No, that's that's that's feet. Why is it ghost?
I
Found a star a star
Am I blind? Where's the ghost? That's a skeleton. That's not a ghost
Two pairs of goggles. Well, that's a rat. He's stalking me in every room. I spy two hooks
ghost a
Star a wooden handle a bone that's stone ghost. Is it a big white dog from Game of Thrones?
What are two hooks a wooden handle a wooden handle, where's this wooden handle guys two hooks one two
one hook
That's just pretty amazing that this game was
Developed it was like a team of about five or six hundred people because it's back when each frame had to be frame by frame
Put together animated and each piece was actually to frame by four. It was like five or six hundred person project
The whole entire game cost about two hundred million dollars it was more I remember it was a huge deal at the time because the spider-man
Broke the record never once spider-man one came out. It was like a two hundred million dollar budget. They passed to this game
It was like one hundred ninety eight million dollars or something
All righty a bone that's stone
That's where it is I give me another piece
That's where it is I give me another piece a bone that's stone remember what are you smoking
um
I don't smoke anything
Just wait till everybody sees the giant climax at the end of this game
Okay, what we got pick up your piece
Okay, are you ready?
Are you ready to show you how?
What right is everyone's gonna do that everyone's gonna do it right now. I'm telling you go upstairs not upstairs yet chess
Let's play chess. Oh
Fuck my life
Watch for the hint and figure out how these objects match
Then empty the bins by clicking on the matching pairs. I missed everything she just said
Here's your hint
Okay, uh guitar v
Violin v
Oh, okay, if you have fly f spoon s
mouse m
Win twice more and i'll have a reward for you. Nice
But watch out the objects match in a different way this time
All right, let's see
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Uh, is this the hammer and then
cane
repairing
um
tennis ball
Dog toys it's predominantly a dog toy
dog food
no
uh
Pencil and paintbrush they both utensils used to draw
No, that's not right
Tennis racket and paint because like fuck painting. It's too hard and you smash it
Oh
Well, that's just
All right, this one's actually kind of complicated so I got uh bat
I okay. It wasn't i'm not kidding. I wasn't looking
I was not paying any attention. I was looking at chat and the the
No, okay, it's easy
I was literally looking at chat. I don't know you did it again. Here's puzzle piece four
Am I going to be done with this in like 20 minutes you can keep playing mystery bins to find more matches
Let's see how fast I can do this
That's two seconds
A new record
Okay, can I let me see if I can beat this in the whole one second. Ready?
Here we go
It's can't click. I can't click fast enough. All right, let's go
Pick up your piece. It's okay. Are you ready now?
I just i'm engrossed
Let's go back in the living room
rip
spring
eyeball cat
moose fire
I get in the fire spy two matches a candle flame
a bone three ducks an f in a frame
a trunk an eye a paper clip
dangling spider and an old clipper ship
All right. So before the stream started
And actually yesterday too
This almost it was going to be this or warband. This was like had almost 50 percent of the vote from the straw poll
And I asked hey
Is this like one of those like frog fractions game where it's like insanely hard and it goes crazy and like a bunch of
Weird stuff happens. Everyone's like don't tell them
Does that happen or is this just a game for like the third grade library? Is this like a he doesn't know scenario?
Uh
I don't know. I I don't know. I thought that was like an intricate conspiracy with this game
dangling spider
Okay, it was an old clip. I needed old clipper ship
You lack critical information
This game is hard as fuck
I gotta be quiet because i'll eat these words
Clipper ship. Okay, so we clipper ship paper clip. We're gonna clip the theme here candle flame
candle flame
Okay, candle flames
A paper clip. I was about to just make like a terrible fucking reference
I'm gonna put my hand up my mouth and be like, oh here's how you use powerpoint
Good thing. I didn't do that because a bunch of people would have been like, excuse me. Not funny
I didn't do that. I didn't make that joke. You can't hold it against me. That was the second match
An f in a frame
Excuse me, sir. That was not amusing. I didn't make the joke. I clearly stated
I preemptively stated
We see a bone
Three ducks
This streamed comedy has been a two out of ten so far
That's better than one. I'm glad you gave me a fucking two
Imagine if it was a one
All right. Let's see
trunk trunk
One match there's a match. Where's the other match?
All right. No, that's not
No, no
two matches
Three ducks
He's cheating
Oh trunk as an elephant trunk. Okay
I was looking for a car trunk
bone
That could mean anything that doesn't have to mean like a skeleton bone
Yes, it does
What else could it possibly be?
Now it's one of the legs of the chair
a bone
Whoa tricky. I'm sure you can tell
Here's puzzle piece five. You're doing quite well
Did this scare anybody when they were kids?
Look outside. I spy a wishbone. Oh, this is outside stuff
howl
a space for a tooth
A half moon an owl face in the sky always here a duck safety pin
a fly a frog
And a face with a grin face of the grin
Uh right there a face with a grin fly a frog a fly
Uh looking for a frog. I could usually pick up frogs really easily. They're my favorite animal
There it is
a frog
Too many concussions. Oh my god, that's not that's
That's i'm really fucking sorry to hear that
face in the sky
This howl
It's from head hitting his desk watching you
Now you're getting four more hours of this a space for a tooth. Somebody's missing a tooth
No, right there space for a tooth four more hours. You're almost done with it
Um, i'll just play it again
But this time backwards
All right pine cone
Pine cone
I spy a wishbone
The hell is a wishbone
That's a horseshoe bone. That's a that's a horseshoe bone. That's not a wishbone
It's going to be in the tree somewhere
No, that's a car air freshener
Half moon an owl an owl. That's not an owl
There's the owl
an owl
Can you stop goofing around?
Uh, yeah
All right. I'm stopping i'm gonna stop goofing around. You ready? Here we go
um
a duck safety
Duck safety
I looked over and cheat somebody said sky thanos. Everything is thanos. We got we can't keep making thanos references
Okay, to be honest
Thanos references are becoming mario references of like two years ago
Remember I made a fucking mario reference every single stream for like a year
Now it's thanos is in every game and it has to be an infinity war reference now every stream
And then it was a wow reference, right? Yep
That's true
I saw the fly
Fly morbid that's what gave this game a t rating
A half moon wishbone. Oh got a wishbone
I kind of I want to see this through just to see what happened
You finished yet another one
Keep solving them all until you were done
Why are you playing this game like it's for adults?
Because it is for adults it
look
You know
E for everyone
It's not E for children. It's E for everyone
It would be C for children. Okay, I think I got everything in here
E for everyone
Where's this go?
To get out. Are you ready now? All right, we're almost done and by almost done. We're almost halfway through
B for boomer
Just wait till I get the fucking bionic boomer suit on
You're gonna wish you were a boomer
with a on the okay i've been with a blue and then
So let's go I don't want to go to the bathroom the mouse move what the fuck was that
dead animal on the ground
The objects you see on these shelves have something in common
Know what it is
Fill the empty shelves by clicking on the objects that belong in this collection
ready
No, they're butterflies. They're all butterflies
Nope
Nope. Sorry. Wait. Oh, oh I have to click them now
I thought it was gonna wait
Oops that was like that was like kennedy. Whoops
Nice collection make two more collections. It's not the fucking infinity gauntlet
But you guys what the fuck
God damn it. There's the mickey mouse infinity gauntlet. Does he have one of those in kingdom hearts?
Mickey Mickey like it he does
Bugs bugs bugs
That's a frog bug
What a bad what a beautiful duck
I thought it was a bug
What was that coin
Give me that piece. Here's piece number seven in the set
Can you read my message yet?
Not yet
You can keep playing to make more creepy collections
Duck duck duck duck duck duck duck
Okay, got that one
chainsaw
Go to the attic. No, not yet. No, no attic yet
How about this way?
bedroom, uh chest or chest
I've actually quite a few places I didn't go
I spy a saddle
This is terrifying a rickety chair
A handshake a handstand
four braids of hair
boy in a frame
a girl in a hoop
a pair of blue jeans
And a yo-yo loop
Okay
well
Uh first things first, this is terrifying. You want to the scariest thing in this whole entire closet?
Nope, it's not it's annabelle. No, that movie's not even scary
No, not the doll. No that this right here
This right here is the scariest thing in here. This is just fucked up dolls aren't fucking scary
But what about the doll? What about like chuckie?
I I I will sprint and soccer kick chuckie in the head
And his and his whole head will explode
You're like annabelle the doll
Just put just turn her upside down and put her in a blender
Oh, but she comes back the next day
Well get a fucking exorcist and cover your house and vinegar or whatever the hell you do
All right, what are we looking for a boy in a frame?
boy in a frame
Just get an exorcist forehead
No, you're telling me that you wouldn't be able to just like
Grab that doll and do like a fucking tom brady punt it to that doll's head
But it has a knife
So do you?
You got a shitload of them in your kitchen ready to go right now
A handstand what if the doll can fly baseball bat swinging amiss
uh a saddle
Okay, that's some noise. I thought it was part of the game. I was like, how did they get that?
I was like what the fuck was that?
Okay crossed legs
crossed legs
a girl in a hoop
A handshake a girl in a hoop
A handshake a rickety chair
Four braids of hair
One does that count as one or two two braids of hair two, okay?
Four braids of hair a pair of blue jeans
Right there
And a yo-yo right there
And a yo-yo loop a yo-yo loop
Tough guy boomer streamer brags about how he can beat up dolls
No, anybody could do that
If you have a baseball bat guys, do you understand in a in a fight especially with like a doll?
Even if it's a demonic doll
Just wildly fucking swing around
You will hit that thing in the face
Just because it's demonically possessed doesn't mean shit
It still weighs like fucking 1.7 pounds
All right, we're gonna go in here. I spy a full moon
footprints three bows
A face with no eyes a foot with no toes
The nose of a mouse a porcelain head an eye back in place. That's pretty fucking scared though
That's scary. I'm just kidding
This is like actually scary
Okay, I spy a full moon
Probably over here
Full moon. That's a that's a half moon the nose of a mouse
The nose of a mouse
Oh right there a full moon
It's the center of the screen. All right, but hold on a second here
This this could be
This that like that's not the moon. Okay. First of all, there are two people standing in front of it
This could be anything
And yes, I know it says what the moon brought
But I like i've been i've been holding my fucking hand up this whole time my thumb out
because like
I i've just i'm like my screen's like fucked up
So i've been wiping my screen in the same spot trying to get this dust and scratches off and like it's covering up that
letter
footprints, okay
Did I write this book?
Have we talked about how like writing a children's book would be the fucking most easy money you could ever make it
Those you guys like wondering oh what's up like I have like some artistic talent
What should I do
Make a fucking children's book
Your whole story can be like 14 words
And just draw like cute fun pictures
If you're like artistically talented like just write a children's book make up a story doesn't matter what the story is
I'll prove it to you guys
Remember to write a children's book get it illustrated and publish it and make like 15 million dollars
I will tomorrow just to prove it to chat here. We could even do it on stream
I'm gonna write a children's book on stream tomorrow
Today
You want to do it today?
You want me to really like put the fucking pedal on here and like write a children's book today on stream when we're done with this
Fine just to prove you guys wrong. No, i'm not proving anybody wrong
Nobody like like as if you guys are saying that that's wrong. Yeah, let's do it fine
And i'm gonna i'll storyboard it out and then i'm gonna get it illustrated
And i'm gonna sell it and i'm just gonna like put it i'm gonna get it published
This will be my real actual book
He's so spiteful
No, i'm just
All right. I gotta think of a good fucking story. Let's get some inspiration
How about a doll that comes to life to like kill you?
And like it's some fucking like kid with a bat
And the whole thing is a doll like peeking around corners and finding him and finally like the kid kid does a full wind up
And hits the doll in the fucking mouth with the baseball bat
And like the ending frame is like the whole family like having dinner and they're all happy
Oh, yeah, it's supposed to be a children's book children's book so
uh
detective teddy the
Teddy teddy's turmoil and it's like, oh no, he didn't take a bath today. I'm gonna make a million dollars tomorrow today
Okay, so we got foot with any three bows
Already, he's been stolen just replace it with any other animal like
mosey the mouses
Bath time shenanigans or whatever it could be anything
Okay, I need to beat this game
That's called plagiarism. No, it's not
If it's original i'm gonna make it original. It'll be so original
Okay, I need a foot with no toes
This shit's gonna sell so many copies
Laugh now, but this will be in the front of every barnes and noble. It'll be a it'll sweep the nation
All right. I need um, this is getting hard an eye back in place
An eye back in place here comes a copy. Imagine if I got like fucking sued
That's why I wrote a book and I didn't realize because like everybody's written a story
About some random stuffy fluffy character
That like has trouble eating vegetables and like I get sued and I go to court and I lose everything
That would be
That would probably be fucking hilarious
That's like the only way I would ever accept like literally like like my career like my stream youtube, whatever
It was all taken from me because I've like plagiarized a children's book
like on accident
That's not a porcelain hand a porcelain head. Oh
porcelain head
Local streamer throws away his livelihood to one up for one guy
This way we're gonna fucking write it man. It's gonna be like not it's gonna be like 10 pages long
A needle
Let me see a needle
No, it's gonna be so original that there's no way anyone would take it three bows a face with no eyes
face with no eyes
a full moon
Where's a face with no eyes?
Oh
look
A face with no eyes
It's going to be so original. No one's going to publish it
We'll get in like paint and i'll make all the panels
a foot with no toes
Isn't that count?
How does that not count?
Foot with no toe. It's a ruler
A foot with no toes
Animals have paws not feet
semantics
All right, nobody footprints, but this is all like the foot stuff footprints foot foot feet
footprints
Where are they?
And then says the guy that foot paw. It's not paw print. It's footprint and that's clearly a paw
and then
I got
I got yelled at because I said feet are paws
unbelievable unbelievable unbelievable
A needle three bows
three bows
It's two two bows
Three bow
three bow
One bow two bows like a bow and arrow like a bow
They're throwing me under the bus here
bow
oh
A needle
I need to find needle
Oh, that's a nice sword
It's nice needle
God that show sucks now foot with no toes
Oh fuck
What people are wondering what i'm talking about i'm talking about game of thrones you're already done with number nine
So
What do you think of this puzzle of mine? I think it's all right
Yeah game of thrones
Still no, it's it's still still watchable
But I mean, can you blame them? The guy was supposed to write the next book
And just went to like conventions for five years
Like the winds of winter is never releasing. I just everybody needs to know that
I got it. You got to come to terms with it
He was just like living the life
Like I love that series. I've read all the books. It's like one of my favorite series ever
But I think I think I'd have to come to terms with the fact that like hbo is just going to finish that story
And i'm one of those like bitter annoying book fans. It's like no the show's not good enough because it's been booked
I like the books better
Find the right you're literally finishing it in april
Yeah, and there's there's still two more books that apparently have to come out for the actual like story to be done
shit
books on a shelf
You never read them. Yeah, what?
No, you know why you don't you know why you think I never read them
I'll tell you one very specific reason why
Because I've read all the books
And that was like in 2011
There's almost it's 2019
The last book came out before some of you guys were even born
And put it
Some of you guys are like nine, you know what I mean?
All right. Wait, wait, can I solve the uh, what's his name pat? Can I solve the puzzle to get out?
Are you ready now? And that's just to show you how with a bug on the
in
you know
books on the string with a
Thomas jefferson this order blue. All right, let's I gotta go back up
bathroom
Nice, okay
I spy a ladder
A rat eye that's red a tea back in place a winner's cup a gyroscope
And a bug crawling up. Do I read a lot? No, not really
all the you know
All wise cracks
Aside no, not anymore
I used to read all the time
Go tea back in its place
A tea back in place, okay
See, uh skeet what why huh?
uh
I spy a ladder we found
A ladder they didn't this game came out before
That song even came out. So
Give him a break
The winner's cup the winner's cup. That's not a winner's cup
I thought for a second. I thought this was a book. I'm like, yeah
There's a lot of those
Where's the winner's cup?
Uh here no, no, here's this is a perfect opportunity. You guys gonna make a perfect joke here
I don't know what a winner's cup looks like because i've never won anything and i've never come in first place
There's like the joke
Come on. I thought you guys were better than that
Uh gyroscope is here
Gyroscope a bug and a bug crawling up
No bug crawling up. I mean
I just had to click it again. Just know what it felt like to hold it
A bug crawling up a waxy mouse head
A backwards book a waxy mouse head. It's this one
A backwards book. Oh sheto
Uh a rat eye that's red
That's it
The rat eye that's red
You finished another you're doing quite well, thanks. You'll find your way out. You're smart. I can tell
Cheeto's evil twin skeeto. I spy a spider
A magnifying glass
A lightning bolt an old gravestone
A water drop swamp three nails a face made of spots and two yellow tails
Okay spider a feather a bone
Oh
Look at that. This is interesting an old gravestone. Now. This is interesting guys
This is where it becomes a little fun here
Look at that horse
Okay, I spy
eek
Sucks no
Yikes a lightning bolt. Uh, okay. Let's see a water drop swamp
Swamp if you look carefully, you can see the copyright infringement where
I'm sorry. I couldn't move for a second. I'm sorry. That's weird
Okay, uh feather
right there
Is this all we're playing tonight? No
We're doing this and i'm going to write a children's book on stream
And i'm gonna draw out the panels and pages
Okay, it's three nails. Do I really need to zoom in for this?
One nail
Water drop two nails
Two nails a water drop three nails. I need three nails. Where's the other nail?
Get out of here. I can't do this with you looking over my shoulder like this
two nails
three nails
A face made of spots
It's not this one
robot
uh
One yellow tail. Okay
Okay, that's fine
Uh, I spy a spider
What the fuck? Oh right there
Get off of him spider
um
A face made of spots and two yellow tails. There's another one
Two yellow tails
scream
um
Oh now that's in a face
That's a fish
There's a face made of spots, right? There's mickey. There's a bone
All right, everybody right now. I want everyone to do your best mickey mouse impression out loud
Three two one go
Okay kids, that's why we're gonna be
Uh kind of sounding really weird in the new kingdom hearts game for some reason
Sounds just like this
Every scene sounds like they're kind of lying down on a bed reading a newspaper
Okay, a face made of spots
Well, that's a face right there. It just is
Oh my god, it was right there. Oh my god. It was right there. Oh my god. It was right there
That's a face eyes mouth
Beard how's that? Not it scream
No, I don't bite her
Be serious a face made of spots. That's a face
That's like ronald mcdonald
I guess that's like a face
could be
Pull find three pull get out of the house when the message is done
Ronald mcdonald does have a face
If it's underneath makeup that doesn't that come on that doesn't count
He has a so he has a mask on he went in a clown nose his regular nose. That's not a person's nose
That's not a face
His face is underneath that material
Say it with me now
His face is underneath the material which is not a face
It's material
Find the right place
Almost done now. He's gonna put in nevada. There it is
One two three only four more games to play
There was still so much to explore up here
I didn't did I go in here? I don't think I went in here. Yeah, I did
Anything else I didn't do in here. I went in the wardrobe
I spy a bar of soap a toothbrush a trap a silver handle a trap a brown
Bottle cap like am I gonna fall to the floor on a pole a square picture frame
Two jacks a nine and a candle flame
Those are huge flies
Just want to make sure everyone's aware just in case you weren't
All right, so we got
Uh, no, that's too easy to say that
I was gonna say fruit punch
That's okay me saying oh look a fruit punch. Um sip yummy. That's me just reaching
To say anything about an object that's here. You know what I mean? That's actually me like what's that?
Okay, what's in there? What could be in there? Oh, is that funny? Say it. No, i'm not i'm not gonna go for that one
Coca-cola classic though, you know what i'm saying a silver handle toothbrush
Sellout is the number six
Oh, it was it was nine, but then it flipped into six a grip on a pole
Uh like that right there
Grip on a pole is where that is something there. Yeah
Pig is a pig something
Candle flame. Yeah right there
a candle flame
two jacks
jacks
jack
Square picture frame a square picture frame. Where's the jack?
snail
These are jacks
one jack
Two jacks you want to talk this is making references to an old game that people used to play in the garage
Right. Nobody plays with jacks anymore
silver handle a brown bottle cap
silver handle
jerry
Silver handle it's not the door handle bar of soap in the tub
Bar of soap I used to put jacks under my parents tires
Why would you do that?
That sounds very very bad
Why?
causing
Damage to your parents automobiles
bottle cap a silver handle
Silver handle I clicked that
Handle I clicked that a silver handle. I went like this
Okay, brown bottle cap. No
Brown bottle cap
Do you see this shit, I don't see it see teeth what is the face on the wall? Yeah, it just kind of painted there
Uh, all right. I bottle cap is almost as big as the sink
How many pieces have you gotten from me?
Here is a hint. It's 15 minus three
14 13 it's 12. It's 12 mommy
Pick up your piece
All right to get out
Are you ready?
Look at his message to show you how
green light
to the with the spider on the
I can't do it yet. I don't know
I
Just burned this house down
I need to get the treasure first picture frame a wooden chair a bat a ball for a game
That's funny two snakes a kazoo
monster face a candle and
Okay, well a skate
Quick get the bat swing as hard as you can
You're looking for like shrapnel to annabelle's coming at you
All right
Let us click
You you guys want to play okay, okay, i'm gonna give you guys one chance good luck
Give me the controller. Okay. Here's what's the cage
cage
He wants to play on the dark level
kazoo
nice nice
What this is nothing what is this?
I always just did that
Cat. Oh, yeah, I forgot everyone clicks on the weird thing or the cat
Like 30 percent of you aren't even playing you're just clicking on the fun thing game
a saw
Use a hint. No, we're gonna go hintless
All right. Thanks for the help guys, but I mean like clearly
Clearly I can do this a wooden chair
a candle a black picture frame
I've got no idea
I don't know. I've no idea a cage a bat. Wait, where's the bat? There's a bat and a doll
Ball for a game give the controller back to your little brother
No
It's my turn on the xbox
That's why we have two different consoles
I have the xbox you have the playstation 3 so we can get in arguments about which console is better
On the walk home from school
That's how you have good healthy competition with your kids
34 years old by the way. No, i'm not that's not true. That's a lie
Don't listen to that person. They don't that that's wrong
I turned 34 this year, but this hasn't happened yet. That's wrong
Black picture frame stop clicking on the cat
Stop clicking on the cat and like the funny dark souls monster
Picture
Wooden chair my turn on the soldier boy ds
Picture frame, where are these snakes? Come on help me out here
one snake
My turn on the Thanos box
Yeah, I can't even make that joke because of infinity war spoilers. I was gonna say something really funny
I was gonna say something really funny about
people owning the Thanos box
Where's the other snake guys people got angry at me for spoiling home alone. Do you think like I can't talk about movies anymore
Is this a snake?
No, that's not the snake. Oh, thank you. Thank you five percent
two snakes
What happens at the end of home alone does the kid
No, no, no, I I could neither confirm nor deny what happens at the end of any feature film. Okay
Here's piece 13
There's no doubt you're about to find the secret way out
Oh my god. Oh my god. That was fucking horrible
That was fucking horrible, I I can't even address what I just read
No
All right. What's the secret message?
Uh, okay, I just laughed really hard really quickly and I need a minute because I almost just like fucking fell over
Jesus christ
It was somebody said something about a cinder block and it was fucking horrible and I had uh,
That's all i'm gonna say. This is a pg-13 family-friendly e-rated stream
Double double toil and trouble solve the riddle where pots of stew bubble kitchen
Where's where's the kitchen
kitchen
There's the kitchen. I spice spice a knife a four and rail
Leave this door a spoon in a bowl a bug in a spoon
A scale a shell and the shape of a moon
Oh
Chairman refuses to spoil the home alone
cinderbox
portion of the
scene
Okay eggs. I found them
Okay, I gotta fucking relax
God damn it, man
Sometimes I look over and and like something is said and fuck I do it throws me off forever
This is this is the dreamcast sucks laughing my ass off comment all over again
I want me to keep a hot dog in a jar. That's like a ballpark frank, by the way
With the fake grill marks on it a bug in a spoon you return it a spoon in a bowl
a bug in a spoon
I spy spice
Where's the spice?
Spice it's weird way to say that. Okay bug in a stew
a knife a four
It was a knife a knife
knife
a knife
Streamer refuses to eat frank on stream
no
Do we ever talk about the the hot dog eating competition with kubayashi versus the bear?
We've done that. We've talked about that, right?
No, no, we haven't
It's like one of the funniest goddamn things
So, uh, you know the the hot dog eating champion, right? So
This guy if you don't know who kubayashi is he used to he could eat like 75 hot dogs
In like 10 minutes. It's ridiculous. It's the coney island hot dog eating competition
And there's they did this segment. There was this old show called like man versus beast
Or something like that
And one of the segments they had like people that were extraordinary at certain things go up against animals
And it's one side but kubayashi they brought him in to go do a hot dog eating contest versus a bear
And it was supposed to be like this huge deal where kubayashi can't he out eat a fucking grizzly bear in
25 seconds and you're thinking oh, this is gonna be interesting
It's not at all
What happens is kubayashi is like mowing down these hot dogs at two a second like drinking water
It's sucking them down as fast as he can and the bear doesn't give a shit
The bear doesn't know it's a competition
So he doesn't care the bear like winnie the pooh moses over to the hot dog
It's like there's like probably a hundred hot dogs laid out in front of this bear
and the bear just was like sniffing them and there's a timer and there's commentary and shit and the bear is just like
Like tilts his head over and like sucks one up hole
And then like starts smelling him again
I think the bear only eats like fucking seven hot dogs. He doesn't give a shit and kubayashi eats like 60
And they thought it was gonna be like good television
Uh, I gotta like fucking find this right now and put it on the stream
The bear like tilts his head and like
The thing is the bear knew it was a competition. He would eat a hundred hot dogs in like five seconds
Let's see kobayashi versus bear
There it is
Yeah, and they got the break up bruce buffer to do like the fucking intro and they had the bear like scream
Uh, I don't this is uh, excuse me ladies and gentlemen, i'll see you in about five seconds when I get this on stream
We're gonna watch this whole thing
I remember when this first aired I remember fucking laughing my ass off
It was like the funniest fucking thing i'd ever seen
And we're well, let's watch it. The quality is so low
All right, here we go. See he's like prepared. He's coming in like strong like doing like training
He's got his water there like all these hot dogs. He's ready
He descends from kodiak island alaska fully this beast stands over eight feet tall do the roar
At one thousand sixty pounds of food in a 24-hour period, but he doesn't know it's a competition
He has no fucking just go what he's hot dogs. Oh, yeah, the contest begins as soon as the bear eats the first
As many as they can is what both the bear is going for it as well. Look at that
I saw a flash of fear for a second in kobe yashi's eye because he's never faced a competition like this
It's unbelievable. See how casual look at how many hot dogs kobe yashi has left. I don't see how
You can make this bear you gotta remember kobe yashi is an eating machine
He's got a formula down where he just goes never takes a break. He's steady
Right and he also as you can see michael
He has the water there because his mouth gets dry and it helps him digest the hot dogs
Well kobe yashi is the greatest professional leader in the world. He's got this eating. Yeah, who thought this is a good idea
It's one minute into the competition now kobe yashi is doing very well. The bear is is scooping them up
Obviously, it's got a very different approach to eating
But see he looks away and he takes a break because he doesn't know it's a competition
He's just a natural eating machine and he'll he'll take the break look away. Look at the lights
Look at our cameraman while kobe yashi never stops. You can see that. Did I misremember this?
Look how skinny kobe yashi is and look at the size of the bear
You know, I was really impressed when kobe yashi first came out. He's in great shape. You can tell he's an athlete
He's got great biceps and he's and he came out with a small stomach
He won't leave with one but he's he's a fabulous looking athlete two minutes into the competition
Kobe yashi is watching that bear like a hot that bear is definitely going through the hot dogs michael
He is he is he's making a strong lead. I can't count in that dish
Yes, he is and I cannot count them from the angle that i'm at right now
But no, he doesn't win. He is in the lead. It looks like no he doesn't win
Very shortly the bear is now looking at kobe yashi. Do you believe that exactly?
He's being distracted. This is what kobe yashi hasn't missed the beat
There's only maybe six seven hot dogs left and there it goes. Oh my god. There's only three hot dogs
Ow, what the fuck
There's only two hot dogs left. There we go. He's down the last one. She must know that's it
No
He's done. I thought he
Has won
The alaskan cruncher is our new champion
I got that so wrong
I'm here with civ martin the bear handler. Did you have any doubt?
Well, you know when a bear comes in he's this bear is really hungry
So when they come in like that, they're gonna chow right down, but I have to give it to him
He really did a good job on keeping up with the bear. It was a real close race
Were you afraid at all?
No, the best part
Seriously like okay, so he said he said the bear has six or seven hot dogs left
And i'm remembering from like two decades ago
That he only ate seven but the point still stands like watch what happens when the bear the bear the first hot dog
That he eats is just so stupid
He just like sneaks over and it's like oh he like tilts his head to the side he eats it
Oh, it's so funny as soon as the bear eats the first hot dog
It is under way it's like this
Oh
I i'm I so I so poorly misremembered that but that makes it funnier to be
uh
people
Old tv was so dumb
You know how much that segment probably cost
Old shows back in like the late 90s early 2000s man. They used to just throw piss money into the garbage can
Oh my god
I fully erect a large bear
I don't even know how we got there what we did
That's one of my favorite television segments
Now I got a fucking headache
The bear really eats like seven hot dogs
Oh, he eats them all actually
all of them
Handrail. All right
Wait, what what are you what am I getting linked here?
What that face is so ugly
Look at this shit
Where did this even come from? When did I do this?
I I book I don't even look human in this photo
Hold on. Look
I don't even look human
I look like anybody ever have a gerbil
Or or hamster
Remember they used to just stuff shit in their mouth
And hide it in their cheeks
I don't that doesn't even look like the same person. That doesn't look like jeremy elbertson. That's not even me
You look like a bogdanoff
What the fuck uh, all right, uh hidden object game, uh
But that was like manned versus beast or whatever the hell it was. I had so many dumb shows like that
Yeah, well the thing is he was really hungry
Shape of a moon big bits. Oh shit. I did I missed him with 50 bucks
Uh 50 dollars from g y h d h f e. Uh, thank you so much for the 50 dollars
Huge money. Thank you. Speaking of hot dogs germa, what do you prefer?
uh
What?
This is just throwing this throwing me off here speaking of hot. What do you prefer tits or ass?
If you avoid the question or answer neutrally, I will assume you like
hot, okay, um
Uh, well first of all, thanks for the 50 dollars. That's a huge amount of money second of all
Uh
That's not uh, that's inappropriate for stream talking
But i'm gonna have to say i'm a i'm a big fan
of
I I like uh
I like the female package, you know what I mean the whole thing
I love you know what I mean?
Now the whole the whole thing like all of it. I like that. I i'd like everything about the about the female
Right. All right. Okay, so let's find some fours
Avoiding it. I just told you I like all of it. I like the whole I like the whole female package like the whole female
Female doesn't matter what body part
Armpit no, you know what i'm saying. All right, what would anybody like some tea?
Where's the scale some knife you guys you guys?
You guys a hand rail hand rail
Bug, I thought it said bug lover
Just fucking help me out here
That was a clock. I didn't know that was a scale
Stop clicking up here
Oh, it's a cat. I remember always click the cat face
Okay, where's the four four four four four four four. Oh, it was in the grout
Thank you for the help guys. You guys fucking rock. All right, give it here
You're one piece away from winning the game be free
One piece away from winning the game
I am such a fucking intelligent
hyper
hyper educated streamer
Tick seven
Jerry okay, uh hand on the wall one two three
Dice pen an upside down one
S plus my crazy taxi rating what about the cinder block?
A backwards number
What's the backwards number?
uh four
Watch out watch out a shadow to the left a hand on the wall. No, it was just so extreme
uh
The rhyme for a three. Hey kids, it's me party b
a crack
Three horns there was one horn. I need a second horn horn skate a skate
Crack
Horns whoa
What is that?
Oh
They mean literal horns
So where's the last one? Where's the upside down one? I feel like the upside down one's gonna be hard to find
the key
He has two
Well, I thought she said two horns
Three
She I thought she was talking about two horns. I thought like actually she meant you found two here
It's because I had one
Where's the upside down one? There it is an upside down one
Crack
If I was if I was crack, what would I be?
That that's a crack right there
All right. It's time to solve the whole thing
Here's your last piece
I'm done
That sounds pretty good to me let's decode the message
Okay, here we go d d plus ear dear it's time to get out. No, I wanted to do this
This message to show you how to go to the room with a spider on the ceiling spider on the ceiling
I've been concealing spider on the ceiling
Find three books on a shelf with a white head hold them in this order blue green then red
skeleton
Okay
So go to the room with a spider on the ceiling and then find a door. I've been concealing
Find three books on a shelf with white
head
Then pull blue green red
Let's find the spider on the ceiling. I don't know what the hell I'm not gonna get out of here
Found it. Okay
Here we go
You did it
Well, that was fun game am I still light
What's with the audio go through my window?
You do escape through the window
To do trick scare hunt
Second floor first floor
Are you here?
We did it
Wait what I stop stop
You're trapped inside my house once more could there be another door
I sure just went to denny's this still open at two if you want to get out now
Go to the kitchen. I'll show you how all right. This is more content
Go to the kitchen
This is loud
Okay, what's in the kitchen to get out this time you'll have to make my favorite recipe
Shrinking soup
First fill my kitchen with ingredients by playing I spy riddles and games
uh
Okay, well
I don't care about your soup
Shrinking soup makes one serving
Makes one serving
You haven't found all of the ingredients yet to find the ingredients
Just hot dogs and bugs
What goes in here?
I spy tick. Oh, no
No, no, no, no
A pen no, no
Sticks for six a teapot talk and a number that fell
off the clock
New game plus
No
Let us do it this time. You know what? What a brilliant idea
I'm just getting just speed run. Let's go. I need to see the true ending come. Let's do it
It's the seven you got it
Got the tick that fell off the clock got the beehive
Yeah, got the apple core the ten we're gonna get through this real quick
pen
sticks for six
Jerry no, it's not right this talk
And then sticks for six
I need the sticks there they are
Reset reset
Where's the teapot guys?
You didn't get me the teapot. Where's the teapot?
Ah nice
Leave leave quick. Leave leave leave
We're gonna blow through this. I need to see the true ending. I have to eat that poison soup
It's an apple
All right, cool, thank you
I spy two red bugs a dime no
Five flies an ear saw teeth two dark brown eyes
It's gonna take a while
This is a fun this is a fun game what a fun children's game
We just wanted to write a chill. Yeah, i'm gonna write the children's book. Don't worry
Saw teeth
I love these books as a kid. Yeah, they were very enjoyable
Dime finish it you coward
Finish it
No, we're gonna have to go through every single room. We got to do this like 15 times
You think you you stink you think you still have the cd for this game?
Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised
It's just two more times. That's it for real
Gotta click on the flies
This is just i'm just cheating this is
I
Hope you guys are enjoying yourself
Because this is uh
This just turned into rush to the ending. All right, what am I missing? Oh, did I just break the extension?
Uh-oh
Uh, I broke the extension is broken. I can't refresh it. No, I need yeah, I need chats help with this shit
I can't refresh it. God damn it. Come on
Shit, hold on. All right. I need your help
Help me did not work. How did I fuck this up restart it? Oh, the extension is just
gone
Shit
Uh, hold on
Configure okay. It's on
I'm gonna deactivate it
Activate
Okay. Now it's activated again
Let's go back here
Can you guys see it?
No, why not?
God damn it
How did I break this?
Let me see if this works
We've used this a million times. How the hell did I break this?
All right. Let's try it again
Can you do it?
Oh beautiful. Okay. Great. Here we go. All right. Help me. We already did that one
All right. It's almost time to write the book
No, not yum
That's not a fly. That's a bee. Does you guys know basic human anatomy?
All right
Where's the pearl from above pearl looking for pearl and then we can get the last ingredient and I can exit
Everyone click on the skeleton for the sans eye
Oh god, all right last ingredient
Thank you
No, that was fun
All right. We're gonna move on
I'm gonna move on to writing a children's book because that's fun to me right now
No, no, no, no
Rage quit. No, we I got to the end
Confugilary read the children's book. We have to finish the soup
You're not gonna eat that shit. Anyways
Do a children's mad lib with click extension. How does that work?
What's in the soup?
radishes apples
chicken stock
And like bird feathers. Yeah, I just saved you like I just saved you guys like 40 straight more minutes
All right. I gotta pee. I'll be right back and we're gonna do some other stuff