Timeless. Legendary. Strong.
Those are some of the words you could use to describe Glooman.
One of our world's greatest superheroes.
And for the first time ever, you can adorn yourself with this upper body garment.
The Glooman t-shirt is now available.
Yes, that's right. Glooman, protector of the innocent, defender of justice,
and warden of all that is good and kind, has finally caved into marketing pressure
to deliver this shirt to you.
Buying this shirt will take you back to moments like these.
Glooman's German wrestling debut.
As a 22-year-old newbie under the stage name G. Grossi,
he made a real splash in his first match when he was nearly killed by Dogman,
the magical dog magician, who at the time was considered at least partially blind.
Each shirt does not come with a certificate of authenticity,
but this might be what one may have looked like if they did.
Signed and stamped by the father of all contemporary German wrestling,
George R. Glooman Sr. himself.
It is a true sight of craftsmanship and quality.
And again, no, you don't get one of these.
How much does a t-shirt like this cost, you ask?
Not $12,000, not $8,000, not even $5,000.
To get your very own Glooman t-shirt, you need only one low payment of $20.
Plus shipping and handling.
Take pride in owning a piece of German Channel history.
Brag to all of your friends that you own a shirt
whose depicted character has been deemed out loud as the worst character ever
and useless by the individual who created him.
These shirts are only available for a limited time and may never be available again.
Head over to teespring.com slash Glooman to reserve one today.
All links will be in the description.
Again, that is teespring.com slash Glooman with no spaces.
Order now.
Or, I mean you have like, you have like three weeks.
You can order in like three weeks.