Good good good. So put it in. Put it in saw. Saw. Finish saw.
Try again. I don't know maybe.
Shit that that really does look like a fucking like dirty diaper.
I just looked at it again. The disc isn't reading. Oh my fucking god guys. We're in trouble.
We're in trouble. Unrecognized disc. Okay good. Um oh shit there's a huge stain on this.
There's like a big like coffee stain. Hold on. I gotta clean it. How did this even happen?
Buying? Why would I lie about that? I can't go back to Ratatouille right now. The save point is
like 20 minutes before I even got to that point. No we're good. We're good. Here we go.
No. Did we determine if it was David or attended the uh ragoon? Attended? Let's uh sign out.
Did it work? Yes we're good. Okay I don't remember anything that was happening.
I have no idea where we were in the game. I don't even know how to play. It's been like
it's been like three months. I have absolutely no idea. It's been longer than three months.
Is it? 11 wait. November of last year? November, December, January, February, March, April, May, June,
July, August. It has not been 10 months. No the date in my xbox is wrong. This one's five five.
Okay shit. Does this look familiar? Okay wait a minute. That's heal. That's flashlight. Left
trigger and okay left trigger and left trigger and a is punch. Never enough time to do the
things we want to do. Is there a detective? All right I think we're good. I don't I don't this is
like a late game puzzle. I have no idea what it wants me to do. Activate the two circuit boxes
to open the door. Why did I think the punching it was gonna work? Okay I have to turn the gas off
here. Is there a sprint? Go back to Ratatouille. No dude. No that's not happening. I need one of
those things. I need a circuit breaker thing. Is there one back here? What the fuck? You need to go
get the handle. Dude open the door. Just hey it's like not even four months has gone by.
Okay go on. Yeah yeah. Three minutes and 30 seconds till the world explodes.
Watch your step detective. Yeah thank you. Oh nothing. I need to think. Is this a save file
soft locked? It might be. I think this shit is soft locked. I don't have any of those and then
no way to be found. What the fuck dude? I got one. I got one. I got one. I got one. I got one. I got
it. Oh shit. Yeah. Two minutes. Two minutes. Two minutes. Do I still have one of those
units? Do I have a unit still? I still have one. Gas. Gas. Gas. I can turn the gas off. Turn the gas.
Absolutely. I only have like one minute. Hurry up. I don't want to do this shit again. Turn off the
gas. Turn off that fucking gas. Ratatouille waiting room. All right I have one minute. Don't even look
at the clock. I can do this in 10 seconds. Yeah. Oh fuck. I gotta go 40 seconds. Oh no shotgun. No
shotgun exploding head thing. No shotgun exploding head thing. I made it. Thank god. Locate the
crematorium. Locate Obi. I have more time than that dude. Come on. All right. Locate. Save the game.
I forgot a drink.
I just got back. Why is he playing this shit game again? Because I have to play this shit game again
because I have Saw 2 now and if I want to play Saw 2 and I don't finish Saw 1 what kind of video
game player am I? Seven and a half minutes for what? Why is this seven and a half minutes on that?
That's too much time. Okay activate the two circuit boxes to open the door. And there's a timer too.
Give me a weapon. Somebody's here. Okay well that's all right. I'll get.
Gresham has its price detective. All right let's shotgun this guy's head off. I don't have time for
this. Punch him. I can't punch through the gate. It's installed fuse. Oh shit it did. I'll go the
fuse box. All right power on. Don't walk out there. All right I'm gonna I'm gonna lure him over here
and then kill him. How do I get this guy to open the door? Pick up a pipe. Let's go. Now you're
fucking dead. Open the door. Now run the fuck away and then zap him. Oh god oh god oh god oh god oh
god. Turn it on turn it on. Turn it off. What do you got on you? Spike club. Elf hypo nail. All right
good. No no no no no no no no. Put this down. Give me that thing. I want his thing. There we go.
Ruined my life and then you killed him. He's running at me with a spiked club. I'm sorry but
I'm gonna attack you if you try to. You're gonna try to kill me? Holy shit. Okay you know when you
put open up minesweeper and you put it on hard. Okay looks good looks good. Fuck. Um I need a
power source over here. I need power power power power power power power power. Oh dick this is
not good. Oh is a power source up here. I think this is six minutes on the clock. Down? All right
not bad not bad not bad. But actually bad. Bad. No no no no no no. I think that's right. That's
right. That's right. That's right. That's right. Right? Right? Wrong. Wrong. Oh no. Oh wait wait wait.
Oh bingo. No not bingo. This is too much. This is too much. Just okay forget it. Do the other ones
first. Do this other shit first. Um this needs to be connected to. Okay this needs to be connected
to here. This needs to be connected to here. This then um then um uh um uh this then goes ah
uh um. Oh hold on. Wait wait wait wait. I fuck. Wait there's only just like three more after light.
This goes up to god damn it. I fucked it. I I don't know. It's too it's huge. It's too much. I
haven't played this game for like four months. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait. Now
now now now now now I go. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Oh how much time? Four seconds? No. Go go go go go
go go. Open. Huh? Dude. Oh do you think I'm gonna do that thing again? Oh I don't think so. What a
monumental pain in the ass. You put it on very hard mode. Yeah cool. That's the joke mode that
was on old puzzle games that nobody wow I'm never gonna be able to do this shit. I put I put the hard
difficulty scale up the whole way. No way this is happening. Get the fuck over here. Fuck you.
Fast. Hurry up. That's what I wanted to do. Yeah give me a thing. Give me your weapon. Okay here
comes this fucked up part with the breathing. God. Okay the controls suck such asshole. I'm
trying to select this one. Like it's it's so bad. It's unbelievably awful. Don't bolt the door.
Take a healing potion. Pipe dial unlock with a what the fuck do you want me to do?
Heal. How do I heal? What's the heal button? Okay where's this fucking thing? Look for like a little
pipe. This is sealed. This is fucked up. Are you serious? Just unlock it. I can't. I need one of
those things. Go back to the box. Yeah I think there's a reason why I said I've never played
this fucking piece of shit ever again. I need a valve. Go run around look at every fucking stupid
wardrobe to find the one thing I need. Shut up saw. Found a fuse. How much time do I have?
Coupler. Okay coupler. All that shit's over here by the way. Keep in mind. Okay let's get this quick.
Hurry up. I want one minute. Go. Oh my head. Come on. Come on. Now it's this way. I don't know. What?
Fuck. Okay got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Little bit more. Come on shithead. Do it. Open. All right.
Now okay that's gonna open the door right? Okay this door. Now I need uh I need um what do I need
now? I got a few minutes. I have to turn on the pipe thing. Do I have that now? Where's my inventory?
I think it's got it. I don't know. I think it's got it. Fucking walk. I got three minutes. Go.
Fuck you. What? Why? Why? I didn't take it? You can't be serious. Take all. A. I pressed A.
I pressed A. I why would I not have pressed A? Stupid feature. Thank god this put is simple. This
is the easy one. Oh shit. I can't do the easy one. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Hurry. What is this? What the fuck? That was for a scalpel. That was for a scalpel. That wasn't
even anything I needed. Get the fuck out of here man. No. No way. I'm sorry. No way. No fucking way.
Un-fucking-believable. Why would this is the dump? This is like not even cool. I'm dead. Um okay so
I am gonna picture of the completed puzzle so I can just go through them and just do it and just
get out of this room. I'm gonna just go look up a walkthrough and just look at the completed puzzle
and just get every single one correct. It's random. It's random. It's random. Oh shit. Okay slow down.
Here we go. Left side first go. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Open the fuck. Open. All right I gotta do this
quick. I'm so bad at these puzzles though. It's not even funny. I don't even have one. Got it. Okay
there's one there. All right. I don't even. I don't want to do this anymore. I would rather play
Ratatouille. I'd rather show my fucking beehive nuts on stream than do this. Up. Up. Up. Up.
What a pain in the ass. What a total pain in the ass. I don't fucking know if this is even
right. It's just not even right. I'm back. I'm begging you. This stream isn't funny anymore.
Ratatouille is funnier. Fuck please. So like all right you know like you dig like the Saw video
game. I know everyone wanted me to complete this but this is dog shit. Let's be honest. We gotta
be completely upfront. Doing like the pipe dream puzzle over and over again like a thousand times.
This game just sucks. I should really just run around and get all the couplers. Mad because bad.
No I'm. I am bad. You're right. But oh my god. Why do you want. Who wants to do like five of these
in a row with a timer. All right quiet. Get them all connected. Do it right. Got it. I need this
connected. I need this connected to something. Where's the power? I need this connected. What
the fuck am I going to connect this to? Oh you piece of shit. It's like a dumb ass fucking game.
Dumbest fucking game on Twitch right now. This is not connected to shit. How do I get this? I gotta
fucking. Okay connected to that. Now this is. This goes up. How do I connect you? That took too long.
I got like three. I got two minutes left to do like eight other puzzles. Who made this game?
I'm embarrassed for them. Go outside in. Go out. I turned it off. Are there cheat codes for this game?
Just a cheat and his fucking no clip through the door. There's four of those puzzles. There's five
puzzles in seven minutes. That means I have to do every puzzle in less than one minute.
Is that even possible to do that in seven minutes? This has to be the last room of the game.
You wish. It's just too. It's too much man. It's just too. It's too. It's too many things to look at.
It's too confusing. It's just. Shut up. Turn the fucking TV off. I don't want to hear him anymore.
My brain's like too tired to do this. I hate this. I hate these puzzles too by the way.
Of all the puzzles they could be. These are like my least favorite.
Okay. I'm gonna be. I'm all right. Like this shit over here. Like this shit right here.
This one going here. This one going over. I don't know. Fuck. I don't know. This one has to go up.
And what do I do about this shit here? Outside in dude. Outside in dude. Outside in dude.
All right. Outside in dude. All right. Yeah. Outside in dude. Outside in. Something gets
fucked up here though. There's no outside in. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. Because once
I get this it's going to take like a minute or two to do this. There's one more. Come on.
Oh fuck off with this bullshit. All right. Go. Did I get it? Get it. Take it.
All right. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
I got another coupler. I already have one. I just have to do the fucking gas room. Yeah. Okay.
Like that's going to fucking happen in four minutes.
Turn it. No. Get away. God. You need a circuit box. Let's put three of the same stupid dog shit
puzzle right back to back. Six minutes. This is fun. Outside in. Oh this one. No. No. No.
I don't understand how this is wrong. Fuck. Oh. Oh. Oh. Okay. We got it. We got it. We got it.
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. How many minutes? Okay. This has to turn. Two. Oh. Oh.
Fuck. Okay. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck dude. Fuck dude. Which one? Turn this one. I don't know. This
one is highways. This one has to go. I don't know. It's so close. Come on. Do it. Oh. What
happened? How do I do this? I got it wrong somewhere. This one thing wrong. I don't even
know where the fuck it is. This is connected to here. This is connected to there. This has
to be connected here. This has to be connected to here. But then you lose this fucking thing.
And then I don't understand. I don't understand. Is this the last piece? I have to pause the game.
Oh my god. I hate this fucking game with a passion. This is the worst game I've ever played on stream.
I want to drop kick this fucking disk into the dumpster. Okay. You ready? I'm taking a screenshot
of this and we're going to up the contrast. Okay. So the bottom. There's no. Oh yeah. I don't need
to take a screenshot. You're right. Okay. This is a screenshot. All right. I'm going to unpause
the game and somebody. Okay. Here we go. Ready? Take a screenshot. I probably should have told
you to do that beforehand. Did you get it? Did somebody get it? Okay. This is stupid.
All right. So wait, is that, is this you? So is this the puzzle solved? Did you edit this?
Okay. The middle right needs to go. I need to like draw on stream. Okay. Somebody,
can somebody draw a picture on there? All right. Somebody draw a picture. So I need you to draw a
picture. Somebody take that photo and draw, draw over it the way it was supposed to look like.
It should take you like two minutes, right? Like I'm not even, I don't want to do this again.
I fucking hate this. I'm going to put, I don't care. I'm going to, I'm going to wait till
somebody gets me the right picture. It's not even the middle right one. Okay. Did you get it?
No, not pixel dick, not pixel dick, not pixel dick. What are you linking me to? I don't know.
This is, that's Yoda. That's Yoda. Please. I need you to help me. Pixel penis. Yeah. Cool.
I can't, I can't throw that on stream. Somebody please help me.
This is super monkey ball again, but with like the stupidest, shittiest puzzles.
Yeah. That's the image, but you didn't, I know I already have the image, but I need correction on
it. I need you to just, I need you to do it for me. Just draw, go and paint and like draw what it's
supposed to look like. You solve it. Yeah. You'll get it. Somebody will get it. I'm not on pausing
till I can verify what it looks like. Mods verify this. Okay. I think somebody's got it, but no,
you don't. All right. Hold on. What, what is it? What am I looking at here though?
This is it. All right. And then I think this is it. Somebody's got it. Okay. So we got it. You got
it. You got it. You got it. Okay. So it looks like we've got the cross in the middle cross in the
middle does not connect anything down there. This is looks all right. I got to turn the one that's
blinking right now over to the left. Okay. Then I got to get the one right below it be like this.
Okay. Turn that one down there. Good. This next one, remember this is a children's game. It's
right at M for mature. You can't even go in and your parents don't have to buy this for you. Bad
parent, bad parent. And then it comes out of there, goes down and then it goes this way.
And then it goes up. Yes. Okay. This one goes which way? Left. Good. And it goes straight over
and this one goes down like this. And then this one goes up. The one down here goes up, up.
The one goes there to the left. That's it. I did it. I got it. Okay. I'm good.
I hate this fucking game. This game sucks. Okay. Hey, how you go guys? You ready for this?
We're going to play a game called. Oh, I need to go get the couplers first.
It better be one right here. I'm going to scream. Thank God. Okay. Uh, hey guys,
make a screenshot. Somebody saw the whole fucking thing. I just broke it. I think I broke the
controller. Why even play? Oh, come on. That was good time. That was pretty good time. That
actually was not bad time. I got five minutes. I need another decoupler though. Take slow down.
One in here, right? Where is it? It's right in here. Did I get it? Good. Good. Good. Good. Okay.
Decoupler. Let's go. This is so easy. Just get it right. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Go. Go. Go.
I need another D. I need another coupler. Shit. Come on, dude. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. I need one of those couplers. Coupler. Come on. Why are you doing this to me right now?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Down. Maybe down. This bang. Turn around. This. Whack. Wham. Whack. Uh, wait.
Fuck. Um, outside, outside, outside. Uh, yeah, yeah. Um, okay. This way. No. Um, like this. Okay.
All right. It's, uh, it's getting there. It's getting there. Okay. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, uh. All right. Yeah. Yo. Yup. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yup. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
No. Yes. Yes. I don't know. Fuck. Somebody solve it. Somebody solve it. Solve it.
Screenshot. One, two, three. Solve it. Somebody solve it. I got time. You already did it. We
already did this is a maze then what's with the gigantic Google search thing
come on where's that one guy that did it before it was perfect mr. ratatouille
says please what the hell you didn't okay thanks for solving the puzzle did a
good job solving this puzzle please play my game German I'm not sure what you
have against rats Chuck E cheese will not be happy about this okay all right you
got it somebody got it here's your image thank you that's and I know I have the
image I need the solution to the problem solved got it all right yes okay so this
one let me get this on screen so you can see all right so it goes you have to go
down but it goes yeah that's right wait you just just trace what I did this has
to go up that then this has to go sideways like this this goes down up
this one curves over nice almost done what happened here this is correct this
is the way this is the way I have it what am I doing wrong this right I'm
gonna got it wrong pop middle one is wrong what solved it hold on top middle
piece goes up okay you didn't solve it you just did one part you can't say
solved and just correct one of the mistakes change the three-way piece oh
shit did I do it fuck it's all that's all that's up I screwed up so I've moved
some stuff though you have to do it again okay so that okay got it here's
this one the left is down this is correct correct correct okay correct okay
correct correct yep so far okay oh shit it's done I got it I got it I got it it's
done what's wrong oh I have 13 seconds I have 13 seconds to get out of here oh my
god thank goodness holy shit oh my fucking god thank you god thank you the
stream savers I hated every second of that thank God I don't have to keep
falling down in Ratatouille crematorium that's where we need to go
audio tape save the game I can't it's does it at random intervals checkpoint
in here right at least the frozen hand into the furnace all right give me a
checkpoint where's the fucking checkpoint guys where's the checkpoint
okay got the crematorium key I got a minecraft stake yeah point all right here
we go you've come to the streamer room he's isolated himself in his broadcasting
fortnight he hasn't been outside for over two months I just don't boil the
guy alive I think I can get it okay here we go outside in that's wrong right
that's correct part two no wrong wrong wrong fuck wrong super this ultra wrong
he's already dead all right this is very wrong good no kind of there it is
there it is got it I'm gonna save him it's good I got plenty of time it's my
game actually and maybe they get that looks good how's that close it's close
it's pretty close right there shit wrong fuck there it is all right come on up I
almost aced the last people 10v1 I was gonna get on the front page at
the way I wasn't ready to come out yet it was finally good game but then you
had to come along didn't you isn't that why you're here Jesus you're just as
crazy as him we're in an asylum we're all crazy the sound of the bat hitting
him right in the forehead as hard as I can I had the choice you have bare feet
oh okay fine jigsaws next clue don't hit him until you get a checkpoint that's
important give bare feet I guess yeah you save a man who does not want to be
safe don't get this weapon here can I give you a weapon I'll take the hatchet
you following me still oh let's go much like dead rising oh okay follow me come
on follow me come on come on follow me come on
you do it you put your hand in there oh I just have to grab it don't spill it
I still have a hatchet right find the clue at least I'm not doing a fucking
puzzle throwing away chasing jigsaw can't you see he's giving you a gift the
opportunity to live life without this obsession you lack perspective I can't
stand by that's me hitting him in the head with the bat his head flying back
so fast it hits the fucking concrete and out of aluminum all right well he's
gone that was stupid comes the final clue final saw clue and then I can be
done with this franchise until like next week when I play the second game I mean
this pipe shotgun shotgun shotgun I have a gun reserve shotgun okay I have to go
down I gotta ring these install light bulb right this is gonna be fun it's
gonna be fantastic I can't wait run run open every draw to find a light bulb to
put in here all right go down ding ding ding ding ding ding ding they're looking
here it's gonna be like a boss open up every draw in the museum room right I
see you tripwire sure oh there's a whole bunch of shit over here the lock give me
in here there's items in here remember they're actually releasing another game
at Saucon this weekend I don't know what Saucon is but I know it doesn't
exist I let's see if I can do this there better be a gun in here on explosive
trap schematics and shotgun shell pretty much 100% useless I'm glad I used a
lockpick to get in here all right let's do it whatever it is
Saucon here I don't know what the combo is okay how long stick to brute force a
three-digit password let's start at zero I'm not gonna do that I'm kidding we
didn't even get a code depends please I'm not gonna do that 643 823 375 74
find it 128 find the numbers I thought I just said it right there all right fine
let's go find the numbers I don't want to play your game yeah yeah yeah wait
that's something on you the numbers up here stage date on the poster okay drop
that that back up I don't care just go the table leg that was here date
November 18th 19 that's 11 11 and 18 there's a lie okay let's go over here
storage you have the code what's the code still a music I was a shit turns on
it's 181 well I'm already dip Marty down here so we're all right all right down
here blah blah blah blah blah yeah yeah whatever whatever whatever here comes
the code the code if he needs me we're gonna get in the code I have the code
no code the flashlight up already have one this dude's gonna jump around the
corner like what do you think I'm stupid well you have an idiot another person
down here Dean venture all right let's do it remember go to sock on for the
code there's no such thing as sock on a guy in a saw mask shows up at like the
horror fest 2018 or whatever but not here holy shit I almost just died didn't
I you were trapped in the room ten minutes to play the hardest level of
what somebody who's texting me hold on I gotta text somebody mom one sec okay no
there's no bit incoming I'm not about to like no I just somebody I actually had
to text somebody we're gonna nail my you interrupted by it wasn't my mom I'm not
gonna say it was my mom I'm off probably watching right now and she's gonna be
like I didn't text that liar oh what else Oh a coupler hmm all right good good
what do you want me to do I completely forgot that existed they're gonna shoot
anyways who will help I need it you know enter the code yeah I don't know what
the code is yet maybe I'll find the code here how much less ridiculous this one
is by the way this one is not even close to being as insane as the other ones
have been good button are they both open let's go anything else in here that I
need to get a medical cabinet it's not good and it is nice like I could steal
the Adderall did I really do all this today I could have just skipped this by
putting the code in was that already walking like all right now I got a
weapon underneath I'm not I shouldn't be scared because there's no monsters and
saws not like a giant dead space monsters gonna I mean I might look like
the dead space guy right now like the thing like doesn't have like a thing on
his shoulders I was on his back nevermind okay I take the shotgun oh I
armed the trap somebody's gonna burst out of the door here what the hell is it
here guilt you guys had already he already killed him this is pre-recorded
all right so he's dead find a light bulb within the staff housing find a light
bulb find the combination to the cafeteria fuck what was it find a light
bulb in the find a light bulb in the staff housing rate or 35 ever real 435
wrong 838 that's wrong too the light bulb is in your ass is it on is it like
is it on I don't understand I don't even know why I laughed that hard at that
that was a forehead laugh it really was cafeteria where the hell my light bulb in
the staff room we got wisdom is the stupid ass staff room current position
the objective circle I don't know I have no goddamn idea why it was wasn't
something loading I hear a guy code what oh shit 038 some of you guys almost got
it too 838 how did you you were close I find a light bulb in the cafeteria
probably gonna need to use these okay there's a guy's gonna blow through here
with a chainsaw there's the other chainsaw I know he's coming where is he
you would have solved it faster if you had just done your strategy of counting
up from zero that actually would have happened you're right that's ridiculous
you're right what the hell's even in here crowbar I got a better weapon
already oh explosive trap can't make it I have gas trap stun trap explosive trap
I already have like a bunch of shit how do I use this stuff almost died you spam
Molotov oh yeah all right this is the cat where's the was the thing I gotta
get in here I'm one of the doors or something I don't know important if you
ever put a light bulb in your ass it'll get stuck and you can't get it out
without breaking it and explodes the safest way to remove the bulb without
maiming yourself is to feed a banana around the bulb what the fuck are you
talking about a gear I don't know what who's gonna do that why would anybody
do that what you're describing no one would ever do what you just said no one
not one person gonna turn that shit off how do I get that how do I get this how
do I get that off would be in saw no one said ass yes they did yes they did I
need to turn it where's a valve I gotta turn the valve off somewhere but where
the fuck is a valve I cap it no it said mouth the one that I read did not say
mouth oh god it's right in the course of corner
ass lighted yeah I mean you might the one that I read said ass well a lot of
molotovs with a lighter what happened to the molotovs I just had like a bunch
of fucking molotovs where'd they go turn that shit off I almost why I'm
getting so lucky disarming these traps you have no idea but an emote only mode
important if you put a light bulb yeah what what before look out oh before
cooking oh before look out you know what I'm trying to say
oh before cooking in the freezer whatever I'm supposed to put in here
the key nothing in this shit milk you piss jerk feed the grinder to get the
key I feed the grinder what like my own arm eat the grinder to get the key can
I put my own it can just put like a shoe in there the shortcut I see any meat
anywhere I don't see anything that guy on floor yeah I don't think I can move
them I can't move them go down here mate he has no head okay this looks like an
elaborate scheme sewing kit oh grind up the pigs hopefully there's not a timer
okay let's grind up some pigs grab a brick to throw bricks at the pig and
knock them down somebody said this is a Zelda minigame yeah it is a carnival how
many more out of how many people do all right this is getting a little full I
think there's one more you have to eat it I do it oh I got it enter the freezer
for my molotovs I don't feel safe without the ball tops dude I love this
event it's Saucon okay very very important question does Saucon have
more than 500 attendees I don't think so that answer is no I don't think so
probably not I don't think it would god oh god no this is the end of the movie
this is gonna be absolute hell this has to move forward this is before this is
back right back it up shit let's go forward this is to go get enough room
to move this I have to move this one forward pull back no pull it back you
idiot use of Molotov good idea all right I should be bad I should be fine for a
minute I can't even see anything this default Photoshop fucking hair a brush
thing is I can't see just do it again so I'm not even doing this right throw
them all tough please how the hell you supposed to do anything like this this
is like getting up in the morning when I was living in Massachusetts if you go to
your car and you clear your car with snow and just looks like this you turn
the car on you to sit in the fucking driver's seat and this is the view you
get no I guess I'll make sure to plan an extra 35 minutes before I can drive the
car this is ridiculous I mean what point do you just I die do I not die I could
just a little bit I could see out that this is gonna be really really annoying
this is gonna suck you know that traffic game those of you that don't didn't see
the last stream of this game months ago it's that traffic game where you have to
move move move move and then get the one car to the left all the way over it's
a cult gridlock yeah yeah yeah it's stupid all the rush hour yeah all right
I'm gonna we gotta go from the back let him monologue for a second it's okay so
this one's got to move to the right so if this has got to move up to move this
one up this one has to move up move that one up these two need to move all the
way over this needs to move all the way over so to do that this needs to move up
this we mean this is right I have to move that good this thing has to get the
hell out of the way this moves all the way over this reason why you can't just
push and hold dude you can't just push and hold come on hurry up I almost got
it go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go push it fucking hurry
I'm trying fucking hurry I'm hurrying come on come on that's it that's it go
go go go go go go go go okay get in oh to the heat why are you guys doing
question you guys are question marking me in the beginning that's the only way
I was gonna be able to move them all I gotta go he sounds drunk I guess he's
probably just been sitting there drinking whiskey what if he just like
falls asleep I can just walk through all the traps it's been in-game in-universe
it's been probably like seven hours in here this dude's probably blasted this
way Julie falls asleep I got one I gotta get number two number two is in the
staff housing room now where the hell is that the freezer my lighter back staff
room effectively you see a circle none of these are even marked yeah the dude is
sloshed
oh I got a gas trap does that sound I feel like the staff room was back here
all the way back here guys I thought that was like 30 minutes left of this
game there's like two and a half hours left actually I would blame the first
hour of this transitioning to here on on the stupid puzzle thing that I got stuck
on the seven and a half minute room seven minutes room like on the wrong way
look for the staff room oh don't kill me I feel the same way when I
laugh at the streamer all right staff room what does it say
cafeteria is that way security is that way I think we have to go all the way
back staff housing I was right I was right yeah check point yeah oh shit
before I had to kind of explode pretty good I'm utilizing the traps we're going
to touch it you know the sound that it makes when you take a picture with a
disposable flash camera that's what that is that's an industry secret want to let
you guys in on it that didn't do it that time but you don't know what it goes you
guys know the one to the left and the right down each path is the light what's
your name and the light no put your faith in the light it's a name how would
that matter they can't put your name in the light I can't see what jigsaw chest
it's open it a strap and ammonia I even open those fucking useless didn't know
anything about saw to saw to as much as of a train wreck as this game is
actually yes I'm hungry oh man what are we doing food today boys and girls what
we do for food Taco Bell now I don't like boys I need a fucking circuit box
and I'm swearing I just I told my mother wasn't gonna do that anymore
there we are hmm on this puzzle in the games
that wasn't too bad my big lane red lobster no I'd rather be able to hold in
whatever it goes down and not have it come up immediately about 30 minutes
later I say that my opinion so I feel that's my personal opinion on the
matter go to go to a restaurant and order bread for food just get bread just
eat bread for the fucking appetizer for the main course desserts eat the bread
eat cheddar biscuit bread I don't even order the lobster why would you just eat
the ethos oh those cheddar biscuits oh no it's not armed what kind of glass why
what those cheddar biscuits though right you shake don't tell anybody
sometimes go to red lobster and I order those cheddar biscuits all the cheddar
biscuits I get them and I like to I look yeah can we get two of these they put
more but they bring more of an I put like two in my pocket this so good I eat
them later on I get all you don't nobody does that stop pretending you do that
why do people have to pretend to like food just eat it who cares I know it's
good it's probably good just eat it you don't have to like pretend like it's
cool god what's so much different than everybody else we're quirky I can't say
that word people get really pissed off when I say that word hey what's a food
brag that you guys have that's what I'm referring to I'm trying to think if
there's a food brag where I'm like no dude it's the bet you got to eat these
are so good no just take two home like what would it be what's like a food
brag and subsession can lead to ruin cinnamon buns place I could see that
yeah all right I gotta pay attention you guys discuss it love to read that
fucking sign no men beyond this point okay no men allowed I guess so we're I
miss a spot this way oh here we go this TV is up here
anybody got a combination not 181 let's get those biscuits snapchat those
biscuits man no it's not that's the worst way to force it all right well I'm not
gonna force it then wasn't I already up here I already I was up here I remember
it you guys remember this right 301 it was on the wall really oh shit it is
right there 301 no it's not it though do I have a like Nintendo power glove on
what the hell is that was flashlights camera oh fuck just close his head in
the trap just grab it by both sides fucking impossible I can't even swing
at him takes three and a half seconds to swing stupid smash his head smash his
head trying to get a picture of it don't your mom is watching sorry she's she
she clicked on the mature audience morning no she did not but in there okay
there is third floor I I've really for some reason feel like I'm going the
complete wrong way on the wrong way right this is wrong this is wrong well
204 204 204 I know you're looking to come room 204 it's 204 nice I'm gonna
get ditch this camera the second I'm able to this thing this sucks back up
drain the battery 204 move on now huh does every game have to have a balance
you don't have to have every video game have a balancing board like why it's in
every game 204 we're in find a light bulb how's that hair ticking sound I'm
ready for a fight ain't thinner and we use it I've not been
utilizing those explosive traps or anything the entire time haven't used
once elevator okay how many light bulbs do I need three what pain in the ass no
men beyond this point this is illegal well what's in here that I'll take the
bat is it right wait now get this thing out of please give me anything else but
this ammonia how's the point of coming up here squeeze through the hole in the
wall too oh no no no no no no no no no holy shit I can feel the air on me okay
I can stop right oh shit okay oh okay I'm good I made it 204 stairs no I need
a new oh it's right hey is the audio delayed right pull it back because the
first game was how's that you should be hearing like a bump right how was it I
need to put it back hearing it before you're hearing it after good both though
no it's early well search the what ten seconds to do what who cares leave what
wait wait wait wait wait what button that's button fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck
wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
that point who's somebody got like caught up we're going live just one hey
hey where's it the rat fuck you okay we're okay
and nothing happened it was just a little dangerous that's all alright what
did what was in here this guy another camera go right delete it from the
game this is a long elaborate shitty thing to be doing right I just get the
key already or the light bulb whatever the hell you want me to do what I have
both light bulbs oh shit I have both light bulbs all right so now turn to the
theater control room with the two light bulbs nice if I remember okay theater
control room gonna get collapsed on by the vein the main enemy right it
collapsed on he's been drinking coffee doing cocaine all morning finally
cabinet wait I was just in the theater you thought that was in the game no you
did not I am mad I'm really glad you did actually all right come on light bulbs
I gotta go up in the you got buzzed in just got buzzed in Jed some light dead
some light I won't let you get away with it whatever it says insert the bulb here
we go one two five one nine five one oh that would take a long time to brute
force this one I five one how's that wrong all right other way German German
whoa whoa whoa whoa what's wrong oof oof oof five nine one five nine one not five
nine one what was it one five nine nine five one I just did six five one was it
upside down nine and fifteen oh five one nine one nine five pretending how could
you guys are getting it wrong too what are you talking about six one two six two
one oh look at it again what a pain in the ass okay so RGB er is RGB right okay
cool so it's red green blue okay that's nine oh seven red green blue does it
have to be a certain color or anything that's the only what red green blue all
right remember these numbers this is eight eight oh two colors from the TV
oh man it's the TV colors on the way in here uh-huh okay what were they she had
some light green blue red we got to be close to the end aren't we green blue
red ray eight three one eight three one somebody you guys had it right somebody
did somebody was spamming that the last one like one three eight all right let's
see the climax of the movie go to the stage and rescue Jeff here comes the
movies climax okay Jeff I'm here for you it's gonna get crushed if I don't hurry
up what why do you have this many TVs that's the symbols what oh it's just a
memory all right um film canister film all right nail hammer it's going back in
all right take it out take it out take it up tape cassette tape rug all right he
stole this one from door of the Explorer run out of ideas okay was it was tape
no rug rug pull it out well it's gone all right we're not hitting any any
organs or anything gun bullets this one which one was it over here coming out
hang in there Jeff hammer nails it hurts going out worse than going in puzzle
puzzle okay tape tape we almost got all of them out we're good this is it he's
gonna be fine saw that oh saw what it's good we got it
art dead he's free yeah sorry dude you gotta give me something harder than back
of a cereal box like Captain Crunch
bleeding to death yeah sure you just want to know his face well I didn't see
him this time either so don't worry Jeff I got this son of a bitch I have
evidence we can beat him
replace the evidence camera flash camera it's on the table back all right I got I
got them good here we go okay the entrance to the library more of this
bullshit Oh double peg fight an infinite game see I live Antarctic Las Vegas two
very very separate climates sometimes I have visions of being on a nice sunny
beach hold socks up for a while she probably trade places great actor oh
thanks man where's this person how do I get out of here
no one said that yes they did and you guys tell what my face looks like when
I'm doing this my teeth my face is scrunched up my teeth are out back it
okay I ruin your life is he telling people I did this I think the guy that
stuck the VR goggles deep into your eye sockets is the one that probably ruined
your life I didn't do that why did you do that
how did you do this he's locked back there you were fine I can hear him I'm
gonna hear him talking Iro that was just give me the fucking key give me the
fucking key keep looking okay I want to keep looking locate the entrance to the
library uh-huh guilty all right I gotta go sorry dude I couldn't what am I
supposed to let you out hang right actual murderer I did not murder that
guy he had a device on his head that I did not put on him and I don't know how
to open the door yeah sorry I murdered this guy in here that guy I killed that
guy I tied him up and put like Home Depot saw blades behind his head and
gave him a timer before it grinded his head into pulp I mean I'm sorry I did
that I must have done that you're almost there one is in the library we're at the
climax of the game you're gonna arrest yourself it's gonna be something stupid
you know it is already we're gonna find out how bad of a guy I am a really bad
guy right I did horrible things gonna be somebody that comes out and it's like
oh are you yeah I'm the bad guy like I'll be like a bad guy somehow like I
arrested saw back like this the whole thing is 16 and I pulled up a few
shingles and then threw the shingles off the roof they called the police you
came and got me and put me in a juvenile home this is payback for when you
arrested me detective you think jigsaw made that graffiti apparently he does
everything um why don't we what did somebody let's arrest jigsaw and make
him a game designer like dude hey how about you like stop this kind of
murdering shit and make us like a new Call of Duty an elaborate setup you have
here this is like designed very well locked locked locked locked everything's
blocked everything's blocked blocked blocked blocked a lot of shit in here
okay let's go now what I went across there and I'm right and then a left all
right you know what I mean me spoilers for saw doesn't the whole thing was saw
the reason why oh he does everything is because and they're like eight of them
it's like eight different saws there's like a saw team like the Wizard of Oz
you know this is the good the guy with his face is there but then like all the
munchkins do all the work saw con right okay so what the fuck was the point of
that just saw you down there all right can I jump down here offices live was
it gonna go to the library I can't even go over here though the shits blocked
off there another way I can go get back down to where that lady was oh shit I
just spoiled the whole movie whoops I spoiled saw I told you they're gonna do
okay look if you haven't seen saw one and two already are you really gonna sit
there and watch all seven of them no you probably don't even care this is
probably the only experience you have with saw you're like I this is all I
ever want I gotta go back down somebody quick link length of rat falling and
landing on his head where's the last fuck man I just need to go to the
library in the game ends yes let's activate that cutscene again nothing
even in here gives a shit fuck off fuck sake what they made a game about the
movie I really don't I don't know what the hell this is supposed to be but
sure wait a minute I go down here well now I know how the cat died huge cat by
the way that cat is almost as big as me that's a tiger in the library sure let's
go to the library that's three in a row real quick we got to get him out of the
way haunting me I know how close I am I tried to go I did it was a Super
Nintendo controller and I pressed X X is the top button in my brain a lot of
times Y is the left one B is you know what I mean a is on the right get this
cutscene to play out I'm not gonna die again
sound like a Snapple opening a Snapple in probably 20 years so make Snapple
apples gross I haven't had it in like almost 20 years I don't know if it's
gross no it might be could be all right let's get the cutscene to play and then
I'm done with this shit yeah you're down there making stuff uh-huh right sounds
good cool let's go down don't fall off the edge like a dumb idiot holding my
chest I swear to God it's it I was just being so careful I was being so fucking
careful why even have that in the game why can't I just walk
I care what's in that room just go over here and activate the cutscene and go
please just beat this game I'm trying me dude I'm trying to do this fast again
just gotta run as fast as you still hold for it okay cool keep looking this guy
all right I gotta get over there where's the way to go can't go that way can't
go this way either real close to the end Pepe left I know that I am I had I played
this game for like six and a half hours or like two and a half hours ago when I
changed the cracked wall cracked wall oh crack hole crack hole crack crack time
crack time crack time crack time where's your crack up top back up top back up
top right not up top or is it down here to crack in the room with the cutscene
oh they're really you kidding me oh right I forgot this game mechanic sorry
guys it's been three and a half months now what don't fall don't fall right
here good okay wait we're golden new tape final gauntlet what would you do
oh final boss incoming dude climb up the wall we have to do that to them I don't
know why that's supposed to shock me at this point we've seen some really awful
shit it's not a big deal in fact that's underwhelming what's your final thing
look I have electricity on the ground and we've been doing that for like the
12 hours dude not a big deal somebody's attacking me I didn't even know this is
the gauntlet am I in the final gauntlet right now I feel like I'm not but I feel
like I should be am I the final gauntlet he controlled that one he pressed the
button on that one no I want to open the door final gauntlet of soul it's
actually a final it's actually a boss oh it's not an instant kill oh my god oh
my god oh my god oh my god oh my god wait do it again how many shotgun shells
do I have it armed oh shit it's not armed oh shit he's fast walk it on him
lock it lock it oh squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze
squeeze squeeze doesn't squeeze through does he stay there all right hang tight
okay get some supplies rock on shell good tripwire I need that nail good
what's he got oh nice free shit elf here he's just standing there yeah that's
fine all right I guess I can do another tripwire
how am I gonna get by him definitely get this this is way better nail bad let's
go softlock no I'm not softlock look okay now how do I use these explosive
trap how do I anybody know how to use these what do I what button do I press
right bumper and then B so it kind of seems unfair but I could totally get a
fucking selfie this guy and people be like how did you get so close to the
pig man bang right there got you that's going on Instagram it's gonna get
fucking 500 million likes what did you it took you that long to duck holy shit
he almost go back and go back and go back and squeeze squeeze squeeze squeeze
squeeze he's way stronger that can be right in the back of the head all right
so RB and then be RB be to use is that what you're saying alright explosive
trap copy that's not right that's incorrect
RB be just keep going you go he's gonna get electrocuted he's gonna do the thing
the dog does when the dog doesn't know where you are and runs the other way and
you catch the dog by the way did Jake so just say he doesn't like that he hates
that he doesn't like being electrocuted what what is this mechanic I have no
idea what I even did oh open that shit okay Joseph it's so anti-climactic I
actually got it all right can we unmask him take the mask off and see who it is
ice oh guys I see a five-minute timer in there I don't want a five-minute timer
or a pipe dream mission please no please no have it be anything else I'll do
anything else but not just to connect the pipe pipe dream thing all right let's
go I'm stalling long enough he made these levels that's how you respond to
yeah you know I changed my mind he shouldn't be a game dev he's repeating
the same level over and over again repeating the same puzzle over and over
again too late that's fine I don't care and God was the wrong way here comes the
climax what happens in the end of saw you have killed my servant simply to
pursue me a living person just as you are does this make you a murderer
detective what will you let's find out I am waiting for you on the library your
final choice lies ahead my final choice there's a bra by this is before I gas
you I'm not even gonna give you the choice you just die detective oh I hope
I get to baseball bat this guy in the head and look it's gonna be see it
wasn't even saw it was somebody else tied up to the chair
Ruth freedom dare Ruth or freedom which door okay so I either can know the truth
and die or leave and just come out of like a subway station somewhere save the
game I can't this is we're gonna do truth you'll pull all right fine let's
see let's see what people think I'll see what people think I mean am I gonna use
this this confirms my own assumptions and yeah freedom is probably just gonna
be an ending cutscene where you walk out with like Sun going in your eyes and it's
really bright and you go oh shit there we go for the freedom I don't think the
pole doesn't even need doesn't even need to be open for any longer there's a
third door behind you that's just the door I walked this door I came in what
door is it this is a third door secret door and he he told me oh no it's gonna
be like oh great can't wait for the puzzles locate the key for the choice
doors we that's we were supposed to go through here hurry now what where how do
you want me to do right in ten minutes dude don't give me a gauntlet of stupid
fucking puzzles what well I don't care I just want to who's that guy oh dick
it's the maze okay this way and then I climb gauntlet there's nothing even down
here is there I've read is wasted like fucking full straight minute that's
fantastic can't go anywhere else what's the point what's the point of even going
down here no reason at all like there has to be
heal please heal heal in here you'll you'll you can't get away from you'll
why is it not healing X to heal I don't have any more heels I don't have any
heels stop oh shit I'm about to go in I need heal heal something I need oh god
damn it oh god damn it oh god damn it god damn it god damn it god damn it get
ready here comes one two he's gonna throw it I'm gonna get a knife fuck you
dumbass but it's okay holy shit don't throw it don't throw it don't throw
don't throw don't throw in the mall tops I need those okay now it is there's
something I can press something and do in here I'm gonna throw them all tops
this guy over here really and I don't have any left where's my weapon do I
have to kill everybody what's this final gauntlet bullshit who wants to do a
final gauntlet this place is so great I can't even tell where the hell I'm
going in hurry I'm going as fast as I can man just open I can just leave you
said I could just leave where's the door to get out of here oh it's right there
okay oh shit okay I know I know yeah yeah I didn't know I could just leave I
didn't know I could just leave you're right I can leave I can just leave all
right get the fuck out of here shit man this is making me want to throw up in my
hands and then wash my face with my fucking puke-covered hands oh god damn
it just kill me I've started I've got I went the wrong way I can't do that how
did you even got up here man okay I kind of feel bad for that guy that guy
actually was my friend I think he was that guy was helping me kind of right
I think he kind of was all right I just gonna go through the building and walk
out I just do hate this area hurry up open okay so I just have to go to the
right no I gotta go up but the best way to go up is to go can I go down and then
up yeah let's go I'm gonna help them all right we just doubled you go back to
ratatouille no all right we just leave I have to kill everyone what detective
okay wait where's the exit right there all right I can just leave oh my
fucking what this calf is on backwards stop stop stop leave me alone leave me
alone leave me alone leave me alone leave me alone leave me alone I got eight
minutes but I went back to you gave me ten he gave me ten minutes why did I
have ten minutes to do that is he giving me extra time we've heard the end of the
saw movie music a dozen times now when is the real ending of this fucking game
it's a time what what what the fuck what the fuck what the fuck what what
there's no panel to turn this off flash flash what okay you got a what do I go
oh my god right through the okay I see it now that I had to time it all right
everybody relax everybody relax a bit I gotta make this a little easier he's
having a lot of trouble she okay detective just checking it on you making
sure that you're okay feel all right I could get you a water if I if you want
a water or something I'm concerned about you man it's a really long time to do
this shit yeah I couldn't get like ten minutes to do the stupid insane puzzle
room why would it have taken me ten straight minutes to do that final choice
key return to the choice doors ten minutes again I was what was on this ten
minutes shit your valve in here come on give me about come on bullshit this day
turn the gas off oh who cares fuck the gas this is wrong this way I open this
there's the water yeah he's actually so fucking done with this game ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding we have a
winner what have they won one this one right here no no no no no no this whole
thing is wrong that gas up right gas is done I can actually see what I'm doing
anytime all right I got all I got seven and a half minutes to do this stupid
puzzle and it's a big one it's a big one be easy here it's a monster one
fuck hold on slow down I got plenty time outside in outside in I know I know I
know okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay what do I do with this it has to
connect to either this one or this one it has to connect to this has to oh shit
come on dude no no no why oh man I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it I
got I got it I got I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it done done we're
done timer still going why is this timer still going we didn't reset it on me
this time hurry hurry um I'm going they do it yes
okay I got it thank God it's time to choose and you guys chose truth this is
what has been decided I killed everybody really hope truth does not add a chapter
to the game read a more truth own truth voice has been made okay that's what the
the truth from looks like let's see what the freedom one looks like just to see I
can't okay I can't take it out it's added another chapter the game find the
truth it's god damn it you added a chapter no I just want to see the end
it's too late I just got a checkpoint it's too late time for the guilty
I wasn't even looking. Gigsaw on a little tricycle doesn't anybody wish that it kind of
was just like a little guy on the tricycle and not just a guy it isn't
no technically no Jason he's so slow get him he's so slow we can keep up he's so
slow guys don't worry sewing kit telephone books that was maybe a health
potion or something white shadowy figure I feel like I'm gonna hit him once and
he's gonna die this is him took his fucking shirt off and just went rage
mode just kind of a big fat guy with no clothes on this weapon sucks why is this
guy still the final battle this people still just down here that had to have
been jigsaw I hope I get a good weapon out of this it was big saw kill jigsaw
where is he he's holding the door
got it is that oh shit you should have paid attention dude you got killed by a
double trap I don't have any sympathy at all or her at all not at all the amount
of times that I have gotten killed by that shotgun trap kind of have to expect
it by now you don't open the final door not look we're doing pizza yeah could
have done freedom hey made our choice break the disc no now we can play saw
too in like four months it was all right I did say that I hated the game I said
that I think I said this is the worst game I've ever streamed that's kind of
harsh I think let's do freedom wait I can't would be 714 right right behind the
door yeah right and we're here this is it right now let's good this is good
freedom earlier than this kind of want to know what it is perfect okay time
first to find out what happens if you pick freedom just skip it all right we
go freedom what is this one but I'm still obsessed with it I can't get over
truth is I think truth is probably a better ending then okay okay I was
trying to skip the credits oh man I was trying to skip the credits I was trying
to skip the credits holy shit okay that was a little intense I was trying I was
trying I was hitting a to skip the credits and that was intentional it put
that in there that was saw and that's the end of the string I'll see you
tomorrow for mafia and do the mafia remake if I still haven't fun then we'll
go back to it a little bit later on this week that is tomorrow also I'm gonna be
streaming on Wednesday night I want to tell you now because it's gonna be very
very late at night playing a VR game that's right we're going back into VR
the our virtual reality is back as of Wednesday playing multiplayer VR with a
very special secret guest and then after that we'll be our games next week I
leaked it already accidentally and I didn't know I'm an idiot that's gonna be
about that was a perfect six-hour stream well right on time the guests gonna be
Otto Otto cannot be in a helmet like that can't put auto with that what are
you talking so we'll see you tomorrow for mafia and then I'll see you for VR on
Wednesday and then FTK is this weekend pretty packed up schedule I would say
this week I will give more details on everything you need to know about FTK
probably Wednesday night good time I think to do it tell you everything you
need to know this week has been chock full of shit but I will see you guys
later we're gonna do the credits we'll hang out for a few minutes a minute or
so there they go these are all the subs all the resubs all the gifted subs
community subs everything for the stream today thanks a lot guys this
stream has thousands and thousands of fucking subs I still sometimes cannot
believe that that many people would pay me money on a monthly basis some of you
for years straight I mean you have been giving money to the stream more than
you've ever given Netflix so I can't even understand how I do want to I missed a
few of these I do want to say thanks to pepper like pepper for five community
subs super Bruce for five subs breed dog for 10 community subs I missed earlier
based Bernie thanks for five subs thanks a lot guys and I will tell you I had a
little this dream I I you know I'm so like I can't believe I couldn't beat
that fucking level in ratatouille I don't know what I don't know why I have
no idea what was going on there I can't believe I didn't do it I am so glad that
I beat saw on this stream and I'm so glad I pulled myself out of the ratatouille
matrix when I did otherwise this would have been six hours of me failing at
that ratatouille level God I have to beat that I did I did in my mind like
three times this is my first stream well I hope you had a good time thanks for
stopping by maybe we'll see you again tomorrow or the next day or maybe some
other time new follower song no you've just sent a clip lots of X's I've
noticed hey you want to be you want to you know stand up from the crowd on
Twitch have your name start with a Z there's only like eight of you in this
chat right now thanks for subbing everybody see you tomorrow get some
sleep we can now actually play saw to whenever I feel like it hopefully it's
not gonna be the second worst game I've ever streamed tonight guys he's in the
same raid yeah let's do a raid tonight I was about to hit the button who's even
live right now
I'll see like nobody I'm following is even online this is pretty rare oh no
wait man this is how I had to refresh oh let's ray you know let's go uh let's go
let's go let's let I can't even say words let's raid Ludwig scream at him
he's playing among us so go see if he fucking loses let's go see if he's a
good imposter player already he's pretty good although I was talking about like
among us earlier about how I'm never gonna play it and you'll never see it on
this dream but let's go check it out I'll see you guys tomorrow have a nice
night goodbye take care good night see you later
I'll go say hello Ludwig's a good dude he's a swell lad I'll see you later
although I'm sorry we haven't gone yet well um where's this coming from where
what why do I have there's like a visit of video playing in the background
where hold on I need to find this yeah have I just been playing YouTube videos
back-to-back to back-to-back okay with Sonic one on the game here I swear to
God I think I think I don't know where this coming from I missed that and I'm
dead and I'm dead I think a video has been playing the entire stream