I am back. Decided to take the opportunity to make another tea. Refill the beverage a little bit
here. And now we're going to play Breath of the Wild. It looks like the switch... I don't think
the switch even turned off, if I'm completely honest. Let me see here. Yeah, I don't think the
switch even turned off. Is this the... this is the exact screen that I was on, right? Did I just go
to sleep or something? I don't know. That's weird. All right, bear with me for a second because I have
to do some audio changes here. I have to delay my voice and the camera. Give me one second. Like this.
Hello, hello, hello! Okay. Okay, that should do it. Now, should I delay? I gotta delay the switch
audio by a little bit, right? We'll do a test. It's not working. It's not ready yet. One second,
hold on. I gotta refresh the camera. Gotta plug in headphones. Are you losing viewers? That's all
right. No, that doesn't matter. That's fine. I don't care. I mean, people want to watch Breath
of the Wild. They want to watch Breath of the Wild. They don't watch any fart trombone game. They
don't want to watch this. That's up to them. That's fine. Hey, don't worry about the view count. It's
all right. I don't care. Why didn't they stay? Why did they fucking stay? They should have stayed.
Whatever. Okay. Headphones are in. I believe I am ready to play Breath of the Wild. Change the input
on my screen. All right, let's go. Let's do a test here really quickly. If I go like this,
one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, five. We good? Seems pretty good. All right.
I'm going to turn this up a little for you guys because it's a little low for me.
How do I do that? There we go. Okay. I'm ready. So what was the last thing I did?
Is it too loud? Is it just right? I had a bunch of shit marked. All right, we can do this thing.
Audio is good. Is it fine? Okay. Oh, the face cam has to move too, yo. That's right. How's
this in a good spot? Turn this down. I feel like this is bright as hell. Why is this so bright?
Too bright. How come you look like the Hulk? It's actually kind of a compliment. All right,
let's go. So I wanted to kill one of the guardians, wherever that is, but maybe I'll do the Zora thing.
Oh, that's right. I'm never around the horse. The horse is never available.
Zora quest is related. Okay. So let me fast travel over here then. Look at the motorcycle.
There's an instant horse TP item near the second stable. Maybe one day I'll get it. Chat, shut up.
Wait, I... Oh, oops. Chat, shut up. Don't tell them that. Well, sorry. I got that info now,
don't I? This is not Shadow of Mordor, which by the way, what a great game. I was about to just
jump off and I thought for some reason it was going to be like... No, that's not how it works.
Isn't... Monolith is making a Wonder Woman game, right? I can't wait for a new Monolith game.
That's going to be so good. Okay. So how do I get down from here without... Oh, wait, I have
the glider. It's been like a week. What am I talking about? You say who cares? I mean,
Monolith made the two Shadow of War and Shadow of Mordor. That'll be their first game since Shadow
of War. All right, let's move. What do I have for weapons equipped right now? Look at all this cool
shit I have. I don't know when to use it. Did you like Shadow of War? I streamed Shadow of War
for like three or four hours. I think I streamed it one day. I honestly don't think it was more
than four hours. That was just odd. That was very odd. I dropped it? How do I throw this?
What the fuck just happened? How do I throw... I... All right, I got to get back into this.
It's like all the buttons are different. Yeah, that's right. The throw button. Okay.
All the buttons are different. Oh, my God. There's so many of them. I can't just sit on
these forever. I have to use these now. I use the spear. Jesus. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
All right, that's two down. You idiot. I want a bow. Do I have any arrows? How do I not have any
arrows? I got the frame rate. All right, that's good. Only one more. I'm good. We got it. That's
a good bow. Are they protecting an unlocking chest or something? I don't see anything. I saw
one earlier. Oh, you cannot point blank me, right? It's broken. Fuck. This shit's broken.
I don't want to use these weapons. I need something else. Did they drop anything else?
Shock arrow. Yeah, well, that's better. What the fuck is going on?
This happened before. I don't know what it did. What does this do? Does this respawn every enemy?
It respawns to every single one. I just went through all this bullshit
and I have to do this again. Oh, come on. All right, I'm getting the hell out of here.
I'm just getting out. There was a chest here, but I don't even want it anymore.
I don't. I don't want this. All right, we're good. There's like a warthog or something there,
but I don't care. Head over here. He's learning the wrong way. What do you mean?
I'm trying to go here. Oh, this turned out to be actually the wrong way. You're right.
Don't fall off and die in the waterfall, please. Is there any way to? I can get up there. It's
raining, but it's okay. Let me try getting up there. I think there's enough places for me to stop.
Yeah, I should be fine. Move this microphone a little bit closer to my mouth.
I think I'm all right. Impatient. You dope. Wait, the Blood Moon is sort of a memory clear
for the Switch. It basically resets all enemies and areas that you've affected in gameplay,
so the Switch doesn't have to keep storing that info in RAM. Really? That's kind of wow. Okay.
I can't climb this because it just rains here permanently. There's got to be a place I can get
up here. Even just to jump up there and then stop. I'll try it. I'll try it once. This is
impossible. I was going to go the other way. I was going to go around the whole thing. All right.
Fine. I thought I could just be a skip Andy and just jump over that and climb it and jump over.
Okay. You missed. No, this is plus plus. We just want regular. Okay. This one's just regular.
No skipping. One of those little dudes. The frog got away too. Come on. Radish. Where does
this person even come from? Fuck. Okay. This is defense boost. I think I'm just going to eat this
or maybe this is just the steak. I'll be all right. Radish is a really, this is great. These are
awesome. You did a circle. I know, but I know, but I just trying to skip. I was trying to skip.
Okay. Just stay on the road. I was trying to skip. Don't eat those radishes. Don't eat them. Why not?
I'm a raw radish guy. I don't want cooked radishes. I want them raw. I want them rinsed.
Then I want to just cut the ends off and I want to put the whole, just crunch the whole thing.
Okay. Now I can skip like a moron. What's wrong with the raw radishes? Okay. A raw radish is
my favorite vegetable without a doubt. Anybody under here? No, they're good. They are. They're
amazing. You're a freak. I don't, I don't know. I think that raw radishes are the best. Call me
weirdo if you want. What about pickled radishes? Those are S tier. I think anything radishes are
S tier. A pretty bush. All right. What's in the way here? Is it going to fall? All right. So now
it's going to stay on the road. No, I don't want to watch the, I don't want to watch the hero
playthrough. We'll watch that later. What is this? What the fuck? This is boomerang. I just,
I'm standing. Get out of the water. Get out of the water, out of the water, out of the water,
out of the water, out of the water, stuff sliding down the mountain. Oh my God. What just fucking
hit me? I dropped something. What was it? I dropped a shield. I severely overestimated how
far I had to shoot that. These guys suck. All right. Hold on. I don't. Ooh, that's a good boomerang.
All right. Where's my bow? Well, I was going to say where's the ding? All right. Give me all this
shit back. All right. Do not stand in water. 24. Okay. That's actually really good. Don't throw
this. Okay. We're good. Floaty dusty thing over here. All right. Hold on. Ooh, nice. A shield. The
shield is great. This thing's got like 28 or something, right? Okay. I gotta go that way.
I'm imagining I probably have to cross the bridge, right? So no skip Andy here.
Tom Scott. This water is electrified. It will kill you if you stand within five feet of it.
Good callback from a few hours ago. All right. I'm across the bridge.
I'm physically incapable of backseating. Oh, look. Look below. Look down here.
They're everybody's favorite character. You're pretty far off. I was sure you'd be passing over
this bridge. So I've been waiting for you. You will be in Zora's domain before you know it.
In fact, I'm going to head that way to meet you there. Whoa, link. Beware warrior. A monster
approaches from behind you. Wait, would you we're doing this? Okay. Annihilated. I haven't seen a
shrine pop up. Like my favorite part of the whole game. Staying on the road. There isn't one here.
Oh, that's all right. I have to cook some food. All I have is food that doesn't heal me. It just
gives me 10 minutes of buzzing around. Oh, nice. This is a deer. I mean, I got Hyrule herb. This
healthy herb grows abundantly in the plains of Hyrule. Cook it. So where's the first guardian?
First guardian was up here, right? This kind of general area. I'll do that after. Do I have a
health potion or something? Drink the milk. Eat the raw meat. I think I was to eat one of these.
I mean, I cooked them for this very purpose. Mid-level resistance to electricity. All right,
I'm going to drink that and then I'm going to eat something that has. I mean, I cooked it for a
reason. I'm going to eat it. I cooked it for a reason. Oh, I'll take the lightning rod. That
sounds fucking awesome. Oh, all right. This is fun. Cool. I want to use. I got to keep going.
I got to utilize this. I got to take the look at this fucking road. You just use the direct path.
I don't like direct paths. I want to be able to climb a wall and jump over. I like to climb over
a wall, jump and fall and take 80% of my HP and skip five minutes of walking. I've been. I'm like
that in every game. You miss something? What did I miss? I don't see anything. Big shiny wall.
I looked at that the first one. I didn't think anything was significant with it.
I thought I could climb it. Did I look at it? Didn't I look at the other one?
Okay, I didn't want to click it again. I just whatever. All right. So a hundred years ago,
King Dorofan ascended to the throne. A stray guardian crossed Upland Zorana into our domain.
The guardian seemed unstoppable. It was then that our King Dorofan, without a thought for his own
safety, came out to face the guardian himself. With supernatural strength, he lifted the guardian
and hurled it into a ravine. The impact of the fall left the guardian pieces and was never to
trouble another Zora ever again. Citizens celebrated the king's valor from then on. Their trust and
respect for him grew beyond compare. You can still see the scar he earned that day in his forehead.
A token of his triumph. What are you reading? There's a lot of people here, right? There's a
lot of people here. I'll read the lore for the people that are here. Harry Potter? No.
You skipped all that boring shit. I'm gonna just tell you right now. Um, you be careful
saying boring and Zelda in the same sentence. I don't, I don't think I would do that. Headshot.
Headshot. Well, I mean, it's just not true. Okay. Cricket. I don't play Zelda games.
This is the first Zelda game I played in a two, almost two decades. I think this is really fun.
All right. What do I have for weapons? What do I need? Okay. I've got, what's this crap?
Yeah, drop this. There we go. That's better. All right. Can I do this? Yeah, I can. Shrine?
I thought you guys said there wasn't a shrine here. To be fair, text-based lore in most games is
boring. Put it in dialogue or something. Um, text-based lore is interesting for extra,
right? It's cool to be like, oh, you know, I could read this if I wanted to. I'll read it if I feel
like it. I never, I genuinely never read, um, text-based lore. I just kind of don't. It's not
that I don't appreciate it. It's just I, my brain just wants to move. I've been waiting for you,
Link. Welcome. Behold the pride of my people, Zora's Domain. Now I shall introduce you to the king.
Hurry this way. I tried to not have the cam come on before I like the hard
blink, but I caught it because the cam is delayed by like a thousand milliseconds. So I caught it
at the wrong time. So you saw it. The shrine's right in front of me. I don't care about anything
else but this. He loves his shrines. I really do. I like the shrines because they're these complete
just total episodes of content. Just go in, do the task. It's a small area and then leave.
I like it. Interesting. Pushing power. So what's the goal? I can walk up here? Okay.
What am I trying to do? Zora's Spear. How much damage does this thing do? Oh my god. Get rid of
this. All right. Push. Push stuff. The goal is to get the balls. I don't know. I'm going to check
this place out first. There it is. Okay. So I got to get that ball into Link. You can definitely
climb that. I think there is, Link, there is no way you can't get up there. How do I turn this on?
Oh, I have to get one of these. Okay. All right. All right. I get it. For some reason,
I thought I had to get that one in there and not any of these ones. No! Give me that. Give me that.
Give me that. Give me that. Give me that. Give me that fucking thing. What the fuck are you doing?
Why does this hurt? Defense. Does this have to come to a complete stop? It has to come to a
complete stop before I don't get hurt. I mean, this is going to work. It's going to go in there
and it's going to work. I could have just done this. Why did it explode? Why did it explode?
No, no, no. I know. But hold on. No, you fucking idiot. Get out of the way. There it is.
I'm just trying to whatever this I'm doing this the wrong way. But okay. I don't care if you
backseat, but confirm. I have to get one of those balls in there to drop the other ball. Or is it
just get the ball at the top that's orange in there? The ball that at the top and orange,
the only one that's supposed to go in there. Is that correct? Or do I have to get one in there
to make the ball drop? I don't know what you're saying. Yes, too. I got it. Okay. So you have to
get this out of her. This shit is stuck in now. Do not free chat. Keep them. Keep them locked in
here. Thank you. All right. Get the fuck out of there. I definitely have to block this with ice.
That's very clear. That's blocked. How do I move that? You know, what would have been a smart idea
was to just walk up here. I didn't even check to see if I could even go up here. I should just
walked up here. I looked up and I was like, Oh, yeah, I don't know about that. That's true. Yeah.
I think I have to do what am I doing? Just go with walk up and look. Okay. How do I actually
move this though? Dude with like an arrow? Move the fucking thing. What the fuck can I move this
for? Link, stop getting glued to every object that's around you. Okay. So I thought that was
just like a nice like spa entrance. I didn't know that I could whatever. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Oh shit. I'm fine. Oh, no, no, no. This way, this way, this way. Okay. That should be fine,
right? Oh, shut up. All right. So the issue here is I did it too hard, but I'm trying to just get
it to drop here instead. I have to move it over this. Okay. That's what I'm doing. That's the
plan. I'm making it go that way. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. If I want it to go that
way, how? I got to block this. Block this shit right now. Now it's not going to go. All right.
That's it. It's going to end up down here. But get the, get rid of this fucking thing. Get out of
here. You're going to mess up everything. Get out of here. All right. Let him out. This person's like,
that shrine took me three times as long as it should have. That was painful.
That took an ungodly amount of time. All right. What's the score IGN? You don't know what you're,
you don't know what you're talking about. All right. That was fun. You're a, you're a
Germaniac today. So this is, okay. So now we're here. So we're in the Zora domain. Very cool. Yeah.
Some puzzles are harder than others for people. Some, look, maybe I'm better at the combat stuff
than you. Maybe I'm better at some of the other puzzles than you. Maybe you're better than me at
some of the other puzzles. But you aren't though. That's you saying that. I literally did this a
week or two ago during the 14 hour stream. That's what I did at that 10 hour mark.
I did that. Remember? That's what I did. Oh, you don't have any fins. Are you Hylian?
I'm the president of Prince Sidon's fan club. My name is Tula. Do you know Prince Sidon?
Oh, I see. Ah, Prince Sidon. Just thinking of you turns me to mush. On the other hand,
if that pack of geezers shows up again, I swear. Oh, I'm sorry. Anyway, Prince Sidon is a man with
magnificent ideas. Oh, I know. Why don't you go and have a chat with Prince Sidon? Yes, do.
I just lapped you three times. Oh, stuff! Is this a pool? You're sleeping in the pool.
That's bad, isn't it? Oh wait, aren't they, they have gills. Okay, never mind. They're fish. Yeah,
I know. I just was, I don't know, I saw the Z's pretty up top singing. That first is freaking me
out. Ah, you must be the Hylian that Sidon brought here, correct? You did well to come all the way
here. I am King Dorofan, ruler of the Zora. Hmm, that object upon your waist. Is that not a Sheikah
slate? Hmm, now that I've gotten a good look at you, it's too clear who you are. You are the Hylian
champion, Link. They're not telling me you've forgotten me. The Hylian champion? You can't mean
the Link? That champion? So that's where I've heard your name before. What a fateful coincidence that
we should cross paths. I cannot believe it. The Hylian champion, Link, has appeared before us.
We have met numerous times, I'll have you know. Ah, so many memories. My mind is overflowing with
nostalgia, my friend. I had heard a terrible rumor that you had fallen in combat, but it appears you
managed to survive extraordinary. I've been sleeping. Oh, come again? Sleeping, you say. Hmm,
is that why you do not seem to remember me? Surely you must remember my precious daughter,
Mipha, yes? You do, do you not? Mipha who? I cannot believe it. You've truly forgotten my dear Mipha
as well. You and Mipha were close, yet you do not remember her. Young hero, please look upon the
beauty of Zora's domain. Do you see that statue? Was gazing upon Mipha's immortalized form still
to not jog your memory? Well, perhaps your memory will return in time. I dearly hope so. Father,
I do not believe discussing my sister is helping matters at the moment. Link sees confused. Oh,
yes, of course. But first, is it worth noting how remarkable is that to see you? I can't,
I can never say your name right. Sidon. That's quite a feat, my boy. That's a good one. Link,
I doubt not that you have endured a great many trials. Still, I must ask you to hear my plea.
Now then, hero, I must inform you that Zora's domain is in danger of vanishing because of
divine beast Fa-Ruto. I shall do you the courtesy of speaking bluntly. We are alone,
and we can't stop it alone. Will you lend us your strength? What? King Dorven, my liege,
please do not speak so. Ask a Hylian for help. Why, the very thought of it curls my fins.
Muzu, I expected more of you. How can you still protest? Muzu, it's rude to speak that way to
your king and his guest. Link is here because I invited him. With such unprecedented rainfall,
we have no choice but to rely on the aid of a trustworthy Hylian. Have we not already
discussed this and arrived at that very conclusion? He's the key to saving Zora's domain. I have no
doubt in my mind. Indeed, Link is a champion, through and through. As things now stand in Zora's
domain, nay, perhaps all of Hyrule is doomed to be swallowed by the sea. This is bigger than all of
us, my friend. Zora and Hylian's alike. We must put aside our differences and band together.
Have you forgotten already, my king? We cannot trust these lowly Hylians. A hundred years ago,
they abused the power of an ancient civilization and turned Hyrule into what it is today.
And that is not the least of it. It is their fault that Lady Mipha was lost to us.
Took a long time for him to figure that out. Oh, Link. Divine Beast of Avrunda has great power.
It has the unique ability to create an endless supply of water. Of late, it has been mercilessly
spouting water into the air. As a result, this area has been plagued by heavy rains.
Can I flip them? I'm gonna flip them. They think it makes more sense to me to flip these.
For us Zora, water and air are as water. So you would not think this would be quite so critical
of a problem. Sadly, the rains have filled the eastern reservoir nearly to the point of flooding.
If the reservoir bursts, as it soon will, I fear immense damage will befall not only Zora's domain,
but also the area downstream from us. There, Hylian lives are in very grave danger.
Divine... oops. What is this place? It's like Bill Clinton. Whoa, look at this thing.
Divine Beast of Avrunda, your Princess Zelda, often studied the Divine Beasts. That is in the
time before the Great Calamity. According to her research, the orbs located on Avrunda's shoulders
are mechanisms that can control the water it generates. However, they require electricity
to work. These orbs are clearly out of control now because there's no electricity cursing through
to stop them. Now second, it was quite shock resistant for Zora. Hit one with a shock arrow,
sure enough, it slowed the water down a bit. Unfortunately, as an aquatic race, we Zora are
terribly vulnerable to the power of electricity. Perhaps because we could not safely strike it
with enough electricity at once, the water soon returned to its full force. That is why I went in
search of a Hylian who could help us. Link, I'm certain you have already figured this out, but
we need you to use shock arrows to get those orbs working properly again. I will aid you in any way
that I can, of course. Please, Hero, I beg of you, help me stop Brutus' rampage of destruction.
What? Princess Zelda herself instructed you to board a Divine Beast and if he's from within?
So then Princess Zelda is still alive? Yes, in Hyrule Castle. I don't have a voice for Link.
I do not believe it. She was alive this whole time, just as you were. The events of a hundred
years ago cannot be altered if it is true, but if we can regain control of the Divine Beasts,
they may yet prove useful in sealing Calamity Ganon once and for all. I did not know they had
such grand ambitions, Link. Wondrous. Naturally, I shall help too. Once it has stopped rampaging,
you can easily climb inside it. Come, Link, let us appease Ruta together. Thank you, Link.
Truly, we are in your debt. Our goal is the same. That means our meeting was nothing short of
destiny. Now then, allow me to offer you this gift of a sure fate. Zora Arbor! Custom arbor,
painstakingly crafted by each generation Zora Princess for her future husband. Wearing it will
give you the ability to swim up waterfalls. As long as you wear this, you can swim up waterfalls.
Just like I said, please take care of it. King Dorfen! Surely you do not really
intend to give this outsider a Zora armor. Countless generations of Zora Princesses have
gifted that armor to the one they have sworn to marry. Princess Mipha made that one there with
her own hands. It is far too important to entrust to a shady Hylian. He may be champion, but Mipha
had no such relationship with him, so why should he receive such an honor? This is just too much,
my liege. I do not understand it one bit. That ruseur is not easily swayed when his mind is set.
You must understand he was in charge of educating my dear daughter Mipha. Naturally,
she means a lot to him. Just as she means a lot to me and the world, too. Ever since we lost her to
the Calamity, he has grown despising. He grew up and he despised Hylians. I hope we can forgive
his rudeness. But what shall we do now? I tasked Muzu with finding the shock arrows we need to
appease Varuta. Now he has rushed off in a huff. Link, do not let his words concern you. I will
work this out with Muzu. I shall return shortly. Oh, here we go. Okay. I'm gonna head downstairs
real quick. There we are. These are steep stairs. Sidon, I suppose that means you are going to tell
him. Link Muzu is most likely at the square down below. Do you mind going down there? I would
like you to try to speak with him. Somebody said down there was like a SpongeBob episode?
What? Awful joke. Oh, hold on. You came all the way here, but it was in vain. I have no desire
to speak with you. Listen well, Muzu. There's something you need to know. He who stands here,
the man called Link, is the one who my sister Mipha had feelings for. I was only a child,
so I did not know it myself at the time, but it is so. I grew up hearing my father tell stories,
some of which were about my sister's undying love for a Hylian named Link.
What? No! You cannot fool me with such a fanciful lie, not Miss Sora. How could Lady Mipha possibly
have feelings for a Hylian like him? The facts are clear. He remembers nothing. Even when he looks
upon Princess Mipha's statue. It's the truth, Muzu, though you never knew it. He was ever in Mipha's
heart. I was thinking. This reminds me of the time. Well, I can't do it, but I'll show up.
You were just a reckless child, always getting yourself hurt at every turn. Every time,
I would heal you, just as I'm doing right now. Funny how, being a Hylian, you looked grown up
so much faster than I did. I was always willing to heal your wounds, even back then. So if this
Calamity Ganon does in fact return, what can we really do? We just don't seem to know much
about what we'll be up against. But know this, that no matter how difficult this battle night gets,
if you, if anyone ever tries to do you harm, then I will heal you. No matter when,
or how bad the wound, I hope you know that I will always protect you.
Once this whole thing is over, maybe things can go back to how they used to be when we were young.
You know, perhaps we could spend some time together. All I'm saying is, I mean,
you give me a full suit of armor, a dagger, and three grenades, and I would do it. I'd be fine.
And like five bologna and cheese sandwiches, and I would, I would save the day here. I would do it
in three days. Okay.
Sorry, that was a long cutscene. I just need to run around the circle for a second. All right,
so I need to bring you proof that I know who this is. Step in fool lucky for us, we have proof.
Link, go ahead and show Muzu the Zora armor my father gave you. Wasn't he in the room?
Wait, wasn't this guy in the room when I got the armor? I want you to prove to me that you have,
that you knew who we are. Link, here's the armor. How would you get that? Oh, I like you. Wait,
I don't get it. I have to put it on? You were in the room when you want, when he gave it to me.
Oh, it has to activate. I get it. Okay. You really think changing your clothes is going to make me?
That's the Zora armor from before. It even made that by hand and it fits you perfectly.
What's the meaning of this? Now you understand, do you not? Now you know who her heart belonged
to and who she made this special armor for. Oh my goodness. How could it be another men's small?
No way. It's impossible. I don't know how. Now the fact that this armor fits Link perfectly should
be made proof that Mipha made it for him and him alone. You've always disliked Hylians even
before the Great Calamity. That is why Mipha never told you. Now that you know, you must promise to
help him save us all. Please, tell us where we can find the shock arrows we need. Knowing you,
I bet you have already figured it out. Never would have imagined she would make that special
armor for someone such as her. I do not approve of asking for help from a Hylian,
but I suppose it is our only option at this point. I am a proud Zora. That means I must take
responsibility for my unwarranted behavior towards you. As promised, I shall tell you
where you can collect as many shock arrows as you will ever need. That tall mountain over yonder,
it's called Floymus Mountain, and there you will find Shatterback Point. A terrifying creature has
made its home up there. This awful beast shoots volley after volley of shock arrows. Even a single
one could be fatal to a Zora. Aha! You must mean that...Lino. He is a man-beast, that one.
That beast does indeed wield shock arrows. Certainly one way to collect them. He's vicious,
to be sure, but I am certain Link will rise to the challenge. In order to reprove the divine beast,
I estimate that you will need at least 20 shock arrows. Do you think you can gather that many
shock arrows? Why do you still doubt him? I know Delta would be triumphant. Okay, Link, let's go.
Fastest way to Plyymus Mountain is to ascend the waterfall east of the domain,
and Zora armor should come in handy. Just swim up the waterfall, and then go up to the waterfall.
I'll wait at East Reservoir Lake, right by the divine beast. Gather at least 20 shock arrows,
then come join me. Okay, wonderful. Together we shall stop that divine beast's onslaught.
Just made the most scrumptious cake. All right, let's do it. You guys remember like three years
ago when I would do the Neelix impression every two streams? I was on that for a long time. I did
it every two or three streams. I said it like five times a stream. I was obsessed with it.
Good morning. Welcome to Marot Mart. This is where you'll find our general store. Okay, cool.
Cool. Let's look at the store. Wait, this is not the store? This is the store. What do you got?
Violet? Salt? Oh, I think I need some salt. I'll take them all. 48 rupees. Excuse me? 48 rupees?
I don't have to pay for that, right? Hey, you're a Hylian, aren't you? It's rare to see your kind
around here. As for me, I was roaming nearby during my travels when Prince
Sidon recruited me and brought me here. That's because I can touch shock arrows,
but I also weigh you well a lot, so there's no way I'll be able to carry you on my back.
That's what Prince Sidon said to me. That's kind of rude of him, doesn't it?
Voice acting! How about this one? If I'm going to do some voice acting, why not? Let's do
how about this one? I told her the Hylian who stole Lady B for a way things. She can just come
wandering in here like nothing happened. What business do you have after all these years?
Oh, it's the weapons workshop. Oh, cool. Okay. What are you doing? Well, I tried maintenance,
you know. Oh, nice. Okay. Well, good night. See you. What other voices can I do? Oh, how about
you? I got to do the voice acting. I don't know. Pardon me. Could you please get out of the way?
Oh, good morning. Who are you? I'm a Hylian. Oh, sorry. If you're a Hylian,
did you come from far away? I asked because. Oh, never mind. My dad told me not to talk to strangers.
I can do one thing. I can literally do one thing. Oh, it's you. Oh, wait. There's a quest here. Hold
on. Okay. You need materials. What kind? Luminous stone. I think I already have these, don't I?
If you have 10 of them, that would be a big help. I think I already have that.
Here are the stones. Thank you. All right. Is this like, should I not do this?
And a one and a two and a three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. What a bunch of
bullshit. Okay. All right. So I need to, this is where we go. Collect arrows. What's the fastest
way to get up here? I imagine from where I am, right? I want to cook some food though.
I'm not just going there. I need to cook some food. Where's the chef? What do you have to say?
What was it again? I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Go to the waterfall.
I should get some more arrows. I'll buy some of these. These are useful. The fish too. Yeah.
Take the whole thing. XD. Oh my God. You're such a kidder. I know. I think I'm going to buy all the
regular arrows. How much is it for everything? Yeah. I'll take them all. Swim up the waterfall.
Yeah. I want to cook food first though. Make some cold elixir things or something.
How do you cook food here? In? Top left. Top right. Right. West. Hello. You are Link, right?
What do you ask? Prince Sidon ran off through the eastern gate. He was shouting something like,
I'm off to stop the divine beast. Link the Hylian is coming with me.
I assume that means you're going up Ploymus Mountain in search of shock arrows. Yes.
I have a request. What is it? There's a red maned monster called a Lionel that lives on Ploymus
Mountain. I really need a picture of a Lionel. Any of any red maned Lionel. Not just the one on
the mountain. What do you say? Can you give me a picture? Sure. Okay. There's this fool in the
domain who goads people into jumping off Shatterback Point on Ploymus Mountain.
It's an incredibly dangerous jump and this guy pressures people into jumping off by questioning
their courage. He's a real bottom feeder. If this keeps up, someone is surely going to wind up
horribly injured. I need a picture of a Lionel to show everyone how scary they are. Maybe people
will stop going up there. Does that answer your question? I'll leave the details to you. Just
bring me a picture. I mean, I don't want to keep my own horn or anything, but how about I leave
the camera with you? I go on the top of the mountain and I'm going to dive off that mountain.
You get a picture of me halfway down. I'll do a flip. Go to the inn. What happened? No! Please climb
it. Nobody saw that. How do I? I'm just teleporting back up here. What the fuck, dude? Title update?
Oh shit, the title is the same. I want to cook. Read the clothing. Swim up waterfalls. Okay. Yeah,
I know. Yeah, I know. I just want to cook. So somebody said go to the inn. All right. Is there
a chef pot here? There's a chef pot right there. All right. Nice. Here we go. I got a lot of shit
to make. So long lasting flame for using your firewood. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Elixir
ingredient. I make elixirs. Okay. Cook dishes that will allow you to endure the cold. So let
me hold this with these. Um, cook it with monster part. Oh, let me do that. Um, stop holding.
Monster parts. This is a monster part, right? So if I do, how many of these should I put in together?
So this is technically a monster part. So what is the, what's, what's the ratio I should do?
So, okay. How many bat wings, how many monster parts do I need to have? Why'd you just make me
press Y? Now I don't know where the fuck I just was. What the heck. Okay. So should I just do one
in one? What would happen if I did two bat wings and one lizard? What's the difference? What happens?
Always do 50-50. One-to-one is fine. There were two huge raids that just, that came in. Granny came
in with a thousand people and then lots of monster parts. Okay. And then Ramola. That was, that's
how, those are monster raids. Welcome everybody. Ramola? Am I saying that right? What's up? Thanks
to the raids guys. Everybody. Welcome. Welcome guys. Raid song. There you go. No, we need to
kill that meme. No more of that. I don't want you guys doing that. I don't want you guys singing
that. We're killing that meme today. But no, thanks. Thanks for the raids. Hope you had a good stream,
whatever you're doing. We're playing Breath of the Wild and I'm trying to figure out how to cook food
because I don't get it. I mean, I do get it, but I don't. All right. I'm going to do two bat wings
and two lizards. That makes sense to me. Okay. Two bat wings and two lizards. What does it do?
420. Boost your movement speed while running. Wasn't it cold? Okay. Now let me cook some other
shit too. When cooked into a dish, temporarily increases your maximum hearts. All right. Let's
put that in here. So I only do one effect. Some salt and that's it. All right. Nice. That's awesome.
Okay. I need to make some more. What's this? Electrical resistance. A fucking apple, two
mushrooms and a third mushroom. Four minutes of electricity resistance. Okay. Now what? Cook one
radish and see what happens. Jesus. What? Why would you ever make another food? Would you ever
make another food for any reason? Radish it out. Yeah. Okay. What about meat? Double meat and I have
too much stealth bullshit. Meat, herbs. Oh, and electricity mushroom and banana. Two mushrooms.
No, some salt. Whatever. Electro mushroom skewer. All right. This one's cold. Three of these. Okay.
Mushrooms. This is going to be cool. So things that increase cold resistance. This is a guava.
I need more cold resistance. Heat resistance. Oh, okay. This is going to be fished. This is going
to be crazy. It's going to be like 40 minutes. 10 minutes. That's a big one. All right. Hold on.
Just truffles individually here too. Yeah. That's pretty good. Cook one pepper. Too many. Don't eat
these because it's not going to, you don't have that many hearts. Make an electro mushroom risotto.
What does milk do? Okay. Let's do, I didn't want to eat that. I wanted to pull. I don't know why I did
that. Eating raw wheat, whatever this is, rice. Okay. So then I need, what else do I got? Attack
power. Double banana. This is going to be gross. Ooh. Four minutes of attack power. Increases defense.
Oh, check this out. This is defense, right? What about a crab? This is going to be,
this is a high level defense boost of four minutes. Two and a half minutes of low level. That's all
right. Movement speed. All right. What if I do three of these? A little dash of salt. Not very
much. Not very much. Kind of running out of food to mix here. Purple mushroom. Oh my goodness. All
right. Yeah. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Back up. Stop holding. Let's do this again
because let's do two of these and three of these. Okay. Cook it with monster parts to draw out its
speed boost effect. I don't think that works. All right. Let's try this. Honey mushroom. All
right. This is five minutes of high level movement speed. It does it just in elixirs, not in food.
Okay. Okay. Rice, milk, salt, bitter cold. Why don't we just make, why don't we do all five? Wait,
what's the, isn't there a crab or something that has cold resistance? Stamina. Attack power.
Silently. Fish here. And salt. Let's go. I mean, I have so much food. It doesn't go bad, right?
11 minutes of mid-level cold. All right. Uh, VR Josh has a good point. I should make stuff that
heals for like four or five so I don't just have a bunch of omega food. That's good. What about
just cooking one fish? This is a waste. Kind of a waste. What about this? Five snails. Whatever
this is. 10 minutes of low level stealth boost. I'm, I can, let's make some elixirs. All right.
Frog. Uh, monster parts. Tail and horn. Let's try it. That was a good one, I guess.
Oh, it says healing on it too. Okay. Stamina recovery elixir. That was a good one too,
apparently. All right. I think I'm good. Heat resistance. Attack power. Stamina. Stealth.
Defense. Stealth. Okay. Defense. Defense. Stamina. That's good, right? What else was defense?
Something else was here, right? Salt. Salt. And the crab. The one that, it'll, uh, it'll negate
the other thing, right? Make it extra salty? Okay. I'm gonna hold off the rest. I have a lot of food.
Look at all this food. That fits so much. Yeah, look at all this. How about a tree nut, two milks,
a rice, and a mushroom. Here's your mushroom risotto. I think I got enough food and I have,
I have plenty of really good items. I'm kind of decked out right now. I got plenty of food.
So now go swim up the waterfall. How far away is this waterfall?
Where's this waterfall that it's talking about? Save the game. Good call. East. Is that it right
there? Yeah, that's it right there. Oh, God damn it. Can we please get a Zoinks? Fine.
Like, Zoinks, Scoob. I fucking banned that person. I actually banned that person for like an hour
because they just made me do that and I fucking hated it. I want that person banned for an hour.
That's what I'm saying. That was like not good. It was like kind of annoying and it looked bad
and like I did it wrong. I want that person timed over an hour. I genuinely want that person banned.
It was good. No time that okay, maybe not an hour, but at least five minutes.
Hold on. So I need to get up there and walk across this bridge. One thing you can say about
Germa is he moisturizes. You get over 35 and you tell me if it's time to start moisturizing.
But I had this equipped. Actually, I need those arrows. That's good. I started moisturizing
because of you. You know, there is one thing that I will say. If there's a few things that
people will take from this stream, don't forget about anything else, right? Drink more water.
Don't drink too much water though. It's like you don't have to be sitting there chugging it.
Moisturize when you get out of the shower. Just a light moisturizer for your face. Just put it on.
It takes two seconds. It takes two seconds. When you get out of the shower, dry your face,
get a nice face moisturizer. It takes just a little bit and just smear it on. That's it.
You're done. Okay, so I can swim up this. Whoa, that's interesting. Cool. Damn, 37. How do you
deal with getting older? Honestly, you just do. You just, everyone gets older. That's it.
There is no, oh, I have to like, you know, you just, everyone's going to get older.
Eventually you get old, but as long as you just keep a good mindset,
moisturize, drink some water, eat, eat okay. I don't eat the best, right?
I know that food pyramid thing I did the other, like a year ago was a meme, but you know,
you know, just take care of yourself. Take care of yourself enough because honestly,
like taking care of yourself so much to the point where it almost becomes like a job on its own too.
Right? Like paying attention to how healthy you are, what you're eating. No, I can't eat that.
I don't want to eat that. It's bad for me. It can be kind of hard, but just take care of yourself
as, as well as you can. But enjoy life too. Enjoy shit. You want to eat a triple cheeseburger one
day? Do it. Don't do it every day. Just do it whenever you feel like it. Turning 30 in a week,
you have any wise words? No, you'll be fine. You'll be fine. Just once you get over 30,
you're going to, you kind of, you, I don't know, you kind of unplug from the matrix and you're just
like, Oh, whatever. Wait, that's a bad reference. That means that that's okay. Hold on. Let me redo
that. Who is this? That's good, right? They're going to find this on my dead body. Oh my goodness.
You almost killed me in one fucking hit defense. I'm going to do defense. Where's my defense food?
Health. This is, which one is he's a defense? This one here, right?
All right. Two and a half minutes of mid-level defense boost. Let's go. I got it. It can't do
anything. I feel like that didn't even negate any damage. I got the picture, right? That one is
actually better. Can I at least get one hit? Let me try to get one swing on this guy. Don't fight.
Why not? So is it a horizontal or vertical swing? Okay. Okay. I can fight this. I can kill this for
sure. This is a dodge better. I have to dodge better. It's two horizontal swings. That's it.
He's standing in water. Are you kidding me? Shut up. What was that? What are you doing?
I'm going to break every weapon on this guy. This is actually bad, isn't it? These are all my cool
weapons. What if every single one of them breaks? Whatever. Let's go. No, thanks. I'm all right. I'm
okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I don't want to eat the high-level one. I think I just want to heal.
Just heal. That's it. Everything is so good. I'm going to eat this. Let's go. Got him. It's
larger and heavier than a horse's hoof. It's useful for making elixirs. Wait. Look what I did,
right? I have to prove that I did this. Otherwise, I don't think that she'll believe me. Wait. Yeah.
I don't know. It's going to be a selfie. Otherwise, how can I prove? Wait. Well,
you didn't even kill it. Yes, I did. Lionel's sword. 24. Oh, man. I'm going to hide. Oh, shit.
What is 10 times three? Three arrows? This thing's almost broken. Just get rid of it.
I can't throw this away. Whatever. Oh, it's a bow. I'm an idiot. And then Lionel's shield.
I can really only... Okay. Wait a minute. Which one of these is better? Am I just wasting the
get rid of one of the guardian shields? That feels terrible. It's only the number that matters. Okay.
Just jest the number that it's only the ma... It's only the number that matters.
Oh, look at how cool this is though. All right. I'll get rid of it.
What is it? Keep the phrenic bow. What should I get rid of instead? The Lysal bow? Soldier's bow?
Phrenic is good. Phrenic is good for long range. Okay. Should I get rid of the
soldier's bow? Soldier's bow sucks. Okay. Well, that was cool. I killed it and I got the
sword and shit. Let's see what it looks like. 24. Very cool. All right. Let's go.
Here are the shock arrows. I need 20 of these. Shock arrow. Oh, what am I doing? Okay. Take a
picture of it and then set the beep beep for it. That's what I should be doing. Go. Okay. I didn't
do this at all in my playthrough. I am going to tell you I probably won't do it that much in mine
either because I will forget it exists. Okay. How many do I have now? Oh shit. There's a million
up here. What's this? Oh, this is the jump point. Wait, that's the guardian right there.
That's the guardian right there. I'm not ready. I need 20. I have 18. I need 20, right? Where are
they? Oh, they're up. They're not just in the base of the trees. All right. There's 20 right here.
All right. I have 20 arrows. It wasn't 25, right? Save, save, save, save, save, save, save. 20,
but the more the better. Well, I might as well be prepared, right? Take it, man. Take it.
Take it. I think I got them all. I believe that. Oh, no. Is it once in this tree higher? Oh, sorry.
All right. I think that's good. I'm ready. I'm going to go fight the first divine beast of the
game. The divine, um, elephant, I think. Let's go jump at your own risk. Um, what was that? What's
your problem into the, um, steam or something? I'm not losing those two hearts. Not happening.
Okay. Well, the quest marker is over here. So I'm imagining maybe I have to go to like the dock or
something. Is there a dock over here? Oh, okay. Sidon is right here. There we go. All right. So I
have my shock arrows equipped. I have, I want my strong bow and Knight's bow equipped. I'm ready
to do this. Let's go. Glad to see you ready to go, Link. Are you ready for this? Do you have your
Zora armor and enough shock arrows? Let us go and appease that divine beast. Here we go.
Gaze now upon the divine beast's back. Shoot the glowing pink orbs with a shock arrow. Okay.
I shall take you right up to the side of the divine beast. And from there, you can swim and
take aim. I know you can do it. I believe in you. Hurry up and get on my back. Good answer. Here we
go. Full speed. It's up to you. Ward off the attacks. Are you ready? Divine beast Varuna will
undoubtedly use its ancient laser and that includes hurling giant ice blocks.
Let's go. He talks. How am I going to watch that ice? How do I, how do I stop the ice?
Sidon, I haven't blocked one. Hey, how do I stop the ice? Okay. I made him hit his head.
Oh, fuck. I think I'm missing something here. Oh, I can shatter it. I can shatter them.
Shatter it. Oh my God. I'm restarting. Yeah. Get up there. Oh, help. Help. Help.
You let me drown, dude. What the hell? Okay. All right. That's it. Sidon, where are you?
Stop swimming around and stop doing this.
Bro, there ain't nothing here. Oh, I got it. Get this fucking blue shell out of here.
Ready. Got them all. Now it's time. What an absolute thrill. Oh, that was the rain. Okay.
That's cool. Floating higher. You wanted to venture inside of it, right? I'll bring you close.
Counting on you. Do good work in there. I have to go inside. This is not just a boss.
Here we are. Looks like this is where the real work starts.
Best of luck. Nice job cutting off the water flow from this divine beast.
Show the enemy no fear. I'll see you back at Zora's domain. Farewell. This thing's pissed.
Do I have my five bologna sandwiches? Three grenades and a dagger. Oh, and I got an iPod.
Just give me an iPod with like the entire Bill Burr podcast on it.
Arrow's every episode. I'll be good.
All right. So this is just a big shrine. Okay. If you hit the eye, the eye closes.
Interesting. Cool. Okay. Okay. So an eye right here. Shock arrow.
I can't electrify the water. I'm standing in, right? This is the first real dungeon. Good luck.
So would you say that these dungeons are more traditional Zelda? Divine beast controls have
been enabled. Yes. Okay. No. A lot more yeses than nos. Good. You've obtained the map of the
divine beast. You will see several glowing points on your map, which represent the terminals that
control Ruta. Take Ruta back by activating all of the terminals. Be careful. Okay. Whoa.
That's very interesting. Okay. So where am I? All right. There's a thing down here. I can manipulate
move trunk. Wait, wait, what? Okay. What's in here? Okay. Use my Sheikah tablet. Remember,
this is the first playthrough. Yeah, it is. Okay. So this is where the main control unit is. So I
gotta remember that where his butt is, right? This is where the main control valve is. Please
remember that because I won't. All right. So I am here. I'm going to bang a right.
I need to go this way. Oh, wait, what's this? Oh, this can, this, this can be manipulated. Oh,
this can be manipulated. It's going to fall, isn't it? Thank you. You fucking idiot. Okay.
This one. So now I gotta go. It's like I gotta go up a level this way. So they were preparing
me for this fight. Oh, these things probably drop like crazy now. Right. All right. Cool.
I love the way these look. I'm buying one of these off Etsy. You bet your ass I am. Okay.
So now I got this thing here. Well, the room, they're going to make this thing turn. What
if I stopped this? Can I? It's on Etsy right now. It's on it. Nobody buy that. There's only one of
them left. Don't buy that one. That thing looks awesome. Only one left. No one buy that. What
about out here? Maybe I can't do anything with it yet. Do I have to get inside? Oh, I know what to
do. Now you're thinking of a gas. I don't know why I went like this. Now you're working with gas.
Why did I like tilt my head this way? Hmm. How do I move this though? Well, I'm going to get this
hundred rupees. All right. I'll take it. I try to stop the flow of water. What can I even manipulate
here? I can manipulate this shit. Wait a minute. Can I just get in here? I don't think I can just
get in there. Shit. I know I said, give me three grenades. What would I do? What would I use them
for? I would go through all five sandwiches and just be starving in here and be like, I should
have asked for more sandwiches. Why don't I bring the grenades? I would be desperately asking for
one or two more sandwiches. What was the point of the grenades? I don't even know why. I don't
even need to dagger. Okay. I think I can do this. All right. So now, um, is this stupid what I'm
doing? Oh, look at that. Where am I? Put that down. I need to stop this from moving. Can I? Oh,
look at that. All right. Cool. I didn't know you could do that. Uh, okay. That's the way it goes
all the way. I have to stop it when it gets to be right here. Like right now. Is that good enough?
Is it draining the water? It is. Okay. Well, I didn't think it was going to drain the water.
It's draining the water. I didn't. Okay. I didn't think it was going to drain the water.
We had a frame drop. Whoa, we did. Holy shit. Why? That was weird. But that was a bad one. There we
go. I'm going to try. Okay. Now that being said, what do I do with this? I mean, what is this shit
all over there? This is, um, junk right here. What are you trying to communicate? Octopus arm? What
are you communicating here? Maybe I should just keep going. What are you communicating? An octopus
arm. Octopus arm slug. L omega lull octopus arm face. Octopus arm fish. Wait a minute.
Is that what you mean when you go in like this? That's not what you meant? Oh, it is? But how come
it didn't work? Oh shit. I did it. I didn't do it. Okay. I get it now though. I understand.
Ancient. Oh, ancient core. I'm all right. Shit's upside down.
Can I make it go faster? How do I make it go the other way? Can I, can it turn the other way?
Go the other way. How do I make it go the other way? Why is everybody going like this? All right.
This is open. I'll be able to see it. Wait, wait, stop, stop, stop. I'm not ready. I want to just
shoot water down this way. Hold on. Um, wait, shoot. How do I make it go further? Can I make,
can I, how do I do this? I think maybe I can block it with the ice. What is this? What does
that mean? What's this? Oh, I get it. I get it. Nice. Okay. Now I see what that is. That was pretty
cool. How do I get up? I guess now I can ride it that way. Ooh. Twinkie. We're good. Right. Okay.
Another shortcut shortcut back down. Cool. Very nice. Well, I got to check over here.
Um, well, okay. Is that a secret or anything? Chest or something? I could have thought there
would be a chest or something. Oh well. I got the shortcut. I'm fine. Here we go. Nice halberd.
Very good. I'll equip that right now. No, let's use the regular guardian spear. All right. All
right. So that's gone. What does that really do for me though? I think I need to keep it moving.
Can I just climb this? Never be that easy with it. Maybe. Hold on. Somebody made a gift of you
farting out the front door. No, it's not. All right. This is just, I can see this in my peripheral.
I just got to go. Can I swim up that first try? No, you can't see the fire. Okay. This fire. I
got to probably put the fire out, but how do I do that? Hold on. What if I go put it all the way
down? Because now can I stand on that? Excuse me. What the fuck are you doing here? Okay. 10 fire
arrows. Nice. Shit. No, wrong way. What the fuck is this? Wait, where am I? Oh, okay. It was right
underneath. Okay. I screwed up. Whoa. Okay. Very cool. Ancient shaft. I think I got it. Where is
this fucking thing? Whoa. What is that? All right. Where, where's, how do I get up here?
But how do I? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know what yeah means. Can I make it from here?
I made it. I made it. I'm on top. I'm on top. All right. Now what? Now what?
Fine. Let's go. I got it. There it is. Oh yeah. Hey, remember the person that said C in five hours?
It was actually one hour. Sorry. So this last one is in his head. The real question is,
how do I get in there? It's right in the center of his head. Do I just drop straight down? I'm
kind of afraid to go anywhere. Straight down right there. I think that's what I need to do.
And I think that's it. This is definitely it. This is it. All right. Got it. Okay. I just spin
this. All right. I mean, that's pretty self-explanatory. Missed it, but that's
all right. The water. I did it. Let them out. They can be free. That was really cool. That really
was just sort of a super shrine. I should probably heal. The music does not sound like I just won
maybe defense food or something. I think I'm going to do defense food. Sounds good. High level
defense food or low level defense food. Well, let's just see what it is first. I'm going to
heal with just regular ass food. This is plus five hearts. I'm doing this. All right. Whatever
this is, it's time to fight it. So I'm going to use my guardian sword and I'm going to use this
cool shield. Let's get rid of one of these. All right. Let's do it. Let's go. All right.
Fuck you. Whatever you are. Fuck you. You fucking bloomin' onion. Let's go. Oh, God. Water Blight
Ganon. I thought that was Water Blight Ganon talking. All right. Leave me a voicemail because
I'm going to be busy here in a sec. Electricity. Electricity. I didn't jump over it. Oh, shit.
Where'd he go? Whoa. Oh, my God. Can you even dodge that? Why are you taking a picture of me?
What? Oh, take a picture. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. No, that's a terrible photo of that. I mean,
that's kind of cool though. Try to keep the water. No. Yes. That's still counted, right?
In a mod chat. Help me here. I think I got a picture of it. I think I'm fine.
I got a photo. I got a photo already. Get up. He's supposed to torch the water.
Link, stop being such a slug. Get up. I already took a picture. Wait. They're doing it because
the frame lag. What? Stop talking. Fucking backseat Andy over here. My bow is broken.
Oh, no. Give me a bow. Take this calamity again. Yeah, I am dropping frames. You're right.
I thought you were saying take a picture. I thought I got the photo wrong.
Pretty good cleric beast. I thought it was like, hey, dude, what the fuck? You take a picture.
Take a picture. Just dropping a shitload of frames. They were doing. Yeah, I see. Okay.
What a bad time for frames to drop. It was horrible. Well, I beat the boss.
Hold on. PowerPoint. Let me just see what this looks like. What was the viewer experience?
Oh my god. Can you even dodge that? Okay. Well, that's unfortunate, but whatever.
Very cool. All right. So now what? I'll take my heart container. That was really fun. Wait,
once you activate, you cannot go back in. So I didn't miss anything important, right? I think
I got pretty much everything important, I think, right? You're good. All right, let's go. So that's
one of four. This is probably the easier of the four bosses. It doesn't have to be, you know,
it doesn't have to be incredibly difficult to be fun. I think it was fun. It was perfect.
Just in case you didn't know who that was.
Since I am now a spirit, my healing power would be wasted on me.
So therefore, I would like you to have it. Please accept Mipha's grace.
What does that do? Yesterday, I was awash in a pool of tears. I had nearly given up hope
and resigned myself to being trapped here as a spirit for the rest of eternity. But now you're
here. All this time, my hope was to see you once more. Promise me that you will not hesitate to
call upon my power if you ever find yourself in need. A summon? Knowing that will let my spirit
rest in peace. I must go. Ruta and I have our roles to fulfill. We are both honored to be able
to play the role of support. We'll annihilate Ganon together. Farewell. See ya.
Oh, that's cool. It's an instant revive on cooldown. That's really cool.
I feel like I could probably use that. So this thing is now back under our control.
Friendly elephant. Oh, you think Calamity Ganon is looking out the window right now?
Oh, no, fuck.
Ganon's gonna be in the tower and just be looking out.
Then we can restore peace to Hyrule.
You'll never get another three. You need four. You'll never get three more.
That's a cool looking tower.
Dude, you need to shut up. This is an emotional scene. You don't care at all.
What are you talking about? Yeah, I do. Cool. Oh, that's so awesome.
I was hard to hold that because he's doing the doggy paddle.
What is this? All right, hold on. Okay, that's it.
And that's also going to be the end of the stream.
I think that's a good place to stop right after that.
No, what do you mean? Oh, I'm sorry. No, you can't. No. Finish. At least,
okay, I'll at least finish the quest. That makes sense.
Honestly, the reason why I had to stop doing that stupid routine
is I actually had no fucking idea where I was going.
Like, okay, I can't see on the map and I'm not going to go back to the...
How would you even know where you were going?
All right, I'll finish this quest and then I'm going to call it.
And then I'll be live again. What's today? Sunday?
How's Wednesday look? I think Wednesday is good.
Same time around three o'clock Pacific.
All right, get back up here. Finish the quest. Get my shit in here.
All right, before I'm going to get it. It's another cut scene.
Whatever. It's cool. 3 p.m. Pacific. Yep. On Wednesday.
Thanks for watching, though. Appreciate it.
Same game. Now, that is a good question.
I'm going to ask everybody here. Do you want...
Let's get a poll. Do you want more Breath of the Wild on Wednesday?
I'm going to need a very large amount of people saying yes.
Saved Zora's Domain.
Link sincerely apologized for my harsh treatment of you.
You were thinking Hyrule's and Lady Mipha's well-being just like the rest of us.
Something else. All right, you know what?
I mean, this is a 90% again, which is shocking.
It seems like you don't like the game. What?
I'm telling you right now, the amount...
Okay, the percentage that is voting yes right now
is at least what I feel about this game for a score.
At the very least. I think this is great.
I'm having a great time.
I just want to make sure you guys are having a good time still.
I'm usually three stream Andy with a game besides Elden Ring.
If you're still liking it, I'm still liking it.
Let's keep doing it.
Maybe I'll play some Splatoon on Wednesday.
That sounds good, right?
Maybe open up with some Splatoon.
Mess around for like an hour or two.
Jump back into Breath of the Wild.
Yeah, we'll do that.
The switch is hooked up.
It's ready.
It's being captured.
Okay, so there's a cool chest over here.
By the way, Link, I see you are without your trusty blade.
The sword that seals the darkness.
Did you perhaps lose it when you lost your memory?
Maybe.
Yeah, so we'll do Splatoon 3.
And Breath of the Wild again on Wednesday.
Okay.
As your father, I am proud of you for fighting the Divine Beast alongside Link.
You've grown much recently.
I know you'll be a worthy heir when your time comes.
Mother, thank you.
The heavy rains have stopped and the Divine Beast is our ally once again.
Truly splendid.
This is wonderful.
Cool.
All right, what's on the chest?
Top tier expression of gratitude.
All right, we're gonna have a party?
All right, so what is in the chest?
Light scale trident.
Cool.
Does this do anything cool?
This can be repaired.
It's a unique weapon and can repair.
Save this weapon.
Do not use it.
Okay.
I mean, I wasn't planning on it.
All these ones like this 60, this plus plus plus plus.
I'm gonna hoard so many of these items.
I'll use the default.
Okay, cool.
All right, guys.
I'll see you on Wednesday.
Thanks for watching.
Have a good rest of your night.
I'm gonna save it right here.
This is exactly where we're gonna open back up.
What about the photo?
We'll do that right when I get up.
When I start again on Wednesday.
It looks like all the last part of the Stream of Conscious Charity is going on still.
Yeah, I'll send you guys there.
Sent you there last night, too.
I think it's Vinny's doing something right.
Go say hello.
Go support the charity stream, obviously.
And I'll talk to you guys later.
See you Wednesday.
Take care of yourselves.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Say what?
I almost forgot.
Yeah, call your mother.
Come on.