Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some Smite gameplay slash commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as Loki, the trickster god of Thor's brother and Zeus's son.
I think that's right, I hope. No, Odin's son, right? Yes.
Well anyways, this is Smite. Again, I'm getting into this game a lot more than I did before, and I'm not exactly sure what the reason is for that.
I think it's just you go through those cycles of games that you play, and this is the one right now that I happen to be playing a ton of.
But I'm gonna talk about this game, Smite. I'm not gonna really talk about the gameplay, really. It's a 12 and 4, I think, 12 and 5.
It's just a couple of montage-y type clips back to back of me getting some kills, getting a double kill, and that sort of stuff.
But I'm gonna talk about a topic and a discussion I want to get you guys to chime in on as well in the comments section.
It's about what makes a game take off, and the reason why I bring this up is Smite is one of those games that's still currently in beta,
but it hasn't really steamrolled yet. It hasn't really taken off yet, at least as of the recording of this video.
It still kind of has a small community of players that are playing it currently in the beta.
Now when the game opens up, this could completely change. This game could be incredibly popular.
A lot of people will be playing it. People will be making videos and streaming it. I'm just not exactly sure.
But I want to get your guys' opinion on this, because I was thinking about this the other night in my bed,
because that's where I do all my thinking. You guys know that.
What makes a game take off? How do you get a game to go from a small community to an explosion of popularity?
And I'm gonna bring up one game in particular. It's Minecraft.
Minecraft was made by like one dude, or like a few handful of people in Java,
and the game just absolutely erupted with this crazy popularity.
And I think you can break it down into maybe a couple different categories.
And Minecraft would probably fall into this one, which is ingenuity.
When there is a game that comes out or something that is being developed that has been never seen before
and has nothing like it on the market at all, that's where people say,
holy crap, look at that game. You could build blocks and the whole world is like eight times the size of the Earth,
and I can get in the multiplayer server with my friends.
There's a whole lot of stuff going on in Minecraft that made it something like that has never been released ever before in the history of video games.
But is that all it takes? Is that all it takes to get yourself out there and to get your name noticed in the gaming industry
is to be able to make something that has never been seen before? I don't know.
And that's why I want to get your guys' opinion on this, get you guys to chime in in the conversation,
because I feel like there are a lot of games out there that require attention,
that if you don't get a chance to play them, you are losing out.
And they are very small, knit groups of people, and I would definitely even put Team Fortress 2 into this group.
As popular and as amazing as the game is, it still has a very, very, very small community,
and there are people that don't even know that Team Fortress 2 even exists still, that you can still play it.
I have a personal friend of mine that plays console, plays PC, plays everything, and he didn't even know.
He did not even know that Team Fortress 2 has been doing these big updates to the PC version.
He thought the Xbox version just came out, and oh yeah, I played it, it was fun, oh cool.
And he doesn't even know that the TF2 version on the PC has like a million different updates,
and all the crazy new maps, all the crazy new game modes, weapons, items. He was flabbergasted at that.
But let's move away from Team Fortress 2 and bring up the second thing that I think makes a game explode,
and it's ease of play. If you cannot just jump into a game and play and kind of know what you're doing
in the first 20 minutes or 15 minutes of you getting in the game, chances are you're going to stop playing it,
or you're going to say, this game is way too hard for me, it's way too ridiculous for me.
Perfect example right here is of Dark Souls. You guys probably saw the Dark Souls video.
If you haven't, I suggest you go watch it. I made a Dark Souls video, recorded the first half an hour of me playing the game,
and I seriously almost diarrhea'd my pants because of how hard that game is.
I don't even know if I'll ever play that game again.
I may or may not do it just for fun on a live stream or something like that, watch me rage or something,
but the game is so, there's so much to it, and it's so difficult, and the learning curve is pretty steep
that it turns off a lot of people, and I would bring Smite into this category as well.
But then again, you take a look at a game like League of Legends or Dota, Dota 2, those games are insanely popular.
They are like worldwide phenomenons. So how come, why is Smite not in that category?
You think of like Heroes of Newerth, you think of, like I said, Dota 2, League of Legends.
Why is Smite not one of those big games right now?
And I'm trying to figure out why, because I love this game.
I think this game is one of the most fun games I've played in the last year or two,
and when the game finally releases and it's not in beta anymore, it's completely free to play, open to the public,
it will get some more players and it will get some more attention,
but it's going to fall into that category of, like I said, Team Fortress 2,
and some of these games that have the really good community, small communities behind them,
like something like Monday Night Combat is another MOBA type game that's like this,
Awesome Knots is another game that's like this, but why are these games not huge?
Who decides that? Who's the one that makes the decisions on stuff like this?
Because I want to meet them and I want to say, look, dude, alright, listen, baby,
you've got to make this game popular because it's a fun game, dude, you've got to play this.
And maybe that is really all it takes.
Now that I really sit down and I think about it, maybe that really is all it takes.
It's just word of mouth telling people how much fun things are,
and then they get it and they get the same thing and they tell their friends and they have so much fun,
and that's where it all explodes from, because Minecraft, going back to Minecraft,
Minecraft really blew up during the YouTube breakout, when YouTube was starting to get,
let me rephrase that, when YouTube Gaming started to really take off,
people were making Minecraft videos, and then everyone started to play Minecraft
because they saw the Minecraft videos, they saw all these people having so much fun making creations
and hanging out with their friends, that's where it comes from.
So I guess before the video is over, I want to, of course, get your input as well
as to why you think games can take off and why some of them don't take off,
and I guess we will end it at that.
So again, please leave your comments in the comments section, let's keep the discussion going,
and thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it,
and I'll see you guys all next time, and of course, take care, everybody.