Welcome back to Animal Crossing. This would be day 2 of Animal Crossing.
What do you mean it was real? I told you we were doing this yesterday.
Garbage game.
In the middle of like a bunch of pogs.
God damn it. It's alright. Don't worry.
Let me just change one or two small things.
Have...eh...
That's good. It's gonna probably flash for a second.
Looks alright. I do have to change this.
There we go. So this is day 2.
Let me change the title.
Micro games 500% hurry.
This makes sense.
I mean this is like micro gaming, isn't it?
Animal Crossing. New Horizons.
Is this on the GameCube? No, it is not.
Not.
So the question is, am I gonna keep a facecam on for this?
Fuck. I mean I turned it on already.
Fuck. I'm gonna have to.
Fuck. Alright, let's go.
Are you gonna get negative viewers? That's alright.
Whatever.
We're just playing Animal Crossing, man.
What's going on here? Is it Donald Duck?
Why is Donald Duck in the game?
Why is Donald Duck in this game?
Testing, testing, test, test, test.
Hello, every...
Oh dear, so sorry about that.
The volume's a little loud there.
Fix the screen?
What's wrong with the screen?
What do you mean the screen?
Make it bigger.
What are you guys doing? Oh dear, so sorry about that.
The volume's a little loud.
Hello. Starting today, I'll be doing an island-wide
broadcast full of island updates going on and such.
I'll go over some things that are very important to island life,
so lend me your island ears for a short time.
It's the only thing that we kick off this daily ritual
with a doozy of an island announcement.
The Saltcrest Airport is now
open for business.
Starting today, you can use online or local communication
to fly to other islands for a visit.
That's not all. No, no, no. The airport counter now offers
a postal service as well.
And just like the Resident Service Center,
the airport is open 24 hours a day, so please drop by
for a look.
I do have one other item to share, and it too is a whopper.
As this very day, a brilliant fellow by the name of Blathers
will be joining us at Saltcrest.
That's the, uh, that's the...
Let Us In.
I'm not fucking giving you guys my Nintendo Switch address.
That's a mistake.
As this very day, Blathers will be joining us
at Saltcrest.
He has a keen interest in biology,
past and present, and he's here to study Saltcrest.
Still, I hope everyone lends their cooperation.
Yes, this is the museum guy.
Alright, let's go pick up weeds and shit.
Let Us In.
I'm not, no, I'm not letting you guys in.
There are streamer codes.
I just want to pick up fucking weeds and stuff
and hit rocks with shovels for like an hour.
Oh, that's gotta change.
I forgot about this guy.
Uh, that looks bad. I don't want to look like this.
Whoa!
Look at all this mail.
Happy Home Academy.
Greetings from the Happy Home Academy, our goal
is to make your home the best.
Alright, gimme it.
The Nook Mileage Program
wishes to express our gratitude for your continued use
of the Nook Stomp and Nook Mileage Program.
The item you claim via our redemption is attached
to this message.
Oh, right, didn't I buy a bunch of shit yesterday?
Hold on.
We got a lot of crap in here.
Wooden mini table.
Sweet, I learned it. Oh, DIY wooden table.
Wait, I got a house now!
This isn't a tent anymore, this is a house.
Hold on.
Important.
What are the tips?
Turn lights on in our decorating mode and open storage.
That's good to know.
Make the room brighter or dimmer.
This feature lets you easily make design changes.
And open storage.
When in your home, you can open your pocket,
select furniture or other items. Yeah.
I like that better.
Okay, what about decorating?
Oh, I don't have anything.
I don't have shit.
Okay, well, let's pick this up. Put this in the corner.
I'm so glad you don't have to push this
and pull this and all that crap.
Switch. Right here.
And then the radio. Put this over here.
This house is pretty bad.
Radio in the middle so we can both listen to our favorite tunes.
And then the switch so we can both watch TV in bed.
Looks good.
No, that's the same thing.
Do I have anything else? No.
Alright, let's go get the elephant slides that I had.
Let's go put them in here.
I've got lots of mail and all this stuff.
Alright, hold on. What's this one?
Oh, eyes!
It's fucking 3D glasses.
Alright, where should I put my slides?
Change clothes.
My dear Jeremy,
how is your new life treating you?
Are you eating well, brushing your teeth, washing behind your ears?
Oh dear, I'm all worked up.
Here's a little something to help out.
Eat it or plant it, but think of me, says mom.
This is nice. This is sweet.
Alright, elephant slide. Get it.
I gotta go sell a bunch of crap.
Alright, hold on. Elephant slide.
Hell yeah.
It's just so good.
Alright, what did mom give me?
Apples. Ooh, thanks mom.
Should I turn it this way?
Spin it. There we go.
Can I get on it? If I can't slide this,
this is not worth 4,000 fucking bells.
I can't slide on the slide.
You've gotta be shitting me.
Put away the net?
How do you just put it away completely?
Tap A, don't hold.
How do you put something down? Down on D-pad?
Okay. I can't get on the slide.
Bring it.
Alright, shopping. I got the loafers.
Can I store this? No.
ZL to check your nook miles.
Are those the same?
Slip on loafers?
What's the difference?
It's green. It's not a big difference.
Alright, I gotta get rid of some stuff.
I can't even open my mail.
I gotta go talk to the museum guy.
Dream house.
How many miles is it? 500, that's pretty good.
Put it in the house storage.
This is relaxing now.
I'm like, this is good.
This is where I want to be.
Okay, how do I put this in here?
Put it in storage.
Am I gonna hang it on the wall?
I can hang the sneakers on the wall.
Why would I do that?
Alright, let's put...
I'll keep everything else.
In Back to the Future 3,
what profession did Doc Brown have?
He was a scientist.
Oh, they're blooming, that's cool.
Good. All the mail has been looked at.
Right?
Wait, where's my...
Alright, I got everything.
Alright, water this shit.
These are gonna be beautiful the next time we play.
Oh, shit.
I just realized something.
So, those of you that weren't here at the beginning of the stream,
I am not gonna be here
for at least a few days.
I will be gone for probably four or five
days.
I don't like to say that.
But,
I have a lot of shit to do
in my personal life.
So, a lot of things going on
that has to be taken care of.
What am I gonna do about Animal Crossing?
Play offline and then update us.
Alright, what if I don't?
What if I just like, don't do that?
Just play it off stream and update you guys?
Is that okay?
Alright, that sounds fun.
I'm not gonna play that much, only like an hour or so a day.
I might not even play it.
I'm gonna be so fucking busy.
Those of you that are curious,
I'm moving.
Staying in Vegas.
But I didn't want to make a big deal about it because obviously
many people hear that word.
And it's really, really bad timing too
because just everything is getting set here.
But,
staying in Vegas, just going to a different spot.
And,
I didn't want to really talk that much about it because obviously
when people hear the word moving, they go,
wait a minute, what, he's moving? He's fucking moving?
What's wrong? And so I don't want to, you know, make a big deal about it.
Staying in Vegas.
Somebody want to link the,
there's a link, there's a hashtag
exclamation point
thing that explains why
you read it,
read it,
it's right there, it's a few sentences.
Somebody's got it, right?
No, no, no, no, nothing,
the exclamation point, there you go, somebody's got it, there you go.
Why isn't that one working?
So you see, since the number of hormones is increasing, I agree that we need
Oh, there's like a person face down with me.
Hold on.
I should probably do that.
I have every confidence that
you'll find a way to handle this little puzzle.
Holy shit, he's fucking
moving? See, this is what I'm talking about.
This is what I was talking about.
Uh, the two of you have been training under me for how many
years now? Hmm.
This should be a piece of cake.
No more of rumor.
I don't, I don't know.
I don't think that's possible in Las Vegas to not
have a rumor. I don't think that's possible.
Are you happy with your home?
Is it meeting your expectations that you'll
be a lot more comfortable now?
Houses are so different from tents.
You can freely change up the flooring and wallpaper.
You've got some
built-in storage so you can put away the furniture you aren't
using.
There's more! There's more.
All homeowners are automatically
registered with the Happy Home Academy.
Uh, and evaluate your
home on a regular basis to send you helpful advice.
Are you going to evaluate my house?
No more streams for another season?
No, no.
The move from Vegas to
Vegas is not the same as
the move from Boston to Vegas.
One of them is across the country.
The other one's in the same city.
So, I will be back
within
four or five days. It won't, it's not going to
take that long. Trust me.
Yeah, the mileage on a hot air balloon,
I'll get there in like four, six,
seven days, something like that.
Four to five years.
Not four to five decades!
Am I even going to be alive in five
decades? How old am I?
I'll be like 85!
Am I going to be alive when I'm like 90?
I don't even, that's like a long
fucking time. Why do I like
Vegas? Well, we,
I mean, you're talking about a conversation
we had dozens and dozens
of times almost two years ago.
I'm here. I love it here.
I love this city.
I want to stay in this city. Pretty much it.
Oh, that
98,000 bells.
Can I pay in miles?
Can you pay in miles?
Oh, no.
What's going to have to do with Tallix?
I think Tallix is staying here. I think
Tallix is staying in Vegas too. That's the
plan. So,
look, the last couple
years has been
sort of a trial period if
it was something that we wanted to even do.
You know, I remember this,
I've never done anything like this before.
I lived in Massachusetts my entire life.
So, coming out across
the whole country was like, you know, obviously
I wanted to spend a year or two years
or so to find out
is this something I actually want to do? Do I
actually want to be here more than a year or two?
That was for everybody involved.
And the answer is yes.
And wherever,
you know, wherever
Tallix ends up wanting to be, that's where he wants to be.
I'm pretty sure he's
staying in Vegas. That's at least the plan.
But that's kind of what,
that's the way it is, right?
I forgot about the nightbot command. Oh, no.
Enter the gamer hubs.
No, he's not staying with me. No, not anymore.
Not after this week.
Is Kim? Yes, Kim is coming with me.
Him and I will be moving and so will
Tallix as well. But I can't,
this is, I obviously
don't want to make a big deal about moving
because I'm not going very far.
I'm staying in the city of Las Vegas.
So you, honestly, I'll be honest with you,
you probably won't even really see a
difference for stream downtime
because
the plan is by this
weekend to be done. We'll see.
What about Otto? Do you honestly
think that my dog is not coming with me?
What, how, what
are you talking about? Yeah,
we're gonna keep it going. Otto, you know, Otto's
gonna go get his own place, I think.
Otto's thinking about going and checking out some places.
He was apartment hunting the other day.
No, he's, he's my dog.
Anyways, uh,
again, don't want to make a big deal about it because it's not a big deal at all.
Not a big deal.
Not a big deal. Are you and Otto still
friends? Payments can be made using
the ABD feature of the Nook Stop.
I think that's everything I need to tell you about homes
today.
Otto is coming with me. I've said it like
five times. I have a nice surprise
for you. You ready for this?
It's a premium miles redemption,
a Nook Miles ticket.
Pretty sick. What is a Nook Miles
ticket?
It's a conundrum. We want to improve our island
but still hold on to that deserted island magic.
Well, now you can do both.
You can use one of these tickets
to do some island hopping adventuring. But yes, just
go anytime you want. If you're looking to meet
some new characters and gather materials for DIY projects,
excellent. Answer what question?
Answer the question. What, what question?
What question do you have? What are you talking about?
I just did. What question do you have?
You got me, you got me for 10 seconds. What question?
What do you got? What about Cheeto?
Yes. Are you and Otto
friends? Yes. Do you eat
ass? I plead with it!
Anything else?
No, she's not. I'm not even going to say it out loud.
Are you still
friends with Otto? Yes. Is Otto
a dog? Yes. You got four more seconds.
What about Chad? You guys don't, you guys
don't live in my house.
No, you won't be coming with me in my house.
Any plans to...
We don't, you don't, you don't live in
my, no, you don't live in, you don't
live here. You don't,
none of you guys are here in this house.
So how can I bring you to the new,
a new place when you don't occupy
this house, this room here?
Alright, fine. I'm turning the fucking
digital vacuum on. No, this is weird.
This is weird. This is going to get weird. I don't want to do that.
Alright, you got me for two more seconds.
I'm not doing like a fucking, Jerma sucks
you up in a digital vacuum thing.
That's fucking weird. I don't like
that. You like the Olive Garden? Of course I do.
I especially love...
Out of all the things there, my favorite part
about going to the Olive Garden has to be...
Smoked mozzarella chicken.
I'm actually fucking just doing ads for
Olive Garden this whole stream.
I didn't even pay me any money or anything.
I'm doing this for no reason.
I am like shouting out the fuck
out of the Olive Garden for
almost two straight hours.
This is just for free.
Whatever.
That's for breadsticks. By the way,
they're endless. If you didn't know.
Alright, I could...
I could play a game.
Get the camera off.
I could play a game. I'm playing a video game
right now. I'll have to take it to the counter
to use it whenever you have travel strikes.
Wait, don't they have recycle?
Alright, let's go. Camera on.
No, no, it's late. It's getting late.
No, I don't... I do not want to
put the camera on. I think it's time
to just kind of hang out and chill.
Take a... I don't...
The camera doesn't have to be on anymore.
What's the point of the camera? What does the camera have to be on for
every day? Doesn't have to be.
What's the point? I can just not have the camera on
when I don't feel like it. Alright, here we go.
Let's play. What are some chores
I can do today? Oh, somebody's like
on the ground over there, right? Wait.
I gotta go down here. Oh, the fucking
game sound is muted.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Alright, where's that person that was on the
beach? Get the bottle? I don't have
any room for the bottle. I don't have any room.
Oh, my pockets are full already.
I just put it down. I don't have any
room. I don't have any fucking room.
What is this? Elephant slide.
You know what? Just... What is this?
Ooh. There's someone out there
somewhere. The latest trend to
hit the waves is a little something I call self-care.
And how can you do that if you can't see yourself?
Take a little you time to make
this and any other recipe that floats
to shore. Cool.
Wooden full-length
mirror. That's cool.
Alright, okay.
Let's go talk to the
new guy. Donald Duck.
The waves. The waves are good. Already the
pool noodles.
I've asked storms to come and brace yourselves,
lads. Hard to starboard,
tough to port, stern to stern.
Oh, it's not Donald Duck.
It's Donald Pelican.
Blur. Do you have my
pickled herring pizza? I already tipped
online, so...
Wait, I don't see a pizza. Where am I? Where are you? Who am I?
Oh, hang on. I know that one.
I'm none other than Gulliver, a seafaring
seagull of the seven seas.
Were you the one who kept nudging me just now?
Thanks for the wake-up call.
Those hasty hallucinations tend to sneak
up on me. You find it
hard to forgive this waterlogged bird brain?
I'm reading your vacant expression
as a yes, you.
As I dozed off and tumbled overboard
again. That's an endearing
character trait of mine. My crewmates love
it when I slip over the bow. Ha!
Don't worry, the fellas
will be here to rescue me in no time. Got an ace
up my wing, you see.
I'll just call for help using my handy
dandy, uh...
Oh my. Oh my
gosh. My handy dandy communicator is
broken. This isn't handy OR dandy!
Oh, sardines. It's all cracked and busted.
Looks like it's missing a few communicator
parts. That means
I'll have to wait for my crew to find me
on their own.
That could take a while. I've only got enough
nautical puns to last a couple more hours.
I'm begging you, will you look for my
communicator parts, please?
Sure.
Communication parts are probably buried in the sand somewhere.
I'm just missing five parts.
Find them, I'll try to clear.
Get them back together again.
I'm sure my crewmates are looking for me, so
I better stay here and watch for the boat.
I'll leave the searching to you!
I believe in you, partner. I don't have much of a choice.
But let me get this straight.
Um, this character is
not in your game. But he's in mine.
Right?
Is this possible?
He shows up in everybody's.
This one everyone gets.
Oh, okay. There you are.
Okay, let's give him some creatures.
Ooh, a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Blathers.
I'm exceedingly interested in the ecosystem of this island.
Thus I have come to conduct research,
if you will. Could you be
that you are Jeremy, the personage
who chose the location for this tent?
I am.
Splendid job indeed, thanks to you, I was able to
uh, I thought they said
I'd. I was able to
I'd. I was able to get on here.
Now regarding the aforementioned research,
truth be told, I am determined
to open a museum and henceforth dwell on this
island amongst you.
If you discover any new types of inspector fish, come
bring it here. I will exhibit
them, as well as those you gave to Tom Nook.
Now there's one small problem.
I lack the number of exhibits needed to secure
permission to open a museum proper.
Empty display cases will not do, I'm told.
Display cases with something to display? That is another matter.
Where are you coming? Allow me
to explain.
I need insects. It's not just insects
and fish. I want fossils.
This is a substantial stretch of land
beyond the river. I would bet my pin
feathers. This primitive plot is flushed
with the fossils I require. On the river you say
I can't just go over it? Well, it's a boat.
Get on one. Pardon me, Jeremy,
while I transmit the vital data to your Nook phone.
I want to drink out of that.
Anybody else want to drink out of that thing?
There you see, with wood
gathered from salt, Chris one can
make a legendary pole vault.
This pole can be used to propel
oneself across the river. Up and over you go. Hooty
hoo. I sent DIY
schematics for a shovel. I dig
fossils from the ground as well, which brings me to my
point. Please,
Jeremy, cross the river and seek out these ancient
relics. My feathers have
lathered on for too long, but let me leave you with this.
Time to open the museum. I must acquire more items
to exhibit 15. I hope
you do it. What do I got? I have things
to donate.
Okay, so I have...
Take this moth. I got a bunch of shit outside
too. Repugnance.
What happens if I miss-maintain my composure?
I beg your pardon. Bugs I do detest
them. Wait, aren't you...don't you want them?
Still, there's much I can tell you about the
insect you apprehended. If you insist that is.
No. I know what a moth is.
That's the joke.
Bugs are the bane of my existence.
Rest assured the wretched thing will get the best of care here.
It's supposed to be funny, Jeremy.
It was!
By the way, I wonder if you have anything else
that could be donated. I do.
Here, take this.
Prussian carp.
Any facts
about the carp you want to know? No.
It's a fish.
It fucking eats algae. Cool.
13 more. This dude's going feral?
Why am I going feral?
Okay, I will get plenty. You know what?
I want...oops, don't do that.
Look at all these animals that I have out here.
I was going to clean up...okay, let's go.
We will get the lore of the hermit crab, I promise.
Why am I not an animal?
Hermit crab.
Hermit crab, ugh, what a wretched thing.
I don't like bugs. Hermit crab's not a bug?
Hold on. Hermit crab is not
a bug. It's like crustacean.
It's like a crab. It's not a bug?
Tell me about it. In that case,
ugh. Hermit crab is not an insect.
Well, it most certainly resembles one,
bleh. It looks much like a spider
with its creepy eyes and crawly legs,
but it is in fact a crustacean.
That sucks. The hermit crab has ten legs and also
wears a shell, but it doesn't grow this shell itself.
It slips its soft body...I mean, we're reading
a Wikipedia article about...that took the first
four lines of hermit crab
entry. We don't need to do this.
I know what a hermit crab is. Talk about a strange
way to make it. Anywho, thanks for the donation.
Any more donations? I think I have one more, yeah?
Yeah, take this.
Bag worm.
Let him do the job. He loves it.
No, he hates it apparently, because
he doesn't like any of these things.
Alright, you can read it. Here. It's caterpillar.
It uses silk.
It's very cute. It dangles.
They hide their bug bodies in
leaves. They eat trees.
They're villains.
Let me go.
Let me in.
Blathers, I've got more things for you.
Is Jerma's character the Joker?
I got a lot of stuff.
All I have are bugs and shit.
Alright, here's another centipede.
Sure, let's find out.
The centipede's name means one hundred
legs, but I tell you now, that's a lie.
These ugly bugs can have as few
as fifteen pairs, or as many
as a hundred and seventy-one.
Because of how their bodies are segmented,
they never have exactly a hundred.
Ooh, it's true.
You know what else is true? Centipedes are
carnivorous, aggressive, and venomous.
Their bite is quite painful too.
Horrible.
Anywho, my sincerest thanks
for your donation.
No bugs are the bane of my existence. Thank you.
Fun fact about centipedes.
If you see
a centipede,
you're supposed to leave it alone. The centipede
is such an aggressive psycho, it
will eat and kill all the other awful bugs
that are even near your property.
A centipede is like the ultimate
ultimate hunter.
And they kill like scorpions and shit,
and spiders, and just leave
those motherfuckers alone. Let them just
wreck havoc
on the pests that inhabit your house.
No one cares about centipedes.
I mean, I didn't tell you
to touch your tongue on it.
Just leave it alone.
If it's in your house, just get it out of your house.
But if you see one around your house, I don't know, just leave it alone.
I gotta bring most stuff.
Is this a fossil? Wait.
That's another fossil?
I need to get a shovel. Alright, back to the...
I gotta go sell. It was one in my room
last week. Man, it probably
wiped out the scary
spider collection that may have been
in your house. So you should just be thankful
of the centipede.
Hello. What would you like to talk to me about?
No, no, no. I'm good. Other person.
Team Spider.
Did I tell you? I saw
the... I said the
other day, but this is horseshit.
It was probably like six months ago.
I saw a
fake widow. Whatever they're called.
They're called like fraud widows.
They look like black widows.
They're big. Their legs are so terrifying.
It was terrifying. It was just outside.
Those things are
scary.
It's a fraud. Yeah, it's actually called like
fraud widow.
Proposal?
Proposal. Sure.
There it is.
False widow spider. There it is.
I'm getting drunk.
We'll need a lot of materials for proper
shops. So bring in wood and
stuff. Yeah, well, we'll do it.
Here's the items.
30 pieces of wood.
Wait, 90? 30 iron
uggets and 90 pieces of different wood.
Okay.
Holy shit, man.
All right. Well, here, I want to sell stuff.
Here, take this. I want to sell.
Let's get rid of
these.
These.
What else
should I get rid of?
I don't know what else to sell. Sell the weed?
Oh, I'm going to keep the weed.
Sell the nest too.
I guess so.
1,400 bills.
I got money in the
bank. Look, I got money in the bank.
I've got $5,500
in the bank. Loan payment.
Pay from savings. Let's do
$2,000 onto our loan.
When am I going to play Odama next?
I don't...
I'm not playing that game again.
You'll never see that game again.
Not happening.
Okay, so I need to find... I need to make
a shovel. Let's take and make a shovel.
Let's collect some stuff first.
There's a rock down here. Let me hit the rock.
I need a bunch of wood too.
Each tree has three wood.
Is that three wood a day?
I might be able to do the shop thing today.
I should probably not.
The wood's the easy part. Oh, I need the
iron. Should I talk to Phoebe?
Yo, Jeremy!
Hold on. I'll have time for you in a minute.
Get out of my way! Get out!
Stop! Get the fuck
out of my way. I've got stuff to do.
Oh my god, you've ruined everything.
Cool. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice. Thank you, thank you, thank you. Cool. Thanks for the lunch.
I figured out how to make a lunch.
Okay, cool. You can make a shovel
now. Thank you. There's gold over there.
Okay, thank you.
I'm rude? I only have about five
seconds to hit this stuff. Thanks for the...
Thanks for that. I'm so rude.
No! I'm clearly working and they
got in my way. You don't go walk into a
guy swinging an axe and go, hey, I have a question
for you. Is my face too close to your
backswing? Get out of here.
I was rude.
I just gave you a shovel. Be more fucking
grateful.
Hey, now you're being rude
to me. It's a never
ending cycle of rudeness.
I'll see you guys next week for the City of Heroes
stream. That'll be fun.
We're gonna work together.
We're gonna have a superhero group of like
4,000 of us.
It'll be really cool. It'll be fun.
Gold nugget. Nice.
Alright, what does it take to make a shovel?
Here, I'll talk to you. I'm sorry.
Am I being pranked? Is there a hidden camera?
Let's talk.
That game is dead.
Omega lol.
Wait, the game doesn't even turn on.
Is the server gone?
The servers are gone. I can't even play it.
He's a
fan server. Okay.
There's a fan server. Well, I don't want to
diarrhea all over somebody's
fan server with like
5,000 fucking accounts made on it.
I'm not gonna do that.
You better invite me over soon.
Did I learn the shovel?
DIY? Play Champions Online?
Here we go.
It's hardwood. Shovel!
Let's have a sleepover.
Ooh, wait. I can make all this stuff.
I'm gonna make a little table.
And we're gonna make a mirror.
I have to have furniture in my house.
Alright, that's good for now. Okay.
Nook miles. What did I get?
I actually have a lot of miles.
5,000 is the inventory upgrade, right?
Furniture. Flower tender.
I almost set the inventory upgrade.
Very cool.
Okay. I need to make another axe.
Do I have enough for an axe?
That's a net. That's not an axe.
Okay. Do the pole.
Oh yeah, the pole vault, right?
New vaulting pole.
Pockets are too full. Shit.
I gotta get, hold on.
I gotta get this stuff in my house.
I gotta deposit some shit.
Okay, so mirror.
Turn the lights back on.
Wooden full length mirror.
Nice.
What can I do with it?
Can I change up my look?
What do you mean change up my look?
Oh, you can change your haircut and stuff?
That's kinda cool.
Alright.
A little table.
Nice.
And a elephants slide.
Put the elephants slide down here.
I'll plant an apple.
Actually, I'll plant two apple trees.
Why not?
Alright, this looks like a fucking temple.
World of slides.
Alright, now...
I wanna go back.
Make the pole and go across the river.
The people want 30 minutes slow mode.
I don't think they do.
I'm not sure they do.
Okay.
It begins.
So, I wanna go help Donald Duck first.
I'll head down there.
Wait.
Come on.
That kinda was a bad haul.
Suboptimal grinding.
I'm not gonna do 30 minutes slow mode.
No, why would I do that?
Flimsy shovel and shovel.
Okay, so I have to do
look for holes, things to dig on the beach?
Oh, the bird gave me the shovel.
Didn't you say my stuff's on the beach?
Pole vault over here?
How do you pole vault?
Use the shovel on the rock.
Damn. Wow.
Holy shit, that one had like 4000.
Dig a hole behind you
so you don't get recoiled.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm back here.
That thing was huge.
How do I use the pole vault?
It has to be equipped?
Oh, hold it.
Alright, nice. Here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, I'll plant apple trees over here.
Yeah, I'm gonna plant some trees here.
Okay. Apples. Plant.
Cool.
And then we do
how far apart do they have to be?
Does it matter? How far apart can I do whatever?
Will this work? Can I do it here?
I can do it right there, right?
It doesn't matter? It just does? Okay, cool.
I'm gonna have an apple garden.
Just at least one space.
Do I have to water them?
I would assume, right?
Trees don't need water. Oh, okay.
Am I gonna play Smite after this?
That's something I haven't heard in a very, very, very long time.
Dude, you're gonna play
Smite after this?
Alright, I'm gonna
make, okay, I've got three apple trees.
Oh shit, there's a lot of stuff over here.
Crap. I already have one of those
though. I don't even want it.
That's a huge fish. Huge fish.
I don't have any money.
I gotta get that space upgrade.
Alright, do I have enough for the upgrade?
I think I do. It's 5,000, right?
Come on. Come on. 500.
Ugh. What do I need to get there?
I need...
That's an easy one. Just take a...
Just take a picture. Alright, just take any photo.
Alright, I'm gonna go get the inventory upgrade.
That's the plan.
Boomer selfie.
I don't know why I'm laughing at that because I don't even know what that means.
Take the bulletin board. What's this?
Free stuff tomorrow only at Tom Nook's house.
Just go in. It's fine. Take anything.
Sign Tom Nook.
Well, that's...
That's still valid?
Is it still open?
5,000 miles.
A pocket organization guide.
I will take it.
Thank you.
Are we actually on 30 minute slow mode? Why?
We should not be on
30 minute slow mode.
I don't want to be on 30 minute slow mode.
I learned some tricks for organizing
my belongings. I can carry a bit more stuff.
Holy shit, that's
so much better.
I can actually breathe.
Is it an almond or Wi-Fi?
It's Wi-Fi.
Wait, it was actually on.
Alright, now I have some room for this shit.
And then I want to store
the other things.
I need storage.
What do I do? Put it back.
You have the ability
to speak now and you want it taken away
from you? Why do you want that?
You don't actually want that.
You sound like a cam girl
when she reads messages.
What the fuck does that even mean?
What?
I don't even know what that means.
What are you talking about?
True though, that's true.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
I don't even know what that reference is.
I know what
it is. I don't know what
what did I say?
It's so true. It's true. What are you talking about?
I think it's just how people read messages
in general. I got dressed for this shit.
What does that mean?
Earlier, I don't want to use
face cam.
Look at me.
Naked frame. Play Smite.
The people have spoken. The people
have spoken. Play Nancy Drew
while you swallow a disc
of smite. Installation disc
one of four.
I didn't store my items.
Store your shit. I know, I'm being
distracted by people saying
things about me. They're saying
things about me.
They're saying things about me.
Store this. Store this.
Store the clay. Store the stones.
Stones. Yes, I'll
get the stones.
Yes, my lord, I will.
I will get the stones.
Do I need any of this other shit? Can you
imagine
not seeing a bunch of movies and not
knowing what the fifth element is? Imagine
not seeing a bunch of movies. You took the Universal
fucking Studios quiz. You don't
know movies? Imagine?
It's a great movie. All right, so
I need to go on
a flash. I need to watch
more movies. German walk.
What's a stack of
fruits? It's one stack of fruits.
10, 20, 30.
Oh, look at those up
there. Rock
40. I feel like that's different from the last
one. All right, here's somebody.
This is a strategy, right? You do one behind
you so you can't be bounced back. Is this the strategy?
It is.
Oh, you fucking can't be serious.
I got some iron, though.
Watched it.
What's over here? Lots of stuff.
No, stop it. I want to just shake it.
Two diagonally by two holes.
Okay.
Whole back seating. I distinctly
saw three peaches drop
and only one of them was collectible.
What's that?
I dug up a fossil.
Oh, cool.
Any fish in here? This is worth 20.
That's rare. Everything is rare
in this game, don't you know? I make a lot of money
from peaches. It's worth $90,000.
What?
That's pretty cool. This time
I'm ready. Got you.
Don't touch it.
I caught a tarantula. The situation just got hairy.
Let's get some more fish
to bring to the guy.
I caught a loach
looking at me with reproach.
What about this one?
What else is on this little island?
Two more spots. Nice.
Fossil.
Fossil and
two more fossils.
This game is terrible for joke
stunks.
Yeah, but we've got to remember
sometimes it's not about the jokes.
Sometimes it's about shaking trees.
Picking up apples on the ground.
Sometimes it's not about the jokes.
Sometimes it's about sending
a message.
Why did you make me do that?
It's always about the jokes.
It's not always about the jokes. Sometimes it's about
just, it's not always
about the joke. Look, if it was only
joke, I could get joke exhaustion.
Alright, well I got a bunch of stuff.
Let's go talk to the, uh, wait.
Is he sentient rock?
Wouldn't that be something?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. Can you eat the grass?
I'm going to blathers.
Balloon present. Balloon present. Balloon alert.
Attention streamer. I wasn't looking.
What's in it? Hopefully it's a fossil.
Bunch of clay. Eh, that's pretty good.
I only had one.
Rare clay? Alright blathers
I got some fossils for you.
I do.
Take this. Does he dust it off?
Let me know that this is a fossil.
Incredible. Wonderful. Remarkable. My intuition
was impeccable. There are fossils
on this island. Back to
the matter at Wing. I must assess your
fabulous find. Let me see here. Hmm.
I can declare
this to be a left
Magello slide. My feathers.
What a fabulous fossil. This left
Magello side would be a sizable
step toward opening the museum.
I wonder, would you perhaps consider donating this
to the cause?
Yes. I'll add this to the collection.
I wouldn't add your light shapes to my collection.
I never thought I'd
say I'd lay eyes on this bunch of
preserved left Magello
side.
Dear me, I might have to give you a short
presentation on the topic. Ah, no.
Uh, sure.
Wonderful.
It's fascinating stuff. I assure you. Now, where to begin?
The Megalosaurus
was a relative of the deer that
lived during the Ice Age, long after
the dinosaurs. It was also known as
Megaloceros giganteos,
which just means deer with
large horns. True to their name,
they were deer with antlers spanning roughly 10
feet across. Imagine the majesty.
While smaller than many dinosaurs, they were
nonetheless a very charismatic example of
megafauna. And that is what I have to say
about that. Anywho, I'll take it.
He's doing it on purpose.
He has to be doing it on purpose.
He has to be.
Oh, Megalosaurus.
Only a specialist can appraise a newly
discovered fossil.
Whether you choose to donate is up to
you. I will assess it.
Okay.
What about this bug?
A tarantula.
Let's learn. In that case,
as spiders go, the tarantula is said to
be quite docile. But have you ever seen
such foul fuzziness?
They're barbed, I tell you.
These awful arachnids let
loose their spiky, itchy hairs to protect themselves
from predators. But seeing how
tarantulas also prey on frogs, mice, and even
birds, one must ask,
who needs protecting from whom?
Who, indeed?
Anywho, my serious thanks.
They eat frogs. That's what they do. That's fucked up.
I got this thing. A loach.
I don't care.
So hold on, the fossil that I dug up, that
the Magellan stone,
whatever it was called,
can I now sell that?
I don't have to give it to him anymore?
You can sell it off and get it again.
Place it.
Place the fossil.
He's donating. Why do you have
Why do I place it?
Place it, like, up here?
Outside. On the ground?
I already donated it.
I keep giving him fossils, but I couldn't select it.
If you get it again. No, you did not.
What?
All the fossils were grayed out when I just talked to him.
What are you talking about?
Wait, he has to assess the fossil first, then you can donate it.
Assess fossils? Okay.
Here, look at this.
Take them both. Sometimes it's automatically
donated.
What do we got?
These are rare fossils.
What are they? What are they?
T-Rex skull. How did I bring this in here?
T-Rex skull?
I never thought I'd say it. Wait a minute.
Hear me, I might give you a short presentation.
How much can I sell a T-Rex skull for?
I know what a T-Rex is.
I'm busy.
Don't put it outside.
Hold on. Put it outside?
Wait, it's a hundred thousand bells
to sell it?
Place it down.
Where is it?
Oh.
It doesn't show up on the ground.
No, I know it's not the right one.
Alright, this is the Archaopteryx.
Archaopteryx.
Take it.
Could it be? It is an Archaopteryx.
It's so preserved. Thank you.
What is this thing?
A skull of a dinosaur. Cool.
I only need five more.
So I need to give...
Let's go back out and explore.
I still need to do your thing.
Hey, communicative parts.
Come out, wherever you are.
I'll answer what it is. It's like they've all clammed up all of a sudden.
Buried their heads in the sand.
Am I responding to him?
Right.
What am I typing this for?
Buried in the sand.
What was that?
Excuse me.
Communicator part.
5G chip.
And the others.
The little water spouts.
I need five, right?
The profit is infected with 5G.
No more.
Other beach, yeah.
Go this way.
Okay, give me more of these clams.
I want that fish too. Yeah, give me this fish.
Good guy.
I caught a red snapper.
It looks pretty dapper.
Come on, little water spout.
No?
Come on.
Nothing.
Bug spotted.
That's okay.
Go get the bugs.
Bugs, bugs, bugs.
Hey, no bug?
Hey, I see a tinted rock.
Come on.
Get it. Here it comes.
That's going to float out right in front of him, really?
I fucking can't believe
that just happened.
My sweaty ass hand just hit the button.
It was there.
Again,
I'm going to say this again and I know people are going to be like,
I know here it comes again.
You can press every single switch button with your thumb.
Every single one.
Every single button on the switch controller
is going to be pressed with one thumb.
All right, bug on rock.
He's not using the pro controller.
I'm not a pro.
Where's this bug on rock, as you were describing down?
Hey, look at that.
Middle of the island on the big black rock.
I'll get the net out preemptively.
Up left, big rock.
Up here? I don't see any bugs.
He's fishing in really weird spots.
It's right next to his turn.
North bug.
Bug on chair.
Of course he turns to the left the second I do that shit.
The horse mackerel, of course.
The bug is behind you.
Looking for another bug.
Found him. Bugs.
Yes, I got a wharf roach.
Wow.
Wow. Whoa.
That was nice. That's cool.
All right, one more and then we're going to go donate.
Yes. Yes, I finally got it.
I got it. I finally got it.
Thank God it took so long.
That took so long.
Yes.
Oh, I'm never going to delete that. That's going to stay there forever.
How do I get up there?
New sub zone.
Big guy.
Come back. Put the pole in your
pool ring.
I knew you could do that.
All right, let's go give Donald Duck his
communicator parts. My pockets are full.
Uh oh. Drop it.
Drop the fucking sea snail.
I don't even want this thing.
Uh oh.
Come on.
Uh oh. I want to say it, but I
don't want to.
Do you know what I mean? I want to say it,
but I don't want to. I don't even want to.
Uh oh.
I don't know why I feel like saying this
right now. I hate that word.
The way that he says it,
it's fucked up.
It's fucking me up.
What did I just bury?
I'm begging you.
I'm going to turn off the mic
and I'm going to do it for me.
I had to do that for me.
I don't want this.
It was a private one.
Please watch it.
I've seen the video by now.
I don't live under a rock.
I've seen it.
Talk to Blathers.
He watches it every day.
I've got something for you to
assume.
I have something that I want you to
Poop guy not in chat
anymore. No, he's not. He got like banned.
Like the Poopoo BLT
guy is gone. I don't think you'll be seeing
him in chat again. Oh, it's a
Megasero torso.
You can have it.
Listen to the description, please.
I don't know.
I wonder if you have anything else. Do I? I don't think I do.
I actually, yeah,
I do. I got bugs and shit.
Fucking roach.
Tell me about the roach.
I see, in that case.
Wharf roach is an omnivore, which is merely a polite way of
saying it will eat almost anything.
This skittering scavenger
and its uncouth
appetite help keep beaches clean.
It's said.
I dare say their long antennae and bulging
eyes burn my stomach.
Unappetizing indeed.
What is the Poopoo bit? Somebody came in here
and said that they were eating a BLT
shit sandwich or something and they
made everybody lose their fucking minds.
Chat went nuts. I went nuts. It was a huge
problem. We're calling it
the BLT shit sandwich scenario
of fucking 2020.
Can I do multiple donations?
I can't do multiple donations at the same time.
This is a horse mackerel.
Do you want some facts?
I almost have enough for the museum.
Three more? Two more?
And
ooh, this big guy. Red snapper.
We'll get the facts on the snapper.
Give us some facts. Hit us with the facts.
Red snapper is the common name of dozens of
fish species and I wonder why it's so popular.
There's so many types of fish that are
both a shade of red and have a tendency to
snap? Were there no other names?
What about...
Uh, garnet...
Brasper? Fuse? Pinscher?
There you have it. Fascinating
stuff.
Once the museum is complete, there you go.
One more donation.
And that's it. The crack stream.
They're all crack streams.
Hey, uh,
look what I did.
I'm gonna click on it.
Yeah, sure.
There it is.
And you don't think
that person should have
received the 25 minute timeout.
For something like that.
And I'm the bad guy?
I'm the bad guy?
You don't think that that deserves
like a 20 minute fucking timeout?
Like, just relax and go over your life
for a little bit?
Alright, pieces of cram back in here. Let's see if this thing can send a message.
Hi there crew, it's me.
Your brother from another
rudder.
So, listen. It happened again. Can you swing by
to pick me up? Send me my coordinates now.
Gulliver. Over and out.
That should do it.
You're the best. Thanks for all your help. I promised to return the favor.
Make sure to check your mail in a few days.
I'm gonna send you something that'll knock your flippers up.
Look at this dude.
Fireman. Yeah.
Fireman's in a lot of games.
Nothing to do now but pace back and forth the next few hours.
I'm gonna play Doom Eternal.
I don't know, maybe.
I had a choice to play Doom
or this and I chose this.
Wait, I still have
two more Gulliver requests?
What about Resident Evil 3?
Absolutely. Without question,
I will play Resident Evil 3. Resident Evil 2 Remake was
my favorite game of last year so I will absolutely.
Alright, so I got yours.
Yours only said a few days.
I need one more
thing to donate. Which, let's see.
I don't really have very much.
Let's go sell these peaches.
Let's go sell all this crap.
What about Half-Life Alyx? I can't
do it. I can't do it right now.
Not only am I moving
I still have this
fucking chest and back problem.
I'm not gonna be able to play that at launch.
He's moving? Alright.
I forgot, like, every hour there's another, like, new
thousand people. I forget that sometimes.
Um, yes.
Yes. Uh, staying in Vegas.
Staying in Las Vegas.
Let me get the hashtag
What the fuck is he talking about? Why is he moving?
Look what they've done.
Uh, yeah, sometimes
I forget there's a lot of
If there's 5,000 people that
are here right now, that means
that 5 to 600
every 10 to 20 minutes are cycling
through. It's a very remarkable piece of data
if you ever get a chance to look at it.
Sell all this stuff. I'm gonna make some money
here, right? With clams.
Zelda. Kauris.
Very remarkable data. LOL
Who the fuck is this guy?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey! Look at me!
Yadadadadada!
Sorry. I got a little
smart there. Let me, like, back it up a little.
Sorry. That's what I meant to say.
Sorry.
What is this one?
Got it. What is this one?
What is it saying? What is this one saying?
Got it. Got it. I can't hear it. Got it.
Got it. Got it. Got it.
Got it. Got it.
Got it. Oh, right. From
WariWare. Okay. I really
should. Oh, this is, I'm so
happy I have this recorded. Because
randomly, I'm just gonna play that.
And people are gonna think it was a real sneeze. And I'm not gonna
be funny or anything. I'm just gonna be
sitting there going, like, I'll make noise beforehand too.
I'll be like, and done! I can buy these
from you for a total of
seven thousand...
God! Sorry. And then just keep
going with my deck.
I'm gonna do that all the fucking time. Prepare.
And done. I can buy these from you. Seven
thousand bells is a lot. It sounds so
real. It was real. It was real.
Two, three in a row.
Okay. Here we go. Ready? I want
you guys to start writing. Like, what the fuck
is wrong with them? Like, that's too many in a row.
Like, dude, do you have allergies? Like, start writing
that. Hold on. Ready?
Ugh. God.
Ugh. No, no, no.
Another one.
Fuck. How many is that in a row? Ah, my nose
is so tingly. It sucks.
You know when you get...
Geez. Oh, I think
the room is kind of
dusty.
The room is so fucking dusty.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have opened up the
bag of flour in here. That was a mistake.
What happens if you sneeze?
Does anybody know what happens?
Does anybody know what happens if you sneeze
like ten times in a row?
What happens if you sneeze like ten times
in a row?
Twenty.
Ugh.
Fuck.
Oh, no. Is that better anymore?
Ugh.
This is the most time I've sneezed in my
entire life.
Ugh. Okay. I think
they're gone. I think they're gone. I think that's it.
I don't think there are any more in here.
Jesus. Okay.
So, what I was saying was
I saw the Star Wars movie and it
was fucking... I mean, it was okay.
If you...
Ugh.
Fuck.
I'm okay now, I think.
Star Wars movie. Very topical.
You lost 150 viewers. It's alright.
I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm a fucking psycho. I gotta relax.
Okay. What's next?
Am I out of stuff to do?
Oh, wait a minute.
I need one more fossil. One more.
Fish. And then the airport. Yeah.
Let me get this last fish
and then we can figure that out.
Where's my fishing rod? God, this game is
so good.
Alright, I took it off.
Can I... How do I put it on my thing?
Register.
That just sneezes were real?
Well, that's not worth anything.
Put a...
That old tire could be repurposed. I've got an idea for a DIY
project?
Wait. That's kind of cool.
Really? Be a fish I haven't seen.
No, I've already seen this.
I probably need to go this way
and go to the river.
I want a rare fish.
It's weird. He does that sometimes
when I'm watching the streams.
He does that fake Boston accent, almost like
he's pretending that he's from the area that he's
actually from.
Does anybody know why he's doing that?
Enter. Question mark.
Ooh, it's a flounder. I caught a dab.
Not bad. Name of the fish.
Well, there's the last thing to give to the
museum.
Looking for bugs? Okay, no bugs?
Alright, let's do the museum.
And then I'm going to do the airline ticket thing.
Actually, it's called a nose wipe.
Yeah, sorry. I misspoke.
Wait, did I do this one? Yeah, I did.
It's a pretty fucking cool looking house.
I wonder who's that is.
I don't know if you're nominating this for the worst joke
taking more than five minutes.
I see the title a little that way.
You don't think I can see what clips are being made?
I can see it over there.
Assess this.
Wait, I don't have any policies, do I?
I'd like to make a donation.
And then the museum can
open.
Probably tomorrow.
This is a dab.
Actually, let's get some facts.
The dab is a flatfish that bears some
resemblance to the olive flounder.
The olive flarden.
Though their mouths are different.
Personally, I'm more really fascinated by each
fish's eye placement.
The dab's eyes are both on its right side,
while the olive flounder's are on the left.
These fish spend
lots of time lying on their sides in the sands.
The odd eye placement makes some sense.
But it's not going to be this creepy.
Incredibly disturbing.
Profoundly upsetting to fans.
And there you have it.
Grasping stuff. Bravo.
Once the museum is complete, it should be displayed
with the utmost dignity. I do believe this
means, yes, we have acquired the number as
specimens required. I'm fed as I am a loss
for words. Never would I have imagined
we could reach our donation goal
on this, my very first day on the island.
The generosity that made this possible,
the passion I am humbled by, the spirit
of Salt-Bressed
Mountain.
Now we can submit our application to build a proper museum.
Oh, I'm, I'm, I must
make haste. I gotta prepare all this shit,
dude. I gotta, there's an opening that I gotta
be ready to open tomorrow. There's so much to do. Let's go.
Thank you so much, Jeremy.
All right. Done. Done.
Both tasks completed.
In record time.
Now we go to the airport.
Holy shit, he's chasing me!
Oh, oh!
What do I do? How do I? Okay, I'm gonna turn around.
Phoebe, do something! Phoebe!
Phoebe, do you have any? Get the fuck out of
here. That was bait the whole time. I had
confidence the entire time. Now I'm gonna
sell this little fuck.
It's mean. Wait, can I just have,
what if I just keep it in my house?
I have a pet spider now. Can I play?
Oh my god, it's a friend. It's a friend.
His friend showed up.
Oh my god, I'm so scared. Oh my god.
Oh my god, what do I do? What do I?
Fuck, I was trying to go for a two.
It didn't work twice. It's okay.
But, here
we go. So, Mirantula,
show it off. Ah!
Place. There's no, wait, what do you mean
there's no room? I can't put it on the table?
Yes!
Wow! It's just you
and me. This is so cool.
Right, here. Okay.
Come on. What do you want to watch?
Oh, you can watch it on Switch, whatever you want.
Put on anything. Small.
He's gonna binge Rocket Power.
I come back in
and watch history is like
every single fucking season,
every single episode of like
Doctor Who has just been watched.
Of all like
20 years of the series. Okay.
So now, go just, do I just go to the airport?
What a mediocre show.
I'm, I think
what you just said right there.
I'm 99% certain that
somebody's going to scream in your face because you said that.
You know what I'm saying? Like I would
someone's probably gonna scream at you.
Where am I going? Where's the
airport? Down here.
So what can I do? I can go to a mystery
island? Doctor Who bad.
Doctor Who bad. Hey, welcome
to your one and only gateway to the skies.
Soft Crest Airport. Nice to meet you.
I'm Orville, ground crew for Dodo Airlines.
Dodo Airlines, the crew may be flightless.
That doesn't mean you have to be.
If you want to visit another island, invite friends
this one. Or go on a mystery tour, this is the place
to be. Oh, we've also got a mail
service at this airport. Sometimes a letter
is just better, you know?
If you want to send somebody a note, take a gander
to your right. Got all kinds of cards
at the card stand. By the way,
you're Jeremy, right?
It's a small island. Word gets around.
I just got a Nook Miles ticket
from Tom Nook with Jeremy written
on it, which makes it yours.
So if you want to use this ticket,
you just got to say the magic words.
I want to fly. Got it? So,
Jeremy, you got anything
to tell me? Thank you, Guy on
Fiverr for your voice acting that I paid
for. It was like $14.
Appreciate it. I want visitors.
I want to fly. Wait,
I want to send some cards
in the mail.
They have a card stand here. Looks like I can send a
message on a card with 200 bells.
Send a letter? Sure.
I want to go to Mystery Island.
I'm not letting chat join this.
I will ruin my whole game.
I want to fly. People are going to come
out here and just start throwing grass on
the ground. They're going to do like the Dark Souls
thing, where they just drop fucking humanity
everywhere until your game crashes. I want
to visit someone. I want...what should I do?
Do I use the Nook Miles ticket?
You want to use your Nook Miles ticket?
Roger. In that case, I'll just take this ticket
I got from Tom Nook.
Ready to get you in the sky right this minute, but let's just check.
Are you all packed? Tools already?
Wait, not yet.
Do I have any...wait, actually, I'm good.
Okay, hold on. Okay, I got a lot of crap in my inventory.
Hold on. I'll visit somebody from chat.
No, I don't want anyone to...I don't want to
visit somebody from chat. They can like reverse fucking
Google Image search my game and find my game.
I'm not doing...no. True.
He knows.
He's paranoid.
Hey, what are you watching? He's fucking
scary. I would never be able
to have a Tarantula for a pet, never, in a
million years. They're just scary.
I'll be honest.
I know they're not, and I know that's me just
being...that's bullshit.
I know, but they're scary.
They're terrifying to me. They
terrify the fuck out of me. Alright, what do I
need to bring? I need
I don't need the watering can. Shovel, net,
pole vault, slingshot,
I don't need the umbrella. Axe?
I need a fishing rod. Yeah. Alright.
Go visit italics? People say visit
Vinnie? Where did my rod go?
But they like playing their games.
I'm not going to go invade anybody.
I don't want to be like a fucking Dark Souls
invader. Another Dark Souls
reference. There it is. Didn't Vinnie say
multiple times he didn't want to do online?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. It's not like
Okay, listen.
If a bunch of...
Let's say somebody was in their house
just sitting down like on their bed
and hanging out with some people. And then
there's like a whole group of people in another house
that want one person to
go over to that other person's house.
Dude, go to that person's house. Go
check out that person's house.
Alright, I'm going. And I'm like, I go over there and I fucking
start climbing up the window and knock on the window.
Hey, man. Hey, can I come in your
house? It's like, dude, I don't want anybody
over here right now. I know, but that's me.
That's me, man. I'm coming over, right?
No, I don't want
anybody over. Hey, okay, just come in.
Yeah, that's right. I'm on the window.
And I fucking slide in. What are we doing?
What are we doing? Can I drink these beers?
Thanks, man.
Oh, that's a good one. You got any food?
I don't know what to say.
If we want to do it, then
we'll do it. We'll set it up.
Sorry.
Oh, sorry.
Well, what? Are you going to get mad at me?
I see your face right there. You're looking at me with a mad face.
You've got a buffet-style fucking
party here. What do you want me to do?
You don't have a sneeze guard.
I visited my
drunken gerba at 3 a.m.
Oh, that's so stupid.
That's unfucking believable. All right.
Put the fire out. No!
No! No!
YouTube! Whoa!
Now it's not even scented.
All right. I'm going to the mystery
island. I got my tools.
Wait, no, I don't. I need a fishing
rod. Build it.
I did that joke yesterday. I'm not going to do
it again. I know. I mean, we're going to repeat
the same thing we just did. I'm
going to go the I am to set it. And then I'm going to
do the re thing.
But he spins. We already did that yesterday.
It's been less than 24 hours since I did that.
Remember, we just saw a frame of nudity.
So what is this?
Tire toy? Oh, cool.
All right. What does a fishing rod take?
Three branches.
Shake, shake, shake, shake.
What is that? Shake, shake, shake,
shake, shake, shake.
That's from Mystic Makers for the Nintendo 64.
I'll be playing that at some point.
Just farm tarantulas.
Just have a house of tarantulas.
Can I just have like every
tile in my house be tarantulas?
Just ride the rides in the amusement
park level. Go to the new island
already. I got to have a fishing rod, man.
And you're going to throw it in all caps
to me? A little annoyed by this.
OK, so we got, we just need
to get rid of these. Sell the twigs.
Who cares? Who even cares?
Sell. Fuck you,
Jerema. You rock. Kind of a weird
statement to make back to back
there. No, I want to sell.
Not B-A. Oh, fuck it.
I just dropped on the ground. I'm going to go on the plane
now. Good job, Jerema.
Nice one, dude. I'm sitting in my
chair right now leaning back.
Nice one, dude.
B'day. Fuck this guy. Fuck this
guy. Fuck this guy. Fuck this guy. Fuck this guy.
God, he sucks.
Who would have guessed that he would use that clip?
You may think I might be overdoing it, but do you
and if you haven't been here for a while, you might not know.
I've been waiting so long to get
that real sneeze recorded on
this stupid fucking thing. It's been
at least four or five months.
I'm sorry. I'm going to use
it. I've been waiting. I got my new toy.
I'm going to use it. Sorry.
It's the way it is. It's just the way it is.
Saltcrest
airport.
I want to fly.
Let's go to
Mystery Island.
Loop the sneeze for three hours.
People would leave. They really would.
I mean, we make jokes, but people would actually be like,
I'm never coming back again.
Time for takeoff.
Did you delete almond or Wi-Fi? Yes, I did.
Dodo one. This is Dodo tower.
Wilbert. You copy? Got a walker
who needs wings. Roger.
Roger.
There you go.
How much time do I have on here?
Is this a limited amount of time here?
We're two down and docked at the
target. First time getting
your pontoons wet on
floor. Let me brief you on the Mystery Island.
First, we run the finder's keepers
protocol here. Lumber, root,
fish, whatever. Yours if you can carry it.
Next up, break a tool. Forget one.
I can requisition or you will replacement.
Got to charge you miles though.
There's one red line item you need
to memorize like your favorite leotard order.
Anything you leave behind stays here. We don't
come back to these places.
Actually burn the flight plans afterwards. Security
reasons. Can't explain that.
Kylo Ren.
No.
Go catch some bees.
Oh, wow. Holy shit. Look at these flowers.
What? What?
I can just take them?
Why can I just take everything?
Holy shit. It's all free.
Let me get this right.
Okay, that's good. Use the shovel on
the flowers. What's the difference?
Oh, it's like the actual plant.
Use the shovel. I know
I see the cow. I'm trying not to get that
excited about it. Trying to stay
grounded.
I just take them all? No, I don't want this
theft. Well, is it theft if
they just told? The guy just told me on the dock.
Take everything you can carry.
I see a stink bug.
I missed it and I'm bucking
furious. How could I
be so stupid? How could I
mess that up?
I can sell this stuff, can't I?
Sneeze alert. What do you mean
sneeze alert? Wait, okay,
hold on. So you're talking about I just need to do
this.
Like that? Is this gonna work?
Cool. Very cool.
He gets it. He gets it. He gets it. I do know.
Are those coconuts?
Fresh coconuts.
Can I plant a coconut tree?
I hope so.
No, those are dumb. I don't want those.
Actually, I'm running out
of space.
They don't stack.
These don't stack. Do they?
No, bury it.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Let's talk to Muriel.
Great to meet you. How are you?
I'm Patty. Welcome to my
Hype-tastic island getaway.
It's not my island, but it will be.
I want to be a pop star in all pop stars
on island.
To your Germans who salt-crest fab, I love meeting new
folks, aka new fans.
Nothing better than
kicking back and chilling on an island would be
to do it forever.
Spending time on an island is the best way to find your inner calm
and hug it as hard as you
can. If I lived on an island,
how now? I'd be the
calmest, most relaxed, cow-pop star I've ever met.
Do you want to live on
my
island?
Move to Saltcrest? Oh my
gosh, yes.
I could move to any old island, but this is way better
since you'll be there.
You hear that, world? I'm moving
to Saltcrest.
Yay.
That's sarcastic.
Oh my gosh, moving. Hey, guys, so stressful. So much to do.
Gotta calm down. Center yourself,
hug it. Find your
happy place. Calm down.
How better? So all I gotta do is
get this train going and just talk to Tom Nook.
Easy. I cannot
wait to have a cheek
Saltcrest zip code.
Welcome.
See you when you get there.
Ooh, there's another rock. I see a
rock. Uh-oh.
Okay. Drop this? I gotta replant some
shit. So let me...
Okay, we're gonna do
one of each. Plant.
And then, plant, no.
Plant.
I have so many yellow ones.
Plant this, too.
I get it.
Stupid. What do you mean stupid?
Don't plant next to rock.
Why? What's going on?
Just eat the peaches.
You don't have to dig.
I don't have to dig.
Oh, I see what you're saying. I get it now.
Now I understand.
Oh, fuck it, it's already ruined, I'm curious.
Anything's already broken in front of me.
What am I gonna do?
I don't know, it's over.
Well, coconut's giving me 2,000 nook miles wasted.
No, it's not, it's not.
It's my first time on Nook Island.
It's okay, I accidentally brought home too many plants.
And I, I wasn't even looking.
Can I dig up the tree?
Do I take a coconut tree with me?
Zero out of 10.
Okay, now I can, can I, do I take this with me?
Oh my God.
Let's get a, let's take all of them.
Eat another one.
Fruits are steroids.
Wait, why is it one out of 10?
What happens if I eat 10?
10, you'll die.
That's bad.
I'll take, I'll take like three of them.
It's a charge.
Oh, okay.
These have to be planted on the beach?
Yeah, well, oh wait, what about my problem
with having beach real estate?
Fuck are you all, you, they're following me around.
I swear to God.
They're following me everywhere.
They just, they're everywhere.
Got you.
Yeah, swap it.
Swap it with these two stones, who cares?
Okay, anything else that I can do?
I got a lot of stuff.
Peaches are not stacked.
Eat the tarantula.
I'm not gonna eat the tarantula.
Shake the pine tree.
Oh, nothing.
Come on.
Come on, fish.
How do you keep getting tarantulas?
I don't know, just check my seed.
Oh, worthless.
Throw it back in.
I caught a boot.
Swap it, can I turn this into something?
Swap it with like a tree branches.
I could wear these if I found another one
and got a recipe.
You get two boots, you can make a pair of shoes.
It's funny.
Come on.
What is it, a tadpole?
Tadpole.
There's another fish over here.
A couple.
Oh, look it, there's a lot of fish in here.
I caught a carp.
I had another one, I could do a carpool.
Sure, swap it with.
I'm out of room.
Oh, I'm gonna get all the peaches and it's time to go.
I can grab the flowers.
Just actually pick them up, yeah.
Plant those goddamn flowers.
When I get back, I will.
Drop them, why?
Why would I do when you don't need peaches?
Can't I just, what's the point though?
Plant them in here.
Wait, aren't I just like leaving?
This is the mystery island.
You only just like leave after this and who gives a shit?
Wait, I come back here is what you're saying.
Oh, no you don't.
Oh, you never do, okay.
I want these flowers, I wanna keep them.
Plants are useless, aren't they?
The islands are just random.
You don't need so many.
All right, I need to make another hole.
I've already expelled that one for the cow.
I already got the cow, the cow's coming with me.
Keep plants, drop flowers.
Okay, so what should I pick up instead?
There's a centipede in here.
I hate it.
Another couple of fish?
I'll try to get another fish.
Every island has a piece of furniture in the trees.
Really?
Are you kidding?
Did I just get it?
What the hell was that?
Rattan wardrobe?
Well, okay.
Time to go.
But that's it.
I got everything I want.
Time to move.
Fun.
All right, let's go home.
What about the fish?
Huge fish.
All right, I'm gonna try to get the huge fish.
Huge fucking fish.
I'm going for it.
Come here.
Get it.
Whoa, I caught a koi.
Swap it with the mackerel.
I don't want the mackerel.
I got a koi.
There's another big one right here.
Koi is very rare.
Is it really?
Nice.
That's so cool.
It actually is.
Kind of.
Cool.
No!
It's okay.
Koi number two.
Okay.
Oh, should I get rid of the clay?
Should I throw my hat in the river?
Throw away the boot?
Okay, I'll throw the boot away.
Well, that was fun.
Time to go back.
No!
Get the boot.
Wait, get rid of the shovel.
Oh, I have a flimsy shovel, don't I?
Yeah, I can just drop this.
I'll pick the boot up.
I'm ready to leave.
That was fun.
I'm ready to go home.
I'm ready.
It is at this time in the stream
that I'm going to go appraise some of the stuff
and move stuff around,
but we're going to start doing the bits
as we're getting to the end of the stream.
We're going to hang out still.
It's time to say our goodbyes.
Probably four and a half days or so.
I'll see you guys very soon.
Hey, what's up?
Do you want to talk?
Are you getting stuff together to build us a shop?
Good, hustle.
I found something to help my things.
Here you go.
I can't carry this right now.
I was going to make that iron nugget
into an extra heavy free weight,
but having a shop's fine.
Okay.
So I'm going to put something on the screen
just so people realize that this is like kind of the end.
That people just know what's going on.
Text on the screen.
There.
So it says end of the stream, wind down.
So you know.
Library stream, please be quiet.
All right, so I got a bunch of stuff
and we're going to start going over the bits now.
Hey, that guy tag.
This is a long time ago.
This is like six and a half hours ago.
Thanks to the 1500 bits tag.
Newer USB 3.0 capture cards have no delay
so you don't have to do audio syncs with them.
Yeah, I'm just a fucking loser.
And I just, I'm using the same equipment
from like 2014.
That's pretty much all there is to it.
That's really what it is.
That's pretty much what it is.
I'm using the same equipment
from like six and a half years ago.
It is a true statement, but thanks tag.
Hey, new place after the move.
I'm going to be professional streamer, okay?
New place resolution, new year's resolution.
Thanks a lot tag, appreciate it.
Ooh, I can make sloshers, whatever they're called.
That's cool, but thanks a lot.
That's $15 from tag.
S10W update.
I know your name is slow update,
but I like saying it that way.
Thanks to the 250.
Hey, Jerm, I happen to be donating again.
Glad to see you in at least functioning condition.
Hope you're living your best life
and can't wait for the Jermania whenever that will happen.
Peace and love.
Hopefully at some point in the fall
is what it's going to be.
In the fall, that'll happen.
Wait, are you moving again?
Yes.
Staying in Las Vegas.
You can get a exclamation point
while you're moving, whatever the fuck the thing is.
I'm going to keep one of these toys.
But the game and the theater screen,
I don't really want to do that
because I'm kind of still playing it.
All right, can I make it like a fish pond?
Place item.
Oh, that's not enough room.
This needs to be like five times bigger.
Push table up against the wall.
I can't.
It's so small.
Well, I'm donating one to the museum.
But yeah, hopefully the Derma Rumble stuff.
That'll happen in the Boston Marathon.
If you don't know, it got pushed to hopefully in September.
So that's the whole point of having the stream there.
We've been sponsoring one of my friend's runs
in the Boston Marathon.
So let me go donate some of these things.
Thanks to the 250.
Thank you, GooBerry Juice of the 250.
Mini games for the mini streamer.
That's a laugh out loud moment.
Can't watch the stream tonight as I got work to do.
I hope you had fun nonetheless.
I hope your move goes well and you like your new place.
Me too.
Also make sure to give the Talics a can of beans
before you drive them out of the forest.
Thanks for the 250.
Oh, I can't donate anymore.
Wait, can I not donate anymore?
Until the museum's open?
Shit, okay.
Well, I guess that'll wait.
GooBerry Juice, thanks again for 250.
Also, I found your nudes, idiot.
Yeah, that was an accident.
That was an accident.
One accidental frame of my like bare shoulders.
Oh well.
You all know the photo.
It's okay.
Should I sell this other?
What else do I have?
Wait, I wanna plant these.
All right, I'm gonna plant.
Donald Duck, get out of the way.
I wanna plant those coconut trees.
I can't plant with other players in nearby.
Well, how do I chew them off here?
But thank you, GooBerry Juice.
Appreciate it.
I appreciate my nudes, I guess.
What?
Get out of the way.
Lizard Amiibo, thanks to the 250.
Lizard Amiibo says,
I'm sure it's my birthday on Wednesday.
Happy birthday on Wednesday.
Oh, there's plants on there.
Happy Wednesday birthday.
Not excited to spend it at home,
but I guess I'll just have to make the most of it.
Anyway, it's been a great stream already.
It's hard to go wrong with WarioWare.
The luck with whatever that stuff
you got going on this week and stay healthy.
I'm gonna try.
I tapped Donald.
Accidentally, I just touched him.
I just like poked him with the...
He got like the stick just like...
I'm trying not to poke him in the eye.
But happy birthday, Lizard Amiibo.
Wait, I'm gonna plant these up here.
Happy birthday on Wednesday.
I'm gonna go.
What?
Oh, I was trying to catch...
What the fuck?
He was hiding behind the tree.
Oh, whatever.
And here's my garden.
You got outsmited by a spider.
Nice.
Yeah, that's cool.
I'll have a big garden over there eventually.
Squiggity-squanky, thanks for the 250.
They say here it is.
I'm not sure what here it is.
It's a clip of something that says regret.
Oh, let me listen to this.
It's an ugly garden.
Well, it's gonna be ugly for a little while.
This is...
You guys hear it?
Turn this down for a second.
All right, I don't know what this is supposed to be,
but we'll find out together.
I got it.
I don't remember what this context is.
Anyways, thank you, squiggity-squanky.
Also, thank you to Archives for 500 bits.
Thank you, Archives.
Archives says,
Hey, Jerma, you may not be able to answer this question,
but I'm going to ask you
since you're one of my biggest inspirations.
When I stream, I get into this weird mode
where I feel like I'm not myself
because I'm in front of a live audience.
Do you have any experience with this?
I love streaming, but I can't seem to find the niche
where I'm comfortable and enjoy every stream.
Well, actually, I'm way more comfortable
in front of 10,000 people than I am in front of five.
So, I'm kind of the opposite way.
I could go in front of a stadium
and do anything and say anything,
but you put me in a room with less than 10 people
and I will have no fucking idea what to do.
It was 4,700 people.
Yeah, I'm rounding up.
I'm rounding up from, it was like 70,
it was 7,500 people here earlier.
I'm rounding up a little.
What, I can't round up on my resume?
Why not?
I mean, really all you can do with streaming
and trying to find what you want to do is just,
you just got to start throwing spaghetti at your fridge
and see what works, see what you like to do,
see how you feel and just try to do the best you can,
try to have the most fun you can and see what happens.
And trying to get more comfortable is,
I mean, that's a process back in like 2010.
I mean, I can't say that.
I mean, I guess I was kind of on base cam and stuff,
but I don't know.
I feel like I've always kind of just been,
I've always kind of just been
the annoying center of attention weirdo.
So, I've always been a look at me.
You know what I'm saying?
I've always been that like fucking annoying guy
that's like, hey, I have something to say today.
And everyone's like, okay, Jeremy's going to talk now.
But I guess we're all going to fucking just have to listen
for the next five straight minutes.
I'm going to pick up my phone
and just pretend to be listening.
So, I've kind of been uncomfortable doing it
for a long time.
But the best way to get better is to just to keep trying
and see what makes you comfortable.
Do the things you like to do,
play the games you like to play
and stream the way you want to stream.
It's your stream, remember, it's you.
It's you doing this.
He's wasting electricity.
No, I'm fucking tanning right now.
Come on.
Wait, where's my tanning light?
Here we go.
I wish you the best of luck though
with streaming and everything.
Heldrich, thanks for $5.
I saw you coming out of the Starbucks bathroom
chewing something,
but I was too anxious to ask you what it was.
I cannot fucking believe that.
I just read that without realizing
what they were talking about.
Thanks for $5.
A John with no H.
Thanks for the 500 vids.
Jerma after yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep.
That's fucking funny.
Very hilarious.
All these kinds of words that you wrote down here.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
You also say, I just finished that BLT.
Uh-huh, I hope you enjoyed
that bacon, lettuce and tomato sandwich,
a staple of America.
Yes, thank you for the $10, John.
I'm not even sure if you're still,
you might even be potentially banned.
I might even be speaking into the wall right now.
When is the next time you're gonna stream?
I will answer this for you.
I'll answer this for you
because the rest of your two bit comments
have been unreadable,
just absolutely un-fucking-readable.
When do I stream in the CBT time zone?
Well, I stream Pacific time,
which is the west coast of the United States.
I'm in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Thank you for your question and goodbye forever
because I probably won't see you again.
You may have been permanently banned.
Thank you, okay.
Anyways, ash686868, thanks for the thousand vids.
What a tyrant.
Here, I really have enjoyed your content
for a couple of years now
and I also love JoJo's Bizarre Adventure.
Can you say Killer Queen really loudly?
It's killer queen, laser beam.
What does that have to do with JoJo?
I don't get it.
There you go, thank you.
Thanks for the thousand vids.
The man with the baby hands, thanks for the thousand vids.
Die to Wario wear wheel, omega low.
That's just so loud.
I think I got a good 10.
Die to Wario wear wheel, sort of.
Not really though.
I'm gonna go sell a bunch of shit.
Wait, I got this wardrobe thing.
Let me see what it is.
Ooh, ugly.
And I don't want this.
Do I change?
No.
I'm not really into the wicker basket looking stuff
for furniture.
I mean, I'll keep it, but whatever.
Hey, Vibio Game, thanks for the 300 bits.
Vibio Game says, hey, Jeremy, thanks so much
for a fun run of streams the past few weeks.
I literally moved halfway around the world from home
just before all the virus stuff started
and your streams have really helped me keep
happy and sane during all the stress.
Best of luck with your move
and hope you keep safe and healthy.
Yeah, that's the worst part about moving now
is just, it was all planned.
Obviously, you try to make a plan as best you can
and then all this stuff started happening
and it's like, well, what do I do now?
Kim and I, we've been trying to figure out
the best course of action to do this
and stay healthy and avoid any potential issues
and it's just kind of tricky.
Game is too loud.
But we're gonna do our best.
That's all we can do.
Thank you, Vibio Game for the three dollars.
Moving halfway around the world seems like,
what the fuck is that thing?
Is this like a crater here?
What's this crater?
What is this thing?
Is this lava?
Look, I dug up a thousand bells.
What do I do?
What should I do with this?
Plant it back?
What do you mean plant it back?
Plant it back, bury in hole?
Put it back.
Whoa, am I gonna have a money tree?
Are you serious?
That's so cool.
I can actually have a money tree.
Wow.
Nice, that's cool.
I can't wait to see that in like nine days game time.
Hey John, with no H, there you are again.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
Jeremy, these are the last of my bits.
I'm done with the BLT joke.
Chat thought it was hilarious
and clearly your sense of humor is several levels lower
than mine because your initial reaction
was to have me timed out.
I love your stream and look forward
to the next time you use the Starbucks.
Yeah.
Yeah, my humor level is so much lower.
My humor level is just so,
like the 10 rungs down on the ladder underneath.
I can't even say it out loud.
You know what it is.
Make it permanent.
Yeah, I love, you know, let's, no, no.
All right, thank you.
See you later.
Thanks for the bits, I appreciate it.
But you've been 30 minute timed out.
That's right, I don't give those out that often.
That's a personal 30 minute timeout.
And not right now, on the night,
on the start of the, on the next,
on the night of the next start of the next stream,
it begins.
30 minutes for you.
The moment that the next stream turns on.
Oh, that's got to sting a little bit too, you don't it?
Thank you.
Hey, thanks, a normal user for the 300 bits.
Jeremy, you're stupid.
Thanks for the, thanks for the 300 money.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
The man with the baby hands thanks for 500 bits.
Of all the GameCube games you own,
you pick the one where you pick up trash for 90% of it.
That's fine.
What's wrong with that?
I wish I had a bigger net so I could catch bigger bugs.
Oh, what if I caught a bug so big
that I couldn't even lug it around?
I don't know.
Do you need a bigger net?
Morkus, Morkus, thanks for $30.
There's no message, just 30 bucks.
That's a big fucking drop.
Let me try to catch some fish here.
No message, just 3000 bits, just a bunch of money.
Thank you.
Come on, take it.
Please move the text that's fucking the animals talking.
Shit, you're right, here.
Thanks for the 30 bucks, man.
That's a lot of money just to give somebody
and there's just no messages.
Thanks for 30 bucks.
I wish I was at Olive Garden thanks for 300 bits.
Me too, man, me too, me too.
Map, map, map, map, map.
All right, there.
Kilkun, thanks for the 1000 bits.
I don't watch movies, I don't listen to music,
I don't watch TV.
What do you do to pass the time when not streaming?
Walk auto for three days?
No, talk into the mirror and pretend
that I'm in an Academy Award-winning movie.
I come up with, yeah, I make up my own TV shows in my mirror.
It's true?
You don't think it's true?
That's fine.
Oh, that's depressing.
I watch movie and TV shows.
Just not those five Universal Studios movies.
Thank you Keta Meme for the 255.
Would you say you're a boomer, zoomer, doomer, zoomer,
or the other one?
I'm just a, I'm a guy that fucking, I'm a guy.
That's it.
I'm a fucking millennial, okay?
I'm none of those things that you just described.
A crunch, thanks for the 300 bits.
First time donating a Twitch, hope I'm doing this right.
Seems like you are.
Anyways, since we brought up ET in the stream,
I'm taking the opportunity to bring up the official
Rushton ET doll when the movie came out.
They're so great and fucked up
and I'm lucky enough to have found one to own.
Wait, what?
This is supposed to be ET?
How the fuck is this ET?
That's ET.
Okay.
It seems impossible.
Bug, get the net, get the net, get the net.
I don't think I've seen this one yet.
This is like, this is a multi, I'm so bad at catching bugs.
It's depressing.
There we go.
So, thanks to the ET doll.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
Esparta Escalada, thanks for 250.
This is me watching you taking that quiz
over and over again.
Over for four seconds.
Did I get this one yet?
What is it?
Shut them ragtime music off.
This is like I live at Steakies Pizza.
Aquatine Hunger Force.
Good show.
Balloon, balloon, streamer alert.
Streamer alert, balloon, streamer alert,
streamer alert, streamer alert.
Alert.
I got it, I got it, I know I saw it.
First shot, second shot, guaranteed.
Third shot, guaranteed or I will never
stream on Twitch again, ever.
I will never stream again if I don't hit this right now.
Okay.
Pedal board?
What the fuck is a pedal board?
Wait, this is like a DJ table?
If I leave this out, is somebody gonna steal it?
Oh, cool.
Let's check my pedal board.
Achoo, achoo, achoo, achoo.
Hey, Friedl Schnitz.
Thanks for the 250.
Pleased with the love of God.
Watch Back to the Future.
I can't, not now.
Some other day.
Peaceful Haley, thanks for 250.
So you've never seen ET or Back to the Future,
but you've seen the shitty comedy Twins.
You are unbelievable.
Also, hope your penis is okay.
What?
What is it?
Oh my God.
Twins is a, I would rather watch Twins
than I can't say that.
Somebody will fucking probably murder me.
Twins is a cool movie.
Oh, the controller, right, right, right, right.
Let me sell this bugger.
Sell everything.
Sell it all.
Thank you, Peaceful Haley, appreciate it.
We also had Goiki5, more dolls from Goiki.
Thank you, Goiki.
Do you ever get the Tetris effect after you stream?
It's when you play a video game so much
when you see it when you close your eyes.
It happens to me all the time when I play Tetris.
Not really, that only happened.
It used to happen when I played Diablo 2,
but not anything recently.
Not anything recently.
I missed bits, what are you talking about, where?
Missed bits, missed bits, what are you talking about?
When, when, where?
What happened?
I got everybody so far.
Yeah, I got everybody so far.
According to my dashboard,
this is the list just going from bottom to top.
Yeah, what are you talking about?
Did they just come in?
Yeah, I'm going in descending order here.
This is how, what?
I'm going, these are bits from like three or four hours ago.
I'll get to it eventually, I'm gonna get there.
I'm gonna get there.
You skipped it already, they're not here.
I just, I'm refreshing, I don't see anything.
Not right, not where I am right now.
There's nothing here from like three or four hours ago.
Let's see if they pop up.
Let's see if they pop up eventually here.
But, let's keep going.
We left off right here, the Tetris effect.
That was Goiki for the Tetris effect.
Tar Alecron, thanks for 250.
Jeremy, you always backdate your Switch system.
You can always backdate your Switch until next week
so the game wouldn't realize that you hadn't played all week.
That way you could just resume like normal on stream
like it had only been one day.
I'd better rather just do it the way it's intended.
I'd rather do it the way it's intended.
Play it once a day.
Your text is blocking the bells.
It's fine, I wanna sell.
I'd rather just play it the way
it's normally intended to be played, you know.
I sell the coin, no, I gotta donate that one.
I can sell him a coconut tree, what the fuck?
9200 bells, holy shit.
That's a lot.
Spliceable Spleen, thanks for five dollars.
Hey Jerma, I saw a white Honda Civic
driving around Vegas the other day
with a license plate, Jerma's.
Can you confirm or deny that this was you?
Not me.
Also, I live near Henderson in the Las Vegas Valley.
Is that where you're headed in Vegas?
Thanks for all the quality content, man.
Best on your move.
There's a lot of places in Las Vegas.
A lot of places in Vegas, people to live
if they wanna live in places.
A lot of great places in Vegas.
A lot of people, about three million people
live in Las Vegas.
There's a lot of great places.
Thanks for the bits, appreciate that.
Actually, there are a lot of great places in Vegas.
He's turning into Trump.
There's a lot of great places in Vegas.
Beautiful places, wonderful places.
All the places in Vegas are great.
Is that close or far away from an Olive Garden?
Thank you, SpliceableSpleen, for the five dollars.
Hey, Kill, KillKun, thanks for five more dollars.
Are Poli-Politan Cuddles moving with you too?
No.
Tara Ollikorn, thanks for 250.
The odds that Jerma manages to move to a new house
set up as an internet properly
and find the motivation to stream is less than 0%.
If Jerma streams a real stream next Saturday,
I will give him permission to personally ban me for life.
I am, you've been around for a long time.
You've been around for a very long time,
but I do have to tell you something right now.
There are quite a few contingency plans.
If the internet does not work,
I will be streaming on Saturday.
You're about to be banned for life.
You've been around for like seven straight years.
So, I'm sorry, but we have to commit to this.
If I'm not live on Saturday,
then you're gonna get permanently banned.
You're gonna have to come back as Tara Ollikorn too.
I will be streaming on Saturday.
Like without question, less than 0%.
It is going to be 100%, 100%.
I will be live on Saturday, 100%.
I just made that.
Have fun being number three, you dick.
Thanks for the 250 though,
and have fun with your permanent ban.
Can't wait to see Tara Ollikorn 79,
or whatever the hell you're gonna have to make now.
Glow in the dark stars, thanks for $5.
He, hey, he sent a message earlier,
but it's a birthday from Lizard Amiibo.
It's Andy's birthday on the 25th.
He's an incredible dude and a fantastic friend.
He got me into watching your streams
and his friends wanted him to hear happy birthday again
from his favorite streamer.
Happy fucking birthday.
Happy birthday, Andy.
Thanks for the $5 glow in the dark stars.
Hope you have a good one.
Coming up.
Luigi man, thanks for 255 minutes into 30 minutes low mode.
I'm starving, please help.
You asked for this.
You guys wanted this shit.
Let me go look at the shopping center.
RTX42069TI, what a fucking unbelievable name.
Utility sync, I want one.
And I want a drying rack too.
No, I don't.
Why the fuck would I want one of those?
You say, hey Jeremy,
I'm happy you're branching out and playing City Skylines.
Just keep in mind that the City Skyline community swears
by absolute perfectionism and efficiency in design.
Oh, I know.
I know.
With some practice, I know you can become a loved mayor.
I think Chad is just mean.
You made a lot of progress over the last few streams.
I hope you play more of this game
and it's not just a 100 plus dollar joke.
Baby's first city builder is what you have to understand.
All right, that's the first time I ever played
any game like that.
No, my roads aren't gonna be fucking all at 90 degrees.
Some of you guys need to take a fucking bath, you know?
You need to take a bath with some Epsom salts in there
and just soak for a little bit.
I'm a more of a shower guy.
Should I pay this loan down for 10 grand?
I'll do 10,000 on it.
8600 lit, 36,000 lit.
All right, now I'm gonna deposit this money.
I get to play with like a bank account.
Look at this.
16,417, cool.
Hope you play more of it.
Um, I don't know, maybe.
Maybe, it depends.
I'd wanna get some mods for it or something.
Oh, I never got the hairstyles.
People are gonna be mad.
It's okay, it's okay.
But thank you to Rock Writing for the 300 bits.
Now realizing Jerma's villager,
walking around in an eye mask that resembles a maxi pad.
That's, that's like a,
is actually a nice metaphor for him
blindly bumbling around in the game,
but in the purest way possible.
Cool watching someone play AC for the first time.
And then we stay safe.
Everyone wishing on auto a peaceful move.
Thank you.
And thanks for imprint,
implanting that image into my brain
that I will never remove.
Until I remove this from my eyes.
Which will be later after this stream is over.
All right, what do I wanna do now before I leave?
Is that enough?
I think I did enough.
I can't really do much anymore.
Until tomorrow.
Okay, let's call it.
I, let me make sure the game's saved.
I will see you guys on Saturday,
guaranteed.
I don't care if I have to stream from my cell phone.
That guy's getting banned.
I'll make sure of it.
So let's actually do the actual wind down screen
and move there.
It's, it's, I'm not done.
Why do you guys, what's going on tonight?
This is how we do this every night.
What's going on here?
I'm a quick read, read, read, read, read, read, read.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That's just the same.
All right, anyways, let's keep going.
Thank you to a literal fraud of 500 bits.
Jerma, we're gonna need to talk about this sneeze joke.
Man, it's not funny.
We need to realize that it's not funny.
It hasn't been funny.
Please, we're trying to get it through to you.
I thought it was funny.
I'm gonna keep pressing that fucking button
until the day I die.
Ozals, thanks for the 300 bits.
Hey, Jeremy, Olive Garden music one guy here.
Just wanted to say thanks for reading my shitty joke
and turning it into an amazing one guy moment.
Can we get one last BB unit before you move?
God.
All right, okay.
I'll get, this is gonna be the, I'm gonna give it to you.
This is gonna be so, I'm gonna do as hard as I can.
I just want to see.
That's like, I clenched so hard doing that.
There you go.
I'm never doing that ever again.
Okay, God damn it.
Hey, eggs scramble, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jerma, great stream.
You looked very nice and handsome today.
Thanks.
I know eating enough healthy food
can be really tough during busy times.
Chorizo, eggs, tortillas, white onions,
couscous, Swiss chard, gold potatoes, hummus,
Ezekiel bread, walnuts, ground turkey.
Have a good week, man.
Stay hydrated.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Those are all delicious things,
but why are they all in a row?
Hey Spooky Fox, thanks for five dollars.
Here, me and my girlfriend are watching tonight
and I've been watching since like 2013.
She's really excited you're playing
Assassin's Animal Crossing.
I love you and your stuff
and also said girlfriend is thinking
of getting some rats at some point
and if she does, she might name one after you.
I'm honored.
I am honored.
I would love to be named after a rat, especially yours.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Jeremy the Rat.
That's okay, that's more of a name that you have
when you get beat up in prison
than a name that it would be for an animal,
but you know, thank you though.
Hey Keith King Crimson, thanks for the 250.
Most of the characters in Jojo
are named after music references.
Killer Queen is one of them.
Also the pro strat is to name yourself a Jojo reference
so Jermis says it out loud every time you donate.
Oh, I guess that makes sense then.
That's what your name is.
Keith King Crimson is the name of that person
that's in Jojo's, Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
Jojo's, I can hear myself talk now.
Jojo, Jojer, thanks.
I promised I would never do that again.
I didn't say I would stop streaming
if I did that again, right?
That wasn't part of the deal?
No, it wasn't, okay, good.
Hey Spunky Spade, there you are.
Thanks for the thousand bits.
Hey Jerm, I hope you're not mad at me
selling every drawing you've done in Animal Crossing.
I'm broke, but here's the bits
equal to the money I made from it.
Wait, are you the red bubble guy?
Are you the red bubble guy?
Are you the guy with like 300 listings?
It's him.
We got him.
It's the red bubble guy.
Ha, we found him.
He outed himself.
We didn't have to do anything.
The, I'm the, hey, hey Jerm,
hey Jerm, we just wanted to let you know
I'm the red bubble guy, first and foremost.
Hey, thanks for the 10 bucks though.
Thank you.
Bulbaswag Desu, thanks for the five dollars.
Can you move the elephant on the right
one space to the right, please?
It's probably bad looking, it's okay.
I'll do it, I promise.
Hey Grave Embrace, thanks for three bucks.
Disney claimed a parody video depicting Bugs Bunny
as a, what?
What the fuck?
Okay, that's fucked up.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
Hey Celestial Maid, thanks for 300 bits.
Hey Jerma, I heard you generate electricity
and miniature lightning bolts while walking.
Is that true?
If it was, I'd probably be on the cover of Time Magazine.
The guy that can create electricity with his hands?
I'd be on there.
Hey Sammy Lant, thanks for the 300 bits.
I made something to help you with rocks.
This is a little chart for me.
Thank you.
A little rock chart?
You say that as if you're not gonna be on Time Magazine
as best streamer, I mean remember the carnival stream?
Yeah, but that's already over with.
Don't you go, guys, the internet has a memory
of about four days.
We gotta go, we gotta do more.
We gotta do more shit.
Time Magazine's already moved on from that.
If I'm gonna get on the cover of Time Magazine,
I'm gonna start to figure out
how to make electricity with my hands.
But thank you, Sammy Lant, for the 300 bits.
Toasty Knight, thanks for the 400 bits.
They say a-choo, a-choo, thanks for the 400 bits.
Hey John with no H for 500 bits.
It's the BLT guy again.
Hey Jerma, just want to apologize
for my statements earlier regarding a BLT.
I don't think I mentioned that,
well now you are getting banned.
It's like, you're hanging by a thread over like the cliff
and like I'm pulling you up
and there's like three other people
and I'm gonna pull you all up.
Oh no, I'm not strong enough.
I got you all, don't worry.
I think I can, no, one of us,
you have to let one of us go.
You just looked up and said, short streamer,
I'm gonna let you go.
I'm gonna be like, that's the guy I'm letting go.
Like you just made my decision so much easier.
You don't want me to have to use my like super strength
and pull everybody up.
All right, fine.
You're not big enough to save all three of us.
Well, you would be let go too.
You would, how many ropes do I have over the edge here?
Am I gonna have to let go of all of you?
Who am I pulling up here?
If you were holding onto the rope,
you're not gonna do this.
You're not gonna say this stuff
when you're hanging by the rope.
Pull me up, got it, got you.
Let them all go.
Now that's just, that's just a sicko thing.
That's just, you're fucking crazy.
You're pulling them all up as much as you can.
Hey, churro captain, thanks for 500 bits.
Hey, Jerma, are you gonna be using a Nook Miles ticket
when you move to your new place?
Yes, yes.
Let us go, we're nine inches off the ground.
You're so fucking funny.
It's so funny when I hear these things.
I go.
Let them go, let them all go.
Let them all go.
Just let them all go.
Ah, people are screaming.
Oh God.
Screaming at all caps.
Hey, egg scramble, thanks for the 250.
Yo, also my 21st birthday on Tuesday.
I'm gonna spend it alone in quarantine,
but your VODs are gonna get me through it.
Can you give me your favorite grocery list
as an early birthday present?
Yes, Cliff Bars, a bunch of them.
Campbell's Soups, a bunch of them.
Tons of Cliff Bars, make sure, and this is,
you might be able to,
oh, here comes another advertisement for a company
that there's no money involved here.
Cliff Bars are, they're delicious.
They're very filling and they'll carry you a long time.
I got a bunch of them.
Also, stuff like boxed macaroni and cheese
is really, really easy to store.
Soups, canned soups are very easy to store,
and they're good.
Tuna fish, tuna fish, it keeps forever,
and it can be used in a million different places.
You can eat that shit out of the can.
There you go, that's my grocery list.
Don't forget baby food.
Yeah, you get that too.
Eight-year-old diet?
No, I mean, we're talking about,
we're talking about the quarantine stuff,
and stuff they can easily,
guys, I'm not eating tuna fish out of the can every day.
We're talking about preparing for potentially
having to be in your house for two or three weeks.
Non-perishables, that's correct.
Peanut butter is another good one.
Rice is another good one.
Although, rice is kind of hard to find
during these kinds of people that go into the store
and they're buying up everything they can.
Peanut butter is great.
Beans are great.
If you like refried beans, just get a bunch of them.
You can just eat them.
Do what you can, right?
I could eat refried beans every day.
Stop talking about tuna, sorry.
But I wish you the best of luck.
Everybody around the world is currently
at a standstill right now,
hoping that this shit just goes away
and we can just kind of hunker down and get through it.
Let's hope so.
Hey, TarAlecran2.
Hey, Jerma, I'm holding the TarAlecran2 username hostage.
If TarAlecran wants TarAlecran2,
I need a bean burrito.
Well, that has nothing to do with me.
That is between the two of you.
That is between the two, that is between you two.
That's between you and TarAlecran2
and TarAlecran is between you two, the two of you.
Nothing to do with me.
Hey, GooBerryJuice, thanks for the 300 bits chat
whenever someone mentions JoJo.
No hate, I know everyone has their tastes.
We don't all have to like the same things
to love each other.
Also, there's new hairstyles in AC Mirror,
one of which looks like yours.
I just don't even, I have no say in any of this
because I've never seen the damn show.
I don't even know what the show is.
That show could star vegetables and fruits and shit
and I would be like, okay, that JoJo's Bizarre Adventure,
JoJo's a banana and he has his band of strawberries
and fruits and shit and like vegetables.
I'd be like, okay, that's a weird TV show, I guess.
I wouldn't even, I don't even know what it would be.
Seems like it could be, I don't know, I've never seen it.
Hey, Kirunch, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey, LateBits, sorry about that.
Don't have to say sorry, we're just hanging out.
I just got confirmed as far as I know for my first job
and I've been wanting to donate to you for a while.
Wanted to do it the day I started it,
but it looks like you'll be off streaming when it happens,
so I'll send them over what I currently can early.
I'm a newer viewer.
I just think you're genuine cool and I wanna help out,
I wish you the best during your move
and during our weird pandemic times
as well as everybody in chat.
I really appreciate that, but take care of yourself.
Make sure you're taken care of.
Make sure you're taking care of your loved ones,
your friends, your family.
Take care of you, I hope you do.
And thanks for checking out the stream when you did.
Say you're a newer viewer, so I'm not sure how new,
but thank you and good luck on the new job.
We had 250 from Pigeon.
Thanks, Pigeon.
Hey, Germa, it's your favorite bird.
It's been a while, but college plus a boyfriend
has hindered my ability to watch all your streams.
Though I try to keep up on the archive.
Cue the you don't have to feel pressure to watch spiel.
I was gonna do it.
You already took the words right out of my mouth.
But now with all my classes moving online,
I have a lot of more time.
Wish I could tell you that you've been super productive.
Oh, I've been super productive.
But honestly, I've just been catching up on video games
and I've been able to watch your streams again.
It's good to be back.
Love you.
You don't have to, yeah, yeah, yada, yada, yada,
the thing I was just gonna say.
If you have time and you're around
and you wanna hang out, then by all means, absolutely.
But I think we're all kinda catching up on video games
and sort of stuff to do in your house.
He hates us.
What?
Why did you just write that?
Doctor says, boyfriend sucks.
Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
Thanks a lot, Pigeon.
Good to see you again.
Hey, Keith King Crimson from JoJo's Bizarre Adventure.
Thanks for the 250.
What if you went to Olive Garden
and ordered endless breadsticks
but the waiter brought out a single,
really long breadstick that stretched all the way
to the back of the kitchen?
And no matter how much you ate, more breadstick
just kept coming out of the kitchen with no end in sight.
Well, I would be a little disgusted
because how would that not touch other people?
How would that gigantic breadstick?
Some people are gonna be stepping over that.
Somebody might bump into it.
Somebody might put their shoe on it.
Somebody's gonna step on it.
I'm not eating that.
No, it's gonna be limbo.
But what if it's in a tube
and it comes out the end of the tube?
I would ask very, very, I'd eat some of it.
And after about two or three loaves of bread worth of bread,
I'd say, who's the guy that spent 40 grand
to make this a reality and why is it only on my table?
I see over there, that couple over there
has regular breadsticks.
And that group of friends over there
has regular soups and shit.
Why are you doing this to me?
And then you hear just a wheeze laugh
deep within the kitchen, just like a fucking wheeze laugh.
I was gonna do the wheeze laugh.
I was gonna smash it out, but I didn't
because I didn't wanna exert my chest cavity.
Pretend I did.
Hey, let's run those credits.
And again, I will see you guys.
Garin, Teed, Saturday, Garin Teed.
If there is no stream on Saturday, then I have hell to pay.
Saturday afternoon, I will be live at Garin fucking Teed.
I gotta stop swearing.
You know, my mother told me to stop swearing.
I tell you that.
My mother caught one of my streams recently.
She's like, oh, that was like really interesting
and really fun.
Can you stop, you gotta stop swearing.
And I was like, ma, ma, ma, ma, ma, ma.
She's like, no, I want you to stop swearing.
And I'm like, ma.
So as of Saturday, I'm gonna say 25% less swear words.
We're gonna clean it up a little bit.
So instead of fuck, it's gonna be shoot.
And instead of shit, it's gonna be crap.
And instead of booger, it's gonna be snot.
I don't know.
Shoot.
Crap is just as bad.
No, it's not.
I'm kidding.
My mother said three swears telling me in the sentence
to tell me to stop swearing, to stop swearing.
And she swore like four times.
We're a swearing family.
Anyways, here come the credits.
They should be showing up on your screen now
in about 10 seconds or so.
Here they come.
Thanks everybody for your subs.
All of the new subs, all tubs, all the ongoing subs,
all the subs that maybe you subbed like 12 months ago
and you never did.
Maybe you got a community sub from somebody.
Maybe you subbed like four years ago or whatever.
Thanks for even considering.
Appreciate it.
All of you.
We're gonna finish up the bits.
We have a couple more to do.
We have Cosmocrat for the 300 bits here, three bucks.
Hey, Jerma, awesome stream as always.
You should play Hearthstone on Saturday.
Not gonna happen.
We'll buy you packs.
Also really stupid, outdated question.
When you fake proposed to Kim on your moving to Vegas stream,
was she in on it?
Yes.
I would not do that to somebody.
That's so fucking horrible.
Play Smite.
Is this like a, are you guys plants?
Are you guys plants?
What's with the plants here about like play Smite?
It's working.
Just wanna let you know, your scheme is working.
You've got me thinking about it again.
What I'm gonna do now is I'm gonna go lie down in my bed
with my iPad and just look at all the stats
for all the gods that have released
in two and a half, three years.
It's working.
Hey, FrozenThor516, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, today when I was watching this stream,
my country New Zealand went into level three lockdown
and going to level four lockdown
at 48 hours because of the virus.
I'll be at home for a month.
Luckily, on the plus side, I'll be able to tune
into all your live streams for one month.
Stay safe out there, Jerma, and you chat.
Lots of love to all of you.
Also side note, no game you ever played has ever bored me.
I dare you to find a game I will hate you playing.
Please step right this way to Mountain Blade
or Europa Universe sales or Crusader Kings.
No one will want me to play those games.
I don't know you guys say those things.
If I play Crusader Kings, I will actually lose fans.
People that are like fans of this channel
will flip 180 degrees if I play Crusader Kings
for more than four or five hours.
I'm just telling you facts.
I would be so unbearable.
People would be, I couldn't even, you know.
See you guys on Saturday.
An anonymous cheer right at the very end, $10.
No message, just an anonymous amount of money.
Take care of yourselves.
Enjoy this week coming up here.
I will be back on Saturday at the latest.
I have to reiterate this one more time.
The latest you will see me is Saturday afternoon.
And that is a 100% guarantee this should not take very long.
Take care.
Much love to you.
Stay safe.
See you soon.
Take care.
Missed bits.
I did?
No, I didn't.
Are you guys gonna raid Joel?
How's he doing?
Joel, what?
Raid Joel.
Playing Super Mario World?
All right, let's go diarrhea over on Joel's channel.
See you guys next week.