Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Counter-Strike Global Offensive Gameplay Commentary.
And before I get into this video at all, I gotta thank special thanks somebody for this Beta Key.
Because this game, if you don't know, is very, very hard to get a Beta Key for.
You are more likely to be struck by lightning than to get a Counter-Strike Go Beta Key.
So thank you so, so much to the person that gave this to me.
Because I didn't get this on my own, somebody gave me this.
And they don't want their name in the video, and I can totally understand that.
But Anonymous, thank you so, so much dude. You don't know how long I've been looking for one of these damn keys.
And a follow-up to this, if you want to get into the Beta and you don't know how,
there is really only one way you can do it.
You have to go to the Counter-Strike website, or I think you can do it through Steam as well.
You have to do their survey. There's a Counter-Strike survey you can take.
You fill it out and you get put on the list, I guess.
I did it a long time ago and I still haven't been called.
But I'm pretty certain that's the only way you can do it.
So now, what do I think of this game? Do I think this is a fun game?
I've played it for a couple hours now. I've got maybe three or four hours into it.
And this game is great. It is a lot of fun guys.
I can't wait till this actually comes out. Because the best part about Counter-Strike,
to me at least, in my opinion, is not the default game modes.
When this game finally releases and the modders and the map makers get their hands on it,
that's when I have the most fun in Counter-Strike.
I'll give you two very good specific examples. One of them is Jailbreak.
If you've never played Jailbreak before, it is hysterical.
It is one of the funnest mods I've ever played in any game.
And I probably dumped in, god, probably a hundred plus hours into CS Source's Jailbreak.
And when they finally get their hands on it and they make CS GO Jailbreak,
you better believe I'm going to be playing that a ton.
I actually might do videos on that, to be honest.
There could be some really funny content coming out of Jailbreak.
Very briefly, I'll tell you what it is. I didn't even tell you what the hell the mode was.
Jailbreak is there's two sides. There's the prisoners and then the prison guards.
And the whole goal is you're supposed to follow the rules as the prisoners.
They open up the gates and they go,
Prisoners come out, everyone listen to me.
And I want you all to walk ten paces to your left.
And Simon says jump.
And if you didn't jump, they would just shoot you.
So it's stuff like that.
And if you were a prisoner, every time I was a prisoner, I would never follow the rules.
I would always like just, oh, Simon says jump.
And then I would just run at him and just start stabbing him.
And sometimes it would work and you could pick up their gun
because you don't start with a gun.
It's just crazy. Maybe I'll do a video. I don't even know.
We'll see in the future.
But other than Jailbreak, really, probably Ice World.
I know there's going to be a new Ice World.
There's always an Ice World in every Counter-Strike.
So Ice World, probably Snow World, but there was a Snow World, wasn't there?
Just that tiny close quarter death match where all the guns are on the ground.
And then you could only buy things if you were standing in the middle.
But it was almost impossible to stand in the middle because the map was so tiny
and bullets are just flying everywhere.
I can't wait.
But anyways, let's start talking about what's actually happening on the screen
and what I think of this game for real.
The actual game, not the mods or the potential maps they're going to make for it.
This game is pretty fast paced.
Most games in Counter-Strike will last less than one or two minutes for the whole round.
And that's great because if you don't know, when you die in this game, you don't come back.
It's just like Arena Mode in Team Fortress 2 or the Search and Destroy in Call of Duty.
Same exact premise, when you die, you're permanently dead.
And it is so refreshing knowing that these rounds are not going to last more than two minutes.
I have OCD, I got ADHD, guys.
I am one of those people that cannot stand no action for more than 10 seconds.
If I die in Counter-Strike at the beginning of a round,
I am so tempted to just hit escape and go to quit game, exit game, and go find another lobby
because it's like pulling teeth for me.
Sitting there for more than a couple minutes is pretty much the equivalent
of me punching myself in my own face 10 times.
I don't know if it's like that for anybody else, but it's like that for me.
And really besides that, the only real complaint I have about this game
has nothing to do with the guns, has nothing to do with the gun mechanics.
Because, I mean, they're all pretty balanced.
The recoil is pretty easy to get used to.
The reload times can be kind of slow on some of the weapons,
and the AK-47 is a little odd with its recoil.
But for the most part, it's a pretty balanced game.
The problem that I have is, shooting somebody in the chest or in any of their body parts,
it takes a lot of bullets to kill them.
And especially when you can get that one lucky headshot on somebody and kill them instantly.
And I know that it has a lot to do with Kevlar in this game.
But really, when I come around a corner, I've jumped around corners before spraying,
and I've unloaded almost a whole clip on somebody's chest.
And then I just get insta-headshotted.
And it's really discouraging, and I know I have to just practice on my aiming,
get those headshots down.
But it can get discouraging, especially when you get the jump on somebody.
That's my only real complaint I have.
So that is going to wrap up this particular video on CSGO.
I'll leave you with a pretty gruesome headshot I got on somebody.
So hopefully you enjoy that, and I will see you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.