Mount Fiji. Mount Fiji. Yeah, yeah. Whatever, Mount Fuji. It's fine.
Somebody asked me what my favorite mountain was in the pre-stream chat and I said Mount
Fiji because I like Fiji water. And I thought for three or four seconds that Mount Fiji,
Fiji was a Fiji mountain. That's where it came from. But that's not where it comes from.
Maybe it is. I don't know. The Fiji River? Fiji pond? I don't know. I thought it was Mount
Fiji for 10 seconds. And I was like, no, it's actually Mount Fuji. They're not different
things. Fiji is the place. The mountain is Fiji. Right. Fiji is a country. Okay. Well,
is there a mountain in Fiji? Whatever it is, that's the one I like. That's my favorite mountain.
Anyways, probably there's exactly one mountain. Well, that's good. That's my favorite one.
Show us your mountain wallpaper. I don't have mountain wallpaper. Not anymore. It's been
changed. And you don't get to see it. That's for me only. But today we're going to finish
Gotcha Force. I have to sell all my toys today. I've got to give them away and sell them and get
rid of them. I got boxes of them. Mom's making me do this. She came into my room and said,
it's time for you to get rid of all these toys. They're everywhere. It's ridiculous.
Don't need to keep every toy from when you were 15. Just come on, get the f**king out of here,
Ma. I want to get rid of them. I'm 35. Whatever. I have like toys and s**t. I like them.
Leave me alone, Ma. Break. Toys from when you were 15. She doesn't understand. Voting to ban Mom.
Don't talk to your mother like that. I didn't. She left the room and I said, f**king what the f**k,
Ma? Shut up. The door was closed. She was gone. I went, yes, mother. The door closed and I went,
shut up. Stupid dumb Mom. We're going to finish Gotcha Force though. I feel like we can get this
done. Very fun game. We're going to see the end. Hopefully. Vito, please. All right, I'll get to it.
I'm going to, I'm getting to it. You want to see Vito so bad. He's going to be on the screen in
about five seconds. Camera's not on. There he is. Be hurry, Vito, Vito. There, there is Vito.
It's the name of the character. I'm so glad that you wanted to see him so badly.
There's a lot of enthusiasm here. I'm seeing Vito in all capitals.
Holy s**t. You guys really want to see him. All right. Give the people what they want.
Anyways, let's go. Welcome back. I'm going to finish this today and then tomorrow we're going
to play Patapon, which by the way, I actually looked into Patapon and it was a PSP game. Oh,
wow. Patapon. It's cool. It's such a good game. You should play it. I thought this was like a two
to three hour experience. Patapon is like a 20 hour game. How, how is Patapon as long as like
The Witcher 2. Don't worry about it. Oh, he doesn't know. I'm pogging in real life so much right now.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to try it. See if I play the whole thing. Witcher started at three. Don't,
they don't make games like they used to. All right, let's get going. We have our team. If
you don't know what gacha force is, you're in for a huge pog moment. Actually, let's do this one.
This one, this one's like dark. Fight in the air battle. All right. Air battle, huh? Well,
this ain't going to work. You want to see your beautiful face? We cannot. Oh, look at this mess.
It's a mess. I have to get rid of them. I have to start to, I'm not going to use some of these.
All right. It's an air battle. So we need air. Just give, I gotta get rid of them all.
Just delete the force. Okay. What? Why are you all the way over here? All right. Wind Valkyrie
and then ice Valkyrie. Where's the airplane? Air, actually airplanes first. It's an air battle. For
God's sake, then bring Valkyrie, a sniper girl, battery man. No, maybe revolver gunman. Just to
like take people off. What should I use? Do all the tornado Valkyrie. I still got money and
soldier and one more. I can do the ninja. It's always in the way. I went to level two, a ninja.
There we go. All right, let's do the air battle. Giant sword, ghost samurai. Um, we'll see. This
might have been a dumb idea. We'll find out. Jump King waiting. I deleted my save. It's not
going to, I'll never open that game ever again. Like that's a fact. I, I ain't ever opening that
game again. Why would I do that at this point? I deleted my save. Download a new save. I'm not
going to download a new save. I've, why do I, I've, the only reason why I opened it is because I had
like four drinks at that point. Ooh, sorry. Get up in the air. It was four whole drinks.
Yeah. I didn't, I didn't, I didn't just tell you that I, I couldn't walk. I just said I had some
drinks and it was like, ah yeah, let's play Jump King. That's funny. And then I deleted the save
accidentally. All right, this is not going to work out. They're not fast enough. They're not even
remotely fast enough for this. It was five at that point. Well, whatever. Yeah, they're not fast enough.
I'm just being outpaced completely. This ain't going to happen. The only, you know how this
happens with this character only. That's going to fly into people and got it. Okay. Same deal.
Again, any other game waiting room? Well, I'll see you tomorrow. That's how long you're going
to have to wait. See you tomorrow. This character is actually really good. Atapog. I'm looking, I
look, people have told me to play that for like a year. I'm looking forward to it. So it's an RPG.
I thought it was a rhythm game. It is a rhythm game. It's both.
Really? Is it like a story? Yes. Is it a good story or is it a story that's in the background
because it had to be there? Give me the truth. It's good. Okay. Okay. It has nudity. Don't stream it.
I think I'll be all right. I don't think that's going to be a problem. By the way, I got my ass
kicked. Is this the last person? No, no, no. I got one more wing person. Oh, you're that high in the
air. I got to get in close. Kill. Quit. Okay. Only two or three more. This is it, I think.
Should be it. I didn't knock that off. How? All right. This is my last person. I got to,
okay, here we go. Let's see if the spam can help me here. Die. Yes. Yes. When's it going to have a
meltdown? Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Oh shit. That actually, hey, what was it? What was it? What was
it? What was it? What was it? What happens every time? What happens every time? What happens every
time? What was it? What was it? Come on. What just fell and like crashed down here? Yes. We
sensor bar. It happens every time. It's sitting on top of my monitor. And if I move my desk even
like a little bit, it just falls and crashes down. And it's, dude, it's crazy when that happens.
It's like, it weighs like less than like 12 ounces. It goes like crash. It's crazy. It's
worth reacting that harshly over. Oh, I got another plane. The crashes and I go, what the fuck?
Even though the thing weighs less than a 10th of a pound. He's just overreacting for the camera at
this point. Asshole. Wait a minute. What? I got one. Gatling gunner. Ooh. All right. I thought the
game crashed for a second. I was like, okay, he's going to keep going. Violet attacker.
Oh, funny Gatling go brr. Oh, all right. Let's make an actual team now. Let's see. Long range
and grenade and then Gatling gun. The gadget booker was in the military. This great man with a
pivoted jaw sweeps away the bad guys with deadly fire from his special Gatling. What was a pivoted
jaw? I feel like his jaw goes sideways at that point. Pivoting jaw? What does that mean?
Uh, this is the fastest one, I guess. Vulcan power beam and napalm bomb. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's a plane. That's all you need to know. Who cares? This one on the other hand, this is
different. This thing's got a bomb. Both power bomb. Fighters have got your book who was created
during the interplanetary mega board war. He can attack the ground with bombs. All right.
I'll try it. Let's, let's use the planes. Are these just the exact same things have different
colors? Yeah, they are. But they're still good. This thing's level three. And now with the Gatling
gunner. I want to try, I want to try you first actually. I feel like I'm really going to like
this character. All right. 420 though. That's a lot. Who else can I put in here? Exclamation point.
Up dog. What the? Dude. Uh, I can't use you. That's, that's good. I'll give it a try. Um,
man is home. A big cockroach parade. Please help me Vito. There are lots of death force
boards that look like roaches. Let's go. Ever played custom robo behind me? We'll play that
eventually. I want to play this first because I remember playing this game when I was just a
child. Holy shit. This is awesome. Oh my God. It has so many, wait, what, what does the grenade do?
There's a very little bomb. That's cool. Long reload, but he can't move when he shoots. It's
to stand still. So it's hard to, how many are there? I guess I can jump and move and do it
like that. But I can't, I have to stand still. Feel pretty good. Probably for like those big
planes would be good. This is what this whole mission is. Killing the cockroaches. Do we get
any bigger cockroaches? When's the next Brownie rant? Oh, let me tell you. Brownie rant waiting
room. What the fuck is that? I don't, what do I need to know what you mean by that?
In before. Tell me you guys just, I swear there's just AI characters in here that have been
programmed to just write something strange every day. Just, I, you know, let's just program my
fucking weird bot. Just write weird shit every day. What am I going to write today? What's
a bot going to just pull from the random? How about in before bigger cock? That makes sense.
Gosh, of course though. This is interesting. What is this? Monsters? Bugs? Oh, wow. I don't care
about this at all. Hopefully. Hey, did he read it? I want to see if he reads this. He did. He
always does. He always does. So it's perfect. Tomorrow I'm just going to write, put a cheese
sandwich down my underwear. It took me two full hours to clean it up. Maybe I can probably read
that tomorrow. Weirdos get out. Weirdos get out. Oh, I don't think you want to say that. I think
that's like, Oh, that's, I would have to leave. You're getting rid of me. I don't think this
channel would collapse if that was the case. Wait, there's a person. No weirdo. Weird. Don't,
don't weirdos here at that point. It'd be like, all right, well, I'm, I think I'll be done at
that point. It'd be like, nah, I think that's good. I'd be streaming to my mother. It's the only one
that would be left. She's watching your streams right now. Oh, maybe I think I have the combination
of this. No, of course not. Of course not. Your mom heard you say the in before line,
but that's all right. My mother knows this is a comedy stream. It's okay. It's just, it's a,
it's a comedy stream. You know, we talk about comedy, we do thought projects. She knows,
she's on, she knows it. This is supposed to be comedy. And sometimes we play games that Jeremy
likes. I mean, no, we don't. Sometimes we play video games that Jeremy wants to play. That happens
to be the last few days. No, you have to play games that I like. Oh, no, is this the McDonald's
thing again? No, it's not the McDonald's thing again. You guys know how many video games exist?
To be able to play your favorite video game, I'd have to stream like 10,000 more times.
You know what I mean? Like everyone has a favorite video game. I can't play your
favorite video game. How does this bomb work? You just drop it? I can't tell where it's going.
This thing's dead already. Benched. I was gonna say flying around. My favorite video game is called,
my favorite video game is, Jerma hits himself in the crotch with a hammer.
Yeah, I know the remake of that one wasn't very good. You know, just the original, you know,
they tried to bring it back and it's like, dude, you hit yourself in the crotch with a hammer and
like fucked up your shit. It's already been destroyed. Like you're going to try it again?
You can't, no, the remakes suck.
No, I missed. No, I didn't. Yeah, I did. This guy's tough. Yeah, they, these two are actually tough.
Kind of, okay, be quiet. Oh, you fucking dick. Come on. I got the advantage right here.
Oh, this is the perfect thing that could have happened. He's so far away and his movement is
terrible. Wow. I can't believe that is that. What a spawn. Unbelievable. Liar gunner. I already have
one of these and I don't really like them. Okay. How, what do we got? Uh, uh, too many planes,
too many planes. I want to replace one of these planes. One of my, I want to try this again
because I feel like it didn't get a good representation of what it was. Try it again.
Let's have you go first. Just change the music. That's all we ask. Um, you want to turn the music
off? No, no, no, no. Music's driving me insane. Oh no. Yes, please turn it off.
You don't like that every single five minutes.
All right, let's drop the bomb. I get it. How big is the explosion?
It's all right. You got it. You really got to time it though. Let's see if I got it.
Uh, kind of sucks actually. This is really bad. How am I supposed to hit anybody with this? All
right. I, that was a direct hit and it was awful. Bench. $250 for this. Let's see how many fucking
skins you bought in Fortnite. How many, how many Fortnite skins? How many, how many like
counter-strike skins do you have? You get a knife yet? Nah, but fuck this guy for getting a GameCube
game. You have two hats. Has the hat market like crashed or are people, is people still buying
them? Are they still expensive? I could have emulated this for free and you could have,
you could have bought a knife at Walmart and then spray painted it green. Do we really have to have
this conversation? What is value? Somebody kill me because I can't aim at, I just, I blow this,
just get this, get this plane. I can't just, what would you do with a green painted knife?
I don't know. You would, you would put it in your closet and look at it from time to time.
Ah, yeah. That's the green one. Where's the red one? There it is. Look at it for a second.
What am I talking about? I'm talking about how spending $2,000 on a CSGO knife skin is the same
thing as just buying a real knife in real life and putting crayons on it and having like your
friends come over and look at it. Funko puff. Yeah. So, so we, what, what's with the criticizing
of what use or I spend our dollars on? If I buy a thousand Funko puffs, who gives a shit?
If you buy a $2,000 CSGO knife, who cares? If I get gotcha force, it's like my favorite game and
I want to collect it and it's $200 and what? What's the difference? There is no difference.
What about somebody said collecting bongs? I don't know. It's your money. What are you going
to tell you? What? I think I have an opinion of you collecting bongs. Did you have the space for
this? Well, that's all. That's my only, here's my only question. Do you have the space for this?
Yeah, I got plenty of space. All right, then collect as many fucking bongs as you want.
He's endorsing bong collection. I only smoke tobacco out of my bong with a happy face.
All right. Well, then you can use a tobacco bong as all this shit is the same.
When you go over somebody's house and they have like 25 bongs with like,
this one's got like Jimi Hendrix on it. This one's like green. It has lava lamps.
You do realize that you probably look at your like TF2 backpack.
It's all the same shit. This is like intro. It's like collecting things and who cares?
Is this consumerism? All right. I can tell you guys are bored. I can tell. I can smell it from a
million miles away. Unfortunately, your boredom is going to have to continue for the next four
to six hours because I'm going to play my fucking $2,000 CSGO knife skin until I'm satisfied looking
at it with all my friends over. And I lost because of you. The argument is you could have
emulated it. Okay. So I, all right. Yeah. So I, I can like, I can watch a streamer open up knives
and like, I can watch him hold a knife in his hands. I don't own it though.
I'm pretending to own it. Right? That could happen. I could download a JPEG of a CSGO knife
and put it on my background on my desktop. Is that the same thing? That mission was too hard.
Do I look like I know what a J? Wait, you guys don't know JPEG? Holy shit. In the middle of this,
somebody gave a fucking ton of money. Do I know what emulation is? I used dolphin like a month ago.
You guys are fucking bored. Uh, phylatrial lich gave $250 in that's 25,000 fucking bits.
And they say, here's money to buy another copy of Gotcha Force just for you to flex on chat.
I don't want another copy of Gotcha Force. Donating to millionaires. Are we going to do,
are we going to bring that up again? Worth house. All right. I'm just going to play my game and I'm,
I'll see, I'll talk to you guys like an hour. See you guys in an hour. He's not denying. We've
already gone over the fact that I don't have a million dollars. I don't have a million dollars.
I'm not a millionaire. Why do we have to keep talking about this?
He's lying. He's lying about the company he owns. That would be fucking, that would be,
I think that's probably illegal. Offshore accounts. No, I don't have any of those.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. All right. I see it. I see it. I see it. He's a liar.
Liar. Let's see. What does it say? My net worth between one and $5 million in 2019.
Okay. This is, this is one, this is so inaccurate. It's always like a joke.
Do you guys know that these websites have no fucking idea? They have absolutely no idea.
You know, these websites pull from how many like clicks your website got.
Monthly traffic was 68,000 people per month, which that means he's worth $60 million dollars.
Somebody showed me one of these websites before and it said I was worth like $200 billion dollars.
Yeah, that's great. So I'm worth like the total GDP of like 50 countries on earth. Sure. I guess.
Okay. Sure. Five million fucking dollars. Get the fuck out of here. Celebrity money.
God, this is probably like a data mining website. Like, why are you clicking these?
E-celebrity cash. Well, let's wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Yeah. Calculator stats.com.
German nine a five's net worth is approximately $112,000.
He's a millionaire. He's a fucking millionaire. How much money did German make today? $49.
Let me buy him my second Lamborghini. That's all right. Okay. Okay. Guys, the main
YouTube channel, I don't want to be completely transparent about the, okay. The main YouTube
channel makes about, uh, four to $500 a month. So no, it's not worth $112,000. It's more like
12,000 or like 8,000. What about the second channel? The second channel as of, as of like
this, I don't make, okay, listen, I'm going to be, let's be transparent here. So the second channel,
I do not have a majority revenue from. And as of bringing on potentially two or three more editors,
I am not taking a cent from the second channel. I don't, I don't receive any money from it. It's
going to be going out to the editors. I'm not going to take a dollar. Zero. As of, because otherwise
I wouldn't be able to, I wouldn't be able to afford to pay. You know, if we have like four or
five editors on that channel, I mean that that channel doesn't make enough money to support
like four people a month. So I've just, I'm just, that's just, I'm not going to take any money.
Why would I do that? But that the main, we're talking about the main channel. The main channel
doesn't like, you're not paying your redditors. You're wait, wait, wait, what? Yes. I don't,
the editors right now get a majority of the ad revenue from that channel. Yes. Wait, what? You
guys didn't think I was doing that? And real soon, my, my like cut from the second channel is going
to be zero. Absolute zero. I'm not going to take any money. I'm just going to, I need to, I need to
be able to be sustainable to have another two or three people on. It's paying his redditors.
What the fuck is this? Bench the bomber. I'm getting accused of things here. Net worth,
Forbes 100 list, Jeremy Albertson, $985 billion. All right. TLDW, too long, didn't watch.
Collecting crayons is the same thing as me buying gotcha force and stamps and shit and coins.
Too long, didn't watch. Stamps are cooler. No, they're not. You think a stamp is cooler
than gotcha force? No, they're not. Now I'm angry. All right, here we go. Here comes the gunner.
No, I caught, I was stuck to them. All right, here we go. $112,000. What's that? What are
they even calculating? How many subscribers the channel has? Gotcha force is an emulated
stamp collection. Thank you. Oh, mirror subs and views. How does like a subscribe to the
channel translate to how much money the channel is worth? Is that what somebody would, is that
what somebody would pay me right now to own that channel or something? Like if I sold it at auction,
would I be like, I want $112,000 for my website. One to five million, $112,000, $10 billion.
Ooh, I want this guy. This guy looks cool. Look at how cool this guy is.
It's the German 985 social media platform. But that's got to be like the biggest hilarious scam
ever to pull. Like, can you imagine? Like if all of my entire presence online,
right? Like say every channel, every post, every Twitter, everything, Twitch, everything. What do
you guys think would be worth? If I would be like, I'm selling it and I'm selling it to any company
that's willing to pay for it. Probably like 250,000, half a million. Half a million you think?
Okay, if somebody paid me half a million dollars for this, that would be the biggest joke ever.
Because the second that it became clear that the German 985 Twitter turned into Crest toothpaste,
you would all leave and no one would ever click anything. It would be the biggest scam ever.
Oh, the German 985 Twitch channel just became like A and B realty group. You would see the
most unsubscriptions from a channel in a one minute period ever in the history of this website.
And then the channel would be worth like 200 dollars that next year.
I would add that. So that would be like a 500,000 dollar just to give for free.
Just do that but make another channel. I just have a mustache. I don't want another normal night.
Normal night sucks. Just put a mustache on and just have a permanent voice changer
like this. Like that. Just like this forever. And speak with an accent. So I speak with an accent.
And people will think that this is a German. No, I don't know who that is. No.
Awful. It doesn't matter how awful it is. As long as I can be consistent with it.
Like for instance, thank you to Silent Serenity for the 250.
Hi, German. Now that you're running for public office, we're requesting that you release your
tax returns. Will we all unsubscribe if you don't release them within the month?
Uh, no, there's no reason. I don't have to do that. There's no reason why I'd have to do that.
Thanks for the 250 though. I would, if I did it for long enough. If I did it for long enough,
I would be able to fucking keep that up forever. It's a good idea. Not consistent. Yes, it was.
What accent do you think I'm doing? An accent. I don't know. Doesn't have to be anything.
It just can't be me talking like this. Do the Boston accent.
Hehehe. Just do Bernie for the rest of the stream. No, I'm not going to do that.
You know, you guys, you know, you guys are breaking the number one rule that every
friend is supposed to not break. Talking about money. How much money do you make?
Come on. I thought we were supposed to be friends. It's rude. Fucking rude. Hello.
Bench the bomber. Bench the bomber. Bench the bomber. Okay. All right. Thanks for the advice.
Oh, sorry. Thanks for the voice. Now, do I put in the dragon? I can't. I couldn't do it.
I can't. I can't do it. What's an accent I could do just forever? Um, I guess it could be something
like this, where I just add an inflection at the end of my sentences. I could do that probably.
I think so. I could do that one. That's the same voice. No, it's not. That's just changing my
cadences. That's you. I don't do that. Put the bomber. No, no. Okay. I got to play. What do I
want? All right. I'm going to do copy man. That's a YouTube documentary voice. Is it possible
that the Mayans had different technology? Could it be that astronauts have joined the Mayans?
Yeah, it kind of is. And then even when they're not asking a question, it's still a question.
Over 200 million Mayans existed in the year 14 AD. They're still asking a question.
You got to speak with confidence and with sincerity. That's a fat earther voice.
All right. What's next? This is the perfect guy for this, by the way. Oh, don't get killed.
Don't get killed. Fat fuck earth theory. Fat fuck earth theory. Space is incredibly large.
Scientists predict that over the next 200 years, Earth might spin at 2% faster than it does now.
Join me in this video as we see exactly how big the Earth can get. Audible.com is a website where
you can listen to music and TV shows on your computer. I'll probably spend the next probably
four or five minutes talking about this. Over the course of this 20 minute video,
we'll take a break to talk about it. And I know. But Earth is a gigantic place. But what if Earth
was 10 times larger? Scientists are calling this theory the fat fuck earth theory. We caught up.
Concentrating. Hold on. Don't want to die. I died. Dude, you gaming documentary videos.
Oh, dude, I'm hooked. This is a currency thing. This foot lettuce thing. Burger King. I can't. I'm
not going to say that out loud. You guys trying to drop my net worth? Crash his stock. I don't
have any. There's no such thing. There's no ticker for me. Guys, if there was a ticker for this
channel, all you memers would just manipulate the fuck out of it. And I would be under investigation
every day. The SEC would have me on speed dial. And I would have to talk to somebody every day.
The JR the turbo ticker has said more unusual activity.
I want to ask you a few questions about this. God damn it. Okay, what is it?
Well, it turns out they sold, then bought and then sold it again. $2 million worth of stock.
And it looks I see if you look at this chart. Looks like they spelled out the effort. Fuck
in the up and down sells and buys. Are you aware that you did you have anything to do with that?
No, I didn't. Actually, I didn't. How do I delist my can I go private again?
No, you can't actually. That'll be a $600,000 fine. I can't but my net worth is only 112.
Looks like you're fucked, kid. Oh, no, no. You already have one. Yeah, but that's just like
pretend goofy money. Every time you buy and sell on that website, all you do is somewhere
in the distance, you just hear like, oh, this is for fun. And it's cool. And that's a real I was
into that for a little while. I thought it was like a cool thing. This is like an interesting
little that's a that's a fun little project. But it's not, you know, it's not real money.
Derma podcast sucks. I wonder if it gets any and then idiot. Thanks for watching, everybody.
See you tomorrow audible.com. Let me see this if this gets any better. I don't want to listen to
that. Somebody sat on the clicker. Wikipedia the we encyclopedia that anyone can edit.
Why did you say it like that? Why did you say it like that? Why did you say it like that?
That's a meme. I don't know. All right, let's bring you you you copy man didn't get a chance.
We'll put copy man first. And that's what what Vito Vito just gave. Dude, you're up today. Oh,
we see. Oh, where? I'm not gonna say anything. I'm gonna just watch this.
It's crazy just how this reflects like actual looks like stock lines. It's always like a top.
There's I bet you if you did actual TA, like technique, if you did technical analysis,
like they did, like they don't stop tickers. You could find like bottoms,
you could find like, oh, that's a double bottom. That's what we call a, a, a, um, a, um,
ah, I might as well be doing technical analysis, because I can't up.
Yes, it's real. Oh, no, we hit the double top. Okay, I gotta I'll manipulate this. I can't look
at this. We love bottoms. Shut up. Wait, hold on a second. That's like, it's like,
holy shit. Elon Musk just tweeted he's made out of titanium.
And he'll live forever. Holy fuck. That's that kind of line.
Holy shit. That's the kind of line where it's like this just didn't McDonald's figured out how to
print money. Each person goes and gets a happy meal gets $100 and a happy meal. Holy shit.
Wait, why would they figure out how to do that? That's that's against the law.
Oh, no, no, no. It would be like this just did. Oh, all cars toys from 2000 to 2005
have appreciated in value by 200 million percent. Only the ones in the McDonald's toy box.
Wait, that wouldn't mean that they would that make McDonald's be? Yeah, because then people
be like, holy shit, I gotta buy McDonald's. Here it goes. Here it goes. Here it goes.
Let's make a camel. No, don't laugh at that. You're not done. OK, now I gotta say something
that's not funny, but that is funny at the same time for like the next 40 minutes.
Hey, no, no, no, no. Look at me. Giant enemy spider. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Poopoo, poopoo, peepee, poopoo. I have a poopoo guy. Poopoo, poopoo, poopoo, poopoo, poopoo.
That wasn't supposed to be funny. Stop buying.
What would happen? What would happen to the stock of like L.O.B.S.T. tweeted like peepee,
poopoo, poopoo, poopoo? Would it go up or down? It would probably go up. It would probably
explode in value. I don't know what the fuck that means, but I don't think I'm gonna buy it.
This is such a fun little thing. You ready? Hold on a second. Give me one second. Hold on.
No, no, no. I want to get it on screen. I'm not. I'm not doing what you think I'm doing. I promise.
Holy shit. OK, hold on. Let's keep this on for a little while. This is funny to me.
Oh, he's going to play. Quick sell. See? Oh, yeah, you got to see the time. OK, there we go.
All right, let's go. A little too big. So if you want to see why I thought this was a funny idea
at first and then I thought this was a really, really, really bad fucking idea. And I was going
to actually have somebody make an extension for this, like build out an extension that did this.
But you will see that it is now. It's it would be like we talked about this yesterday, didn't we?
I couldn't. It would be like it would be all I think about. I wouldn't be able to concentrate
on anything. Quick do a Shpee stimulus package. Oh, there was an estimate that there was going
to be a Shpee stimulus package and it didn't happen. Oh, shit. All the investors were expecting
it. It didn't happen. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. No, yeah, it's like it's it's 430.
We're waiting for a Shpee announcement here. What was going on? Investors, German 985 comedy
investors around the world are stuck right now. They don't know what to do. They were expecting
this and those that bought in very, very early back in 2011, they're still holding and they're
but they might start to sell. We're going to see some real capitulation here.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We're going to get we got a live feed from German 95
bedroom. Here he is. I slept in way too late. I slept in like way too late.
Investors around the world are weighing what they think about this. Is that too that may
have been too much stimulus? See how they feel about it. Trying that the the bulls are really
trying to take this up. Yeah, I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna find out how to do this.
I'm gonna make like a comedy currency that's like built in with an extension
so people can like buy and sell comedy currency on this channel.
Even if it's only like active for like fucking a week. It'll only be live for like a week.
This is like funny. But this this is like insane. Do channel points. Oh my god.
Channel points. Okay. Yeah, we could do channel points. Channel points for like the IPO. Like
you have a bunch of them right now. You like got into the initial what? ICO. Initial Comedy.
I don't know. That's I don't want to use that. Initial Comedy Offering. No, I don't want to use
ICO. Don't want to do that. Hey guys, I'm making an ICO. That would be very bad. I don't I would
not want to say that one. Initial Comedy Offering. It's kind of like sad in a way. Last time you
heard somebody say that they were going to do an ICO. Holy shit. That's like 2016 2017.
I got to figure out how to do this because I think it'd be fun. They started right next to me.
I could have just put one of these guys in. Bugleberry is going to crash the market.
But I love Bugleberry. I think this could be fun for like a week. I have a pretend like
Twitch comedy traded channel points. That's built into that's baked into the channel.
And like people could buy and sell. And you could just lose a bunch of channel points and stuff.
We'll gain some. I have to be very clear. It's like I'm gonna be clear now about it to just
because I fucking have to say this and I'm going to say this. All of this is a comedy routine.
Like this is all a joke. It's a comedy routine. And nothing. It's not real value. It's just fake.
It's just fun. A little joke. That's not if it's real. You make sure I'm very clear about that.
What? I have to say that. This is a stock market parody without real value.
None of this is financial advice. It never was and it never will be.
Wait, are you guys selling because I'm telling you it's fake? Is that why?
No. CEO of German 95 Enterprises says that all of money in his stock is not even real.
It's not real money. CEO of major company says, sorry guys, I have to make this really clear.
Oh, the stock is worthless. It's not real. Holy shit, that would be insane.
And this would be funny for like a week. But that's all it could be there for. Because you know.
Because with everything, it doesn't even matter if it's not even real. There will be little groups
that like forming it like, all right, at 830 am, we're gonna dump it and then we're gonna
there'd be like discord calls about this. You know, it's gonna happen. But it'll be a little
experiment. It's already it's happening now. This is one of those charts where if you like
owned a stock in here, you it doesn't matter if it's like 8am or 8pm. You've probably opened
a bottle of whiskey. Holy shit. Oh my god. What the fuck? What do I do? This is fucked.
Try to like turn it off. Or do I do I buy it? Or do I sell it? I've gone up and down in
portfolio value 100% both directions in 10 minutes. Oh, I think I I think I'm gonna take a bath.
I think it went off the screen. Yeah. And then there's going to be the people that just want to
watch the world burn, right? And they're just going to sell and buy at the same price and just
manipulate it. So it goes up and down like a heart monitor. No matter what. Oh, shit, I'm gonna lose.
Okay, I'd have to put some like, some like rules in. And maybe you could only do a certain amount
of like a certain amount a day or a stream. I don't know. Oh, I also have to put this on
screen too. This is hold on. I don't want people to think that like if they just come in right now
and it's like, well, what stock is this? You know what I mean? Like I got to hold on. Oh, shit.
Oh my god. I'm kind of Oh, I just lost right there. Hold on. Did I lose it? Did I win the loss? It's
not supposed to be funny. That's not supposed to be funny. That's I don't want people to come in
here and be like, what the fuck are they doing? You know what I mean? Like it went up and it went
down and then it went up and it went down. No, no, no, no, no. Like this is very clear that we're
just this is a this is a fake my streams comedy ticker. Somebody's gave $50.
Kajtech thanks for the 5000 bits. $50. Dermot, I have to inform you as a lawyer that this concept
already exists. It's twitch stocks. I'll be forced to minus two your stream if you do not cease and
desist. Well, no, I'm we're doing we're talking about comedy points. This is not a stock. This
is a comedy point. I'm a comedy point. Don't call it a ticker. This is a comedy point.
I almost turned on the webcam and I don't have a shirt on. I was going to be that would have been
like buy or sell. I don't know that would have moved. That would have moved the comedy points
a lot in some direction. I almost did it. It was close. Yeah, I got to get okay. I don't like copy
manners. Oh, who can I fit? Man, man, girl. And we have come on, Gwen. I like it. I like this new
group. You have to show it now or we're going to dump your comedy point. I'm not going to be naked
on camera. Yes, if you want to if you want to dump my fake comedy points, which doesn't affect me,
where being like naked on stream ends my career. And then this channel really won't be worth
anything. And then that that little net worth thing that you that you linked that goes zero.
I am going to figure out how to get that to work though. I think that's funny.
You guys are going off the screen. Oh my god. I fucking hate clicking on shit. Stop.
I don't think that's effective. CEO of comedy company sees comedy points drop by 80% in one
hour tweets stop. Shocked that it didn't work. How do I get this guy, this bird guy? He's so fast.
Take him out. Take him out. Take him out. Take him out. We still want face cam. No,
I'm not turning on face cam. I love this. You know, it's really funny. I love watching the
people type in minus five. It don't work like that. Sorry. What happened here? I woke up
in the morning and I saw I just looked at the chart. What's the news? Oh, CEO, CEO tweeted out
picture of asshole with two middle fingers on it and said fuck all investors.
Oh, holy shit. That's the only way this would have happened.
This is not natural. Are you buying that? You shouldn't be purchasing that. Oh, I got one.
Finally, acceleration ninja. Oh, imagine buying it up. I don't care. I give a shit if I see the
guy's asshole. The company's still worth $6.7 billion. What's wrong with you guys? Who cares?
CEO tweets picture of asshole with middle fingers and says fuck you to all investors.
And then two minutes later does another tweet shaking hands with two to three scientists
and doctors saying he has the cure for every illness on earth. Holy fuck. Quick. And then
the people, the people that bought like two hours ago that took a shit and came back when it's back
to normal are just like, I'm so glad I had diarrhea. I'm so glad. Holy shit. I was so I
was cursing the toilet and oh my god, I'm so glad I didn't look at this. Thank you. Thank you.
Based diarrhea. You're gross. Back to where it was when you bought it. Derma comedy. JCP now worth
more than oh my god. What the fuck? Activate. Activate. Activate. Derma's got a monopoly in
the Derma comedy point on comedy points. Yeah, the antitrust got involved. He's got to shout
out three YouTubers a week now. Yeah, that was the rolling. That was the rolling from the pretend
exchange people. Okay, you guys understand that this has to be complete comedy and complete
fabrication. When do you get one of these drill tanks? I want one of these things.
I mean, I'm worth five billion. I can get one. Come on. Come on, girl. Come on. Nice shot. Good
shot. Good shot. Be funny. What? I can't look. I can't pay. This is why it's only going to be
around for a week if I do it. It's I'll never I'll have to be like, what is that? What is that?
What is that? What is that? Is she the last one? No, who's left? Oh, shit. Okay, I gotta be careful.
Oh, oh, he just slam dunked me out of nowhere. Oh, fuck. Bad. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes. Thank God. Big Mitz. Big Mitz. Oh, you're right. It's $50 from ACDC freak. Thanks for the
five. Finally, a tank. Thanks for the 50 bucks. 5000 bits. Thank you so much for all the laughs
you've given me over the years. You helped me through so much, especially during these really
hard times. Thank you again for all you do. Thanks for the fucking incredibly kind message. And thanks
for the huge amount of money. It's just 50 bucks, like $50. Thank you. Finally, a drill tank. Give
me two of those. Finally, a drill tank. All right. Hold on a minute here. One of these revolver
gunmen have a blue shirt on. Yeah. Why do you have a blue shirt on? What's the difference?
What? It's just a different color. Oh, all right. Time to clean this up. All right. To the warehouse.
I'm not ever going to use you to the warehouse. You are new though. Samurai. Oh, rolling slash.
I'll get, I'll try them. We have too many of these revolvers. Warehouse. Warehouse.
Somebody, what is it? Yeah. You're level three. Warehouse. You can stay. I don't,
wire girl. No, no, no. I don't know. Probably not going to use wire girl. I got to clean this up.
I got to get rid of that. I told you, look at the title. I got to get rid of my fucking toys.
I'm not going to use spinner girl. Go over here. I might need you eventually.
I want to try the tank and I want to try the, what's acceleration ninja speed type, mid air,
kamaitachi, kamaitachi, and then ninpo full throttle. Oh, he's got wheels. This guy's cool.
The fastest gachaborg in the assassination unit. The amazing speed of his ninpo full throttle
sends any enemy that bumps into him flying. Cool. I mean, they're new. I have to try them.
Here we go. Yeah. What animal cleaning I need to do? Yeah. I'll do it later. I'll do it later. I'll
do it later. I'll do it later. I see. I do that so often. How many of you guys start cleaning your
room and you see just how much shit you have to do. You pick up like three pieces of paper
and wipe just the area you can see with your eyes. And then you go, fuck, there's so much.
That was a good start. And then it doesn't happen again until you need to clean the room again.
It happens all the time to me. Plus two better than nothing.
I don't want to do the boss battle. I want to do this. I don't know if I like these new units.
As a homeowner, I know what you mean. Yes. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. Let's check the samurai.
He is fast, isn't he? He is fast. He's fast. He's fire. Think fire. Think fire. Think fire.
But why am I getting minus two? Because you guys don't know what the fuck that is.
Not even Kingdom Hearts fans. Holy shit. Holy shit. Not even Kingdom Hearts 1 and 2 fans.
I mean, Kingdom Hearts 3. But the first two. Those were good. Weren't they?
Wait a minute. That was my favorite game. Minus two. Minus two. Minus two. Minus two. Minus three.
Minus three. Minus three. Minus two. Minus three. I'm going to do minus three because I love
Kingdom Hearts 3. Minus two. Minus three. In the middle of all this, somebody just writes,
dude, chill. You're right. I'll chill. You're right. This guy's good. He's a little beefier
than the other one. The tank. Actually pretty good. Really, really beefy too. It's got to be,
you got to hit. This would be really good against big units. I can't really dodge that well. That's
actually really good. Nice. I love it. It has a lot of health. Oh yeah. I guess, no, it can jump.
All right. That's cool. Lay an egg on screen. So you want me to go get like a comedy egg
and for like two or three months, make you really aware that I'm sitting on it.
And then after like a month or two, have it hatch on screen. And I play the Jurassic Park.
Look at how cute that is music. And then the thing attaches to my face. It's just biting me
and I like destroy the room because it's latching on. I won't let go. And it's like killing me and
hurting me in this free man. Like an alien face hugger is just like, Oh, look at how cute it is.
Oh, wow. Look at him. Come on. Come on. And I'm like, Oh my God.
Please. I'm like running around like bumping into walls and shit about the thing. Like is
feeding off of my blood. It's like a three week break. And I just got, I come back wearing a
neck brace. Like he clearly is like biting me on the shoulder, like on like the arm.
And I come back with a neck brace on. That's pretty good. I think, I think that would be fun.
You spoiled the whole joke. Yeah. You'll forget when it happens in like six months.
Showdown to the death base. Put a dog cone on. I keep, I keep like trying to like put my head
over and like lick. I'm just like, God damn it. Oh, I just want to come on. That's pretty good.
I'll see you in six months when this happens. I put my foot up and like try to get under and
like get it off by like scratching underneath. Like my foot comes up and have like big fake
dog feet made. So like, I can just have like a little bar that I pull up and it's a big dog
foot and I'm going to scratch under. All right. Oh shit. This is a real battle. Wait, having dog
feet is too far, but having an alien creature that hatches out of an egg latches onto my face
and is killing me. It's not too far. I must make, make sure I'm clear on this. Okay. Oh, it's this,
this is the hardest enemy in the whole game. I hate these guys. It's so, they have so much health.
They're so strong. They can move so quickly. They have to think. Look at that axe. I was trying to
go in whatever tank time. It's a good hit. Even if I have to trade here, it's fine. This is his best
unit. Speaking of, Oh yeah, this is done. Nice. Look at that. Look at the GF go down. Another one
except it's, she's come on. Okay. It's all right. It's all right. Who's next. I don't have play with
this guy. Oh my God. Where is he? Holy shit. This guy's insane. He's too good. I don't know how to
use them. Stop. Stop. Stop it. I love the way he skates around too. What is this charge? It's so
long. Oh, it's just a big AOE. Come on, block it. Come on. You don't even know how to use that.
What? Juggle. Juggle. I think who's next. Thank you. So you beat me. Vito, I'll give you this.
This belonged to my father. When you have three of them, the gate will open. I got three. I've got
three. Why did his father have a death crystal? I don't know. Beat the deadly UFOs. I like this
team. Stop making fun of kids. Not a bad graph. We're doing all right. Can I get on top of that?
Oh, probably should have picked somebody that has better long range capabilities. I don't know why
this is in my head. Why is this in my head? Destroy. Destroy. Why is it in my head? Imagine
not playing Star Fox 64. Yeah, I know. This thing is better than Spikehead. You were like 23 when
this game came out. How old do you think I am? 23? How old do you think I am? Honestly, this game
came out in 2003. How old is he now? 28. The death gate has opened. Nice. I need the dream team here.
Save the game. It's been like a year. I was like 17. Do the math. 85 to 2003. I was like 17. Let's
see. 85 plus 10 is 95. 85. 95 plus 10 is 100. 2005. So subtract three years. I was 17 years old,
not 23. My God. Getting rid of you. Let's get Spikehead. He's just very efficient.
Well, I need efficient. You are probably going to be good here because you've just been spam.
You'll be good here. We got 300 more points. Basically the same thing. This is not the same
thing. Why is he so mad all the time? Because I don't even have blood. It's just liquid
fucking gas. It's like a hot burning liquid. I have lava for blood. Let's see. Liquid water.
He's got Mountain Dew for blood. This last slot is important. Who do I want on the plane maybe?
Yeah. This plane's good. He's got code red in his blood. The decisive battle. Defeat the Cosmic
Dragon. This must be the death gate to the Death Fortress. This place is going to be your grave.
You wish. Let's go. Defeat the Cosmic Dragon. Who do we need for this one?
Heavy hitters like Tsutomu. Is it the Ender Dragon? Fire. You missed.
Oh. Why is it bouncing off? Oh, he's got that portal. Holy shit. He's dead. I'm going to kill
a dragon with this one guy. He's dead. There's more than one dragon. This game. I think it sucks.
No. Stop. Turn the fan off. Turn the fan off. Kill. Pissing into the wind. Is there any more
Ender Dragons? No. Point blank. Got it. Point blank. Uh oh. This is bad. This is bad. This is
bad. Bad. Bad. Good thing I got this guy. Okay. One more. Oh. Get back over there and hit him in the
head. Oh my. How many more fucking guys do you have? Here we go. That's his last guy. Got it.
What do you have left? What the fuck? This is not fair. Back up. Where the fuck is my friend?
Where's my head? Give me that. What do you have left? This is ridiculous. That's the Ender Dragon.
Okay. This is the Ender Dragon. What's that mean? I got to get my head. Oh. Oh. Don't. Oh. That hurt.
No. No. We need that power up. Oh, who's left? All right. Sniper Girl. Is anybody apt to Sniper
Girl or is this it? Oh, underneath. Go underneath. Underneath. Underneath. Underneath. Underneath.
Underneath. Get out from under there. Yes. That was a secret mission, by the way. I definitely got
something cool. But, uh, I had a plan after that. Nice. I thought that was my last character.
Oh, hell yeah. Oh, yeah. Elemental Knight and a Thanatos. 100 energy. My headaches.
What am I doing? You fool. Galactic Emperor. You can't stop me. The time draws near.
That's the haunted house when you're like eight and one of the lunch ladies at your school is
behind the microphone doing a scary voice. What happened? All right. I made that joke. Do it again.
What's going on? Made that exact joke before. Twice. Guys, I've said every word in the dictionary
at this point, so I might repeat a joke or two once every like three years. Sorry. Grownups have
finally noticed the Death Force, but they don't know what to do. What? Of course, they have no
idea what we are dealing with. Right. Only Gachaborgs can defeat Gachaborgs. Um, I think
if you just, if you were an adult and you picked up one of these toys and snapped it in half,
that would work. Let's split up and take them on separately. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Elemental
Knight. Elemental Punch. Elemental Sword. And Elemental Slash. This strange Gachaborg's armor
is empty. And as life force appears to be contained in his sword, his elemental sword was forged to
destroy a legendary ancient knight. Hope you're not bad. Okay. I like this. I'm gonna do Elemental
Knight. Listen, Vito, you gotta help me. To the warehouse? No. Does Elemental Knight have a sword?
What just happened? I just died. What happened? Why did he explode? He's, oh, I got a defective
one. He's broken. I have to return it. He's cool. I got a broken one. Okay.
Uh, well, command girl, just fly away. Just get the hell away. Get the hell away. Just get the hell
away. Get the hell out of here. I just out ran it. Plane! Come on, plane clutch, plane clutch,
plane clutch, plane clutch, plane clutch, plane clutch. They all crashed into each other. That
was perfect. Sunnyside Park is safe. Good. No, I need to save it. Yeah. Let's do this one. These
ones are the important ones, right? You're late. I want to see, I want to play with the knight.
Here we go. Okay. Dude, he's got some good, he's got a cool combo. What's the other one do? What?
Okay. What is that? He explodes. Oh, he formed. Am I not targetable when that happens? That's
actually pretty great. Oh, you shoot your hand out. It's like a rocket punch. Do not target.
Holy shit. This guy's awesome. I'm kicking the shit out of this guy. Rocket punch. Wow.
He's so powerful with the power. When you get the superpower, he's so good.
When you're juggling them around, come on. What happened? Somebody said, oh my god, the minus two
and plus two grab. Yeah, this is bullshit going on earlier. It's all right. That punch is really
effective too. This is really good. I haven't even had to change characters and wham. Crash, crash,
crash. There's no reason to. This guy's dodging me. Don't like it. Dude, I just did half his health in
one hit. Bang. Oh, you know, you're a streamer. Cool stuff going on on the screen. You haven't
said anything in a while. Bang. Bang. Right there. Nice. Streaming tips. The German 985. Nice. Bang.
Great turn on the face cam. No, I'm not going to turn on the face cam. How many bullets? What the
fuck? This game is so good. Everything's not about face cam. Okay. Good shot. That was a long range.
That was a blue plate special. Do another one. Oh, I just missed it. Back, back, back. No. No.
Give me the head. No. Top of the top of your head. Let's punch him. What? What's going on here?
Hey. No face cam. Oh my god. A chainsaw knight. These guys have kicked the shit out of me through
the whole game and now I got one. What is that? A lance knight? I could have it. Holy fuck. We're
getting a lot of stuff. Come on. Is it two of them? Is that it? Did I get lucky? Where's the
chainsaw knight? There you are. Huge damage. No weapon. Just has wire arm and chainsword.
Chainsaw Knight is a breakaway soldier from the Knightborg Corps. He wields a huge chainsword
and can slash anything to pieces. Grab enemies with the wire arm and then slash them with the
sword. Nice. All right. We're going to have to... What's more important? Plane's going to have...
Sorry, command girl. I know you're level three and you're one of the best characters that I have,
but I'm sorry. I need to try a chainsaw guy. Everybody's selling. Sell. I didn't save it.
No, my life savings. The plane's mediocre. Yeah, but it's really good to maneuver around.
Wait, is this like having a movie on in the back seat? The graph is having a movie on in
the back seat of a car? What do you mean? Don't hurt me. Defeat enemy, got you more.
It's distracting. That's what I mean. That's why if I do this, I only want to do this for like a week
and have it be real for a little bit. Can I pull the whole ship? Kind of. This guy wasn't really
made for this, was he? Okay. That was not a good representation of what he does. Fire, fire, fire,
fire, fire, fire. Missiles. Missiles. Oh, that's not good. All right. Tank versus tank. Jesus.
What is even firing at me? Doing a lot of damage, but what are you? What are you? I can't move.
I'm stuck. I have a debuff. Here we go. Melee. Not a good choice. Yeah, not a good choice.
Melee was not the right thing to do. We need long range shooters. We need.
Oh, here's the last resort here. Holy shit, it worked. Give me a hat. Give me one of these hats.
Did I get it? I got him. One more hit and he's dead. I need a hat. Where's one of my hats?
Just avoid him. He'll be killed by this ship. Ship friend will take care of him. Good. Already
back down again. Guys, this shit used to happen to Bitcoin every day for like three months.
You guys just pretending to be the BTC chart from like early 2018. Like somewhere in like the mid
2018. This shit happened like every day. It was, it was infuriating. GT area is safe. Oh,
oh no. Don't get your ice cream on me. He's a crypto trader Redditor. I'm going to,
I want to keep the melee. I like this team. Cooperate with Kakarou to retake Serenity Street.
There's no reason for this. There's no reason for this. It's because of the face cam. I mean,
he's all right. How did I miss all those? What the fuck? How did I miss them all?
This is pretty good actually. You can land it. How did you dodge all those?
Got him. Is that my ally? This will be good. Big thick beams. There they go.
It can't go any lower. It can't go any lower. I don't have clothes on. I can't. What do you
guys not know about terms of service? You're not allowed to be naked. Don't let him come over here.
Shoot him. No, I did it. You were there. Good shot. Sack. Sack. Sack. The guy didn't stand a
chance. This tank is so good. He's left. Tank is so good. We're at all time lows here. Shit. Got it.
No. Okay. I've had enough of your bullshit. Let's get found. Fucking melee. Fucking melee is not
working here. There's just missiles surrounding me. Where am I? Dead. I'm dead too. Pick it up.
Where is it? Get it. Did I not hit you? Get the hell out of here. Big guy. Probably one of the
last things left. Damn it. Just enough. I just need a little bit more and I can throw as many
as I want. We're going off the chart. Oh shit. Careful. What does that mean? What is that?
Who cares? Don't get scared. Just kill him. I need my helmet. Give me one. No.
You fucking asshole. Do something. Do something. Help me. All right. No, no. Don't turn it on yet.
I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back. What do we got? Okay.
Okay. Base cam. Sell. No, we don't. Buy it. I think it's broken. I think. Hello. I think
my pretend funny stock tag is broken. Hold on. Let me reload it. Here we go. Let's play. Crystal.
What's in the crystal? Ooh. That's the guy that shoots the huge beam. Plus two. Dunky donut.
All right. Another data crystal. What is it? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. You
know when your hair is so bad that this is solid. I was trying to run my hands through my hair.
I tried. What the fuck? I can't. It hurts. Look at how much there is in just the worst places.
This hair just in places that it shouldn't be. It's just everywhere. Like it's all back here.
It's just all back there. Get a haircut, please. I can't.
Do you? Um, excuse me. Are you? Do you? Wait. I can't really. I can't go anywhere.
Do it yourself. I'll mess it up. Could it look any worse than this though? I don't know.
Just shave it. What if I just do like a big fucking big ponytail up here? No,
I can't even do a ponytail. It's too long back here. And it's too short up here.
How would that look? It's so funny how you can go from. Oh, check me out. Just look at it.
I have like a second head that's back here. If I would have like moved this.
I have so much mass back here that there's probably like a face that's just like
sticking out its mouth and its eyes and shit. Like I'm hiding another like head under here.
Too much hair in the back. That's. Don't do spoilers for movies and TV shows, please.
I know. Look, this is the worst I'm ever going to look. So who cares? All right. This is like
the worst I will look. By the way, Darth Vader playing a fucking piano. All right. Goodbye.
All right. We have recovered. Thanks for having fun. Hey Vito, our town is a total mess.
Did somebody say I wonder what his hair smells like? Or am I just making that up because I saw
I wonder what his hair and then adding the rest. I'll squash all you bug. No, I said that. I know
that's what I'm saying. One got it. Ooh. And they even got a new camp. Oh, fixed cameras,
fixed camera and go stupid. This character is actually really good. Why are you getting
this close to me? You know what my skill set is. Okay. I tried it a lot. I have a plane.
Holy shit. I just instantly died. Oh, it's because these tanks got to go. Oh, man. Shit.
I got to get in there to that tank. He's going to just do that super beam and pull up and pull
them in and pull them in and get them in. It does a lot of damage if I can hit the damn thing.
Yeah, I agree. He's annoying, annoying brat. Holy shit. That went far. That's him. You're hitting
me. It's hitting me. He's so dumb. I don't want to be on the same team as him anymore.
All right. Let's clean this up. Please clean it up. You could please. Who's left? See you later.
Making noises. Hey, it's me. I have turbo. I do noise. Can I please run away? Handling. Don't
fall for it. It was a one hit kill. This character is I think probably the most consistently just
good. It's just so good at everything. That's why him and I click so well together. You know?
Come on. Really? This chart turned the face cam off all of a sudden. Oh, we got. I want another
command girl. This is like the fourth spinner girl. Ask and you shall receive another one.
Yes. Well, I'm the coolest. You're such a loser. You are such a loser. I want to try this new tank.
Okay. Now, um, I want to command girls. I'm over by a lot. You're cool, but you've got to go
over by 150. What was my level three? Okay. You go first by 180. Do I have anybody that's 180?
No, I don't. I think one cooperate with the UG to retake the pit. Where are they? Wait,
didn't they say? Where are the adults? Didn't they say the adults were here now? Where are the adults?
They're dead. Huh? Yeah. Keep that shit over there. I don't want to get out of here with that.
I hate when they kept you in that junk. That was a nice shot. Oh, you got keen on what I was doing.
5300 points. Holy. Come on, man. A lot. My crew is only worth like a thousand or like 1800.
What was that? Did we just get like, did we just get a?
What was it? Is it? Is it? Sure. Sure. Sure. Sure. I'll get it. What's the one that goes, um,
how does that one go? Can I give it to me phonetically?
Some, that's some, that's some, my cake, that's some, that's a mock, that's a mock,
kicks up. What is it? That's my thoughts, I think. He's trying. I, when I say it, when I go,
let's start to, to look at that sounds more than when it's touch my spin, but it can, I can't say
it. Say it. Atsuma, NA education. Sorry. I didn't learn Japanese. Is it Japanese? I'm just going to
hold on. Ken spin move. Tatsu, Tatsumaki, Tatsumaki, the Tatsumaki. What is the Rio spinning
kit called? Sen, Senpu, Senpuku, Atsumaki Senpuyo. I can't hold on. I need to, I gotta hear it.
To me, it's in my head. Cannon. It's that. Let's see it.
That's tight. Good. Good. Good.
See that's tight. Good. Good. Good. That's tight. Good. Good.
Good. I got, I'm close off rope. Cringe. What is that? Is that what he's, what is the top
That's not even what you said. I just, that's what I thought it said.
Top. Oh, wow. Dude. That's something. That's some top rope. Cringe. That's a top rope.
Elbow drop. Cringe, dude. That's a fringe off the top rope. People's elbow. Cringe, man.
Why is it so laggy? Oh, this is the new car. Too much lag. I can't even see. Fire. Fire. Flame.
Fire. What is it? It's another one. Oh yeah. It goes yoga. Flame. Yoga. Fire. Yoga. Yoga.
Yoga. Flame. Yoga. Fire. Yoga. Fire. Yoga. I remember that's the only thing I could hear.
These people just spam it. Almond or cringe. Or are you sure it's not? I think I like this
tank better than the other tank. I'd love to get another one of these. I want one of the big guys.
These dudes. They run around. They have all these super plasma moves. A double grab.
Bullshit. Link. Link. I'm in the, I'm in the middle of something. I'm kind of in the middle
of something. I agree. The bigger they are, the harder they fall. I finally got to hear it.
We've been waiting for that for three days. Well, that was dumb. Come on. Hold this through.
This dude's fucking all over the place. Holy shit. I need to just relax and.
Wow. You can't even dodge. How are you supposed to dodge that? You can't even dodge this shit.
Got it. Okay. What is it? What are we looking at here? Cool.
Oh, I drew me. What do we get? Barrier Girl and Super Frog. I have two of these.
How many do I need? Let's see. What is Barrier Girl? 500. Whoa. Actually pretty good. Charge
gun, beam yo-yo, charge shot, and barrier. Barrier Girl was trained as a secret agent
as well as her weapons. She also possesses a barrier generator. Use her when you need brute
force. Most expensive character in the game besides G Red. All right. Let's try. I don't
really like this thing. Speaking of G Red, let's get him back in here. Co-operate to retake his
home. I gotta shrink this a little bit. It's blocking my view. All right. Barrier Girl. Let's
see if you're worth the 500 battery power. The charge shot. I don't know if that hits. It's
probably pretty good. All right. What is the barrier? Wait, am I invincible? It kind of.
I'm not sure it's the greatest thing in the world. 500.
Oh, it's you. This is a Jeep thing. I want one of these. This thing can just peel out. That
thing's awesome. New car. Maybe I'll get it. Kill, kill, kill. Kill, kill, kill, kill.
Ow. All right. That ship has got to go. It's a pain in the ass. You know what to do. Just
shit out. Long range. I'll go unboxing waiting room. Nice. I wonder what he's going to get this
time. There it goes. Jeep versus tank. We all know who wins this. It would have been stay back. I
octane vehicle combat. Yeah, kind of. Does every encounter play the same song? Yes, it does. Yes,
it does. I know. And people probably just. I'm going to turn the music off. It's kind of getting
in my head too. And I have, well, we'll play some other song. Simpson's hit and run doom,
eternal OST. Is that, I, but I need to, okay. Doom, eternal OST. I'm going to skip to halfway
through it. How's that? Just play the America's funniest home videos theme song over and over
again. Okay. Is there like a, how long has there like a 10 hour version of this?
Well, here's all of them. Here's every single one. We can, we can. Okay. Let's judge
these. Cause this is, this is an eight minutes video. I can't turn the sound off all the way.
I'm going to go down to, no, I can't. I have to just, I have to just turn off the audio coming
through to crank AFV. All right. I'm just going to mute it. Okay. Let's, let's critique each
America's funniest home videos. I can't. Okay. This one just, the audio quality just sucks.
Okay. Let's go. Let's, let's, here we go. Let's get back to the game. This is the first one.
Nah. Bad. Now bench it. This is recorded with a phone. Nope. Not very good. No. Why, why does
this have a laugh track? Well, it's because they used to show clips of people like falling down
stairs. This is long. It's going to, I'm going to be too late. I can't sing along.
Did they keep the same singer the whole time? Okay. That was that one. This is, here we go.
Wow.
I've missed this show. It's still on TV.
I feel like Vine and TikTok took this over.
America's funniest home videos is now just every Vine you've ever watched.
You might be a star tonight. How many Vines and TikToks exist of like somebody falling down or
like breaking something or like trying to do one thing and then something horrible happens.
It's like, oh, I just dropped it. What am I fighting though? Use barrier. It's snacks.
Stacks. Don't wait. I'm, it's still going. It's too much power. This is too much power.
Nothing. Look at that. I'm dead. They're like five times.
Yeah. Okay. Now we're getting into like the 2000. No, no, that's too much change.
Too much change. How many cartoon sounds do you look?
I, yeah, I got it. I caught it. I caught it. I don't even know what it means, but I just,
they're like sounds. I don't know what it means. Okay. This is the lag character. I don't want to,
she's good, but laggy. Tempo change to, what are you thinking? Is the game, wait,
is this slowing down with the game? Why is this video tied to my frame rate on the GameCube?
This is actually freaking me the fuck out. I hate this.
Funny things you do. This is you. All right. Well, the last, this one's bad.
It's from like 1998 or something. 1997. Eh, not good. Okay. No, I don't like this one. No,
no, no, no, no, no. I don't like this one either. I feel like it was,
had to knock on wood, but I'm not someone who has, they made me want to read back to it.
Yeah. Is this the same song? America, this is you. Did they say that at the end?
For the Buddy Buddy Boston song? Wait, there's a mashup out of those two songs.
This is actually, I told you. This is a good song.
The best part about the mighty, mighty Boston, there were like 200 people in this band.
I owned this CD. I owned that CD. I used to listen to this on repeat. They're a great band.
Play the actual song. Is it going to get, I'm not getting in trouble with this.
It's going to be the VOD. VOD's already gone because you just played four
America's Funniest Home videos. I want to hear it. It's been a long time.
This song is all right. Whatever. It's worth it. I love this song. It's a fucking awesome song.
Let's, let's fucking jam to this for a little bit. It's like, there was,
yeah, there's a ton of people in this band. Sick. This is genuinely my wedding song.
I mean, that's great. That's a really good song. A lot behind these lyrics.
All right. All right. Don't, don't, don't claim this video. I just want to hear it for a second.
All right. Now back to the, back to the other one. You can't claim this. This is the different song.
Nice. What's the next one? This one's epic. Dude, this one's epic.
Which one is this? Persona battle music. It's the same again. Yeah. Wait. This is good.
This is good thinking music, but when the family has to come up with a final answer
and they're scrambling around trying to figure it out.
Double dragon. What is this? I just got smoked. Oh, that was fun. Okay. This song is fucking awful.
Why? Why do you hate it? Do this one now, now, now, now, now, now, now.
Superman. Wait, this is also the same one. Oh shit. This is sick. Okay. Dude, you know,
why wouldn't, okay. Imagine if you had these two musicians, if you, why, why does this not exist
some company that's just like, let's just mash up songs and like just split it 50 who you wanted
to just get 50 50. Just put this album up, put up like a mashup album and just get permission and
give them 50 50. People love this shit. I'm not matched up. I know. I don't care. I'm matched up
in my brain and in my living room, but not on your screen. Okay. Don't claim the bond. What's
another one? What dragon can fight a tank? None. Put it back on. No, we're all going to get in
trouble. What's this one? Uh, no, I don't want to listen to Pokemon music, but you, you wrote ass
next to this one. So let's see what this is. Oh, I don't know. I don't know what this is. No.
Um, this one's called, this one's just called penis music. Wait, this is the, somebody made a
video with me doing this with like the people behind the, like into like the restaurant kitchen.
That's what it's from. That's the meme. This is, this is it. This is the meme. Who are,
who are these characters supposed to be? Are these from like a cartoon or like a kid's show or
something? They're from Megamind. Oh, all right. Well, cool. I get it. I guess. What's this one?
Remember when Jerma spoiled Megamind? I did. Uh, all right now. All right. All right. All right.
I'm going to, let's put on a Yoshi's story. OST. What's this? You don't want to put on
Yoshi's story. OST. Wario land music. Wario land four. Hurry up. Okay. I'll try it. Nah,
fuck that. I know what we're doing. Oh, fuck that. I know what we're doing.
It's the Neverhood OST. One of the best OSTs ever. Terry Scott Taylor. This shit,
fuck, this shit is just pops up and down, left and right, every which way.
Defeat the Cotcher Borg. Hey, there's a little penis music part here for you.
Holy shit. Pog. When am I going to stream the Neverhood? I streamed Army Crog.
Nothing can compare. If I can get it to work, I would. It's so, you guys would love this shit.
You guys, I can't believe that like Twitch has not been, a lot of you guys don't even know. You
guys would love it. It would be like your favorite thing. I'm doing it. I'll find a way. There's one
part that just pops up and you need like a save file to patch over it. I don't even know if that
file exists anymore. It's my favorite game ever made. Yeah, it has to be. It has to take number
one. It has to. Ask Vinny, he did? Really? Still ask him what he did. Terry Scott Taylor also did
the soundtrack for Army Crog, but unfortunately, it was a lot of just kind of background.
Didn't really sing on it. It was, I think there's only one track that he actually sang on and his
lyrics are just like this. It's just kind of gibberish. It's great. There's a few tracks on
Army Crog that are awesome. I mean, not like this, like listen. Where's that? We'll go back to this.
Where's the Terry Scott Taylor demo for Army Crog? When he's talking about going pee pee in his pants.
You guys would love this guy. I'm serious. I can't believe nobody likes this. I can't believe nobody
loves this guy. Here it is. Let's listen to it. You guys are going to love this song.
This is from the Army Crog demo.
There it is. Yeah, that's Terry Scott Taylor. We can go back to the Neverhood soundtrack.
If you like that, there's way more on the way.
It was kind of loud. I'm sorry. I just like burped in your ear.
You'll need this game forever. Don't worry. You're never going to see it again after today.
Never play. What's going on? Relax. All right. You guys have to guess my favorite song in this album.
Spoiler. This is one of them.
Oh, fuck. That's a big dragon. I love this. This just turned into a listen party.
This is also a good one. He just coughed. Oh, that was such a good shot.
Don't die to this. I'm dying with this music on. I'm not going to fuck this soundtrack as a kid.
Hey, that makes two of us. I have the Imaginarium soundtrack, which is all of it. It's behind me.
I displayed it on my Reddit shelf. We're going to do, I think I've played this one before, but
this is from Skull Monkeys. When you went into a bonus room, this is what played.
If you went into a secret area, this is what would play. It's just great.
You can linger because I'm your video friend. Think of me as a father figure with a hand to land.
Here's a little bonus room where you don't have to worry.
Take your sweet time. You need not hurry. Oh, you're looking incredible.
You're the bomb and me. I'm kind of like your dad and a little like your mom.
There are no monsters here. Hey, wait, look over there.
I was just kidding. Don't be scared. And when you turn this game off in the real world once again,
you won't have to play, make me leave or try to pretend because I'll be right there when you
open your hand because I'm your little invisible musical friend. So show me to your pets or show
me to your pals. You really will impress every nifty guy and gal. Show them you're individual.
Show them you are bold. Besides, I get residuals for every game that's sold. I'm your little
invisible musical friend.
For life. Hey, speaking of Skullmonkeys, why don't we just get on with the Skullmonkeys theme.
That was the sequel to The Neverhood. Didn't sell very well.
Wasn't it? People weren't really a big fan of it, but you know, whatever.
Boringly gameplay. I think I'm doing pretty well considering it.
Somebody said we're listening to bad music. Um, careful here. You are referencing probably,
probably the number one, my most favorite thing on earth is this series. So I would be careful
here. You're talking, this is like literally one or two of my favorite thing that's ever been made.
Okay. Just want to make sure we're clear. Be careful here. Be careful. Wait, what was I playing?
Let's do this one. Wait, where is it? Did I X the window out? Did we listen to this one yet?
Did we listen to this one? Slapper. This one's a classic. Yeah, this one's a fucking classic.
This is the first thing you hear in the game. That's right. This is the first song you hear
in the game. You wake up. There's no fucking tutorial in this game. You just wake up,
this music's not playing. You got to figure out what the hell you're doing. What the fuck?
What a 10 out of 10 game. I'm not talking about this game. This game's a three out of 10,
according to fucking publications at the time, which that's wrong too. Played Neverhood. I will.
I will. I will. I will. I promise. I will. I can't play Armor Crog on launch and then be like,
Neverhood, yeah, it's a good one. It's my favorite thing ever made, but maybe one day.
$150, three out of 10 game to read all the Neverhood lore. The game was just a huge,
there's this huge fuck you in this game. I don't want to give spoilers for it, but it's so fucking
stupid. It's like the worst, like just fuck you. You guys know what I'm talking about.
Hold on, pause it. Those of you that played the Neverhood, I don't, don't give it away because
we're going to have to, we'll see it eventually. But there is a massive, massive tedious thing that
you have to do or you cannot complete the game. And it takes, I think like at least 15 to 20
straight minutes of doing this wicked, boring, shitty thing. Oh, like the game you're playing
now. Quiet. Careful here. Careful. I enjoy you, but be careful. You understand? You're talking about
one of my, this is definitely not one of my favorite things ever made. This is probably like
somewhere, yeah, maybe top 100. No, probably like 101. This could be 101. Dude, listen to my gamer
noises. You don't get to hear these when there's no sound. This game sucks. Admit it. Why would I
stream this game for three days in a row if I thought it sucked? Why would I do that to bite
you? I actually think we're probably getting close to the end. Why does chat hate this game?
I don't think they do. I think it's, I think it's like, I don't think it's very, I think it's only
like a few people. I think, I don't think it's true. I think people think this is sick. I'm
going to keep the flying saucer though. That's good. I do think we're getting close to the end
of the game though. And I'm not going to do like new game plus, new game plus, new game plus.
Don't worry. Just enjoying a thing that I like. And I know that a lot of people like it too,
because they've told me I've gotten two or three DMs in the last week. One of which,
hoping to go fuck myself. But the other two were about, this game seems kind of fun. I hope you
keep playing it. So two, yeah, that's enough. Here comes the big battle. Oh, you have a helicopter
note. What about the comedy points? What about it? They look all right. What does that come?
Does it come out of the bottom? Trying to figure out what this thing does. I think it comes out of
the bottom. This thing's really good. Holy shit. That was an instant kill. Whoa. Actually, I don't
like it. I don't like that thing getting replaced. It's too expensive. Swim down? What do you mean
swim down? Just swim down, man. Yeah, just stand still and spam. It works. So is there like a
Patapon bundle on PlayStation 4? Or is it just the first one that's available? And is it a scenario
where Patapon 2 is just Patapon 1 but better? Kind of like the Pikmin games. Does it matter?
Yeah, Patapon 2 is so much better. Patapon 2 is a straight upgrade. But holy shit, look at this tank.
What is this? I think this is a bug. I don't think that's supposed to be like that. Patapon 3 sucks.
So should I just, should I play Patapon 2? Or should I start at Patapon 1?
2 is really good. Play minus 2. Don't play any video games. 2 is just one but better.
Ooh, Atra Witch. You win, Jerma? What is this? An unofficial poll? That doesn't mean anything.
Gotcha Man. I don't care. I like his voice. I love Gotcha Force. I hate Gotcha Force.
So 26% of people, whatever. Play 2, then 1, then replay 2. What are you talking about?
I'm getting rid of the saucer. It's too much money and it's too hard to use. What do you do?
Oh, pretty weak. Stick it in large. Wait, that's what that is. Big spell.
We could magnify others with the big spell. I have to try it. 480 left. Get rid of you.
Where's the knight that I like here? This guy. Ah, 540. Fuck. 370. Here we are.
Let's love 260. Where's Command Girl? Command Girl, where are you? Level 1. No, I have a level 2.
It's a fucking mess. There we go. Uh, you. No, shit. Um, you. No, you're too much too.
Who's 2? Any like a 280? A great dragon parade. These are getting more and more intense.
Remember when this was organized? Yeah. Please vote. Your vote counts. Is this a different poll?
Okay. Big. It's huge. Go get him. Bro. Can I, does it stack? Did I just make him bigger?
Uh, all right. Well, what was that? Somebody just dropped a bunch of pots and pans over here.
You're too big. That's. Wait, how many? This is 8,000 points. Oh my God. This is going to be
a pain in the ass. I'll just use it. Come on. Spawn. This can take forever.
How many dragons are there? Each one's a thousand. So there's probably seven more.
Oh, come on. I just got caught in a double beam. That sucked. Land already. Oh, helicopter doing
work. What's going on? His face on the wall. That was funny. Don't get killed. Okay. Here we go.
What a pain in the ass. This is all dragons. At least they're huge targets with my tank.
Oops. All dragon. What's that from? What is that? Captain crunch.
Oops. Oh, very. That's, that's funny. What a fake captain crunch fan.
I like original captain crunch. I don't like, I mean, crunch berries are good, but I don't follow
all their, I don't follow all their changes. What is happening? Fake fan, fake fan. I like
original captain crunch. It makes me a fake fan. Apparently fun. He's at the last three or last.
How many? Three. All right. This is it. Destroy, destroy. That was, this one was a pain in the ass.
Shoot him. All right. Let's end it. All right. That one was long and tedious. All right. What's
the, what's the poll at now? See, I like gotcha force. I don't care. I hate gotcha force. See,
plays a dragon. I'll play as one of the dragons next mission. I promise. Not this one though.
Maybe I will play with the ice dragon who has the most power. Oh, this is a mess. Uh, 10, 50,
240, 210. All right. I can do one of these. Where's, uh, no, it's so unorganized. I hate it.
I'll try the dragon. The sm I thought it said smell battle, the small battle, small, huh?
You sniff battle. Ooh, pretty good. Actually that charges up fast.
Oh, are they getting too close? All right. Fly. Get in there. Get in there. Fly in the air. What
are you doing? Fire. Well, he killed a few people. Oh no. I let out. Oh, Ed.
Okay. That, that, wow. What an easy level for late game. I love it. Finally. It only took
15 hours of playing this game to get the powered gunman. Whatever that is. Are you getting tired
of lettuce, lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this town? You forgot the most important part.
That don't quite make it. Yeah. Double shot. Punch kick. Powered shot. Powered long shot.
Let's try it. What are you 380? Ah, we'll do, uh, we'll do, uh, copy paper in the beginning.
But hot, hot. Keep it cool. Cool. Defeat the girl Borg unit or defeat the machine Borg unit
or showdown hero Borg unit. Let's do this one. Wait, save the game. DLT, McDLT, hot beefy McD,
cool crisp LT, new McDLT, the new McDLT. Look, I can do better. What rock? All right. Let's copy
B for somebody. We're going to copy B for this guy. Bro, bro. Oh, first of all, the,
I look at person's fucking Tommy gun. This guy sucked for this scenario. It was bad. All right.
Woody. Oh, it's like a big burst. You get in close with that. He has a double shot. I mean,
it would work if, you know, if I wasn't surrounded by five fucking people, the dragon's going to come
in and just wipe out everybody. I can't wait. All right. Bring out the fucking dragon. Let's go.
Hey, huh? That's shrink. Just run them over already. Shit. This is my last guy.
It's a bad matchup. Thank God. You say you want a burger to be hot and delicious in your lettuce.
No, you got it wrong. Ice cold. She, I didn't even see what that was. Ice cold cheese. I mean,
it's time. What's, what's, what's, what's, what's with this one man spam? What's with this one man
spam? I'm seeing one man spam. Oh, no, don't time that person out. You say you're getting
tired of lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it. Yeah. You say that
just once you'd like your hamburger hot and your lettuce and tomato cool and crisp all at the same
time. Yeah. Well, I say you got it. I'm talking McDonald's new lettuce and tomato hamburger,
the McDLT, I'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot, hot side and the hot stays hot.
The new McDLT, hot, hot, crisp lettuce and tomato on the cool, cool side and the cool stays cool.
The new McDLT, cool, crisp. The beef stays hot, the cool stays crisp. Put it together,
you can't resist. The hottest taste, the coolest dish. Keep it hot, hot, keep it cool, cool.
McDLT. McDLT. McDLT. McDLT. It's a good time for the great taste of McDonald's.
Why am I such a shill from McDonald's? Um, I love McDonald's, it's like my favorite place.
Oh, what's this new guy?
What, he's like a construction bot?
Donald sucks.
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I
hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
What's the point of this?
Can I just drop it on his head?
He hates him.
Alright, just kill this guy.
Yeah, you can drop it on their head.
Now we get to actually see how useful this person is.
That shotgun's gotta be real close.
I'm gonna try to get in close to one of these guys.
Like this.
Oh!
Alright, what about the charged long shot?
Holy shit, that looked insane.
That hits.
Ooh, it's very good.
Come on.
It's pretty good.
Nice, hold him in place.
Nope.
Good.
Who's left?
Uh-oh.
My arch!
That bitch is...
I wanna shoot this way.
What are you doing?
Holy fuck, it does hurt a lot.
Shit.
He's so good.
Oh!
Damn it.
Still hit it.
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit.
Oh!
It's okay.
We got our dragon.
Ice dragon's pretty good.
Wait, it's the Israel dragon?
Hold on.
Wait.
What is the...
Uh, I...
Don't get killed.
Attack!
More!
I'll take sugar.
And water.
More.
More, please.
You're gonna get in the melee range
with fucking
Dragon?
What a fucking idiot.
What...
Bro...
What?
I get excited.
I am an excitable person.
You have a problem with that?
Turn off...
If you've got a problem with that,
turn off the stream.
Or what?
Okay.
Oh no.
End up the stream.
End up the stream, boys.
No, not yet.
No, not yet. I want to beat this. I got two of these though. That's good.
I don't want to- the construction robot's stupid.
Is this game on Steam that we awesome if it was if they just remade it?
They added more stuff and made it more- have like multiplier and stuff and balance it.
I got a data crystal for one of these and then just got one of these. It's like fucking Christmas. I want that guy.
Gared, I don't like this guy. He's kind of dumb.
390. No. I do like Woody. I can do a command girl. That's good. I like this team.
Defeat the girl Borg unit. Ooh
Huge we have massive air support now
Come on mirror. I'm so glad I have the huge airplane thing
They're very fast. Just like I am. Kill the support. Kill the medic. Kill the medic first. I've played games before
Wake up. I just shotgun to her in the face. Oh my god. That guy didn't even get to spawn. Oh
No heal. No heals. No heals. Oh
All healers. Come on. All right, just get in. Nice shot. Hell out here. Oh, he's a- he actually punches. That's cool
I'm ever gonna do a secret
EUTF 2 stream. Very dope. Did I hit it? No. Oh you healed you piece of shit. I did some good damage
I'm good. I did some good damage. Check out the dragon. I gotta land. Step.
The range. Big mistake. What the hell were you thinking knocking me all the way back here?
Get it. Just fire. Two huge distractions. This is good
Ice dragon is so good. This was supposed to be long and difficult, but not with the ice dragon
Hey, you got a long way to go. Come on over here. Oh, hi. I'm bouncing around too much.
Log Pyra would destroy you
Well, that would be assuming that the flog pyro
Was in the game for more than five minutes without getting vote kicked
Another wire girl. So many of these random crystals. I don't have
They don't have all the capabilities to combine them though
Another one. Damn, okay. What's this one?
Defeat the wing and angel Borg
Defeat the diver unit
training
Mr. Reverse Bolt
Defeat the bombing unit
Cold battle, I think I want to do Mr. Reverse Bolt
Does this game ever end?
Yeah, it does. I think we got it. I think so
I'm not doing a fourth stream. I promise you that
I do love this game though. I do I just it's fun just to fly around and just like
The streamer enjoys things how dare he
He's supposed to talk about how the rays of death at our sucks
He's not supposed to like this
What will be your new mouse? I don't know. I only know the death adder. It's the only thing I know
So I have no idea
I don't like a shitload of buttons and I don't like
I don't like it to be all jagged and like metal and shit
I just like a big palm mouse with two good easily clickable mouse pointers
and then just two
Or three big buttons on the side on the thumb side
Like you go to like the best buy and you go to the mice
And some of these things are fucking transformers. I don't want that. It's like why that's annoying to me
I just want a big palm mouse
But I want there to be buttons and I want to have like decent dpi and decent scaling
And have a good optical
Ratio on it
Wow, you went across the whole map
G pro wireless. What's g pro wireless? I don't want a wireless mouthy. I don't I don't want a wireless mouth either
If I wireless mites
they
No, because I can feel the input delay. It's like two milliseconds, but I know it's there. I don't want a wireless mouth
I can feel like the bluetooth delay
I don't want it g 52. It's literally faster than wired
Pop honey in this band
the diver
Beat the bombing unit
the oriental battle
Yeah, and that game's banned on steam
Whatever you banned streamer
Banned on steam but not on twitch. Oh, you just stay why are you so close?
Get out of here. Get out of here
27 there's a lot of them. Oh boy
Oh boy
These guys probably worth like two three hundred each so oh she didn't have a punch. All right, fine. Let's go
So I think i'm winning. That's a good mouse. Hold on. It's a good mouse
amazon amazon amazon
Oh, why mouse?
I just have a kawaii mouse
and not like a
I don't want that
Smile creepy devil
G43 wait
gaming mouse sold out
This looks like look this is like what I want though. It's just got two big buttons and it's a big palm
This is good
g 43
This does look like exactly what I want
Hmm, okay. All right. I'll try it. How much is it 69 dollars?
Got him. It's trash
What are you guys making me buy a shitty mouse or something?
I'm gonna look at some fucking reviews on google
Shotgun quick. Okay. These guys are getting too close. I can't even
Back up back up. Oh, well now you're all dead
No
Who spawns?
Come on somebody spawn again
Ah
We're so good just standing different opposite corners with the huge guys and then nobody can do anything
Get out of here. Get out of here. They're on to me her and the skill gameplay
I never said that I just said it was fun
an elsa dragon
logitech's logitech mx
Look it up. It's the best mouse you can buy
let's see
specifications
32 bit processor. Why does a mouse have a processor in it?
Normal ninja there's like five there's like 10 missions left. I think the whole game. Give me one of these
next 518
see images
No, I don't like I know I don't want it
It's like shape. It looks like molded clay. It's got like the little divots on the sides and it fits
I need a big one. What's that up on the g40?
Let's get a g502
No, fuck this. This is the thing I was talking about
Okay, if pieces, uh, no
This is the thing. That's like a robot. It's got like jagged pieces
Get the g403. I'll try it
Whoa, I got a tau master
four
We already have one of you
Okay
300 what arranged?
almighty type
Cosmic tempo spirit shot and tau sword
That's right. I feel like he's playing been playing the same level for five
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. I'm gonna pee
I'll be back when I come back. We're gonna finish the game and then i'm gonna see tomorrow
You're back. Yeah fun
Having fun selling
Okay, what's what's a good what's a good mission? How do we get to the end? What do you think?
Stop fooling around
One more bong hit
One more bong hit and then i'll see you later
Now how's this
Wait, he throws these swords. Ooh
Not bad
Actually takes a while to throw
Rose swords. Yeah, not bad
econ say something funny
What do you want me to say
I'm fucking dance around
I'm fucking dance
I don't think I will
Might as well take this capitalist down
What are you guys talking about guys I sold four hours ago at the bottom it's true
What life advice?
Just look at the market. Look at my look at my gamer market
Holy shit that link man
You couldn't you couldn't have condensed it a little. Oh my god. That was so ridiculous
That was like taking a an image right from google
Like the google link not the actual website link
Fire oh, sorry got the giant enemy friendly
Dragon, I just wanted to share a funny mouse
I just wanted to share funny mouse
Who's left? Oh, I wonder if you'll win
Uh-oh
Don't get cocky
cocky little freak
I could have done that louder, but I didn't want to and it would have been better
Is it a funny mouse?
I mean the the kid with the ship
Is just to keep him around forever
Let me see the funny mouse
What is that? That's like a super copy
Okay anymore. We got you over here the cold battle
the funny mouse
vertical mouse
Can't take you but I want to
I'm starting with dragon 220. I don't want I don't want to use you regular gunman
Where's that other? Uh, I use
220 is not very much
Going back to back
Can I see you?
Oh shit
Okay, I gotta get it off first
He's distracted
Land what am I what's going on? Oh, I was standing on an ice cube
Any more cold? Yeah, there is
Uh-oh. Well, there's more than one
no
Turn shoot
Do the missions in the dark areas to beat the game?
Whoa bad bad bad bad bad
All right, i'll do it
I'll do it just because hope just because it's helping too
Why would you do that? You fucking idiot like what an idiot like what an idiot?
You just launched him away from me. I'm just
Stupid come on stop invincibility
Any more? Yep. There's two more one more
What the fuck?
This guy's so good. I love uh, I love woody. How much health do they all have? Oh, this is it
Oh, you're so fucking annoying
It's just somewhat an irritating enemy
They're they're just trying to make me irritated
I don't even they're not even good at the game
Just like it's sucking is like they're getting lucky and shit. I'm good
Gamer rage, they're not even good. They're fucking not even good
Just like getting like lucky shots and shit and fucking whatever this guys suck
Why is he so high?
Now slam
Why am I slamming?
To feed the diver unit
Always tama come on and slam
Why people say that don't get in my way ice dragon is the best
Can I just have only ice dragons?
They're i'm just guaranteed to win
And I can be the only person on twitch that's beating gachi force from start to finish
Turn I can shoot this shit through walls, dude. You're not safe. It's the guy that beat gachi force on stream. It will be
eventually soon here
You should watch space jam on screen
I can't do that guys public domain movie night is not
What's your favorite movie?
I I can't do some of these things
turn
Jump get the fuck out of here, man
Turn good we need to watch killer bean
i've
i've seen
Most of it
I want to watch it that you guys haven't seen before i've seen it twice and I hate that. I have seen it twice
Why?
All right, defeat the wing and angel borg unit. I'm not gonna change anything. This is dream team activate the jelly diver
I gotta fly
See, I almost got attacked
Hey, i'm gonna say that's supposed to be doing damage to you
You're not fucking defy me
Jelly donut one more shot good. I gotta land and now we're gonna go forward
He's so good. He's better than all the dragons
There's no dragon better
Hey jump king lol
Yeah, that's funny
That's funny. All right. I gotta tell you it's it's not a big like I don't care that I did that
I'm not all broken up about this
Is it like ah shit? No, and one of my like gamer achievements is
Isn't available to look at anymore, but I that's I as it is
I streamed it. I can watch it if I wanted to
One more i'm so glad I got this
I got the good roll and I got the ice dragon
Did you just watch me beating jump king no
Already have one of these can you skip the unlocking sequences? I know you can't all right
Do the ones that are in the fire defeat the vehicle unit?
All right, anyone know how much longer there is anybody know like does anybody know I don't know
It's at least two hours. Is there really I feel like it wasn't that long
Nobody knows
You've done side missions all stream
Well, we had a few distractions
One of them's on screen right now
Just do the right missions and it'll be about 30 minutes
Let's go
I have to complete this
Even if I play the same character and do the same attack over and over again, i'm gonna win
Where are the missions? I was explicitly told
I was told
What's going on?
Do the kid mission
Use jelly diver now no
Put jelly diver in in the last two missions
We just have the two most overpowered things there's a giant ship and a giant dragon
I won't eat him
Pretty good wise what he said. What's with it? I thought there was a no anime game policy
um
This is like
What do you mean anime?
What have I ever said that policy?
That's not my policy
The kid's getting talk
Just because I don't want to play doki-doki literature club does not mean I have a policy
Where I won't play a game that has like an animated character in it
more of these
Training with these people
Why will I not play doki-doki literature club?
because
I don't wanna
I already know
I already know everything
I don't need to do it
How hard these were until I got ice dragon
Ra turn turn
Do you know how challenging this game was for me a little bit? I had to jump around dive dive dive
Shoot shoot shoot shoot dodge dodge
Oh, I am powerful. I am the overpowered character
anime game policy
I played that
recetteer shop game
It's like hyper anime game
Because every time I pressed the a button in that game
The character would go
That was every a button press I had I thought it was fun
Apologize. I didn't say what you said
I said die chokedista
which means
God help us
Yeah, it means like help help me
Here it is
Somebody just linked it click it. Oh cool. Uh magnet robot crash
It means are you okay? Wait, I think I got it. No, what the fuck how?
How did I get two c's?
No, I want no
C b a oh I need four
It's a d somewhere
God damn it
Hi
negative
That was just as every stream I do
It was me talking at first and then you guys
What are you gonna do?
No, don't fight me
Just stand still while I press x and win
Stop fighting me. You're supposed to just lose
Dude, you you've lost
He just did the thing
It's not even good. This team sucks his team fucking terrible. This team's fucking awful
He just did it
Look at that damage
Yes burn
burn
Yeah
Oh it is i'm just over here. I just play
Is the game over yet? Not yet. I'm getting so many characters. Where were this at the beginning of the game?
Oh, I need to try it. Oh, I need to try it
That's going against
Beat the death force unit beat the bombing unit
Beat the death force unit
Oh, it's going against the strategy use jelly diver. No
Okay, fine here
It's been so long since he pressed a button other than x
I've pressed b sometimes
I do
see
Gee
This is too good. Why would I do anything else?
It's called me a furry
Uh, no, i'm not actually the term is fucking scaly o c o's
Somebody told me that like two years ago. So on this stream
What was that?
You know how many times i've been corrected on this stream about what is and what isn't a furry
And if you by the way, if you have a frog, you're not a furry. You're like an
amphibioid or something, right?
What is it? But how could a frog be a more that doesn't make any sense?
It's a scaly
Frog how was a frog scaly?
It doesn't make any sense a slimy. Is that what they're called?
Be real with me here
Stop i've died just telling you what i've been told
Yeah, i'm just we're here you're here to correct me and help me understand these things
So it's slimer a scaly
Yes
Oh my computer is crashing
Oh type into your computer
Help fucking game sucks
What is making that?
Teacher noise
This is the last one finally, this is the weirdest counter-strike rats level ever
Probably gonna get a bomber
Time bomber remote bomber. It looks like we have another problem
Watch out veto. We're receiving a strong signal of the death force
Look at the greater tri-city area
It's a huge monster
What?
The gigantic battle defeat the cyber death dragon. I didn't save the game in like an hour
All right cyber death dragon
versus
Let's do an edit here. I want we want jelly. We want jelly
Jelly jelly jelly jelly. All right fine
I want to put in what is time bomber
on board
set bomb bomb shot
Good with bombs
It sounds too hard to do
remote bomber
Set bomb detonate
They both did the same thing
What was that wrestling group back in like the 90s?
The guys are the spikes the legion of doom
Yeah, i'm gonna put this guy in because he rhymes with the legion of doom
Uh
And where was the jelly guy?
I have done it. I don't know where the fuck he is. I'm gonna dump this whole box of toys in the recycling bin
Oh, wait, there's a worm
Okay, i'm gonna take the dragon out for now. I know you're gonna you're gonna go in the one good spot
You're like your own house
Okay, and
There you are
You too. I'll try you
You're like a
arrow
punai
shuriken and nympho
kagenyu arrow
Find enemies to the ground. Ooh, we'll try it
Oh
At least four anybody less less than four
3 30
I already have a woody gunman
Who do I put in? Oh, yeah
No, he's four. No
Here we go
Let's try it. All right defeat the giant
enemy
dragon
Again, that's another stream that i've done this team sucks. I don't even know what the bug does
Wait, oh I get it
He shoots out these spikes
They stay they stay
And he puts them down behind him, too
This is I kind of guy kind of cool but terrible at the same time
Just make death trap for everybody
So loud
Who is doing?
You're annoying
Anybody to tell you that?
Die, come on
It's like the final battle
Here he comes
Fuck didn't do anything
Whoa, oh this dude are they blowing up on it? I didn't read the instruction manual. Is it working?
Uh, I I did it. I'm the character that puts the suit on and has no idea how it works
But the suit is doing all kinds of powers
Who is it taking me? Whoa
I'll handle this jeremy. I'll handle this. What are you tired about? Whoa
He's dead. No, i'm dead jello. Oh slow motion in here
He's great
I just need to get that back and do it again
Stupid. Oh this is bad. I actually might still do it somehow magically
If I get another one of those things
Who's last?
Somebody's last
I have one or two more people left. Who was it?
Oh, he's dead
No damage before you died. Who is it?
New guy
I don't know what new guy does
New guy's about to die
Uh new guy's dead. Who's last?
I'll give you guys an A for effort. I did it. I beat the final dragon
I didn't know that a gachabor could increase in size like that
My headache stop. I am
Now the time has come
The galactic emperor has stolen his her personality
I have obtained enough gf energy from this human
You're not going to use the power that destroyed our planet again. Are you?
D-red this time with your help we can stop him
Give us your courage
We can never be defeated by the evil galactic emperor
Vito get ready for the final battle against the galactic emperor
Here we go the final battle. Just kidding
Here we go. Uh, just do the orange ones
Defeat the elite unit
This is this is okay. This is like the this is the hardest shit that we're at the end. This is the end
Do the last like five missions
Get rid of the jelly if I I can't get rid of the jelly now
All that matters is I have this ice dragon
What I mean, it's right there it was the last level
It was the last level
No
They figured it out. He's too slow. Just run around him
idiot
Falling in front of me. No, that's good
Don't let them fly. Don't let them fight. Don't let the fight do it
The cool dragon I know
I know but we're almost done. Don't worry
Godzilla godbeam is so good
Imagine if I didn't have that
I probably would have gave up
I would have been like guys. This is gonna take too long. I'm mostly going to scream for like four or five hours of dead time
I'm sorry. I can't do it anymore
But we got dragon so i'm able to
Damn it. They are
Fuck who do I have? This is the dumbest character in the whole game. Why is it even on here?
But I want the character to be the thing that I was gonna say i'll say it after the end of the stream
No, i'm not gonna say it. It's it's a literal
Bull I can't how come I can say it at the end because everyone's gonna leave
Did I make it? Oh fuck. Come on. Give me the next one
that's
I want to get a rare one. Come on. Do it. Let me have this
shit
Final but dude, there's my guy
150 this is the team that I want. I gotta have somebody else get some glory here who?
um
150 all right a normal ninja
Level three here somewhere
Where's my level three ninja?
All right, whatever. I don't care. He's not here
All right. This is the final battle
You promised what?
normal ninja
Omega lull
Everyone is here, right?
I had to sneak away so my family wouldn't notice
Grown-ups are panicking
It would be everyone can see the huge monster in the air
I should have stayed hidden after all
I can do this. I can do this. I can do this
We have to save orochi, too
Just don't count on me
I want to go home
time to attack
I mean, let's do it
This is it g red
You're on the bench. We're going to use all of the gf energy to grow vigor and defeat the galactic emperor
Believe in the power of the gachaborgs believe in yourself
veto
Everyone go for it
a final battle
ice dragon woody
rare bogus
tank
and normal ninja
These were the five
saviors of our earth
The earth is flat
That's the big reveal actually
Let's go
Oh, no ice dragon sucks. He's not good here
Should I fly?
Go this way
I'm seeing it's him saying those things
His mouth is opening out
Oh, yeah
I'll get it. Here we go. He's in pain. You're laughing
All right, I gotta have to get up here anymore eyes
Going up up up up up. You can't make it
I i'm hitting it. I hit it. I hit it. I hit it. I did it. I did it
All right, just stay right here and kill him
Dps phase
Oh, no 143
He's almost no. I gotta kill all the stuff
Oh shit dragon. Mana. Where are you?
mana
Mana heal. I need heals
Where are you?
How do I get up there?
Can I go in like a teleporter?
Do I have to go in? How do I get up there?
Let me in
Oh shit
Let's go woody
Why woody?
This sucks
Oh
Fuck hit the fucking thing. No, fuck these ice crystals are just blocking everything. Um, I don't no
No
Get in there
Uh, uh, uh
Don't throw it throw it this guy's not very good at this point because he had all this stupid bullshit
Who's the final character? I have I don't know
It's normal ninja
No, it's not it's tank
Dude, what the fuck?
Can I have power?
All right, this is dumb. This is dumb
Get in real close
Come on normal ninja get in there
Okay, here's something that I learned. Where are they? I only have one ice dragon
I need just one shitty person. Wait, you can fly around and stuff. Wait
Dragons let's go
I know what I need to do. Just only beam. So take up take out the here we go. Take out the eyes and just
Oh, then then go home
Here we go. This is it. Is it working?
It's not
Are you sure just go up there and teleport but he'll get hit by all the bullshit
Get in there
Let me in
Port me up
Okay, muahaha
That's why I didn't want to go up here
Okay, they broke his neck
I have to stay down here
No, get on the ground
Am I on the ground?
I had a good spot last time. All right, here we go. I'm on the ground. This is it
Come on do it again and shoot these fucking things
Where is it? I need help down here
You guys are dumb
Beam this shit's gonna work out
I don't know why you're flying right now, but fucking kind of a moron
This is gonna work
I'm gonna get another one of those super beams
Here we go
Oh, you can't see my health
You haven't been able to see my health for the last like four hours
Hit it. Am I not hitting it?
Move left idiot. Let me move left. This shit goes through walls
I can't even move left you understand like this
And I just moved left and now they're all attacking me
I just made it apparently easier for them to hit me
Come on
again
Come on again. Give me the beam. Come on
What the fuck? Oh, no, then you get in there drop this fucking shield
It's a smooth brain
What the fuck
What are you talking about?
Oh my god, i'm gonna die
How am I still alive?
What the fuck have I not been killed?
It's a matter of seconds before I die
It's only a matter of seconds. Oh
It's two dragons of stride two dragons and then I don't know woody
Just throw all no, it's got to be two dragons and don't fucking move
Get rid of the normal ninjas and then
320 put in the blue ninja
Gatling gun is op
Ah, but we lose
But we lose the dragon
Who is fire dragon? He's fucking he's a thousand. He's a thousand
He's a thousand just put the ninjas between the dragons to build meter. That's a smart idea
I don't know why I didn't do it. All right, here we go. I gotta move move just back up get the eyes
Oh puny human
That's good. All right back it up
Okay, now just stand here and land
This is it. This was calculated
Shit, this is not it's apparently not in a good spot. It's not hitting it. There we go right in the one in the corner
Okay, we're all right again. Okay, again again again. It's in the perfect spot
He's fucking dead right now
He's dead
Okay, don't panic. I have plenty of time
What just happened to him?
Okay, we're good
Build meter get up there and just hold the button down
You motherfucker
Okay, come on dragon
No, you gotta move man
Okay, right there. Don't move
This is good, right? This is in the right spot
Okay, I got 270
What where am I?
No, it's in the wrong spot
beef core
Oh cop
Okay, turns out the gatling gunner. Uh
No, I can't even go so I can't even go up there
I can't even go up there with that guy
I brought the gatling gunner up and he just bounced around a hundred times. No get out of here
We're doing normal ninjas only
In the middle
I can't do three dragons. It's too much
I didn't even choke the flame dragon got fucking juggled around. I can't prevent that. I had a good spot
Fuck flame dragon just fucking blew it. Good asshole. He got knocked around and then out of place
Oh shit, let's go hurry up
I had it too
Bullshit what the hell even happened there?
All right. I'm not in a good spot. I gotta move
This is it. This is the spot. It's right there. Don't land you fucking idiot
turn
Go turn. What are you doing?
Don't step forward. I didn't tell you to do that
I need the power blast
All right, break it
Just kill him don't even do another phase just kill it. Oh you motherfucker
Oh, he's so close
Who's next?
I thought maybe crashing into himself. I don't know why
Okay, wait, I have a better idea
No, that's a terrible idea. Just kill it aim at it
Get me in that's all I want now. It's broken beef core. Whatever kill this. Okay. Here we go
It's not that kickball where you put your head down
and spin
until
Just stop
It's not even in the right spot. I have the power
Okay, stop right here
Land the fucking ship
Activate it stop turning
Turn the other way turn this way
Eat shit, I win
You just didn't play kickball. You put the bat down and you spin around a bunch of times and you're wicked dizzy
I win we did it. Oh, we got an animated end
No, you just made me choke on my water
The bat in kickball no
Bye oh that's how big they were I thought it was like 100 feet tall
Holy shit
battles 156
82 percent win percentage 82 gotcha boards 16 hours and nine minutes
battle results
team
Oh this how many times they were on the team?
Okay
Didn't really use the guy on third very much
Oh, that's not good
Apologize to mana
Just because they were on the team doesn't mean they did anything
You should know from doing group projects
She could have just been sleeping at her desk
The end see you again
Nice see you tomorrow. See you tomorrow. That was gotcha force one of my favorite game cube games
Beat it fun
It was cool
Glad you enjoyed it
I'll see you tomorrow for pat upon
Pat upon one or two. I don't know. I'll figure it out before then we'll figure it out
That's gonna be it
Thanks for joining me as always
We'll see you
Oh, yeah, we'll figure it out in pre-stream chat. We'll figure it out
But we'll do the bits
We'll see you tomorrow. We'll see you tomorrow
Let me just get this other screen here
Move this over
It was a lot of fun. I'm glad I got to experience that on stream
Tell us the thing I will at the very end
At the very end, but for now we have 15 from shadow teddy. Thank you
Like the comedy chart. Oh, yeah, let's go before we go
It looks let's see
Not bad
It's that little part in the middle. That's all
But thank you shadow teddy for the 15 dolls recently stumbled on your streams after years of watching a youtube vid youtube vids
Much love and thanks for the entertainment. Thanks for the 15 dolls and
Welcome. I was on youtube for a long time and
I'm about to be
On twitch for the same amount of time that I was on youtube if you could believe that
They're about to be tied
I was on youtube for about five to six years and now we're on twitch for about five years. So we're coming up there
Peaceful hailey. Thanks for the 250
I've been doubting myself again whether I should be streaming or not
Everyone always compliments me on it and like is super nice
But I get that one person who puts doubt in my mind whether I should be doing it or not
It's what I want to do, but i'm a girl
So I feel like I can't make it on twitch and i'm terrified
The compliments I do get feel like I don't deserve it
Like it's really a me issue. Well, i'll tell you right now. It sounds like you're second guessing yourself a little too much
streaming should be something that you want to do something that you've that you really feel like doing and
Sure, we make jokes on this channel about like, oh what do you want me to do? Look at me
What oh chat's bullying, but i'm gonna bully you you're bullying me what came
but at the end of the day
you need to
kind of be in control of you and
Be comfortable with what you're doing
Streaming should be something that you every time you turn it on you like this is what I want to do
And there will be people that are going to say negative shit. Unfortunately, this is the nature of the internet
It's the nature of kind of where we are. It's unfortunate, but it's true
and you either take some of the maybe more harsher criticisms or
Some of the negative comments of people that say things
And you either just ignore them or you know you
It's hard to not be like oh you shut up
What are you fucking dumb?
but just make sure it's something you want to do make sure something you really feel like doing because if it's not
And you'll know
Make the criticism feel you to do it more to do more and work harder
um
It's hard. Yeah, but at the same time some people just kind of come in and just say shit just because they're just being crazy
And some of the criticisms are some of the kind of attacking is just because they feel like doing it
It's not like oh, hey, here's what I think how I think you could improve your stream
But I wish you luck
Make sure you want to do it though. That's the most important thing
oiki, thanks for the five dollars
Remember chat has ruined me. I started saying resident sleeper in casual conversation or in texts when things were boring
And how to explain it to my mom what it meant
Then last night she sent me that she used it in a post on her political blog
But she talked about how much she hates joe biden, please help. Oh boy
oh, man
I I got nothing to say about that one. That's
that's a
you uh
Mom is now using your lingo and now you're gonna have to figure out another words
Because once your parents start doing it, you can't do it anymore. You gotta get resident sleeper
Now you gotta come up with a new one. It's over
Resident sleeper
Well, I hope you figure that out. She'll probably just get over after a while
She'll probably be like, I don't understand this. I'm gonna go back to saying
tired
Maybe not. Maybe she's here now
Major moose man. Thanks with 250 first don't know a long time fan. I've been only watching regularly since sakiro
Streams have really been helping me through college
And I know you said that if you didn't play it in november, you wouldn't stream it
But I was wondering if you ever play star wars jedi fall in order. It's not perfect
But its combat is like sick. I'm gonna stop you here
I played it for about 45 minutes off stream and I did not like it
I was not a fan first hour of that game or hour and a half was was climbing
Metal boxes and then sliding down and then I got killed like 15 times
by
That weird like pig dog thing. I was like, I don't want to play this. I love star wars. You got
mount fiji
You rage quit the tutorial. No, I got out of the tutorial and I got to that first area where you have to
Like track down the the jedi's smell
And I stumbled into this cave and there was like a boss in the cave and I was like, oh cool
The first boss and I died like after 10 times
And I was like, I don't even like this game. That's what happened. I'm just telling you the truth
I'm just telling you what happened. It went from 15 to 10. So that means it was 20
If you're paying attention
I love star wars. I just wasn't a bit. I yeah, I just wouldn't didn't grab me
Drummage door. Thanks for the 250. Yo funny man guy bro, dude mate friend. I watched your rhythm heaven heaven heaven. Hold on itchy
I've watched hey
Let's try that over. Hold on itching my eye. I watched your rhythm heaven fever stream. It's kind of a hard string of things to say
Uh, maybe realize you'd most likely really enjoy fantastic game called thumper
Uh, some have classified it as a psychedelic horror rhythm game. I've actually
I don't think I can play this from I remember looking at this before
This game really hurts my eyes
Something about like that moving with the neon colors and it kind of hurts my head
Yeah, my brain melts
Unfortunately, it looks fun, but I know I wouldn't be able to I'd be like i'd have to fucking stop after like 30 minutes
But no, it's it does look fun
One less game to get in the way of jeru crew
Red wall was thanks for five dollars germ a longtime watcher
You really helped me when I was just down in the dumps a while ago
Just wanting to know that but also i'm wondering if you're going to play armored core
I don't know
Here's the problem I have with armored core
I want to have like
12 of them. Do you have I mean, what's ones do you play? Do you it doesn't matter?
There's a lot of them just
There's only four
It's 15 games play them all or just play four
Okay, which one what what if you guys can give me reliably?
The one or two that or the one that is the best one like the one that you should play
And i'll probably give it a try four is the one it's four. Okay
Uh, maybe
They'll say also warhammer 40k space marine too because I want you to suffer with the rest of us
Bad thq died. Thanks for reading. You're a goblin
I know hey jason. Thanks for the 250 germ
I'd like to thank you for letting me borrow your lamborghini and letting me stay in your penthouse for free during the pandemic
Since you're a multi-millionaire, I guess I could help you out too. Enjoy the 250 on me, bro
Um, you're welcome
Silence serenity. Thanks for the 250 germ another you're running for public office. We're requesting that you release your tax returns
We've caught this one already
um
I do my taxes and I pay my taxes
Okay, we got a guy
I got a cpa
I'm running for fucking office
You understand how badly I would lose
The oh there's so much here. The only political ad they'd need to do was
I mean they you got me saying
You're from mayor of vegas
I like forgot like i'm like, oh look at all the horrible things i've said
You go back and like oh pissing my face. I'm like i'm gonna shit in my toilet and eat it or whatever
Like oh, that's it. I don't think that matters anymore
They would love it
That's why they would vote for you
interesting thought project
Ajax thanks for the five dollars. I can't tell if you were doing a british or australian accent
It was just an accent doesn't need to be from any part of the world
Hey jason, thanks for 250 more
Remember, it's me again. Thanks for giving me a small loan of nine point eight five million dollars
I won't pay it back directly since I pay taxes on things I buy from the grocery store already
It's a really good callback
Thanks for the 250
One one one two e thanks for three dollars number 15 burger king foot lettuce
Last thing this is a coffee pasta
I remember it was spammed for a while
Thanks for the three dollars
Man with baby hands. Thanks for five dollars
I was expecting spi, but what I got was this funny sounding guy calling himself germa pretending to be spi
plus two
Thanks for the five dollars
Oh, yeah, I did say it like 10 times
Silent serenity. Thanks for 250. I'm a software engineer for a living
I'd love to work with you to make a germa coin a reality. Let me know if you want to discuss absolutely not
Absolutely, not no in a hundred million years. No zero absolute zero. No interest at all zero
No, no, no, absolutely not. No, okay. I think we're clear good. Thanks for the offer though
Uh, thank you. I try way too hard for the 15 dollars
Thanks to the 1500 bits
Germa, you should contact orb
Look into his orbit system. He has for the comedy economy
He is actually how I found out about you back when he visited pax east one year
Love the streams. Keep it up. He's a he's a great dude. He actually came to vegas last year. It's great to see him
We don't like play games at all and we don't really do anything with each other anymore
But he we like it we
When he's around we hang out. It was great to see him last year. I heard that name in a while
Bragging about it. Yeah, I am. He's I like him. He's cool
Uh, yeah, maybe i'll hit him up and see what I do what how he does it. Thanks for the tip though
And also we had more 52 more fifteen dollars fifteen hundred bits
Back to back one from abomination zero and one from big mama
Uh, big mama says I will pay you so I don't have to hear more stock jokes, please
My children are crying
They you're gonna have to hear them for a little while longer, especially if I end up doing
Uh this thing
Might not happen
Uh, we also have it's an image
It's a t-shirt design from abomination zero. Thanks again for the 15 dollars
And here's the t-shirt
I don't know if here's the thing about
Like this could be
On a website right now and I have no idea
I don't know if you're making a joke or if like if you found this
I'm not sure if this is something you made or someone did it already
but
There's this
Jesus hey video games mcgee. Thanks for five dollars
I'm fighting the urge to buy those mozzarella cheese sticks that they sell in the school cafeterias
Only available in bulk of 200 cheese sticks. Is this a normal problem to have please help?
Where are you gonna put those?
Are you gonna put 200 mozzarella sticks? That's a lot. That's too many
Um, but those things are great
I actually love those things. So i've you're not gonna get any
Um kick back here from me
Thanks for the five dollars
Blueberry juice. Thanks for 250
Remember, thanks again for banning me yesterday
It let me get all my work done. However, there's a new problem that I need your advice for
See, I was doing some yard work where I had to spread this 10
Bag all over my lawn
And then they say sorry, I fucked up I sent that last one way too soon. It was another 250. I fucked up so bad
I'm kind of emotional because of this
But yeah, I was doing some yard work and after laying down that giant bag of soil
I wanted to seed it with clover. It wasn't bad. It was a good workout and I got it done in about six hours
Now I have a real problem. These little birds keep coming by and eating all of it. This is one out of three
Hold on
Uh jeb guys gave three dollars
Jeremiah i'm starting my chem phd at brandeis next fall any good food places in boston I should visit
Thanks for being the best streamer buddy
You know, i've been so far out of the game
For boston restaurants. I couldn't even really tell you it's been like three years since i've eaten any of them
Trying to think of and then some of them might not even
um
Like three or four years ago. This is probably the last I you know what? I don't think three years since you've eaten in boston
Uh, the burger places are good. Yeah, like boston burger company is awesome. Somebody already said it
boston burger company is fantastic
Um, if you don't like hamburgers, he's a fake bostonian go to yeah, go to the north go to the north
Okay, here you go. Go to the north end
Uh spin around in a circle and then walk in a direction
To any of the restaurants because they're all good. What's that pizza place called? It was fucking fantastic
Uh, oh my god. It's like the most famous fucking it's like the best
It's like the most famous boston pizza place
What's wrong with me?
uh
Regina ppf pizzeria regina regina pizzeria
It's incredible boston italiano
Yeah, I would say yeah those but go to the north end some of those restaurants
They're they're insane
I don't remember very much any specifics, but i've had some of the best seafood i've ever had my whole life from the north end
I wish you luck. It's a great city. Have fun
All right, gooberry juice that we're talking about you soil that you play you get a real problem
Got some bird
Okay, i've tried everything to scare off these birds, but they're just too smart
I hung up tin foil strips and some cans to make some noise, but they don't give a shit
I try to I put the sprinklers to go on but they just wait till they turn off and they go back to eating
I made a scarecrow
This is your scarecrow
This scarecrow isn't gonna do anything
How would this scarecrow?
Ooh, that's macro
Um, why would that work?
I bought I broke down and made a scarecrow. Okay, I think they even ended up liking the scarecrow
I'm being jebaited by birds. I can't live like this anymore
Please if there's any advice you can give me to help my bird plight. I would be eternally grateful
By the way, that wasn't my sweater. I have a sex life all the time. That's good to know
Um, okay. I'm gonna i'm gonna solve your problem right now
You ready buy a bird feeder
Fill it with bird seed
And move it 10 feet away from where you want them to avoid
I just solved your problem
Get bird seed get like the most delicious bird seed that you know find out what kind of birds they are
Find out their eating habits and what they like
and then if you like if you have a bird problem over here with the soil and
No, no, no, no, no, their favorite restaurant is 10 feet away. Why are you guys saying? No, don't do not do that
Are you saying bribe the birds?
I'm saying create a bird restaurant that they go to that you can just fill with like
Four dollar bag of bird seed that they like once like every three weeks
And then and then they'll hang out and you'll have like some music while you're out working in the yard
And you get to enjoy the cool birds over at the bird restaurant
But then you're probably gonna get another problem squirrels love that shit
So then you'll end up having a squirrel problem and then I can't help you after that. I have I I only solve one problem at a time
uh
Don't take any advice from me ever everything I say is made up. Thanks for the uh, thanks for like the fucking
$15
Yoda 985. Thanks for the 250 35 year old man plays a scuff of 5,000 14 year olds
35 year old man plays scuff of 5,000 14 year olds
Come on. Give yourselves a little more
Come on
This probably they're probably a thousand 14 year olds
4,000 of you are at least probably over the age of 18 19 20
They might have been like two four to five hundred. I don't know. It's like they're a good band. They're a family-friendly band
What are you talking about? What's so wrong with playing the mighty mighty boss stones?
They have like positive messages in their songs. I listened to the mighty muddy boss stones when I was 14
That's when their cd came out. That's when I owned it matches up perfectly a bulbous swag
Thanks for the five dollars. You're now the number one ska streamer
Check out big d in the kids table good songs. I can recommend are shining on and my girlfriend is on drugs
Give it a look
Dev a kitty. Thanks for the 250 the afv intro music is true penis music
Also your phone in the toilet april foos joke fits directly into an episode of afv
Yes, it does, but that would just be a vine the zoomer afv is vines
And tiktok compile them all those watch tiktok compilations that you guys tell me to do
It's just america's funniest home videos for the new generation. Thank you though bingo sunshine
Thanks for the 250 the digimon movie soundtrack was basically a best of 90s ska compendium at times
Small bits means small message. I guess germa auto. Thanks for the 250
Uh arrow son gave five community subs and I missed it. You still hear arrow son. Thanks for the five subs
Appreciate it
What curve bumble? Thanks for the 500 bits five dollars. Thanks for giving this game more exposure
And it's probably had in 17 years
It was great to watch you play it kind of a dream come true
Also, if you're somehow reading this before the end, please turn the audio back on this is literally the end of the game
Yeah, I wasn't gonna just yeah, I don't worry. I wasn't gonna just have there be no audio
Thanks for the five dollars though
Bingo sunshine. Thanks for 250. Please don't ever play this music again. Love you bud
What are you referencing the neverhood? You just got yourself a
Minus one streamer to chat person point rat plushies on etsy
What do you want me to look what do you want me to do from a 95 rat plushies two sizes rat?
Regular rat x how big are these?
My giant rat came so much quicker than expected and made me so happy when I received it
I really appreciate the shop absolutely beautiful the most perfect item. I've had the pleasure of purchasing
Very well made
Actually, these are pretty well made. This is very well made. This is exceptionally well made
Like these are great
You need to get it for the reddit shelf
Should I get one should I get one for the reddit shelf?
I should sell them. I don't own this. I don't own this
Yes, you do I own the idea of a giant rat making all the rules the character of the rat
It's already a character that I don't own
Yes, you do
Windows is an ad for the windows movie maker game
Yeah
What's what what's wrong with having an ad for the windows movie maker game? That game's fucking fantastic
by
3d movie maker. I can't how am I gonna who am I what do I call?
Uh, my hundred and twelve thousand dollar net worth according to fucking twitch statistics, whatever
I don't think it's going to cover even the legal fees
To go to the civil court to be able to transfer those files to me. You understand guys?
Maka-sh bill gates. That's cool though. That's really cool
Uh, yeah, that's cool
Smarky mc gave fifty dollars and I didn't see it. Thank you. Smarky five thousand bits fifty
Fucking dollars and I didn't see it. How did I not see this?
Remember, can you please read the entire wall of lore when you play neverhood? I probably will at least most of it
Thanks for the huge amount of money. I really appreciate it. I'm probably not going to do that
Thanks for the gigantic bit drop
smarky mc
Freak out. Thanks for the five dollars freak out. You've been banned. I don't read your message anymore, but I will give you this
Um, well, I have to put my foot down
They sing the curious george theme song in their bits
But I you know, i've said i'm not gonna read their messages anymore. I have to stand by that
Play the song. No, they sing the song in text
That's so sad. What the fuck happened to you? Uh, what I have to put my foot down
You know how many you know how many fucked up messages i've received
He's changed
Would you call his message fucked up now? No, but you can't you can't burn the barn down
And when the police show up you start singing the curious george soundtrack
And think that you're not gonna get arrested
Oh shit, he's gonna start locking people up
Thanks for the five dollars though
All right dark soul. Thanks for the 258 germa. Just want to thank you for introducing chat to my favorite genre cringe core
The streams have been great while I work on my ascension to godhood with a custom full-body vr chat avatar
Also, i'm shutting down the dru crew pod squad is now on the job until you play skyrim vr
Hey dinosaurs rex. Thanks to 250 check out neil
Cicierega have fun pronouncing that I did
He makes mashup albums. My favorite album is mouth moods and my absolute favorite track of his is mashup album of this track
A little listen, okay. I'll give it 15 seconds. Give it a 15. Look, we'll give it 15 seconds. Let's see. Here we go
Pretty good good very good
Wait, if you do a double copyright, just one copyright like kill the other copyright. How does that work?
Does one supersede the other do they do they copyright fight each other?
How does it work?
hell
That's really cool. I'm gonna have to listen to more of these later when i'm in the bath
Oh, i'll tell you a quick little story about the bath. I took a bath last night
and um
I
Have this device
That I put my ipad in
And it hooks into the ipad and it's this big stretchy
solid it's
Like a big wire that I can fold and move around and it can the ipad can stand up
You can bend it you can put it around your arm. You can put it on the edge of a bed and it's pretty cool
It's actually a really cool device
Um, so yesterday I was filling the bathtub and I was setting this thing up
And it was like getting it ready
And I turned the water on and the ipad
shook a little bit
Because it was like I had it standing up on the edge
And it fell into the water
And by the way the water wouldn't even like really turned on it was like just barely like not even a tenth of a
Centimeter of water on the ground and it like went into the water and like I grabbed it immediately and then I was fine
And I wiped it off quickly with the towel and it's fine
I mean, no the water was like on but it wasn't like the whole bath
It was like just hitting the surf that was hitting the bottom. You know what I mean? It was a good story
Water wasn't on he just dropped his ipad in the bathtub and he added the water part to make you think
That wall that could have been crazy, but there was no water in that tub. He's a liar
No, there was water in that tub. Not very much
Were you naked when it happened? Yes
What were you gonna tell us at the end of the stream you phony fucking piece of shit. Hey relax
It's a thought project
No, I actually did drop the fucking in the bathtub. It was bad
Uh, what was I gonna say the very uh, okay. Hey listen
So that jelly character, okay
I'm gonna no no no no it has to be the very end because I want everyone to be able to leave to not have to
Listen to it
Let's do the credits and lying about putting like drop and shit in his bathtub
Really dude
Oh, I turned the water on the water wasn't on but I turned it off and like I tried this thing and I put
It on the side, but it fell but the water wasn't on but the water was on
Fucking piece of shit got him. We got him. We got him now guys
We got him now
If you forget i'm leaving well, you're gonna leave anyways because the stream's gonna be over five community subs
from chibi
Fumako
Thanks for the five subs
Right at the very end. All right, let's get the credits rolling
All the subs today
Thank you. Once again all of you here they come
There they are
subs
Thanks everybody
for your subscriptions
Thanks for subbing the channel. Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for watching. Thanks for being around
Thanks for being here you i'm talking to you you you in the back back there you in the back
You've been talking through the whole stream
You know, there's a part in um
Bill Murray
Did this movie called Scrooged?
and
It's about Bill Murray. It becomes
Ebenezer Scrooge. It's kind of a weird movie. It's a good movie though
At the very end of the movie
He's thanking everybody for watching. He's like, hey, thanks sir. Thank you. Thank all all the men
Thanks all the men there all the women. Thank you all the women
Thank you. Thank the dog
And you the person that's been talking the whole movie he points right at the
Screen and I was watching the movie with my cousin at the time and the cousin freaked out
We were like 12 like 10 whatever and she was like what me?
Oh like he's talking to me and i'm like, holy shit. He's talking to you
You were talking this whole movie. What the hell? How does he know?
Hopefully I just did that to somebody else. There's another made-up story
No, what a dumb thing to make up
All these things I say
But i'm I just fucking I got you. I you have no idea what could be real
I have such i'm such a master of illusions. You have no idea
I I might not even be fucking 34 years old. I might be fucking 40. I might be 20
You have no idea how old I am. Yes, you do. No, that was funny
It was a funny thing that happened when I was a kid
Hey, thanks for the subs though. All of you brian the last dinosaur
Thanks for the three dollars get a logitech mx-5 18
I think we caught that one earlier
It's a perfect mouse that will last you literally decades like my old one did
I have to tell you logitech is a good company, right?
Logitech makes pretty good shit. Don't they from what i've seen and heard?
Kind of yeah
What about the music? I got you
I'll have to give it a look
Animal jason, thanks for three dollars. No, you can't just watch a streamer because he does funny voices. Haha grandpa voice go brr
That's true
Oath horse. Thanks for the thousand bits really fun stream today
I painted a bob ross painting while listening the pog market is a hilarious idea
Looking forward to seeing what you do with it
I love your childlike enjoyment of gotcha force nostalgia over a game that literally no one in the chat likes
I love that you don't care
Also, the music makes me want to claw all the flesh off my face
Well, I mean there's a story there. I'm not going to get bullied twice in a row
Beautiful joe was like escape sucks. It's boring do something. I hate this and I was like, okay fine
It's not gonna happen twice in a row. You got your veto your vetoed beautiful joe
I'm gonna play my two hundred and fifty dollar piece of plastic
CD made out of plastic metal
What is a cd made out of?
Aluminum metal. I that's an I seriously what?
Is a cd made out of is it plastic? It's like a weird compound
Tough brittle plastic called polycarbonate
And sandwiched in the middle is a is aluminum, right? Okay. I had it right plastic and aluminum. I had it right
No, it was fun. Thanks for the thousand bits
You have a kitty. Thanks for the 250 germa. You won't be the first one to finish gotcha force on twitch
uh
Some summa did it a few weeks ago ban this person
Is this where I go? What's who's summer?
What's who's summer and then you say summer
Is this when is this how is this how this joke plays out?
Yeah
right, okay
Dark soul. Thanks for 250. Are you not able to do the amazon watch together streams on here or something?
I've seen other streamers able to use that and watch like star trek
We should see what's on there and maybe we can watch something pog instead
By the way, if you're going to do half life alex
You should do that before bone works because bone works is so good. I think alex just sucks
damn a strong opinion
Uh, I don't know man. Um, the reason why I didn't do the amazon watch party is because
It's a very limited catalog of stuff
And it's only available to the united states
So I was like, yeah
Maybe if they start opening that up that might be fun to do like officially
But yeah, it's only united states and it's only if you have amazon prime
And I i'll be honest. I'm not in the market of trying to make less people watch my stream
I don't that's not i'm not into I don't want to do that. I have no interest in doing that
You have to have amazon prime you have to have twitch prime you have to be from the united states
Like I just like carved off a significant portion of people that watch
I'm in the market of wanting people to watch not telling people they can't
It's a kind of like an exclusive club thing that I don't really want to do
If they start expanding it, then yeah, i'll try it. But as of right now, probably not doctor zero fox
Thanks for the 15 dollars
They say u w u
U w u
Thanks to 15 bucks
Hey dried cleaner. Thanks to 300 bits germa
I was wondering if you ever played fable 2 or streamed it some of the best games ever
I recommend it for one of your streams
I played this shit out of fable 2 played this shit out of fable 1 and I got to the part in fable 3
Where you opened up chests to do things?
And said this game sucks and stopped playing it
It was like within the first hour and a half, but I do I love that franchise
I've played the hell out of the first two games
They're very fun, but probably not on stream. I've played through them multiple times
With multiple characters doing multiple builds there's not much else
I can do in fable 1 and 2 that I have not done in a playthrough that i've done years ago
They're great though peaceful. Haley. Thanks for the 250. I don't want to be a debbie downer
But to be honest, I don't have anyone in my real day-to-day life to talk to
But an hour ago me and my boyfriend split up after five years
We've known each other for longer, but god, I never thought this would happen
I need to focus on me now. I don't really know what else to say. Thanks for listening
That's a long relationship. That's a long time
But you're right
Now you do you
You take care of your life
And move forward
That's really all you can do
You don't back up on the highway
forward
Maybe you don't
Your analogies suck
What if you're on the highway you go forward you don't stop you don't go back you move forward and you go to your exit
If you miss your exit
You don't stop you fucking go forward and you find another way to get off the next exit and you finally figure out you fucking
Where you go?
You clip through the trees
No, you don't do that
You go off road
What kind of car do you drive?
but anyways
Uh, i'm gonna say it again. You don't go reverse on the highway done and that's exactly how you should feel
Forward don't look back forward clip through any trees. Don't just fucking go forward
right
Chat beta streamer doesn't turn around on the highway
Yeah, beta streamer doesn't
Die in a car wreck
Okay, that sounds good. That sounds great. Actually
Good. Okay
Why the trees on the highway?
Can you imagine if they were just a bunch of trees in the road and you have you going like 60 plus miles per hour?
Holy shit, what a design oversight that would have been
That's challenge mode
It would be like skiing in the olympics those flags
but anyways, hailey
I wish you the best that's
It's not the best thing to happen
But you'll be all right. Just keep going forward. Don't fucking go on. They don't hit the brakes on the highway
And the germa 985 says dog shit advice
Literally never ask germa for advice on anything because all of his advice
is
dog shit
true
Hit the brakes ever
No, don't no do that when you're getting off
Do that when you're getting off you have to hit the brakes when you're getting off
Otherwise, you're gonna be in big trouble. I wish you the best though. Take care of yourself. Take care of you
Hey, thank you mick for the $15 germa. It's good to see you play a game
You like so much
And i'm excited for you to get back to finishing every nancy drew game back to back. You're gonna be very disappointed
Thanks the 15 bucks old 70 ham. Thanks for three dollars and 20 cents
Hey germa
Here's some bite-sized bits because you're epic. Oh, thanks. Do I get the junkie donut? Thanks for three bucks
Rock writing. Thanks for the 300 bits
Uh, you don't have to read this if you want to wrap the stream up. No, we're good. We're good
I mean i'm i'm about 30 minutes over my
Time but at my maximum time, but we got an over heel going. It's okay
This is this. It's good. Just not like eight hours
Like i'm I just can't I gotta stop doing like the fucking seven to
Eight plus hour streams. I can't do them anymore
Like I physically have to stop doing those
I'm sorry, but it's just the it's reality
No more 12 hours. No, the lord of the rings stream will be the longest stream
I will ever do ever until the stream doesn't stream anymore
It sucks. Well, actually i'm actually kind of happy about that. That's fine. But anyways, they say
Uh, my fiance and I watched the complete lord of the rings trilogy last night perfect timing
And I hate that now my nostalgic connection to the soundtrack
Has been replaced with a fever dream. That was when I fell asleep to your two towers stream
Then woke up at some unholy hour of the night to the uruk-hai theme
On a seemingly endless loop and you trying to knock down
Those damn orc ladders playing his gimli
Anyway, my best to you chat and auto, you know, it's really sad. Is somebody telling me that I have
Ruined the lord of the rings for them. That's heavy
That's
That's tough to hear. Holy that's not that's bad
Something that is so hard to ruin for somebody is that franchise and i've done it somehow
I've never seen the films looked boring
Really good. You'll like them. Just watch them watch them when you have like the amount of time
When you get like three weeks to yourself
Watch the lord of the rings, but thanks rock rock writing. Sorry to have ruined your favorite franchise ever mine, too
Thanks, three bucks
Shadows one disciple. Thanks for the 250 germa. Your enthusiasm forgot your force is palpable
It's great when you love a game. Don't let chat tell you differently
I would probably enjoy this game too, but I don't have a game cube
I played the hell out of a similar game on playstation 3 called battle of z
However, I am more concerned about something else. Where did you get your degree in gaming slash gamers licenses?
I couldn't find a certificate of gaming for you in nevada, massachusetts nor anywhere in new england. Are you certified?
You don't have to have you don't have to yeah, I am
Look, I got my certification when I was like eight years old. So this doesn't expire. I got my championship
Uh, I got my gamer championship license thing that I showed that happened when I was a kid. They never expire
You never have to renew them the blockbuster video game championships. Yeah, I got two free rentals a month for a year
I have certified. I haven't been recertified in a long time. Doesn't mean I wasn't thanks at the 250 though
Thanks at the 250 though wembley ttv
Thanks to the 250 I showed a pal of mine who was a gt driver the burnout spy cam video with no context
His first reaction was looking at your license photo saying what is that?
I guess you do have that sort of effect on people
Yeah, I remember. Yeah, I remember this
Yeah with the the terrifying
Balding head face down like a long face with the nose. Yeah, it's horrible
That's the second image on the internet that I hate
The eye crazy eyes mouth one is number one
And in the bathrobe head pointed down eyes up is the other one. Thanks to the 250
Hey dark soul. Thanks for 250 if you want to play another fun robo game, you should try gundam breaker 3 for playstation 4
You have to import it or use an hk account
HK account is on amazon and play asia in an english version
It's a really good game, especially if you want to make your own cool gunplay fighter
Don't play new gundam breaker on pc though. That one sucks. All right done. Stop making his list bigger
Don't make his list bigger
The list is never ending. It's like your christmas list. Did you guys ever do the christmas? Okay
I remember when I was a kid
we used to get the
There would be this catalog that came in the mail and they I don't know if it was like jc penny or
With some big box store and they had a toy section
And I remember what I would do is I'd take the this huge catalog and I would just take a sharpie
And I would circle every single thing I wanted for christmas
and give it to my parents like this is what I want here it is and
it was like
Two grand worth of stuff. It's like oh, oh, oh, this is what this is what you think santa's gonna bring you
Wow, okay. Well, we'll see
And you're getting like a quarter of a percent of the stuff on that on the stuff you circled and you don't even remember
Like maybe like not even a tenth of those things is what you got for christmas. I just don't oh wow
Yeah, I like this. I don't remember circling like
125 items got to be young more like one 100th. Yeah
Did you expect to get it all mine was a wish list? I don't know my like
Seven-year-old brain thought that hey, this is what I get. That's what I want
Yeah, it's a wish list means I wish I had all this
Here wish-grant hers make this a reality parents. That's how it was. He's a cringe rich kid
What?
Spoiled no, I just told you that they would be like, oh, okay, and I would get like I would get like
Maybe six items. I see some of your fucking christmas tweets and christmas things you guys get
I see some of the toys that you get some of you guys get like fucking sneakers like 300 dollar pairs of sneakers
How does he know? I know
I used to have to walk around with loaves of bread on my feet
That's what we did. We had two loaves of bread and we would squish on them and walk on them
And how dare you guys?
Family walking around
Like let's say you got a family of five
That's 10 loaves of bread and they would just get all mushed up and it would only work for like not even a day
You'd be going through like 50 loaves of bread a week
loafers
Okay. All right
Yeah, and then and then when we got you know, it was a huge deal and we got like the big pieces of naan bread
It was like they were it was awesome. I think like 10 loaves of naan bread
might actually be
More money than a like two or three pairs of shoes
How much is a pair of just just shitty sneakers? How much is a pair of just like I just go by
Here's another great thing about when we talk about the computer that's all the way to the left at best buy
What is the shoe all the way to the left at the shoe store? Well, what's like the dell in spiron of the shoe world?
20 at walmart like 15 like crocs new balance omega low
knockoff toms
Just go to pay less
these ones walmart images
Why is what what a weird what what is this fucked up website?
I5 dot walmart images dot ca. What the fuck is this?
Those are virus shoes
It's canadian
It's canadian walmart. Why is it walmart images?
These how much are these?
Are these expensive like what how much do these cost?
I mean they have max toe
Maximum toes in there
But does that mean you can fit 10 in there the maximum toes?
That you have are 10
is
Like 10 out of 10 toes is the maximum you fit could you fit both feet in there?
That's the max size for canadian
I lost my place
I lost my place in the bits
There they are
Uh, where were we right here? Hey manly leprechaun. Thanks for five dollars germa. This is my first time donating to a streamer
Glad you're my first
I don't know how often you make you take game recommendations from viewers
But you should play fossil fighters for the ds. It's a goofy fun and interesting game that could be entertaining to watch
What is it sloggers?
sloggers
I don't think I want to
Sloggers
Even saying that
Hey, what'd you get for a pair of shoes?
Ah, you know
sloggers
I got a good pair of sloggers
Why is why do I think when I think that I think when you step down the wet sound is heard like
Like they're already pre-wet they've been pre-wet like they dunked in water and held under there
So it gets into the foam and shit my sloggers
Wait, wait, what happened? Oh manly leprechaun, right?
fossil fighters for the ds
There's a lot of cool ds games
Although I don't know how well it would run on an emulator
If you even use those just want to put a word in for what I think would be an underrated gem
Either way keep up the good work and give auto a belly rub for me will do
Absolutely will
fossil fighters rocks
Maybe yeah. Yeah, let me see
That's just the name alone is making me go. Hmm. So you got me. You got me so far. Thanks for the five bucks, though
Atlantis thanks for five dollars. Fuck you chat. This game was fun. You guys are just mean
I didn't say it you did. I mean all I can do is like retweet you
You know, I didn't say it but like
I didn't say it
Chat is one person sad face
Peter oh shit
That was a peter griffin. Damn it. You got me. Hey ajax. Thanks for the 15
Dollars a germa probably can't donate for a while, but i'm grateful for everything that you do. You've already given
Way more money that I could ever imagine somebody would ever give to an eclan
So thanks for the huge amount of money you've given
Appreciate it. Don't worry about it. Thanks for the 15 bucks
Thank you eyes melt of heart
For the three dollars. What did you smell? I don't know
Did I smell something? I don't know what it was
I don't know. Uh, thank you your cat for the 15 dollars your cat
Jerma, just want to say thanks for playing gotcha force. I played this game through more times than I can count as a kid
Always trying to get all the different borgs
May be happy to see it get some attention. Take care. Me too. It was a lot of fun. I loved it. It was great
Glad to give it some attention
I can't believe my cat donated. Yeah, it's kind of cool. Thanks for the 15 bucks
Hey crispy
Crispy wizard. Thanks for the five dollars jerma. I've been watching since jerma is mad part two
It's a long time this day. You're the only person I've ever watched on twitch
Your sense of humor is so unique and I never laugh so hard on a consistent basis. Keep up the good work
Looking forward to the easy bake oven stream me too. It should be fun. Thanks for uh, watching this guy
On the internet that long like 10 years ago
And eight nine years ago now. Thank you
Thank you neck wills for the 300 bits. Have you ever played a short hike?
Very relaxing 3d platform. You can knock out in a little over an hour. Thanks for being a funny streamer
What's a short hike short hike? This looks kind of cool
It's an hour
It's like 45 minutes
Maybe i'll play it. This is cool. Hey, it's it's a short hike
I would make it more than an hour
Could I is that even possible?
It's gonna be if it's a one-hour game. It'll be six
Just do the tuber joke. I don't know. Maybe i'll play it. This looks kind of cute. All right, put it on the list
Thanks to 300 bits though
App low. Thanks for the 300 bits app low
No message
Jay browning. Thanks for the five dollars. Please play cubivore. That game's more expensive
Cubivore is like four hundred dollars. I think it's like the most expensive game cube game that I looked at
Gotcha forces 250 cubivore is like four
You would love cubivore
You can afford it lol
All right, but if I get made fun of for buying a 250 game
Double that and you know what just what should I just despite chat buy a 400 game?
Didn't somebody somebody gave me 250 to say to do that. I would only be i'm only playing myself here
Huh
Shows you chat. I spent four hundred dollars on a game cube game. Oh, that's I did that
I have to live with that
I have to buy that game for four hundred dollars
You don't have to do that
You could literally just open up a youtube like gameplay video of it right now and just watch it for like an hour and be like
Oh, this is stupid
Okay, just go watch a gameplay commentary on it
Yeah, I did look at it. It did look good though. We'll see
Hey lizard. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey germ bob me boy
I'd like to recommend to that guy asking about restaurants in boston and even if you
And you if you even bless us with your presence again
Called kaido santuka in harvard square. It's the best ramen i've ever had
also red bones in union square if you want good barbecue
sounds like
two
Awesome places I would listen to this person. Thanks for the 300 bits. Appreciate it. Hey x in x
Thanks for the 250 when's toontown on
mmo grab bag two
Be happening a little bit like probably in may at some point somewhere in may
in may may
Maybe the end of may maybe you know like a may maybe in may and maybe somewhere in may
I don't know. Maybe in june. Maybe may into june june 3rd june. I don't know. Happy 4th of july
Grab bag two. Hey adventure crab. Thanks for the 15 dollars 1500 bits. Have you considered playing custom robo?
It's pretty similar. I got it. It's coming on the shelf behind me. I will be playing custom robo
Somewhere in june and may and maybe july happy 4th of july custom robo. We'll make a firework character
I own it though. I'm ready to go. Thanks for the 15 bucks
Hey one trick wizard. Thanks for three dollars worm club. Thanks for 250
Incoming ha ha weed so sorry for that one, but one time some friends forced me to listen to neil
Cicierega's mouth moods for hours while I was way too high. It was really upsetting experience. It still haunts me. That's
Hey bug smoke. Thanks for 250 germa. Thanks for all the good content over the years
You know, I used to hate your tf2 videos
I used to hate your tf2 video phase before actually watching and realizing you were funny. I'm glad you glad you
Turned by the by by the way
If you ever play roblox on stream look up the roblox hellzone galleria 2.0 and play it
Gpm played it on stream and loved it. Did you give everyone a laugh? I've seen a lot of monkey s's. I'm sure that it's probably uh
a normal zone
But hey, thanks for watching used to hate the videos and now you like them appreciate it
Got him. He got infected by you
Bingo sunshine. Thanks for the 250
Remember these streams convinced me to pick up the game
Albeit through nefarious means because physical copies cost a hundred times more than this donation laughing my ass off
Anyway, the game is gorgeously emulated. It's entirely legal to own backup copies of games you already own
So would you consider emulation in the future for stuff? That's going to be a display piece. Anyway, that's the thought i've done it already
Uh, no more heroes one was played on the dolphin because no more heroes on the wii
Runs like an absolute trash can and I didn't want to put up with it
I didn't want to have you put up with it either. I admitted that you guys already knew that
I don't
look
The wii is right here
The game disc is right there and the wiimote's right here
What do you mean? I never told you yeah, I did
I talked about how it how it looks like I would ran like such dog shit that I had to emulate it
I've like held up the shit. I was like look look at me
Yeah, some games need it because they just don't run well and they don't pull a lot of some here's another thing some games do not
Pull through a capture card well either
at all
you've seen some of those games that are like
Some of them sound horrible being pulled through capture cards and being scaled
So it's only out of necessity and I I only if I own the games and own the consoles
I don't do it ever
I don't I don't do it. I don't I don't do this
Right dot dot dot, right
That's dumb
Right, right. Okay, let's keep going
Uh bingo sunshine. Yeah
Uh, I it is a thought on a lot of things and about I consider everything I I consider all options
maxi kaspersky
Thanks for the five dollars germa told me to never reverse
And i've been accelerating into this brick wall for 15 minutes. Please help. I'm going to run out of gas
Hey medhi merrin, thanks for the five dollars
Hello germa. I have a question
I'm quite a bit of a workaholic. I have adhd and I can't stop my head from thinking
So I try to think about productive things
Ever since quarantine there's nothing left for me to do
Done all my work and chores and despite there being nothing to do
I feel like i'm wasting away and failing at something that doesn't exist
Do you have any advice on how to teach myself to relax?
exercise
jogging
walking
Lifting and you can even do it. You can do it in your house. Do it in your room
push-ups sit-ups
That's not a bad idea
Yeah, do them right now
play an mmo
It's all it's also good to stay at least somewhat active in the middle of something like a quarantine like this
because
If you like for instance me right now
If I don't move around and I don't get up and do something or at least do like light exercise
You really got to keep yourself loose
And other people said do something creative start painting. I'm not sure where you are
I'm, not sure if you can still get like amazon deliveries or and if that's a possibility it should be
um
Order some paints
Had them just dropped at the door
Do some painting who cares have fun?
You could read
You could take a bath. I love baths. I've become a huge bath fan
I love just getting a light in a candle
Getting in the bath
You just sit there and you just take it in
Have some salts sprinkled
Lightly
I've been so into baths recently. I really have omega low rip the ipad just don't dunk your ipad in there
Don't just don't dunk your ipad in there. I lied about that
Like an hour ago don't do that. Don't don't like drop your ipad in the water
Like I like I made that whole thing up. So like don't like do that. It's wacky
No, it actually did happen. I wish you luck though in this
uh trying time
Thanks for the five dollars. Also. Thanks for five dollars. Dr. Clay. I have a dumb dad joke for you
What do you call a prank?
A jedi pulls using the force
It got you force event
You've been till tomorrow
So you have the pat upon stream?
It was cute. I liked it. Don't ban him
Just scare him
Hey, see hund. Thanks for the 300 bits jerma
I've been watching your contents the tf2 days and finally decided to watch your live streams
And not from the archives. I know that you've decided to move to the great city of las vegas
For someone who has boston
Is one of the top picks on where to move?
Do you have any suggestions on where to look?
Like where to live?
I mean if you can live in boston
There's a lot of awesome places in boston just you can just walk to everything. There's so many great bars and restaurants
And just stuff to do if you if you live like in city limits
Just go live in a bar
It is it is expensive
It is expensive
I only said just said go to hell why?
Ban that person till tomorrow's pat upon stream
Well, you don't know I talk about go live in hell. Oh, no, no, they're safe. That's fine. I would say if you can
In the city is is awesome
If you if you're able to afford it can get very expensive though safe for now
boston more like bossed out
Hey, johnny nice mountains. Thanks to 300 bits jerma. Are you familiar with the souls games? I've never heard of them
I have no idea what you're talking about
Don't get it. I don't know what that means. Is that like a meme?
Did I just say something I wasn't supposed to say did you give me is there like a like souls?
Like these nuts or something. I don't understand. I'm I'm I'm a funny joke, I guess
Hey peaceful. Haley. Thanks for 250
Just wanted to say I appreciate you and your community a lot. Everyone is so kind to me
Also, I said this years ago, but I still look up to you
And I do want to stream i'm just hard on myself and I want to do this more than anything
Thanks for being the thanks for thanks for the backing up into traffic advice don't do that
Streaming is fun streaming is really really really
Awesome, but you want to you gotta want to do it
You shouldn't have any pressure
to turn it on
and if your pressure is coming from
Needing to have to do it and I'd say that might be a problem
Wanting and needing you got to want to do it and just have fun doing it and just don't think about anything else
Not at all. Yeah, that's it. Yeah, I want that's good
Because the more that you start to need it the more you're going to give yourself
Potentially unrealistic things that you have to do. I hope that helps like eating a shoe
We don't talk about that. What about wanting to stop on the highway and that person and don't let them drive
All right. No, don't they're okay. They're asking a question
Hey bingo sunshine. Thanks for the 250 germa. The point was the games look and sound better emulated. Just emulate them
I mean, that's what I said, but I kind of I like putting the disk in and I like loading up the
Well, you know, I actually don't get to hear that I always mute that part
Got you
um, I like to bone stuff
I and and
It's it hasn't been that big of a problem
Plus like let's be honest. I know that
Look, it's anybody can just sit here and go
Just do it. Just do it. It's fine. Nobody cares. Twitch doesn't care
They don't care
But if somebody ever wanted to
It's still it's still
Technically illegal
You know what i'm saying? So like I have to just be I have to be careful
I don't want to be like yeah, everything I fucking own is pirated
Here's my folder with 300 gamecube games in it. I've didn't buy a fucking thing
Hi, i'm germa985 streamer with
6000 people watching don't you know look at this you can just get all this shit for free
I I gotta like be care. I don't want to I gotta be careful
You listen to copyrighted music. That's just as illegal dumbass
Um, that's no it's not
Playing a mighty mighty boss stone song from the youtube channel of mighty mighty boss stones
You can't go to youtube.com
And open up a window
With got your force in it
You can if they don't give you an easy legitimate way to get the game then fuck them
Yes, and I know I know I know but this this difference between listening to a song on stream
and having
thousands of dollars
In game products downloaded to my hard drive
That I did not pay for
Even if it's not available. I just I just have to be careful. I just laughed so hard. My parents probably woke up
Sure roger that mr boomer and like like nintendo games wasn't that like doesn't it isn't nintendo?
Like do not fucking do that
Didn't they they've removed all that they cease and desist fucking people hosting that shit all the time
It's been seven hours. What happened to oh, I can't stream for more than four hours
I had to be gotcha force
And I mean the stream has been over for like an hour or two. He's been hanging out
But I did I did say that I did say I didn't want to go more than six seven hours
I said no, I did say that sometimes
Needing to finish stuff I I would be able to it'd be okay, but it's primarily to
Avoid my it just completely give me a hard wall to not have like eight plus hour streams ever again
The same nintendo sells shitty ports of super mario world on every console for 20 dollars
Yeah, but they still sell it. That's the point
Look, i'm not gonna i'm not gonna sit here and like argue any like
Copyright they deserve to charge that they don't fuck those companies like i've used emulators on this stream. You've seen it
And I probably will continue to do so
If I've you know find it necessary
I mean what what you didn't buy the dos games monkey ass
Yeah, but the dos games are like archived into fucking they're like that archive.org is like the public domain of all things
It's an abandonware. Yeah
playing abandonware versus
Capcom still owns the rights to beautiful joe
Like capcom didn't go, you know, hey, you know what beautiful joe is abandonware now
No, they have that shit under lock and key
But they aren't doing anything with it
Uh, welcome to my argument for uh, why won't gino just be added as a nintendo character?
There's been there's been like three or four cases where nintendo employees have been like yeah, that's a cool character
Maybe we have to be fun. Wow, I think oh gino's really cool. Yeah
He's just locked in a cage
at square enix
And then hey square enix. You ever gonna use that character? Nope. Can I use that character? Nope
I they're good doing business with you
But that happens a lot
Long story short is that I just I just gotta be careful whether I use it or don't use it
I know like I know everyone's saying this person does it this person does I know and that's all right. I do too
We say hi to peaches. Hey peaches
Welcome to the stream
See you tomorrow
Have a good day
A good day. It's a good night. What am I talking about?
I'll see you tomorrow for pat upon
Either pat upon one or pat upon two
Me and pre-stream chat tomorrow are going to decide
The thing I was going to tell you
Okay, this is really really really deep heavy heavy spoiler heavy. No, no, no
I'm gonna do this one day. No, you don't get i'm sorry
I like to put that but it's a big spoiler
No, I like hate that. Oh, I hate like I don't want to type like the fucking like a huge boy. I don't I hate that
Okay, it looks like something
Oh, I can't
I don't like doing that because people but you could like clip me saying this
Just like give it to somebody and be like, hey look
And they'll click it and be like thanks. Uh, okay. Let me just finish the bits. Hey j cup brah
Thanks for the 300 bits germa. I am a newer viewer
Watching for about three months. Well, welcome to the channel
I thought it was pretty cool to see a streamer who used to live in my hometown. You're a funny dude
And i'm glad to watch some more in the future any advice on starting a youtube channel
Just go just do it
See what happens
But I did
See what happens?
No, that the the the just do it forehead is actual advice for this
Started 10 years ago
true
true, I
The best advice you give to anybody starting any new creative endeavor
Go for it
Do it as best as you can
And try to set realistic expectations
Do it for fun. Do it because you like it do it because you want to tell something do because you want to show something
Same advice I would give for anything
Don't do something because you feel like you have to do it do it because you want to do it and do it as best
As you can
If something good happens if you get some viewers then fucking awesome. Keep going keep doing it
If you don't get any viewers right at the bat
Keep going
Just keep doing it
And then find out over the months coming weeks and months if it's something that you actually wanted to do
You've said this advice six times today
While it was asked at six separate times
And people might not be here. They might have left
It's homework advice
Don't take youtuber advice from this xtuber. That's another thing. I don't know the game at all and I never did
I didn't know I you think I knew what I was fucking doing
When it came to like how to make it big on youtube
I like ran somebody over with a car in gta and laughed at it
What happened? How did I get here?
true
Now I obviously I put a lot of work into that channel and a lot of stuff that I really cared about
That's a jokey little like hey, it's a funny thing. I spent a lot of work. I spent a lot of time on that channel
In quotes work. Are you supposed to be banned?
Wait, i'm not supposed to read what you say. You don't put that uh, ban that person until tomorrow's pad upon stream
And I actually mean that this time
No, I'm not actually yeah. No. Yeah, i'm not supposed to read what you say. That's i'm not supposed to read you
Now you've gone till tomorrow's pad upon stream
Yep, i'm about to turn the stream off and now i'm not yep. You're tomorrow. You're not gonna see me until tomorrow
What was I talking about? Oh, yeah
I would just get ideas and do them and if people thought they were funny or they liked them then they did and if they
Didn't then they didn't and I just kept doing them
There's a shit load of channels that people like didn't think were very good
That's okay
I learned and I tried to make them better
There are videos people thought were some of the best things that i've ever done
You learn you say okay. What was what did that work? Let me do more of that. Let me try some more of that
How why did you just hit me?
But um incredibly long-winded word fucking soup I was going to word soup after like six or seven hours
um
Do it because you want to not because you need to that's like the best advice I can give to anybody doing anything creatively
Thanks for three bucks. We only have three more donations from held rich five dollars
Jeremy, I found a glowing review for gotcha force from 2004 if you wanted some vindication
Also, there exists toys in manga and a manga series, but they're all extremely hard to find
Anyways, keep it up
from nintendo world report
Oh, yeah, the tagline is it's the best unofficial transformers game ever
What do they give for score?
graphics seven
sound
three
control seven
gameplay eight point five last ability nine
final score of eight
crows here
are multiplayer features
respectable computer allies and opponents simple and fun combat system and tons of cool and unique boards borgs
cons
ear-burning voice clips
Only story mode unlocks new borgs and there are camera problems
We're doing cheese toasties with tomato soup. Sign me up
That sounds incredible
Pretty good review. I would agree with it. Hey to sewage to capsicum. Thanks for the five dollars
Jeremy, I realized the other day that you don't actually wash your hands
They actually wash each other while you just stand there and watch
Thanks for the five dollars
Maxie kaspersky
Thanks for the five dollars final bit message of the evening. Jeremy, please I can hear sirens and i'm still driving into the wall
Can I back up now?
Turn off just turn the engine off
Get out of the car
Call your insurance and be uh told that they're not going to cover it. What the hell were you doing? Thanks for the five dollars. Okay
You ready?
I'm gonna talk. There's a major spoiler for my big game
But this is I this is something that you're gonna see
But you're gonna see this eventually i'm just spoiling one of my own streams
but
I can't do that. I don't that's why i've stopped. I've brought it up like four times over the last stream
And i'm just like no, no, no, because I don't I it's a it's an incredible reference
But what game is it? Uh
Uh
No, fuck but I what if I don't all right
Leave leave if you don't want to hear this
Just leave leave leave if you don't he's gonna spoil breath of the wild. No, i'm not. I haven't what the fuck you're talking about
Help me. I choose okay if you choose to sit here and hear it choose, but I want you to see this on stream
Okay, if you don't want to hear this i'm serious, please leave i'm going to give a major spoiler for a game
That i'm not sure you've even played or heard of it's an old game
All right, we safe
Don't say it. No, i'm not gonna spoil more wind. I'm this is this is like
No, I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to
Okay, here's when you're gonna see this game on stream soon
And i'm gonna point it and go there
Jelly
And you guys are gonna go what the fuck? Oh my god. I can't i'm not i'm
I'm not gonna say it. No, i'm not gonna say it. No, I can't I can't do it. I love this thing
And I don't want to ruin it
Just say it. I can't say it. I can't no I can't tell you the game either because then it ruins everything
This is a big deal. It's a big fucking deal. This would I wouldn't even play the game anymore after this
Stop you blue balling us. I
At least say the name of the game
No, because then if I say the name of the game, then you'll know the fucking very end of the whole game
You will say that you will you will know the end of the game
Stop your
Destroy this footage. All right five five. All right, uh, it's
um
a uh, it's a it's a um
it's
the thing is
I've the character