One of you, you guys are like doing different instruments.
We have to all just do that song in our own different ways with like different parts of the song and it's over Skype too so it's going to sound awful because it's not going to be synced.
Wait, you're saying, you want me, okay so I'll do the drums. I'm going to do the drums. Boo, what part do you want?
Wait, who's doing what now? You're doing the drums. I'm going to do the drums.
Dude, I don't even know that there's more than one part. It's just the song. That's all that that is.
Yeah, but we're going to make it our own thing. Do you know the concept of instruments?
Yeah, and it's just a saxophone. That's all that plays then. Saxophones? What?
That is not a saxophone. That's a trombone.
What do you call this? Is this like Bill Quinton? It's like a saxophone.
He said, I hope you guys don't mind if I pull this tank is effing slow.
Wait, I didn't even see that. Where did he write that? You're a liar.
He wrote that like two minutes ago. Oh, really? No, he didn't. I'm scrolling up.
Oh, he thinks he's like so funny, huh? We'll pull it. Okay, fine.
Not going fast enough for you? Sounds like a plan. Sure, we'll go.
You're just going to run to the end of the entrance. Run to the end of the dungeon.
That's right. That fast enough for you. It did fast enough for you.
Let's let's hope we can actually like do this. Pull more is what he says. Yeah.
All right. It's not my fault. Get the boss. Don't get the boss. Don't get the boss.
Don't get the boss. We will actually wipe if you get the boss. I got the boss.
Oh, dude, why don't get the boss? Oh, you're attacking me, you dummy.
I don't have any mana. Oh, my God. What is draining my mana?
Dude, my mana is getting drained. I just divide shield. You guys are on your own.
Oh, great. Pain the asshole. Dude, for that entire duration, I had almost zero mana.
Well, that's why I can't heal the guy because he's a bad guy. You know, we should have just done.
Oh, we just killed him. He's dead. Wait a minute. What were we supposed to do?
He was attacking us. We just killed him. I don't think we were supposed to kill him.
He like Insta dropped. Hey, was that the guy that was complaining that I'm like a shitty tank?
I got out of it. I'm not ready. Don't pull. I got ready.
All right. Hold on. We're going to mess with this guy a little bit. I'm going to stand here.
Every dog is trapped on my carpet. I'm going to be like 45 minutes.
They would just be like 45 minutes. I would just get you would just vote to kick me and replace me.
I mean, that that is literally for anybody in that trinket. That trinket like sucks ass, by the way.
I think that thing is horrible.
That really is bad. I'm going to read this. I'm going to read this to you guys.
You know, we've like pulled a lot. Yeah, these guys are not elites.
So let me let me read this to you.
The worst drinking in the game. I'm going to read this to you in what I would assume somebody would be telling me.
This is how they would sell Ramstein's writing books.
Yeah, to drink it is press eight hit and harness the power of writing to dress down.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
I was just like, kill us.
All right. Back to what was I saying here?
Whatever. I just created one, two, three, four.
We're missing somebody. We're missing the hunter.
No, we're all in here. You don't know how to count one to.
Oh, if I keep you're not a pet. I keep thinking you're a freaking pet.
Let's go. Oh, get the Lord.
Oh, it's done. This is the last box of the dungeon.
The undertaker.
Jesus Christ.
I got so worried about the undertaker.
Well, what's that? Give me that.
Have you guys done that blackout swordsman sling?
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not.
Thank God. This misery is over.
And then he leaves.
God, this misery is over.
Oh, well, that was a night.
That was a nice man.
Thank God. This misery is over.