Are you playing on a server now?
Yeah. I told you I was fucking pumped up for like duty shit.
Yo, I'm pumped up right now. We're both pumped. Call us the Pump Brothers.
You wanna be the Pump Brothers?
No.
Yo, you don't wanna be the Pump Brothers?
I really don't actually.
You don't want me to pump you up? You don't want me to pump you?
I don't want you to pump me.
I think I'm just gonna spectate you.
I'm gonna teach you how to pull it off, Star. Are you ready for this?
I wanna see how to pull it off. Luigi, hee hee. Show me how to pull it off.
First of all, you wanna jump. No, this is important. You wanna jump up on this rail.
Jump up on these big spindydoodles.
Once you get on the top spindydoodle, then it's really important that you wait here.
My carcass is everywhere.
That door. You don't wanna go in that door.
Oh, yeah?
Go to the spindydoodle. Go. Just go. This is...
Hit something.
Don't worry. I'll pull this off. You wanna see how you pull it off?
Time to turn it on.
Turn it on.
That's how you pull it off, this one.
Oh my god. What a hip shot.
Hey!
Wasn't even aiming for him.
Wasn't even aiming for that guy.
Oh, there's a sentry over here.
Sentry. Spy, you gotta do your work. Get in there and get that sentry.
Get the health kit. Get the health kit.
I can't. There's a sentry right there. Are you stupid?
No.
Not as in the type of dream that you have that you didn't like,
but as in the Soul Calibur II character,
as in the 3-3-B is a very good launcher.
There's a lot of damage. I think 72 damage.
Okay, we're gonna watch you pull it off, man.
I'm gonna pull it off.
There's just mini sentry.
It doesn't count because there was a mini sentry.
Didn't pull it off.
No. Redo.
All right, fine. Redo.
You get one more shot to pull it off.
I'm gonna pull it off.
Ready?
This time the mini sentry won't get me.
All right.
Looks like he's gonna see a demo man around the corner.
No, no. Here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna go...
It didn't pull it off again.
That doesn't count either
because he's the guy who builds mini sentries.
This is your final chance to pull it off.
Dude, I am just not pulling it off right now.
You have a chance, right? No.
Wow. You are just not pulling it off.
No, it does. It does.
That was three pulls.
No, it's my turn to pull it off.
No, it's three strikes. You're out.
Yeah, you're on strike four right now.
I'm pulling it off.
The first one didn't count because it was a mini sentry.
That's fine. I'm pulling it off.
I don't care. I'm not watching you because I'm about to pull it off.
No, that's fine. I'm pulling it off before you pull it off.
There's no way you're gonna be able to pull it off.
Oh, really? You think so?
I think so. Go for it. I'm going for the sentries.
If you pull it off before I pull it off...
If you pull it off before I pull it off before you pull it off,
then there's gonna be a big problem here.
No, no, no, no. Don't let up. Yeah, shoot him, Heavy.
There's two... I didn't pull it off.
This is like the worst I've played in my life.
I didn't pull it off either.
It's 13 seconds left to pull it off.
I mean, come on. One of us is gonna pull it off.
Somebody... Okay, I'm going demo.
Somebody has to really pull this off.
There's no time to get over here to pull it off.
Come on. You gotta pull it off.
I could pull it off if I had another minute.
This is a lot...
Okay, what's the lineup here? What are we looking at?
Punch heavies.
Both of us? Yes.
You know we're gonna meet? We have a specific meeting point.
No bullshit.
No trickery. No tomfoolery.
Okay, no attacking each other.
No bullshit.
No tomfoolery.
We just want a straight punch heavy fight.
No bullshit.
I think I found a way.
Oh, are you typing to someone?
I'm talking to MLC stuff.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Are you working with him?
Yeah, I've been typing to this sniper.
Just wait, he's gonna come.
Have you?
Yes.
He was sitting here just waiting, aiming down here.
This whole fucking time I've been typing.
Can you pull it off?
Yeah, I can pull it off. Just let me get the health.
And we'll have our battle royale.
Okay, you ready?
Wait, wait, wait. I'm not ready.
Okay, I'm ready.
Are you ready to have the actual battle royale?
Okay, battle royale.
Get that health.
Shit!
It's the same sniper.
That sniper almost got me again.
He was waiting in a corner to Dorati.
Are you instructing him on everything?
No, seriously, have you heard me type?
Alright, wait.
Kill him.
Oh my fucking god.
He just gunned you down.
He thought about it until you saw him think about it.
Invisible potty.
Have you ever read Invisible Weekly today?
I did.
I didn't like the part where it said we were a bunch of chumps.
That part was not good.
Invisible Weekly has been really going downhill.
It used to be about articles, but now it's just about the naked ladies.
I know.
Always the invisible naked ladies now.
Yeah, I know. You can't even see them. It doesn't make any sense.
Stand over here.
And I'm going to decloak and shoot this sniper in the back.
And we're both going to cloak at the same...
To make it so we're just permanently invisible.
So they have no idea where they're getting shot from.
I'm going to keep annoying people.
See where the pyro is right now?
Shoot him and then we're both invisible forever.
I'm going to go to the other side of the map.
So it's both angles.
I'm going to climb up this rock.
I'm going to shoot this soldier.
God damn.
I'm going to shoot the pyro.
I hit that pyro.
He's coming back.
Are you invisible?
He has no idea what's going on.
He's coming up here.
See the sniper?
He's shooting at me.
I shot him.
I'm going to shoot him.
You shoot him now.
I shot him.
He's going to be right back in spawn.
I pulled it off.