Is this really happening right now? Am I about to record a Team Fortress 2 video on this channel?
Wow. Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
It's been a while since you've seen TF2. It's been a long time. And why am I doing it now?
Why have I decided randomly right now to make this TF2 video? It's because I just played Overwatch.
I just got back from the Blizzard event where they showcased Overwatch to a bunch of people.
I was one of the people that were there. It was a pretty cool event. Got to play the game for a few
hours. Sat down with it. It's really fun. And now I want to play TF2 again. And sort of the unintended
consequences of going to the Blizzard event was there aren't very many games like this that are
on the market right now. And getting that initial taste of Overwatch got my juices going for TF2.
Which is a really good thing. That means that Overwatch impressed me enough where it got me
to want to play at least a similar game because I want to play more Overwatch. So we're going to
break this down very, very quickly, very easily. I'm not going to go over gameplay mechanics.
I'm not going to talk about how many knots per second this character moves at sea level.
I'm just going to say one, one, one thing. I keep getting this intermittent rash that I cannot ever
get rid of. And I always try to use different products. And you know the type of rash I'm
talking about? It's on your back. It's in a really weird spot where your left hand has to come
wrapping around your body and try to scratch it. Your right hand then swoops around and you reach
down and you're barely touching your two fingers. But you can't get it. And God did that. I got to
go to the doctor now. You go to the doctor. You walk in. The doctor prescribes you Team Fortress
2. You go down. Team Fortress 2 clears up the rash. You're smearing that TF2 all over the rash.
And it's filling. It's scary. You're using a lot of the Team Fortress 2 tube. An antimonth though.
And after like three or four years, you run out of the ointment. You go to the doctor. The doctor
says, oh geez, you got it. I'm running out of that TF2 medicine. I take it. This is all I got left.
It's another two-year supply. You take that two-year supply. You're like, yes, I'm so fucking glad you
rub it more. The rash is deceding. It's going away. And then the rash comes back up even worse
after that. And you go back to the doctor. The doctor says, I don't have any more Team Fortress
2 medicine. They just continued that shit in like 2014. And you're like, no, what do I do?
This rash is starting to take over my body. It's itchy all over. And then Overwatch comes out and
it's a new medicine. And you've seen the ads on TV. You're like, what is this new medicine? I don't
like the side effects. Side effects may include stinging and burning initially. And you're like,
I don't want to be stinging and burning initially. So you get it. You fucking, you don't even want
it, but you get it because, okay, I'll just take it, I guess. You put it on. It stings.
And then like a couple hours later, the rash is starting to feel a little better. It's going to
go away. It still hurts, but the rash is going away. And look, I don't even, I can't even tell
you, dude, the Overwatch might make the rash worse. You know, you get some medications where
it makes the thing that you're the problem you're having worse. And you're like, what the fuck? I
got this because I had a rash. I didn't get this because I wanted a bigger rash. But then what's
going to cure that rash? Nobody knows. And I'm not going to pretend like I do know. I'm not going to
pretend to sit here and tell you that Overwatch is going to be the best game ever. That when it
releases, it's going to be a 10 out of 10. I don't know that. All I know is it was really fun when I
played it. The characters all feel great. Bastion is probably my favorite character out of all of
them. If you don't know what Bastion is or what the character is, he's this big goofy robot guy
that can turn himself into an immobile sentry. And you find those places, you find those chokes
where you know people are going to come through and you just turn into a sentry gun and you get
this big shield in front of you to help protect you and teammates and laying down that suppressing
fire. It's great. I love being the support characters in games like this. It's one of the
reasons why engineer is my favorite class in Team Fortress 2. It's because of the almost indirect
help you're giving people. When I build the teleporter or when I build the dispenser as the
engineer, I know people are using it, but I'm not making people use it. Like I'm not grabbing
somebody by their pant legs and their shirt collar and tossing them over the point to go to B. Like
I'm not directly teleporting people. My shit's doing it for me. Same thing with a character like
Zenyatta in Overwatch who has this orb that you simply place on somebody. You can only go on one
person at a time and it just heals them. You give somebody a personal pocket medic and you don't
even need to be near them. You just have to place it on them. But the characters in Overwatch, just
like in Team Fortress, have the personalities behind them to make it so you want to play as
a certain character. You'll connect with one of these characters just like I did when I first
started playing with the spy. I thought I got his spy. I thought he was like the coolest thing ever
and I wanted to play spy even though I wasn't that good with spy. I just wanted to hear him talk and
that's so huge for me in a game like this. Like the reason why I continue to play TF2, why I like
Team Fortress, why I've been playing for as long as I have, it has a lot to do with the personality
of the characters. It has a lot to do with the shorts, the source filmmaker videos, the Gmod
videos, the comics, the whole world that has been realized around these characters. They're each
their own person. They're each their own hysterical awesome character and I really hope that's what
happens with Overwatch. I hope Blizzard takes that seriously because we love to see these characters
play out situations and be sort of these living breathing people when in fact they're just kind
of mercenaries that are playing in a multiplayer shooter game. Now however you feel about Overwatch,
if you think it's going to be terrible, if you don't like it looks, if you think it's too much
like TF2 or whatever, at least it's trying to do it. At least it's trying to fill a potential void
that TF2 will inevitably leave behind. When is that going to happen? I don't know. I don't know,
it could happen tomorrow, it could happen next year, it could happen ten years from now, but
that's the problem with the Team Fortress series. It is covered in this gigantic shroud of the
unknown. We don't know where the direction of the series is going. We don't know what they're going
to be adding. We don't even know if there's going to be another installment in this series. We just
get the stuff that Valve gives us whenever they deem it necessary to give it to us.
That's it. That's just the way it's always been and that's the way apparently it's going to be.
But it's just refreshing to see a company like Blizzard that has the money and has the experience
making games stepping up to the plate and taking a swing. And I'll parrot what I said in the
beginning. I'll end this video simply by saying the time that I spent with it was pretty damn fun.
I'm starting to get more interested in it than I was before. And even if it's not the rash cure
that I initially think it's going to be, I'll find another fucking prescription. But we'll leave it
at that. Just know that I don't want to overhype it for myself. I made the overhype video. I'm
getting excited. I don't want to get this excited about it, but I'm starting to get excited. I don't
know what to do. Somebody please help me. I'm getting too excited for Overwatch. Somebody come.