Today's video we're gonna open up a box on camera. Oh, I've already done it. I've already done it.
Out of the arena and look out, look out, hey, whoa, whoa, watch out!
Mayo coming up the front of the court over the Boston Celtics sign, passing it over to Knight, Knight layup.
That's two points for Milwaukee. Now we've got Gabe Glewman Degrosie gonna do, well that's what he typically does.
And it's in! Another three points for the Boston Celtics.
A deficit like this is gonna be hard to come back from for the Milwaukee Brewers.
But maybe they can mount something. They need to get some type of offense and keep the defense alive.
Oh, what a fake there, passing it over to Sanders. Two points for Milwaukee again.
You gotta give Milwaukee some credit here though. They've showed perseverance this entire game.
How do you go up against a team like the Celtics of 1997? I'm not entirely sure Degrosie now.
Passing Technique, that's another three points.
If you can hear the speechlessness in my voice, it's because I need somebody call a nuclear physicist right now.
And ask them, how is this even possible to score three points every single possession the entire season?
You've got Gabe the Glewman Degrosie. They gave him that name because he's got hands like glue.
And he can throw the ball so well. And he was able to teach the entire team how to do this.
And I just don't understand. And Degrosie's not gonna get the ball.
Wallace, Wallace is gonna do it now. That's gonna be three points. They've never missed one time the whole season.
I haven't casted a game for the Celtics, but this is the first time I've casted a Celtics game.
And I must tell you, ladies and gentlemen, this is one of the most remarkable basketball games I have ever encountered in my entire 67 years on the planet.
So now we're gonna just try to calm down here. Glewman, how do you calm down? How do you calm down when something like that happens?
How do you calm down? How am I supposed to...?
Knight's got the ball now. We have Knight on the Milwaukee team with the ball.
He's gonna try to come up court. He's gonna do a jump shot right at the paint and he misses.
But Frank Pizza's got the ball now. Frank Pizza with a toss. And it's...
Oh! He missed it.
Frank Pizza just missed the first shot of the entire season. And that's just unbelievable. I really can't believe that.
And of all the things we've seen here tonight, ladies and gentlemen, I can tell you I did not expect Frank Pizza
to be the guy to ruin the streak of the Boston Celtics. But can we start it again?
We're gonna start it again! Start that counter at zero and add one to it, ladies and gentlemen, because that is the first of many from these Boston Celtics.
They are making a speed leave again, which is something that their GM over and over again has said in interviews.
Dan Bringus, we caught up with him earlier this afternoon.
Look, I'm gonna say the same thing I've said like 12 times now. I fucking hate this job and I hate this whole fucking organization.
And this whole throw the ball as hard as you can from the back of the court was a joke to get me fired. And it didn't work.
Wiser words I don't think have ever been spoken. But down to the final 15 seconds, Milwaukee down by nearly 200 points.
Not even entirely sure why you shoot the basket right there. I would just go take a long shower and think about this.
Jordan at the buzzer for good measure gets the final one at the buzzer.
And for the 67th time, the Boston Celtics are going to win in near perfect fashion.
And because obviously it's the end of the game, as we see the players all take off into their respective locker rooms,
I'm going to have to give the player of the game award to Gabe Gloomander Grossi.
That's right. The fan favorite. You all know him. You all love him.
I really truly think he is one of the best players to ever live.
And honestly, I hope to God nothing bad happens to this guy like 10 years from now.