But anyways, we're going to move on from there. Oh, it's blue, sorry. I apologize for the blue.
We're going to transition here to the slot game coming up as Jerma Slots. This is the community
game. They changed the title. This was made by CAD, and I'll tell you, actually rage quit.
We got other things to do today. And by the way, this game is going to just be downloadable
on Steam for free. Just a free game. I did not have anything to officially do with this.
This is just something somebody made. And it was really, really interesting, really cool.
And I wanted to try it. This looks pretty elaborate. I've been told it takes about
an hour or two to complete the whole thing, depending on how lucky you are. And we're
going to find out. So I don't know what to expect, but I'm sure it'll be interesting.
This is Jerma Slots. Just open it. Okay, here we go. There it is. Please read.
The slot machine in this game has several winning three of a kind combinations. Each
combination is a special event tied to it. If you want to see an event without naturally
spinning a winning combination, hit escape, go to the pause menu and check the enable
cheats box. A cheat drop down will become active under that box. Select the winning
combination from that menu and the next spin will give you that combination. Okay,
most events will occur only once restarting the game resets all events. Click on my face
to begin. What do you got against David Bowie? Well, here's my, here's my old intro
from like 2011. That was quite the intro. Here it is. This is the menu. Here's the
options. Let's take a look. Resolution full screen, graphics full. Intro is on. Okay.
There it is. I have no idea what to expect. I'm looking forward to this.
This is not out yet. This will be able to be downloaded after this stream is over,
potentially even Monday because steam, I'm not sure you can, there's a release schedule
thing. It might be on Monday. So I got a free, I got a press copy of this game.
Just want to make sure everyone knows this has been, this key was provided to me.
I'm ready. Let's see how this works. So I can look around. This is, is it W A S D? Oh,
you dick. Press E to go. Oh, you just really, you're killing me here. Can I do anything else?
Can I interact with something? Can I jump? That's a cool, I'm going to, okay. Let's
give myself a boost. Oh, let me look at the stickers. What are these ones? It's Jax,
Slug, Asteroid. Oh, this is emotes. That's awesome. All right. How much money do I get?
This is so cool. Press these keys to bet and spin. Press E to buy more bald coins. Okay.
So how many bald coins do I have? What did I just put in? I put in a $25 bill? All right,
here we go. So I'm going to do, let's spin. How many, we've got max bet this thing, right?
There's nothing. So there's rat, glue man, my face, two rats. How much, how much down am I?
16 bald coins. I can't hit anything. Oh, you can, you can hold, wait, hold. Wait,
wait. I need the instructions. F1, F2, F3. E is interact. Okay. So F1, F2, F3.
If the player has enough money, they may hold up to two of the three wheels in order to
increase their odds for winning combination. A player can unhold held wheels by pressing
the same button again. The cost per wheel increases depending on the bet amount. Okay.
Cost 10 bitcoins per wheel. That's like $50,000. That's not, that's not good enough for me.
I'm out of money. Free rats!
We're the rats. We're the rats. We pray at night. We stalk at night. We're the rats.
I'm the giant rat. Holy shit.
Let's see what kind of trouble we can get our sense into.
What is that worth? Five bucks? That was awesome. That was only five dollars.
I need to put, how do I, I need to put money in. No, I want, I'm gonna do it again. Spin.
Okay, hold the rats. Press E to, life is pain. I hate, there's bits on there by the way.
So that's, all right, that's 50 bucks. Max bet. Glue man, glue man. All right,
hold the glue man's, right? Hold the glue man's. Wait, I can't, I can only hold one of the glue
man's because my bet's too high. It's 10. God damn, I need more money. I can't hold, I need to,
I got a max bet. I'm sorry, I have to. I can't, no, I can't, lower the bet. What if I just,
what if I do one instead? Okay, I can hold it with one. Glue man. Yes! Glue man wants to
fight. Fight, item, germa, run, item. Let's go with, let's go with fight. Elbow drop, Jex mode,
attack, wrestling, buff, legend, presto, majesto is a debuff, bake, save, attack, that's shriek.
Super effective. Glue man uses choke slam. This is awesome. Do you have any items?
Pure cholesterol, old pizza, fully heals me, heals germa for a moderate amount,
fully restores all of germa's abilities, cooking wine, ice coffee, fully restores one of germa's
abilities. I don't think, I don't need these yet. What does this mean? You have no germas left.
Okay, what about presto majesto? I missed it. God damn it. I'm gonna have to start eating
pizza. All right, what is Jex mode? Okay, let's try Jex. Germa uses Jex mode. Glue man uses hail
mary and he missed. So I got plus two here. All right, and now I want to do elbow drop. No,
no, back, back tap. All right, good. Germa can't move. Glue man uses showboat. All right,
we both hit plus two. Shit, he's gonna kill me. He crit! That's a critical hit?
Ah, all right, I need to eat something. I still can't move? I gotta heal. Old pizza.
Germa digs an old pizza out of his bag and eats it.
All right, showboat is worn off. I think I'm all right still. Let's fight. What does
elbow drop presto majesto? Confused. Glue man is mesmerized. Good. Now we're gonna back
stab. Okay, mesmerized still, right? Yep. Glue man shakes off the magic and uses showboat.
I'm gonna talk about, damn it, bonding agent. I need to heal. Elbow drop. I fucking missed.
Drinks wrestle sweat. Chokeslam has been restored. Uh oh, I need to eat pizza again.
Shit, this is kind of safe. It's level 99. All right, he's a higher level than me. That's not
fair. You have no germans. Oh, what about, what about ice coffee abilities? Pure cholesterol? No.
He's confused. Let's go again. Let's do, try elbow drop. I want to land this. It's not very
effective. So we gotta do, but he's still confused. We're gonna have to go with backs.
We're gonna have to backstab again. Nice. All right, keeping confused. Still mesmerized.
Perfect. Can I do it again? Do it again. Keep it in a constant state. Again. Shit.
I need to use an item. Uh, cooking wine. Fully restores one of my abilities.
All abilities are restored. He just healed. Shit. Uh, presto majesto again.
No, god damn it. He's gonna kill me. Presto majesto, Jex mode, then backstab.
What happens if I die? Hit it. Critical hit. Look at that health drop. Do it again. He's still
confused. I can do it again. Crit again. Oh, he looks pretty close. Still mesmerized. Again.
Hit it. Yes. Here we go. Crit. Uh, he's still confused. I need to heal. Uh, eat another,
eat another pizza. We're good. I might be able to end it right here. See, how many do I have?
I got two more presto. Uh oh. No! No! Shit. Oh no. I, at this point, if it's, uh, I,
it's a race now. Oh my god, he keeps healing. This is never gonna end. No, not a full heal
yet. Not until I desperately need it. Stop eating pizza? No, back it up here. All right,
here we go. Give me a crit. Bring it down. Stay, yes, still confused. What do we got for items? Uh,
I have to do bag of diced coffee again. Good. Give more off. Try it again. Yep. I'm gonna beat
it. One more of those. Stay confused. Yes! Again. Yes! He's so close. Yes! No! Don't heal.
Oh god damn it. What? Uh, oh my god. No. That sucks.
What happens if I lose? Do I die? I got greedy. What was I supposed to do? I had to try.
Don't worry, I'm gonna crit twice. There's one. Again. I'm fine. Everything's fine. He's still
confused. Okay, we're off. We have to try this again and then I have to use. How much more
cooking wine do I have? Good. I only have one more cooking wine. Wait, I'm gonna use the cooking
wine. I still have my food. Here we go. Presto Magesto. Jex. Mesmerized. I need to get like
three or four crits here. Do it again. Stay there. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Again. That's
a big one. That's a big one. I only gotta do this one more time. Stay, he's still confused.
Okay, here we go. Presto Magesto has worn off. Should I do? That's it. I win. What? Wait, what?
He still has health? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Oh no. No, no, no, no. He's gonna kill me.
Oh, this is bad. Please. Yes. All right, we should be safe here. End it. Stay there.
Okay, this is it. We're going all in. All in. Time to win. That's it. Glueman has fainted.
Jerma is victorious. You looted a hundred vault coins. That's a hundred bucks right there.
What a battle. That was awesome. Now what? Okay, should I? One credit or three credits?
I feel like we could make some money here. Three credits. Let's go. Three rats. What is
it to hold the rats? 20. Hold on. God damn it. Glueman, Glueman. I'm gonna lose it all.
Rat, rat, rat. That's a big hit. 15. Fuck, I spent more money trying to hold the rats.
No, don't hold them. It's more money. It's not worth it. Minus five bucks. There we go.
That's a hit. I gotta go down. I gotta drop my bet. I'll drop to two.
Shit. All right. That's okay. That's 10 bucks. Coward. I don't want to... I just got a big... I
just made a hundred vault coins. All right. Is there a pay table? Oh, look at that. There
it is. Okay. Here we go. Look. Vault coins are worth the most. A full Jupiter is worth
the second most. Yeah. All right. So the rat symbol is the reason why you've seen the
most of it is because the rat is the least special blend. So we're looking for
Jupiters and vault coins. Use the glue. Oh, look at this. Props. That's cool.
They said the rats were there. That's the glue. That's cool. There are the vault coins.
Termillionaire. Use the cheat screen. I'm not cheating yet. Vault coin, vault coin.
Shit. What is Glueman worth? That'd be 60. It's worth it. Give it to me. God damn it.
Damn it. No. I'm going to have to put a little money in. Take it down to zero. Hey,
coming back. We're not broke yet. I can't do it. I can do it with tube. It's not worth it.
Shit. Try a different machine. This one's rat infested. Life is pain. I hate...
$75 now. Well, technically $50 down. Here we go. All right. Let's bring it back.
Another one. All right. Again. Free beers. Okay. That's... Life is back in us. All right.
This is important. You ready for this shit? Hold them both. I need one more vault coin and
that's $2,500. And that's just, that's a win. That's a completion of the game. God damn it.
I got to drop the bet. Hold both these. Give me the beer. Come on. Damn it.
No. No. What? Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing? Oh, I... Life is pain. I hate...
Give it to me. Oh, it's right there. It's right there. Oh, yes. All right. We got it.
We've unlocked the mini game Beer Crossing. However, this works. I'm not sure.
Burgers collected. Injured beers. Level one. What?
I have to cross the street? Five burgers. All right. What do I need? Three more?
How much time do I have? Can I go in here? Level one complete. Three burger value menus. $7.99.
Burg... I got five out of five. Let's go. Oh my God. Okay. That hurt. So that's one
injured beer. Does that take away from my money? Oh, you can see the corpses stay.
That's so funny. All right. Did I miss a burger? There's a burger down here. Wait,
I thought you said there was a burger down here. Oh, shit. There is. Okay. That's five.
I got it. It's done. Only two. Oh my God. Okay. Get across. Come on. Come on. Come on. Go,
go, go. Is that Otto? Oh, that's awesome. Hello, Otto. Any more? I think that's it. $7.99.
I missed a burger. I don't know what that was. I missed one. Level three. This is so cool.
You stay on the yellow line. White line. Whatever. Why are the hamburgers on the road?
I'm soup. There's probably eight. Seven. Oh, free the beers? Are they trapped?
They're not trapped, are they? I don't think they are. I think they're supposed to be.
Okay. All right. Slow down. They're not trapped. I can't save them. Free them.
There's no, I don't free them. They just stuck in here. All right. Hold on. Is there one more?
Here it is. Eight. Wait. You missed that one. Try another. That's so cool.
Look at all these references. 75%. I think that's it. Five injured beers. Eight out of eight
burgers even. Good. Next level. How many levels are there? Does this progressively just get
harder? There's one. Wait. No. All right. So this way. God. I'm panicking. Stop. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. Okay. Okay. I need way more than this. Five, six, seven,
and eight. Is it nine over there? Quickly. Get across the road. Oh, fuck.
This is so awesome because there are just so many here waiting.
The lore. The live system in this game. It makes complete sense. Oh my goodness.
This is kind of hard. All right. I'm going to slow down. I suck. I can't do it. Hold on.
He's running into the cards. I promise I'm not. All right. Safe. There's only one more to get.
Oh, fuck. Your stomach can get hit by the way. Yeah. Your stomach is a hit box. It can get
makes perfect sense. All right. I'm going to run this way and. Oh, fuck. Is there any more?
Oh, got it. Smile face. Hold on. Is there any more burgers over here?
There's Otto. Get out of the trash. Don't go in the trash. Bad dog. No more. Okay. I get 12.
12 out of 12. What the hell is this? This is a boss fight? What? Are you serious? Oh,
okay. I get it. I get it. Do I have to get burgers? I'm dead. Keep going or game sucks.
Okay. Obviously going to keep going. Shooting burgers. I got to watch out for the bullet
help. Oh my God. I got to go across the whole thing. How do I attack? Is there anything I
can do? I got to stay in the middle. What does that mean? Oh, they trap. No comes out.
Oh my goodness. This is cool. This is elaborate. All right. Watch out. I can find the right
spot to stay in. Spread them out. What's that? Tire? E. Oh, shit. I get it. Okay. This is
I have to throw tires at him probably three times like Dr. Robotnik style.
It's getting faster. Oh, God. All right. This is phase two. Just keep running in circles.
Oh, he has a, yeah. Mecha Burger Boy has a health bar. I got to hit him six times.
Oh, come on. Hurry, hurry. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Quick, quick, quick, quick.
I almost just missed. This is going to be impossible. I have to do that four more times.
Holy shit. Please play out. Oh, no. Oh, God.
Shit. Imagine this on like times five speed at the end. I was just gonna hit by that.
I completely forgotten it happened. All right. There's one. All right. Let's go.
This is going to be the rest of the stream. I'm going to beat this. Here we go. Faster.
Faster, faster, faster, faster. I'm only 500 pounds. Feed me more. Watch the fire.
He changes it up. He's starting to, he's starting to juke around. Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Come on.
No, wait. I'm too slow. Oh, God damn it. I threw it the wrong.
I didn't know that was possible. Yes. Somebody got it. Yes. That was the
Big Bertha arcade game. All right. I'm gonna get it this time. You gotta be quick because he moves
fast. Tire. Get it? Can we stay? I think we stay at this speed. I don't think we go any faster than
this. Oh, maybe it's only this for two phases. Oh, shit. That's faster. Oh, Jesus. All right.
Here it is. Give me. Oh, it's going faster.
Where? Anymore? Or in the middle? All right. I gotta stay right in the middle for this. I gotta
be, I just bullet hell dodge. Here we go. All right. Just dodge these. I got one more.
How many did you just shoot? Come here. Oh, got it. Oh, God. One more. That's it.
I only did one credit bet for this, by the way. Is that? Don't get hit. Don't get hit.
Don't get hit. Don't get hit. No, don't leave. No, no, no. Leave me at crossing. No.
Fuck. No. God damn it. It was so close. I just got confused by the car coming down.
That was a choke. It's because when the car came down. Oh, shit.
Damn it. I got it. It's harder than Jebel. No, just take the patience. God damn it. Just gotta
watch out for the... Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Mr. Mosquito. What does it say
behind the burger boy? Mine was just choke. There's this bird. All right. Here we go.
I'll get it here. Just gotta be patient. All right. Bullet hell. Three more. This is it.
This is the last speed. Oh, don't fuck it up already. All right. Come on. He's gonna move.
Here it comes. One move to the left. Oh, shit. Good spot to be in. Good RNG. Good RNG.
Yes. The meeting of the beers. The vault of burgers is ours. 26 injured beers. 31 out of 32.
That was fucking awesome. 10 bucks. 10 dollars. Because I was only doing one credit.
That would have been 30 bucks. Hey, it was the ride. The ride was worth it.
All right. So let's see. Cool. Surrounded by burgers for completing that one. So we've
seen rat burger boy glue man. There's still three we need to see. I've got more money to spend.
That was awesome. Nice. Always three credits. I wonder what the germ of fear face. I'm curious
what happens. I can't believe this game is just more than just a shit post. Oh, this is
amazing. This is a lot of work went into this. For real. Damn it. How much money have I put
into the machine? I don't even know. It's a hundred dollars, right? Now you can see the stats.
Let's see. Music. Play intro. Events. Minigames. Enable. Enable cheats. Not yet.
Use stats. Steam achievements. Slot. Slot spins 84. Reels held. Bits spent 500 dollars.
50,000. When did I spend bits? Minus 212 difference. Terma wins. Vault coin. Jackpot.
Event. Oh, this is cool. Perfect games. No perfect game. Fastest perfect game.
Jupiter. I don't want to see these. I don't want to see these.
Damn it. Oh, it's a hundred bits. It's a hundred dollars in bits. Oh,
come on. Hit me something. Jupiter's worth a lot of money. Oh, I got it. That was 30 bucks.
What's this? Let's check out some fruit. Fruit. Not just a healthy snack, but also
very cheap and affordable. Go to your local grocery store and buy it by weight. You can
do it with apples. You can do it with bananas, or you can even juice some oranges with your son.
Fruit. Crisp with a refreshing crunch. It's no wonder it's the doctor's favorite.
At just 95 calories, it's the guilt-free party fruit. Invite some friends over,
or just enjoy one in your home. Apples. Nature's candy. Oh, that's fucking awesome.
We got it. There's the jaw. The championship belt. My voice is two seconds behind. Yeah,
because of the PlayStation 2. Should be fixed. All right, now we can max bet. Max bet. You never
won the Rumble, and it's still my championship. Still my league. We need a Jupiter. It's only
five bucks. No. There we go. Again. There we go. Again. All right. Here you go. Ready? I'm
gonna hold the Jupiter. All right. We got two Jupiters. Holding both of the Jupiters.
Let's see it. Oh, do it again. Yes. Solve the puzzle. All right. You did it.
That's it. Solve the puzzle. You have unlocked the advanced puzzle.
Oh, no. Oh, God. Are you kidding me? Five, 10, 15, 20. All right. Eight. I'm stuck here.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three,
four, three, two, one, one, one, one. I can't believe it. Okay. Four, five, five again,
five again, five again, and then eight. Oh, God damn it, man. Eight, nine. So this is one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine. I can't. This is fucking fantastic. One, two, three, four, five. Five is in six.
This is done. One, two, three, four, five. This is done and this is three, seven, four. One,
two, three, four. One, two, three. All right. One, two, three. One, one, one, one, one, one,
one, two, three, three. I can't believe that you actually made a pit cross level,
five, six, one, two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four, one, one, two, three,
two three two one one one this is correct we're talking about that's done okay so now we need this
is motherfucker i swear to god one so seven how many here one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven so one two three four okay so that's three let me just make sure i'm getting
this right one two three four five six seven one two three four five six seven so this is the
first one is this three one two three three one two three three what emote is this going to be
that's the question okay that's that so it's 20 by 20 so that's three
nine one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
so it can be four into the side right so one two five six seven eight nine okay
this is definitely the same thing in the middle here because they both nine one four
let me count here three six let me see what's down here this is eight seven one two three four
five six seven one two three four five six one two three four two three yeah this is correct
so this is three space this is three space it's five in the middle here five five six so one two
three four five six seven and then this is a two this is three two all right that's part of
the six that's the one so that's five one three four one two three one so it's gonna be
right here that's one excellent commentary oh i'm trying to concentrate i can't screw this up
i'm trying so hard to like pay attention one two three four one two two four one three two four
one one two three four i think i can get this though let's see no look at me is there a big
number here let's see five one three it can be somewhere over here this is part of the three
what about this way there's a nine in here a 20 by 20 of course you're gonna do that too
four let's see seven ten thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen let's see here
two nine three hold on i can i can i do this whole thing three four five six seven yes i can
this column is done so that's four then three has to be in here one two three space one one
it has to be like right here that's the one and then here's your three in here somewhere
one one two three four has to be in here somewhere okay we're getting we're making
progress now that leaves me here this is this is one of the twos one two five has to be here
there's the two there's another two so now i need a four four seven six six yeah that's done for
four this is a one in here somewhere how far away is this now this is nine so four this is
three okay don't have it yet but this has to be a two it's probably right there two two
this is one of those games you play in a retirement home kind of yeah
seven oh is wrong how is oh wrong the three has to be in here somewhere row 18 column m
what's wrong with it is you one f is wrong no you guys are getting in my head all right no
you're getting in my head fuck you can fill some of oh yeah i can two one two three four
six seven eight can't be any of these so let's see one two three four five six seven eight nine
it has to be all these one one one one this is part of four five one three four i could do
that why did i remove those crosses i don't know you're right what's what am i doing
okay here we go that helps this out one two three four five six seven eight nine
10 11 so that makes sense let me see that's one three yeah okay because this can't one two
three four five got it there's a three all right it is the three this row is done three three
one three that leaves us with let me just see here three this is it has to be three right
the middle here right and there's one three here has to be right here that's two so that's
three three one three four this is two two two this is one of the fours two it would be here
it kind of has to be here right why not i messed up row 18 how no it's fine it's not
messed up i can do this again here though because the same amount there's one okay three
because this is nine what about here row 18 is done i knew that bingo now here's okay okay
wait wait wait wait so this has to be here this is okay i got it wait wait it's calm down calm
down two right here this can't be down here because this row is now done therefore
this is the two this is the three this row is done we're getting there close four three one
five three three we're good that means what does that mean three one three i'm not gonna
somebody just gave 50 bucks who just gave money uh magical marissa gave 60 dollars and says you
should probably hire someone else to do this puzzle no i can do this thank you for the 50
bucks and then 10 bucks right before it's 60 dollars from magical marissa thank you that's a
ton of money really appreciate it i can't rush through i can't rush through this seriously
because like i if i fuck up one thing i have to go all the way back and it's gonna ruin
everything but 60 bucks thank you so much that's an absolute shit load of money four hold on wait
i'm just checking four one two he's so good at what he does two two one four that's the
whole row is done i'm gonna break the mr mosquito disk in fucking half okay here we go
one three can't be here because that's one two right easy slow down that's the one this is
done done one nine here we go one two three four five six seven eight nine two that's done
one two nine one okay and then that's done there's your two all right hold on slow down
one two how many twos are here there's one two three four there's four twos and then
then this so there's four twos in here so you got one two can't be there it's got to
be like that two two two all right that's all i know okay seven can i put any more in here
i don't think so what we got this is four one four so this is okay all the twos are done so
this these are both fours so this has to be like this what the fuck is that
this is my video made this all by myself hi why is this playing why is this playing
is this supposed to be distraction
did i do that right one four four that's it that's it okay three
three
okay that was fun this is three three one three three one three this is done three three one
three four four four three one three three there's too many sounds all right it's gonna
loop it's playing the second one three
one two this is the three
this is this done i think this is done three one three three
two this is four so one two three four one two three four five six that's done
um one three two one okay three two is over here somewhere three one one
cookies let's see this is a two right three two
five one two three four five oh my fucking god
you're killing me
your house
where's the six down here that's that's me doing that that's not even the actual voice
uh
this is three here this is a one two three four five six seven
two
i'm trying to finish this as fast as i can
one two it has to be up here right because it can't be this way because this is two one two
show the real three this is done
this is three one two
that's it right
one three four one one five one two three four five four
one all right i got it it's getting there it's getting there it's almost done
it just replays it four two one four three this is done
oh that's done one two three four five six seven eight nine ten that's correct because this has
to be here two two three four that's done two one two two there's one more two here
oh fuck hold on
one three one this is three one two five one two that's done all right i got it it's done i got
it one two three four all right hold on it's almost done
oh why are you doing this to us i'm sorry this it just popped up on me what am i supposed to do
one two three two one one two one two three four done what's left what else does have what's left
three oh i can't think it's done is it not done one two three four five six seven
one two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight nine
two one that's it
that's 50 bucks we did it bald coin let's take a look what else what do we get for that
we anything new for that that was the jupiter right oh there it is i forgot that this was
slots yeah me too we just need bald coin and that's it we've come to the end that's the
only one thing we haven't seen come on give me a ball coin give me a ball coin
ball coin so i can respin come on come on there it is here we go again do it again
come on do it we need to see it oh oh i'm gonna lose it all what's up i just need to hit one
look take a look up here it's 500 bucks if you hit one oh okay check the service buttons
i don't think i can press it 500
no shit i need to make money i gotta come on i gotta like hit something just let me hit let
me hit a jupiter like this all right come on i need to get to like a hundred again nice okay
again again we got a couple chances here ah look at the left reel no no uh it was worth a
shot oh no can i i can't put money in no i can't put money into like ah i have to go to zero
shit i need to hit it i need to hit it organically no cheating i have to hit this
organically with money i'll take a germ of fear too all right i'll take it i'll take it we're
gonna be here a while this is where all the bit money goes you guys down to one let's do
it give me another one all right this is the real deal here we got like we can do this like
two times come on last chance ah damn it oh i miss pain i hate come on oh get more cash
oh i you gotta hit something to get cash maybe it's worth uh maybe see if i can get it
damn it kim kim kim thinks i's kim i'm sorry but
kim life is pain i hate i'm gonna put another fucking hundred
sorry kim just hold a rat every time ah no more money life is pain i hate come on no
there we go all righty what about your groceries i
buy car payments i'm fine everything's fine i just need to hit it come on this is the strategy
wait i'm just spending the same amount of money every time this doesn't do anything
that's not helpful no maybe another one hundred dollars ago i just need to get the big hit
do it no don't hold the rat wrong button life is pain i hate 30 bucks if i get it
i can't even do it if you cheat i'm unsubbing i'm not gonna cheat i'm not cheating i'm not
gonna happen what about groceries what she needs to know what you want for groceries i want
a a bottle of kefir and orange juice and uh jupiter
just give me the jupiter again it's 150 bucks then we get it i gotta get i gotta get a streak
going okay that's a pretty good streak two credits hold them both that'll be
60 bucks you ready let's see it god damn it oh my god i just want to get the bald coin
all i care about is the bald coin uh i can do two that's 30 bucks though it's not even worth it
oh my goodness if i cheat i wish i could put in like 500 come on uh there we go all right
hot machine machines getting hot big hit
why are you using the three every time because i'm trying to get a big hit
i'm going i'm going for the big one i'm going for a big hit incoming big hit big hit incoming
i'll do two okay bring it down to one this is the opportunity for the jackpot
you ready oh come on look it's right there
god damn it all right 32 it's worth it free credits hold them both big hit oh fuck
all right i'm only gonna do one credit no matter what come on come on no
oh five thousand people watching a man go bankrupt i mean you're gonna say
it's five thousand people watching a guy hit the bald coin bonus right now
eventually my luck's gonna turn around it just did you know i mean it's impossible
for your luck to not turn around it's just impossible right here
life is pain i hate i gotta hit this organically before i turn off the stream the streams on it
just hold glue man and just try to get three of them hold juke okay
let's try to get a jupiter come on give me a jupiter let me get there it is okay come on do
it come on no just break mr mosquito for good luck shit i'm not gonna break mr mosquito
it's gonna turn around right here this is 30 dollars do it oh my god no
life is pain i'm 725 dollars in the hole hold whatever cost the most yeah that's what i'm trying
to do oh what give me something i haven't i haven't hit anything in like 25 straight minutes
come on hit me something all right this is it this is the one right now here it comes
bingo bald coin bonus i got a few more chances here no no no oh it's right here
higher higher bets have better rolls maybe let's try three no what yeah
it's fine if i get to like how much money do i need to get to before i
life is pain i hate you can press e now you see you can only do it when you get to zero
come on whoa i did it i did it i got it all is forgiven all is forgiven i got it
i did it 500 bucks i win still these as achievements there's still achievements to do
what else is there to do still in the hole could i have the help get it get it get it
get me out of the hole come on
no come on do it it's all crashing down no oh i i just had five no i can hold after
putting in money i didn't know that if you don't get out of the hole i'm going to unsub you
understand that that's almost impossible to do that right now this where's the cat there's no
cash out machine i can't turn this into money just cheat ice coffee sipped oh right okay
ice coffee sipped life is pain i hate service button i don't can i press i don't think i
can press it service sir how do i press the service button hold up oh wait was there like
a controls you e and enters use interact select general movement uh i don't think you can do that
i think it's just there god damn it no one knows how to play this game yeah that's right
i'm the only one that has the controls here i just hit something all right settle down settle
down everybody all right here we go here we go no there we go you ready oh do it come on
do it this one this one oh this one this one do it last chance i did it are you serious
what no way no way three times in a row well all right that's it get 100 should i break it see
what happened no service button i you can't press the service button i think that's all
there is to see we'll see wait the dev in the chat all right we got dev in the chat how
do i get to the credits there's a credits page yeah and there's something i can press
did i hit a jupiter i did he did say something where was it cad it was cad restart the game okay
restart game it's only from the main title yeah okay is there anything else to see besides
the uh in here david bowie seriously suck a fart out of my ass why so mean david bowie i
totally got you failed the jupiter puzzle okay all right here we go credits so there's something
i can do in the credits and actually you know what this was a good idea absolutely fantastic
this was hilarious oh this was so much more than i ever could have imagined for a community
fan project discord now you've been in discord talking about this for a long time so
absolutely claps by the way anybody can play this uh if not after tonight's stream
then on monday just gonna be free it cad has decided just to anybody it's on it's gonna be
on steam it's just on steam you just uh have fun with the play with so that's amazing these
people go give them a follow right now okay so i was told that there's months
work he's coming back up to a chair i don't know what month it is i don't know what day
it is this is not true is that if i don't work on the game i get hit and i have to eat
auto's fucking dog biscuit
oh
fuck is this oh my god that was terrifying uh but ktd and cad absolutely fantastic job
this is fucking amazing oh it's like a special thing shit let him go i don't i
click the bird i think this is the only one with me can i click me oh i just clicked on that
it and it did it just i think yeah it opened up my stream my stream won't even load that's
funny all right so i think we've seen everything there is to see in germa slots
oh fail jupiter right okay let's fail the jupiter yeah we have to do this again great
that's a nut button down there i didn't see that what the hell was that all right so
let's uh let's cheat it let's fail jupiter all right so fail this how do i feel it
now lose to glue man okay let's see if that does let's lose what about run there we go
should i run yeah let's run you ran away what a coward oh that's it so okay what what does
this mean though what is the germ this j e r m a you have no germas left what does that mean
oh switching pokemon okay he missed he's not playing as good as he was last time nice
good hit i'm gonna win by accident i guess i could just do jex over and over again yeah so
he's gonna heal he's disappointed you cheated sip the ice coffee yeah i gotta drink the ice
coffee like five times no but hold on what happens if you run out of all your moves
uh i think you just can't use them okay so let's see what did we not okay ice coffee
restores one of your abilities we didn't we didn't okay i want to see what this does
germa injects himself with pure cholesterol just want to see if there was an animation for it
because that would be the only thing we didn't click on i know i just wanted to see what it
did chokes land there it is i know it was a full heel oh whoops that's the wrong thing
good thing he shook it up restart the game once more and check out the stuff on the floor
and in the trash can okay this was so much fun though before you get in the chair okay i see
trash is gonna be full of memes it better be but uh well i have a second here i must say
this is uh this is fucking incredible i cannot believe that these references and these jokes
and the things in this community i can't believe it this is fucking amazing all this exists
because we all collectively think the same fucking thing is funny or interesting uh it
it's absolutely fucking incredible to me i don't think you're funny
me it's all right even if you don't all right kill me glue man let's go kill me
i don't think i've hit that any one time how am i breaking free all right blue man
drinks wrestle sweat there it is choke slam critical hit what happens it's super effective
germa has fainted blue man is victorious you lost a hundred bald coins he takes
money from you if you lose well that's funny all right let's go see what's in the trash
so what all right cat i got a question what achievements am i missing there's two more
achievements that i don't have what are they you know is there is there a secret
well the perfect bia game okay like it turns better don't tell them it's i'll try to press
the service button all right so start looking on the floor yeah all right that's fucking amazing
okay where are those actually where are they about the author a snake in the clouds what else is in
there i can't see there's something underneath it is it a snake it's my children's book
oh there it is it's my book okay so the other achievements are yeah i can't hit the
service button so the other achievements are to perfect the bia game and then to get 10 000
organically that was awesome i missed a giant jupiter where organically we don't have time
for organically i don't think you need to do it organically uh not a perfect bia run just
all the burgers okay i see uh cad uh cad vip that is fucking oh this is great this is like a
solid hour and a half two hours worth of like game content and you and i are gonna probably
have a little discussion after the stream here because this is like this is next level uh-oh
he's in trouble was it the short joke you know you're not gonna have a little bit of
convo about some of these things and i uh i well there's a bunch of people here to talk
about it i was supposed to today if you didn't you missed what happened earlier i was going
to do a scratch ticket for charity thing and this but um there's no state lottery in nevada
it doesn't exist scratch tickets do not exist in nevada and it was a major massive oversight
on my part for not assuming that there was no state lottery in nevada i had no idea i'm from
massachusetts originally i was under the impression i could walk into a gas station
and just buy uh but so i know that is pretty ironic it is so what's going to happen here is
there's a couple of scratch ticket things that i can do possibly but for the immediate future
i'm just going to give two hundred and twenty one dollars to the nevada humane society so
retroactively we're just going to say that each death in securo was a dollar so that's
just going to happen and if i can somehow figure out a way to do that with actually
getting tickets i was a little disappointed today but mr mosquito was a lot of fun until
i broke the disc and then this was incredible so i'm very happy 221 not two dollars and 21
yeah there's also like that i could do have somebody send them to me and then like i just
cash them out in that state later there's a couple of ways but just for the immediate
future to wrap up like the securo thing because that was to wrap up securo so i'm
just going to donate the money so for the purposes of the rest of tonight i'm going to
take a break uh and we'll come back and i'll just chill we'll probably just hang out might put in
might put in uh there's a couple of options here i don't know if i want to do i'm not sure
if i want to do monster rancher 4 because i'm probably only going to stream for like
another hour so i think we're just going to come back and just chill and like i'll turn
the camera around let's talk and hang out as it means i gotta go put clothes on more mr
mosquito no i that was that became that gave me angry but we'll figure it out maybe
we'll do something else i'll be back and we'll hang out for a little while longer before i turn
off the stream see you guys in like two minutes three minutes just keep the music playing why
if you take it off uh i'm i'll see you in a couple days i'm gonna take uh two days off
so i'll be back on what's today i'll see you on saturday sunday see you on tuesday
but for those of you sticking around um by the way next week is vr so i'm gonna get back
into vr probably start with mind show maybe or end with mind show geoguesser i could do
geoguesser we could just hang out and play it but uh those of you that are sticking around i'll see
you very soon be right back