Alright, pretty good defense down here. This is looking pretty good. Pyro, maybe trying
to help a little bit. Thank you so much. You would have backstabbed me. Now, let's go
fight. The enemies are going to come from over here. Follow me. Turn left. No, you didn't
turn left. Come back up the stairs. Go back up the stairs. Oh shit. I think I startled
them. I scared them. It's okay. Calm down. Calm down. It's okay. Don't worry. It's okay.
Calm down. Oh shit. Oh shit. I don't want to lose this. I'm going to have to use this.
I can't go anywhere. Alright, come on, Shmee. Do something. Go out there and stab somebody.
Oh my god. You're kidding me right now. Why did you do that? Baby Shmee again drops the
ball in the fucking end zone. No, you go. I like you. No, you go. I like you. No, you
go. Watch out now. Watch out now. Watch out. Get along now. Well, let me take care of that
for you. Whoops. What is this guy doing? I'm just like target practice with this guy right
out. He's going to get it eventually. Oh no, he's gone. He's like, oh shit. There's a Pyro.
Oh, that was awesome. What the fuck is this guy really seriously doing? Red Heavy. Red Heavy,
I'm going to come out disguise. I need help. Shmee. Okay. Hi. Where do I spread? To wrap this
video up, I just want to say one more public service announcement about the species and how
we can protect them. Please donate to your local Shpee foundation. My favorite is the
species are we and the species are we and it was like watching that I like can't even do the
outro. Anyways, good night everybody.