Does it work? You guys see the stream. What happened? 25 million...
late? Yes. What? I was? Oh. I was just testing the stream.
Look, if you lose by 7 seconds, you still lost. If you lost by 4 seconds, you still lose.
I hate to tell you that, but that's... Hey, look, if you get...
If you get Blackjack at the table, and the dealer gets Blackjack too, I'm sorry, you didn't win.
I know it feels kind of horrible. I trusted you. Double Blackjack? I did not do that on purpose.
I really didn't. Hello, everybody. How are you? Let me just make a tweet. Today, we are going to
play a video game. I know that yesterday we had some problems. It has been essentially confirmed
for me, even though nobody confirmed it. I confirmed it myself with just how I feel about
the situation. There was something wrong with where the traffic was coming from for some
streamers to the Twitch ingest servers. I know I wasn't the only one. I remember Ludwig was
talking about it. We both had the problem yesterday. It's working now. There's not a
problem now. We got the free space. Why are you playing Bingo? I'm playing Pikmin today.
This is not a Bingo stream. Yeah, I got Pikmin 2s ready to go. I have the Wii version. I don't
know if that's a bad thing or not. People are going to be really pissed off that I have the
Wii version, not the GameCube version, but that's the way it is. It's been upscaled from 480p to
like 520p. Those extra 40 resolution pixels are worth it for me, okay? Let me grab my drink. I'll
be right back. Two seconds. Also, I made a mistake here. I was brewing a tea. What's going on with
my mic here? Come on. Get up here. My mic stand is fucked up. What the fuck? I brewed a tea
and the tea bags, I had black tea and a green tea. They were right next to each other and I didn't
know which one was which. I wanted black tea and I was just kind of rushing to get things started.
I didn't know which one was the black tea. I kind of switched them around too much,
so I just put them both in and didn't even care and just brewed it. I don't know if that's a
problem. Is it mixing black and green tea like a bad thing? I wasn't gonna wait like the two or
three minutes to ruin the water because if I put the green one in... Oh shit, it's the green one.
I wanted black tea. No, I don't want the green tea. I would have to like... Okay, I guess I'm
gonna drink green tea or what? You redo it, you re-boil the water and... No. So I just put them
both in and it's like a weird mix of black and green. I don't know, mixing like different tea
drugs. What? We don't have to... I didn't even tweet this. What the... That's the whole point.
I went and got my phone. All right, what should I... What should I title this? How about just
Pikmin 2 is fucking fun as hell. Pikmin 2. Let's go guys. No, I'm not doing that. This tea tastes
bad but I don't even care. I want it. I knew this was gonna happen too. This is gonna cause
some frustrations for me. I knew it. I'm hunching over because my mic is fucked. Hold on.
And also I'm like stalling right now because I'm terrified that I'm gonna get like twitch...
The server's gonna fuck up again. So pardon my paranoia right now while I wait to make sure
this is gonna be green for an extended period. It's too teasy. All right, I'm gonna mute because...
Okay, are you ready? Are we ready for Pikmin 2? I have not... I've only played like maybe an hour
of all this one entire series. So I don't know if it's any good or not. I need to adjust this.
Pikmin 2. That... Wow. That really is like kind of 1080, isn't it? That is 1080. Kind of. I mean,
I'll fix it. It's 7-1. It's 7-something. I'm probably gonna make somebody sick by doing this
but I want to get this right. Oh, don't go to a black screen. No! Oh, that actually... Yeah,
that's perfect. Almost there. Almost got it. Almost got it. Almost got it. Got it. Done. All
right. Pikmin 2. I don't care about the cutscene. I don't know anything about Pikmin 1. It's a guy
that like pulls flower people out of the ground and throws them and stuff. I don't need that much
of an explanation for it. I can't imagine the story is that intricate. Is it? Is the story that big
of a deal? Hello, this game is shit. You're about to get attacked and I look... What am I supposed
to do? I'm looking from like the rafters of the base. Looking down at you running around
with like a pickaxe or something and there's like 200 people with like machine guns around you
and you're running around like, let me in! Hey, let me in the base! Pikmin 2 sucks!
And I'm just looking down like, dude, I'm sorry. You're dead. There's nothing I can do for you.
They're all... You're surrounded. Just like... You're dead. I'm sorry. And then you like throw
the pickaxe up at me like I'm the problem. Like, oh, fuck you, buddy! It's like, no, I didn't...
You just did that. You pissed off like a thousand people. And by the way, you hit like the middle of
the castle. You're not strong enough to throw that high. Now you don't have a pickaxe. Now you
fucked. I gotta test this too. He's stalling. I'm just making sure it's green for 10 minutes,
please! I'm so paranoid. I'm paranoid. I'm not putting... I'm not putting a face cam on for this.
Oh, you're not getting a face cam. All right, I need to test the audio and that is a real
thing. That's not a stalling thing. You ready? One, one, two, three, two, let's go. Pick. Good?
Sounds pretty good, right? Good? All right, let's go. Pikmin 2. Does this have motion controls?
Begin. Great Pikmin 2 save data. Yes. We want to see your face. Uh, no, I'm not doing it. I'm
not putting my face cam on. It's not happening. This is a pre-recorded thing. No, it's not. I
think we're green though. I'm fine. Uh, new ships log. Sure. Are there upgrades in this game?
Alcatate, a freight, is a long-haul deep space shipping company. One day, it's only employee
of any merit. Captain Olimar, his entire first game, got hit by an asteroid and crashed into
Earth on interstellar vacation. There, he was aided by indigenous creatures, which he called
Pikmin. In the end, Captain Olimar escaped. Good. Don't need to play the first game now.
But in Olimar's absence, his employer, Hokatate Freight, ran into financial difficulties.
It was way too hot. Dead. There's Captain Olimar. And by the way, people that say Olimar,
we don't listen to those people. President of Hokatate Freight, local employee Louie.
Oh, this is a spoiler. I knew he was in the game because I played Smash Brothers.
Olimar, I'm so glad you're safe. Yes, very glad. Quite glad. But, sadly, I have an announcement
that is not so glad. Our company is going under. Yes, we're finished. On his first mission, Louie
here met a ravenous space bunny. His entire load of golden PikPik brand carrots was eaten.
I took out an enormous loan to repay the debt from this loss. I decided to sell assets to repay.
I fucking forgot about something. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. I just want to make sure that the water boiler was off.
I was like, water boiler. Wait, is that on? Oh, fuck. It's off. We're good. It was off. Making
sure. Missed the story. With Captain Olimar, you too will save the galaxy. I mean, restart.
Okay, I know that he's probably his cousin or something.
It's a little brother. Valley of... Okay. We have to repay the debt together as brothers.
Nintendo loves having Super Mario and Super Luigi. I get it.
That's a lot uglier than I thought it was going to be.
That was close. I have averted a crash landing.
Running diagnostics. Alert. Danger. Louis is missing. He must have somehow fallen out of his
cockpit. He hates the game already. No, I don't. He is not responding via his communicator.
He is either flouting protocol or in danger. Oliver, fuck. You must find Louis before he
freezes to death in the cold of this planet. Wait a moment. Look. Look. It's a Bunger Burger and
Pikmin. Could these be Pikmin? They look like they're about to be devoured as we speak.
You must help them point at the screen and press B to call them with your whistle. Oh, no. It uses
the Wii pointer. Oh, God. I already hate it. I already hate the game. Okay. You can also hold
B to make the sound of your whistle carry farther. Remember? Nope. All right. Let's see what happens.
All right. Where's my... I point. Oh, shit. Okay. This game blows. No, it's stop. We haven't even
gotten five minutes in. This is like everyone's favorite game in this channel. Pikmin ran to your
side. They seem to remember you, Captain Oliver. How fascinating. Give them instructions and do
not delay. Hold A to grab a Pikmin. And I got to lean back to this one. I'm sitting back. Hold on.
And point at the screen and release to throw it. Shit. Okay. So hold A, grab Pikmin, then hold...
Then point at the screen and release to throw it. Cool. Actually, I might actually like this. We'll
see. So hold the Pikmin. Actually, it's actually pretty good. It's not bad. That could be a lot
worse. I'm going to need like a wrist helper though. Hold on. Yeah. I'm going to have to rest my
wrist and just sit here. Attention, Captain Oliver. I have just reestablished my communications link
with Louis. It is fortunate we have managed to confirm his safety. Press minus to communicate
with him. Cool. Do the fucking bingo. Wow. I'm going to do bingo of my own stream. If I look at
the bingo, when I not want to do those things, you're going to have to update me later. I'm
quite interested in the details of his condition. I'm not going to look at it. Why would I do that?
No, don't have any fun. Okay. So let's talk to Louis. Louis. It's Vin Diesel. And introducing
Vin Diesel as Louis. Louis, allow me to assess your condition. As per our safety protocols,
are you at all injured? Is that so? And my concerns are eased. Our communication link
shows you are nearby. Okay, cool. You make your way to our location. Rejoin us. I will navigate
for you. Press plus sign to contact me and obtain information about the terrain. Louis doesn't have
any Pikmin. Louis has no Pikmin. So I just run up through the... Oh, okay. Yeah, we are nearby.
Thank God there's a map in the game. I'm so happy there is. Is it worth one? Looks like Louis died
on impact. That's how they open with it? That would be horrible. Louis, the odd object before
you appears to be one of the Onions mentioned in Olimar's report. And this is where you get
the Pikmin from. This is where they are born. The seed, the onion ejected just sprouted according
to Olimar's report. It can be plucked with A. No fucking way. Oh, it does the wee moan sounds too.
Oh, he's so cute. This is a red Pikmin. They have fire damage. Maybe. This must be one of the Pikmin
creatures from Olimar's report. It is staring at you. You can press down on the d-pad to issue
objectives to your Pikmin squad and direct their movement. You can disband your squad with C.
Interesting. What is C? Oh. Olimar's description of the creatures resembling PikPik carrots was
strikingly accurate. Louis, my sensors have detected drool in the corner of your mouth.
Are you all right? Well, he just got in like a fucking plane crash. What are you talking about?
He's probably like really fucked up right now. So now it takes one to get the one coin, right?
Oh, that's cool. All right, go get that. Go get that. Hey, stupid. Go get that. To throw him,
why can't he just get it on his own? Oh, it's worth one coin. Is there upgrades in this game?
Eventually, am I going to be able to upgrade stuff? Because I will like it if there's upgrades.
So these ones give me more Pikmin. Oh, interesting. The onion ejected more seeds. The pellet from that
flower must hold nutrients that breed Pikmin. Holy shit, this is cool. Yes, the Pikmin gather
nutrients, haul them to the onion, and further propagate the species. The onion is a Pikmin
mothership. Reviewing Olimar's report, it seems repeatedly tapping A lets one rapidly pluck
Pikmin sprouts. Oh shit, okay. How many can I get? Oh, I just have to do it. Okay, so I have three.
How do I call them back? Oh, we go. All right, and so that's down B in Smash Brothers. I get it.
All right, so you go get that one. You go get that one. You go get that one. Problem solved.
Why am I getting minus two for that? That's just a fact. That's my only experience with Pikmin is
being Olimar in Smash Brothers. Oh, that's cool. Okay, let's get even more of them. How many can I
have? What's this one worth? Get it. Olimar is the worst character. Wasn't he pretty high tier for a
while? This game is legitimately hard. Have fun. Well, this game is legitimately hard. Have fun.
Do they have a health bar? Okay, so now I've got I've got 11 Pikmin. Where should we go? They're
kind of slow. There's a Duracell battery. Wait, it's actually a Duracell battery. Is this like
branding in the game? Perhaps this object is one of the treasures that we are searching for.
The only reason we found it here is because this is where you crash landed. How fortunate.
I would like to appraise it, but you must regroup with Olimar first. Can you see him?
Press Z to move the camera behind you. You can also press left or right to zoom it up or down
to change angles. Okay, that's good to know. Okay, that's like just a turn camera. Oh, that's very
important. That's disband the group, right? Oh, I don't want to do that. All right, let's go to
Olimar. Look, I've got friends too. I throw them over there. Hey, hey, hello. Can I pick this up?
Wait, like go into the bag? All right, one of you go up there and investigate.
One out of 15. What? I need more. Wait, can I twitch back to Olimar? Oh, it's a puzzle game.
Now what? It's gonna be an RTS. We're gonna have Olimar on the right side with 10 blue Pikmin,
five purples. We're gonna have Louis on the left side going to collect like a gold mine from
somebody else's base or something with like 10 purples, right? Oh, God, I'm gonna lose my mind
in this game. You're reunited at last. This has been a troublesome start to our trip.
But now you must feel assured that your combined wits can get you through anything, correct?
From now on, use B to form a single group, C to take solo action. And that's to change the leaders.
Okay, form a single group, C to take solo action. Walk around by yourself, okay? So, okay, let's
get everybody together, right? We got everybody? Let's take this though. Over here. I want you
guys to get that. Yeah, all of you. Bring it back to the ship. Let's dissect it. And then some of
you come over. Wait, what about getting the battery? Oh, this is cool. I need, I'm probably
gonna need 15 people to get the battery. How many people do you think it takes to get the battery?
All right, let's go get the battery. Or is it back here? How many? It takes, what's it doing?
Why can't they get it? Take it out. Oh, this is cool. Okay, dig, dig, dig. And they're gonna
pull it out. I like this game. I like this game. Oh, I like this game. I like this game. A lot of
people were potentially, oh, I need 20. I don't have 20. We need another seed. All right, you guys
come with me. Wait, hold on. We just, it's because we fed the machine a body? Is that enough? That's
enough? We have to feed the machine bodies to make Pikmin. All right, get in there. Give me that
battery. It's probably worth like $1,000. It's called recycling, Jeremy. Well, hold on. I need
it. I need like a, I gotta put like a notebook underneath my arm. In fact, I'm gonna turn this
way. I'm gonna play sideways. You know, I'm gonna put this on the other monitor. I'm playing sideways
right now. Easier on my wrist, like rested on my arm bit, on wrist, arm wrist thing. Right now I'm
sitting kind of sideways looking slightly to the right because my arm wrist thing, my chair, is
propping up my Wiimote so I can just wicked slowly like slob like move this around. It's taking
them a long time. Your hand is too shaky. Duracells are heavy. They're doing their best. I like this
game. All right, I'm probably gonna like the first four or five hours of this game and I'm gonna hate
the rest of it. I just want to be very clear. 280 bucks. A courage reactor. Oh, that's cool.
I love the sound it makes. You hear that? That's, I love that noise. Cool. Our first day of
exploration has yielded our first treasure. We will be done in record time. I took liberty
of naming it when I appraised it. The name reflects my current thinking. Leave it to me to think up
catchy names for hit products. It is but one of my many talents. We shall end our first day here
and report back to our president. His face will surely be joyous. However, to communicate with
Hokotate, we must fly into low orbit above the planet. We will not return to the surface until
morning so as to avoid the indigenous nocturnal creatures. That's Minecraft, okay? So you have to
during the, oh my god, it's Minecraft. It's, at night you have to get out. It's timed. This is
what you guys are talking about. Where's all the Pikmin? Oh, yes, but minus two. Oh, come on,
it was one Bunger Burger we could have taken. Days, I thought they said Toeklase. Toedays report.
There's money involved. You like cash in money and you have like storage of Pikmin's and you view,
I spend this money. You found your first bit of treasure. Fine work. Our future depends on
your effort so check your treasure hoard regularly. I'll check it often. Keep up the pace.
Definitely safe. Oh, here's the song. Treasure hoard. Oh, cool. Zoom in on it. What did the
journal say? We've recovered our first treasure. Amazingly, the Pikmin remembered how to salvage
it. Oh, I can't understand their adorable language and I don't know what they're thinking.
Yet, I am so happy to see them. When I crashed on this planet, the Pikmin helped me locate my
missing ship's parts. In my darkest hour, the Pikmin were there for me. Now that I'm reunited
with them, I know everything will be alright. It will, right, Gordon? Oh, this is New Things
in the Piklopedia. Why are you Professor Oak? I don't know who that is. Let's go to the area.
Day two. I kind of just sit and listen to this music. Excuse me, what? What are you talking about?
How what? What's going on? What did you want? Pretending. What happened? Professor Oak. What?
Somebody said I sounded like Professor Oak. What? What's going on? I'm freaking out right now. What
are you guys talking about? It's a career ending statement. I don't understand what's going on.
Somebody said you sound like Professor Oak and I was like, oh, I don't know what that is.
Professor Oak from Pokemon. I don't know who that is. I have no idea who that is.
I don't know who Professor Oak is. Guys, there's like 5,000 NPCs in those games. I've never played
Pokemon. Is that the guy that assesses the Pokemon? I don't know who Professor Oak is.
I have not consumed even maybe 30 minutes total of Pokemon. And you know, it was probably watching
the intro of the Pokemon. Gotta catch him. You and me. We'll do it our destiny.
Like 15 years ago when that meme was out. I don't know. I think I've never seen it. I don't care.
I thought something was wrong. I was like, oh, I don't know who that is. Like Professor Oak,
I don't play Pokemon. And I look over at chat and it's like, it's as if I like shit like diarrhea
in my pants and you heard it. And it was like, what the fuck was that? I heard like diarrhea
sounds. Like, is he all right? What's happening? Is he sitting in his own shit? What happened?
I don't know who Professor Oak is. Wait, hold on. Let me, I gotta ask. Is Professor Oak the character
that has the lab coat on and he has like the spiky white hair and he works in the Pokemon center?
Yes. All right. Okay. I know who that guy is. I didn't know what his name was.
And on top of that, I don't know what he sounds like. I just, I've seen like a picture of him.
Good morning, workers. Ready for another day of toiling the profit of your company?
The Pikmin seem to still be asleep inside their onion. What lazy creatures. No wonder they lack
survival skills. Stand beneath the onion and press A to call them. I'm not going to stop doing that.
I'm sorry. Let's call them up. Everybody. How many do we want? Take out or return Pikmin? Wait,
I have a finite amount? Not yet. Let's assess the area. How much time do I have? Oh shit. Get that.
I'm going to take 10. 10. Come on out. Five of you get that. The five, the other five must
have gone the other way. Oh my God. Wait, just the five. How many are in there? One, two, three,
four, five. You, how many do I have? Five? Shit. I should have taken 11. Take all of them. If they
die, they're gone permanently though. No fear. Take them. Okay. Fine. I'm going to get that one.
How many need to be on here? 35? Do I even have that many? Hurry up. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh shit. There's something right here too. Get that. Any up here? Oh my God. There's so much
to explore. There's nothing up here. All right. Pull them out. I need 35. Pick them up. Pull them
up. So many activities. There really are. Okay. I have to, I got to, I'm going to make you guys
happy. Or some of you angry. I never gave this game a chance because I didn't know it was like
this. I thought it was like level one. Go. Level two. Go. I didn't think it was sort of this open
sort of, you just go collect treasure and coins and stuff. I was unaware of that. Nice. We got it.
All right. This is definitely going to be like an old toy. Kill. Kill. And then eat his body.
Somebody die? All right. Get out. Go. Let's go. Oh my God. I love this game. All right. Let's keep
going. Wait a minute. There's a big guy. Don't wake him up yet. Hold on. What's over here? Is
that a crush can? 35. Okay. Can we get this without waking him up? All right. Nobody get that.
You know what? Hold on. Wait. Wait. Separate. Louie, you stay here in case shit hits the fan.
This is on GameCube. This is on the, technically the Wii U. Oh, fuck. This is the Wii version on
the Wii U. It's pretty good. When are you going to play Smash Brothers? No, I got completely turned
off forever from playing Smash Brothers ever, ever again. I already told you what happened.
I did that. That single player mode was cool for a little while. There's almost too much content
in there though. It was like 60 hours of content in there and it was kind of overwhelming.
That was cool though. But I played online two or three matches with italics. We just like,
yeah, let's get, dude, I'm going to start. I'm going to get good with Simon Belmond. You just
watch me. I'm going to start. I'm going to get good with him. We played two or three online matches
together, just hanging out. We got beat so badly three or four times in a row. This is a true
statement. Neither one of us has ever played the game again. I have not turned it on since that
happened to us. We just were looking at each other just after like four or five matches of getting,
let's just say we all had two stock. We couldn't even get anybody on the other team past like
a hundred percent on their first stock. It was awful. So we never played ever again. It's not
going to wake them up, is it? Basically, get on there. Kill the big guy first. I don't want
to lose any Pikmin. Are we doing this? Oh, Olimars are over. Can I fight with Olimar?
Oh shit, you can punch. All right, I guess we're going to go for it. You ready? Attack! Holy shit,
we got it. Anybody die? We got him. Oh, nobody else can do it. Okay. Wait, some of you guys get
the can. Oh, this is perfect tactic. Push it over. Just keep pushing it. I need everybody for this
one. How many Pikmin am I going to get for this? Don't ever attack the face. Oh, okay. Oh, that's
what his voice sounds like. What was I doing? I was like, oh, Gordon. All right, so let me get that
right. What are you doing back here? You too. Stop that. Do not.
Oh, I see it every time. And it's just every low voice is just Mr. Satan. I know and I'm sorry.
All right, help. Get over there. Get on it. Oh, fuck. I'm sorry. Is it everybody on it that
it can be on it? I guess so. What does red mean then? So red is capacity too, right? Number plus
10 is usually the max. Okay. Red means stop it. Good 450 bucks. All right. So there's still a
whole day here. Where should I go? This way? Where have I gone? Oh my God. Okay. Um, is there
anything back here? I could go. Should I go this way? Let's go over here. Break that wall. What wall?
Break the wall. Hold on. I have anything over here. This is wrong way. Um, I just want to see
anything over here. Oh, on Wiimote. Hey, motion controls. Fuck you. All right. Go for it. Relax.
Use a GameCube controller instead. I feel like I'll get used to this. I'm already starting to.
It was a wall. Let me see. Hold on. These guys are kind of slow. Where was this wall?
Wall. Do I have enough time to do this? Come on. Hurry up. Oh shit. There's a wall here.
Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike. Go, go, go. Get on there.
Take it. Break it down. No, no, no. Wrong button. No, wrong button. It's what is it down? What
button is it? Okay. That's I don't like that. I'll tell you a reason why. Okay. So the Wiimote,
the Wiimote's controller is not for buttons. It's just, if you press down on the Wiimote,
sometimes you'll press left or right on the D-pad. I'm not a fan of that. Get it. Can we help?
Apparently not.
Are they imagining that somebody else walked in the room that likes Louie and is like,
oh, what does Louie do? Why are they doing this again?
It's just recapping. Oh, okay. Wait, don't put them into the geyser. What is this?
It's for old people and children. Right. Interesting.
What's in there?
Well, I'm sorry. We're going to have to do the pebble test here. We're going to do the rock test
first, Mr. Tin Can, whatever your name is. You grab a rock and you let it go in there
and you just put your ear over it and you wait until you hear the noise.
Oh, yeah. Just go ahead and jump on in. Why would I do that? You let the rock go and you put your
ear over it. So you stand over there and go, drop. We ain't going in that one. I'm sorry.
I guess we're going in. Wait, I don't have enough time. Do I have time to do this?
All right, Louie, I need you to come over here. You take some and I'll take some. How many should
I? I need 50. Stop, stop, stop. Time stops in caves. Oh, how many do I want? I'll go in there with
50. Take them all. I thought I could only take 50. Wait, what? Oh, okay. I have 59. Okay. Okay.
I don't know why my brain. I don't know. My brain's insane. Game has been saved.
Fuck. Did you notice how half-assed that was? I started to think about doing it and then I kind
of gave up halfway through and I pulled back really hard. Yeah, I gave up halfway through that one.
I wasn't sure about that one. Intriguing. My heart sensors indicate that this hole has life in it.
It's warmer than on the surface. Analyzing suggests danger lies ahead, but the promise
of treasure is tantalizing. If you wish to check underground terrain, press the plus sign to
communicate with me. I am not just a ship. I am an all-purpose support pod. You have any guns?
Ooh. All right, split up. I want to take like 25. Olimar, you take this group. Louie,
you take this group. Here we go. We're going Louie first. Get everybody in the right spot.
Oh shit. I just zoomed out into the fog of war that I could see and I see that Red
is desperately trying to group up his enemies 30 feet away from my base and he doesn't think I can
fucking see him do that. What's that? Take it. Whatever it is. All right. Why am I splitting up?
Why do we need to split up? Everybody come with me. Are we going to fight? Are we fighting? Are
they hostile? Get them. Get them. 550. Nice. Seven up. I love seven up. It's way better than sprite.
Fight. Fight. Oh my God. This fucking Wii mode is going to drive me insane.
I'm telling you pressing down on the Wii mode. It was the worst idea ever.
Kill it. All right. How much does it take to get this fruit thing?
Take it out. Just throw them. Throw them. It squishes the enemies. Oh.
How can you possibly consider this beast a treasure? Beasts are incompatible with my
circuitry. I suppose I will store your finds in my hold. But I do think, I do not think beasts will
be worth much. Well, what can I turn them into Pikmin? I thought that was the point. All right.
We're good. What about this thing? We go in this? This hole appears to be quite deep. My sensors
indicate more treacherous terrain. Oh shit. Louis, do you recall that you can adjust the camera with
Z and up left and right on that? Yes. Your expression suggested you are. You do. Yes, I do.
Don't worry. All your Pikmin will follow you. Approach the hole and press A to enter it.
I don't know. I only have like five. Can't do this today. I need to put this orange in.
Wait, you want me to go down there and just have everybody get killed? That doesn't sound like a
fun time. Oh wait, maybe I should. How much is an orange worth? 180. Citrus lump. What did I call
it? Fruit thing? Oh, wait a minute. We still have, I only, one person died. That's it. I'm going for
it. Time is stopped here, right? What's going? Four died. They did? Send a letter. This goes even
deeper. Oh, I had 59. Final floor. Oh shit. Okay. This is the, this is important. This is very
important. Get the camera in the right place. All right. Everybody come with me. Kill it.
But all right. Yeah. Now pick it up. Deliver that. Oh, a globe. It's inconceivable that such an
immense object has been buried here for so long. The design on the outer shell resembles the surface
of the planet as seen from space. Perhaps this can be used for something other than salvage.
Is it a map? How will we ever lift it? I fear that even a hundred red Pikmin will be unable to lift
it. What? What? What do you mean? We can't get it? No, we have to be able to get that. Come on.
Okay. Well, it's like, it's like a Metroid game. I'm going to come back here with the forklift and
lift it up. Oh fuck. Kill him. How am I not landing on him? You know what to do. Get it. Good job,
guys. Kill. Good. You know what to do. We'll bring the bodies back. Kind of running out of Pikmin
though. Okay. Get that one too. How many do I have? 23? What is this? This must be, I think this is a
new Pikmin. Yep. It's going to be a blue Pikmin. Astounding. A flower blooms in a cave deep beneath
the snowy landscape. Clearly it is warmer down here than above. Look, the Pikmin are restless.
Purple. Oh. It looks as if they are, they yearn to be tossed into the flower.
And it makes a purple. And the purples are strong, right? The purples are really powerful. I remember
that. They didn't fly very far, but they did a ton of damage when they hit somebody in Smash Brothers.
What should I get? Like 10? I don't want to get rid of all my Pikmin. All of them? What do you mean
all? What? Do all? What? Why would I want to do that? Amazing. A purple Pikmin. It has hair,
and it is quite stocky. It seems very heavy and strong. Each flower can only make five. Oh, okay.
Pull the bar. This Pikmin is an entirely new type of Pikmin. Transforming Pikmin by tossing
them into flowers. Intriguing. Perhaps there are others. All right. So we're going to get 10 big
guys. It's a fat Pikmin. Yeah. And they're worth like five red Pikmin, right? How do I do five at
a time? Throw it faster? Now we can get the globe. Yeah. I think that's it, right? All right. I think
that's it. Is there a way to? Oh, this is going to be hard. Globe. Let's get it. Go up the geyser.
Pepe left. Okay. They're so slow. Come on. Get over there. Get it. Get it there. 100. 100.
What's it going to be worth? All right. I'm going to show this link.
Links. I'm going to tell you. Let's go over this really quickly.
Links are going to be completely removed from chat. Permanently. In the very near future.
And it's going to be replaced. Links are going to go somewhere else that I can pull from that
is not in the chat. So they're not being removed from the stream. They're being removed from chat.
It will be a nice solution where you can post a link somewhere and it can be looked at and then
I can get a hold of it. It's just not going to be in chat anymore. Oh, keep that in mind. That's it.
200 bucks. Let me just show this on stream real quick because I found it to be a little humorous.
This game is humorous. Don't use Discord. I'm not going to use Discord. It's going to be its own
potential custom solution. We'll find out. I'm going to do a little research.
This is device resembling a microchip embedded inside the sphere retrieving the data.
I could only decode a portion of the data but I did retrieve new geographic charts. Oh, new location.
Ooh. Put them in somebody else's chat. Oh my god. Can you imagine how dog shit that would be?
That would be the most unbelievably awful way to do that. Put it in somebody else's chat.
I just make a new account. It's Twitch.tv. I'm not going to say it because I'm too late.
I don't care. It's just a chat full of links. That is not the solution, by the way. But how
fucked up would that be? That's so stupid. Okay. Exploration kit. Oh, that's so awful.
Now that we have this new data, you should explore the decoded territory tomorrow.
That's total keel. K-E-W-L. Keel. Is everybody here? We didn't leave anybody behind, right?
I think we're good. Let's go. Oh, that's not a portal.
I can't wait to see the guitar version of that song. How did you lie about Mr. Slime? I didn't
lie about Mr. Slime. It was just a lot of things I had to do. Didn't we already go over this?
Thinking of something fun to do or an idea that might be fun to do is not
me telling you that it's going to happen in three days. You know what would be awesome?
I wish Cheetos would make a hot version, but have it be a Chipotle hot version.
That's a good idea. And a year later, they don't make that. You can't be mad at me for
coming up with an idea. Why don't those Cheetos exist, Jeremy? You thought about that. That
would have been delicious. I fucking hate you. I guess I would be the CEO of the Cheetos company,
right? In that case. But even still, if the CEO of the Cheetos company is like,
hey, you know what would be really delicious? If we had a Cool Ranch Cheeto, that's a good
idea. You should do it. Now, maybe. I don't know. We got other things from the pipeline.
Fuck you. But wait, try our new flavor. We got like five flavors coming out in the next couple of
months. Try one of those. Not as good. When are you going to put cat ears on, CEO? Let's go. Back to
the service. Cry, cry. One voice Andy. Hey, you know what? I'll be five voice Andy, okay?
I'm going to tell you right now. I'm going to stand up for myself a little bit here. I might be
five voice Andy, but would you rather me be like 30 voice Andy and 25 voices are terrible? Or would
you rather have completely calculated, clean, cool, five perfect voices that can be used in
a million scenarios? You want like 30 or 40 crappy voices that you're like, oh, that wasn't
that good. Or would you rather have completely refined five to six complete voice work?
Your five voices suck. I want you to record yourself doing this and I want you to send it
to me tomorrow. I want you to record yourself doing that and send it to me tomorrow.
Like, don't ask for that, the challenge. That's not a challenge. I just was talking to one person.
Challenge accepted. No, I didn't. Don't do that, by the way. That takes years of training. That's
hard to do and it can hurt you. That low, gravelly, deep into the chest voice, that took me 30 fucking
years to get that right. Be careful. I'm not issuing any challenges here. No challenges.
It's difficult to do that work. I've missed all this dialogue. Fuck. 30 years.
Olimar and Louis, since you will explore a new area tomorrow, today's work is done.
Do that. Also not a challenge, by the way. No, when I said you, I was referring to like the collective
and when I meant do that, I meant like do it as in like existentially, like nobody can do that.
I can do that, right? That's what I meant by that. Like you as in collectively you and do that as in
like I bet you couldn't. Like because I'm like collectively speaking like in existential terms.
There's a backtrack? No. Okay. When I say you guys, right, I'm not referring to like one single
person sitting in their room. Otherwise, I would say, hey, Dave Anderson, watching the stream right
now, I hope you had a really good birthday last week. And that's that I'm directly addressing one
of you. It's always Dave. Why can't it be somebody else? No, don't do anything. I'm kidding around.
It's a joke. What's so special about Dave? I don't know. The easiest name to remember.
You guys want a little bit of insight into my brain. It's very, very difficult for me to come
up with first and last real names. If I sit here and try to come up with a name, Mike, Dave, John,
Smith, Anderson, Stevenson. I don't, it's hard to come up with like a full name.
Jeremy, but that's my name. That's not me making up another name. That's me just using my name.
Just say Andy. Just say Andy. But here's the thing. We don't come up with names for people
anymore. We come up with the thing that they didn't and then add Andy to it. It used to be
you'd put that shit in quotes. Like it was like, Oh God, Jimmy, the schnoz.
Acapella or something, right? Now it's just schnoz Andy. We don't come up with like full names
anymore. We just give them the kind of a description and then add Andy to it. It's kind of ruined my
way to process people's names. Schnoz Andy. But you know what I mean though? Like Twitch, it started
to like get into my brain. Even in emotes and stuff. Like I don't even, I'm 35 guys. I'm older.
I'm an older gentleman and for no reason I'll randomly just think of, Oh, that was so cool.
I don't even talk like that though. I don't even talk like that. It's just in the head.
I have never said that out loud, but internally I say that. Not like Monka S. I internalize that.
If something's scary, I'm like, Oh shit, like Monka S. Like fuck. Language is sort of changing.
You can, emotes are becoming, you can like communicate with emotes now.
They used to do this stuff back in like the hieroglyphics days. Hieroglyphics are coming back.
We're having a midlife crisis? Yeah. Yes, absolutely. This is absolutely what that is.
So yeah. Oh, I want to look at these. The purple pitman were somehow able to carry this. Now I'm
to get into my head because I have five voice Andy. No, excuse me. Sorry. I'm going to rephrase
that. Jeremy, goofy voice, Albertson. There. I'm not doing, I'm not doing that anymore.
The purple pitman were somehow able to carry this massive treasure. Today we measured their
physical strength using a ship's onboard beef abator. It seems that we have 10 times the weight
and physical power of any pitman. When I throw them, they land with a resounding
foot. I've decided to commemorate the cave first encountered them by naming it an emergency cave.
Mr. Potter. I can't even read this shit. We're going to go back. Kylo Ren auto. Oh, give me a break.
Awakening woods. Let's go. What the fuck is this game? Wait, hold on. Are you whoing
Pikmin? That's not possible. Is it? When did the last Pikmin come out? Pikmin three, Pikmin four.
Morning. How are you? It should be pleased you to know that the purple Pikmin are lodged safely in
my home. Confines of my interior seem to suit them perfectly. Well, they do occasionally tickle me.
That wasn't Bernie. That was supposed to be Arnold Schwarzenegger.
I think I've got to focus. I have to focus. Good morning. How are you? Fuck. That is Bernie.
Good morning. How are you? How are you? How are you? Good morning. Good morning. Fuck. It is. No,
but it's not though. It's kind of not. Stand in the ring of light below and press A to call the
purple Pikmin out. Okay, let's get the purples. I want 30 red Pikmin and then Louis, I want you to
get purple Pikmin. I want five pur- all? I don't want to take all. All? What? What if they die?
Jeremy Elbertson Andy. Louis has Olimar instructed you on the particularities of the Pikmin
creatures. The Pikmin form groups based on color when disbanded with C. Grabbing Pikmin with A
will also cause them to group by color. Now for the bonus lesson. First, press and hold A to pick
up a Pikmin. Then, while you hold A, press B to swap between different colored Pikmin.
This is the first time you have heard this, Olimar. Remember to properly train new employees.
All right, that's cool. Yeah, you guys are gonna be at work. There's gonna be a new employee
at your job and the name's gonna be like Greg Michaels and that you're never gonna call them
Greg Michaels. You're always gonna call them new employee Andy. Language is changing. All right,
let's throw some- let's get these and then let's crush these guys with some big ones.
Oh, what's that? Whatever it is. Kill it. Kill it! Just kill everything and pick it up.
Nice. Okay, I'm gonna get that. Oh, there's a big one over here. We'll get- we'll group up
after this. Go. Very cool. Cool. All right, there's more. What's the actual cap? Is it 100? It's 200.
Holy shit. We could handle that? No, no, no, no. 100 in a party. Okay. All right, let's do it.
Um, wait. Somebody get that. Anything else? Zoom up. Oh, nice. Get these too. I love this game.
It's really fun. Fight! Ah, get them. Yes. Cool. All right, now get these too. Somebody pick up
those. All right, and then the rest of you. Anything up here? Wait, let's kill the big guy
first. There's a strawberry up there. Hell yeah. All right, we're all gonna- we're just gonna rush
into his back. Let's rush into his back. All of you at the same time, all run into his back.
Get him! We died. All right, bring it. Good job, everybody.
Grow for crits. Oh, okay. Grow purples at the back. Okay. Thanks for the tip. You're wasting time.
I am? Wait, what's over here? What is, like, hiccuped? What is over here? What's this? Honey?
Oh, they've ranked up.
Didn't you note that no more than 100 Pikmin will venture into the planet at once?
But I currently observe only 95 on the surface. Could there be wild Pikmin somewhere?
Oh my god. Everybody settle down. Settle down. I promise we'll get ice cream after the field trip
is over. Pick them all up. I want ice cream now. Well, you can't have it now. Sorry. All right,
let's keep going. I have so many Pikmin. All right, where do we go? Get the strawberry.
All right, one big guy. Get strawberry. That should be enough, right? How many do I need?
Then another one. No, no. Stupid. Wait. Oh, okay. I guess I have to switch it every time.
I'm just gonna fit on there. More. We want more speed. Go. Get it over there. All right,
the rest of you follow me. I can't go up here. Where can we go? This way.
Oh, what's this? This fight? What's going on here? Oh, they're picking the fruit. All right.
I'm splitting you guys up. Go this way. 1,100 bucks. Name Sunsea Berry. They are yellow.
Okay. 10% of debt recovered. Oh, nice. Just like me. I believe I've also recovered 10% of my debt.
All right. Oh, they got little berries. Oh, berries. Jerry, they got berries.
Somebody pick one up. Pick up the berries. What kind of berry is this? This red berry contains
an ultra spicy essence. It does not appear to have any monetary value, but I should research
it for use. Cool. Bring me another one. Okay. Well, I'll bring you like 10 more. I got like 10 on the
way. I forgot about that word. We can keep getting them. Oh, they just kind of respawn. All
right. I don't know what that does, but whatever. 85. Where's the other guys? Missing people? All
right. Into the gate. You're wasting time. I'm just... Look, this is not going to be an efficient
playthrough. Captain Olimar, my research on the red berries that you discovered has yielded a
powerful potion. Behold the ultra spicy spray. Although it is untested, I believe it will have
spectacular results. Spray it on all of your Pikmin by pressing two. When necessary, I can
produce one bottle of spray from 10 berries. Press that button to contact me and confirm your berry
count by pressing left. Should I just do that now? Okay. What is that thing? Get him. Get him.
Weigh him down. He dropped an egg. All right. I want big guys. Everyone over here,
drink that. Drink up that stuff. Can I make a different... I want the purple guy to drink.
I guess you can't really do that, can you? I could split him up. Oh, well, I did it.
Now they got it. They got it. All right. Should I get more berries? Separate button. All right.
Shit. Okay. Right. I'm going to get some more berries. Four. Three guys on berry duty.
I need 10, right? I hate that so much. I'm now... I'm seriously just pressing down on the D-pad.
This fucking cheap Wiimote controller. They just... They couldn't make it four buttons.
They had to make it one giant button. How dare they? How much did this console fucking sell?
Like 50 million copies? Fucking failure. 100 million consoles sold or something like that?
Absolute failure. Come back here. That should be enough, right? Give me one more group. How
many Wii consoles actually have been sold? It was like 50 or 60... 100 million something,
right? What was it? No, not 50, 60, 100 million. That would be... There's not that many people on
earth. 101 million. Oh my God. All right. The rest of you just go over here. 101 million?
There are way more people on earth. Whatever. I'm going to split these guys up. All right. You go...
You stay over here. You go get the guys that delivered the berries. Bring it back. There are
more Wiis than people. You know... I wouldn't be surprised if there were more iPhones than
people that exist right now. And I'm talking all the way through every generation. I wouldn't be
surprised if in the next few years it was that. Come on, get in there. Find a spot.
Something's going down. Hurry up. There's an insane amount of e-waste in the world, unfortunately.
Oh yeah. Whatever that is. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Run away. Run. Run. Oh my God.
Don't eat him. He ate him. All right. I don't know how to fight that guy. No. I'm trying to hit B.
I'm trying to hold B. You have to hold somebody and then hold B. B calls people back.
Nintendo. Nintendo. That was a mistake. B calls people back. I have to hold A and press B to
switch Pikmin. Nintendo. This was a mistake. What's left? Holy shit. Kill it. Kill it.
Kill it. Oh my God. We're good. We're good. We're good. This is a dangerous world.
It's not an electric thing. I can't. I don't want to go there.
All right. It's almost sundown. How much time do I have? The sun will be setting soon. Call all the
Pikmin to you. This planet's native nocturnal life forms are ferocious and therefore dangerous.
Load your Pikmin into the onion and yourself into my hole so we can take refuge in low orbit.
Pikmin in your squad will enter the onion on their own at a day's end, so call them all to you.
Oh shit. We gotta go. What the fuck? There's like a gold coin up there. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Everybody in. Quick. Get it in. Get it in. Get
it in. Get it in. Get it in. Get it in. Get it in. Get it in. Get it in. Get it in. We're missing
somebody. We're missing somebody. Who are we missing? Doesn't matter. No, it's over. Yeah, go.
Take out over. No. What? How do I leave? How do I get out of here?
First field trip. Check the map. What do you mean go back? I have five seconds.
You have time. As long as they're in my squad, it doesn't matter, right?
Shit, they're up there. Yes, that doesn't matter as long as they're in the squad.
Okay. I don't think I have time to do this. Straight ahead. Come on. Where are you? Where are
you? I found him. We did it. We're so concerned about Pikmin. Louie's just like picking his nose
200 yards away. The alligator just monster comes up from under the ground with mouth open and
closes it around him, crushing him. I got a bunch of stuff. I got a bunch of fruits.
Best gamer moment. No, that was a general gamer moment. Who died? No. Eight have died in battle
so far. Best gamer moment. How's progress, Olimar? Remember, you'll never get anything done if you
sit back and watch from afar. Press left or right on the D-pad for a close-up view of the action.
Move my body over here. Okay. All right. So, above ground, there's still things to do on this one.
Maybe I'll go back to that one. This is a new thing. Let me see. Honey wisp.
It's floating left from just effortlessly on the winds. Upon death, its physical structure
instantly collapses. If we could simply recover a live sample researched on the spaceship,
I would have to take it alive? How do we do that? It's a scary piranha plant thing.
It has eyes in it. Just be careful. Watch out for eyes. Flowers that have eyeballs in them.
Be careful. Press A. Wait, what? What the hell is going on here? Why am I throwing carrots?
I just gave them food for like four years. I don't know. What am I supposed to do?
Okay. I don't think that does anything. Wait, I can feed carrots to this thing.
Oh, it's eating the carrots. Whoa. It didn't like that. It doesn't like carrots?
This thing is terrifying. This is like Pan's Labyrinth. I don't like this guy. What about
these guys? Do you guys like carrots? Okay. What about you? You guys like carrots?
That's cool. It's like a little petting zoo. All right. Let's keep going. Do I want to go?
I want to go back here. There's still stuff I didn't do here. What was it? Let's find out.
No. What? I'll go back. Okay. All right. This time I'm going to go. I saw there was a gold coin
over here that I want. Give me a gold coin. I want 90, 80, and then as many of the purples
as I can get. Actually make it 95, right? Yeah. All right. Let's do it. Don't waste any daylight.
Forget about that stuff. I don't need it right now. I want to go over here because there's a
gold coin over here. There's also this bridge. Can they go in the water?
They die if they go in water. Let's test it. Yes, they do. Okay. Come on. You're good. Okay.
I can throw them over there though. Golden butterflies. Get one. Get one of those.
Bring them back. Bring them back to the base. Nice. All right. Come back. Come back. Come back.
Back. Back. Come back. Come back. Come back. All right. There's a bunch of nectar over here.
All right. They're good. How many died? Wait. No. You didn't collect them?
All right. I'm good. I've got 93. Who cares? They die if they go in water. All right. Well,
let's go this way. Where can I even go? Down this way? I'm going to go this way.
Over here. Whoa. There's something munching on those. Get it. Whatever it is. Climb up there
and get them. Get them. Get those little caterpillar guys. Get them. Get up there.
Good. Good. Good. Good. Drop them. Drop them on the ground. Nice. All right. Bring it back to the
base. Excuse me. Bring it back. Is it still alive? What's fighting him? Is that a bad thing?
There it is. Okay. 200. I don't think I have enough. 180? No, I don't. Press two. I wonder
how... Where do they walk this? No, I can't. Two? Press two. Two. Two. What does two do?
Cave to the left. Yeah. Let's go this way. It adds weight. Hold on. I'm going to go this way first.
Another globe. Why does it look poisonous? Come back. Come back. Come back. Come back.
Is it poisonous? Emergency. Pikmin are suffering. If you blow your whistle with B,
you may be able to help them. Okay. So I can't touch that. Your Pikmin are suffering, Jeremy.
There's a cave over here. Yes.
Biological sensors are reacting violently. The readings are ominous.
Beast of unknown power lurks in these depths. A large Pikmin group would be reassuring.
My sound sensors are picking up hostile roars of many beasts.
Expect dangerous encounters. Extreme heat pockets. You may need flame-resistant Pikmin.
But my records indicate no such data. Are my records incomplete?
I have to assume reds are fire-resistant. Should I leave the purples? I feel like I don't want
to bring purples down here. All right. Louis. Louis, you stay here with the purples. Take them
all? I'm scared to bring everybody. Always take them all? Jeremy, you're wicked funny. Thanks,
dude. This is how we're going to do this. I saw a good chat message. Louis is going to be in charge
of purple and Olimar is going to be in charge of red. So where are we going first? We've got
a few directions to go. How about this way? Get over here, Louis. Use the purples to fight.
Get them. Yeah, they do like a big ground stomp. All right. Pull these guys back.
Louis, good job, Louis. Wait, we got a... Oh, what's this? What's this artifact? What's this
over here? Oh, it's a single button D-pad? Oh, wow. Yeah. They used to use these fucking shitty
things. Back like 5,000 years ago. Yeah, definitely collect that. This dark soul is that
fucking guy. Yeah, they used to put all four buttons on this rotating weird axis thing.
Yeah, it was really, really interesting. I'm saying, yeah, we don't do that anymore.
Didn't they used to think that you had four humors in your body?
Yeah, I think that was the same time period. All right, let's get going.
Fire this way. One of you take that for research. One of you take that for research. Did you not
listen to me? Over here, Louis. I love the purples. It's so unique. It's so cool. They
have that unique ability. Anything down here? There's nothing over here, huh? All right, hurry
up. In the meantime, while they do that, you... That's the... Go to the next level. Did I miss
something? I feel like I missed a thing to grab. I just want to check. No, there's nothing in here.
Wait. Yeah, I got it all. Okay, I had to. All right, everybody follow me. Good. Nobody died.
We didn't lose anybody. We got an artifact. Let's go. The noise means you got all the treasures.
Okay, cool. That's good to know. What noise? Just so I can be aware of it. The power down noise? Okay.
The whole of beasts. When the Pikmin are singing, it means you have everything. Oh, okay.
What's that? Let's float it up. An egg? Pick it up. Don't break it. Pick it up. Why did you break it?
Oh! All right, we need the cleanup crew to... Everyone pick up. Pick one up. Oh, wow.
Look at all this nectar. Everyone's full. I have all flower Pikmin, I think. Well,
hold on. Let me just double check. Holy shit, I got a whole crew of full flowers.
Nice. All right. That was over there. Let's go. Is this another egg? Okay, I was expecting spiders.
Nothing on that side. Is it behind us? All right. Let's go deeper. Oh, purple. Purple, purple,
purple, purple. Let's do it. Now we can go drink the nectar. Sick. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Those
of you that didn't drink, come over here and drink. Slurp it up. All right. One of you didn't get it.
I think there was one more over here. There is. Sing the nectar song. You guys keep... Every time
we raid somebody now, you guys demand a song from them. Let me just give you some streamer
insight on this. If I got raided and I was in the middle of doing something... Let's say I was in
the middle of an important match or something, or something really, really I had to pay attention to,
and I look over at the chat and it's like, sing the fucking raid song. And I'm just like,
what are you talking about? Raid song? Too bad, Omega Low. Sing it. And then they have no idea
what you're talking about. You know, I'm surprised a bunch of you guys don't get banned immediately
when we raid. Sing the raid song. Fucking no. Ban all these people. It may have. I don't stick
around for all the raids. That may have already happened. Fire. Here we go. Let's take the fire
guys through. No, you idiot. Okay. I can just walk through this. Wait, they put it out? Oh,
they put it out. Oh, this is Floppy disk. Oh, by the way, somebody linked me. I saw on Twitter,
somebody, I was in the discord talking about attack on Titan. And I said like this show sucks
and stuff. All right. Let me, I gotta be very clear about this. Listen to me. I have, I have seen,
I am like a big fan of that show. People were pissed that I didn't, I wrote, what did I write
exactly? I said, oh yeah, I'm 10 episodes into attack on Titan. Oh, I don't get it. Like this
show sucks. Why are they Titans? Like stupid as fucking show or something, right? A little
bit of people know that I've seen every fucking season. I've seen, I'm like a big fan of the show.
I just was bait. Yeah. And people thought I was really stupid. They're just like, wait,
he's seen 10 episodes? No, of course he doesn't like it. He's fucking, his brain is too small.
Anime fans, do you bait? Yeah, it was. Give me this Floppy disk. It was also, some of you guys
miss out on some random in general chat stuff that I do. A few weeks ago, I was in the general chat.
It was like maybe three or four o'clock in the morning Pacific. And I wrote a bunch of stuff and
nobody responded. There was maybe like one person that was there. I just wrote a bunch of shit and
nobody responded. And I wrote like, what the fuck? No one's talking. Like, what the fuck is this
bullshit? And nobody said anything. I think like maybe two people did like minutes or hours later
or something. It was three a.m. I think I got everything, right? Are they singing? So that means
I did it. That right? I'm good, right? I have to be careful because I just write, I just say and
write random things that don't mean anything. And sometimes I feel like people might see that and
out of context might go like, wow, he's sick and fucking asshole. Oh, well, we've got a big
bunger over there. Wait, check back here. All right. We've got to, we've got to have, we're
going to split this up. Uh, Olimar, too many. No, no, no, no, too many. No. Yes. Louis, wake up.
Okay. Now I want Olimar. No, get out of here. I fucking hate this controller. This thing was
meant to be shook around, not pressed any of these buttons. Very nice. Very nice.
Oh, there's an egg. Uh, I'm not going to break that yet. Let's go kill the big guy.
All right. Let's get this set up. I'm doing my RTS setup. Jerma's not a gamer.
Maybe a little. Three, two, shitty. I got him instantly. Oh, it's a gaming watch. Cool.
Oh, there's more over there. What's in here? Oh, oh, it's a flower. Nice. All right. Get the,
I love aces. I love cards. I'm a huge card fan. Put a 10 on there. You know what I mean?
Drop a, drop a jack on top of that. You know what I'm saying? I'm sorry. All right. I need,
uh, we got to put some more of these guys in here. Yeah. More purples. The ace of spades
worth $140. Luck wafer. That's cute. It's very cute. David's spade. Go crack that egg.
So we can get some nectar. Who has not drank nectar? Which one of you?
Where's that egg over here? What's that sound? There's an egg. Where's the egg?
What? Okay. Well, they stole it. Oh, there it is. And all right. Get in there. Who hasn't drank,
drank it. One person hasn't. Oh, two actually. Nice. Drink it. Very good. We can keep going.
I demand heal. Oh, no, that, no. I misread what you said. This one's deep.
You know, actually, I could go for one right now. I'm not even kidding. I might go get one.
What is it? Final floor. All right. This is important. I think this is the first real test.
What is that thing? It's a giant cat. Can I take a picture of it and upload it and get data on it?
That's huge. Oh, boy. I feel like I'm going to do this in two parts here.
All right. It's time. How do we go about doing this? Spray everybody first. All right. So hit
two and then I'm going in. Great. Astounding. The heads of the Pikmin are glowing and they seem
extremely agitated. The ultra spicy spray appears to increase Pikmin speed and attack power. Oh,
man. Okay. Get that again over here. What? What? Why did? All right. Go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go. Is it temporary? Get in it. Kill it. Where's the other Pikmin? Oh, my God.
He's going to roll over everybody. Did he kill everyone? He killed every purple. Come back,
come back, come back, come back. Oh, my God. I didn't know he did that. He killed every purple.
Oh, no. No. Get on his head. Come back, come back, come back, pull back.
What the hell? I feel like shit now. Every purple is dead. How bizarre. This device is emitting
black light. It must have been ingested by that creature. What an absolutely repulsive life form.
Did I get soft locked? Reload. Can I? No, I can't. No reload. No. Oh, every single purple is dead.
Every single one. That's so sad. That's so sad. Why couldn't it have been the red ones?
I can get them back. Yeah, I know. But it's still sad. I'm glad I have enough to actually lift this.
200. Just reload the floor. No, I know. I have to live with consequences. I can't be a Dave state
every single game I play. This contraption seems to react when it approaches treasure.
I will connect it to my radar. Oh, like beeps. The treasure gauge is now fully operational.
20 purples died. That sucks. Please restart. No, come on. You need them. Restart.
No, I'm not restarting. I have to deal with the consequences. Is that it? We wasted three gas.
Yeah, but I can go get that gas back. That was a lot of money. That's over a thousand dollars.
38 people died. God, that's unfortunate. Farm more at the caves first. Do some farming. All right,
I'm getting a heal. Let's take a break. I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back. BRB.
It's actually kind of funny. Whenever a cat boy image comes up, I get to kind of watch
the PUBG blue thing start to be right behind some of you guys. All of a sudden it just gets like,
whoa, whoa, whoa. What's that? Run. The zone, yeah. Just wait till I actually put the costume on.
You just wait till I turn the camera on one day and I'm in like full cat boy.
Please don't. Here's the thing about, I think I've said this already, but I'll say it again.
That stream is going to be the most unfollowed and followed stream I've ever done on Twitch.
Let's just be clear about that. All right, let's get back. I got my heal. Oh, and it's delicious
and it's giving me tons of recharging fuel. What heal flavor? I mean, there's three flavors,
and I'll give you the rundown. There's a chocolate, there's a berry, and there's vanilla.
The chocolate one, I think tastes the best, but I think it's a little too thick. It's very
milkshaky. It tastes good, but I'm not a big fan of that. The vanilla tastes very good,
but I don't like the texture. It has a weird texture to it. It has a texture that I'm not
like a fan of, and I don't know why I can just tell. The berry though, it's smooth. It's got a
good flavor. It tastes kind of like a strawberry yogurt drink, and I would say that's my favorite
one. There's no soy in it. The person that just said that timed them out for a minute. This is a
non-soy product. Anyways, let's play Pikmin. All right, what are we doing? Oh yeah, a bunch of
purple Pikmin died. Hold on. Heal's in the way of this Wii sensor. There we go. All right, so let's
pull up these... So I need purples. I can't believe I have no purples. All right, where do I want to
go? The treasure meter is blinking. Let's go this way. I need water Pikmin. That's definitely what
that is. We can't go that way. Oh, berries. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's do some berry farming.
Berry farming it is. Guys, there's no fucking way that the dev is in the chat. No, no, that is
impossible. You're right. Who even made this game? I know it was Nintendo, but what studio? Of course.
Was it just like a... What first party or whatever Nintendo studio? This is a Miyamoto game. Is it
really? Wait, Miyamoto made this? What? Yes. Is there anything that he can't do? Is there anything
that that man couldn't do? Honestly, if you told me like, oh yeah, Miyamoto like flew overhead with
like a Superman cape on and he can shoot lasers out of his eyes, I'd be like, yeah, I'm sure he...
That would not surprise me. I'd be like, oh yeah, that makes sense. I want that. Sacrifice somebody.
I want to see what it costs. Never mind. There is a gate up here. There's an electricity gate.
I can't get that. I can't even get up there. I have to get rid of this thing. This is 200. Shit.
What can I even do here? This has got poison gas on it. What's the play? I have to go farm
purples in the cave. Do I have to do this like three or four times? You should have reset.
But I mean, I can't just... Look, we can't rely on everything to just restart a game save.
God damn it. I'm actually going to try heal because of you. Well, don't be angry about it.
Don't be upset about it. Don't be mad about it. You don't have to do anything.
But I didn't like... I'm not making you do that. It's the next level, right? I don't even want
these things. Let's go. Mega-lul, it's working. Fuck you. I'm doing it. Influencer Andy,
you're abusing your reach to malnourish children. I'm going to tell... I mean,
let me tell you something. That person that just said that, you must have not done any research
on the product at all. It's 400 calories, 20 grams of protein, no soy. I'll read it again. I
don't even care. No one's paying me to do this. I don't care. These things help me a lot. I swear
to God. That's a true story. Let me get this. All right, here we go. I'm just going to keep
doing this and reload. No, I'm going to give you the real, real honest to God reason why I got
these in the first place. And you can be your own judge. How's that? Those of you who know,
like a year ago, I was having a lot of pain. And I still kind of am, but I'm still working on it.
Anyways, I lost like 25 pounds. I was like 133 pounds like a year ago. I don't know if it's
combination of stress or annoyance or part of me. I don't know. I thought my diet was okay.
That was also part of the reason why we kind of talked about with the doctor. Like, hey,
am I losing weight? What the fuck's wrong with me? So I decided I looked at a few different
companies. I was like, uh, maybe I could like supplement this and like help with like,
maybe trying to maintain some weight or put a little bit of weight on whatever.
And I got these. And this is, for me, this is, I'm not replacing food. This is like,
I'm just adding some of this. You know what I'm saying? Wait, is that more? So I didn't get these
to like, oh, I'm only going to drink this like fucking product. And that's the only food I'll
eat. I would drink one like in the morning and maybe drink one at night. I am 152 pounds now.
I gained a lot of weight. I feel a little healthier. I got a little better. You know what
I'm saying? Now I do look, I'm not going to tell you that I'm going to attribute it all to
doing that to dry. You know what, guys? I drank Huel and weirdly enough, I was like 10 times
stronger. I became a fucking superhero. No, but it absolutely did help me in my particular case
of trying to put on some weight when I like was having trouble. So there you go.
There's the true story. And even though I'm still, I don't want to get any heavier than
like 152, 155 is kind of where I started to draw the line there, but I like them.
It's nice. And I don't drink them every day anymore. Maybe like during a stream. That's
a really good like stream snack too, because it's just right there. I can just sip on it.
It's really good. So I just kept it. I kept it going. Pump iron on. All right. Can I leave?
Can I get out of here? Give up an escape? Can I just leave and then come back in?
Or is this going to be bad? That was a Ted talk. There's another purple. Oh,
there is another purple flower. That's right. Where is it? Does it taste good? Yes. Otherwise,
I wouldn't drink it. I mean, I am very picky with what I eat. I'm serious. That's why I just told
you like that. The chocolate one is probably taste the best, but it's too thick for me to
drink it. It's a little too thick. It's the thickest of the three of them. The berry one
is probably the lightest. If you if that's what you want, you're like, you know what,
I don't care if it's a little thicker. I want the chocolate and you'll like it.
I think that's that's probably the one that tastes the best flower.
One more floor down. You buy it in stores and online. I actually don't know. I think it's mainly
online. I think that you might be able to get it in some stores. I don't really know.
Nobody said that. Why would I read that out loud if nobody said that?
Does it just appear in your fridge? I have everybody, right?
Yeah, you can order it online. You got to go to your Heal dealer. What is it a car?
The infinite Heal fridge and a Heal branded fridge. No, I can't. I'm not doing that.
Rank it. This should after I get another 10 or so, that should be good, right?
What is that flower? Where is it? I know it's in here. I don't have to wake him up.
Nobody make any noise. Oh, God. Fight him. Fight him. Fight him. Fight him. Fight him. Fight him.
We're good. All right. I think we got enough. That should be what? 10, 15.
You will flower. Actually, no, no, no, nobody did. Don't do this yet. I got to clear this out.
I don't know. Do you hear what I said? I said stop doing that. I'm trying to just,
I don't want to have them walk through this and get burned. OK, thank you. Remember,
you ever thought about how mirrors are some insane alien sci-fi technology and we just,
and yet we just have them and everyone acts like they're normal? What? You know,
it's funny you say that and not cellular data technology. It's the mirror. We're worried about
mirrors and not about like how a Wi-Fi signal travels. That's pretty ridiculous. The fact that
information can travel through the air, I think is way more alien technology. Like,
holy shit, bro, than a mirror. But mirrors, mirrors are really kind of weird, too, though.
But I guess the way you can describe a mirror, I mean, it's just it's just really shiny. It's
shiny to the point that you can see a reflection in the shininess. So it's not that really that
weird. It's just it's so it's too shiny. It's reflecting. It's very reflective. It reflects
too much. By the way, you want to know something that'll freak you out? This is something a lot
of people don't understand. And this is, I'm going to really turn a lot of you guys' world upside down
with this one. So when you look in a mirror, you're not actually looking at what you actually look
like. You ever put up a cell phone to your face and you go, why do I look so fucking weird?
It's because you are flipped. When you are looking into a mirror, you're flipped. And if you have
even a slightly asymmetrical face at all, if you don't look in a mirror, you think that you look
crazy. You guys ever do that? I'm not ugly. No, I don't want to fight this thing again.
I need to go back. How do I get out of here? That was, that was, it was, that was like watch
mojo type of like information. Mirrors, what's going on there? Did you know that your cell phone
reflects you sideways and flips you around? Insane. Ridiculous. Top 10 things that people
might not have known about objects in their house. Mirror. Mirrors reflect light sideways and flips
you around. Whatever. I don't care. And look, you want, okay, fine. Watch mojo has like 600
million subscribers. So somebody's fucking listening to that and somebody cares. So what I
said was information that was cool. And it was like, well, who'd have thought info run past him.
Oh, okay. It's you. Oh yeah. How about this one? Oh, you intellectuals. If you take a mirror,
a small one, and you hold it up on your chin. So the mirror is flat going forward from your chin.
If you put your chin down and hold it flat against your chin and look down and walk around your
house, you're walking on the fucking ceiling. It's so cool. Just be careful. You don't trip
over anything in real life. I think he's sick. Attack on Titans. All right. I got my Pikmin.
I had to get some more. That is really fun to do though. If you, by the way, all you guys make
it fun of me for saying, they'll put the mirror up to the tip of your chin and look down and lay
it flat and walk. I got that from Nickelodeon magazine in like 1993. So, and that shit was
awesome. So don't come after me. Wait, what's over here? What's over here? Something over here.
What is this? Is it flowers? There's a treasure over here. Where is it?
Get this guy. Kill him. All right. We got it. There's something still over here.
I'm so confused. What is over here? Is it? Oh, it's these. All right. I'm going to go back to the,
can I weigh that thing down yet or no? It was a beetle up there. It was a beetle. Beetle. I saw
it too. It's buried treasure. You need another Pikmin. Oh, all right. Let's just keep going.
What do I need to weigh that down? If I use the spray, will it make them weigh heavier? I don't
have it. I definitely don't have enough. I need more. I need more purples. What do I need? I need,
I need a lot more. Spray them? Is that going to do it? No, I need eight more. Fuck. I need a bunch
of purples. So there's nothing. I have to go back and get more purple. I left people behind.
I heard a hule fart. Why are they over here? Oh my God. There's so many over here. Why were they
stuck? Didn't deny. All right. Give me a bunch of people. Let's see if we can do it.
I can't. It's hard to play right now. You guys just fucking me up so much.
Don't fight it. Just go. Is this enough? Hurry up. Oh shit. Whatever. Knock it down. Hurry up.
Get on there. Shit. I got it. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good.
I'm okay. Everything's fine. I got everybody, right? All right. We're coming back here tomorrow.
And I'm going that way. All right. Good thing I got them.
Click this link. I was getting farts. I've had a hule and I've been farting. Foul,
sulfuric rotten eggs. It lingers. Well, I can't. This did not. This is not happening to me.
You guys understand. I can't. You guys, people eat apples and they get diarrhea and shit. You
know what I mean? That's so hard to tell. There are a bunch of people that eat pasta and then
they fart all day. What do you want me to say? That did not happen to me. People's bodies are so
different. What makes some person have an upset stomach? Somebody could have a thousand of.
My dearest dear, how are you? Your boss gave me this space email account and told me all about
your business trip. Just remember you have a family to think about. Oh, you guys. You guys.
I don't even know what to do with you. Okay. I'm going back there and I'm going to go in that thing.
Okay. Let's pull everybody up. Is German making less sense than normal?
No, I'm trying to respond to people. What? I'm getting linked an image of somebody talking
about how the lava sulfuric acid farts. How am I supposed to react to this?
This is a very abnormal thing to react to. All right, everyone go. All right. Here we are.
Let's get everyone out here. We're good. Come on. Let's go. Hurry up. Me. All right. Now we're
going to. Here we go. Let's get this started here. Okay. Eat him. I don't care. We're good.
Somebody died. Yeah. One red died. That's okay. There's the gas again. I can't. Oh, I can go down
here. Wait. I'm going to go. I'm going to follow them. I want everybody to come down. You know,
you go around like Twitch and you're like, what's this streamer's chat doing?
Having a conversation about stuff. Like, oh yeah, let's talk about what's happening in the game. Oh
yeah. Make sure you get two purples, 15 reds and the blues are coming up soon. I just want to let
you know. I take a look at that. Hey dude, like what's everybody up to lately? Everyone doing
something fun. What did you do last weekend? No, no here. Here I look over at the chat and I just
see in all capitals. He'll farts. He'll fart. Andy farting because of fuel. He's becoming. He's
farting. I can tell. Put your mic in your ass so we can tell if you're farting or not. I read.
That's a real one. I read. Put a mic onto your like asshole so we can be sure you're not farting.
That's what I have to read over here. That's what I have to read. Mythbusters. Mythbusters. What was
that? Astounding. My metal detectors are reacting violently. What could be down below? No. If you
find trouble below, press that. Yes. Yes. Yes. What's down here? This is gas and fire. No,
I said my piece. It really helped me a lot. All jokes aside, it did a lot of good for me.
It really did. That's the honest to God truth. Oh, this is cool looking. Watch out. All right,
now pick it up and bring it back to the ship. Consume its blood. How many calories are in one?
400. 400 calories and you don't. What was that? That's. Oh, somebody brought up. Somebody said
talking about sugar. It's five grams of sugar in the bottle or in one serving if you get like a
powder. Only five grams of sugar. Some of you guys are drinking like a fucking Mountain Dew
right now and it's like 40. So just to let you know, Mountain Dew is 60. What? No, it's not.
What? Mountain Dew is 63 grams of sugar in a bottle in just a like a 16 ounce bottle. No,
it's not. I thought it was like 39 or like 43 or something. It's 63 grams of sugar. That's
unfucking believable. A Coke is what? 38, 37. What? Why is it that much? Okay. Is it my opinion
that once you cross a certain threshold of sugar in a drink, you can't even tell it's in there
anymore after like 30 to 40 grams of sugar. Can you even tell that it's 60 instead of 40?
I can't. It's 46. I have an experiment for all you to do. If you drink coffee and you put,
you know, milk or cream and sugar in your coffee or something, if you get just a regular from,
I'm going to use Dunkin' Donuts as an example, right? Or even Starbucks, whatever. Doesn't
matter. Just getting a normal just with cream and sugar at any of this one of these random
places that don't that just a big coffee shop. Start doing half sugar. You're like, oh, yeah,
I'll take a regular iced coffee. But can you do a half distribute put it? I bet you you won't even
tell the difference from 50% to 100%. I started doing that and I couldn't tell. I actually could
not tell the difference. And what you're doing is you are reducing the amount of sugar you're
taking in every day, which let's be honest, it's really not that great for you. It really isn't.
You know, you can't even tell it's based and healthy. They're ignoring you and putting in
regular sugar. They're not. It's just, they just didn't even change it. Yeah. Okay. Half sugar.
Okay. Nope. Not doing that. That's no, that's not true. I've seen people make the coffee.
Holy shit, that's fire. And instead of going like one, two, three, four, five,
with like a sugar, it's one, two, done. I've seen them do it. Well, they have the pumps,
right? That's a lot of places have pumps and they take your coffee over and they go.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop too much. Way too much. You can specifically ask for like
one pump or like two pumps. Start doing that. I'm serious. I want fire only. Get in there.
You can't hurt them. They're fire. A generous 12 pumps. And I have another thing to tell you.
Oh, he's got more to tell us. Oh, okay. Everybody watch out. That's a diamond over there.
If you are asking for extra cream and extra sugar in your coffee,
you're, you're eating a cake. Just, just go eat a cake. Go order a cake at like a bakery and eat
the cake. You cut back, cut back on that. That's a lot. Extra cream, extra sugar is just a cookie.
And you're just drinking a cookie. Not worse than that. I wonder what like extra cream,
extra sugar at like a Starbucks or a Dunkin' Donuts. I wonder what that actually is.
What is it? Well, how much is, what does, what is the actual, um,
like milliliters of cream and sugar and stuff? And then how much like cream and sugar goes into
baking a whole cake? I'm interested to know. Can they get this? I can't get that. Can't get it?
Is he dead? Can they get it? Sacrificing five, um, breads. Were they walking it? Oh,
they get, they got it. They got it. They got it. They got it. I love this cream. Have you ever
wanted a way to drink? That's not even real. Making that up. All right. No more. I got it.
Is there any more layers? Yes. There's a customer that, my friend works at Starbucks and somebody
comes in and gets seven shots of espresso and extra sugar. What? That's a lot. Is that person,
I feel like that's like the joke drink that the Incredible Hulk drinks in one of the last
movies or something. Eight shots of espresso with extra sugar. And it's tiny in his hand and you're
like, yeah, it was light. Ooh, different flower. Cool. I get seven shots of espresso.
One shot of espresso is one coffee, right? So therefore you're essentially drinking seven
coffees. That's a lot. No, it's less. Is it more? One shot of espresso is two. It's one to two.
Well, I'm talking about the caffeine count. One shot of espresso is about one to two cups of coffee.
Two shot is a medium coffee. Like six coffees for seven shots of espresso.
Did you hear that sound come out of my mouth? It was like the Pikmin look as if they long
to be tossed into the flower. Well, let's, I don't want to do it to purple. Is white electricity?
We'll find out. Or water? No. White is poison. Oh, so the gas. Okay, cool. Get in there.
I'm going to go get some gas.
Incredible. A white Pikmin. It's tiny, but it looks distinctly swift. Its eyes are an unseemingly red.
This type of Pikmin was not mentioned in your notes, Olimar. It must be an entirely new type
of Pikmin. A data record on this type is a blank page since a certain captain never documented them.
You must experiment and make detailed observations for the benefit of future generations.
It's omega low Reddit. Kind of is the Reddit Pikmin, isn't it? Oh, why can't I not go in?
I just put three. It was a waste. No, it wasn't. Louis, get up here and help me pull these.
Just replants them. Cool. Well, I got 15. Okay, let's get back to the group.
Something in here. What is in here? What is it now? Perfect. Oh, it's dinging.
Hey. Amazing. The white Pikmin have unearthed a treasure that was completely buried in the ground.
Perhaps those beady red eyes of theirs allow them to sense objects buried in the dirt.
Hooray. How thick is this tape? All right, this is a joke how thick this is. Everybody get on it.
We'll keep looking. Oh, rank up. No, no, no, no, don't all. Only red Pikmin just rank that.
You have to share it with everybody else. Share it. Share it with everybody else. What the hell?
Greedy. Too greedy. $80. Super stick textile. Cool. I like it. That's it for this floor. Let's get
everybody else. Follow me. We got the whole crew. The whole Drew crew. That's right. That's you guys.
You are the Drew crew. Was it February? All right. So in June, I don't have to say that anymore.
Well, here's the gas part. Oh, shit. Everybody split up. Remove the gas. They're fighting. What
are they fighting? Oh, they're fighting the gas. We'll pick that up. They don't carry that?
Is the white Pikmin not picking anything up? I can't take this with me for research.
It's a pipe. I can't like rip it out and take it with me.
All right. Let's go. Oh, wait. That's why the one behind me doesn't even. Wait,
can I get the mushroom? Easy. Easy. Don't go that way. I'm going to be safe.
I can get the mushroom. Cool. And everybody. Yeah, they can get the mushroom. Bring it in.
This is, hey, Jerome, it's my birthday today. It's Enver. It's my birthday. Could you be
really rude to me for five minutes? Happy birthday. I'm going to be really rude to you.
Why would I be rude to you on your birthday? Doesn't sound fun. Treasure. Can I get up there?
All right. Now walk that way. Get it. Let me get up there. This fucking controller is going to drive
me insane. I get it. Get it. Careful. Deliver that. Somebody help them. No fall damage. Yeah,
that's good. You don't need to take all the Pikmin to the entrance of the next geyser.
They follow you if you enter as a captain, even if they're not in your party. Really? Okay,
that's good to know. Do a Pikmin impression? Sure. Okay. Which one? Let's see. This is red.
Let's go. I'm not going to say that, but you know what I was going to say. Catboy practice? No,
you have no idea. I can't wait to tell you about the Catboy stream. The thing I want to do in the
Catboy stream. I can't wait to tell you about it like a year from now. Final floor. Let's go.
Din din din din din din. They should put that in. Din din din din din din. Din din din din din din.
Run run run run run run run run run run run run run run. It's a fucking bird from Donkey Kong.
Run. The red liquid you see contains refined ultra spicy essence. One drop contains one dose.
Press two to spray this extract on your entire group. Have you tried it yet? I have not,
but I will in just a second. Spray. Spray it. I spray it. Let's go. Pull back, back, back, back,
back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
Is he going? Attack. On his head, on his head, on his head, you dopes.
Run under his chin. That's a weak part. Oh no. Where is he? Get on his head. Get on his head.
What is the sound the Wiimote is making? What's the sound? Why is my Wiimote calling me?
Well done. Captain Olimar, you've defeated that freakish half bird half serpent hybrid.
Oh no, don't tell me that treasure was ingested by the beast, wasn't it?
I think I'm going to turn this off. I'm going to go into the settings and just turn off the Wiimote.
Being able to make noise. Very cool. All right. Is that everything in here?
That's the last floor. Go deliver it. Use a game cube controller. I'm on a Wii U.
I'm not on a Wii. This version doesn't support a gamepad. Okay. Get an adapter, you cheap bastard.
I just put my arms in the air and went like what? I didn't even know I was going to need it.
I thought it was like a Wiimote game. If the material looks comfortable,
I will use it to patch the boss's favorite sleeping bag. Ooh. Seam test. Conclusive.
Cross stitching successful. The knapsack is complete. Oh, also Pikmin 2 is like incredibly
fucking hard to find too. It's another one of those games that's like a shitload of money.
And it might have taken long to get here. I don't know. I did not anticipate a lot of these first
party old Nintendo games are going to be this hard to actually get a copy of. And I'm not going to
say this again. All you guys telling me to emulate a first party Nintendo game, you're going to get
me fucking thrown in jail. They're coming after me if I do. You're trying to get me fucking,
you're trying to get me taken? A first party Nintendo game? You want me to emulate and be
like I'm emulating first party Nintendo game. What do I care? Alerts go off at Nintendo headquarters.
Wait, when you have an unoccupied time interval, press and hold C to take a nap.
Everyone does it. I don't care if the Queen of England does it.
You would hold C. I don't want to hold C. I heal as Olimar. That was so cute. All right,
somebody just wrote, I used to emulate Pokemon at school back in the day, you boomer.
Did you do it in front of 10,000 people saying, hey, I'm emulating. I didn't buy this.
I think that's a small difference. Yeah, I did actually. Well, it looks like you got away with
it. You don't have to say you're emulating it. Oh, people will know. I'll hit like escape and
somebody will see like the emulator running and all of a sudden that's the running joke for the
next like three days. You know how I know that? Because it's happened before. If I have to emulate,
I do. Let me be very clear about that. But if I can play on original hardware, I'd like to play
on original hardware for a couple of reasons. It's kind of cool to actually own the consoles
and stuff. It's like sure, could I have like emulated the entire Dreamcast stuff? Yeah,
but I own the Dreamcast now and I have all that stuff. It's just kind of cool to have.
Now, that doesn't mean I'm against doing it. I've emulated plenty of games.
Okay, I can do the gas thing now. Yeah, criminal. Where's the gas down here? Right? Wait,
I want to harvest this stuff. I'm going to stay here for a minute. Nintendo interest has intensified.
Look, I just I don't want to fuck around. Nintendo really had a major crackdown on emulating
and emulated games and roms a year or two ago. I don't. I'm sorry. Nope. You need to
good lawyer. Instead of having to worry about having a good lawyer, why don't I just play the
one on Wii? Okay, I could either like hire a lawyer and have like a thousands of dollars
of a retainer fee or just play the game on Wii U. I think I would rather do the Wii U one.
How do you like it so far? It's really fun. It's very fun. All right, gas. Get through the gas.
It was this way. Oh, it's another globe. Cool, cool, cool. Oh, new level. Yes. All right, where
are they? You're kind of stuck, aren't you? Go get it. This is going to take a very long time,
isn't it? Use the spray. It's true. I got one person. I didn't get anybody. I didn't hit one
person with that. Why? You, Louie, you stay here. What else can we do in the meantime?
I just screamed at him. What can I do in the meantime? I don't think I can do anything in
the meantime. Please look at a Pikmin idol animation. I'm begging you. Okay. Hold C. No.
You're fine. You're fine. You're fine. Get over here. You're fine. Okay, I can't do anything.
Dismiss and then watch. They sit down? Why is that such important? Why do you need to see that so
bad? Okay. Can Olimar walk in here? We could kill that guy. All right. Let's kill that thing.
Oh, no, we can't. No. We get it. Yes. All right. Let's get in here. Get the globe.
Look at the flowers. What are you guys? What have you guys done? No. Nope. Not even going to
fucking address it. Fascinating. This object is highly similar to the one you found in the
Valley of Repose. By examining this further, I may be able to extrapolate new planetary data.
Oh, excuse me. Fight. Good. Blow him up. All right. We're going to have a lot of things to take
here. We have take his face and take the globe. Get that. Nice. Everybody on it. Bring it here.
Here we go. Cool. We've got a head. We got that. Where's Louis? Oh, he's right here. Nice. Okay.
Good. Bring it. There's a log there. There's one more thing over here, isn't there? Oh,
cannot go over here yet. This is like a Metroid. You have to get the right pick and come back.
You go back to the old levels and a Metroidvania. I'm sorry. I will apologize for that one. I'm
sorry. That one deserves an apology. You know how to do it. I'm a bird. You know what to do.
You just have to, you just have to call to me and I will call you. I will do it.
All it took was somebody to write just that doi doi doi in chat and I just did it.
Please do the scrumptious cake. I've said that so many times. Just go back to one of the times
I said it. Do Megalovania doi doi doi please. I don't think I can do that. I don't think that's
possible. It's too hard to do. Am I just the weird guy at the lunch table? Hey, hey, hey, dude. Hey,
hey, watch this. Hey, hey, dude, do the doi doi doi, but this time do this song. Okay. Sure thing.
He did it. He actually did it. He's going to get, he's going to get detention now.
Jeremy, what? You think it's funny to make noises in the middle of the lunchroom?
Yeah, I'm just having fun. That's two more days of detention.
I'm reliving what happened when I was in fucking high school. That's actually what happened.
Okay. Hey, dude, hey, do doi doi doi again. Like turn, do it like right into the air and then
make an elephant noise after. No, I'm not going to do that. I'm not going to do an elephant noise at
the end. Yeah, dude, come on, do it. It'll be funny. I'm not going to do it. All right.
This actually was real. Same shit happens on every stream. All right. I got to go back.
Everybody go home. Let's go home. Do doi doi doi. It'll be wicked funny. Don't go to sleep.
Oh, dude, do doi doi doi. It'll be wicked funny. Pause the ends day early. Oh, okay.
Pikmin top left. What? Chairman, it's my birthday today.
Oh, it would have been if you didn't throw me into the water two hours ago. By the way,
I am red Pikmin number 94. Oh, sorry about that. That was a lot of money today. 810 bucks.
That's pretty good. Who died? I've only lost Pikmin to battle. Nothing else.
Hold on. Good work so far. I hereby promote you to perennial manager. Press C to divide up work
and to delegate more to your subordinate leader. New level unlocked. Where is it?
New treasure. Very cool. I want to see the tape up close. Oh, that's good. What do you say for his
wife? The vivid color of this red stone reminds me of my wife's eyes when they burn with rage.
Just between you and me, I've noticed lately that she's been getting more wrinkles. Now that I
think about it, I've probably caused her a lot of stress. When I return to Hakau Tate,
I'll take her on a long vacation. I thought this was like a piece of shit or something.
Well, it is, but I thought it was an actual like shit. This is shoe polish. There are several
different patterns drawn on this object's surface. They appear to be characters or letters. I can't
make any sense of them. This is just an educated guess, but I wonder if this object is kind of an
alien bulletin board. The size of the object seems about right for it. Oh, that's cool. What's this
one? Today, I delivered an impromptu lecture on the basics of wilderness survival. As Louis
Superior, it's my responsibility to teach him these skills. Walking around as much as we do
generates an intense thirst, so water becomes very important. I told Louis that we have to ration our
water carefully. That's what I was thinking until I found this. I so parched that I couldn't help
myself. I drank all the water in the canteen. It tasted so good. When I turned around, Louis gave
me a cold stare. Let's go to area select. Okay, well, I have new... I'm gonna go back to the first zone.
I think I could probably dig something up, maybe? I'm gonna go for a zone. No, I need water first.
I guarantee to get water pickling here. John Oliver. How many zones are in the game? Four. Cool. So
you're just supposed to go all around and go back and forth and stuff. The two types are sleeping
well and do not quarrel. I have made them most comfortable. That's good. You can call out the
white Pikmin by standing in the light beneath me. Yes, yes, yes. Give it a burp. Well, there you go.
To retire early for the day, press start and then press right on the d-pad. All right, so what we
need? I'm gonna assess the area. Oh, yellow. Wild Pikmin, can you see them? Captain Olimar.
They're yellow Pikmin. You encountered them when you crashed on this planet, correct?
It would be most helpful if they remember you like the red ones did. Yes, most helpful.
Where are they? There's a frog guy over here. There's a cave right there. All right, let's
just take the crew. They're like a competing franchise. What's that? Oh, no, that's yellow.
Okay. All right, I'm gonna take some. I'm gonna take a crew. All right, I'm gonna take 50 red
and then all of these and all the purples. What does that leave me with? I can still get a few
more. Okay. Well, let's first kill this thing because why let it live and we can dissect it
and research it. You can kill anybody, right? Who died? A red Pikmin died. That's okay.
Wait, where do I bring this? I gotta put that in the yellow one. Where's the yellow? All right,
let's just follow them. Am I putting this yellow one in the red one? Whistle them. Put the lime
in the coconut. You put the yellow in the red, it explodes. Well, okay. I know that's not real.
I think I'm supposed to put that in the other one. Follow me. Sing it. Big subs.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight. Why is he going in there by himself?
I could hear how bad that singing sounded so I stopped immediately. Sometimes I can do pretty
well. This hole is filled with wretched nasty bugs. Are we fighting or what? All right, take those
bugs. There's a flying one right there. Crush his head. I'll take him. What's back here? I
can't go in the water. I can't go in the water. I can go in there. Hold on. Go over this way for a
sec. Be careful. Can we get up here? What does that mean? 201. Okay, now we're going to go
do the balance this. Is that what this wants me to do? It doesn't want me to go up on top of this.
Why is it lagging so much? It's an elevator. What's the point of this though? I don't know.
Why do I need to use this? What's it for? I just don't get it. If one of them is... We can go up
and then... Oh, wait. I can't get there from over here. Oh, I thought I came from over here. No,
never mind. Hold on. No, I thought I came from up there. Oh, Jesus. Bring him down. Kill him.
Why is it running? Shit. Emulator. Hold on. I need to shake my hand because holding a Wiimote
forward for three and a half hours sucks. They didn't think about that though. It was just play
with your grandmother Wii Sports for 15 minutes. All right, I'm ready. Eggs. Split this up for a
second. Hold on. No, no, no. Get over here. I want to get everybody up here. Oh, stand on that. Back
up. Can I not get everybody up here? I'm trying to like weigh this down so I can't. Oh, we need
that guy. Oh my God. Hold on. I got to take a break. I got to like stretch my arms. My right
elbow is dying right now from holding my hand forward like I'm changing the channel on a TV
station. Hold on. Oh, shit. Pause the game. I kicked tennis elbow. Wii elbow. End of the stream.
No, not yet. Let me stand up. All right. I wish I could do... You know what? I wish I could do this
with my eyes. See, they really fucked up this technology. Imagine the Wiimote pointer. You
could just do it with your eyes. Let's try this again. Instead of having to like lean forward
and like creep and hold my hand out. All right, so you stay here. Get over here. No,
why do you keep giving me people? Why can't I fucking do this?
I'm missing something very important here. Why can't I do this? I'm just going to throw them up
there. I thought I'm not supposed to like move to get on the escalator elevator with like two
people or something. I'm starting to really hate this fucking controller more than anything.
Oh, God. Oh, go! No, don't go. Louis, are you not strong enough to do this shit?
Why is it? Why can you do it now? All right. Fuck off, all of you. I'm running out of daylight
here. Fuck this controller. It was made for three games. All right, you take this guy back.
What, can they? Baste and rage pill. I'm serious. This controller works well in like 12 games out
of 5,000. All right, Louis is down there. Can I do anything else here while they get that gate?
Can we take this? Oh, we can. Get it. Bring it back. I'm out of time. We're out of time. Can
these guys even get down here? Let's just walk off the edge. The wheat moat through the screen
already. I know it's almost time. I know, I know, I know, I know. Can you guys get this please in
time? Come on, you can do it. There's a huge thing in here. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on. They couldn't do it. They couldn't do it. They couldn't do it. Okay. Wait, left behind? Wait,
how many? 30 people were left. No, they were. I thought I went down there with Louis. Fucking
elevator. Yeah, why is it even there? Fucking stupid elevator. For what? I'm going to throw
the Pikmin up. I throw them over the elevator. I was so hell bent on figuring out what I need
to do with the elevator. Just throw them over there. I went to Happy Hawkatate Savings and Loan,
but it seems my loan came from the shop next door, all devouring black hole loan sharks.
That sounds bad. Okay, I'm going to go back here. Did they even get the... They got it back in time,
right? Did they get the big guy? Or did they not get the big guy? All right, let's go. We lost one
big guy. Damn it. All right, everybody follow me. I want to go back to that gate. This time I'm not
going to sit here for 12 minutes fighting the stupid elevator. All right, can I go in here?
Whoa, what is this? A maze? Kind of. You all right? Did somebody die? Well, just keep up with the
group. What the fuck are you doing? Why would you stop to fight that thing? We're all clearly
running this way. What are you, insane? It's cruel. All right, let's do this stupid thing again and
I'm just going to just go up. Louis, you stay down here. We're just going to say you're a cool guy.
Hey, thanks. This thing's dead. Oh, you little things. Okay, this way. Get it. That was a shitty
reaction. I mean, thank you. For a second, I thought it was sarcastic. It may have been.
Did they get it? Good. Okay, so now there it is. There's the yellow ship. All right,
I've discovered yellow ship. Hello. Okay. Okay. Hi, guys. Hey, can we fart together the next
TwitchCon? No. The yellow Pikmin have climbed down the tree. They appear to like high places and
seem to be quite light. They have very large ears. Ear Pikmin, but I will give them the name
Olimar gave them. My static electricity sensors are reaching violently. What could that mean?
It means they're electric. All right, now we can deposit the things here. Let's do that now. That's
a big 10. Bring it into the ship. Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you going?
Where are you going? Where are you going? It has to be yellow that picks them up? Oh, it has to be
predominantly yellow that carries them. Okay, I see. Get back here. Look.
Okay. Well, hold on. You little dicks. All right. Spread out.
Fuck. Louis, go get that guy. Wait. Louis, stay down there. Oh, don't let red take it.
Where are you letting red take it for? Put it down. Put that down. Put it down. You know what?
Leave it alone. Bring it. Okay, we're good. How are they going to do this? Wait, why? Where are
they going with that? They're too far away. Where are they going? Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
guys. Follow me, please. Don't get eaten. You got fucking eaten, you dumb guy. Oh, come on.
Fuck. No. What? Shit. Come on. You stupid guy. Why would you walk it all the way if you can't
bring it back? Why would you just go back up there and hang out for a while? Shit. Did somebody just
die? Give me another one. Okay. Ten. What do I even have up here? I have three yellow Pikmin.
How did that happen? All right. Everybody spread out. Oh, shit. Purple doesn't have a place. Oh,
nice. Okay. Purple doesn't have a... Doesn't... Excuse me. Excuse me. This really is just
chaperoning a field trip. Everybody get out of the way. My fucking God. Did they just all
ran off the edge? My God. Are they drowning in water? They're not drowning, right? Okay. Well,
whatever. All right. There's a big guy over here. I need to collect everybody.
Louie, you're just going to be stuck back there probably. Too bad. Where's this other three?
Yellow can jump really high. Oh, that's cool. Oh, shit. They're just like pulling these apart.
All right. Everyone, we got a full team here. Blue swims, red's fireproof. All right. Stomp them.
Nice. Good job. Nice work, everybody. Don't even bring them back. What's the point?
I don't know what that is, but it's freaking me out. Somebody go touch it. What is this? A strange
mold-like botanical entity has spread across the ground here. Interesting. I am detecting other
plant life suffocating beneath it. I guess let's save them. Somebody's trapped under here? Somebody's
suffocating under here? Who is it? Oh, watch out. That's a fire pig.
Right into the water. Are you shitting me? Don't go into the- My God. What have you done?
What have you done? Why did they go that way? All right. What are these things doing?
Are we going to climb this? Oh, it's the- Okay. Cool. We'll get a log. Hold on. Oh,
they're killing this guy. Get him. Where's everybody? Okay. We're good.
Knock this down. They're making a bridge.
Oh, okay. Of course. Nice work, everybody. Kill, kill, kill. We're good? We're good. That was a
blue one. All right. Back here. Dude, are they getting chased? No. All right. We're good.
I can't get these. I'm enjoying this stream because I don't know what Jeremy's supposed
to be doing, so I can't get mad at him. This is ultra bitter essence. It does not appear to have
any monetary value, but I should research this. This is another spray. Same? Well, I have to get
more specimens. Oh, no, I don't. No, I don't. Where is everybody? Where is everybody? Where's
everybody? There's nobody over here. Just Louis. Can Louis die? All right. Louis will get everybody
else. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Is it for yellow? Where are they? Where are they? Where is
he? Got one. Okay. Where's the other one? What about the other ones? Oh, I got them all. Yes.
This game looks boring. It's kind of just a game to play for fun. It's good. Dodge the situation
with your parents. I need to make more money. I need to make $10,000. I'm only a third of the
way there. Who died at sunset? One died at sunset today. It's like a cop of my loan agent. He's got
a scary voice. His voice is very scary. Are we going to have a raid coming in? What's the raid?
Slime raid? Oh, let me see. Let me see. Let me see. Slimecicle came in with almost 2300 people.
What's going on, everybody? Thank you, Slimecicle. We're playing Pikmin. Very fun. I've never played
Pikmin before. It was my first experience playing Pikmin 2 jumping right to the sequel because
I heard it was better. It'll be a good stream. Whatever you're doing. Raid song for them. No,
I don't do a raid song. You guys say we do, but I don't. I've never heard of this before. No,
I'm so bad at coming up with lyrics. I can't do it. I can't do it. Hey, thanks for joining
this morning. How's your mother? Hope she's well. I don't know. There's an electric fence here.
This is why nobody likes us, chat. I didn't say it, but hey, you can't just...
What do you mean? What do you mean this is why nobody likes us? Do we have some type of
reputation that I don't know about? What do you mean? What are you talking about? We're going to
go 30. We're going to do... Let's go like this. Bad reputation. Take all the purples. Okay,
that leaves us with... I'm just going to do mostly red now. Do I have any white? I don't think there's
gas on this level. I don't think I need it. Maybe I will. Why not? I'll finish it off with yellow.
Where do these guys come from? Oh, there was yellow there. Okay. All right, here we go.
Welcome to the stream, guys. My name is Jerma. I want this to be yellow. Oh, whatever.
Everything changes. Why don't you grab it? We're running out of time. Let's go.
These kids look dope. Thank you. All right, I need this electric fence somewhere over here.
I know it. I remember it. Did he die? Where's the electric fence? The fuck is dying over here?
Something's blinking. Beetle. That's the beetle that we tried to find last time. Get him. Break
his shell. He's dropping coins and shit. Keep going. More, more, more, more, more, more, more.
I can give them a free one, right? I guess so. Can I just do it? Oh, nice. Behind you.
There's a piece of treasure. The white can dig, can't they? Is there a way I can make them dig?
Where is this? It's up there. Yes. Dig it out. What is it? Let them dig. Oh, it's like a coconut.
What is that? Oh, it's, I don't know, like a seed or something. He might as well take his dead body.
It's like a plant. Children bulb. This is very sad. These guys are so cute, though. They really are.
They're the cutest. Everybody move. I want yellow to take that. Why are you bringing it?
Why is it red now? What are you people doing? Bring it to yellow. I feel like I'm running out
of space. Do I have enough space for all these people? You don't want that. I already have a lot
of red. All right. That's what I'm, I remember that. That's why I came here. And I also want to do
electricity. Where is that? Oh, plant life. One of these things. This way. Where's that electric
fence up here? Why is he still playing this? Um, correct me if I'm wrong here, but you don't
really just like play Pikmin for 15 minutes. It's not like, oh, I'm going to play this for like 20
minutes. What's wrong with this? There we go. Okay. I do want some of these. Not ready yet?
Oh, fine. Treasure somewhere. The buried treasure. I don't care about that right now. Kill it. Kill
it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Good job. I want yellow to take that.
No, no, no. Yellow, yellow, yellow, yellow, yellow. I want yellow. I feel like the
level's not big enough. All right. Take it. We have to keep harvesting people. Leave them alone.
All right. Electricity was, oh, gas. Nice. All right. I can get this done. I need the white.
You know what to do. Get over there. Okay. They're going to be working on that.
Now let's take this guy back. It's going to be red. That's fine.
What does that lead to? Another elevator. Great. Spray, spray, spray them, spray them, spray,
spray, spray. Can I spray them, spray them, then throw them back? Here we go. Go for it.
All right. Now what? Wait till that's done and then...
Fuckin' arm. Where's this treasure? It's up there, right? How do we get up there though?
Oh, okay. This way. End of the stream. No, not yet. You know what? Hey.
Louis, go get those guys. There's like 10 electricity dudes over here.
You guys said yellow can jump higher, right? Excuse me. Yellow can be thrown higher. Okay.
Let's see if I can get it. This is going to kill me, isn't it? Are they going to get it?
Where are they going to bring it? Oh, shit. They can just fall down. Nice. All right. What is that?
Chapstick? Oh, hell yeah. That I... Who hasn't drank out of this? A lot of the yellows. Okay, good.
That wall almost down. That's a glip one. Chapstick. Healing cask. I'm going to keep
these guys back here because I'm afraid to go over there because it's almost time to leave.
They almost got it. Electric fence is up here. I'm coming back here next level. You got it. Yes.
We're good? All right. Now. Fucking elevator. The things I hate the most.
I didn't mean to do that. The fucking Wiimote. I swear to God.
I didn't want to do that. I started to get really, really heated in my brain.
No. Oh, my God. This Wiimote. I'm going to fucking swallow it whole. I swear to God.
Come on, bring it. Get it down here. Let's go. Yes. Get some more of these berries. I demand it.
Imagine losing to a fucking scale. Stop. This game used to make me bite my Wiimote. Okay. I doubt it.
All right. Come back. Come back. Come back. Okay. We got to go. There's other ones here. Where are
they? I'm not missing anybody, right? That's the ship. Where's Louis? White Flower Garden?
Wait. What the hell is that? I think I'm good. There are 32 that are free. Where are they?
That's it, right? Five that are free. Where are they? I think it's the blue ones. We're good.
Yeah, we're good. We're good. All right. I want to come back here and I want to go back
up to the top there. Actually, maybe I can't. I think I did everything I can do here for now.
I could go in there, but hmm. Oh, there's an electric fence up there. That's right.
I'll go back. I like this game. It's fun. This game is really cool. We'll probably play this again.
We'll probably do this again on Sunday. I'm not in the stream. Super Bowl Sunday. I don't care who's
in the Super Bowl anymore. Tom Brady's not in Patriot anymore. You have to say that. You have
to say that. You have to say Super Bowl. Whatever. I don't even fucking care. I'm playing Pigment on
Sunday. Hi, Papa. Mama heard you got a promotion, so she's very happy. You have lots of people under
you now, right? So does this mean you're a super captain? It's 1130 at night. Son, you're calling
me. Why are you not in bed? You're supposed to be in bed at 1030. It's a different planet.
I'm angry because it's local time here. All right. We're getting a lot of yellows because
an electric fence that I want to get to. I got 55 yellows. Holy shit. Let's do 30 yellow.
30 yellow and a bunch of purple. And then I think, should I even bring any? I'll bring like two.
We'll bring four and then the rest spread. It's 95. Cool. All right. Let's go to the electric fence,
which was up this way. Do you know that Joel thought you were a Christian streamer that
didn't swear before he started talking to me? Well, you guys did that. What's your doing?
That's not my doing. Where's that electric fence? Right there. Okay. Oh, a stupid elevator.
You get on there. Where did you go? Oh, oh, they all fell off. Joker laugh. Whatever.
They should profile you in the newspaper. Why? So like fucking 15 people can read it.
It was like kind of rude. All right. We're going to go up here. Only bring yellow up here.
That was extremely rude. You millionaire. No, that's not what I was talking about. I'm talking about
that. Like who? Okay. Let's go ahead and go over this because a lot of you. When was the last time
anybody in this chat read a newspaper? Say one. One in the chat. I'm serious. When was the last
time any of you read a newspaper? You're, you're a liar. And no, no, no, no. I'm not talking about
like an online publication of a newspaper. I'm talking about a newspaper that you hold and fold
in your hand. All right. Wait, should I fart on them? All right. Get in there. Let's go take that
down. It's free. So I read it. I literally get my New York times delivered. I don't think you do.
I'm missing a couple of guys up here. Come on. You can do it. There's a lot of you guys down here.
Come on. Let's go. I can't tell you the last time I read a newspaper. Reddit.com is most of the
millennial generation's newspaper. Am I a boomer? I'm, I'm not a boomer. I'm a millennial. Just like
you. We're the same. Okay, cool. So now there's another place to go. Should I go down here? Let's
see. Uh, where's, hold on. You guys stay there. NX? No, I'm, I'm a millennial. I'm a millennial.
Yes, I am. And they all even fit up here. Not really. Rod German, you're five years younger than
my mom, mate. You're not like me. How old are you? 39, 39, 40. I, yeah, I am kind of old, aren't I?
I wasn't even reading any of that. What did it say? That guy could be like 21. Oh shit. Oh my God.
I'm too old. I'm way too old. I'm a dinosaur now. But I don't need a blue Pikmin in here.
Ooh, what's this? Wait, is this a red flower? I don't think I want to turn anybody red. Is this
orange or red? I don't think I want red. That guy looks scary. Hey guys, we're the big guys.
Oh shit, he killed a few people. Okay. Easy. Easy. Oh shit, there's a lot of those guys.
I want, I want purple first. Easy. Help me. Relax. Ooh, what'd he drop? What is that? It's a jewel.
There's such an overreaction to that. Oh, there's a guy on me. Okay. 150, that's a lot.
We're still clover. I am going to turn some reds into lights here. It's okay to react to things.
Yeah, I know. I'm just kidding around. All right, let's keep going. 91, that's it. All right, what
else? What is it? I don't know if I should turn. No, he's reacting. Someone stop him. Remember,
why is your chat the weird table in lunch class? Did you just hear me do the doy doy doy to
Megalovania? This is, uh, it's kind of, I think it's been like this for a little while.
Yeah, that was lunch class. I love that. I'm going to, I'm going to talk. I'm going to say
it like that from now on. Lunch class. I love that. Does this guy fire? Get him. Don't put
his head. They're immune to fire. What do you think you're doing? God, I'm sorry. I'm having
like too much fun just being like a fucking weirdo. I'm sorry guys. Uh, let's take these guys. Diamond.
All right, when do you pick it up? Uh, now I want, uh, I want you guys to go get that diamond.
Pack it up. Oh, wait a minute. Now that's a really bad idea. I have to do that with red. I did not
even notice the geysers. Jewel. Ah, thank you. I'll get stuck. That was a good clean run. Nobody
died. What are you going to have for lunch? Um, that's a good question. What do you feel like?
What do I feel like? That's another good question. What do you wish I get? Oh, by the way, I want to
give you guys a quick little update on something. So I mentioned something called the archaeology
stream. Uh, trying to get a solid date on it. We're very close to giving a true solid date on
the archaeology stream and it will be as long as we get a confirmation on it. If it's confirmed,
it will be within the next 30 days. We've been working on it for a little while. I'll give you
get just a quick, a quick little, uh, what it is. Well, an archaeology stream. I'm going to be
opening up a bunch of geodes on stream among other things, among other things, but we're going to be
opening up geodes from small to big to medium. Oh, no, no, no, no. Don't kill everybody. Please.
That was terrifying. I thought he killed like a hundred people. There's going to be a lot of
weird shit on that stream. Should be fun though. More white flour. Hold on. Oh, this is kind of a
battle. Fight. Everybody fight. Watch out. Everyone move out of the way. Don't let him do it.
Bring him down. Good. So we'll pick these up. Nobody died. There is a treasure somewhere.
Done. Let's turn a few, a few more reds into yellows. Oh God. All right. I want red. Get in line
behind red, please. Come up. All right. I don't want to do it that way. I think there's a lot
more fire here, so I got to be careful. Louis, don't get stuck behind the plant. Really? That it?
Okay. Follow me. Follow your nose. Follow. Hold on. My Captain Crunch cereal. I'm working on a Captain
Crunch. Let me know how you think. My Captain Crunch cereal and crunch berries are full of flavor.
That's pretty good, right? Somebody just wrote it all caps. Drunk. I guess
that is something that somebody that was drunk would just do. That is something a drunk person
would just do. Hey man, we're going to make Captain Crunch. What do you think? My Captain Crunch cereal.
Just shit faced on the couch. Just eyes closed. Eyes closed on the couch.
Leaning back, lying back. There's a movie on TV, by the way. We're all watching a movie.
Eyes closed on the couch just randomly. My Captain Crunch cereal is the most delicious crunch berries.
It's like fucking Jesus, man. Like stop. It's just trashed. Where is this treasure?
I'm losing my mind. Where is this treasure? Hey, hey, hey, hey. Pick it up. Trashed.
Oh, it's a seashell. Oh, sorry. Anautilus. 40 bucks. That's it. Okay. Let's go. I feel like
I'm going to get my ass kicked. I'm afraid of this. Remember, do you like us? I feel like you hate us.
Why would I hate you guys? Purple. Nice. Electricity. Oh, all right. All right. Let's do this right.
First of all, what do we have for a team here? Let me see. Line up. Yeah, we're getting rid of
more reds. I have so many. You hate us because we bully people when we raid. Hey, you guys,
people are trying to stream. You can't just bully people that we raid. I know you like to have fun,
but if somebody's streaming and they don't want to sing a raid song, they don't have to sing a
raid song. Do you really want us to be like a lunch table where only five of us can sit at this
lunch table? Ooh, nice. Yes, that's what we want. I almost get shocked. Okay, that's good.
What is more? Electricity. Ooh, more purple. Electric bugs. All right, well, let's go.
Hold them back. Hold them back. You just killed. Oh, you fucking asshole. Okay, hold on. Pull them
back. We're going to bait the big guy over here. Shit. Holy shit, I'm fine. Kill it quick. Kill it.
Kill it. Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up. Okay, separate that again. That could have been
much worse. That could have been a lot worse. Bring him back. I want to turn the camera. Okay,
there we go. I think he shit himself. I may have. What happened? Oh, am I religious at all? Not
really. All right, let's get the... Hold on, not yet. Any more big guys? Everybody come back.
Now, hey, I'll tell you, I'm not religious. I'm not religious at all. But, I mean, I don't know.
It could be. Aliens could have made us. They could be a god. I don't know. I have no idea.
I really have no idea. I couldn't tell you either way. Agnostic Andy. I don't know. I couldn't tell
you one way or another if like dinosaur poop turned into us. If aliens decided to come by one
day and drop off like a specimen into the water and just run like it was a fucking prank. I don't
know. Or if like God created... Watch out, watch out, watch out. No, don't line up that close
together. That would be a pretty good prank. You know what I mean though? I don't know. We could
be an experiment. What's going on in here? Something in there. All right, drag him out.
Get out. Get out here. Get out of your hole. He doesn't want to come out. It's too bad
because I think there's probably something in here. Golden fucking bug! Whoa. What is that?
I just got a golden bug. That's like a... Holy shit. Okay, cool. What does that get me? Does it
get me anything? I got a gold bug. That's it for a golden bug? I don't think that's enough.
I think that's more. I need more. I want to kill this guy. But, you know, can I flip him over with
a big dude? All right, everyone get him now. Don't let him get up. Overwhelm him. All right,
now bring him back. I got all the treasures. Cool. Nice. Did you not get it? Come on. You
cannot pick that up. Come on, boy. Of course, you can. Who hasn't eaten? A lot of the purple's
haven't. Ooh, nice, nice, nice, nice. Okay, cool, cool, cool. Now what? Do I have everybody?
I think I do. Yeah, let's keep going. I got all the treasures.
All back's kingdom. Is this a boss? I'm going to get another boss. I don't know.
It's still not the bottom. Shit. Okay, hold on. Why not? I'm really getting the hang of this. I'm
starting to understand this a lot. Devon chat. Real Devon. Why is everybody saying that? Seven
gold? That's not that much. Because they're here. I'm just hitting the head. Who hasn't eaten?
Pine cone. I think everybody has eaten. Look at that. We got full bellies all around. 50 cents
or coins. Those look like Mario coins. That's not it. There's another one in here somewhere.
Oh no, that's it. All right. This was kind of a small area. This is randomly generated. This
seems tiny. Level five? That's a bomb. Okay, this is bombs. Level six. Hello, Mr. Otto. What's the
matter? Are you hungry? Me too. We're still not at the end. All right, this looks dangerous. I'm
going to go this way. More red. All right, same deal. Okay, good. Pick up that medallion. Holy shit.
All right, cool. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Call back, back, back, back, back, back, back,
everybody back, everybody back. That was my mistake. I fucked it up. I thought I could throw it over
the guy's body. Mr. Noodle? Mr. Noodle? Mr. Noodle? Mr. Noodle? I am a fucking bird. I really am.
Entry. This creature showed symptoms of poisoning after consuming the white pikmin.
Perhaps white pikmin excreted poisonous substance when chewed. How fascinating. Lost a couple people
though. All right, whatever. What else is in here? Fire stuff. Let's put you guys up. Turn off all
these geysers. Get it. Tell it. These things even fight back. I feel like they don't. Oh, fuck. Pull
back, back, back, back, back, back, back. There's a bomb in there. Pull back, pull back. I think I'm
good. All right. Let's just clean this up. Pick all this stuff up. Any of my other buddies? Where's
Louis? Oh. Look at all that nectar. It's too bad I don't even need to use it. Everybody's already
pretty much maxed out. I'll take the money though. Oh, hold on. 81. All right. Again, bring the fire
over. Can't kill it. None of them landed on his head. That's kind of weird. BF bugler is in check.
Oh, I can't believe it. Oh, more purple. Purple.
No fucking way. No way he's in check. There's a buried treasure somewhere. I don't know where.
Maybe we can recover all the energy in the radar room. When we find that beta,
we'll find Dr. Bob. Sorry. I'm so fucking high. Are these guys fire? Me too. I'm not, actually.
Okay. There is a treasure in here. Oh, no. How am I ever going to get that?
That's the blunt. I don't smoke marijuana. I mean, I do, but not that, not really that often.
Once in a blue moon. Let's get that skull. 81. Let's go. Once an hour.
Is that a bomb? Run, please.
He didn't make it. He didn't make it. He tried. It's okay. Poor purple Pikmin number 25.
So, just to clarify again, it doesn't matter. They just have to be alive down here, right?
I can just go in. Okay, cool. 140. Am I almost halfway through the game? Is 10,000 the debt?
After 10,000, that's not even close. Really? Oh, shit. Okay. Full debt is halfway. Oh, wow.
Okay. Here we go. Final floor. Let's do this carefully. There's definitely a boss down here.
Fire only. Snakes in here and shit. Hold on. Are they fire snakes? Are they fire snakes?
They might be. Those are eyes. Oh, shit. Okay. People are going to die. People are dead. Like,
let's just be honest. What's the strategy here? I want purples on... I want reds and purples
on Olimar. Or no, just purple on one. I want only red on Olimar so I can be...
I can be... Okay, that's what I'm doing. No. What do I want? That's it.
Should I leave the other ones here? Maybe it's not even worth bringing them.
Because aren't they just going to die? If it's a fire boss, then I feel like they're just going to
die. Let's try it. Let's see what happens. Okay. I don't know what he's... I don't know.
Run, run, run, run. Just run. See what he does. What does he do? Is he like a charge move or
something? Probably charges. He's kind of cute. He's kind of cute. And this music is so cute too.
I haven't seen anything. He doesn't charge. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Don't scoop up enough like
a whale with a school of fish. Okay, good. He has a big tongue. Where can we go? Oh, my God.
Don't stand still. Don't throw it in his mouth. Everyone back up. Everybody back...
Oh, Megazord. It's fascinating. I still have... Oh, he killed so many. So many purples again. My
purple friends. I'll replace him. It's all right. And there's a gate here. This is just a regular
gate. There's more. I'm surprised there's more. Well, start working on that. It's a Megazord worth.
That's it. I'm a boss. Material has perplexing properties. I will try fusing with a spare
space suit. Health increase. I let us mention the Scorch Guard. Thanks to the heat-resistant
alloy, this suit is now impervious to fire. That's cool. The rest of you, get over there.
Got it. What's the point of the second part here? There's another treasure here, but where is it?
Let me see. I have to take fire, guys, with me. Wait, can I even do that?
I fell. Shit, I can't get that. Yeah, I can. Follow me. Thank you. You know what to do. Take
that out. Hey, now can I? Now go get it. Come on, two more through. Get up there. Get up there,
guys. Really? Get it. Oh, all right. I'm immune to fire. Bring this shit. Don't go that way. Go
this way. Thank you. Aha. I did it. Next time I play this, I'm definitely turning off the sound
thing. If they went into the water, that would have been very bad. What's this one worth? It's
cute. Well, my compressor is making it so you don't hear it all the time, but make no mistake.
It's just doing this forever. 250. Holy shit. Nice. Turn it off in five seconds. Press the home
button. Yeah, but I think I'm going to start with that because then people will know that it's
turned off, and people will be very upset if I turn it off now, won't they? They'll be like,
I wanted that. Why'd you get rid of that? If I start with that on Sunday, I'll just be like,
hey, it's off. People will be like, oh, it's off. I know. I'm just kidding around. That's a lot of
money today. 1350. Cave complete. I think that's probably a good place to stop, too.
After this day is over, I think this is a good place to stop. 40% of debt recovered. What else
can I do here today before the time runs out? Hmm. I'm not sure there is anything I can do.
Did I get the blues? Wait, let me refill. Give me some more reds. All right. 95 Pikmin. Let's go.
Where's the blues? So if I go through here and around, blue is that way. Okay.
Ooh, there's a yellow thing here, too. Interesting. Okay. All right. Where is it at? Wait.
That's where I need to go. Okay. Here's the plan. I'm going to throw you over here,
and then I'm going to run around the side. Everybody up. That was painful. Wait, why?
I want to bring everybody up here. Look there. A wild blue Pikmin are chasing prey near the
water's edge. You can split up the captains. Oh, yeah. That's right. This is why I heard the
Pikmin 2 is the worst one. It's like the whole splitting the captains thing. I heard that that
was a reason why everyone didn't like this one. There's like 12 on Rotten Tomatoes. I get it now.
I apologize. I was momentarily entranced by them. Now back to work.
Bad angle. Oh, yeah. I know this is universally the most loved one. I know. That's the reason why
I'm playing it right now. I would have started with one if that were not the case, right?
Get away from the fence. What are you doing? Why would you do that? That was not smart.
Where are you going with that? Oh, I guess fine. Go ahead. One's actually better, but don't tell
anyone. I mean, this is really good. This is very fun. I don't know how much more different
the first one is. The time limit was really scary as a kid. It was scary as an adult too.
Come on, you can get it. Come on, break it down. In Pikmin 1, you had 30 in-game days. That's it?
Well, is this day like six? I'm on like day six or seven and I don't even have the blue Pikmin yet.
It's day nine, right? OK. I know it says it in the top right corner, but I am currently looking
over at a chat room. I'm staring at the chat, reading what you guys are saying. Since I brought
that up, I have been looking at the chat box. I don't have four sets of eyes. All right, let's go.
How do I do this? Wait, nobody move. Don't. Please. If I walk in the water, this is going to die.
You shit-eating dumb fuck. Why do I have to be eating shit?
At last you have encountered them. They seem to have gill-like ducks on their cheeks.
They must be blue Pikmin. Like the other types, they look like they want to talk to you.
He looks really fucked up right now. All right, come to me over here. Deliver that. Deliver this.
They're just fighting these tadpoles. Not yet. We're not strong enough yet.
Not yet, I said. Are you eating them out of the ground? Better not be. Kind of hard to see.
Oh, fuck. Hurry up. Come on. Hurry up. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Get it. Get it. Get it. All five of you. All five of you, pick it up. Get on it.
Gone. Okay, that was really fun. Come on. Excuse me.
We did it. We made the other 100. Where are they? There's 20 somewhere. Where? Oh my god.
There they are, the other ship. No. Weemote, please. Did I get it? I think I got it. I was
trying to get the motion over there all the way to the edge. I skipped it. I didn't even mean to.
They're fine. They're at the base. Okay, cool. Game is stressful. We made a lot of money. We died.
A lot of purples died. Yeah, 34 died today. Three died from like, one from explosion. Oh right,
in the cave. You made it stressful by sitting at the gate all day. It's all good though.
It's all good. Almost 5,000 out of 10,000. Cool. So now that I have water, I can do
most of the shit over here. That'll be for another day. So I am not streaming tomorrow.
I ran into the unfortunate problem of I was supposed to stream yesterday,
but the Twitch server's had problems. So I have something I have to take care of tomorrow. I have
things, I have some errands I have to run, but I'll be live on Sunday. We will continue Pikmin 2.
It's really fun. I like it. It's a really good game. And we will pull the stream back on Sunday
as well. So we're not going to start at 4 30 Pacific on Sunday. We're likely to start somewhere
around, let's see, somewhere around 1 PM Pacific. Pull it back by a few hours or so.
So that's it. I'll see you guys on Sunday. Have a wonderful rest of your day, rest of your night.
Sorry we couldn't stream yesterday, but you know, sometimes shit happens, right?
I like it. I can't promise that I will beat Pikmin 2, because if what you're telling me
is true and the game's like 30 to 40 hours long, we might do it one or two more times and see how
far we get. We'll see. If I still am having fun, I'm still going to play it. He's not going to
beat it. I don't know. We'll see. Any news on Bionicle? No. The only news that I can share
with you is there will be an archaeologist stream in the next 30 days. It's the only news
I have for you right now. Let's do a raid. Let's see who's live right now. Let's go to...
Let's go to Joel. Joel's playing Super Straight Fighter. It's Fightcade Friday. Sounds like fun.
Thanks for all the subs, everybody. This list is extreme every single day that I stream.
This list is... This is a... We essentially have filled an entire guest list of people
at a fucking party. A concert. Thank you, everybody. Go say hello to Joel. This party sucks.
We'll see you soon, though. See you on Sunday, around 1 o'clock Pacific.
Thanks for watching, as always. Have a great night. I'll catch you guys soon.
Thanks for hanging out. Good night and goodbye.