Hey, what is going on, everybody? Welcome back to more Hitman Absolution.
This is going to be the second part of the Terminus mission, the Upper Floors.
So let's go. Welcome back.
Yeah, well, I pretty much just killed, like, everybody downstairs.
There was a lot of people that didn't die.
Uh-huh. Seal up tight.
Come on! I didn't do anything. I wanted to hear what they were saying.
You know what, buddy? I'm going to restart this mission, but just because you are a jerk,
I'm going to blow your faces off! All three of you! Yeah!
Alright, so I guess how it works is if you are disguised as a group of people,
they will see through your disguise. That group will see through your disguise more often than not.
So you can't just, like, walk into groups of people that I'm disguised as.
I know. Too bad. That's too bad.
I don't know where to go. There's people everywhere here, man. Where am I supposed to go?
Let's follow this lady. Maybe not, because she's in, like, somebody's room.
Point of interest. Over here. Alright.
A lot of paintings on the wall.
I thought there was blood all over the ground here. It's flowers.
I thought somebody got, like, riddled with bullets in this hallway for a second.
Indicates a nearby fire escape.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There's nobody even here. What? Who am I hiding from?
Was I not supposed to come in this room? I probably wasn't, like, allowed in here,
because, I mean, it did say do not disturb, so.
This lady's like, uh, sir, what the hell are you doing over there?
Nothing, I'm just standing here. Hi.
Alright, let me, will you get out of the way, bitch?
I didn't mean to call you bitch, but you're just getting on my nerves. Alright.
What is this?
The musician won't leave his room without a reason, so this guy apparently...
Is anybody even in here?
Oh, he's right there.
Is he just in there rocking out, playing the guitar?
Well, sorry, dude. I'm ruining your stuff.
Can I go, I can't go out this window. Can I just, like, crouch back here?
No, no, get in this thing! Get in here! Quick! Get in!
Alright, is he coming out? Yeah, he is.
Oh, your room is crazy, man. I can't wait to go in there and break those lights.
Uh, you're gonna have to turn around, so...
If I come at it, he's gonna see me!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, make your way to that speaker. Go fix it.
There's a problem there. You're gonna have to deal with it.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy. He doesn't know I was here. Oh, boy.
He's still fixing his stuff. What am I doing here?
What the hell am I supposed to do in here? There's a bottle.
Uh, sure. This room is gonna make me, like, start to hallucinate.
Oh, he's back. He's back! He's back!
What am I doing here?
I like, I broke in this guy's room for, like, no reason.
Wait a minute. Um, I think I'm gonna have to bottle this guy in the face.
That's really my only solution.
Because I don't know what to do, but I'm gonna hide his body. Don't worry.
Oh, that didn't even work! Come here!
Alright, we're good. We're good.
Okay, I'm good. Nobody heard that. Nobody saw that.
Now I can, can I take his disguise? I cannot.
Can I play his keyboard? Let's hope so.
Dump his body in here.
I can't believe the bottle. I didn't, like, hurt him.
I threw a bottle at this guy's face and it, like, didn't do anything.
I should probably put the shotgun away. That would be a bad idea.
Pizza? I'll take a slice.
So what was the purpose of this room?
This son of a bitch had nothing in here for me to do.
There's gotta be something in here. Why would, why would I be coming in here?
Oh, wait a minute.
Mmm, whoa. This is, no, this is the same...
Can I go with the window? Is there any, oh, there's a window.
Fire extinguisher? Nah, I don't think I want that.
This guy's got food literally everywhere. What a freak.
I don't know. Let's go.
So maybe I had to come through there? Ooh, can I go, oh!
I can, like, go up here, can't I? That's where the guy is. That's where, like, the target is.
Climb. If this, there's not some guy just standing right here, is there?
Oh lord. Progress is only saved to, oh yeah, definitely activate the checkpoint.
Minus one thirty five oh, god damn it.
Well, what's, whoa, whoa, see ya!
Oh my, oh my!
That's a long, oh, he just broke his back! Wow!
Well, why do I always do that to people?
I always do that to people!
I probably could've just let that guy, like, smoke his cigarette or whatever he was doing and he could leave.
You think this guy's gonna be suspicious that his, like, best friend just is not here anymore?
Maybe I can pull this guy out too. Do I have anything?
No, I don't, can I make any noise? No, I don't think so.
Uh, only one guy in here.
Will you get out of the way? I don't, this guy's gonna see me walk by, go.
Okay, I need a new disguise, man. I can't just be, like, walking around.
Maybe these guys will have a conversation. Maybe not.
I have to, there's really no other way unless I go down.
I don't really wanna go down. This is gonna take a little bit of thought, hold on.
Uh, I can go in here, but these guys are in there.
Come to the window. Come over to the window and take a look.
You're gonna meet the same fate as your friend.
No, this guy's still just staring at me.
Damn it! Wait, is that the target right there?
Um, I guess I can drop down.
But then again, I wanna be, like, up on this top floor, don't I?
We'll see. Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I might be able to get behind this guy right now.
No, there's another guard in here. Damn it!
Let's go down. Looks like I can get in this way.
Hop down again, maybe? No, that's it.
I can either go up, I have to go in this door, or this window.
Damn it, man.
Now that these guys are all the way to the back, I'm gonna try and distract them.
I got an idea. I got an idea.
At least, oh, you know what, I can just try and do some crazy stuff right now
because I do have that checkpoint right there.
So, let's just go in.
When this guy turns around again, I'm going in this window.
Turn around, come on. Turn around.
I'm gonna ask you nicely one more time, and then I'm pulling out the gun.
And I'm gonna shoot you in your face.
Turn around. Turn around! Turn around, there we go!
Turn around, that's what I like to see.
Okay, I have reached the eighth floor.
My word, this is gonna take a lot of, like, good, like, stealth.
Oh, the piano. I can knock the piano thing down?
Oh, boy. Oh, boy, oh, boy.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy!
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't come over here.
Do not come over here.
This is the most nerve-wracking thing ever.
So, if I knock down that piano pin, is there a place for me to hide?
Can I hide in the fireplace? Hmm.
I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna grab the bottle, I'm gonna throw the bottle over there,
and I'm gonna try and make my way silently out the left side.
There's only one guy there.
Let me go bottle, and throw it over there, and wait for them to freak out.
Yeah, yeah, go! Whoa, right there!
There's a guy right there!
Knock this down.
Oh, no, now that's all of them, all of them, all of them, all of them, all of them.
Am I actually gonna get away with this?
How the hell did I not get spotted right there?
Are you kidding me?
I need that bottle.
Oh, I need to just go in the room behind me, but I can't.
I'm gonna alert this whole entire upper floor.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Are you? Come here.
Come here, you!
Come here, you son of a bitch!
Quiet! Just be quiet! Shut up!
What do I go? What do I go?
Is there anybody in this hall?
Come on, come this way, this way, this way, this way, come on.
Give me your disguise.
No, get up, get up.
Get up, get in here.
There's so many people on this top floor.
Oh, I got up to 12,000 points, guys.
Doing things correct.
What do you know?
Doing things correctly.
Now where on earth am I going?
Okay, don't want to go that way.
Did I just, is this the exit? Did I do this?
Pick lock?
Ooh, I'm picking the lock.
This is where I gotta go.
I think I just did it.
I just did it!
No, I didn't.
Not quite.
This is the room, though.
Is this something I gotta do?
What's that?
A direct approach is not an option.
I need an alternate point of entry.
All right, well, here we go.
I'll come in like a spider.
I'll snatch you up.
She's worth a lot of money.
So that's the target.
All right.
Come at me, bro.
What's going on?
I don't like drugs.
I'm on like drugs right now.
What's happening?
I think it's...
What's...
I did it.
Nice.
All right.
I unlocked some things, too.
Hey, that's not bad.
That's not bad.
I'll take a minus 5,000 points.
But I got 12,000 for the first part.
Oh, the second part.
Let's take a look.
Nine to...
Oh!
I killed 11 people downstairs.
Well, that could have been like a good score
if I didn't murder 11 people.
All right, let's keep going here.
Hey, how are you?
That's a big dude.
Oh, you're getting choked out, baby.
That didn't work.
No, because I'm Hitman, baby.
What?
Are you kidding me?
I look pale.
No, he's a goddamn Hitman.
He's a goddamn Hitman.
That's a Hitman.
Everyone's got such a naughty, vulgar mouth.
Listen to all these, like, swears.
That guy's like nine feet tall.
This guy is a creep.
Look at this guy's face.
Oh, boy.
That's not good.
All right, so this guy's like framing me for this murder
that I just did, apparently.
Now he's going to torch the place?
Oh, what a son of a bitch.
Well, that's one way to go about getting yourself framed.
I didn't do it, I swear.
Please don't kill me.
Whoa.
Run for your life.
All right, let's run for our lives.
So the guy that I just went to kill
torched the room and framed me.
He killed some maid over here.
And now these police think that I did it.
Welcome to Escape the Hotel.
Here we go.
I have no idea where on earth I'm going.
Let's go this way.
Fire, fire.
Somebody put out your fire.
Through here.
Of course.
At least I got the knife.
Wow.
Can only go one way.
They got a helicopter on me?
What is America's most wanted?
My god, stop it.
Leave me alone.
I got to climb up.
So wait, wait, wait.
You're telling me that from that like little bottle of whiskey
that that guy was...
Oh, wow.
Am I going to get hit by that?
You're trying to tell me what I was saying was
the little thing of whiskey that that guy poured on the ground.
You're telling me lit the hole, engulfed this entire hotel in flames.
Are you kidding me?
That's pretty ridiculous.
Whoa.
Wow.
Wait, that's a guy right there.
How are they on the roof already?
Can they?
It's like they can't see the smoke.
All right, so see through the smoke.
Go, go, go.
You can't see me.
I'm good.
Can I hop over?
I can't even hop over this way, can I?
Get me over here.
Damn it.
It's all right.
They can't see.
They can't see anything right now.
What's that?
I'll take the wrench.
Can I hop over this is the question at hand?
Nope.
I'll wait for them to go down.
Come on, get out of the way.
Oh, I got an idea.
Go get it, officers.
There's a wrench over there.
Only one of you is going to go over there and do that?
No, wait, that guy's going over here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Hurry up and go look at the wrench.
Do you have to like phone it in where you're going?
Go, go, go.
Good.
Sneak through the pipes here.
Hey, look at that.
Beautiful.
Get me the hell out of here.
There's the exit.
Break the door down.
The question is, did I make it?
Probably.
Whoa.
That's a pretty dramatic entrance.
Chicago's finest.
Where's he at, boys?
And that's going to wrap it up for this episode, ladies and gentlemen.
I will see you guys all for the next part where I try to escape from the Chicago Police Department.
But yeah, that'll be pretty soon here, guys.
So thanks so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And take care, everybody.