Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. Wait a second. Yeah
Kick player tanklop. No reason given. Get him out of here. Oh get him out of here booted. Hey, welcome to Facecam Fortress 2
My name is Jerma. Welcome to the party. Good to see you. Glad you came. There is a spy standing just right here.
Vote failed. I'm currently
NACL is my name on here. What the hell is going on?
This is just cottage. Playing as the combat engineer, like I said with the frontier justice, the gunslinger and the pistol.
Yeah, that's the pistol.
See if we can't keep them in their spawn. That would be fantastic. You know what? Let's just put another one down.
Get out of the way. Who's gonna? Well, what am I bumping into? Oh my god.
Get out of here, man.
Spy on top of my spy. Slapping my spy. Anybody? Come on. Come on now.
Who wants to come out? Scout wants to come out. You're gonna get riddled with bullets, dude. I told you not to do that.
So how about this? Every time I die, I'm gonna chug some Dr. Pepper. We're gonna chug, chug, chug, chug.
There's nobody. Is anybody even gonna get out of here?
That sniper just went right through my, almost through my face. Yeah, we have them just trapped in here.
Get me out of here, please.
That guy can't even, like, build me. Like, are you real? Yes, you're real.
Uh, where's my dispenser? Where is my dispenser right now? I don't even know where I put it. Oh, it's up there.
All right, if by two minutes they do not get out of the spawn,
I'm gonna switch teams.
See if we can't make something crazy happen.
Two minutes. You got until two minutes. Come on now. Somebody come out. Oh, we only got 13 seconds.
10, 9, 8, 7,
6,
5,
4,
3. Kick this dude again for no reason and
time to switch.
Can't even switch. I tried. Oh, I died. Yeah. Can I please switch teams?
All right, so we got a team scramble. That's what I like to see. Hopefully the teams are a little more fair now.
I'm not gonna be able to get this sentry out right away.
So let's just go. Hopefully I can put it like one or two back.
I remember every time I die, I got to chug Dr. Pepper. That's what happens. That's the that's the punishment.
But is it really punishment? I find that to be quite a reward to be honest with you.
Let's see if I can't get this in here. Yeah, and this is also right here. Hey, hey, hey, get out of here.
Get off my lawn, you rotten kids.
Hello. I need the teleporter to be here, facing this way.
This is one of my favorite places to put a sentry.
Or I like to go up, like there, like up here. But I was a little late as you saw, so
let's do it. How's that teleporter built? Let's hope so. You,
are you real? I don't think you're real. You're being real. You're acting really odd here. Oh, but that's great.
You, come here you. Hey, follow me this way Pyro. I dare you. A double dog dare you. All I see is a sniper's butt.
Get your butt out of my face. Level three. Good, good, good.
Fantastic. I need to get this. You know what? We're gonna go like this. It's gonna go back here.
I know it's probably gonna get taken up by a spy, but you know what?
Sometimes you just, what is going on here? Oh, we're good. Get that Pyro. Get him. Get that Pyro, you hear?
Scout's going around. What on earth is this guy doing? No, kill him. Nice. Build, build, build, build, build.
Get that to level three.
Level three's the way I wanna be. Make sure you don't get backstabbed by a
spy like this one right here.
You. I'm so paranoid. Whenever I play engineer on upward, I get so paranoid because they really could be literally anywhere because it's so hard to play engineer.
It's so scary. Take that so no spy can get it. Level three and we gotta, I'll help you with that.
Let me help you with that my friend. Let me help you with that. Here we go.
And they, I might move this entry in a second here. Whoa.
Come on, build it, build it, build it, build it. Come on, build this damn thing.
Yeah. Yes. Oh, get it.
Get destroyed.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about. That's what I'm talking about right there. Let's pull up some kills here, baby.
Nobody can destroy the century of doom.
Save my century. Save my century. It's dead.
Oh, no.
Mortis dur soul stealer. No, they're gonna get it. They're gonna get it.
Somebody just, somebody just, spy. Thank you spy. That spy was fantastic. No, don't let him get it.
Don't let him get, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
How did this guy get back here?
Wait, oh my god. This, I thought that was three snipers. Don't, don't let it happen.
I, I don't care if I have to club somebody in the face. Come on. Come on.
They're gonna get it. They're gonna get it. They're gonna get it.
No, they aren't. No, they aren't. Use your body. Use everything.
No, oh, damn it. God damn it, man.
All right, I'm changing up. No, I'm not. Staying engineer. My century's still alive. Where the hell is my century?
Where is, oh, my century's right there.
Come on, little century. Take him out, little century.
Hey, at least if it goes down now, that's okay. I'm okay with that.
I'm, I am okay with that because I got nine revenge crits. I'm okay with that.
Just gotta get something going here. Me and my suit jacket.
Oh, no, no, nothing much. Me and my suit jacket are just having a good time.
Three minutes. We can hold them. Three minutes. Hey, hey.
You, that's it. You know what? I'm sick and tired of this. I'm just gonna go down here.
Who else wants to get crit? Who else wants to get?
Soldier. No. Pyro. They're gonna like steam roll now. This is not cool, man.
What do I got for pyro? Good enough. Good enough.
Just hold them. Hold them. Hold them. Hold them. Hold them. Don't let them get over here. I just saw
a bastard right there. What are you doing? Oh, get clubbed. And I walk right into that.
Are you absolutely? That made up for the second time. Oh, I supposed to drink twice
because I died before that as the engineer. I don't even know if I did this or not. I forget.
This can is empty. That was a bad idea. Chug. Chug. Chug. Ready? Ready?
Come on, everybody. Crit fire. That's the name of the game. Get over here, man. Where's this sniper?
Heal me, please. Somebody heal me. Medic, please heal me. Please. Thank you. Thank you. Who wants
it? Who wants this? Oh, you want this medic? You. You want this? This is what you want? This is what
you want? Oh, whatever. Just get him. Just shoot him. Oh, I'm like burping every eight seconds.
Get rid of that. Get rid of that. What the hell is going on? Did you see how long that just took?
What was that all about? I got nothing to drink. Dude, I was holding. What is my ping? Why can I
don't? Why is tab not working? All right, whatever. I was holding the button down on that mini sentry
for like way too long. It's all right. We got this. This is going to be a GG if I do say so myself.
Maybe not. Maybe not. Maybe not. Maybe not. Get off of this. Get out of here. Oh, it was
worth it. It was worth it. No, they're going to cap it. Oh my god. Get him off that. Get him off it.
Get him off it. Come on, man. Come on, man. Three, two, one second. Yeah. Nice job, guys. Nice job.
You did a fine job tossing your little balls around. So that's going to wrap it up here,
guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, the strongest man in the world. Take care, everybody.