My hello there. Sorry, my mic was a little fucked up.
Can you hear that? Speaking of fucked up, the internet's not having a good time right now,
is it? Uh oh. This is happening two nights ago too, wasn't it?
I can't listen to this thing. If you're wondering what that noise is,
that's the Dreamcast. But can't really do much of anything right now.
Figured that we were just kind of going over a bad internet bump, but it's not the case right now.
Dropped a thousand frames in the first three minutes of the stream. That's not good.
We'll give it a few minutes, otherwise I am gonna have to get off and call,
because this would be the second stream in a row. We've had about two straight good months
of no internet problems, so. Anyways, if we do get to stream, the idea is,
can I like, all right, it's gonna, all I have to do is cover the vent. Where the fan comes,
just cover the fan with like a piece of tape, and then you can't hear it, right?
I forgot how fucking loud of Dreamcast is tonight. Sorry, I'm getting thrown off a
little bit here from the internet problem. But those of you that remember, it's a nostalgia,
it's a nostalgia trip tonight. I'll show you just how much of a nostalgia trip in about
five seconds when you see the date that's on the screen. Set up a date and time for the Dreamcast
12-27-1998. 2008, 2018, this is 21 years ago. What's today's date? Can you, are you even
allowed to go past the year 2000? What's the final year you're allowed to put in for Dreamcast?
I guess it can go as far as you want.
I wasn't even born yet? All right, let's keep it nostalgic. No, wait, isn't that gonna fuck up
like the internal clock or something? What if I play a game that needs the correct date?
Well, this is not connected to the internet, so it doesn't matter. All right, today is,
uh, what the hell is today? January 20, it's January 25th, 1998, and it is, is this a 24-hour
clock? It is. It is three, four, five, six a.m., seven a.m., eight a.m., nine a.m.,
ten a.m., eleven a.m., twelve noon, one, two, three, twenty-one.
All right, that looks good. Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes! Oh no, wait, what?
Where was the, the intro? Where's the Ted Talk intro? I pressed back?
I gotta restart the console. All right, well, we're good, right? What about music?
What's even on here? Oh, I gotta show this on camera, too, because, whoa!
That's me, uh, okay, so again, I gotta be careful here, uh, because that is,
so take a look what happens, right? It take, it captures the last frame that you did.
So for like, I gotta remember, like, hold on, whatever, I don't fucking care. All right,
I should be in sync now, whatever, I don't fucking give a shit. You think anything
embarrasses me anymore? Not really. So here's the Dreamcast controller, if you don't, if
you've never seen this before. I wasn't naked on camera, okay? I, look, I was going like
this, I was like this, and I leaned up and you didn't, you just couldn't see,
I, these were bunched up under my chin. I just didn't, look, I didn't have a shirt on,
but it was like closed up. Anyways, okay, here's the Dreamcast controller. The interesting thing
about, I can't even do like a look and welcome to the stream tutorial, look at the Dreamcast
controller now. It's fine, whatever. I don't think anything fucking embarrasses me anymore.
The interesting, the interesting thing about the Dreamcast controller is, if I can get it out,
shave your armpits. I, I will. I actually did that. My armpit hair grows exponentially.
So the interesting thing about the Dreamcast is this thing comes out. Isn't that interesting,
folks? This is the memory card and the memory card is also a little screen. And you put
that in here. Look, there's a slot right there. You can have two of these in there
if you didn't know. Take a look at that. It snaps in and there it is. Every game has a little
screen. Every game has fucking long armpit hair and every game turns on their webcam
with a frame of them with no clothes on. So anyways, let's get started here. We have to
reset it so we can hear the Ted Talk intro. I'm going to put it in. The reason why I'm
not going to start with Tony Hawk is because if I start with Tony Hawk 2,
that's going to be the whole stream. And I can't just do the whole stream as Tony Hawk.
So there were a handful of other great games for the Dreamcast that are exclusive.
Like for instance, Survival Horror. There were a handful of Survival Horror games that
only came out on the Dreamcast. Like The Ring, Blue Stinger, Carrier. There's at least three
or four. We've also got Dynamite Cop, which is one of my favorite arcade games ever made.
And we've got some other random fucked up stupid shit. So I'm going to probably have
to say we're going to start with The Ring. We have to. This is The Ring. This is the game.
This is what the movie was based on. What? I don't know why the fuck. Logitech and OBS.
Why did you do that? So Logitech and, uh, okay. Here it is. This is The Ring,
Terror's Realm, exclusive to Dreamcast. Can't get it anywhere else.
Let's go ahead and do this. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes.
It didn't even do it. Why? What? Do it. Here it comes. It's not even going to do it.
Wait, I can't reset it right now. Listen, this is like somebody's cutting meat at the
deli. Listen to this shit. Hey, you want some salami? I'll get it for you.
Is that good? Is that thickness good? I gotta move this thing down.
Please, you have to help me. First Dreamcast game of the night
is going to be The Ring, Terror's Realm, and Dreamcast. That's what that's true.
I need to, this is so unbearable. I need to fucking move this down and I can put
like a blanket on it. Let me put it down here. It's too loud. I can't even concentrate.
Okay, that's better. This looks like a SNES menu. Yeah, it does.
All right, let's, uh, let's get started. This is The Ring. 1991.
New game, low game options. Nickelodeon presents The Ring, Terror's Realm.
Okay, uh, I'm just going to play, I think. Meg? Robert, get the job? Yeah, I'll be working
with you starting tomorrow. So I guess I'll be seeing you soon. Really? That's great.
So why don't we go out for a celebratory drink? Okay. I'll be ready. Promise? Promise.
Bye for now. Is he going to watch The Ring video? She thinks she is. She hasn't any idea
of how important this project is, but it's not a goal. What's happening? Robert, he didn't
sound so pleased, even though it's been quite a while since we spoke. He's absolutely missed
a thick head. Easy! What the fuck was that? Well, today's the day. He has to make up for it.
Don't go out of a garage like that. You got to slow down. It's a new Resident Evil 2.
This is the GTA driver. Why is it so dark? Robert? Yeah, I think we're just gonna have
to do it that way. And that's just it. Hey, hey, miss. No, I'm sorry. You can't
come in here. You're gonna have to get out of here. Or do you live here? What's
happened, officer? What's happened, officer? I'm asking you a question. Do you live here?
Hello? Miss? What the fuck? Hey, hey, stop. That punch sound. They only had like four
punch sound effects. I got hit sound. You okay, lady? Okay, this is way I need to
increase the brightness or something. Meg, Meg, what's going on over there?
Like, hey, man, what's happening here? Hold on a moment, sir. I know the two of them.
They're friends. What happened? I don't believe this. I see. Oh, Meg. Could you
explain your relationship to either her or the victim? This is like a bunch of
YouTubers made this or something. I'm Jack, and this is Robert's girlfriend, Meg.
Oh, I see. Well, I'm sorry. What happened to Robert? Actually, we don't yet exactly
know what happened to him this evening. You don't know? Isn't this a murder? It's
unlikely to be a homicide case. Not a murder? Then what's that? Did you see his
face? What's happened? Oh, my God. Well, we'll get to the bottom of this.
I'm still alive. I'll work for this company. I'm still alive. Don't worry. I
shouldn't mourn your death forever. Right. I can't help it. The Dreamcast is so loud. Hold on. Wait.
Wait, wait a minute. Tell him it gets worse.
Make it stop. Here? I can fix this. This is my room starting today. It's a weird feeling.
When do I get to control the game? Robert. No good comes from me moping around all the time.
I have to do my best. Is this the same lady in the cutscene that we just watched?
Okay, I'm walking now. It's tank controls, which that's fucking fantastic.
What the fuck? Oh, that's sprint. Is it, though? How did I just do that? I have no idea
how I'm doing that. Is it reverse tank? How do I get out of the door? Get the phones ringing.
Hello. Meg, it's Jack. Are you settled in? Yes, today's my first day. I'm so sorry to make you
worry so much. Don't worry about it. I know you're going through tough times and I'm like
this. No. At times like this, it's easier to be worried about others. I'm reading this so
wrong. Oh yeah, by the way, did you look at Robert's computer? Computer? I see his laptop
here. Something the matter with it? No, actually I heard a slightly strange story. A strange story?
About a CQC lab. I'm not pressing any buttons. Died at the same time in the same way at Robert.
Same time in the same way. I don't think it's a coincidence I've never seen anyone die like
that. You're right, but what does that have to do with the computer? Yeah, about the computer.
Both of them were found dead in front of their computer. Jack, now isn't that a coincidence?
No, I have more. Robert and both lab workers running a program called Ring on their computers.
Hang? Yeah, hang. The police thought it was suspicious. They tried to analyze it,
but no matter what they did, it wouldn't boot. The program wouldn't boot? Yeah, apparently this
is just two AI talking to each other. This is just learning English. Take this text right
here and add the learning English YouTube video bullshit on here. Yeah, apparently. In any case,
I'll check up on the details about it now. But until then, I think it's better if you
didn't touch the computer. Don't touch the computer? But it doesn't boot, right? Besides,
Jack, are you saying that Robert died thanks to a computer program? You know, I am a
scientist. I would rather understand. I would understand if it was a virus in CQC, but from
a computer, I know, but I have a bad feeling about this. You're a worrywart. I'll be fine.
In any case, I'll call you again when I find something out. Thanks. Now I'm taking over
Robert's job starting today. That's good. I'm sure Robert's happy about that. I don't think
Robert's happy about being dead. Why would you be happy about this? Thanks for everything,
Jack. Yeah, I'll call you again. Just talking to the fax machine. All right, bye. That's not
the phone. That's a calculator. Okay, that was, let's go. I gotta examine Robert's computer,
right? Am I about to watch the Ring video? Ring, the killer computer program. This is
silly. This is what the movie was based on. This is it. Don't watch it! Don't! I don't
want to watch this! Meg. Uh, by the way, guys, everybody that's watching right now,
I'm really sorry, but it's seven days from now. I think we're gonna be around.
The reason why Robert died might be hidden inside this. I'm gonna try.
There she go. Uh-oh. We're all gonna get ringed. Here it comes. This is the Ring video.
It's people in ice cubes. Wait, why are we in here? This is the Ring video?
I booted up a program called Ring on the computer. Anyway, I should investigate. What are
you doing? What I'm doing, booting up this computer. What are you saying? Well, in the
situation we're in, I can understand you're getting confused. The situation making me
wear this and all. Where in the world is this? This place? This is our battlefield against
them. Them? What are you saying? Oh, I'm in the computer game. We have no time for this.
One of them has snuck in here. I'll check the first floor. You go check the second.
Check the second floor? Enough of this already. Is that gun you're holding a fake?
Quit yacking and go kill them off. If you're too slow, they'll get us.
Kill them? But you're the one that made me hold this gun. There's no way I can use
it without learning how. I'm appalled that someone would stand here without knowing how
to use a gun. Are you with the informants? This is just learning English. Here's a
quick rundown. Keep your ears open. First try pushing left trigger. That turns the flashlight
on. You can move it with just complete darkness there for a second. Okay. If you keep the
flashlight on, they'll find you immediately. So be careful not to try pushing right
trigger. Now shoot me! That's your aim. The gun automatically targets within 45 degrees
in front of you, but it only targets where the flashlight shines. The gun shoots if you
push the A button while aiming. Try aiming and firing. Yeah, that's it. That gun has a
laser sight, so it should be easy to tell where you're aiming. Be careful, some weapons
don't have sights. Next, equipping weapons. The status screen appears when you push.
What does this have to do with the ring? Somebody came up with an idea for the ring
for a video game, and then they realized that what are you supposed to do besides
watch the movie and die? So they put you inside of a computer program, which is
like an FPS shooter game, and this is us watching it, I guess. I have no idea. This
is Resident Evil. They were like, yeah, I guess just make Resident Evil again somehow.
Item. There's a handgun and a knife, and we are fine. Everything is just fine.
S item. Still dropping frames. This is kind of consistently sort of awful.
It's, oh, it's okay, but not good. We checked, right, and last changing viewpoints.
If you push the Y button, it'll shift to first-person view. Change the line of sight
with the analog thumb pad and look around. You return to this view and you let go of
the Y button. Oh, you have to hold it. Those are the basic controls of the game.
Anything else you need to learn on your own? Do you want me to go over that? No,
don't go over that again. Go check out the second floor. Be very careful. What's this?
How do I pick step up? You found a healing jelly. Pick it up. Yes.
Why would you ever play this game? Is there a speedrun with this game with all,
all the lights turned off? I can't use the analog either, and there's no fun
Dreamcast thing in the middle. What's upstairs? Oh, I forgot. It's an old game. You have to
actually load. It's too dark. Give me the healing jelly. All right, this is actually that the
perspective is actually kind of scary, although it's hard to even determine what the hell
my character is in these hallways. I'm gonna get jumped out. What was that? Oh,
flashlight in the screen, I guess. What is this? There aren't any enemies here.
This is stupid. That's the enemy. He wants me to kill that. He's reckless. I have to do it,
I guess. All right. Who bullets over here? It's like a book or a briefcase or a bullets. What
is it? Handgun bolts. Okay. More handgun bolts. Good. Next. Hold on. Not yet. Not quite.
We have to get past the first tutorial area. So did I do it? Is that the only thing he
wanted me to do? At least give me seven minutes in this game or seven, well, seven days. Never
mind. That would be a bad idea. I hate tank controls so much. Here's your five second loop
of the same song. I defeated the upstairs enemy, but now how do I? What? My body.
I feel I'm getting pulled pulling out is what's happening.
So now I die in seven days because I watched the shitty Resident Evil
game. That was the ring. Uh oh. I passed out this program. What was that about?
Ring? It's just a game. Really? Jack should hold off with his jokes once in a while.
Jack? Sheesh. I have no, I have to give him a piece of my mind.
Hello? Oh, here it is. Yeah. Seven days. Here it comes.
Seven. Dead. Oh. Seven more days. Seven. Only seven days.
Power outage, a crank call, and a weird program.
Seven more days. I'm going to die in seven days. You've got to be kidding.
Oh, because he loaded a fucking Doom II box here. Open the box. Nothing in here.
Healing jelly in the office. Nothing of interest here. Nothing in the sink.
Uh oh. It's Chris. Excuse me. My name is Chris. Are you Meg? Hello, Chris. I'm Meg.
Meg Rainman. It is a pleasure to meet you. You don't have to be so formal. My pleasure
to meet you. I know it's sudden, but the chief is asking for you. A guide to the chief's
office. I can't take, I can't. Sorry. It's fine with me. He-he, you're acting so formal. Well,
then this way. It really is. It's Chris. Meg. If the boss's name is Peter,
and there's a lowest involved too, then we've got the whole family. Oh, Brian.
Chris. Meg. Please tell me this guy's name is Brian. Or Peter. Nice to meet you,
chief. I'm Meg Rainman. Sorry I was late. I'm at your services starting today.
Chief Brian. What's his name? Thanks for coming. I'm looking forward to your work.
I'm sorry we caused you so much trouble with this case. What are you saying? We were the
ones who were serviced by Robert. It was a shame to end up that way. We have to work hard now to
make up for our loss of Robert. Yes, I think so too. By the way, about Robert. You heard that
three lab members, including him, passed away? Yes, I heard that they all passed away at the
same exact time. That's right. For such an accident, there is a high chance that it was a
virus. I assume so. This is the CDC after all. Yes, this is the best facility against disease
for the public. No, for the world. I don't even know what he said. We are investigating on our
own but cannot figure out the cause of death. However, the executives are fretful. They want to
make an explanation as soon as possible. I can't. I have to turn the music off. Just now an
evacuation order has been issued. They're shutting this lab down. They've prohibited
us from leaving the facility. It's speech jamming. Prohibit us from leaving? That means
you could say we have been quarantined. Impossible. I'm so sorry about this happening
on your birthday, but it's not that unusual for this stuff. Well, the evacuation order
for the whole town is, rest assured, it will only be for two, three days. All right,
I understand. Fortunately, you are free to roam in the facility. Have a look around the place.
Right now we're checking for virus leakage from the basement. You know, just like my water cooler
broke. Look at my virus leakage. I'm gonna call like an HVAC guy. All right, then Chris. Yes.
Mute the music. I can't. This card will be your key and your identification within
the facilities. Make sure you don't lose it. Yes, I will be careful.
Look around. Excuse me.
There is no, I can't do it.
There is no muting the music, guys. It's here forever. Doesn't open.
The reference room. It doesn't open without a key.
All right, let's go to the kitchen.
I like the music. Can I use the fire extinguisher?
You know, it's funny because I'm just like in poker, right? I got a deck of cards and I got
a hand. I got a good hand. I'm gonna fold a couple of bad hands. Forget this reference.
I can't talk with this music playing. I'm taking my headphones out to say this.
So, you never want to show your hand in poker, okay? You guys don't know. Right now you can see
like, this is like a 10, right? You know, I have like a jack, I got a queen, I got a king,
and I also got an ace. And they're the same suit, which is the Dreamcast.
So don't worry. Okay, now I can fucking put my headphones in.
What the fuck are you doing? All right, here's, okay, if we go back into the game,
if we have to go back into the ring video game, then I will change to the next game.
But, hold on. The locker room, I see. This facility is sure well equipped.
I have to kill the ring. I'm not going to complete this game. I literally had to mute
the stream. Oh my god. All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll get it
out of here. Hold on. I first need to do the Resident Evil, open the door,
transition loading screen. Wait, this is, uh, Lucino. This is the men's locker room.
Do you want anything? Sorry, I made a mistake. Yeah, I didn't know today's my first day.
You know, that you can get out now. Sorry. Okay, I'm gonna save everybody here. There.
It's nice to have nobody around. No changes at all. Do I have to go back in the computer?
There's nothing much here. All right, here we go. I'm gonna go back in the computer.
I'm gonna log back in. Nothing happened. I can still hear it. Okay, I got, I activated,
I activated the event that I need to activate. Phone rings. Pick it up. Has it, I've been
walking around for a full day. I heard there's a possibility of a virus leak from the CDC.
It's the top headline on every news show. It's only a possibility. They said it wasn't too
uncommon around here, so don't worry. They say it's not uncommon. Anyway, Jack, that ring you
mentioned earlier, it was just a game. That program booted? I had no problems, and there
can be no way that a computer program can kill someone. Nothing really happened. Nothing.
You worry too much. Although, speaking of something happening, I had a prank call right
afterwards. All right, call. Yes. Hey, there was a weird word on the screen.
It said dead. What do you mean weird word? It said dead. I think it meant game over.
That's not too funny. Anyway, did you figure anything out? All right, well,
every time somebody plays Dark Souls, that's like, that's not funny. I don't like that.
That's right. Apparently, Robert's body was handed over to the CDC.
The CDC. I wonder if it's to find out the cause of death.
But now, I guess I'll be able to find out directly. Thank you for your
Dark Souls reference in every stream. Don't go overboard. I'll call you again if I find anything.
Talk to you later. Yes. Robert. Am I gonna get another phone call? For now,
I should ask the chief. Oh my god. Not much longer, I promise. They were the ones
that Robert's body was handed over to. I know the chief is looking out for me still.
I wish he had told me about this. First thing now is to go talk to the chief.
That's why I opened the door. How many redundancies are there in one video?
No, not much longer. Don't you guys know the rules? When we do like a retro game night
on an old console, it's 40 minutes. We have to give it at least 30 to 40 minutes.
Yeah, that's the rule. Where's the chief's office? There's no information on here.
Information? What information? I don't see any information.
Where's the chief's office? You don't get a hamburger from a restaurant and take
one bite and then put it down. No, it's two bites. The first bite is to go,
hold on. That's all right. No, I don't know. And then the second bite is to
determine if you're gonna get food poisoning, right? And the third or fourth bite is if you're
gonna get food poisoning but you don't care because you're hungry and you know it's
gonna happen anyway, so you just eat the rest of the rotten turkey sandwich that was in
the trash. Does anybody remember where the chief's office is? All right, all right.
It's been like 40 minutes. It has. All right. Oh, I gotta go. I'm on the wrong floor.
You guys are good. Oh wait, there's a new character introduction here.
That's okay. No, that's Peter and Megan. This is a localization joke. There's Peter.
We found the localization of humor. Yep, that happened. Yes. This is somebody just,
this is 1998, okay? What happened was the person localizing this, wherever they were,
just, what's, what was popular in the West right now? Family Guy was just barely taken
off as a popular show, wasn't it? Whatever, just name them. People in the West love Family
Guy, all right? Hold on, wait. Family Guy came out in 1999. When did this game come out?
There's no way. No, yeah, there is Family Guy. When did, when did, when did the game come out,
though? Well, I don't care about this. I'm looking at the front, okay? This came out,
the copyright on the disc is 2000. So not 1998, 2000. When did the first episode of Family
Guy air? 1999. So yeah, it had to be. All right, let's move on. So that was a survival
horror. That was the Ring, Terror's Realm. I'm going to put that in the collector's dish,
because it's a collector's item. So I think we got to move on from there. We got to play
a good one, right? And I'm going to play right now, one of my favorite arcade games
ever made. So Strapping, you might be here for, this is going to be at least a 40 minute
thing here. Going in next is none other than Dynamite Cop. This is the best arcade game
ever made. It actually, I think it was called Die Hard in the arcades. Maybe we'll actually get
to hear the intro. Wouldn't that be great? Did you just say that this game was bad?
This game's bad? What? Here we go. Ted Talk. Today, we're going to talk about
setting goals. Here we go. My favorite fucking arcade. Caution, a memory card is required
in order to save Dynamite Cop data. Please select a door without a, yeah, it's this one.
Now prepare yourself for Dynamite Cop. We have a situation down there. Some modern day pirates
have hijacked a huge cruiser. They're holding 2,000 hostages inside, including the president's
daughter. We have to invade the ship, clear the pirates, and rescue the hostages, especially
the president's daughter. I'm on it. There ain't even no title screen. That's how good this game
is. You just go. Some of your favorite, some of your video games you like have fucking title
screens. Oh, there's, there's, I love this game so much. Here's the title screen. Never mind.
I'm going to beat this fucking game on stream. All right, let's go to other,
just for a second here. Options. Use what? Options. Every time you go into a beat-em-up
style game like this, you always want to make sure that you check to make sure that
there's no, you know what, I'm like the lowest amount of rests.
And some of you boomers will know what I'm talking about here. Dynamite Cop.
Ooh, there's more. Wait, there's two? This DLC campaign? I guess we're doing this one.
All right, I gotta pick. Wait, that guy, why does that guy have like a, I need to see
this. Wait, is this even the same? This is the same name. What? No, is this, is this
right? Am I, is this the right game? That guy has like a little animal on his shoulder.
Okay, I don't know what the controls are. Hold on. Where's kick? That's grab. Yep,
there's the suplex. That's kick. Okay, here we go. They all do the same scream when they die?
Yep, I remember. This is the tutorial mission. Yeah, it's different pitches of the same sound.
There's weapons, there's guns. I think there's quick time events too, if I remember.
Give me that. Come here, come here, come here. There's a gun. There's a turtle. Who's the
turtle guy? Wait, give me the soda. Yeah, it's a heal. I remember. I think I'm super mode right
now. DDT, double DDT, double DDT into a scoopslam. Can't get it out of that one. Anything else?
Let's go. The guns! If they have guns, you're in trouble. Captain Gonzalez. Oh boy.
Jump away, jump away, dash dash dash. I don't even, I got him. That's a power up.
Where is he going? Bazooka. Give me the airship missile. Oh, are they supposed to?
I just dropped a fucking nuke. Now I remember why they love this game so much.
Give me the lawn chair. Anybody else? No, that's the little mini boss. Give me the
heels though. This is in your face, fast paced. What? Why is she inside the suitcase?
This game was in arcades, but they kind of remade it.
So this was a die hard game, I think. It was in the arcade, they licensed it,
then they ported it to Dreamcast. Entirely different from what I understand. I could be
wrong and I might be remembering that completely incorrectly, but I think it is.
Anybody else? Fix the audio. What's going on with the audio?
Audio's fucked up? What do you mean? Out of sync? You're talking about like my voice to
the game or you're talking about like the game audio is not synced right now? It's the game
audio. Okay, hold on. So you're hearing sounds first. Oh, wait, kick! Got it. Now that sounds.
Oh fuck, he scoops lemon. His head's on sticks? Shit, he's got the head.
No, I don't want to die. There's different combinations you can do as well. Oh fuck.
Oh fuck. I believe, I believe like 80 and deep. Holy fuck, he's got a double.
Pick him up. Off the ground. Oh, I remember this. Oh, this game's so much fun. Hair sample?
What have we got? That's the end of that guy. I think I got a boss coming up here. Give me
the food. Stay up here. Is it a loaf of bread or is it a missile? I don't know.
Shit. It's a French roll. Stream saved. What happened? No, he doesn't have a gun. How do you
throw? Looks like there's a throw button I think where I can just with it.
Why the fuck did I throw this thing? I don't want to use the bread anymore. Get rid of it.
Why do I have an axe? Food. I need to eat. Eat the cake. What? Oh, throwing the cake at
the bread. Oh, fuck. Cake. Just eat it. Eat cake. There it is. Just lost all the health I just got.
He just linked me. Come on, man. You good? I'm good. Oh, the chef. The burners turn on.
I don't think they do. Food. Give me the apples. Just eat them. There's got to be more
food in here than just fucking god. He just throws dynamite in his own kitchen.
Oh, fuck. Crab walks back up. Any more food in here? Donkey Kong barrel. How many? I think I got
three continues. Give me more. I need more environmental stuff. Bridge? Those grenades?
Give me the grenades. Yep. You can't eat grenades, can you? Should be doing way more
damage. Shouldn't it? What else we got? Take the whole thing. Any more burners? All right,
back up, back up, back up, back up. Can I reach in here and grab anything? I don't think so.
I think I got all the environmental stuff out of the way. Oh, dropping frames again. It's
going to happen. Once this frame is over, I've got to make a few phone calls,
because this is the second day in a row. Well, second stream in a row where we've
had problems. So, going to have to get somebody else out here again. I'm not even
going to get up from that, I don't think. No, it's not. It's a profit with the internet
here. And it's very distracting. It's very annoying. I've got to get a full health pack, too.
Yeah, we'll probably drop like 50,000 frames this stream.
But, whatever. Not much I can do about it, unfortunately. This is dying my cock,
those of you wondering. That was not graceful at all. It just fell out of there.
Get him! He shouldn't be able to do that, that's not fair.
I still can't. All right, finally he comes up. Trying to aim at him.
Throw him this way. Is it really just getting worse? God.
It's like I still bet he died twice. This is a good gun. I think I can bounce him around.
Come here. So, it's hard to try to pay attention to two things at the same time.
Is it like, unwatchable? It seems just consistently not. And right when we get to
the crab enemies, really. You're gonna give me this internet bullshit when I'm doing one
of my favorite Dreamcast games with the fucking crabs. That's unbelievable.
Come here. Get him. Give me the piece of meat. 71 hundred fucking frames drop.
God damn, it's been one hour. Ah! So aggravating. Let's go. Take that suitcase.
Oh, I wasn't even... I just broke my fucking neck. I just... whatever.
Give me the black box. I'll stand on those.
No! I was trying to juggle him. Everybody wants the black box. So bad. Come here.
Is something in there still? There's still one missile left. Nice.
Really? Do I get infinite continues? I might get infinite continues. This is great.
It doesn't even matter how bad you are. Make sure you... a nuclear bomb does not get rid of
this guy. Two nukes. Okay, you're dead. I'm not gonna fail this one. I'm gonna be able to
pay attention. Hit him with a wrench! I told you, this game is insane. Plug?
Power, power, power. All right, I got power up. Right in the middle. I got boxing gloves.
Don't kill the octopus. The octopus has to die. Jump! Die! Help pack. Oh, you gotta see
this though. This is great. So I'm... I'm kind of confused. Are they not aware
that she's inside of the crate? And he just... he's bringing his just pink suitcase around.
He doesn't know that she's in there. I think that's what's going on. He just carries his
luggage everywhere apparently. That's a nice chicken in there. It's a monster rancher. Monster.
Dead. I can't go in there, but they can come out. Can I open this? I might be able
to break it. I need to do some more suplexes and stuff, but I don't know. I forget how to do them.
I wasn't trying to kill him. I was just trying... I was trying to open his crate.
Oh god. All right, come on down. I'll get you with the pendulum.
Where did you get the gun? You just have a pistol? How can you get...
You just pulled that out of nowhere. They split every time.
My god, that hurts. Don't even let him get up. That guy just tried to raid me.
Did he block the bullets with his hands?
Can I get Boko swords? I'm trying to do other moves. I remember this shitty game.
Shitty game. Who said this game was shitty? This is a classic slot machine. This is such
random shit in this game. I just got pizza. It's a hand toss. Let's get rid of this thing.
Oh, pepper. Can I eat the pepper?
He just makes him sneeze. What are those recovery moves?
That's like a horrible new trailer. Get pulled out of the room.
Okay, can I do something with this slot machine? Come on. Seven. Seven.
No! Do it again. Give me something cool. If he pulls it, does he get the whatever's in there?
No, I don't want to leave here without getting the jackpot. Here I come. No. Spin it again.
Do it again. The machine actually broke. Why? What the fuck? That's unfortunate.
Jervin has played Quiet Man and Dynamite Man, but this is Dynamite Cop. Two back-to-backs.
I gotta dump him into the ocean. I don't know why these were so much harder to do in the
arcade. Maybe it's because I was 14 or something. But I remember that was a big deal. Did I just
kick that guy into the balls? Bow and arrow is cool. Double machine guns?
Make sure you don't sharpen an axe with your hands, guys. That's a bad fucking idea.
Infinite continues! That was stylish. I sharpened my axes. I thought I could pick up the
mast. Sharpen my axes with my face.
All right, this guy. I was gonna say this guy shouldn't even let me.
No! He's breaking up my combos! You dick! Stop! Why is my combos breaking?
This way. Would you classify this game as a reverse Bayonetta?
The more damage I take, my clothes come off.
As an Bayonetta, the more damage you do, your clothes come off. Now you're doing this.
Dammit. That didn't work. Come here. Come here! Got it. Now it's time for the final boss. I'm ready.
He said, step on her head! You were in my suitcase! You threw my beach towels out of
there to get in there, didn't you? How did he change his body? Uh-oh, this is not gonna go well.
Standard combo. That's it. Where did he get the gun? He's shooting at his face.
That's wildly unfair. Watch out! How are you supposed to dodge that? This is the
way that they farm quarters. Yeah, I remember this. This is like the... I remember me and
my friend on the car ride, home of my mother's car, talking about to each other, back and forth.
Like, you know, arcades are so fucking stupid, man. That's like a way that they'd just be
guaranteed that they take quarters from you, because you're gonna die like five times.
I really had that conversation. Ask him! He lost his sword. See? Look.
All right, let's go, man! Come on! Don't let the continue go down! And then sometimes
you have to debate with your friend whether or not you want to put another quarter in.
You're... you both put like seven and a half dollars into the game, right?
And then the countdown is happening. If you don't continue, you start from the very beginning
again, and you have the debate with your buddy whether or not you want to move on to
a different game or you've got to finish this, we've got to beat it. And you have five fucking
seconds to figure it out. Oh no, he ripped off my clothes! Dodge, right? No, don't bring
back those memories. Got him. Great cutscene. I didn't skip it. A little smoking cigarette?
Why did she just kick me in the head? Wait, what was that traitor's shit in the end?
The island is still there. He didn't even get rid of the island.
Some other bad guy will take up shop in there.
There's two more chapters. Two more DLCs. Thank you for saving my life again.
Roundhouse kick to the part of your head where it's going to kill you, right? That heel went
directly into the back portion of my head where my skull connects to my neck. That is
dead. That is... you're dead. Is this supposed to be ominous that I lose?
It freezes at such a perfect time. All right, let's go. Let's try. Let's see the other campaigns.
Let's go. Let's go one, two, three right down the aisle here. Let's do a gene.
Back to the ring. No, I'm beating all these. Mission one, mission two.
Wait, this is the same mission. Oh, look at that kick though. Oh, the girl is great.
Gene Ivy is great. Look at these moves. Now I understand a few things about this game that
I didn't understand before. The thing that I understand is one.
Yeah, that's the whole game. But what's the other one though? What's the showdown one?
This game is like 40... this game's not even 30 minutes long. They were just farming
quarters. Oh, I just want everyone to do me a quick favor and just remember just how much
money this game was. I severely underestimated just how much content was in this game.
I think this game was like somewhere around a hundred dollars to get. I think. Oops. It's like
a very rare Dreamcast game and I thought it was going to be like... I'm keeping it and
guess what? It's an asset now and it's going to appreciate the value. And then 30 more years
I will give Dynamite Cup to somebody in my family. Hey, check out this Dreamcast system.
All these are going to appreciate the value. No, get the... This is different. No, this is
different. This is different, guys. It is. It's different. Yeah, it's the same enemies
but you fight them in different sequences. Can you get hit by those? The power-ups,
come on. P, P, P, P, P, P, P. Yeah, this didn't happen in the last game. The same cutscenes?
This time she's under the bed, not in the suitcase.
Different variations of the cutscene. Procedurally generated. Procedurally generated
hiding girl. That's good. Okay, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme. No, gimme, gimme, gimme. No,
I don't want the spear. You sissy. No! I have a lighter. What does a lighter do?
There's gotta be one that cycles between items, right? Let's see if I can grab him.
He died. Let's see what it just does. Just uppercut. In the bathroom? Yeah,
okay. These are new environments, guys.
I'm trying to do my best impression.
Hey, I'm available for consultation work. It's a deep cough.
Sneeze herself to death. I told you sneezes are very dangerous.
Uh oh. Oh god, the clothes are coming off. For those of you guys that are wondering,
I'm gonna move to the next game. This was very expensive, so I'm gonna get,
I'm gonna get my money's worth, because I want to play through the game.
I can't just play this for five, ten minutes and then go on. No, I wanna get, I hate,
I wanna get my money's worth. I don't remember what jump is. All right, here we go.
It's the, is this the same? This is not the same boss. This is a different boss.
It's, I'm so confused. All right, give me the fish. Can I eat it? Oh, that's a lot of tuna.
Somebody count the deaths from the last, anybody have an opportunity to do that?
How many times did I die last time? Because we're gonna determine how expensive this was.
We'll see if it's the same amount of money that it was on Amazon. Those grenades.
No way, no way, did you see that combo? He's going to Evo next weekend.
Evo's in August. Evo next weekend. Let's see, where, where, where is she now?
Under the bed, in the suitcase. Hanging somewhere, like from the rafters or something,
like peeking over the rafters. Still not graceful.
I just arrested that person.
How did I do that? I don't know how to, how did I arrest that person? Pizza, pizza face.
What would you rob? You can only do that with a handgun.
Empty your pockets. You're, you're not only, not only are you under arrest,
but I want the money in your wallet. Empty your pockets, pizza face. That's a little wild.
And then, perhaps this time, they are sharks. Still aquatic in nature, but not,
not in the land. He slid. Don't start singing the baby shark thing.
That was unbelievable. That was essentially breaking every bone. Baby shark. Why would
you say that? I didn't say it, somebody else did, and I just, let's go, applied to it.
Still under the bed. Okay, still under the bed.
Can we not get her out? I am really confused, because they took her in the
suitcase last time, so she's still. No, I want to freeze.
Assholes. So many broken bones. This person is not. Have I died a few times in this one?
Just give me the nuclear bombs. It's fun to shoot these in here,
knowing that only one of them will blow up the whole island. Don't shoot.
I said no, Luigi, because he has a green costume on.
Still the same octopus encounter. No, no, dodge it. That's why I need friends
to play. Somebody distracts the squid while other people fight it.
It looks like it could hit the head, too.
There's guns over here. Give me the other, whatever this is.
Oh, the July popsicle thing. What are you dropping from the ceiling? Is it gonna blast
them? The squid wants to fight you. Well, it's happening. Super deep talk. I love it.
Can I arrest the squid? No. Imagine you could put his arms behind his back.
Wait. Ooh. Now what do we have here? Don't move. I was under the bed, too. I was also hiding.
Where did that guy come from? Oh, that was so hard. That was so hard. Even more casino games.
Good. Well, we found the speedrun character. You just need a handgun. What's this? Coin bucket?
Oh, the casino.
This is back when casinos still had, like, coin buckets, isn't it?
Break his neck. I'm dead.
Throw this away. How do you? I wish I just threw. I'm not sure there is. All right, arrest.
You're under arrest. My god. Why do you have reach across the whole map?
Yes. You're on. Now I can't even arrest them. Caution. I missed the top.
That was awesome. There's another one. There goes Nat Pagel. Those guys are just bringing
booze to a party. You get these last little snippets. You just stabbed him in the
fucking skull with this. No. Give me the gun. Arrest.
Come with that. Can I pick up the piano? That's unfortunate. Maybe I can break it.
When you get powers up, you get extra moves. That's good.
Piano. Give me that. You died before I could do anything. Don't shoot me.
Only have four continues left. Same guy. Stupid fools. Your captain is long dead.
He's fish bait by now. I'm so broken up by that. I only have four. I only have four
continues left. You're right. Is that for real? Shit, it is real. All right. No more.
I can't fucking run. I actually have to beat this. What the fuck? That was unbelievable.
Ah. Oh, come on. What's the stamina bars? Why do you have a bigger stamina bar than me?
Yeah, you're trying to fucking farm coins from me. That's not what I want to pick up.
Rhinoblast in coming.
Three continues. No. I tried to dodge it. I'm trying to get away from you when you do that.
No. He gets like a guaranteed hit. Give me the cheats. I got the cheats.
It's gonna spin again. No, he's not. Back suplex him. Throw him over the... What the fuck was
that? He just shoved a meatball out of his eye. Right in the face. No. Yep, you gotta hit him.
One credit left. I can't fuck this up. Just play it safe. That's not safe. I just did.
See the new ending. Thank you for saving my life again. Okay. Wait a minute. He's done.
What? What a hacker. There's no way. Okay. To double click on your desktop and open up
hackprogram.exe, it'd probably take... You ever opened up Photoshop? A program that's that
elaborate. It's gonna take like 30 to 40 seconds to open. There it is. What is this
game and how do I play it? This is... Dynamite Cop is for the Dreamcast. It's only on Dreamcast.
There's only two ways you could possibly play this game. You have to get a Dreamcast
or you have to emulate the game. And emulation is fairly difficult, but it was really the
only two possible ways to play it. All right, here we go. Game over. Emulation is fine.
Um, it really depends on what emulator because I've tried to use like PS2 era plus PS3 era
emulators before. And they're not quite there yet. They function and some of them
function fairly well, but for the sake of making sure that there's no problems,
I've emulated before and it just doesn't work out well. All right, we got... We're
gonna try... Well, we're gonna do the last mission. We're gonna go to Eddie's and we're
gonna do mission three. So this is from underwater. The only emulated games that you
physically own. That's pretty much how it works. Plus, I like having the actual physical thing
here. Having a Dreamcast or having a PlayStation 2 is... Can I ride that?
Why do I only get four credits? What's with the four credits? You seeing that?
I gotta play well. Are they alive or... Yeah, I guess it actually is hard mode.
All right, I got super and I got the gun. No, why did you... Why did you do that?
Animation death. This... Over the rail. This from this early? Isn't this just like
more than halfway through? Ah, shit. I'm not supposed to get hit. Oh, bad positioning.
Oh, I didn't catch it. Some tryhard fancy for real. Because I don't... I want to do this.
I want to get to the end. It's three different sequences. Plays out three different ways.
We'll find out for real here. Hurry up with that bomb. And where is that girl?
She got out. All right, she's sneaking around now. Oh no, he's here. I wasn't ready.
What is this? Umbrella. She's dead. I need every heal. All right, I'm almost at full health.
No credits can be used. Pretty much full health. Good. No, what? Nopes. Weight room.
Pick up the bike machine. Yeah, those don't weigh like 4,000 pounds or anything.
Guy just got out of the sauna. You're never ready for a fight when you get out of the sauna.
The guy brings two guns into the sauna. Relax. They're hard days work. I love the
poster in the back. It's a beautiful poster. This dude's got the best combos. Seems like it.
So what's the chef going to be? Because we're about to fight the chef. And we're going to
see what is inside of there now. Twist. All right. Back. Give me the... what are they?
Pork buns? Oh, these are mine. No, shit. They don't even heal as much as you're gonna hit one time.
Let's go. Come here. No. Load a clip into the axe. Oh, I ran right into it.
All right, you good? These guys do a lot. The dual welders do a lot of damage. Like that.
I'm just getting poked. Those are tiny pokes. Do you have... is there a heal over here? There is.
Health. Get it. All right. What is the chef? It's...
there's no way you're gonna be able to stun lock me over here. You probably can. That's
dog shit. Come on. Right into the fucking camera. Oh, don't crap walk over here. How
did you not get hit by any of those? No. No credits. Come on. There's a drink right there.
Barely even healing me. Got it. All right. Watch out. There we go. I'll get him here.
Block every single punch. There we go. One credit down. Where's girl?
Haven't you found her yet? Never mind. It's time. Blow it up. Activate the bomb.
No sign of the girl somehow. Gotta utilize this.
One dead. Both dead. Move. Can't pick that up. That's weird. I'm trying so hard.
All right. One more and I get the power. Why... okay. Oh, he's the liar. He's the liar.
That's awesome. That was so cool. I'm glad we got to see it. I didn't screw it up.
I have a lighter. Holy shit. No! That was so cool. There's a lot of damage probably.
Come on. It doesn't feel like it's doing that much damage.
No! God damn! I think I don't want that right now. I don't want to pick that up.
I think it's a waste. I'd rather save that for like a boss or a hard encounter.
Okay. Come up with a broom. Come on. Why do you have so... this guy has so much health.
Okay. It's looking good. There's only one major boss left and it's the last guy.
This way. No, actually there's two bosses. These cutscenes are ridiculous.
They're so quick. Why'd you just hit me in the face?
Dead? No. I need the health. I need it. I have to take it. Give it to me. You stupid
fucking game. That's okay. It's actually pretty good here. This is not going to be
good. This ain't looking good. Puffing. Is that going to dodge quicker than that?
This guy's actually worse than any of the other bosses I think. Just because he's so big.
Okay. You got a health pack? You don't. Oh, you're so annoying. You have to have one.
What? Christ. Oh my god. The helicopter flew by twice. Can I rest? You can. That's a
strat. Get it. Wow. I can't be standing on top of something. Is that what the problem is?
All right. Is that a heal? Dollar bill. What do you do with a dollar bill?
This will be so easy. He can't teleport away. These guys are so horrible. Okay.
Really? Did I just get... Oh, the thing sticks out. You can't do it to the guy with
two swords, unfortunately. God damn it. How did you even... I just hit you in the fucking
face with a spear. How do you keep scooping me? I'm scared Jeremy. Hurry up.
Can I rest the crabs? Probably not. Nope.
Give me this. Come on. Oh, there's another hand gun back here.
Come on. This is back here. Fire axe.
He's dead. Come on. Give me something from the slot machine. Good. Good. Come on before it
drains. This is it. This guy and then we go up to the top and we fight the last boss.
I just need to be very careful. I don't have an actual gun to rest. That would help a lot right
now. Guns. Don't they gonna shoot? Oh, there's nowhere to go. There's two of them on the
ground. Head in the head in the head in the head. How many times do I have to shoot you
in the head? All right. I got the power for the boss. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. It's different this time. He was down twice in a row. Stupid fools. Your captain
is long dead. He's fish bait by now. Another combo with the axe. Forget it. Just take him down.
I can do it. Come on. I just gotta get it. Don't. That's almost three combos and he's
almost dead. That's it. And I got. Give me the special. Yes. All right. I'm ready to go.
One credit. He's gonna dodge at the right time. And I got a special.
All right. Dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge. Watch out. He's gonna kick.
Kick. Oh. Get out of here. Get out of here. Good to see the last cut scene.
Thank you for saving my life again. All right. How does this one play out?
He's dead. Arguably the worst one. That was the worst one. It just explodes. I think they
got him right at the time. First impressions? Um. I mean it's not first impressions. I played
this game. My first impressions 15, 16 years ago were I'm gonna burn $20 in this machine.
But wait. Hold on now. Is it after credits scene? Well now you just burned 100. I don't
think this one was that much. Post credits? This one was like 70 maybe. Or like 60. There's
no post credits scene. You said 100? It probably was. I don't know. I'm just trying to make myself
feel better. Uh. Did I unlock the? Well did you take a look at that? Showdown. I was so
good at the game. Um. Fast. I kind of like the combos with Eddie. Oh. Mission. You are
hurt. Do not wait. Weapon. Uh. This is just hard mode. Weapons, hits cause more damage than normal.
You are hurt. Do not take any more damage. Get to the next scene before time runs out.
So this is you one hit and you're dead. This is you. Everything does more damage and this is time.
Go! Move it! Apparently we're doing this one. Let's see what happens. 30 seconds to get the-
Is it? Do I have 30 seconds to beat the game? How is that possible? It's got a time
crisis isn't it? Let me just see what happens. Okay so we have 16 seconds.
I'm just curious. Yeah all right. So you have a certain amount of time to beat every screen.
That was fun. That was dynamite. Cough. Classic. I'm glad I played through it a few times.
I'm gonna go ahead and turn this off so I don't like hurt anybody's eyes or anything.
Next up we've got. What do we got? There are a few options. We could do another survival horror.
We could do- all right. There's three categories guys. There's game actually good,
survival horror, or stupid. That's pretty much what's available. Do you want to go through a
stupid one? All right okay okay wait okay yeah we just did the ring. That was survival horror.
Then we did dynamite cop which is good. So now we're gonna go with the floygan brothers.
Which I'm assuming is really stupid. The floygan brothers. Did somebody just get 50 subs?
The Olaf won thanks for the 50 community subs. My god. Thank you so much the Olaf.
Visual concept. I don't like this company. I don't- what? I'm being taunted.
Good floygan brothers. Episode one. Why how is this episode one? Is this a whole series? Is
this a tv show? But honestly thank you so much Olaf for the massive amount of community subs.
That's fucking crazy. It's Ed, Ed and Eddie Mario Brothers and uh the walking dead had a-
no it's not. The walking dead.
Oh
what's a seven-letter word that means circles of sugary baked dough
with chocolate chips in them. Cookies. Let's make cookies.
We're gonna make cookies. We need sugar. Pass me the sugar bowl big brother.
It's on the table. It's a pretty good show.
We need sugar. Do I just make the cookies? I move around. I get to be- I'm the- I'm the small
floy- yeah okay. You can already read the comments. Sugar makes cookies good. Of course.
Uh I need the sugar. Where was it? Right here? Reach the sugar. God,
Freudian weapon tank community subs. Thank you, Freudian weapon tank. Ten more.
I better be tall enough to open this door. I'm gonna say no way.
I thought I was Floygan. Oh no wait it's it's it's Hoygan? Hoygal Floygan?
Hoygal Floygan and what's the big brother's name?
I think yeah that that is a talented voice actor by the way. That's Frank- was Frank Welker?
Moygal and Hoygal Floygan.
That's their catchphrase. I'm gonna make him dizzy and then jump on his belly.
That didn't work. There you go. Moygal. I'm gonna- I'm gonna jump if you keep playing this. Don't.
Easy. You wanted stupid and I knew this was going to be the worst one of the entire bundle.
This is the worst game that I've that I've purchased. The worst one.
That's not true. This is Dreamcast exclusive. You can't get this anywhere else.
Okay there are- hug.
So what's the inevitable issue that they both have to solve together instead of just baking
cookies and being weirdos? The aliens land, the military shows up with the rifles or something.
Like what? What is it? The aliens have the radar gun. What is it?
It sounds like Otto from Otto's Big Adventure. I'm getting flashback.
Get to cookie. Where's the oven mitt? The cookies are burning. I gotta get the oven.
Where's- is it in here? Cookie. The house is gonna burn down. I don't know where it is.
Moygal. Where is it? Up here? This is gonna burn.
Hoygal. Hoygal the kitchen's on fire. It burns. Go let's get in here again. He's dead.
That's all right.
So this is- I anger my little brother and he tries to hurt me.
What? This is- brother's fighting. What happened to the cookies? It wasn't- what we're having a fun
time? We're killing each other. You burnt my cookies. Now I'm going to beat your face in.
Call the cops. What's he doing? Here he comes. What does this even do? Well it stops him
from hurting me because I stand on like the don't hurt- what?
What? Offer Moygal an apple when he's hungry. This is such a confusing brother relationship here.
I have to teach him. What are the options to teach? Let's see. Teach high five.
I did- why did I- I lost points. Moygal will high five with one hand or ten
with both hands. Use the analog stick to choose up down right or left and press
five for one hand or ten for two. Press go to start a help for-
This is the oddest game I think I've ever played.
So this actually was not the precursor to some larger scale story.
I'm very interested though. I need to see how this plays out.
So I taught him how to high five. Why is somebody like this using the oven?
What does he want? How many points should I give him? Ten? Nine? Five? Nine. Does anybody
understand what the hell is happening right now? He wants three. We're giving each other points.
That's not a place where you should have- wait, hold on. He just pulled- what is that? I don't
think I want to touch that. What the fuck? This is not gonna go anywhere. This goes in a
circle, Moygan. Oh no! Moygal has lost control of the train. Run and dive to catch the handle
at the back of Moygal's train. I don't have- I really don't have anything to say.
How do I get on the train? At the back? But the camera doesn't let me-
Where are the parents? How old are they? They're like 40 and you're learning how to high five
at 40? What do you mean before it's too late? I'm not sure what too late means. I'm not fast
enough to follow and he- my fucking god. I can't. You're going too fast. No, get off the ladder.
Just fall off at this point. The camera can't be moved. And then we can go make cookies.
I got it. That's how the adventure starts. They haven't been out of their house.
They have no idea what the outside world looks like. They get like dropped off here
with like a bunch of cookie batter. You've completed your Floydgan Brothers training.
Now on to the main episode. Moygal's secret project. Have fun playing games with Moygal.
Here he comes. This is why we waited that long. He just picks him up and starts eating him.
Is there a whole open world here?
I'm not gonna tell you. You got me again. Grab the lettuce.
What are you building in there? What scary twisted fucking
messed up device are you building inside of that shack?
You want to help me? You can help me find these seven things. It's part of the surprise.
He wants a muffler oil.
House friends? You talk to mice now? Go now, big brother, go.
No surprise without you, so just- He wants like kerosene and shit.
What the hell are you doing in here, man? That's my little brother. He talks to rodent.
Uh-uh. Rope. Syringe. Moygal meets Hoygal's help to find seven parts to finish his secret
project. Watch out. When Moygal's mood changes, they might be something new to do. Don't forget
that the mice can help find things. All right. Wait. This is Pac-Man. This is the Pac-Man Adventures.
It's just from a third point perspective. This is unbelievable. Okay. Hold on. How does it work?
All right. Go cry in that box. I'm gonna get Moygal sad.
I got better things to do. Okay. What do you- what do you like, Moygal?
Can you like take care of this? Beat him up. No, that makes him mad, not sad.
All right. We got some- Man. The mailbox. Is this one- is this anger? No, this is unconscious.
Hey, come here. Let me get to the mailbox. I will. Just a second. Just pass out here for
one second. Can I get over here? How can I maybe jump on him more than once?
Bounce, bounce. This is kind of interesting. It is, apparently. This is actually pretty
interesting. It is. I'm not sure how to get up there. Is there a double jump?
No. Huh. Maybe I need to maybe be closer. I was gonna be angry.
All right. That's fine. Come on. Follow me. Let's go to the mailbox. Is this the mailbox?
Mice, can you help me out here? What do I need? Look. Well, there's the yellow switch. Thanks,
mice. Hey, there's an item over there, Gerbil. Okay. Oh my god. Fruit? Oh, he eats these,
right? Will this make him happy? This is not gonna make him sad. Food? Wait, food is repulsive.
Are you gonna eat it? I'm offering you an apple. There really is something fucked up going on here.
I don't like help your strange brother build a dangerous thing in the shed. I don't like that.
I don't like this game. Okay. Well, we got the box. Five points, though, right? Let's see.
Teach. What can I teach? Teach, lift up, R the W. Round the world yo-yo. Let's teach.
Teach him the F word. Uh, how are you doing? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Cancel.
Teach around the world yo-yo. Ten points. I just had a piece of fruit right next to you.
Oh, I'm gonna make him cry. Come here. Where's the cry box?
Come here. Let's go. We're gonna make him cry and then he's gonna open the cry box. Sure.
Come on. Got it. He's filling the river because he's crying. All right. You want to play a game?
What was the game you want to play? Play. We could play high five. Hide and seek. Running
a race. Catch. I don't want to play high five. This is boring. Yeah, I know how to play.
I'm an expert at this point. But this is giving me points.
Yeah, this is not based on some original cartoon. This is just the game.
There is no... but this is episode one. I'm gonna assume that they thought maybe
there was a possibility that this would take off and they could make a bunch of stuff.
Toys, TV shows. It's based on every cartoon. That is true. What is this? Oh, it's candy.
Come here. Here. Come here. Eat the candy. No points. Here. I was trying to throw it in his face.
Whatever. All right. All right. Anger. Here we go. Get the key. I'll be... all right. It's
time to be fair. You ready to be fair? For a game that came out like 20 years ago.
It was Dreamcast exclusive. That sucks. This is a great game. Like this... imagine 20 years ago.
I thought that said Moegle's Children. I'm like, why? What is there? Why is this here?
I was like, what the fuck? Oh my god. Oh, I gotta get out of this game.
Like from back here. It's so blurry. I just... all right. What are we doing? You want to...
I had the plant already. I threw the plant. Where did it go? Did it come down here?
What's this emotion over this way? Happy? Yeah, that's happy. Is he happy now? Did you know
that the Texas Chainsaw film was based off of this? I didn't... you know, I didn't know that.
That's... punch. No, no, no, no. It's... I gotta teach you. Lift up. Hide and seek. I want to
teach you around the world. Right here. Eat this, then. Take it. All right, now we can learn.
Speak. Teach. Around the world. Floyd Gainesaw Massacre. I'm not sure what this does.
Isn't it around the world? You spin it around a circle? Why is he doing this?
Did he learn it? That's not around the world. Insult. Scores. Play. Teach. Did you
not do it? I guess that is what he did. Okay, how about... can we do it now? Can we play now?
No. No. We gotta... I'm almost... it's almost time to move on.
It's getting close. But I kind of want to see one last thing.
Do you think you could buy the rights to these characters?
No. I don't think so. Oh, it's because he has a full tummy. Okay, I get it.
Why do I have to bribe you with points to hug you?
It's a game... a competition that we're playing against each other.
All right, come on. Go, go, go, go, go, go. So what does this open?
Swipe? What am I supposed to grab? Oh, this water is like poison. All right,
I think that's enough of the Floydgan brothers. Keep... I can't keep playing this.
This is the... I don't... I can't play the Floydgan brothers for like another 30 minutes.
Keep playing. Oh, really? You want to see more Floydgan? This game sucks.
I'm... I didn't say that. More Floydgan. I did open this though. No, I didn't. Hey,
go get that. Go open the gate. You can't do it? We need more Floydgan.
No, you definitely don't want more Floydgan.
Okay, so somebody has to be standing here already. Stand here.
Get over here. Right there. I just got rejected. Gotta be fast like me. Okay, so I get it. Come
here. I'm gonna hug. I'm gonna open this gate. We're gonna see what's in here. Why am I still
playing Floydgan? No, let's hug. Let's hug. No, shit. I just punched him in the stomach.
The pulls are in. It's a steal. I don't have any... I can't bribe him. I used all my...
I used all my brother points. I gotta play... I have to play a game to build up points.
All right, we're almost done. Trust me. Spam the pull. No, no, no, no, no, no. We're gonna be...
Now it's a timer. It's a timer.
It's just some resident sleep.
That was one guy though. That was one guy.
He was trying to bait me. That was... I had one or two seconds to do that.
Now how many points did I get? One.
It'll be two. And then we can get in the gate. And then 25 seasons from now,
we're gonna find out what's in that basement. I've had the key around my neck for about
seven years now. Okay. Give me a hug. Let's go. Activate lever into the gate.
What? No, I don't want to do the... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What? Get in. Okay. There's a dog in here. Dog. Dog. Plus 500 viewers. Dog. There's a dog. Dog.
What the hell? Is he winding up a punch? All right. How do we play? Play with dog, right?
No, I don't want to punch... Oh my god. Here. Play ball with dog.
What's your thing, Wiggle? Yeah, I'm gonna throw this with a dog, Wiggle.
Run and dive to catch spits by the tail. Win by catching spits three times. Lose if the
timer runs out. Minus 500 viewers. We're almost done with Hoigl and Moigl. How many
times do I have to catch the dog? How many times do I have to do it once? How many times?
This is Super Mario.
Restore. That's Hoigl and Moigl. The Moigl Brothers. I don't even know what it was called.
It's called the Moigl Brothers. Now this one I am excited for. I can't wait to play this one.
I don't even think this is a Dreamcast exclusive. I just saw it and I said,
okay, I think I need to have this. I have to own this. It's not Crazy Taxi. It is,
you'll see. It's not Seaman. I had to return Seaman because they forgot to put the mic in
the box. This is ECW Anarchy Rules. I'm excited. Louder, louder. There's a dumpster
match in this. That's all I needed to see. That's the first thing I'm going to do,
and probably the last thing I'm going to do. ECW don't even exist anymore. It was absorbed
a long time ago. Blood and guts. They used to throw each other on fluorescent light bulbs.
They used to jump off buildings. That guy actually hit the head with a rock.
And then it fell to his hand. Okay, all right. I think we get the idea. This fat
guy's is thumbtacked. The game does not look anything like it. Okay, let's just go.
Anarchy Rules. It's got to be lowered. The volume is way too low.
Insufficient space. Pay per view needs 93 blocks. Wait, what's on here?
Freudian weapon thanks to the 10 community subs. 10 more. You know this is the first
place we're going. You gotta, there's no way there's something on here. That's impossible.
Create. Body. Loading screens for every single one. Mail. Oh my god, that is, that's very,
very large. How skinny can they get? Let's go with muscle. Hairy, scarred, bruised,
cut, diseased. Okay, let's go with rib. How do I select the color? What's the, how do I make
them, how do I make them like green? Yeah, make Thanos. That's not a bad idea. It is
loading so heavily. What does Thanos have for eyes? Nope, that's, that's my eyes.
That's not bad. You can't control him. This is very early character creator, so
mouth. Got a kind of a large mouth. Whoa, there we go. Getting there. 22 looks kind of like it
could be. No, 22, 21, 22 is probably the closest. No, hold on. Grimace. There we go.
Mouth 12. Oh, why does mouth 11 have to not be, come on, go the other way. Vertical.
That's not bad either. But he doesn't have the lines going down.
Oh, no, Thanos doesn't have hair. None. No, but maybe goatee would look a little better.
No, this is the real way to do this, guys. I'm making the goatee purple.
Almost. Look at that. That's pretty close. All right. Mask. What do you have? No, no mask,
right? But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Accessories, head gear. Does he have anything
on his head? Or on his ears or anything? Or body? He doesn't have clothes, does he?
What does Thanos do? He has armor. It's like gold armor, right? That's pretty good. Add-ons.
Don't need any add-ons. Chest gear. Oh, wait a minute. There's armor. Bulletproof chest armor.
Gold. There we go. Shoulder pads look okay. The whole thing. Come on. That's annoying.
Take off the shirt. No, he's got nothing on his arm. Take the shirt off, the dude looks like.
He's just wearing like a children's section t-shirt. Okay, all right, all right, all right,
all right. Gloves. One glove. That's, come on. That's really cool. Nice one glove.
Accessories. Oh, wait, we can make it. I think we can make it. That's pretty close.
Hold on, because the, that will go. Yeah, that's as good as it's going to be.
We gotta make it gold. I'm not sure you even can. Give him a corsage. How is this yellow?
Okay. Well, there is kind of yellow. My mood bracelet. Well, all right. It was back here
somehow. This is ugly. It doesn't even matter. He's getting thrown in a dumpster
in about five minutes anyways. That's okay. That's all the infinity stones are activating
at the same time. He's got the mood infinity gauntlet. Where's the stupid glove? One glove.
There it is. Mood gauntlet. This thing sucks. Eww, you mood gauntlet, infinity gauntlet,
or is he just wearing like a gushers? He just squashed a bunch of gushers and taped
them together and put it on his arm. He's wearing like a candy bracelet. Okay, a little
darker. Somebody's saying the chest is wrong. Add-ons, right? So wait, it needs to be black?
Give him a vest. This is the shittiest Thanos. Come on. It was this 2001, guys. I can't make a
perfect Thanos. This is actually kind of the vest he wears. This one right here. That's it.
What color is the vest? Black. Black. Black. Black. Who cares? Use buckles? All right. Buckles.
Black. He doesn't have sleeves. Guys, it's not going to happen. I don't even know what he
looks like. Hold on. I haven't seen that movie. Let me just look it up. Oh, Thanos.
Okay, so this is pretty... He doesn't have sleeves. It doesn't matter. I already had it.
It was already done. The vest doesn't need to be on here. That's pretty close already.
All right, what do you have for pants? Good. Okay, boots. Looking good. They're not blue.
All right, that's it. Accessories. That's good. They're good. I get a bit of socks on them.
Oh, shit. I don't like those. There he is. Text. Rant. Okay, we're done. What is Thanos's
real name? Does he have a real name? Just one name. Okay, attributes. Let's do this correct.
So I would say for charisma, I've got one. Recovery. Speed. Toughness. Okay, he's tough.
He's strong. He's very fast. He's... Maybe his mat skills might not be great because he's not
used to being in a ring. That's pretty good. They need to be balanced. No, I don't even know
who any of these... DeVito. Is there anyone with a T? Thanos. Personality. Crowd is gonna heal.
Fighting style. Yeah. Theme song is important.
They all have the same song. Hectra. Entrance. Um, don't care. Okay, voice grunts.
That's pretty good. Booger.
I'm a damn handsome man. I'm a damn handsome man.
Oh, baby, these shorts are tight. Oh, baby, these shorts are tight.
Now this is booking worthy. Come on, admit it. You're jealous. So what if I'm a girl?
There will be no appeal. The shorter they are, the harder they fall.
I hate this. I believe in this match. You're the joke.
Why did we make Loki? I believe in this match. You're the joke.
You're about to give Magma the key with the dangerous alliance in my stable.
Fear me. I'm insane. No. I'm Martian boy. I'm not a wrestler. I'm office.
What? I'm Martian boy. I'm not a wrestler. I'm office. I'm office?
I'm not wasting my time with crap like you. I'm gonna show you where I'm the original
gangster. You might think you're good, but I'm super. This match ain't gonna make a
best of tape. After I take you out, I'm gonna take your old lady out and show her why they
call me R- Brother, I'm the American dream. Chicken. It's time for everybody's favorite
rest. Simon says I'm more intelligent. Simon says I'm more intelligent. Simon says you need
some discipline. I am the Sandman, the hardcore icon. Left ear. Oh, he was only in the left ear?
Hold on. Wait, I gotta put my left ear in. Simon says I'm more intelligent than you are.
Oh yeah, it was just one ear. You can't beat me. I'm from Calgary, Alberta,
Canada. I'm the original gang. I'm gonna leave the broadcast booth just to kick your ass.
Good night, Chesty. Wherever you are.
Who is this? What three-year-old was in the extreme championship wrestling? What?
Where was there a child?
I'm prodigy, son of the great one. Your head is so tiny.
You're just another speed bump in my push to the top. Tonight, when you scream,
it had better be in tune. Oh, man. I'm gonna take this fist and shove it down your throat.
I may look like an underdog, but don't let that fool you. I've got a tremendous bite.
Be forewarned. My capacity for violence has yet to be ascertained.
I'm gonna take this fist and shove it down your throat.
I may look like an underdog, but don't you. I'm gonna take this. I may look like an under-
That's fucking hilarious. You're just another speed bump in my-
You're good.
Okay. Save. Save. Okay. S-A. Whatever. Wrestling name. Thanos. Change.
Fan po- Oh, I don't care. Go back and do the hit sounds. This kid. Hold on.
Name. Attributes. Moves. Personality. Fighting style. Theme song. The kid. What is the kid's
theme song then? Blazed Orphe. What a kid. Voice grunts. The kid. The kid. The kid.
I just have the kid be the running partner. Well, we don't- I don't even know how to play
the game yet. We gotta get there first. Hold on. Frickin'. I can't get over that.
Create. Okay, that's it. Create a pay-per-view. Edit stadium. Hold on. Let me just see.
This is all dumb. It's the entrance sign. Scaffold. Ban? All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. This is an exhibition. One-on-one. Lumberjack. Battle Royale. Hate match. Team
rumble. Stable match. Well, let's just- let's do a eight-man tag. Can I change the rules?
Battle Royale? What the hell is that? No. There's no kid. There's no the kid.
Okay, so we're gonna do the trainer. So I'm just gonna be-
Okay, so order list. No, I can't do that. Back it up. I'm really confused about how this whole
thing is working here. How many can I have in here? Wait, why is this so many?
Match. I can't change that. I don't understand. I can't see. This is just a Battle Royale.
Win modifier is none. Belt channel is no. Simulation on- is it just a rumble?
Brick. TKO. Off. This is just a bootleg rumble. It is. I think I want to play,
though. Maybe not. Let's just go. See what happens. Thanos is- yes, he is. Thanos is
right here. Are there no entrances? You're just begging. You're just another speed bump
in my push to the top. I hate this already. I don't like it. I really don't.
I want to play. The commentator is still on.
I want to play. Where's the crowd? Why is there no audience sounds?
They keep doing low blows to me. That's supposed to be an audience member.
So I wonder what the entrance is like for the kid. There's no music either.
How do you lose? Do you think it's thrown over the top rope?
Because only four people are allowed in here at one time and there's 30 that are supposed
to be here. This is gonna take a very- this- I think we have to do something else.
I'm not sure it's gonna be a win or a loss.
Exhibition versus one-on-one, right? Or three-way dance between me, the trainer,
and- this is- no, that's victory. This guy. Match options. Death match. Barbed wire.
Dumpster match. That's what I'm talking about. Brimstone match. Dumpster match.
Win modifiers. Simulation. On. No, off. I want to play. Let's go. This is a dumpster match.
Where are the entrances? There's no entrance? This is not the entrance. No, it is not.
I'm gonna knock you out cold with the orange bond and then finish you off with the trainer
song. I've proved in the past that being a champion wasn't a fluke. Now you get to
experience my skills. Let's go.
How does dumpster match work? Do you have to get thrown in the dumpster?
That's block. Okay. Can you guys fight each other? This is supposed to be a fatal three-way
and down stays player one. Ascending the turnbuckles. The trainer climbing up. Can I go
outside? How do you leave? Okay, that's run. Let's go use the dumpster.
They're not just gonna keep doing this, are they?
Off the ropes. Against the ropes. Into the ropes. Oh, you figured it out. Good.
The bounce off the ropes. He's taking it to the outside. He takes a well-deserved
change. How do I change who I want to look at?
Low blows. Don't give me that. There's a, a nose.
How does this match work? They won't fight each other. They're just gonna fight me,
which is bullshit on its own, right? I'm gonna lose. I'm almost out of health.
You can't pin me. There's no pinning.
It's over. I lost. I got put in the dumpster.
Who's bleeding? Why is there blood all over the ground?
Can I get out? I think I'm just in here. I think I lose. That's it.
Why am I dead? We have to do Bravestone after this. I need to know what that's like.
The disc just had to load to pull that audio off.
Looks like the trainer is going to beat an actual wrestler.
This game has a 38 on Metacritic, even back then. All right, I don't know much more I can
take of this. It's a different weight category. That might be true. They only have five minutes
and 45 seconds to finish this. Most of the sounds in this game are just diarrhea cramp
noises. His back? There's nothing with his shoulder. He bladed on his shoulder. He's
bleeding. I think this is the end. Just throw him in the dumpster. That's all you have to do.
You don't have to do anything else. He's red. Speaking of red,
LaCrando just gave a hundred dollars. LaCrando, thank you so much for the hundred bucks.
Hey Jeremy, remember me? It's time for some free shit.
The bounce off the ropes?
Okay, that's over, but thank you LaCrando.
Those of you that don't know what he's talking about, there's an extreme amount of money that
was given two days ago. It was one of the most outrageous things I've ever had on stream
for monetarily. It was ridiculous. Thank you. I don't know what this means.
Do you know how to do the secret poo move? I don't want to do a poo move.
How about mother jack, four way dance, and I do brimstone. Let me just do one on one.
Hate match, death match, cage match, street fight, barbed wire, dumpster, table, brimstone,
rage in the cage, back lot, brawl. Street fight? Let's try street fight.
Isn't street fight just a match with weapons, is it? Oh shit, it might be. I'm not sure
what's very childlike about this. I would do this if I was in the ring.
Okay, I did trainer again, didn't I? Just gonna walk. Do it again, same thing, do it again.
All right. Wrestling is not real. You're just another speed. He said wrestling's not real.
So there's punch, kick, and then there's a grapple. Vertical suplex. That's grapple and
it's up. Yeah, okay. So that's how that works. Emmerlock, reverse that move.
Reverse it. How are these street rules? Arm wretch. Wrestlers around the world use that move.
Where are the weapons? Hip toss. Emmerlock. I seem to only know how to do the arm wretch.
There we go, you have to down, up in a direction, left in a direction. Okay, I get it.
Use the infinity gauntlet. Emmerlock. Give me a goddamn weapon. That's smart, take it to
the outside. Arm wretch. Look at the crowd. Do you reach underneath? How do you? I want to
pick up some. Take it all the way out? Can I reach in the crowd? Most of the games allow
you to reach in the crowd. Nope. Can't go back that way. Fantastic. Yeah. Emmerlock.
What the fuck can I even do? All right, we're gonna. Street fight.
I'm not seeing much street and I'm not seeing very much of a fight either.
Win location anywhere. Move list. Hip toss. Body slam. Spinning DDT.
This is really kind of boring actually. We're gonna do a brimstone match.
It needs to be like a bunch of fire or something. A four-way dance and a brimstone.
Doesn't matter. Brimstone, here we go. Let's go. Moigan and Floydgan had superior combat
mechanics. All right, it got interesting. Remember how excited I was for this? I know.
This is a bust, unfortunately. I'm gonna say a funny baby line and then we can move on.
Now go to my comic. Funny. Against the rope. Finally, somebody's not fighting me. How do I go?
Can you not go outside? Hip toss. I've even seen fans do that.
It's just fire out there. You can't go outside.
Yeah, now this is all fun. It could have been. Half-a-tentative.
But unless I see somebody burn here. Player one is down and he's hurt.
Do I only have two moves?
So what's the point of the PNG outside around the edge?
Body slam. Is there no point to that? A move like that will never make the highlight real.
He stays down. There's just a blinking bitmap image. Why am I doing this?
They're all against me.
Somebody fight somebody else, please.
What's with this guy and everyone being able to do every move?
Oh, you know, hip toss. My grandmother can do that. DDT, fans can do that move.
Come on. Reverse that.
Hip toss.
Into the rope.
It's not as easy as you think. I've left their aggro range like four times.
Get away from me, please.
He's wide open. This game makes me nauseous.
I didn't like that sound. That was a very, very bad sound.
Not much skill needed there.
Is there any move that this guy doesn't think is not impressive?
Against the ropes.
I just light me on fire and so I can be done with this.
Player one can't keep his hands up.
Who's gonna throw me over? Who's gonna burn me?
Why are you pinning?
I stuck away.
There is nobody there.
Oh, ref, that's like a 12 pound.
He's still pinning.
He doesn't get it. He still thinks I'm under there.
Somebody kill me.
Just kill me already.
Can I just drop a cinder block on this guy's head or something?
Seriously, the guy that's lying down.
Can a stage light fall and hit him in the skull?
Why don't you get in the ring?
Nobody can go outside. It's actually just not even.
It's there for show.
Brimstone match is just to keep you in the ring.
There's no cool effect. There's no fire.
It's just there.
I'm just waiting for somebody to throw me over the edge.
The trainer doesn't do anything.
All right, that's it. I'm out of here.
It actually was just like a PNG.
I just need... I'll just wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Calm down, calm down.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Trust me, trust me.
Hi, Mom.
See? Look.
Here comes a much needed beating.
Is this it? Is this all? It's back here.
Wow. Yes.
Arm wrench.
He really seized an opportunity there.
There's nothing else there.
God damn it. What a bust.
That's so disappointing. What a bust.
What an actual bust.
All right, we got...
We got Tony Hawk 2 coming up here.
Either Tony Hawk 2 or...
No, wait, this one.
This one's going to be fucking fantastic.
I can't wait to play this one.
Hear me out on this one.
We got Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2,
but I feel like I need to end on that one
because I'm going to play it for at least an hour or two.
Right?
When we... I don't know.
That's tricky.
We'll see.
We don't have to do all of them in one day.
These can happen over the course of a few days,
over the course of like a week or so.
In the meantime, just give me a second.
I want to grab water.
It's been about four hours
and I want to grab something to drink.
I'll be right back.
So coming up now is...
This is a game about evolution from the description.
Those of you that have ever played Warcraft 3,
there's a game mode, a custom game mode that used to exist.
It was called Evolution,
where you had to eat and grow
and eat other things and other players.
You could transform into other things.
No, not Spore.
Not Spore.
That's called Darwin's Island is what it was called.
And I begged, begged for an actual real
developed version of that game.
And we got it in 1998.
Five years before Darwin's Island.
Sorry about that loud noise.
The story is fiction and it resembles actual names
or historical facts as coincidental.
Anything else?
Is it voiceover or something?
Nothing.
It's Mars.
60, 70 million years ago, Mars turns into Venus.
Full motion video cut scene.
Are they gonna be real actors?
I hope so.
A nice gentle rain falling on the terrain.
I thought you start as like a little tadpole
and you can grow to be as big as that mountain.
How did they get video 70 million years ago?
I have no idea.
Probably some, some like Rick and Morty episode.
Seventh cross.
Is there a melee missile?
Random missile?
What does that mean?
They're relaxing, relaxing things to say.
By the way, I can't save.
What the hell is even on this?
Should I stop removing shit from the VMU?
You barely understand what the game is.
Don't worry.
It will be, all will be revealed for you.
Here are six boards.
Select a more appropriate color for each board
from balls above.
Is he saying rats?
He's saying rats.
This board signifies offense.
Press the A button when you have selected a color.
No, what?
Does the color have to do with anything for offense?
Blue offense.
Water, fire, water, lightning, poison, holy, decay.
I'm not sure which one I want.
I got poison.
Okay, what's this one signify?
This board signifies PSI power.
Pounds per square inch.
Press the A button when you have selected a color.
Okay, so we've got power washer.
Vice grip.
Hydraulic press.
What white is.
Yellow.
But PK.
PK fire, PK freeze.
Go yellow.
This board, defense.
So defense.
Holy defense.
Or light defense.
Decay defense.
I'm gonna go with water defense.
I feel like it's gonna be very important.
Intelligence.
Holy, decay, white, red.
I'm just gonna say white, I guess.
No, no, no, no.
We look a holy person?
Yeah, let's do it.
This board signifies healing.
Ah, that's not good.
I got rid of the white one.
That's probably like holy.
Or light.
Could be.
No, red.
Maybe this is something cool.
Okay, let's do it.
Finally, dexterity.
Red.
What do we get?
All colors have been selected.
Okay to send color image to DNA.
Yeah, 3D print something here.
Come on, let's see it.
It's a dragon.
Light is supposed to be born.
Please give it a name.
Cheeto?
No.
I'm gonna make it Thanos.
Why?
Thanos?
We just did that.
I just made Thanos in the ECW game.
You want me to make Thanos the single cell organism?
No, no, not Xanos.
It was in my head.
You guys were all just talking about it
and I just did A-N-O.
All right, here we go.
I don't understand.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh shit, hold on, there's another one.
There's another animal over there.
Okay, there's a bunch of animals.
Eat the kelp?
Evolution?
I died.
All right, how do I eat?
Option, let's look at the controls here.
I can't.
Just have to survive, but how do you live?
Where do you eat?
How do you grow?
Is it a smaller animal or something?
I can't leave, I don't have legs.
I can't breathe air.
There's that crab again.
I have to assume it's eat the...
What's that?
Kelp?
Got it.
All right, I leveled up, I'm a slug.
Can I avoid the crab?
Come on, I got to at least get somewhere here.
What's this?
Slug again.
I can't leave yet.
I just ate some dirt.
Once you start hearing the Slenderman shit,
that's when you have to leave.
Where's the crab?
I don't see the crab over here.
Kelp?
Right here?
All right, what else?
What do we know?
Ooh, okay, I got somewhat of a body growing here.
I don't want to eat that anymore?
Okay, I don't like eating those now.
Do I have to change the food?
All right, I'm going to save it.
No, no, no, no, where's the crab?
Where's the crab?
Right there.
Oh, fuck.
How do I get out?
Oh my god, he's right behind me.
How do I eat more food?
Let's look at the status window.
Enterable terrain.
HP five out of five.
No part data.
I can't go down here.
Wait, here we go.
Got it.
Can I leave?
Okay, hold on.
Mutation EX power.
I have a heal.
How do I turn that off?
I gotta save again.
Where's the crab?
Oh, shit.
No, it doesn't want me to leave.
Why don't we use some kind of leaf monster?
I don't know what the hell it is.
I'm picking up random stuff and eating it.
Where's the crab?
Right there.
Press buttons.
The buttons I'm doing are B, heals.
That's my magical spell that I have.
I need to find something to eat.
Mutation.
Level one head, level one arm.
Defense, intelligence, heal, dexterity.
Eat crab.
I don't think I can eat the crab.
I can barely move down here.
Oh, cave.
I can't go that way.
I can't go down there.
What the fuck?
What am I supposed to eat?
I just killed something.
Okay, I just killed and ate something.
What was that?
I don't even know what animal that was.
How much more food do I need?
Can I fight the crab?
I'm so afraid to fight the crab.
I don't have any more VMU data left.
All right, here we go.
Fight crab.
I got it.
Okay.
Did it?
Am I evolving?
Did I evolve?
Am I bigger?
Evolution.
What the fuck am I doing?
Okay, so I need red.
Red head.
Is everybody getting this?
The manual?
Well, let me just save it.
I don't think I have enough room.
Can't save insufficient memory card.
There's a bunch of dog shit on here.
I think I have to kill the crab.
This is the most intricate part of the game
and certainly the most frustrating
that you need a manual.
All right, well,
somebody give me some Minecraft skin coordinates
and I'll make one.
I can't even attack it.
Coordinates.
Mine is 57.
Here's the FAQ.
Hold on.
Hold on a second, everybody.
Let me just see what they got here.
I'm just going to do the first one I see.
Getting started.
Stage one.
Surviving in the pond.
Okay.
Small strands of seaweed.
It smells green microorganisms.
Okay, first a slug.
Then bigger than that.
Third time you'll grow
probably your first working set of limbs.
This is the origin creature.
From here the real fun begins.
Your creature now has a functional head.
Go to the main menu and select mutations
to view your origin and its glory.
Find things that are moving
but look harmless.
Small and brown are your watch words here.
Some look sort of like pitcher plants
or sea cucumbers.
Some like crawling forearm slugs.
You earn EVPs for everything you slay.
For a small fry like you, you're hunting now.
You'll get one apiece.
Crabs are worth two.
If you are killed, you keep your EVPs
and return to the starting monolith.
So don't fear the crabs too much.
And then select evolution.
You only need two EVPs
at the beginning of the game
to build a new part.
So you can either make a beeline
for the monolith after two kills
or build up some points.
All right, here we go.
So that's the problem.
That's the problem.
We need one more point.
We need two EVPs.
We have one EVP.
So look for the little things in the ground
like this guy right here.
Kill him.
What about that?
That wasn't a crab.
That was a little guy.
I had a little slug here.
Oh, right there, right there.
All right, I'm getting the hang of it.
I'm starting to figure out what's going on here.
Come on, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
Got it, okay.
That's two, right?
Pick that up.
Got one more over here.
All right, before the crab gets here.
All right, let's build level up.
Shit, I keep them though.
I'm stuck.
It is an invisible wall.
I can't go by the invisible wall.
So I should have enough to do this.
I should have three.
Three, all right.
Okay, here we go.
A button mash.
Evolution.
You're presented with a 10 by 10 grid
to draw in in six colors to choose from.
Not surprisingly,
these are the same colors you chose before.
You task it to draw whatever design seems appropriate.
Then click send.
So it doesn't matter.
I got arm level two from Shito.
I got it.
I leveled up my arm.
All right, so I'm going to do more damage.
Can I kill the crab now?
You have to equip the new arms.
All right, mutation.
Arm, level two, low fish.
Ooh, okay.
Head.
Nice.
All right, so now I actually have usable...
These things are probably...
Okay, time to kill the crab.
Oh, maybe not.
One more, right?
Right here.
Find the invisible wall there.
Die.
What the fuck?
I am surviving one hit,
but how many hits does it take to put at least 2,000 hours?
Don't give me that bullshit anymore.
All right, this should be two.
I should give this another opportunity, right?
Killed a slug.
How many EV points do I have?
EVO, EVE, what is it?
I should have two, right?
Let's go evolve again.
I want to get a head this time.
Well, I got two now.
We're going to clear it.
What else can I draw?
How about a pizza slice?
Bad idea.
Fuck!
I don't want this one here.
That's fine.
Oh, my fucking God.
It lags when you press the button sometimes.
How do I fix that?
Can I clear it?
How do I clear?
All right, it's fucking deep dish, all right?
Is it the same thing?
Low fish.
It's the same thing.
Shit.
Turned out to be a waste.
Sorry, we can get it back.
Stupid crab.
No, we can't be done with this one yet.
Not until I get out off the moat.
I got two again.
I'm going to draw a face.
Games for the Dreamcast are rare and expensive.
They sure are.
Two out of two, right?
There it is.
All right, no pizzas.
I'm going to draw.
Let's go with like...
What was my attack one?
Blue?
Was blue attack?
Blue is offense, right?
No, I did.
I did, guys.
Sorry.
No, you didn't.
I did.
No, I did, actually.
Don't I have three different arms, though?
I wonder if I can get the fuck out of here.
Arms on feet.
Can you do that?
No.
All right, there's one.
One more.
Again.
I have to kill that crab before I put another game in here.
That's two.
Back to the evolution table.
Wait, hold on.
There's another one right here.
I'm going to get them.
Just get them.
Farm them.
Two, four.
Grind it out.
But I want to be careful.
I don't want to run into a crab.
I'll get six.
One more should do it.
Bubbles.
Slug.
One more slug.
Come on.
It's falling somewhere.
Well, let's just go.
Yeah, there are no crabs around, that's true.
Okay.
Let's do white.
Let's make a piece of real abstract art.
Put it in the arm section.
Let us draw.
What do you mean, the arm section?
But I think that's the last three things I made.
Let you guys do it with click maps.
You want to click each individual cube.
That's like a fucking snooze fest.
Not like this isn't.
Let's see what we get.
Is there a...
Can I...
Don't use the same colors?
This is...
What?
This is yellow black, yellow black red, blue black, white...
I've never used either one of these two colors.
Don't put it in the arm section.
What if there...
Where's the other section?
Wait, hold on.
Hold on a second.
Wait.
I have to select that arm.
I can't move it from here.
I can't select anything.
You can't click on the head, but I can't click on anything.
There's no...
I can't move the cursor over to head, body, and legs.
So I have...
But wasn't I doing yellow before?
Yeah, but look.
All right.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Look at...
Look at body down there.
Yellow.
There's only red and yellow here.
Why didn't I get a head or a body?
Don't draw in the bottom left.
Let's try it.
Let's go white.
Let's go here.
Okay.
What?
Do you understand how this doesn't make any sense?
Look.
Listen.
Listen to me.
This is a full cube.
This is not just bottom left.
This is bottom right.
This is all of them equally.
This one I can understand.
But what the fuck?
This one?
This one is the...
Every single square is filled up.
Arm has priority.
It's just going to default to arm if it's full.
Okay.
Let's put the head on.
Head.
Desert bone.
I look pretty fucking ugly.
So now I got...
I got some.
I got an opportunity here.
All right.
Let's go kick that crab's ass.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Should I?
I just got baited.
I was aiming over the other side.
I can move in one crab now?
Nothing.
Got it.
I just killed my first new animal.
Looks like nothing.
Got two more.
I need a body.
Fight crab?
Not yet.
All right.
So body is top right.
And should I do yellow for body?
That's kind of the idea or does it matter?
I don't think it does.
Legs.
Do legs instead.
Bottom right.
One big beefy leg.
Green legs?
It's not gonna be arm two.
Green, white, green.
Too bad you can't be as creative.
But yeah, that's why I was drawing them.
Come on.
I guess you just have to make a random pattern.
What do you say?
Is chat wrong?
Level three.
It's random and I'm unlucky?
I hate this daft punked guy that just keeps talking.
Well, at least, yeah, it's level three.
There's a crab right behind me.
I gotta move.
You have to draw a leg to get a leg.
That's not how it works.
All right.
Leg.
Not arm.
Arm.
Low fish.
High fish.
His attack goes to 23.
Ooh, kind of like butterfly wings.
Do I fight crab?
All right.
Crab, let's go.
Not yet.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not ready.
I gotta get out of the water.
I need legs.
Come on here.
You gotta fight them on your turf.
It's true.
I gotta get legs.
Bring him up to the land and I'm gonna step on his head.
What do I got to say?
Oh, they both took two crabs.
All right.
Come on.
Come on, hurry.
Go, go, go.
All right, I need legs.
So is this just horse shit?
Should I be listening to you guys?
I don't think I should be.
I'm gonna go with blue.
Do one dot.
Leg section.
Draw a car.
Fuck it.
Blue?
No, I'm making two legs.
Give me legs, Jack.
You were very wrong.
You draw legs in the leg square.
That's what I just did.
I just did that.
I can't fight two crabs.
Come here, slugs.
I need two more.
Come on.
I can't go that way.
Why?
Get out.
No.
Thank God.
Why can't I put this on?
Why can't I put the head on?
Try all sorts of designs.
You might be surprised at what you find.
Geometric shapes, mirror images, symmetrical designs,
like little random U shapes here and there,
little random dots.
Head.
That's because I'm back to being scrub level.
The crab over there?
No, not next.
Not yet.
If I get out of the water and the game sucks,
then we can go from there.
But this is an interesting concept.
Where is it?
I just need to get out of the pond.
Once I get out of Goldshire, I'll be fine.
I need two crabs.
Come on.
Why are they so fast?
Are there any other squids?
I can't tell if that thing is...
I mean, how am I supposed to fight these?
I have a constant crab.
There's a bug chasing me too.
The bug hit me.
It didn't really hurt that much.
Please give me legs.
Get the crab away.
Legs.
All right, we're going to draw something cool.
Ready? Watch this one.
Little shapes.
We're going all in.
The designs are only worth arm level two.
There's a bug fighting me.
Where...
Look at him.
Hit him.
I know you can do it.
And now here comes the crab.
Get out.
Quick.
Get away.
Get out.
Get away from me.
I just want something else besides arm two.
I'm going to do like...
I don't know.
I'm going to do an elaborate tetris thing.
I can't put this on.
Powers.
I have wind.
How did I get wind?
Come on, kill it.
Is it still alive?
I need...
I need my arm level three.
Why did I de-evolve my arms?
I didn't.
When you die, you have to come back and do it again, essentially.
He's dead.
If a design creates something that's almost useful,
say a leg that's too powerful for you to use,
or one that's underpowered for you,
try modifying it just a little and resending it.
And some...
Add some dots.
I still can't put it on.
Come on.
Here comes the crab.
There really is no point to the crab being in the tutorial.
And there's no point to those rocks.
And the rocks that just...
You can't go through them.
You can't...
Oh, man.
I very clearly could go through those rocks.
Do I have any evolution points here?
Do a U shape around the grid.
So, like, you're talking about, like, this.
Would you classify that as a U?
Around?
Is that a U?
No, U.
Your mileage will vary.
No, no, no.
Small U shapes.
So we're talking about, like, these.
Just don't put one in arms.
Okay.
Send it back?
Hold on.
I need to...
I can't even put these on.
No!
The crab!
Why do you exist?
Do I get the colors?
All right.
I did...
I did white and black before.
It was still the same thing.
I can't pick him up.
I had to because crab.
All right.
I'm trying this one more time.
Before I just rage.
Quitting something else.
What color have I not used?
Red?
I did.
Okay.
Blue U's.
That.
Whatever that is.
Blue legs.
Blue and white in the corner.
Black and white.
Green and white.
Blue, black.
Red.
We're going red.
Let's see.
Do you have to...
I don't even know what to ask.
Is it the color?
So if it's blue in the top...
Blueprint?
Somebody got a blueprint.
Is that for real?
It's time to stop.
No, it's not.
Not yet.
It's not...
Maybe soon.
No, this is the...
I can't.
I'm backing myself in the corner.
I gotta back up.
I gotta get out of here.
Gotta go, go, go, go.
No, no, no, no.
No, there's two crabs.
Are there three crabs?
Really liking the zero slugs that they've got here.
This is great.
Head.
Still can't put that on.
This streamer's gonna leave an angry yahoo...
I just...
Just wanna get out of the pond.
That's all I know.
Just gonna get out of the pond.
And then we can play anything else.
I have to get out of the pond first, though.
That's very important.
It's loud.
Let me turn it down.
Should be better.
Do I have enough to evolve?
Another...
I need five to evolve?
Why?
It was two for so long.
What?
Thank you, Frodeon, for the 10 community subs.
Thank you so much, Frodeon.
Make a big white Z pattern.
God.
Can I just redeem arms?
I would love to.
Oh my.
Please.
Just get away from me.
Wind first.
How do I even use it?
I can't...
I don't even know how...
I can't even use the weapon.
I'm gonna get stuck.
Yeah, I didn't die from one hit from a crab.
No...
I need fi...
It's because I made too many fucking arms and I can't do anything with these.
I need five.
I might as well just redo it.
New character.
No, get away from me.
Red and green only.
I need to make a new character...
No, nobody wants to watch me do that.
I wish I could go down here.
Exit.
No, get me out of the game.
Oh, this game has so much potential.
But no, we're so out of reach because I made too many arms.
Just do it again.
Out of reach.
Yeah, that's funny.
I can't...
I know I can't edit.
There's nothing to edit and I can't do anything about it.
Going ahead.
Like this.
No.
It's gonna take a very long time to get where I am now.
But look at the spawns.
I need like five slugs to spawn.
Here's one.
Is somebody actually linking a...
Like an Imgur to a full-on leg blueprint?
You know what I'm saying?
Is there a leg blueprint in chat here?
No cheating?
No, I don't care about cheating at this point.
The game's cheating.
I gotta even it out.
Okay, how many more?
Two more?
Finally.
You finally started the spawns.
No, I can't move.
I'm stuck here.
When I looked at the game,
I looked up stuff about the box art
and I saw the description.
I thought this was going to be the best one.
I thought this was going to be my favorite Dreamcast game.
It was very, very...
I'm certain of it almost.
I need one or two more slugs and I can do this.
I'm trying this one last final time with the Imgur link.
Okay.
All right.
I can do that.
I can do that one.
All right.
Let's do it.
I need nothing...
Ah!
I can't like modify these.
Can't like change them.
I really don't even mind getting killed by...
I thought that was a slug.
It's a praying mantis.
Getting killed by the crab resets the slug spawns.
So I'm actually all right with dying.
Oh, somebody just kill me.
Just kill me.
Do it again.
Am I hitting anything?
I got it!
Whatever.
I got slug spawn.
All right.
I'm going to try this thing.
Somebody put a legit blueprint in the chat
and I'm going to use it.
Let's go evolve.
You could just kite the crab around and shoot it.
I mean, I...
He moves.
Well, not when you get stuck.
I could try.
No.
No, this is not the crab sitting right next to you.
Somehow didn't die.
I don't think I'm going to be able to do it.
Just give it to me.
They're going to kill me.
Because he can still move.
Because I can't move right now.
See?
If he has a good...
Oh, here we go.
Okay, kill the crab.
I'm going to get a crab killed right now.
He's stuck.
Holy shit.
I mean, what is a crab worth?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Y'all thought we were going away from this game?
Nope.
Okay.
Blueprint.
I don't care about colors.
I'm following this blueprint exactly.
It's minion art?
Wrong blueprint.
What do you mean?
Minion art.
Okay.
God damn it.
I'm so antsy right now.
I just want something that's not an arm.
Okay, here we go.
This is the...
Somebody has to link this.
Here we go.
Ready?
Leg is like pink.
Pink is red.
Red and white.
Red and white makes pink.
I can edit these.
But am I allowed to resend them with no...
I need EVP to resend them.
Sooner or later you're going to get whacked.
Probably quite often.
When you do, you wake up next to the initial monolith
back in the origin stage.
Once you stop screaming...
What?
Just do the American flag?
Joel says make American flag.
What have I done even so far?
I've done the automaton.
A slice of pizza.
A happy smiley face.
Guy jumping at you.
Chat was wrong.
Chat was wrong too.
Chat was wrong three.
Random to try to get anything.
Chat was wrong four.
Guy playing golf.
Golfing.
Chat was wrong five.
And chat was wrong six.
So I'm not clicking any part of your Imgur links.
One red cube in the lower right
is what you're telling me I need to do.
Okay.
All right.
That's it.
Relax.
Everybody relax.
I can't even put on the desert eagle
where the fucking thing is called.
Small u around grid.
I need some more slugs.
I can't stop playing this.
We've been looking at the same image.
Four more.
Put on the head and the arms.
I can't.
I'm not strong enough.
My character sucks.
I can't put him on now.
Watch.
Ready?
See?
I can't even wear these.
Because my my prot is too low.
Fire.
Where did I get fire from?
Why do I have fire?
Okay.
Fire crab.
You got it.
Can you go like any faster?
Okay.
Back this way.
Back it up.
Back up, back up, back up, back up.
Got him.
Get his body too.
This is food for a month.
Play floygan brothers to calm down.
Is that enough?
Don't tell me that I can't
go down here to pick up the body.
Oh my god.
Am I gonna play resident evil 2?
Yes, I am.
Just not today.
I'll need to start that tomorrow.
Or, uh, I don't know.
We'll see.
I am going to play it though.
Okay.
I got enough to do one.
So let's do the American flag.
Okay.
Without looking, I'm going to do the American flag.
And that's not that's not that's not the American flag.
Hey, arm two.
All right.
I think I have to give up on this game.
I think so.
I mean, this game is stupid.
But look what I was supposed to do.
I keep getting arm two.
Black top left red bottom right.
I've tried this last this the last time I'm going to do this.
There's probably so much video game here.
They head behind arm two.
Can you imagine how much is in this game that you cannot access?
Let's try it.
Black top left red bottom right.
Wait, wait, except both.
You guys are saying all like three different things.
Black top left dot bottom right red dot.
This is this is going to work.
You're telling me.
Yes.
Do it.
Body ten.
What?
Why is it body ten?
That was a cheat code.
Somebody that's a cheat code.
Stab scorpion.
I can't even use this.
Not even close.
I need to level up like 48 times.
So I have to eat 48 bodies.
Are you trying to keep me here?
You're trying to lock me here?
No, don't go away from me.
Play this for the rest of the night.
I feel like everyone's going to run away.
Realistically, how often can you watch the guy on the stream
in front of your computer using his goldfish hands to punch slugs
before you're like, yeah, you know what?
I guess there's something else I could probably do right now.
And I can't go down here.
Do blobs.
There's only one or two blobs per.
If I walk on out of here, then the real stream begins.
You understand?
I stand up on my own two feet and I'm walking over that mountain.
It's a real stream coming up here.
Here we go.
I'm going to do what I would consider to be a real blacktop left and nothing else.
But it's going to be another cheat with its level 10 hands or something.
Don't waste the proteins.
Who cares if it's cheat?
Okay, here we go.
Somebody says green square right in the middle.
Is that what you want?
Is that what we're talking about?
No, just one black dot in the top left.
One guy said it, whatever.
I can't use this.
What am I supposed to do with that?
What do you want me to do with that?
No, I'm doing Minecraft Steve next.
And it's going to get me something amazing.
What even is it?
Arm.
Demon.
Demon arm.
This is end game content.
I can't do anything with that.
All right, Minecraft Steve.
Minecraft Steve.
Okay, he's got the hair on top, right?
It goes down like this.
And then blue eyes, right?
He also has a goatee.
Can I do, I guess this?
It's not Cheeto.
Minecraft Steve?
No, he's got like a nose too, doesn't he?
Color so that it doesn't nose.
It's an emoji.
SpongeBob.
That's my, hold on.
I said I was going to do Minecraft Steve.
So I'm going to do it.
My God, no, no.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Okay, try it again.
What was the other thing I was going to do?
One yellow line down the bottom.
I don't even have enough fucking protein powder.
Do I have enough to even just make a T pose?
I can't believe that didn't do anything.
Okay, okay.
I can put on my level three hands.
And crabs aren't going to kill me anymore.
I can put on my desert bonehead.
So that looks good.
Okay.
I'm kind of decked out right now.
What, 14?
Demon arms I can't do.
All right, let's go.
Who's even, I can't even see who's down here.
Okay, another slug.
That's enough.
There's the crab.
Oh, he's getting in close.
Do it again, again, again, again, again.
Okay, let's try it again.
I think you're supposed to lose, guys.
You're supposed to get your ass kicked.
Get tons of protein powder points.
I'm at a point where I can reliably kill all these.
In one or two hits.
Observe.
Okay, you want me to make it just a big Z?
What's this, what's this one?
So you want a Z.
A giant Z.
I gotta make sure this is correct.
No, fucking stupid, the yellow thing.
Hold on.
Okay, there's your Z, I make a Z.
And it's done.
Somebody got it.
We got legs.
It's done.
I'm so excited to put these on.
Legs, new legs, high fish.
Put them on.
I'm still in the pond.
We can't leave.
They're not legs.
Yeah.
Can I go on this block?
I was holding it in.
Into the cave.
What the fuck was that thing?
I think that's a boss.
I'm not going in there.
We just got access to the deep pond.
All right, don't screw this up.
I just need some more.
And then I can get a good body.
And then I can throw my entire career down the toilet
by playing this game every day.
And nothing else ever.
Save game, I can't.
I don't have any more space on the VMU that I bought.
Which, shame on the place that I got it from.
Because they didn't even have the wherewithal
to remove the shit that was,
oh, hold on a second.
I gotta pay attention.
There's a bunch of random games
that are still on here from some dude in like 1998.
I don't have any powers.
I can fire.
What?
Water?
Where is this camera located?
That was my responsibility?
No, it's the responsibility of when it comes into used
and somebody selling it used, you wipe it.
I don't want your like fucking tabs on here.
I don't want your like internet cache on here.
I actually think I'm pretty good right now.
Nobody can hurt me.
Crab doesn't do very much.
Okay, we're fine.
I love looking at what the mystery person played on their Dreamcast.
Yeah, it's all right though.
I think I can actually do something interesting here.
I think I can pull this out
and delete stuff off of it handheld.
I have so much EVP points.
Let's see if we can make something happen.
Equip that body.
No, I'm not there yet.
I can't do demon arm either, guys.
Land?
Can I?
I can't.
Uh-oh.
That's it.
I don't want to get killed here.
Got it.
You can walk on land with the leg, but hold on.
Just wait one second.
Oops.
These guys killed me in one hit before too.
What the hell is hitting me?
I'm not going to do any evolution stuff until I have at least 50 of these.
That's right.
You heard that.
Don't adjust your audio there.
That was five zero.
I wonder how many people were watching
that we got to the point where that was arm level two
like the 15th time and they were secretly hoping.
Oh man.
I hope he does not actually get out of this.
I hope he rage quits the game.
Where's Tony Hawk?
I would say it too, probably.
In fact, I think I did.
Where's Seaman?
I'll explain Seaman again.
I was going to play that today.
Unfortunately though, when I bought it,
where I bought it from,
the person did not put the mic in the package.
That was just the game.
And the game doesn't do anything without the mic.
Unfortunately.
Okay.
I got 25 of these.
All right.
I need something interesting.
How about we do guy eating cheese or cheese eating a guy.
Flip it on him.
I mean, you messed it up.
You messed it up.
You can walk on land with these.
Wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy.
What Pac-Man is a good one too.
How did I screw this up last time?
It's one in the middle here.
That's it.
Yeah, that's it.
So you tell me this is something else.
Is it different?
Thanks for dumping my protein powder in the sink.
All right.
I was going to eat that and go get a pump on, man.
Let's go with Metroa.
How about what have I used so far?
Let me see.
I got plenty of options.
Get Minecraft Steve, Pac-Man, Pac-Man.
I got to get this right.
Is there a green ghost?
He's going up and eating them.
Should I do the whole background black?
He's a circle.
He's turning.
He's turning up top left.
And opening his mouth and going that way.
Simple shapes.
Okay.
What's the point of having this
if I have to do like two squares and then go?
Oh, well, that's a fun fucking game.
What is it?
You fucking assholes.
Unbelievable.
Now you're going to gnome me after that shit?
Why?
Why would you do that?
Whatever.
Okay.
Stab Scorpion.
I need two more.
Level 11 by two black squares.
Draw.
Yeah. Okay. Fine.
Draw the gnome.
No, I'm just going to do this.
This is the dumbest game ever.
This is stupid.
I spent the last hour and a half just trying to figure out like,
oh, draw stuff and maybe do a pizza, a guy, a design, a shape.
Try this shape.
How about these shapes?
No, just do two squares and get a level 11 and 19.
Draw the American flag.
Okay.
I got lizard legs and I got monkey legs.
It's time to walk on land.
Too many squares.
It's really about the minimalist approach of one or two dots.
What do I have right now?
Eat the blobs for protein?
Yeah.
I'm just spawning random places.
God damn it.
All that time wasted trying to...
All we had to do is two dots.
What do I have right now?
49. Is that close?
Lizard Rex, 59.
67.
I think I can put on something else though.
What's the body?
10.
Okay.
Scorpion body.
I might be almost ready to fight that giant slug in the other room.
Not quite.
I need some more protein packs.
I demand bean bag Sonic.
I'm not sure we can make bean bag Sonic.
If you walk on land, I will sub for five months consecutively.
I gotta do that now.
I'm gonna get on land.
It's gonna happen.
We have the legs already.
Protein blobs.
My brain is stuck over here.
Why is my health low?
Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
Do I have a heal?
Water first, water second.
Does I have a better water ability now?
Let's try it out.
Water two.
Pretty good.
This guy over here.
I hear a crab.
Crabs are still dangerous.
And I think we're looking upside down right now.
If you max out your creature, I will sub for 12 months.
I don't know if that's gonna happen.
Another crab.
I'll be happy as long as we got out of that stupid little pond in the beginning.
No, I gotta get out of this pond.
It's very important.
If I beat this game, you will give me 1.2 million dollars.
If that were real, that's the easiest money anyone could ever make.
That's a very bad investment.
I'm gonna tell you that that's a not sound use of your money.
I would refrain.
I'd say refrain from doing that.
Let's see.
There's one red dot in the middle.
Let's go with green dot.
We're gonna go green in the corners.
Oh no, green like this.
Arm 25.
Yellow.
Head 12.
That's pretty good actually.
And we're gonna go blue.
Blue in each corner.
Arm 25 again.
At least we have a lot to look at.
Let's see.
Head.
Lizard head.
Can't use it yet still.
Why?
Why not?
Prot 66?
Lizard Rex.
I'm not sure I'm understanding this though.
So I can't wear these because I have 60 too, right?
So if this was minus...
If this was minus 60, wouldn't it put me at two?
You have zero.
So I'd have to take it off of other places.
I see.
Okay.
Your fish sucks.
I wonder if I can fight that slug over there.
Ah, hello, hello, hello.
Let me have the control of my character please.
All right.
Let's see if I can unequip a few things and walk around.
Because I'm just curious.
So if I take off the arms...
That leaves me with a K 11 and a 7.
All right, I get it.
I see.
Take off like the body too.
Just want to see what happens.
Legs.
Lizard.
Eyes 42.
I still can't do it.
I need 112.
I can put the lizard head on though.
I'm not sure it's worth having that.
I don't think so.
Yeah, this thing sucks.
Put the high fish, the stab, scorpion arms.
Wait a minute.
Oh boy.
I think I'm ready to tumble.
Whatever.
What's my attack?
I got still the high fish and it's done with the body.
But what's better?
Having higher defense or having a huge amount of offense right now?
Probably the defense.
I mean, that's a huge increase, but I still have to stab shit.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's try to fight the boss.
I got everything equipped.
All my arms.
No, I can't do any other arms.
Nope.
Just desert bone.
All right.
Let's go fight the boss after I get healed.
Do I have good spells?
I have water.
I've got the level 30 water one.
I'm sure that's going to do some damage.
I guess I could just run through more protein blobs.
If I get one shot, you better believe that I'm going immediately to the next game.
Absolutely positive.
Because that would be so sad.
What is this game?
This game is for the Dreamcast.
It's called, I don't know why I was just going to say Steins Gate.
That's not what this is.
They're not even remotely similar.
Save before the boss.
Okay, hold on.
Let me see if this is even possible.
Can I just pull out the fucking EMP device?
This ain't going to crash my game, right?
Shouldn't.
Because I can go through this and like delete shit.
Okay, here we go.
I can turn this on.
How do I turn this shit on?
Can you act to access the Dreamcast screen?
Do I have a second Dreamcast I can plug in?
It needs batteries.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
I think the battery is already in here, aren't there?
It's okay.
I'll get that.
When I take my next break,
I'm not going to die.
I'll grab some batteries.
That beep means it has none.
Okay.
It's good to know.
D'erba is taking longer to grow legs than actual prehistoric beings.
All right, I'm getting stuck.
Crab doesn't even hurt anymore.
Look at how far we've come.
Please, batteries, save us from this hell.
Now, I am a crab now.
That's right.
Okay, I need protein blobs.
You're not really going to come at me, are you?
Just go fight the boss.
I need batteries.
I can't do that yet.
What kind of batteries go in here?
They're not like AA or AAA.
Is it like a watch battery?
What do I got for the prod?
Where is my prod?
It's not even on here.
It's a quadruple A.
I haven't ran into any blobs.
For some reason, there's no audio anymore.
Okay, there it is now.
Go to Walmart and get them.
No, we just can't lose.
I'm not going to lose.
That's all that has to happen.
Where are these stupid blobs?
Finally, it took you ages to spawn.
What do I got now?
All right, I'm going in.
I'm going in.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
Really?
Water 2.
Bingo.
Dead.
One hit.
Where's my character?
Why don't I have control of the character?
I'm fine.
Look at that.
It's okay.
It's all right.
We're trading hits.
Dead.
I'm going to run out of shit here.
What the fucking god damn it?
Come on, why?
What the hell?
Back it up, that's it.
Okay, I have a heal too.
Look at all these random powers.
How do I get EP back?
I wonder what's most effective against the slug.
Fire, lightning.
Water 2 does a lot of, I would assume it's way more damage.
Use lightning and make you both crispy.
Yeah, that would happen.
All right, I got to get out of the menu.
All right, let's go.
I am going to heal though one more time to get to full health.
I wasn't taking very much damage there.
And I do have a heal so I can run around in a circle.
You are just pathetic.
I remember you too.
I did like a YouTuber scream when you guys came over that first time.
Not now.
I can't get the cursor to attack to go over you.
Get over here.
Okay.
Yeah, I've got power now.
And once we beat this boss, we get to unlock the next zone.
And then I get to put on the monkey legs.
Let's try it again.
Lightning.
Thankfully, the internet has gotten back to normal.
All right, lightning one.
A little zap.
I'm going to take a hit here.
That's fine.
I thought that the disc reading that you thought was my heavy breathing.
Watch out for the fucking cave entrance.
Oh boy.
Like I probably would have been able to trade blows back and forth.
Why is that even in the game?
I'll tell you, I can tank the hits at close.
He's barely hurting me up close.
He's dead.
I win.
Everyone thought I was going to lose.
You all thought I was done.
You thought I lost.
You thought the game was over.
I win.
And I'm going to eat him.
I just ate his whole body.
That's going to be at least like 500 points.
And I was going to touch the stones from Diablo.
Teleport.
Evolution.
No!
I'm not ready for this.
Can I go back?
I'm not ready.
I can.
Let's try maybe...
We haven't really done very much red.
That's not been very much red at all.
Arm 16.
Too many.
Too many dots.
Green and white.
Head 28.
I need more body.
I only have two bodies.
Red and blue.
There it is.
Body 15.
Perfect.
I can do another one.
I can do one more.
Yellow and blue.
Try yellow, blue down here.
Three yellows and then blue tipos.
Head 13.
All right.
Can you explain what you're doing right now?
Well, essentially, I have no idea.
I couldn't tell you if I tried.
I have absolutely no explanation for what's happening in the game.
How it works, I guess, is you have a grid.
It's a DNA algorithm where you have stats.
All the different colors are stats.
You pick stats in the beginning of the game based on a color's attack.
For instance, like offense is red.
Defense is blue.
And then you use the grid here to make body parts
when you get enough protein or EVP, especially protein.
And then you put together and then you make a body part,
which you have whatever it is.
All right.
So we've got lizard, head, lizard, Rex.
Crystal is the head.
So lizard.
Still can't put it on.
I've got new arms too.
Stab scorpion.
Electric mollusk.
I can just, no, I can't.
Electric mollusk and demon.
Electric mollusk sounds kind of cool.
That's a huge attack.
Hammer lobster.
Well, that's quite a defense increase.
And that's a much better heal.
I'm going to say it's probably worth it.
There's one more, right?
Lizard, Rex.
I feel like I need a PhD to understand this.
Hey, I, yeah.
Let me just take a quick look.
It's okay.
The organisms are idiots.
They can't even hurt me.
We're fine.
Oh God.
What's that?
What's that thing?
I do want more protein though.
It just, it seems so rare.
What is this?
I think it's just another area.
Yeah, we're out of the pond now, guys.
There's more than one zone.
I'm going to get so lost.
Still no protein.
Where's the protein?
Anywhere?
Come on.
I'm dying here.
There's another random little enemy.
Oof.
This is, this is not going well here with the frame rate.
Spear nose.
It barely hurts.
Oh, no, no, no.
Just attack.
You can't, nobody can hurt me.
Am I overleveled?
There was another one.
Why did I, I just got really bored right now.
It just happened right this second.
Look at all these things.
That guy hurts.
Okay, I gotta run.
Those guys hurt a lot.
I'm fine.
EX power, water, water too.
Here they come.
They're still on the way.
This game is depressing.
If I could find some more protein, that would be a start.
I'm just going to keep going.
At least straight here.
They went too hard on the gas.
You're in a pond.
We were just walking around in the pond.
And now all of a sudden it's an expansive gigantic ocean with no end.
Does the compass mean anything?
I really have no idea.
Somebody said earlier that it means that there's a food source or something.
I haven't been able to figure out what the hell that means.
Now we're going deep sea.
Oh shit, too deep.
I need the level 20 flashlight head.
I think this just might be the end of the game here, the end of the world.
I just want to put on the monkey legs.
Monkey legs don't help if they're underwater.
That's true, but in the same fashion.
Don't, doesn't somebody gonna sub for five months if I got out of the water?
Why is that the thing moving me forward?
Is that protein?
Damn it.
Just swim up.
I can't swim up.
There's no scale there.
Well, that was, uh, super evolution.
I don't know what the game's called.
Your protein gets drained when you recover HP.
Does it really?
You do not go on land in the whole game.
At least you do.
I guess that guy's not going to be subbing.
It doesn't seem like it.
It's okay.
This game reminds me of the games my dad played in the 90s.
That's because it is the game that was made in the 90s.
It's a 90s game for 90s dads.
Is there a reason why I can't pick that up?
I need the monkey legs.
All right.
Well, if I can't reliably get some more protein to progress,
I think we hit the point where it might be time to next the game.
Interesting concept.
Wish a game would come out like this that's current gen.
Thank God.
What?
This was fun.
I had a good time.
It was worth it.
So we have a couple options here.
That was EVP 14.
No, it's not.
That's what the screen says.
Shield your eyes.
It's going to...
No, it's not.
I got it.
I turned off the stream to watch paint dry.
And it wasn't as exciting as what I was just doing.
So there are a couple of survival horror games that remain.
Tony Hawk is going to be a long time.
I don't think I'm going to do Tony Hawk.
I think I'm just going to play Tony Hawk 2 tomorrow.
Like I'm just going to play the game.
I'm just going to just beat Tony Hawk 2.
As that's going to be at least a few hours.
Blue Stinger is a survival horror game, I believe.
Power Stone?
I still got Power Stone as well.
Why is this sealed so strangely?
How can one single piece of tape be this powerful?
What was that game that I just played right now that was...
That's not...
It's not the Flogen Brothers.
I just took it out.
That was called Seventh Cross Evolution.
Seventh Cross Evolution.
Steins Gate.
I'm not going to snap the disc.
All these games were at least like...
At least like 20 to 40 dollars each.
I'm not snapping a 40 dollar piece of plastic.
Maybe not that one.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not doing that.
I need to go remove shit from this.
All right, let's see.
File.
So we've got NHL 2K Saved Season from the year 2000.
Okay, we need to get rid of that.
Star Wars Episode I Jedi Power Battles.
There is a Pac-Man in here somehow.
Get rid of that.
ECW.
Who's going to play that ever again?
Namco Museum.
High score.
We need these blocks.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is Ready to Rumble Boxing.
Mike.
Okay.
And then this is just a saved game options for Ready to Rumble Boxing.
What do you mean stop?
What is this asking me to do?
What does this have to do with a saved game wipe?
Oh, there's a fork and knife.
Okay, I get it.
All right, we're free.
Ready to go.
This blue stinger.
It's going to be so fun.
Let me pee one more time.
While this game loads in...
Actually, no, let me get to the menu first.
So fun, yeah.
It's going to be fun.
What are you talking about?
Climax Graphics.
Is this the company?
Blue Stinger.
1999.
So just give me a moment.
This will probably end up being the last thing we do tonight
because it is getting to be a little bit later.
Been about six and a half hours on stream.
Probably going to go for about seven to eight.
And we'll pick it up again tomorrow.
And I'm going to play the absolute shit out of Tony Hawk.
I will show you a one million point string of tricks.
You don't think I know how to do manuals.
We're going to go back.
I'm going to complete the floor again, brothers.
Just kidding.
That's not going to happen.
All right.
Blue Stinger.
What's going on?
He's breathing.
Just going to say what?
What did I do?
You didn't say you were leaving.
Didn't I say I had to go pee?
And I'll be right back?
I said I have to pee and I'll be right back.
I cut myself off.
What did you think I was going to say?
Difficulty.
That's fine.
Blue Stinger.
You were talking about Floyd again.
All right.
Cut scene, cut scene.
You got to be quiet.
Is it cut scene?
Hold on.
All right.
I glanced away from the screen and I turned back.
I didn't expect that helicopter is going to drive into the ground.
I'm not a pilot of that helicopter.
Did I just ghost ride it into the ground?
Nice sneakers too.
I skipped it.
I didn't skip anything.
I didn't skip any cut scenes.
What?
I did not skip the intro.
Those sneakers absolutely look like they've made out of chocolate.
Those don't look like real shoes.
Analog.
I feel like this game is going to be fun.
Let's go.
Follow the press the start button.
This is Elliot Balad.
Easter Troop C730 over codex.
This is Janine King.
KISS Dinosaur Island Security Officer.
The pilot is under an emergency situation.
Do you read?
Dispatch T-70 for rescue.
The location is-
I fucking forget to mute the mic.
I hate that noise.
Just as much as-
I got cut off.
All right.
I'm Elliot with one L.
It's Brutus.
Oh, that guy's not here.
Is that intentional?
Yeah.
You found Small Hassy.
What was the point of that guy?
That's it.
He's just stalking me.
But apparently he's not.
All right.
Through the front door.
Let's go.
Another codex call.
Who is it?
I repeat.
I need an EASER unit now.
Elliot Balad.
Do you hear me?
Same damn thing as Ibleed.
This is Elliot Balad.
We request D7 equipped rescue unit now.
The location is-
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
I'm on vacation.
I'm totally unarmed.
So-
So?
I need help too.
Oh, great.
Tell me your location, Elliot.
Yeah, I have my favorite past time.
All I can tell you is that-
Jumping out of helicopters and crashing them into the ground.
Okay, Elliot.
First, find an ID card.
I'm sure there are a number of corpses around.
You should be able to find one of them with an ID card.
What happened to her?
What happened?
Corpses?
Did you say there are a number of corpses around?
Where?
More diarrhea cramp sounds.
What's with all the Dreamcast games
and everybody having stomach ache problems?
Okay.
Oh, no.
Corpses!
I'll call you back.
You found a credit card.
Is there a sprint?
No.
What does my shirt say?
They're gonna get up.
I thought this was a survival horror game.
I guess it technically is.
Except I'm gonna make a reference here.
No, don't make that reference.
People are gonna be like, what?
And then some people are gonna be like, whoa.
Speaking of-
Okay, that's-
There's this is a survive-
This is a-
Yeah, it is.
Oh my god!
Okay, that was fucking scary.
No sound, no noise.
No sound effects.
Just scary.
The parental controls are turned off in the options menu.
Really?
Alright, door's locked.
I have the key though, right?
Yeah, your level four arms couldn't save you.
Level two arms.
Jesus!
Monsters just got way, way cooler.
Well, there he is.
This is fucking Wario.
With his shorts.
That was close.
Thanks for helping me.
My name is Elliot G. Balad.
Where's Tim?
Breaking every rule in filmmaking.
Dogs.
I'm a captain of the SSDN.
If you're Elliot, you must be with Tim.
Breaking every single rule.
Tim is what?
Dead?
You're looking at the same part of the screen.
I don't know.
I don't know!
Is that Aesir's answer?
You know, Tim once told me he had a high level Aesir member as a friend.
Where are you going to the island?
I am still a rescuer.
There are people there who need help.
What a joke.
Just changed to 180 degrees?
Obviously.
Why would the camera do that?
Good help, like me.
I can't let a wimp like you go alone.
Whatever.
The guy's a magician.
He's just gone.
He seems to have that ability.
Somehow.
You wimp, you'll never make it by yourself.
Puff of smoke underneath him.
Go back to the freezer aisle.
Keep selling fish sticks.
Gorton.
How do I get in here?
That ID card doesn't work?
No, okay.
All right, we got some more dead space enemies.
Magazine of arrows.
Okay.
I'm gonna stand up.
This is already ten times better than the last game.
He's he just appeared next to me.
Kill it.
Is it inceptioning something into my brain here?
Sell all of your stocks.
Nephilim.
The hell is that?
It was a Nephilim.
I'm not sure.
Bad feeling about this.
Bye.
It's just Deckard Kane.
Uh-oh.
Monster mutant.
I guess I do.
Items.
Food.
Small Hassy.
Would you like to have a small Hassy?
Oh, what was the funny Illbleed story?
Oh, sorry.
Now this game kind of just threw me off for a second there.
So Illbleed is like almost a hundred dollars.
And I had to cut it because I was thinking of,
okay, we'll do a Dreamcast night, see how people feel.
I think Illbleed is like 70 or 80 dollars.
Good thing I'm in that realm.
A character from the evolution game.
I'm gonna get revenge.
No.
It's just dead.
What the hell?
Over there.
I am not skipping cutscenes.
I can't believe it.
Shooting from that far?
No shit.
Janine?
A woman?
This is Janine Over.
You're great.
If you're an ESER member,
you'll definitely be ranked A plus.
You're flattering me,
but you won't get anywhere that way.
You can get in here by taking the slope shuttle in front of you.
If the shuttle is moving, that is.
And forget it if you don't have an ID card.
Oh, where am I gonna get an ID card?
Phew, tough girl.
I like it, Janine.
Who the hell is Janine?
My kind of girl.
So stay away from her.
Uh, that's, um...
You literally just had a conversation.
You just saw her from a distance.
And I believe that was four sentences.
I think you might want to pump the brakes just a little bit.
Door's locked.
I need a key card.
Gate check.
Door locked.
We don't have the card to open this door.
Push the old guy off.
Uh, he's not on the screen.
Did I miss something over here?
Door's locked.
Change character.
This guy's name is Doggs.
Do I have the key?
This guy, I thought he was just wearing socks.
Um, am I stuck here?
Wasting ammo?
I don't see anything.
I mean, map or something?
There's no info here.
I mean, this is this.
I don't think he has the key for this.
Door's locked.
There's really only one way to go.
His defense.
Everybody wore jorts back in the 90s.
I'm not so certain they did.
I don't think they did.
Well, I did.
This door's locked.
Scan your eyes.
There's no one else to go.
Is there anything else back here?
What just happened?
Uh, I guess I'm gonna go this way.
No, I don't wear jorts.
Where is this?
What is this door?
There was a room I didn't...
Okay, to the right?
Bridge tunnel.
Tunnel one.
Is there a place to the right over here?
I mean, this is the beginning of the game.
I don't have an indicator on the screen.
Let me look at the map.
Do I have a...
Is there a blip that's supposed to be me?
I don't think it...
I don't think it exists.
Uh, shit!
Okay, I'm...
Come on.
Where's this room that I didn't go in?
It's not here.
Can we go back to the ring?
No, not tonight.
No, not this way.
No, right.
Okay, we're just gonna keep going.
Continue forward with it.
Push the crate to the right.
This crate?
Why would anyone ever do this?
Why would you ever move this?
Why would you even look at this crate?
He really is Wario.
Yeah, he just went like...
There's more than one item up there.
Is there no ID?
A gun?
There's lockers.
This is a very claustrophobic...
Do you want to turn to download the map?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, download complete.
I got the map now.
And there are two items up there, somebody said.
Here you go!
So there's another thing...
What is this?
You found a handgun magazine, okay.
All right, let's go.
Now I can move on.
Blue Stinger.
Move on to the next game.
Hold on, I just...
I'm almost about to go through the first door I haven't been able to go through.
Turn off the key.
The door over this way?
No, I'm not done.
That's breaking the rule.
There we go!
Through the door.
There's like tendrils.
All right, got it.
This music is going to drive me crazy.
What's with these Dreamcast games?
And their EDF soundtracks?
Can't open this one.
Or fan-made Star Wars themes.
There's a huge keypad right here.
The person is going to get up.
What's that?
An magazine of arrows.
That's good.
Do you want to download the map?
Yes.
Vending machines?
Display contents of v...
Oh, it's a save point.
Do you want to...
Yes, I do want to save.
Really, is Wario.
Select the item you want to buy.
A hot dog is $120.
Hamburger $160.
Or a Hasee is $60.
Okay, it's an expensive hot dog.
God damn it.
Now I want a hot dog.
I'm hungry now.
I got the map.
Where the hell am I?
Brain area?
Brain.
This door is unlocked.
It can't be unlocked.
So I went in that way.
This door is locked.
So I have to go this way.
Control room.
Okay, I threw up the other party member.
Emergency alert.
Shuttle section should be stationed.
I wonder if I've been in Vegas.
It's about four months now.
Negative pressure on the shuttle holder system has increased 20%.
The security limitation is exceeded on shuttle system.
Security break has been activated.
Shutter outer seal has been broken.
Once shuttle reaches security limitation stage, shuttle may descend rapidly.
Hey, somebody is on board.
He's locked up in the shuttle.
He screamed.
Activate the emergency stop control.
Remember the sound that I've played a couple times now that on the...
A shaft entrance lock has been deactivated.
That's the stock sound that I...
Activate the emergency stop control.
I'll play it.
Safety break will be destroyed in 125 seconds.
A shaft entrance lock has been deactivated.
Activate the emergency stop control.
Safety break will be destroyed in 120 seconds.
A shaft entrance lock has been deactivated.
That is the bugleberry.
A shaft entrance lock destroyed.
The shuttle is going to fall.
I got a time limit.
Fuck.
What do I have to do?
I didn't...
I was trying to find a scream.
Which way do I go?
This door is unlocked.
Okay.
Out.
Dodge.
Nice nonchalant running.
Lots of blood.
These huge pratfalls.
That looks painful.
I'm almost there.
What?
Uh...
Wasn't supposed to go there apparently.
Oof.
Ah.
This...
I don't do anything here?
I don't climb up this or anything?
Nothing?
Oh.
Just put them in the pocket for a little while.
So that was the wrong way.
Let's see.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
What was that?
Was that supposed to happen?
Why was there a countdown for that?
I guess that was supposed to happen.
So I walked all the way up here.
I was supposed to stop it?
The Dreamcast fucking sucks laughing my ass off.
I don't know why that's making me laugh so hard.
Why?
It doesn't though.
Dreamcast is a great system.
We didn't even play Tony Hawk yet.
Dynamite Cop was awesome.
You can't deny that.
Listen.
We didn't even play Shenmue.
Shenmue 2.
Sonic Adventure.
Space Channel 5.
Crazy Taxi.
All of which were ported and run way better on PC now.
But they were on Dreamcast a long time ago.
That's what matters.
What do I have to do here?
Okay.
Shuttle A is deactivated.
Shuttle B is deactivated now.
Am I gonna get another timer?
Please just let the Death Star blow up already.
All right.
This door is locked.
How do I open the door?
Was that actually...
All right.
I gotta calm down.
Hold on.
Just give me a second.
I can't mute the music.
It's impossible.
I have to mute the whole game.
Okay.
I can't get it out of my head.
I can't get it out.
Okay.
So do I have to reload the save?
I don't know why this is doing it to me so hard.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why.
Let me heal.
No, I don't want to...
I'm gonna just get the other guy.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know why this is happening right now.
Okay.
I'm gonna backtrack.
My god.
Okay.
So that fell down.
Therefore, I'm gonna turn the music down.
I gotta mute...
All right.
So I downloaded some new maps.
We got brain area.
Let me look.
So that's...
Where was...
I'm gonna go check the tunnel that I was in again.
Okay.
I'll try.
Check that slope tunnel again.
Okay.
I should've...
Why did I get this instead of Ill Bleed?
It's making me laugh so hard because...
It's just...
I can smell the boredom coming from that person's comment.
And like, these are the games that are being shown.
And if you've never heard...
If you've never seen the Dreamcast, you've never heard of it before.
This like...
This sucks.
But there's so much more in Dreamcast.
Dreamcast is like a great system.
There are actually like at least...
At least like 10 games that are really fantastic.
Like genre-defining experiences.
But anyways, check the slope tunnel again.
Name three Shenmue.
Shenmue.
Power Stone.
And Dynamite Cop!
How do I get out of this?
I have to push the crate up the slope?
What crate?
Do something!
I'm sorry!
I don't understand!
The timer ran out and I have nothing to do!
There's a ladder?
Where's the ladder?
On the right side?
I just passed the ladder on the right side.
There's a ladder up all the way to the top.
I got my sound muted.
Why is he running...
Okay, I see a ladder here.
It's just like...
You're talking about the most chameleon ladder I've ever seen.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
The A shuttle is out of order.
I'm gonna progress.
Oh my god.
Pull?
Just keep walking?
Where the hell did I end up?
What the f...
Where did you come from?
I'm gonna have to drink that large hassy in a second.
Are you gonna kill me?
You killed me.
I can't get out of here.
Oh yeah, I can.
No, I gotta give this game a...
No, this game's not...
This game's fun.
You give games too many chances.
No, this is a fun experience.
It's a genre-defining experience.
It's been 40 minutes.
God damn it.
Has it actually?
This genre sucks.
No, it doesn't.
Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 is best played on the Sega Dreamcast.
When it came out, it was at the best graphics.
It was played the best in the best control system.
Look, I don't want to play the whole cart, you know?
I told you at the beginning of the stream.
I got an ace, I got a queen, and I got a ten.
I don't want you to see the king.
Or the jack right here.
Well, the ace...
No, actually, this is the ace and the king.
Power Stone and Tony Hawk 2 are probably the best games on the system.
You've been playing Uno cards.
No, this one's gonna take a while.
So what did we go through tonight?
It's also been seven hours.
Let me just double check to see for tomorrow.
Let me take a look.
We've got an ace, a king, a queen.
We've got...
And then two terrible games.
And then one more survival horror.
Okay.
I'm gonna call it here.
Because it's getting later.
It's been about seven hours.
Seaman also...
I want to...
I didn't address Seaman.
I did a couple times, but I want to do it again.
I was supposed to play Seaman tonight.
But the microphone did not come in the package where I bought it from.
They sent me...
They missed...
It was missing.
And it explicitly stated the microphone was in the package.
So I have to get it again.
I have to reorder it.
Anywho, it has to be a specific mic.
Only one mic works.
It's the one you plug in to the VMU slot.
That was a pretty good C minus stream.
At least it wasn't an F.
I'll take that.
Jerma got scammed.
No, I bought it through Amazon.
I had fun.
Dynamite Cop is actually one of the better arcade games.
I think that was a blast.
What else did we play?
ECW was terrible.
Seventh Cross had potential and it was fun for a little while.
Floggin Brothers was terrible, but it was still interesting.
The Ring was barely even a playable video game.
Floggin was like, all right.
Yeah, it was.
So tomorrow, we got the ace and the king.
We got the real games lined up for tomorrow.
Power Stone, Tony Hawk 2.
I'm going to put a ton of time into Tony Hawk 2.
So be prepared for tomorrow's stream to be
Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 for like four to six hours.
And then we'll go through some of these other ones.
All two good Dreamcast games.
And by the way, all the other great like Shenmue, Jet Set Radio,
Space Channel 5, I own them on PC.
So they're still going to happen.
It's just I kind of need to get through the ones that are connected to the actual console.
Because once these are done, we can move on like Sega Bass.
Yeah, it's on Steam.
There's a whole package on Steam.
I own them all, but I have to kind of do these first.
So we're kind of going through a little bit of the garbage can first
and some other classic ones that are not available anywhere else.
But I still have a lot.
I had a lot of fun.
I it's something oddly satisfying and interesting to go through old
games that you've never really seen or played before.
It's like a new it's different era.
It's it's I like it.
I like just putting the disc in.
And what do we get?
It's something it's like a it's like a little Forrest Gump box of chocolates.
You know, you just never know.
Sometimes you get like three or four duds in a row.
Sometimes there's a really good one in there.
So we're going to go with bits.
And then when we're done with Dreamcast stuff,
which would probably be after tomorrow,
there'll probably be only a couple left.
Oh, what do you guys think?
So should I start with like should I start with the rest of the dog shit
and then move into like the good ones or should I start with Tony Hawk
and just play Tony Hawk?
I'm trying to figure that out.
Now that makes sense.
Start with dog shit and then go from terrible games to okay.
And out here is like that was like a couple hours.
There they go.
And now we're going to play Tony Hawk for the rest of the night.
That makes sense.
You can only go up at that point.
All right, let's do the bits and the subs.
Thanks everybody for watching.
It's always an interesting time.
If you stick it around.
Awesome.
If not, then I will see you hopefully tomorrow.
Probably around the same time.
Three ish PM Pacific.
It's open.
Oh, Resident Evil 2 Remake is going to start
once we're done with the Dreamcast stuff,
at least the physical Dreamcast stuff.
So after tomorrow, I'm assuming I'll be done with all the physical stuff.
And then that brings us to what?
Friday?
Today's Saturday.
That'll bring us to Sunday.
So I'll probably start Resident Evil 2 Remake on Monday.
But thanks for watching.
Sometimes you guys just do it to me, man.
That shit was I don't know why that one comment made me fucking laugh so hard.
It was like I couldn't even control myself anymore.
So many things are going through my mind.
I'm going to be laughing about that in bed tonight.
I'm just going to be lying there with my iPad,
just looking at like Reddit or something.
And I'm just going to happen.
Anyways, I hope you guys had a good time.
I hope it was interesting enough.
If it wasn't, then we'll try again tomorrow.
So let's go back to earlier tonight.
We have a dollar from Dr. Steen.
What are the plans streams for the near future after Dreamcast and Resident Evil?
Oh, that's a good question.
I really I leave it kind of up in the air.
I usually try to plan out a couple weeks of streams.
So on the when I have like a day off,
I usually try to sit there and think of, hey, what can we do?
What's something fun to do this week or next week or something?
Obviously, a major game release ties into that.
But there are a lot of requests people have.
There's a lot of recommendations that they could fit in.
I was always curious about Blue Stinger and Interested.
Yeah, but that's you got to remember this.
It's not like the best representation of the game
because obviously it's very old
and there's probably so much more after it.
And I might maybe I'll try to jump back into it again tomorrow
because it's it's definitely worth playing.
I think maybe the music's a little too loud, but it's OK.
But after that, after Dreamcast, after Resident Evil 2,
I don't know, there's a couple of small projects
and larger projects that I want to try to do
and get done at some point before the spring,
which should be fun.
And you'll find out maybe more about those a little bit later.
There's also the movie Encore Night.
The green screen Encore Night is what I mean.
I want us to get that set up too over the next couple weeks.
But I don't I don't plan out three, four weeks,
so a month out of streams.
They kind of just whatever I feel like doing
is what I usually feel like doing.
But thank you to Dr. Steen.
Thank you.
Trust no one for the one dollar.
Hello there, Jeremy.
I can clearly see that you had such a chill
and pleasant stream today.
It's so nice and sweet.
Yes, indeed.
However, please never forget that life is pain
and you hate it.
Let me remind you of that.
Mind you.
Actually, let me turn off the Dreamcast.
There now you can hear me clearly.
Let's see.
Let's get reminded.
What the hell is this?
This is German 95.
Only competent Dark Souls streamer of 2019.
I've seen this year.
That means a lot considering I've struggled a lot
with this game when I first played it.
Wow, that what a confidence boost.
Thank you for that.
Seriously, that was a super confidence boost.
I can do anything now.
I'm capable of anything.
Oh, I'm facing the wrong fucking direction.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dude, this is hell.
I can't even.
Oh, what the fuck happened?
One hit, what the?
I'm fucking deleting that weapon.
The Watchers is not even going to be as hard as this.
Same.
Suck my bum.
Come on.
Come on first person.
Holy shit.
It's so hard.
Barable.
Oh, it's so hard.
It's too much.
It's too much to handle.
The distance.
It's hard to tell what the distance is.
It's my mind.
I don't know why I continue to do it.
I told you I was going to beat it first fucking try.
That was a great video, first of all.
Second of all.
Dirtiest NFL cheap shots.
I'm not going to watch.
I don't want to watch that right now.
No, that was very hard.
That's one of the hardest things ever.
The dodging and the fra-
I don't even need to explain it.
Too many emotions on that stream.
But thank you for that.
That was great.
That was Trust No One.
And here's the link to that video if you'd like to watch it.
Thank you.
Thank you to FutureGamer for the $1.
Do you ever get those gluten tests back?
No, I actually have not.
I have to go back to the doctor to get them back.
And I had a series of-
I had a shitload of things come back.
But the doctor that I have right now is-
I can't get them over the phone.
So I actually have to physically go in for a doctor's appointment
because they won't tell me the results over the phone.
So it's like, okay.
So I got to make a new appointment and go back in.
And I haven't done that in the last like week and a half or so.
So I got to go back.
But everything else was great.
I had a lot of other tests to make sure that nothing else was going on.
And all my blood work was okay.
There was some- I had some high calcium.
Like, I don't know if you guys remember.
I brought it up maybe like three or four months ago.
I had a fairly high blood calcium for no reason.
And I guess there's like, oh, you make sure you keep an eye on that.
And I had another couple of tests done.
And over the last couple of months,
it hasn't really gone any higher.
It's receded back a little bit.
So it's not a problem anymore.
So that's good.
But everything else is fine.
Just going to try to find out if I'm intolerant.
I did a full food allergy panel.
So we'll see.
Kidney health, kidneys are fine.
Kidneys are fine.
Liver is fine.
Everything's pretty much perfectly fine.
But I appreciate the concern.
Thank you, future gamer.
And all of you, everyone obviously with the love in the chat.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Hack it fast.
Thanks for the $1.
Jet set or choo-choo rocket.
Also, I eat ass.
Now that's on you.
That's for you to do and decide if that's what you're going to do.
Hey, pigeon.
Thanks for the $1.
They say, if you decide against it, it's none of my business.
And I'm okay with that.
Thanks for the great content.
Keep it up.
Changed my name recently.
What is this?
The Sega Dreamcast microphone.
Yeah.
That's the worst part about the things I bought.
So I bought Seaman and it was very expensive.
It was an embarrassing amount of money to pay for something.
And when it did not come with the microphone, I was like,
number one, somebody might be trying to scam me.
Or number two, they just forgot.
But I did a refund through Amazon and it apparently works.
So I just have to set it back.
But the fate of Seaman, you will see it.
Just not within the next couple of days.
I'm just going to load it up one day.
And just play it for like an hour and just fuck around.
But pigeon, thank you for the $2 here.
It's similar more links to the microphone stuff.
Which I will definitely be trying to get one.
Whether that's through another Amazon order or through another means.
So definitely.
Thank you.
Dorkcube, thanks for the $1.
What a plot twist that you would end up interacting with Joel more than Vinny.
I interact with Vinny.
They're both fucking cool.
What are you talking about?
Why do you...
What do you mean neglect?
I don't have any...
It's organic.
Organic.
Something that if you hang out with somebody,
you don't hang out with somebody.
Like versus Kraken was in Vegas.
You know, when was the last time somebody like streamed with Kraken?
You hit me up.
Hey, I'm in Vegas.
Yeah, I'll let come say hello.
Yeah, that organic.
We did and it was great.
Thank you, Dorkcube.
Thank you, Gib for the $5.
Maggie Simpson, binky sound when you swim.
Thank you, the cows are watching me for the $10.
Hey, German, just want to tell you thanks for all the great laughs through the years.
Hope you have an awesome 2019.
By the way, love the Kenshi streams.
Thanks.
Thank you for supporting any of the content that I put out here.
Any of the video games that I play, any of the stuff that I do.
Thank you, it means a lot.
And I just hope that you're having fun.
One of the reasons why I purchase stuff like Dreamcast
and buy a bunch of random games
and just see what looks like could be fun or interesting
is because that's why I want to do it.
I want it to be an interesting experience for all of us.
And it is, I think, a lot sometimes.
I know that was just an oxymoron, but
arm level two is going to be in the next year of a rumble
and it's going to be a tiny small person with just one jacked arm.
And that's kind of has to happen.
But thank you so much for the $10.
Hey, LMM, thanks for the $3.
No message, but thank you.
Also, I want to say this one more time.
Well, I'm going to kind of transition it over the next couple of weeks.
I'm changing the minimum bits for readings.
But I didn't really want to just throw that and be like,
Darn it! Okay, it's $3 now.
So over the next couple of weeks.
And then I'm going to kind of give like a cutoff.
We talked about it a couple of days ago.
Just about streamlining things.
And it was a very long conversation about money.
So it is turning into three.
300 bits will be the minimum for reading at the end of a stream.
And I don't think it is not $3 now.
I'm going to just, I just want to make people aware that in a few weeks,
somewhere probably in February, that I'm going to keep talking about it.
I'm going to make sure people are aware.
Because I think last time, a lot of people weren't aware of it.
And I kind of just made it $1 like a year and a half ago.
And then people were still spending, you know, 25 cents or 50 cents.
And they were writing these very nice thought out messages.
And I just wasn't, I don't think they even knew.
So I'm not just going to do it immediately like I did kind of last time.
But I have to do another explanation for it.
We just, we've seen such extreme growth on this channel.
With viewership and money and support.
And it's kind of, it's kind of a necessary evil at this point.
You know, even just in viewership alone,
it's gone up about nearly 35% or so in just people that are just here.
Hope you guys understand it's I'm not trying to just bleed money out of people.
I'm just trying to have, I'm just trying to like run the best stream that I can.
I hope you understand.
And we'll maybe, we'll see.
We'll see how it goes.
Another year or two, I mean, I had the last minimum for about a year and a half, right?
Maybe a little bit more, like just over a year, maybe.
I don't really see there's an opportunity why it would be increased again anytime soon at all.
And maybe never again.
But that will be happening in the next few weeks.
Just want to make people aware of it.
But thank you LMM for the three bucks.
Thank you Dork Cube for the one dollar.
Those poor developers.
They put all their time and effort into creating a new IP only for it to die on
the operating table.
But you, Jerma, you can continue on their legacy.
That's right.
Floydgan Brothers for Jerma Rummel.
We, you know, there was some talk that we've got potentially like a C minus stream here.
But interestingly enough, even in like a C minus stream,
there are probably five new characters that I can put into a wrestling event.
That's pretty great.
Floydgan Brothers tag team match that messed up Alien that I made.
Level two arm.
They're a lot.
But they're all C minus characters.
But I kid.
Kidding.
I missed the stream so it gets an F.
No, I had fun.
There was one or two places where I didn't.
But not really.
Out of a seven plus hour stream, I think I had fun for about six hours and 42 minutes.
I wish I had like an exact screenshot of when that happened.
I think I remember who it was.
Exactly.
It was, it was, it was Penny.
It was Penny Kettle.
It was just perfect.
It came at a perfect time.
Yeah, that came at a perfect time.
It was unbelievably timed.
Like that's a bravo.
But thank you, Dorku.
Thank you, Smelly Boy, for the one dollar.
The Floydgan Brothers better be in the next rumble.
They will be.
Hyena Dip, thanks for the one dollar.
This is just of Mice and Men, the game.
Casey, thanks for the one dollar.
The voices of the Floydgan Brothers are the voices of Scooby and Max from a goofy movie.
This game even actually had legitimate DLC.
Yeah, I can't, I, even when we were playing it.
Sure, it's a little slow.
Maybe a little too potentially boring for a stream, maybe.
But as a video game for a kind of young audience,
that was probably great back when it came out.
It just, it was, had to have been.
Thank you, Marvish McGally, for the one dollar.
Watching you beat Dynamite Cop with just four credits was very much worth it.
It's a great game.
Thank you, Freudian Weapon, for the two dollars.
Definitely going to track down a copy of Dynamite Cop for my Dreamcast gamebook's bonkers.
Yeah, it is more than one player.
It is, I believe, two players at least.
Oh, did Penny got gifted a sub?
Well, thank you for whoever did that.
I missed it.
What did Penny Kettle do?
Nothing, nothing bad.
It was just, it was very, very funny to me.
I was running up and down a slope in a game, and I can't even explain it.
It just was perfect.
I can't.
Wildfox, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, something you said recently maybe remembers a saying
that I came up with some years ago.
Political differences destroy friendships,
but complete political indifference destroys lives.
Refusing to talk about politics is a good decision, especially on stream.
On a side note, sorry if I haven't brought up depression a few times
with the few donations I made,
but it's very relieving to vent about it in a way.
No, that's okay.
Don't worry about that.
But yeah, politics and we touched upon it.
We talked about it already a few nights ago,
but I don't want to turn this stream into a debate
because that's not what it is intended for.
My intention to broadcast and hang out here
and do stuff and hang out with you guys
in like this live kind of broadcasted community thing
is not to start debates.
That's not why I'm here.
We're here just to hang out and have a good time.
That's it.
But I really appreciate it.
Thank you so much for the one dollar, Wildfox.
Lazy Luke, thanks for the one dollar.
We got a top 1,000 streamer piece of work here.
Did I go up any higher?
I was top 800 a few weeks ago.
Did I fall back down to earth?
What happened?
Am I back down to the top 1,000?
Then you played the Dreamcast and went back down.
It's a great system with some genre defining moments.
Coca-Cola classic.
But thank you to Jules for the one dollar.
I never heard of Dynamite Cop,
but Die Hard Arcade was also my favorite arcade game.
It's the only arcade game I ever beat in an actual arcade.
When I was like 12,
my brother and I spent hours in one sitting
playing this game.
I don't know how many quarters we spent playing this,
but it was so much fun.
After we beat the game,
I was surprised to see a crowd of about 30 spectators behind us.
Glad to hear that this was one of your favorite arcade games, too.
It is so fun.
And we're getting coxed here.
Just a little.
Jerma is a great streamer with some genre defining moments.
He sucks though, laughing my ass off.
It's the laughing my ass off part that I think did it to me.
But that's awesome, Jules.
Thank you for the one dollar.
Thank you, Snoozing Copter, for the one dollar.
All right, Jerma, how can you enjoy Dynamite Cop this much
and not even play 20 minutes of God Hand?
Don't answer, I know.
It takes time to get used to the controls in God Hand
and at least one or two hours.
Please play it again.
You'll love it.
Yeah, I did kind of just give up on God Hand, didn't I?
I don't know why.
Everybody threw their hats in the air and cheered.
But I think one of the things with these compilation,
retro kind of streams is because there are so many,
it's hard to put more than an hour or two into one of these.
And some of them obviously don't, I mean, there's a lot of them.
Most of them don't really necessarily even deserve an hour or two.
But the ones that do, in the back of my mind,
I'm always thinking, oh, I've been here for like two and a half hours,
but I got to stack this high next to me of other games to play.
But stuff like God Hand that requires that time,
especially during like a compilation night,
maybe it wouldn't be a bad, I mean, I still get the thing over there.
I just did, there's still like six, at least seven,
maybe eight PlayStation 2 games that are still over there.
All in due time, all things will happen, hopefully.
So many games and so little time during the day.
Yeah, I was thinking about going a little longer tonight,
but I really need to eat something.
I got to go take like a proper break and eat.
We are, let's see.
But thank you, Sneezing Copter.
Thank you, thank you Jess for the $1.
You remember Jamsters, what is a Jamster?
Holy shit, yeah, I remember this.
I forgot about that.
The original scam.
The original phone scam.
I buried that and you brought it back.
I forgot all about those commercials, but thank you.
Yeah, Crazy Frog was one of them.
Remember he was in the go-kart in some city at night?
It was a weird like Batmobile thing.
That's fucked up.
Thank you Carrot7 for the $1.
Two games in, I have determined that Dreamcast games
are the most chaotic neutral items in existence.
Kind of, yeah.
Thank you Alec for the $1.
You should play Bounty Hunter for the PS2.
Bounty Hunter, Star Wars, think you're talking about.
I do remember it being a very fun game.
Thank you, it's time for Slime for the $1 and it's a link.
Why would you give this to me right now?
I didn't even find that.
So the best part about this.
The name, this was uploaded in 2014.
This is called the Ring Terror's Realm.
You ready?
Are we still live?
This YouTube video is called the Ring Terror's Realm.
Most annoying music looped and extended.
So you guys weren't, it wasn't just you guys.
That's enough of that.
Getting some, I don't know what's going on with the internet recently.
We had a good solid probably five straight hours of no,
well I think, did we actually turn off?
I don't know.
We're getting kind of killed right now.
We're still live.
We're not going to zero, which is a good thing, but
the first hour or so of the stream was very chunky.
It looks like the last 40 minutes or so here have been also pretty chunky.
The middle about six, five or six hours was fine.
I'm going to make a call.
I'm going to have to make another phone call.
But we're good.
Thank you.
It's time for Slime for the annoying music.
Thank you Divus for the $2.
Appreciate it.
Someguy9 thanks for $5.
Since people seem to like my ARF video from last stream,
I'm back with another shitty meme video.
What the hell was that?
What was, what's a classic?
I don't any of these like meme videos.
Thank you Someguy9 for the $5.
Thank you Carrot for the $1.
I can't tell if I'm watching the ring or the room.
This game is a beautiful disaster.
Yeah, I just wish the game wasn't awful.
If we got to power through that and see more of those cutscenes,
the game just sucked.
It was just sloppy, bad Resident Evil in between some great cutscenes
and the whole cast of Family Guy.
It's just too bad that the game was unbearable.
Thank you Sawdust Bunnies for the $1.
Dreamcast was my first console,
so it's nice and nostalgic to see you play these great games.
There are some great ones.
Thank you Superman for the $1.
Hey German, notice you're wearing a UNH t-shirt.
I just wanted to know if you've ever visited New Hampshire
because I grew up there and had some of the best experiences of my life there.
Since I moved to California,
I've hated it and miss seeing the snow every winter.
Uh, that's not my shirt.
But yeah, I've been to New Hampshire plenty of times.
New Hampshire is a great state.
There's a lot of awesome, especially the mountains.
My family and I sometimes will go up and rent a house
and stay there for a little while.
Not so much anymore because I'm obviously across the country.
It was very easy just to be like,
all right, that's what we're going to do next weekend.
We're going to go for two days.
It's not even like a, it's barely like a two hour drive to get to New Hampshire.
Speaking of snow, yeah, didn't, um,
it didn't New England get kind of just crushed with a bad storm recently.
So what was up with the naked thing at the start of the stream?
Was that just a weird joke?
Um, a weird joke.
The camera captures a one frame and it keeps it there in the naked thing.
New England's about to get crushed by the Rams.
I don't think so.
Is the audio getting weird for people?
I keep seeing people say that.
I thought it was like a funny thing to do.
It's just to have no shirt on and like be unshowered.
Like I've got, my hair was just all messy and like greasy
and I like didn't have any clothes.
I thought it'd be like a funny joke.
Music is just cursed.
But yeah, I love New Hampshire.
It's a great state.
Thank you Casey for the $5.
Thank you for playing my favorite console.
There are still people that,
there are still people playing Dreamcast online if you can believe it.
Really, really hyped for the Tony Hawk stream tomorrow.
I grew up on that game.
It's one of my favorites.
Tony Hawk 2 is also the best one in the whole franchise.
It just is.
I am looking forward to it.
I am going to play the shit out of that game tomorrow.
But thank you Casey.
I do very much enjoy the Dreamcast as well.
Very, very interesting system.
Especially because it's Sega's last system.
So it's an interesting piece of hardware.
Hey smelly boy, thanks for the $1.
You better be ready for that one bare shoulder frame
to be in every piece of fan-made content for the next two years.
That's okay.
It was a funny fucking joke that I did.
It was a joke.
You think I was like,
you think I actually would do that
and make all the references about how I don't have clothes on ever?
Come on.
Like, Kappa.
Thank you Hasnain for the $1.
I lost $100 because you didn't die on Wednesday.
Thanks a lot.
Why would you ever take that bet?
That's a very bad bet to make.
Hey Trotter, thanks for the $1.
Jerma, what are you doing with the camera on when you were naked?
Setting up the stream.
That photo was taken at probably,
that frame was captured at probably like 2.45, 2.50 Pacific.
And I came back after showering and getting ready
and setting the stream up.
And it was setting up the live stream.
You had the door open so you just walk around naked.
I wasn't naked.
I was not naked.
I thought just walk around with just nudity.
I don't, that's not what happens.
Thank you Smelly Boy for the $1.
I saw your nude shoulder.
I'm sure you did, you did.
Thank you C4G for the $4.20 weed joke.
Will Jerma read this?
I just did.
Thank you for the $4.20 C4G.
Thank you Sam K42 for the $1.
A little tip for the stream.
Love you, Jerma.
Thank you.
And then Timmy Tim Tam, thanks for the $1.
Wow, I'm really tired.
Always a pleasure to hear these.
Housework.
I'm really tired and now I have to go home and cook.
Do you make dinner every night?
Yes, I usually make dinner and my husband washes the dishes.
I live alone so I do everything.
Sometimes I eat out though.
There are some good restaurants in my neighborhood.
Where do you live?
Near the Penn Center.
Oh, that's good.
There aren't any good restaurants near my house.
Does your husband help you do housework much?
Um, yes.
He sets the table almost every night and he makes our bed every morning.
But I usually make all the meals.
How about cleaning?
We clean the house together every weekend.
I vacuum the rooms and he usually sweeps the floor of the kitchen.
And he does yard work.
Your husband helps you so much.
Both these ladies are on coke.
Or like crack.
This is like this dude that there are drugs involved here.
They have, there are.
Does he help do the laundry too?
Well, he's never helped me do the laundry.
He's talking like so fast and with such a strange rhythm.
Small talk.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Well thank you for that.
And we had a few more come in as we were going over the other ones there.
Thank you RTM for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma, I was listening to the stream while playing Remake 2.
Just one review.
We're going to take a look at it on stream.
If not, definitely check it out on your own time.
It's an absolutely gorgeous game.
I'm going to be playing Resident Evil 2 on stream in a few days.
That's going to be the start of the next week.
I'm going to try to just complete it.
Because it's, how long is the game?
Well Kim, you don't do any of those things.
And then the laughing my ass off face.
Any of what things?
Well hold on, hold on, hold on a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's just go over a couple things here.
It's pulling weeds.
What about the pulling the weeds?
That's housework.
What about scrubbing the steps?
Is that not housework?
Took about an hour or two for me to do that.
Pulling weeds, huh?
That's yard work.
Well I do the yard work and Kim does the housework.
And then I do the dishes.
And then sometimes she sets the table.
I can relate to this.
Come on.
That's not the right video.
That's a different YouTube link.
Two hours to clean.
You don't have any idea.
You know how many times I've vacuumed?
My hands are raw with the amount of just yard work that I've done.
Breaking up rocks.
Pulling out shit.
Testing, you know.
Tapping, tapping, tapping.
Licking fingers.
Like is that good?
Is that clean?
Oh she's just having fun.
Okay.
It's in the oven?
Food is in the oven.
Oh okay.
Well thank you.
I'm sure it's delicious because you made it.
And I know it's going to be absolutely scrumptious.
Kim isn't modded or subbed.
Is that even the right, was that even the right Kim?
It's better than my rotten cooking.
You've never had the most succulent salmon of your life.
Unless you've had it by me.
Okay.
I do a butter au jus on top.
It goes in the pan.
I do the idea.
I tip, I put the oil in the butter and the cheese.
I tip it.
I do the Gordon Ramsay scoop, slap, scoop, splash, scoop, slap, scoop, splash.
Oh the oil gets all over it.
You baste it into the oven.
420 degrees.
It comes out.
You can smell the whole hell smells like it.
The whole house stinks like fish.
Like delicious salmon fish.
And it's wonderful you've never had anything more tasty in your whole life.
I sprinkle a little bit of rosemary just because I fucking can.
And then I do a little bit of a drizzle with EVOO.
Oh extra virgin olive oil.
And it's lemon infused.
Not your typical shit that you get on the grocery.
No they get a special order the lemon infused one.
Talk more about my cooking how it's not very good.
It sounds awful.
What?
I if you wanted me to I would do a cooking salmon infused lemon tang stream.
And I would show you all the whole house is gonna stink and it's gonna be great.
But anyways how do we get there?
Yeah I'm gonna play Resident Evil 2 probably on Monday.
Hey Mr Kool-Aid thanks for the one dollar since we're on the subject of Dreamcast.
I very much recommend Skies of Arcadia.
The world is vibrant.
The music is fantastic and it's genuinely fun RPG.
They did remaster it for Gamecube but back in the day it was the best reason for ever
owning a Dreamcast.
If you decide to play it it's quite the classic.
Another Dreamcast did have some of the best RPGs for its time.
Now long-winded 50 hour to 100 hour classic RPGs on the Dreamcast.
I'm not sure they'd be I don't think I'd want to stream them.
But I do appreciate that they exist.
What kind of pan do you use?
My hand.
I hold it in my hand.
I put my hand over the burner.
That's a pretty good job.
No you can do it in cast iron.
You can do it in a non-stick skillet.
You can do it in a pan in the oven.
Actually in the oven it's...
I actually prefer it in the oven because it can get it cooks all around.
And you take it out to get the medium rare texture inside.
Nice medium barely opaque flaking salmon buttery fish.
I would put my salmon up against any five-star restaurant salmon and win.
I don't care who it was.
Jerma is an insecure masochist who made up a salmon recipe to impress a bunch of...
What?
What are you talking about man?
Lifting shirt from neck grabbing and pulling.
I'm really good at doing that.
Hey thank you Barry for the one dollar.
Jerma it's okay we understand.
Also please have a meet up in Vegas.
I go to college there.
I'll casino meet up.
Will we all...
A casino meet up where everybody gives a dollar
and we put a dollar on every single symbol at the roulette table.
No we make it so everyone goes in and we have everybody gives a dollar
and we just put like a hundred bucks on every single number
from double zero all the way to 35.
And then whatever hits we just you know that's good something's gonna hit
but they don't you know it that's 3500 bucks goes to charity.
But that would mean that they would be have to be way more
it would be like we'd just be losing like three or four or five thousand dollars.
Why wouldn't we just give 10 grand to charity?
That doesn't make any sense.
But I don't know I don't I don't I don't know I don't really do meetups
unless they're at like a convention or a place where I know I want to be or
I'm fucking I'm a weirdo guys.
I'm I don't I don't know those of you that have met me in real life
you probably can attest to the fact that like he was a fucking strange person.
You know he went like this that this and I scanned every item individually
and that that really happened and it was embarrassing.
I bet there's at least a couple of casinos that would be happy to host a charity roulette
game just to have the exposure and more people in the establishment playing other games.
You'd be surprised though a lot of those places are very very heavily regulated
and have very very very strict rules on what is allowed and not allowed.
That would be a tough cookie to sell I think because then they're very very particular.
Buy your own casino.
You know I had this weird dream and for some stupid dumb reason I looked up like leasing
prices in Vegas.
I had this weird dream about this like video game restaurant and I was like oh
that's kind of cool like on the strip that'd be cut look on the strip of Vegas
like a video game with like arcades like in like a cool menu
and like it serves alcohol but it's not Dave and Buster's
but it's like way better it'll be like a better version of Dave and Buster's
and it was like for three or four I think it was like $300,000 a year to lease it
like a place on the strip it'd be like Dave and Buster's but there's no prize games
it's more of a bar restaurant that has like three or four pinball machines
so it's not like Dave and Buster's at all it would be a bar restaurant that has three
or four pinball machines and a video game themed menu this is a bad idea
and I hope they deny me the loan.
Hey Tingy thanks for the two bucks what's this about you being naked
did I miss something while I was at work you didn't know
you didn't miss anything and what you did miss potentially was I was done on purpose
because it was funny you know
hey thank you Kinky for the one dollar snap your discs for more
not snapping a disc thank you Senator Chu Chi for the one dollar clueless sniper for the one
dollar thank you to Jug for the three dollars I would be down for arms level two emote
god uh special thanks for the one dollar hey Jeremy have you seen the Garfield game for
ps2 and pc it looks awful it's not Garfield cart and they link a speedrun I don't want to
look at it because if it's something I want to try them then I want to go in blind
thanks for the laughs from Australia it is Australia day happy Australia day
also please do the cooking stream perhaps invite the egg everybody loves the egg
but thank you uh if it's on ps2 or pc maybe I'll
but that would just push more Garfield I'm not sure if I want to do that
hey dr stein one dollar do a choose your own adventure cooking stream where you have a
shitload of ingredients and if chat choose which ones to use and when using the click feature
you are asking for me to burn down my kitchen that idea though choose your own adventure
stream don't talk about that something that might happen soon and by soon I mean like
that's it's currently the cogs are turning with a few people
um it's gonna be it's not gonna be like a huge thing it's gonna be fairly simple
but it's gonna be fun we'll see there's all kinds of ideas flying around in my salmon brain
thank you tingy for the one dollar someone had a good idea since nova is streaming you
should rate him considering last time we tried he went offline yeah sure uh thank you
Barry for the one dollar have a meetup at the pinball hall of fame it's super cool if I
ever feel like doing a meetup yeah I'll pick somewhere cool and interesting well let's
get the credits on the screen that's all the bits thank you everybody for your
monetary bits support and also to everybody that's subbed and resub today and all the
gifted subs there are a lot of those too thank you guys so much I will see you all tomorrow
and let's raid nova that sounds like an interesting idea hopefully we don't click
over on his channel and see the offline image what emote do we use for germa raids
um let's that's on you guys whatever you feel like don't all right so how do I do this
forgot how to do it again oh here we go I could pick a channel to raid
okay I would hold on wait not yet not yet so uh so let me get this right so I gotta we do
this we say here we go and then I I hit raid we queue up for it then I turn off my stream
and then do send the raid right that's what we do right okay but we're raiding we're raiding
nova we're raiding nova clear at least I'll see you all tomorrow that was his stream
I'll see you all tomorrow probably on the same time around three o'clock pacific
Tony Hawk two we don't know well either do I see you very soon Power Stone Tony Hawk
it's monster give everybody a good night good night uh by the way Nova Nova's playing Resident
Evil 2 not sure how far into the game they are but that's what they're playing if you're
like oh shit I don't want to see like the second boss I have no idea go uh go give some
love go say hello I'm the game apparently is very good right from my understanding it is
very well made and very very fun pretty good well I will be the judge of that
thank you everybody for your subscriptions see you very soon tomorrow let's queue up the
rig ready to raid who's going have a great night guys see you tomorrow