Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho.
Welcome to the- I founded my book of spells, it seems.
What house do- what-
We're gonna go with Slytherin.
Cause I have my ceremonial wizard garvan.
Look at my hand.
I'm like glitching through this.
Care to take your wizard photo?
Okay, give me my wizard photo.
I'm- am I a wizard yet, mummy?
Defacing a library book.
wait it looks like it's a frog which
illustration from the page and let's see
where'd it go it seems our mischievous
vandal wanted to kill me a frog
sure to practice I got ya go on then
give it a go cast winged I love you sir
and then try levitating that's told he
got here oh he's gone see ya do I get
another frog good all right I gotta do
when guardian of yosa there's mr. frog
goes you need to be a bit more careful
I need another frog way to treat an innocent
toad I need another frogs please
respawn the frog please thank you very
much all right tonight where am I
supposed to put him he's going way too
far away come back of course this toad
was just conjured up oh there he goes
you need to be a bit more care watch
where you spray that thing where's the
book that looks bad oh look out look out
man I got you it's like a super so good
cover that's a super so good commercial
like oh got you look out to me what do
you want goodness keep your water under
cool let's let's go now right let's move
on and go back later if you like book
was upside down fascinating here's to be
a look look at you see in that hole there
look at it there I feel like I'm in a
universal studios right boss oh where's
your book gone there we go oh what the
shit I'm back I'm back huh it was a joke
you will need to go back and finish that
later that was a joke I was just fucking
around all right let's go the master of
the test I'm afraid you're not ready to
tackle the chapters final test yet there
we are
pull up the glowing text on the page to
begin oh this is stressful to cast
their try again I think water is the key
to solving this bit of the test not
quite sure which spell you were trying
to cast their try again the fuck is it
not quite sure which spell you were
trying to try again I can't I'm why am I
looking down at the book to see what it
is the book is not there's nothing here
it's that's not here why get some water
in there it's not full yet get some more
water into the fountain you need to keep
filling it with water use oh I spilled it
oh come on you tell me that's not gonna
spill out are you kidding me right now
this is just like jello in here
what the fuck is going on changing water
demon that's keep it up open your book
there's things left to do in this
chapter I'm stuck right now get up get
off of me fuck I'm stuck in my robes you
see these like birds these butterflies
and I just really can't have a kiss
it's back to patrol us I've had a kiss
what would have kept it difficult is I've
got a kiss I don't have us broke oh well
this clock is broken lock needs mending
I gotta oh it's all over me oh boy what
do I do riparrow oh come on now I get it
what the fuck is this nearly there
trial number three looks straightforward
my guess is you need to make things a
bit more balanced big big man making the
scorpion smaller won't help making him
larger might though that's make the
scorpion big I don't want a big big-ass
scorpion done it wait it's still
growing looks like this trial was a
trap hey hey hey I'm in a kiss ready for
your next spell turn the page jet okay
I'm turning the page I think I busted it
I'm pretty sure I broke the book I'm
pretty positive the book is all screwed
up right now if I hold it come on come
on what the fuck is going on the book
is messed up book of spells my ass it's
all glitched out it was like the
calibrate button make sure it's closed
with the front cover facing upwards if
you towards me right now and your
wonder book on screen try moving back a
little press the move button when you go
off your wonder book I don't even give a
shit