Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a gameplay commentary.
Tonight's episode of gameplay commentary is going to be what my favorite game to play in bed is.
Now you might be wondering, what do you mean your favorite game to play in bed? What are you talking about?
You have a PC, you've got like computers, you've got consoles. No, I'm talking about a game that you can pick up
and lie down on your bed and play for seemingly hours before you kind of drift off to sleep or to relax for a little bit.
I usually play this game to relax, although it doesn't have a whole lot of replayability.
And before anybody says anything, I need to say this very, very clearly, nobody paid me to make this video.
I didn't get paid money to make this. The guy that made this game, The Room, did not hand me a sack of hundreds
or like a sack of dirty sock full of fucking $20 bills. I like this game, so I'm making a video on it.
I did not get paid a single dollar. Please do not think that.
And if you say it, God help me, I'm going to be very mad at you and you're going to get in trouble with the Jerma police.
But anyways, now that that's out of my system, I play a lot of games in bed.
I play a lot of mobile games and I really should get myself something like a DS or a Vita,
because I spend so much time when I'm lying in my bed, just like sitting there chilling out and relaxing before I go to bed
or even when I'm in downtime during the day. I love just chilling out and playing the game.
And sometimes you just want something that'll do that.
You want a game where you want to program or something that you can just get in a different mindset,
take yourself away from the typical like shooters and like jumping.
Like sometimes you want to take yourself away from that.
And by far out of any game I've played on the App Store, at least, and this is Android, this is iTunes.
As long as it's iOS 5 and a recent device, you can't play this on like a 1997 iPod or something.
As long as you have a recent Apple product or a recent Android product, this will work on it.
It's called The Room. A lot of you guys have probably already heard of this game.
A lot of you guys probably saying, I played that game. It was pretty cool. It was pretty awesome.
I'm getting a frog in my throat. A lot of you guys probably played this game before.
I don't want to show a whole lot of the game.
I'm going to try to put some other stuff in the background probably because I don't want you guys to see all the puzzles
and all the boxes and all the openings and all the cool things that kind of happen during the time you play.
I don't want to give away any of the puzzle answers.
You can figure that out on your own or you can go find the answers if you really want to.
So I'm not sure what I'm going to be doing for the background of this video.
There might be like some random footage of me lifting weights.
I don't know. Something will be there during the course of this because I don't obviously want to give everything away.
But what this game is, it's a 3D adventure kind of point and click exploration game
where your whole goal is to open up this box that's just sitting on a table.
And it's not as easy as you think. It's not just like opening up, taking the crate and like prying it open with a crowbar
or just taking a key and opening and open up the box.
No, it's a series of crazy contraptions that you have to figure out.
And, oh, let me take a look at that. Let me put this device here.
And like it changes the box and it's one of the most satisfying gaming experiences for this type of genre that I've had in a while.
And there's a sequel to that recently came out last year.
This is not a new game.
And it saddens me that a couple of years ago I didn't find this when I was looking for cool games to play on the iPad or on my iPhone
just when I was in the doctor's office or something.
Now, the one problem with this game that you might have is, well, Jerma, you made a video pretty recently
about how shitty some of these companies are with their freemium, free to play, paywall type experiences.
That's not here. This game is one dollar and that's it.
There is no in-app purchases. There's no like super clues to buy.
Oh, I need to buy like a super clue to find out this, but no, it's all there.
Everything is there for you for one dollar.
As long as you are OK with having the experience be done and not really being able to go back and play it again.
That's the one thing of this game that you can't really do because you know all the puzzles.
And although it could be interesting to see how fast you can go through maybe like a speed run or something, but you can't really speed run it.
It's one of those games that you have to take your time and see all the animations and all the cool 3D models and stuff.
That's part of the game. And it is pretty short for the entire experience for both the room and the room 2.
You can probably do them both in less than 10 hours, but it's only going to cost you four bucks for everything anyways.
And it's one dollar for the original game and three dollars, two ninety nine for the room 2 as it stands right now.
These prices could change. They could drop. They could go up. I don't know.
That's what it is right now and recording of this video. So I'm just recommending it.
Just saying you guys, if you want to try it, go check it out. It's a really fun experience and go lie down in bed.
Go get yourself like a chocolate milk and go start the room and open up the boxes and see what's in there.
I think it could be a hat. No, it's not. It's not a hat inside the box.
All right. Well, that's going to wrap it up here, guys. Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. And of course, take care, everybody.