Why did that just change back to Saw?
Oh, it's cause my streamlabs thing, it just took the stream from yesterday and said,
this is the stream that's today!
No, I got it, I got it, I updated it, I got it.
Alright, I'm not supposed to be here, I- hold on, beer B.
Okay, cool.
Does Saw again? It really shouldn't say Saw.
It should say... City.
Does it really matter?
Does it actually- I- okay, when you- think about a title.
Who am I trying to grab right now?
Am I trying to grab you?
Am I trying to have a cool title for you to come to the stream and be like,
whoa, that's a crazy title, I gotta cl- no, it's just a city, we're in a city.
You know what you're gonna get here.
I'm gonna crash the car five times in the first ten minutes.
I'm gonna run somebody over, I'm gonna punch somebody in the face and get out of the car.
And then the car's gonna explode.
And then I'm gonna have to restart the game four times.
Like, do I really need a title for that?
I mean, if I could do that for the title, I would do that.
No, you know what? No.
Fuck that. I ain't gonna do that today.
I'm gonna- in the first ten minutes, we're gonna do the first mission.
I'm not gonna do anything weird.
I'm sorry. All right, let's go.
I don't know why I did that. I'm sorry. I don't know why I did that.
That was so awful. That was evil.
Hey, is this a controller game, by the way?
He's amped up.
Evil Cloud.
I am actually a little amped up.
I'm looking forward to this.
Guys, we get excited on this channel for third-person punching driving games.
This is like my favorite thing in the world.
But I'd like to answer my question if I could get an answer to that question.
Is this a controller game?
Or keyboard and mouse?
I'm assuming it's probably controller, right?
Third-person?
Yeah, it's definitely a third-person game.
So I'm gonna use the controller.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, definitely controller.
Great. Are you guys ready for Mafia?
How's that sound? Does that sound too low?
Nice and rainy out today.
You know, actually, I kind of missed this.
It hasn't rained in Vegas in probably, I don't know, wait.
Can my computer not run this game?
I think I just got a warning.
I think OBS just gave me a warning saying that the encoding was too high.
Can I not run this?
Uh-oh. Find out.
How much CPU is too much CPU to use for a game?
I gotta turn something down here.
All right, options.
All right, yeah, we gotta turn this down.
Stream is experiencing issues.
Fuck. Okay, hold on.
Hold on, I think I can fix this.
How bad does it look right now?
Is it all right now?
All right, display.
Yep, the field is off.
Which one of these is taking up a ton of CPU power?
It's a budget PC.
Yeah, guys, I have a 1080 in here.
I haven't upgraded my computer in six years.
Is that bad?
That 1080 is still fine.
Shadow quality low.
Yeah, that's probably that's what was hogging all the CPU.
It's not a pre-built, please.
At least give me a little bit of credit.
Somebody else built it for me.
What else should I turn off?
Everything else should be fine.
What about volumetric effects?
I think it should be fine.
All right, let's go.
Back it up.
Carcyclopedia.
Motion blur?
I turned it off, didn't I?
Yeah, motion blur is off.
Who the hell wants motion blur in their game?
All right, you ready?
I'm not going to go back and do Ratatouille again.
I ate the disk.
I ground it up and do a fucking spaghetti grinder,
and I put it into pasta.
Put vegetation on high.
Let's just see if this Walmart PC can handle it.
Story mode, here we go.
Medium, classic, hard mode.
No.
Players who want a fair fight.
There is low aim assistance.
Police respond to fewer crimes.
Enemies are more dangerous.
Police will respond to more crimes.
Fewer UI indicators.
Classic.
Enemies are lethal.
Police respond to more crimes.
Fewer UI.
And ammunition left in the clip is lost when reloading.
No thanks.
Play classic.
No, I'm not doing classic.
I'm terrible.
I'm not going to get past the first boss.
Can I change it in the game?
Can I change it mid-game?
Enemies are lethal.
This is...
Am I playing stalker?
Why is this even in here?
No manual transmission.
Tutorials, that's fine.
You can show them.
Here we go.
No, no, don't, no.
Game is piss easy on anything below classic.
Yeah, but I don't want to...
I don't care about how hard the game is.
I just want to drive around.
Hey, this is not a...
Look, maybe five, 10 years ago I would have cared about that.
Now I just want to hear the rain hit the side of my window
and the thunder.
Guys, I want to be able to just...
You know what?
I'm just going to turn this on at night later tonight
and just sleep to this.
This shit, I don't have to pay any more extra money.
I already paid $40 for that.
Here comes 2K presents.
Fucking 2K.
WWE Battlegrounds.
Get the fuck out of here.
The game's stupid.
I'm already angry.
All right, I'm going to be quiet.
I'm just waiting for one of these birds
to just crash into the camera that is our view
and it's Borderlands 4.
And then no rest for the wicked starts playing again.
This looks pretty good.
This looks good.
This looks really good.
Come on, my computer sucks.
I can't handle it.
But it's still like it's a little choppy for me.
But it should be all right.
Pre-rendered.
Oh, now you got my hopes up.
I'm just an annoying fucking drone.
That's the neighborhood kid with his fucking drone.
Watch out.
It goes by somebody's head.
Turns around.
The guy's got a huge bald spot on the top of his head.
You little bastard.
This is really fucking loud.
It's a cut scene loud.
Don't worry.
It'll be all right in a minute.
Oh, shit.
Lost another drone.
Lost another one.
You know what's the saddest part about this video
that we're watching right now
that was filmed on one of those drones?
It's unbelievable.
Wow.
What cinematography?
How beautiful.
You're gonna scroll down.
840 views.
Somebody said, you are so funny.
Ban that person.
I don't want to see them again.
Or at least a minute.
You think I was gonna catch you say that?
Hey, I only pick up the negative comments.
I'm a streamer.
I don't see any positive comments.
I see four messages an hour.
All right.
I can't talk.
No more talking.
I had something to say there, but be quiet.
I'm not looking for any associates.
It's a fucking huge hands.
Because I'm on the net.
Can't even pay for the coffee.
But I got plenty to trade.
Well, that's yours.
How long you've been in town?
Three years.
Caught my teeth in Empire Bay.
Well, they handed you the Morello case.
Right out of the gate.
Just want him to keep lighting cigarettes.
Just have like 12 cigarettes lit on the table.
They just keep picking up different ones
and smoking them.
Case must be getting pretty cold by now.
Or you got something might warm it up.
Yeah, I might have some.
I don't know what's my end of the deal.
Uh, you want money?
Some sort of immunity.
They didn't even care whose was whose.
I got people I need to protect.
Please.
Always the Achilles heel.
All right.
I'm gonna write a sick mom or a wife and a better kid.
Wife and daughter.
No one else to watch your back.
I'm guessing you wouldn't be here otherwise.
Pity that.
I always said a man needs friends if he's going to survive in this world.
Yeah.
Well, in my world, it's the other way around.
I have no idea what's happening.
All I know is cigarettes in town for a few days.
Cigarettes.
Not until I hear what you're trading.
So are you talking or are you just killing time before they come for you?
You think I'm on the run?
Oh, I know it, Tommy.
Jesus, look at you.
Surely gassed.
You haven't slept for days.
Your neck's gotta be aching from all that looking over your shoulder you're doing.
No, the way I figure it is you got someone powerful mean on your tail and they ain't
The annoying friend at the movie theater.
You walk out that door without maybe both.
No, you're not making it five steps.
Boss, yeah, you stick around.
You tell me your story and maybe you got a shot at living long enough to walk that
girl yours down the aisle.
Either way, it looks like I'm buying you a cup of coffee.
Chris, I don't know how everything got so balled up.
I know exactly what you're talking about, too.
No one ever sees the hairpin until it's too late.
Your friend is talking during the previews and you're like,
I hope he shuts the fuck up when the movie starts.
And the movie starts, the first one minute goes by, he's still talking to you.
It's like, god damn it, man.
We're both here for the same reason.
Please don't.
That's me right now.
What a hypocrite.
This isn't even a fucking movie.
All right.
I got a rebuttal to that.
I'm the 12th streamer you've seen play this game.
I'm like five days late.
It was at the end of one of those shifts when I first met Polly and Sam.
I was loud.
I don't watch anyone else.
Oh shit.
Well, I'll be quiet.
We've waited for you.
Oh, it's too loud.
Imagine being in a movie theater.
It's too loud.
It's supposed to be loud.
You fucking asshole.
Shut up.
It's THX.
Oh, okay.
Let me break your immersion for a second.
Sorry.
This doesn't happen in movies, but it's happening here.
Is that what infinity war starts?
I know it's like the loop.
Who's so desperately the all right.
How do I how do I drive?
All right.
Where are we going?
Find ways to lose your tail.
I don't have any tutorials.
Oh, there we go.
I feel like I'm driving a toy car.
Is that us?
Hold LT to slow down.
Yeah, break.
Root to destination is shown.
Wait, we have GPS in like the 1930s.
That's kind of all right.
I'm glad that that would remake like hell.
We're back.
I'll wake up the doc.
I don't know.
It might be okay.
He's getting the call anyways.
The graphics are too good.
You don't get to listen either.
It's hard to drive.
The graphics are too good.
So do that.
I'm turning the graphics on low.
I actually it's hard to do this.
Where am I taking you once we're over the bridge?
I'm getting tired out of questions.
Drive to central island.
Can I change the camera angle?
Turn limiter off.
What?
How do I change the camera angle?
I don't like this view.
I want to be a little closer.
What?
I know some shortcuts that'll slow them down.
I don't care how you do it.
What happened?
Shake them off.
Lose your tail.
Is encoding lag?
No, it's my computer.
Actually, we're going to have to turn the graphics down.
1080T omega lol.
8 omega lol.
These guys really don't like it, do they?
No, I said I wasn't going to hit anybody.
Good.
Master Shake?
All right.
Find ways to lose your tail.
Hold on.
It's still wait.
We're going to figure this out right now.
Hold on.
It's still fucking too loud.
And we got to put it on a little bit lower than this.
Geometry detail can put it on medium.
Decal is low.
Medium.
Look, you don't order a rare steak.
You don't order a well-done steak.
You order a fucking medium steak.
That's my reasoning for this.
Better?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't order a medium steak?
That's what everybody does.
Okay, that was pretty funny.
I have to do that again?
What happens if I back through it?
It is Master Shake.
It's the same actor?
It is.
What's his name?
Dana Carvey?
No, not Dana Carvey.
What's his name?
All right, hold on.
I have to try something.
Come on, do it.
Yes.
Video games.
Aren't they great?
Oh shit.
Didn't kill anybody.
Don't shoot that lady.
What are you doing?
Custom character creator, is there?
All right, I don't want to do it yet
because we're right at the end of the mission.
But if I hit triangle, or why?
Will I just fall out of the car?
That's Carl.
That was Carl from Aqua Teen.
It's Aqua Teen Mafia Force.
Did it.
Now your night's not over.
I hope somebody just chimes in and just say,
yeah, let's get over there, man.
You think he squealed?
It's me, me.
Wrong.
I think you zip it tight.
We'll talk it through back at the bar.
That'd be so awesome if there's a guy that talks like that
that's in my friend group.
Hold on.
I don't like this.
Did I change this?
Hold on a second.
There we are.
Okay, vehicle camera pitch.
Does that make it better?
I didn't think that didn't do anything.
I made it worse.
1080 Ti.
Should I put this at 720p?
Shit, my light.
Wait.
I don't have a graphics card update.
I haven't updated my drivers in probably three years.
Should I do that?
Clock the frame rate to 30.
We'll see.
Is it CPU or GPU?
It seems, during cut scenes it's fine.
But just driving really fast is when my computer starts to hang a little.
Do a driver update.
But if I do a driver update, the screen turns off.
CPU is the problem.
Yeah, probably.
Don't do a Smash Brothers thing.
I did already.
I've refreshed the page and I got a Travis Scott burger advertisement.
Yes.
That's one of four ads on Twitch right now.
Hey, you want to go to McDonald's and get a hamburger with bacon on it?
We'll get it.
Anyone ask where you got that money?
You wanted a poker.
Scratches on your car?
You swerved.
To keep from hitting a little old lady.
You got it?
That actually did happen.
I just barely missed her.
Somebody bullet holes.
Wait, that's a different franchise.
When I opened the envelope...
That was pretty good.
...I had a heart attack.
Fixed the cap.
Nearly enough to buy a new one.
Thought about what Sam said about work.
I wasn't interested.
The money was good, sure.
I didn't want to get in with criminals.
I just wanted to open the fridge and there's like a hundred packs of cigarettes in the fridge.
And the freezer.
So, right there.
Back then, I was out.
Hey, Chris Weed Piano, thanks for $50.
5,000 bits from Chris Weed Piano.
Jerma, could you tell me now when you're doing Weed Week?
There's no such thing.
That's a lot of money.
Thanks for the 50 bucks, dude.
That's a fucking extreme amount of money.
All right, 1930.
After that night with Salieri's guys,
I was back working as soon as I could.
But it felt different.
I think it's the lighting.
I gotta turn the lights down.
I need to get a fucking 3080.
All right, here we go.
First time on foot.
What's the punch button?
All right, wait a minute, wait.
Hold on, lady.
I'm currently trying to get my graphics to look okay.
I'm gonna turn on V-sync.
I'm gonna drop the FOV to like 85.
I'm gonna put the vegetation,
direct lighting below.
All right, there we go.
There we go.
That's pretty smooth.
I'm ready.
So where to?
St. Michael's Church.
All right, St. Michael's Church.
Careful, please.
I always drive careful.
Then you'd be the first.
Turn the speed limiter on.
Why would I want to put the speed limiter?
Motorcycle, motorcycle, motorcycle, motorcycle.
Oh, wait, I was doing a mission, right?
I can't do that with a lady in the car.
A cab driver is like,
oh, yeah, take me to 42nd Street, please.
Sure thing.
Motorcycle, motorcycle, motorcycle.
And they run the guy over.
What a fucking psycho.
So where to?
St. Michael's Church.
Directly.
Careful, please.
I always drive careful.
You have to obey the rules.
You'll be the first.
Turn on the speed limiter.
Oh, I see.
I don't want that on.
Get.
I don't honk the horn.
Church, it's Sunday already.
Eyes on the road, please.
No.
My milkshake brings all the...
It's in every fucking game, I think.
I can't get away from it.
What do you want me to say?
A goose laugh?
Oh, drive carefully, respect the law.
I am.
I'm doing a good job.
Game's too good looking.
I like games that have like 2008 graphics,
not like 2020.
I should just play the original one.
I'm complaining about how it's good it looks
and how much it's bad it runs on my computer.
I could just play the original Mafia.
I ain't gonna do that, though.
Here you go.
St. Michael's.
That'll be 30 cents.
The only tip I'll give you is to stop smoking
in your vehicle.
I felt like I was sitting in an ashtray.
Sure.
Whatever you say.
I thought everybody smoked in like 1930.
All right.
There is no punch person button.
Fair.
Run her over.
I can't.
I'm not just gonna run her over.
All right.
Search the streets for fares.
Okay.
This is just crazy taxi.
Is there a person here?
You need a fare?
You?
Anybody need a ride?
I'm looking for Dave.
Lift for Dave.
Fucking God damn.
Hey.
Looking for Dave.
Your ride has canceled.
Oh, wait.
They can't...
I guess I did that on purpose.
Oh, here you are.
Come on in.
Where are you going, sir?
Where can I take you?
Art gallery.
Get me there quick.
Get there quick.
Quick, I can do.
Is there...
Do they have handbrakes back in the 30s?
Didn't turn off the graphics.
Oh, right.
Hold on.
Let me try that.
It didn't change anything.
I think it's just a game.
Yeah, that didn't change anything.
Turn off the visuals.
I get to be busy.
Your busy day is going to be looking at old paintings.
I have a business meeting there with a copy.
It's the driver.
Actually, to be honest, it looks fine.
Yeah, it does.
Maybe you'll understand.
CPU can't handle the game and stream.
Yeah, yeah.
That can get you.
What the hell?
Let's see.
I got a six-core CPU.
The thing was expensive back in like 2014.
I got to hurry up.
I'm getting...
I'm just up...
I'm upgrading my CPU and GPU and motherboard.
I'm just going to get a new computer or whatever.
I'm going to get like a...
I'm going to get a 64-core computer.
That just spawned.
That taxi just spawned.
All right, get out.
Get the fuck out.
I'm going to do 1080p streams.
I don't know.
That's a good question.
GTA V runs good on this computer and this looks the same.
This is running fine, but you know, you get the idea.
I'm not going to do 1080p.
No, there's no reason to.
GTA V was in 2012.
Yeah, but...
Fuck.
That's right.
All right.
I'm getting a new computer tomorrow.
That's impossible.
Great deal.
Okay.
You can...
You can do that.
Wait.
Wait, run, run, run, run.
How do you run?
How do you sprint?
Shit.
I'm back.
So where were we?
Holy shit, dude.
He actually waited.
Yeah.
It's a handbrake button.
Stop and pay the fine?
What fine?
All right.
I'll pay the fine.
How much...
Wait.
Under arrest?
How much is fine?
It's like...
How much is it?
Ten cents?
How much is a fine?
That's a whole dollar.
Wait.
How much money do I have?
How do I get in the car?
Wait.
Oh.
All right.
You go first.
I don't want you to see me do anything illegal.
What's the speed limit?
30?
Oh, shit.
You have to do the speed limit.
That's kind of funny that you can do that.
You can put a speed limiter on your car.
You know what?
It's rendering the buildings.
You don't even render these buildings.
Just make them like bitmap cardboard cutouts
and the game will be fine.
I don't give a shit about the fire exits over there.
You can just remove them.
It's just unnecessary...
Oh.
I beeped at somebody.
What?
Beeping is illegal?
No.
Fuck that.
I'm out of here.
Oh, shit.
Boiled again.
I beeped at a pedestrian.
All right.
Hold on.
I got to...
Are you kidding me?
Right at the fucking end.
That's disturbing the peace.
So don't ever use your horn.
I've been working since 5.
So you're telling me...
It's your excuse.
Doing this...
Where are we going?
Is it going to get me arrested?
Okay.
If I don't tell the cops about the liquor on your breath,
you don't tell them when I break them.
I hear a siren already.
Don't loud noises in 1930.
Got any earth today?
Never enough of them.
Who's got the money for...
This isn't GTA.
That's true.
Yeah.
I'm going to stream at 900p.
It's going to look crystal clear at 60fps.
I'm going to get a 3090.
I'm going to be a psycho and get a 3090.
And the 64 fucking core like 8 gigahertz processor.
I'm going to be able to...
NASA is going to be calling me to fucking CPU usage.
I'm going to be routing like air traffic control to this computer.
It's going to be so powerful.
Put the limiter on.
I don't want to get arrested.
It's illegal to drive in this lane, right?
Or is it?
Yeah.
Unkeyball in 4K.
All right.
We're almost there.
Let's get a sponsor so you get a free PC.
All right.
Excuse me.
Uh, can I have a free computer?
I have a streamer.
That means I got a free computer, right?
That's the email I sent.
Hey, uh, I just was hitting you up
because I'm a streamer and deserve a $5,000 PC for free.
Thank you for your time.
I, uh, respectfully yours, Jeremy Albertson.
I don't remember this person.
Do I get a bat though?
I'm so excited for the bat.
Let's get him.
Oh, why to vault?
Nice.
Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm on classic mode.
This is not a joke.
We've got YouTube tutorial music in the background.
Run.
By the way, all videos with this song behind it
are less than three minutes long.
They're like two and a half, one and a half minutes long.
It's a quick DIY scripted.
You were supposed to do that.
That tripled Joe.
Trying to talk to that cabbie over there.
That's all.
That right.
Yeah.
What is he?
It's a Don's favorite driver.
So anything you got to say to him, you can say to me.
Is that right?
Well, I'll tell you something, pal.
We ain't leaving empty handed.
That's for sure.
Well, then maybe you ain't leaving at all.
Bad graphics.
Leave me alone.
The lighting is way too hard.
The face animations are bad.
Stop laughing at me.
At least we could do.
I'm going to update my graphics card.
I'll be back in like 10 minutes.
Yeah.
He's going to want to hear about this.
Why does it look like Toy Story 1?
Oh, it doesn't.
It looks like Toy Story 2.
Fucking God damn it.
Okay.
You buy my computer.
It's going to be a monster.
It's going to be insane.
I've waited long enough.
It's been six years.
It's been five years and five and a half years.
I've got to get a new computer or something.
I have to get like a new graphics card.
I can't just have it.
1080 is not going to take me forever.
As much as I wanted to.
I can't believe that a 1080 is worthy of Toy Story 1 graphics.
That's fucking crazy.
No, no, no.
Thanks.
No, thanks.
I don't want to learn from a mafia guy.
No, thank you.
I'm not looking for a handout.
This is when you just rip the fuck out of the seat
and run out as fast as you can and run.
I didn't want a shot at the bastards who wrecked my cabin.
You hear that, Frank?
The kid wants my permission.
Yes.
Okay, Tommy Angelo.
All the Morello's girls hang out at a bar he owns.
Paul, you know the place.
Boss?
It's not just you.
You're good.
You can ride along with Tommy.
This game is really stressful.
There's a lot right next to the bar where they park their cars.
Damn.
They'll smash up a few tin cans, send Morello a message.
He can't rough up hardworking joes in my neighborhood
without getting a black eye.
Thank you, Mr. Salieri.
I won't let you down.
People with better computers than you have frame rate problems.
Oh.
Oh, so the game sucks.
Okay, let's just check it.
I should turn the graphics back up.
It's not just a meat problem.
Okay, so there is just frame rate problems in the game.
Okay, I got you.
Well, let's go to at least Toy Story 2.
Okay, let's do medium.
I'll do medium.
But keep lighting.
Fuck lighting.
We're on max?
What are you trying to do to me?
Optimal?
Oh, that looks kind of good.
Look around the bar.
Can I talk to people?
Oh, what's this?
Prohibition here to stay.
I pay left.
Update your drivers.
But then I have to turn the stream off.
And I don't...
That's going to be a pain in the ass.
Oh, what's this?
We can wait.
Let me just check and see if I have...
Hold on.
Just do it when you have to pee.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I'll do.
When I have to pee, I'm going to update my drivers.
I wonder if it'll turn the stream off.
It might not.
It takes like 10 minutes.
Yeah, well, on a break, I'll do it.
Not right now.
That's pretty cool, though.
What am I doing?
It said I was looking around the bar.
Going to be a restart anyways.
Shit.
All right.
How does the frame rate get better when I put the graphics on as high as they can go?
Does that make any sense?
Optimal.
Turn up the game audio?
I will.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Yes.
Finally.
Cocktails here.
No, thanks.
I don't drink.
Can you look back and forth?
And everybody does that exact same fake weird laugh.
All right.
I got molotovs.
Wait, there's a thing on the table.
Can I have your card?
This is pornography.
Was it?
I don't know.
I couldn't tell.
Guys.
Did I ever play the original Mafia?
Like a long time ago.
Yeah.
Not really, though.
I feel like I played it on this stream.
I played one of them on this stream, didn't I?
Mafia 2?
Mafia 3?
Oh, Mafia 3, yeah.
Hey, Gene.
Get your head out of here.
Fuck you, Papa Polly.
You can't just sneak up on a guy like that.
I'm sorry, Ralphie.
I'm just busting your balls.
See, you're still a limping.
Guess we got two cripples working here.
That kind of looks like me.
We ain't nothing alike.
You got that, Ralph?
Sure, Papa Polly.
Yeah.
Tommy.
Tommy Angelo.
Good to meet you.
Like I said, Ralphie here's a crack deck.
Well, you bring him a stolen car.
I'll make it yours.
It's only one voice actor?
Tell him to meet.
We got a job to do.
We need some wheels.
How about this one, Papa Polly?
That would be pretty funny, actually, if it was one person.
It'll get you across to the town.
All right.
Let's go.
You're driving.
And don't let me catch you loafing off again.
You caught that with one hand.
You do a two-handed clap catch.
That's not cool looking.
You don't look cool doing that.
One day I'm going to cut a line, asshole.
Holy shit.
I don't know what Ralph's trying to pull giving us this motor.
I want to show you something about the good life
and you're driving something my mom could have bought 20 years ago.
If I know Ralph, he probably got it taken out of our yard.
Hey, the car's fine.
It's good to get a change from the cab.
Oh, drive fast.
Don't be nice about it.
This thing's a tin can.
Megalol Disney game.
Is that whiskey back there in the truck?
We're on the frame limiter.
Yep.
New supplier.
You guys deal in broad daylight.
Normally not.
Is this...
There's no such thing as traffic lights.
Cops know better than to come sniffing around our turf.
How the fuck do people drive?
We're out.
The guy who's argy got it.
Oh shit.
I'm in the wrong lane.
We have more friends in the forest than us.
Arrest this guy.
He's beeping at me.
We're okay.
Be careful.
For our shoulder.
Is that the Canadian whiskey that comes through?
Guys, that's...
Dude, the game actually, like, improved.
I turned on the graphics.
I'm no big drinker.
I used a tip-back bathtub.
I didn't just stuffed up a bunch of crumpled pieces of paper
into my CPU bottleneck.
That stuff's no good for you.
You don't have to go boss.
You got a line in the good stuff.
That's good of you.
Thanks.
Not just the booze is fine.
Oh, the 1080's fine.
We're good.
It's the places we deliver to.
The deems they got in these places.
That's tables.
That's food.
That's a skirt.
Some way to live.
Right now, all I wanna do is wreck the day of the bastards who wrecked mine.
Sure.
All right, take the limiter off.
No cops.
Let's go.
This could get a guy in trouble.
Trouble says the guy is about to set fire to Morello's parking lot.
What?
It'll go fine.
But you don't understand.
Well, if it don't go fine.
He's gonna do that at some point.
He's gonna do the hi, Master Shag voice.
And we're gonna all laugh.
You hit him so hard, they don't remember it.
I laughed.
Yeah, I did too.
We all did.
If you didn't, you must be immune to fun.
I'm gonna just lean back in the chair and went, ugh.
And they tried to click the X,
but they misclicked twice and opened up a new tab
and that pissed them off even more.
And they're not coming back to the screen.
They clicked wrong.
They like minimize the window or something in a fit of rage
and they're just like, fuck, I'm not coming back.
Hey, they'll be back.
Don't worry.
Oh, that was illegal.
No, no, no, right on red.
That's okay.
There was a guy there.
There's a crime.
In general, we look after little Italy
and his guys work North Park and more besides.
You're walking on the wrong sidewalk.
You can't turn right on red in New York City.
You can't?
Oh, well, all right.
They start appearing on street corners to stare you down.
This is not New York City.
Oh, okay.
This is Chicago.
Right.
Okay, not New York City.
Every game where a guy is in the mafia
does not take place in New York City.
As much as I apparently, I think that it is.
It's not Chicago either.
What is it then?
Where the hell are we?
This is not Boston.
I know what Boston looks like, guys.
It doesn't look like this.
And you might say, what do you do?
No, no, Boston's looked the same since 1930.
Nothing has changed.
It's a fictional city.
All right, follow up.
Okay, there was like a gravity hole over here.
That I just got pulled into.
All right, press right stick to sneak.
When do I get to use the bat?
Boston's a fake city.
Okay.
Open the gate, onto the roof.
You got it.
Holy shit, Polly.
That was fucking crazy.
Wish we got to get you in the Olympics.
Oh, I'm Tommy.
Right.
Okay, whatever.
All right, I'm up here.
Sneak up up.
How do I jump down?
Keep distracting him.
What does that matter?
Why does that even matter?
What do you mean?
Who cares?
Oh no, Polly.
I cut his legs off.
Take it back and start swinging.
Oh shit, there's a weapon wheel.
Oh my god, there's a hitman feature.
This game is cool.
Hold on.
What do I do with them?
Okay, use the bat.
It's a weapon wheel?
Oh shit.
It just got fucking real.
Oh my god, the game just got real.
This became, might be one of my favorite games of the year.
Just because I just watched.
That animation's all I care about.
This is a crow hop swing.
Oh, this is going to be great.
Okay, let's go.
No, no, no, no, no.
Is there a Batman in the head?
In the head?
Molotov?
Oh shit.
It's right bumper and then you...
Oh man, this game's fun.
This game's fun.
Holy shit.
Okay, you cannot do that to a friend of yours
and have your friend trust you ever again.
Oh man, I was just messing around.
No, you weren't.
Man, I don't think we can hang out anymore.
It was intent behind that swing.
Go.
Watch out, lady.
He is in the ignition here.
Oh wow, this game's really cool.
Oh, sick jump.
Yeah.
Are they going to do it?
No.
What's a bicycle for?
Oh no, no, no, no.
That's handcuffs on the right.
Stay out of sight till they lose interest.
What's the handbrake, dude?
I don't know what the handbrake is.
Fuck, what's the handbrake?
Does anybody know?
Is it B?
It's B, okay.
Didn't expect me to hit the brakes.
It's not Y.
Y falls out of car.
They're right behind us, dude.
Hey!
What are you...
I feel like I'm playing Mario Kart
and someone's trying to make me stay in second place.
Get away from me.
Bingo.
It's pretty clean.
Did he do it clean?
Nope.
Press X real quick.
No, I know what that does.
Clear.
Okay, stay out of sight till they lose interest.
All right, are we good?
There's a car behind us.
What a joke of a streamer.
Hey, is that a cop right there?
What's the blue thing right there?
Is that a cop?
Blip on the minimap.
Blue blip.
What is that?
Yes, yeah, okay, okay, okay.
We lost them.
Stay out of sight till they lose interest.
All right, we're almost out.
I want to run this guy over so bad.
Okay, I'm good.
Blue blip is a Dunkin' Donuts location.
You know what's funny?
I know for a fact that what you're saying is a joke,
but there definitely is a Find the Dunkin' Nearest You app.
Why would you ever want that app?
What's it for?
Why would you even need to know that?
Drive one mile in any direction in New England.
Why do you need an app to tell you where to go?
That's like being like,
can I find a McDonald's anywhere at some point in the next 20 minutes?
Yes, you can.
Just drive straight on any road in the world.
You will find one.
If you ever feel like going to McDonald's,
don't even put in your GPS.
There's no reason to.
Take a road.
You'll find it.
Is he brainless?
Brain limiter.
And he's an old bastard.
I care, but we don't need the attention.
And one day I found myself in the yard behind a bar drawing with Vincenzo.
10 years go by and I'm still there.
That says a lot about society.
I got a suit now and Vinny's an old bastard.
I always thought that to be in a family you had to have more
connections.
Fuckin' society.
Or your uncle.
Oh, some guys.
Sure.
Your cousin got made or you like Carlos.
Pop went way back with the Don.
That means you get trusted more when you're starting out.
There's plenty of us who keep me in on the street.
I'm thinking we get here in front of the boss.
Then we tip a few.
Well, I don't got plans.
So what's the green eye?
There's a green eye right here.
Vinny so much booze that Luigi.
What's that for?
Green eye.
I'm good with whatever.
Sure you are.
Can you do like peel outs in 1930?
No, the engine ran on like fucking humidity.
You can't.
We get it.
What happened to the Christ sent you out with?
Why?
Yes.
Ray never killed nobody.
Why is the tire fire?
Wait, one of the tires is on fire?
Baseball bat him.
You can't.
You can't baseball bat your friends.
That's not going to work in this game.
Hey, fellas.
You get to play pool?
Because I'll never play it because I hate pool.
I think it sucks.
It's a dumb sport.
I was really vicious for no reason.
I'm just kidding.
I like pool.
I play it.
I play it like I played it like two weeks ago.
Come on, guys.
He's not going to be able to think straight for weeks.
See, that's the difference between me and Meroa.
I'm a businessman.
I do everything with this.
I just want to start eating cigarette.
I make?
It's what's good for the business.
Boys, a Merela is a hothead.
And all that anger burns out the brain.
And when he gets mad, he gets stupid.
You got nothing like that to worry about with Tommy here.
He was aces the whole way, boss.
I'm glad to hear it.
I got a growing business here.
We could use a guy like you to help out around the bar.
I'm scared of you.
Maybe run some errands.
Make sure the bills get paid on time.
You up for that?
It'd be an honor, sir.
What do you think the room would do?
But you need to understand we have a few rules around here,
so you listen and listen good.
First, no cursing on the premises.
There's a million words out there.
The man who needs to resort to fuck this and fuck that
is just ignorant or lazy.
Second, we don't deal in the hard stuff.
I don't want any dolphins in this neighborhood.
We'll let Merela poison his own people.
What would happen if I said, yeah, that's great.
Can you lean forward a little bit and say that into my chest?
A little bit clearer and loud this time.
You cross the line.
The rest will come after you.
You understand?
Yes, Mr. Celieri.
Then I'm going to only ask you for one more thing, Tommy.
I didn't even have a wire on.
It's a bad prank to pull on the Don.
A lot of guys out there are bigger and tougher than these two.
And I don't keep Frank on a payroll because he's smart.
Though he is an artist with the numbers.
All these guys in this room, they're here because they have
the only thing that matters to me.
The only thing that should matter to any of us.
Your dog.
You know what that is, Tommy?
My dog.
Your dog.
His dog.
Somebody's dog in this room.
Money.
That's right.
Now, you stay straight with me.
You're going to be living the high life, Tom.
You abuse my trust.
Don Celieri, you won't ever need to worry about me.
Until halfway through the game.
When you double cross me and then I get angry and we fight
and I end up shooting you third person mode.
Or a grenade.
Eating one of those is going to work probably in the next two or three hours.
Now I'm starving.
Luigi, let's eat.
Is that guy going to ask me for the Everlasting Gobstopper recipe?
Not much for Cook, but his daughter, Sarah.
What was that guy's name in Willy Wonka?
Squidward or something?
It was something like that.
Oh, that's my associate.
Squidward.
What is it?
What was his name?
It's something like Slugworth.
Yeah, that's Slugworth.
The guy eats and delivers messages.
The guy's busted balls and told stories from the old country.
Mostly we just waited.
I got to thinking.
Maybe life in Celieri's crew wasn't going to get me clipped.
What did I know?
Fight practice?
Ooh, that was a good move.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Wait, is it the...
Can I play too?
All right, guys, that's enough.
Settle down.
Wow, they actually listened.
Holy shit, the whole place cleared out.
I have power here.
Holy shit.
All right.
Anybody in here?
All right, I gotta go back into the room.
There he is.
Sorry I'm late.
Take a seat.
It's a fun game.
I like that game.
Aren't we just in here?
That's collection day, boys.
Tommy, you'll drive?
Bully and Sam can handle the rest.
It'll be routine.
Just a handful of stops today.
Bill at the motel was a little short last month.
We'll make sure he pays us the interest he owes.
No problem, boss.
Don't lay hands on anyone unless there's no other choice.
Our clients need to understand that we provide a valuable service.
They need to look at you and see Santa Michael.
They need to believe you'll protect them.
So let Morello stoop to bring them in.
Need to believe?
We're better than that.
The bills still do?
Wait, this is illegal?
Everyone pays up.
We can handle it.
Um.
Go see Ralphie about a car.
Okay, boss.
Yeah.
Yes, very.
For a second I thought he was smoking the cigar backwards.
Like, holy shit.
What a Chad move.
Probably just wants to tell you some bullshit story about some guy he whacked 20 years ago.
I kind of like this outfit.
I feel like I would wear this.
Nah, lose the tie.
Lose the tie, lose the hat.
Zip it down a little bit more.
Like another four inches.
All right.
Hey.
What'd you see?
Something new?
Wait, what do you mean?
You see like this little shitty gun you thought of me?
You didn't see like a rifle or a bazooka and think of me?
What's that supposed to mean?
You think that's funny?
What am I funny to you?
You think that's a joke?
Fucking little gun?
Funny like a clown?
Funny?
Funny how?
What an incredible scene.
Oh shit, I just tried to shoot him.
Do you think he would hear that?
There's no bullets in here, dude.
Oh, okay.
He can see it.
How do you reload?
Oh.
All right, X is reload.
And don't shoot yourself.
Thanks, Vincenzo.
Don't shoot yourself.
I got it.
Thanks.
All right, Ralph.
I'm ready.
I get my gun.
I know how to reload.
You guys are in the way.
No, you're not.
Do a diaper check.
All right, Ralph.
Do we all have guns?
One year since the crash.
The worst?
Yeah, Wall Street crash.
Right.
Beyond Meat.
Easy.
That was really easy.
You're a regular magician, Ralphie.
Oh shit, that's right.
These are when the doors were made out of, like, clay.
I forgot.
Opening a car door was as simple as just pulling it a little harder than normal.
These things don't even turn on, man.
This is a lemon.
Al's late again?
Seems so.
That's too bad.
What happened to him?
Is he okay?
Drive safe, Tom.
Holly's real belly.
He's alive still.
Stop it.
He's all right.
He's fine.
Drive to the collection.
Oh, now that's what we're talking about.
I can't snap my fingers and drive the car.
By the way, can I tell you what my favorite game, Billiards?
It's one of the best.
I like to go just, like, to the bar and play a round or two with the friends.
Is he drunk?
At what?
Are you asking me if I'm drunk at 1 15 in the afternoon on a Tuesday?
Yes.
Turn up the volume.
Set a reasonable volume.
All right, we have to collect money, so don't hurt them, right?
Just drive up here and be like, give me the money.
And aim the gun at him, but don't shoot.
Got it.
Easy.
Hey, Tom.
When it goes smooth, it's a breeze.
When they put up a fight, sometimes you gotta think on your feet.
Sure.
Just follow my lead.
Oh, did you guys hear Otto sneeze?
He just went...
Okay, done.
We're good.
How's little Julia?
How's the money?
I mean, how's the restaurant?
This letter is a notification that you are in default of your obligation
to make payments on your agreed loan.
This amount has been overdue since July 15, 1930.
You've ignored requests to pay this debt,
unless the full amount is received, within two weeks,
I will have no choice but to instruct this bank
to begin the foreclosure process of your home and business.
That's us.
So we have to do, like, protection?
We have to rough the place up?
Should I just eat a bunch of bread?
Stop picking up loaves and taking bites?
All right, let's give him one another month.
I think he deserves another month.
Double or nothing.
If he doesn't have the money in three months,
then we come back and we, I don't know,
we, like, take his sneakers and we sell them.
There's drugs back here.
I don't feel bad anymore.
Dude, he's got a Sam Trappini card?
This is gonna...
This is, like, worth, like, five grand.
What's he saying?
Able brown envelope.
That's not...
Oh, I would...
I probably wouldn't be doing that if I were you.
Lady, you're lucky that this is a fucking World of Warcraft sanctuary.
Otherwise, a chair is flying across the room.
I got it.
You need anything, anything at all.
Show the wheels, Sam.
Daily WoW reference.
Yeah, that's the one.
That old lady has more power than the Dawn.
Somebody's gonna fight back.
And then I'm gonna have to take out the bat
and start swinging, right?
That's how this is gonna work.
No, don't...
What's the point of that?
That doesn't do anything for me.
That was just gonna be violence.
Just for violence.
Like, no, I'm not doing that.
We're just gonna drive.
Well, that's what we called him.
Probably slammed his head into the counter back in...
27, I think.
Yeah, it was hilarious.
After that, no problems at all.
If you look, you can still see the blood.
Poor old bastard couldn't scrub it out.
Is it...
Can I go?
I don't know the rules of the road.
I don't know the right-of-way tears.
Slow down.
I'm going over the speed limit.
But we don't know Eugene's nephew,
so he might need reminded, too.
People just go.
It's not even four-way stop signs.
It's just drive across four lanes.
This is bad.
Welcome to the 1920s, yeah.
I'm not going over the speed limit, right?
Don't break any laws.
There's a cop right here.
That guy's a cop.
No.
That car is a cop.
Something over there is a cop.
Go ahead.
Go, go, go, go ahead.
Go.
Get ahead.
Move.
Oh, there's a guy in the way.
If there's a pedestrian in a crosswalk
and you're waiting for the pedestrian
you get beeped at,
that person deserves a middle finger.
I was backing out of a spot.
Okay, so this is the story
that I think about sometimes.
I was backing out of a spot
in a parking lot one time,
and there was this lady
who was parked perpendicularly
right behind me.
She was stopped.
She wasn't parked,
but she was pulled up in the parking lot.
I think she was waiting for somebody or something,
but she was right in the way
of where I was trying to back up.
She was right just blocking me,
and she didn't move.
This lady did not move.
It was like I had to finagle
so much around her car,
and she kept on closing her door,
and she's like,
no, back up, back up.
Yeah, you're good.
You're good.
And she's like, okay, what the fuck?
I did my good.
I'm out.
And right at the very end,
I didn't say anything.
He's doing the story.
Right at the very end,
when I finally,
after a full minute of doing
an eight-point turn
to get around this lady,
I put my thumb out the window
and gave up a thumbs up real quick,
and I think she thought
I gave her the finger.
I was like, yep, yep, I'm good,
but I think she saw the finger
and was just like,
fuck you.
But it was a thumbs up.
It was like, I'm good, yeah.
Did we get out of the car?
That was a sign.
That happened in Seinfeld.
Wait, that happened in Seinfeld?
I'm not lying.
I didn't watch an episode of Seinfeld
and then pulled it out of my memory.
I gave the thumbs up to somebody.
Here he comes.
That's not a fake story.
I swear to God that happened.
It happened in Seinfeld.
Dude, this dude just watched
an episode of Seinfeld
and then somehow made it
a part of his life.
No, this happened three weeks ago.
It was not that long ago.
Holy shit, that guy just
monster trucked that dude.
Kind of not hot.
I don't know.
Stealing jokes.
Is it stealing jokes
if it happened to you in real life?
We've been working these streets for years.
You come in and you think you know it all.
I'm not saying that, Sam.
I mean, you've been a day on the job, pal.
You haven't seen what we do.
You haven't seen how we do it.
I swear to God.
No, Polly.
This punk thinks he can walk in.
Why did I think that was a good idea?
Hey, Ralphie, I said.
Tom sure can drive.
No working after hours.
We OK?
After me and Sam.
No chance of that.
I thought it was grass.
I just got like loony tune.
No, Polly.
This punk thinks he can walk in here.
You hid.
You knew I was going to try
to go through the cut through the grass.
And you put a bunch of rocks in them.
Sorry.
I'd say sorry.
If I couldn't see the bullshit smile
you're trying to hide.
I could smell the crap in your pants from here.
No, you didn't get me.
When little Pony first came out with us,
I had him on his knees before he knew.
This is beautiful.
This beautiful countryside.
Where are we supposed to be?
I want to visit this place.
New York.
New York City.
I hate it out of the city.
You hate it most places.
Yeah, but out here it's worse.
How come there's a place so far out of town on our books?
Out of town's the safest place for deals.
Safest place for card games.
The safest place for most of the things we do.
Card games.
We're expecting a big bag of money today.
The guy owes.
All right, I gotta ask you guys a really important question.
This is the definitive moment of the stream.
Yeah, this place is a real earner.
Is it mafia or mafia?
The places that give you the most dough are the ones most people all get twice.
A lot of people say mafia.
I'm going to be playing mafia.
I'm going to play mafia.
Last stop before I lost heaven for rum coming up from Cuba.
Oh, shit.
Is it good at this far?
Sure, they do.
And that's how we can sell it so expensive.
What am I talking about?
People say mafia.
Mafia.
The rates get exchanged.
Salieri protects it,
but he lets the other families use it too.
Even Barolo could keep the peace.
Not mafia.
Plus, it's far enough away that no one cares.
So long as everyone does that.
Yes, they do.
No one's going to rock the boat.
Be on the meter here, Tom.
I wouldn't be saying it if it wasn't true.
Anyone else starting to miss the side of the streets and sidewalks?
You're not one for the great outdoors, Polly.
He's not one for anything.
Indoors, out of the city.
Oh.
Like when we sit in the field doing some booze handover or something.
It's always knee-deep and shit and most times it's dark and cold as hell.
That's why it's good we got you now, Tom.
You can do all the jobs that Polly hates.
Make pronunciations.
I've heard people say mafia.
Mafia.
People say Mario.
Super Mario.
So it's not above what?
This is not even right.
He's just going to love you.
People say Super Mario and mostly they're over the age of 50.
Don't tell me that your parents did not call him Super Mario.
Yes, they did.
Those people are wrong.
That doesn't mean they don't happen.
Cool, man.
The name Mario existed before that game.
So?
I'm not arguing the origins of the name Mario.
I just said some people pronounce it Mario.
Herman, you're like five years younger than my dad, Omega Lo.
No, I'm not.
Dad's like 39?
How old are you?
Are you eight?
What are you doing here?
This is a legal stream for you to be on.
Look, it's...
Where's the rock?
There's no rock in there.
I was hoping for an explosion.
I'll be honest.
Okay, let me be...
I'll come clean here.
I was hoping it was a gas tank explosion.
I was going for it.
Wally, go do your thing.
Find a way into the motel, sure.
Got to be a secret wall here somewhere.
Okay, there would be no suspicion here.
You would think there was an animal outside.
Like a raccoon.
Let my friend go.
What's in here?
A bed.
Take care of all the thugs.
I will.
There's a thug over here.
Where is he?
Oh, shit, I thought he was sitting at the dinner table.
Is he underneath me?
Who the fuck is this guy?
The front door isn't going to open.
Okay, the floor...
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The green indicator is not an enemy.
Oh, shit.
It's on classic mode.
He's so bad.
No, I'm not.
I'm...
All right, I'm kicking into overdrive.
I'm going for real.
You're going to die so many times.
Like, no, I'm not.
No, I'm not.
Watch this.
If I get...
Okay, if I take one fucking damage from here on out,
I will...
I will eat...
I will do...
I will do chubby bunny with marshmallows.
Like, in a week.
And I'll do a chubby bunny thing with marshmallows.
Hey, Jerma sucks.
Thanks for five subs.
Go back in, going this way.
Remember, I didn't say if I get spotted.
If I take damage...
Where the fuck is he going?
But no, if I don't care.
Who's in here?
Oh, shit.
I got to hide him.
I got to hide his body.
One...
Okay, we got one, two, three, four.
Oh, no.
There's a lot of people in here.
How many...
I used all my molotovs.
Shit.
Of course I did.
Okay, what if I shoot this guy in the head right now?
I didn't take any damage yet.
I didn't take any damage.
Fuck, chubby bunny.
I don't want to do that.
Why didn't I say like 100 community subs?
I would rather do that.
I would rather give 100 community subs to this channel
Let's go.
Then do chubby bunny.
He wants to see that.
I don't want to see that.
And neither do you.
Fuck, I didn't think there was going to be like 10 people here.
Give me the knife.
I don't have any marshmallows.
I can't do it right now.
All right, give me the knife.
How come there's not a Metal Gear Solid like...
Huh?
Stab him.
Stab him in the head.
Oh, shit.
That guy's a gun.
Why wouldn't you have shot me?
Oh, fuck.
It's on hard mode.
It's on really difficult.
It's on classic mode, which is really hard.
Okay, I'm going to get it this time.
He's actually so bad at video games.
No, I'm on the mode where if you take one shot, you die.
Not this time.
Here we go.
Use the gun?
I don't need a gun.
All right, there's three guys downstairs.
Nobody in this bed.
Can I get anything in this...
What do you mean we'll find him?
Is there an animal out there?
Wait, that's the raccoon.
That was causing all the noise.
Right, okay.
Anybody coming?
All right, we're good.
They sneaking.
I think there's a guy in here.
Yep, there's a guy out here.
I know there is.
There's reach for the window?
I'm trying to hit the fucking fox.
All right, what am I doing?
Is there nobody else up here?
There's a guy checking over there.
Checking over there.
All right, it's gun time.
You have a DDT.
Oh, what?
It's a fake.
What the fuck just happened?
That was another player.
Stop it.
Why are you coming from?
What?
Open door?
They're all in there?
They're all just clown card into the room.
Okay, keyboard and mouse.
Oh, not fucking around anymore.
Here we go.
FPS mode.
Fuck this.
Why did he fall off?
Where you at?
Come on out.
Let's go.
Why is my sensitivity so high?
Because I didn't even change it.
So high.
Okay, hold on.
I got to fix that.
It's unbelievably high.
Game.
Controls.
Mouse sensitivity.
Yikes.
I can't.
I got to get through the first mission.
What do you mean pretending?
The guy just like glued to my body
and swung twice and hit me in the head and I died.
There's a guy right here.
How do you crouch?
Okay, fucking god damn it.
Just open the fucking door and die.
Got him.
I'm over here.
Where's somebody shooting?
I thought somebody was on the roof.
What the hell just happened?
Somebody shot me.
What happened?
I hear a guy sprinting.
I hear somebody sprinting.
Somebody sprinting.
I need help.
Nice.
Okay, we're good.
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
This is fun.
All right, there's like one more guy in here
and then we're good.
Where is he?
Oh, okay, we're good.
One guy behind the pool table.
By the way, it's one of my favorite games.
Hiding behind my favorite game.
That it?
It was fucking hard.
Uh-oh, guy with a duffel bag.
Oh no, more of this.
Oh, got knocked over into your favorite game.
Don't run up over for a joke.
Shoot while driving.
No, don't shoot that person's car.
What did they do?
Somebody leaning out of the car trying to shoot at me?
This person's just in the fucking way.
Shoot at everyone.
Come on, dude.
Why?
Just use the car as a gun.
Catch the thug.
I'm going as fast as I can, man.
How am I supposed to shoot the guys?
Oh my god.
Stupid.
All right, we're good.
All right, wait till it gets like the indicator.
I'm just, I can't even aim this.
It's just, I guess I'm shooting at the back of their car.
That's why for a speed boost.
Spam it.
I don't think that's going to do anything for me.
Fucking asshole game.
It's not rocket science.
I was doing it.
I know, guys, I've been in this chair for like 30 years playing video games.
I know that you shoot the car, but I can't even aim the gun.
Got him.
I've been in this chair for 30 years.
Oh shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please don't do this to me.
Fucking aiming and driving with a controller.
I may as well dunk my head under water and fucking just start gulping.
I may as well just put my head under water and scream.
Okay, this is the one right here.
This is the one.
Oh fucking, I can't.
I hope you guys forget about the chubby bunny thing.
I really do.
Am I even hitting him?
I'm hitting him, I guess.
I don't hit a fucking tree.
I love a god.
All right, I got it.
I got it.
This is the one.
This is the run.
Watch out for the rocks.
Come on, dude.
Really?
Out.
You're not turning to me.
Is he dead?
Search the car.
Get out.
30 years in this chair.
That's how you show up.
Everybody how you do it.
All right.
That was a really bad victory fucking exclamation.
I don't know what the hell I was trying to say.
Chapter complete.
Intermezzo.
30 years just to do a chubby bunny stream.
That's going to be so embarrassing.
Thanks, you boy, for the 10 community subs.
Raglan.
Thank you.
10 subs dropped right now.
Thanks a lot.
Have the run of the city.
For every buck sellier he made.
Don Morello would turn 10.
He paid off cops, politicians, judges, and anyone he couldn't buy.
He scared him to look in the other way.
Kermit, that can actually kill you.
It's not the city jumping in its own shadow.
I'll give you that.
What?
Do you hear anything about Joey Crackers?
Yeah, got his name in the Moretto file.
Sure.
Boxer, right?
Yeah.
That's the guy.
I could die from chubby bunny.
Kids have died doing chubby bunny before.
I'll be very careful.
I'll dunk him in water first.
No, I'm not going to eat them.
I'm going to turn the cam off and I'm going to do a big smear puke out of my mouth.
Into like a trash can.
My fault.
No, I just, I just, I ain't never been in no accident.
Well, repairs are going to be expensive.
Oh, you're not going to need that, sir.
Tires are just fine.
Grill's a little bent up is all.
I mean, I got a cousin I could...
What?
And that's how you went to jail for the rest of your life.
Hey.
Someone spun you a tale, pal.
You got an informant right there says Morello made a mint every time Crackers went to the mat.
That's true, too.
And still Morello left that poor, sad, dead in the street.
Pizza Hut, a warm-up box thing when they delivered the pizza.
All right, I wasn't paying attention.
I could've, I could've been funnier.
Maybe to Don, though Joey's career was on the downhill.
Maybe he was trying to scare someone, a guy in a pay-in-off.
Who knows?
Don Celieri chalked it up to Morello not being able to think straight when he was mad.
I love when people get so pissed off.
It's just like, what the fuck is he talking about?
Do you have any more run-ins with...
It gives me energy.
Not at first.
For a couple of years after I joined up, things were quiet.
We got into a few dust-ups with guys trying to muscle in.
But else-wise, it was just the usual routine.
Who's out for protection?
Me and the boys doing rounds to collect small time.
What is it?
What is it, Chubby Bunny?
I ain't gonna lie.
You get marshmallows and you put them in your cheeks and you say Chubby Bunny after you put one in.
I'm not gonna do that many.
I'm not gonna do a dangerous amount of marshmallows.
Guys, I'm not gonna put enough marshmallows to kill me in my mouth.
I'm just gonna do enough for it to be accurate.
It's a great investment.
The kid can't lose a race if he walks the track.
He graduates from the Junkers to Gowjobs, and I start placing a few bets on him here and there.
Next thing I know, I've made all my money back and more.
Hey, Sam says he's the guy to beat.
He was.
We ran all the competition out of town.
But now Ralph says there's a hot-sock European...
Here it comes.
Oh, fuck.
And he's got a car faster than our boys...
Five-hour mission.
Okay.
How much do we stand to lose?
A truckload.
But not just our outfit.
A lot of guys from the neighborhood come to me for financial advice.
They've all put money down on this kid.
It'll be like Black Thursday around here if he loses.
Well, for everyone except Morello.
No, you think he's from the European?
Oh, I'm certain of it.
Odd friends, skip 10 hours.
He wants something to happen to the driver.
Can't find him.
You're giving me a lot of power here to want to beat this really, really quickly and really skillfully.
...disappears now?
None of our wagers will stand.
Five fouls and a race is fixed.
What about his car?
That's the ticket, Tommy.
Ralph knows a guard at the track.
You go down there tonight, you boost the Europeans' car, bring it to one of our mechanics.
I'll make a few adjustments when you bring the car back.
Should be no problem, boss.
Okay.
Talk to Ralph.
Odd viewers, skip to two hours and 36 minutes and 14 seconds for the next mission.
That's very specific.
Hey, Titi Tommy.
Big day coming up, right?
Hey, no.
Time traveler.
Kinda hard to miss.
I'm still here.
He isn't going to let Morello break his winning streak, huh?
No, no, sir.
I had to send him a message.
So tonight, borrow his guy's motor from the track.
My friend Bobby is a guard.
For a little dough, he'll show you where it is and look someplace else while you t-t-t-turn the key.
You like Bobby already?
Sure.
Get in there, there's a Sutter guy, L-L-Lucas Bertone.
You take the car to him down under the Ju-Ju-Giuliano Bridge.
He'll, you know, tune it a little.
Make the race tomorrow more, more, more interesting.
Then I take the car straight back and Bobby can stop looking someplace else.
But you gotta be quick.
Bobby comes off shift at 1.30 and then the next guy, he's an ass.
Am I saying the Travis Scott Burger?
This mission made me cry growing up.
Hey, if you need somewhere to keep your m-motor seat where no one can take them,
feel free to use the garage.
Oh, because you just saw the ad.
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Everyone saying that just saw the ad.
Right, right, I forgot.
Oh, shit.
All right.
What do I got?
Taxi, six, the V8.
Yeah, I want the V8, man.
You kidding me?
This thing's sick.
Add V8s to the garage by driving them.
Meet with the guard at the racetrack.
All right, this is a fast car.
This is the last mission everybody plays before dropping the game.
Okay.
This is the second mission in the whole game, realistically speaking.
Can you pass on the left in the 30s?
Yes.
I want a motorcycle so bad.
I want- I'm gonna do-
No, I'm gonna do motorcycle.
No, I'm not.
It's gone already.
Never mind.
You guys are really talking up this mission.
Dude, I gotta prepare for this then.
A long way away, isn't it?
All right, here we go.
You Bobby?
Yep.
We can take your car to the garage.
Place is empty.
What, I have to suit this thing up?
Your friend Ralphie's a friend of mine.
I mean, if you got the money, sure.
30 years of gaming about to come to an end.
Tomorrow morning they start coming.
Whole city.
They smuggle in hooch.
There's fighting.
I hate it.
Ah, come mine.
Name a better place to pick up a date than this place this weekend.
Don't get me started.
Big brain cigarettes?
All right, here we are.
This is it.
All right, I'm just stretching.
Ooh, there she is.
99 Karazela C-Series.
Best in class.
It's a shame you gotta wreck it.
If they see this down the road,
the cops are gonna ask questions.
Try to keep it in one piece, too.
Try to keep it in one piece and-
So, I gotta be back from Breton by 1.30
before the next guy shifts.
Yeah.
It's timed, is that what it is?
It's timed.
Okay, let's go.
We're good.
Just keep the car in one piece, get back in two minutes.
Holy shit, this thing is fast.
It's all right.
I got one guy looking at me.
We're good.
So far, so good.
I'm at 50% damage.
Oh, get this thing out of the way.
What the fuck are you doing?
I got a full minute.
We're gonna take shortcut.
Shit.
Shortcut to the checkpoint is what I meant.
Restart.
Already don't like it.
Bad start.
All right.
Really bad start.
Just restart.
Or not.
Let's see.
All right.
The handling is insane.
So, just slow down.
How do I re-
Just restart from checkpoint.
Punch yourself in the face?
All right.
Easy.
Don't go crazy.
You probably don't have to go that fast.
It's just addicting to go fast in this game.
Okay.
Slow down.
Big turn.
That was stupid.
I touched the bumper.
Okay.
So, bounce me across the whole game.
I just gotta get good car spawns and I'll be fine.
Pass this guy on the right and then lean to the left a little.
The right, I mean.
Sidewalk drive if you can.
Okay.
We're fine.
Right down the middle.
Right.
Slow down.
Losing control.
I got one minute.
How much further is it?
It's right there.
I got 39 seconds.
Hardest mission in the game.
You kidding me?
I'm done.
It was so hard.
Yeah.
I mean, it was tricky.
Oh, that's not a garage door that opens.
Oh, shit.
I'm good.
We don't have much time.
Hey, I'm a fast worker.
Sit tight.
Hey, hey.
You want a health stick?
Yeah, sure.
I'll take a health stick.
Okay.
Now what?
Thanks, Lucas.
I gotta get back before anyone catches on.
This turns on with 10 seconds left.
I'm gonna laugh my ass off.
Misbehave.
Hey, tell Mr. Salieri.
I'm always available for this kind of work.
I do stuff for a lot of people.
But I always know where I stand with you guys.
Hot cars.
Getaways.
Anything for the right price.
Let's just hope Salieri's guy wins tomorrow.
For all our sakes.
Okay.
It's gonna misbehave.
I'm careful.
Two minutes.
Okay, I got two minutes.
It's gonna misbehave.
Is that what the engine indicator thing on top is supposed to mean?
What happens if it...
Okay, so it can't get that hot.
Don't hold the minigun down for that long.
This is an easy straightaway.
No, and shit just knocks you around too.
It bounces you around.
It's all right.
This is not as bad as I thought it was gonna be.
Pull it down.
Punch it.
To the right and then to the right.
Move.
All right.
Wrong side of the road.
That's where I shine the most.
I'm almost there.
Just get out of the way.
32 seconds.
I got it.
Move.
Out of the way.
Right here.
25 seconds.
Shortcut.
Should I do a shortcut or just do it?
12 seconds.
10 seconds.
8 seconds.
5.
4.
I thought I could go through the fence somehow.
All right.
Here we go.
Don't let up.
I'm gonna get there.
Here we go.
You know I should go the other way.
Idiot.
Fucking idiot.
That's not even my fault.
All right.
What happens if the thing goes all the way up?
Does it explode?
As long as I keep it under that bar, I'm fine.
Damage doesn't make it go higher.
I'm okay.
That was a pretty clean transition out of that spot.
That's a hard spot.
That's a hard turn.
Wrong side of the road.
Good.
Oh my god.
I almost just hit the side.
Sorry.
All right.
Watch out.
That rice-a-roni truck.
You dick.
Okay.
That's the part that's gonna be a problem.
I think I still got it.
20 seconds.
That was close.
I filled it all the way up.
That was really close.
That would have been a 500-yard shot if a golf game was in this.
Oh, dude.
This is impossible.
This mission's not even completable.
Did I win?
Come on.
Oh, wow.
You just get...
All right.
That's not bad.
That wasn't that bad.
Okay. Let's get out of here.
Big day tomorrow.
Oh, wow.
We just got a monster raid from Kitboga.
What's going on, guys?
Welcome to the stream.
Thank you, Kitboga, for the raid.
That's a...
Yeah, it's a monster raid.
Hope you had a good stream, dude.
So Sam walks out of the bathroom...
We're playing Mafia Remastered.
...because our tenor's gonna hand over what he owes.
And his two sons...
Gonna be fun?
...closer.
Some of the most fun I've had in a long time was on Kit's stream.
...feel like brick shithouses.
The pleasure to have you here.
Welcome.
...his crazy bastard.
He waltzes out of the bathroom and pisses it all over the joint.
Really?
Is this the actual hard part?
Sometimes you just gotta make him think you're crazy.
Yeah, pizza buddy raid.
That's right.
You got the moment.
Actual hard part?
You guys...
You can't...
Boy, who cried wolf.
First, it was the first part.
Oh, he's not gonna do it.
Second part.
Oh, it's impossible.
Third part.
It's impossible.
Stream chat that cried wolf.
I think.
He doesn't know.
Sing the raid song.
I don't have a raid song.
I have a follower song.
I don't know how it goes.
Fill the lyrics in.
You know how they go.
All right, so I have to just win the race.
But do I have to kill somebody in the race or what?
Just win.
Okay.
All right, if I hold it on the buzzer, do I get a boost like in Mario Kart?
Something's wrong with the car.
Just win the race.
I took that guy out.
That guy's not gonna race anymore.
It's crazy.
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
I got three laps to get to first place.
Shit.
Oh, it's too fast.
I see it.
Don't go that fast.
It's funny now.
But yeah, I'm probably going to be very, very agitated in about 10 minutes.
We're laughing now.
Oh, he hit the guy.
That funny moment is going to be a rage-inducing moment in about 15 minutes.
Just restart.
I've got this three laps.
I'm...
Look, I'm closing in.
I'm closing in.
Right?
That's...
Yeah, on my neck.
That would be very painful.
That would be horrible.
Nothing matters until the last 10 seconds of the race, guys.
Don't you know?
I could be two miles away in last place.
As long as I just come in first, who cares?
I mean, I'm very far away right now.
I'm gonna get lapped.
Are the other drivers still on the course?
Guys, yeah.
All I have to do is get a blue shell.
They give all the fucking losers back in 10th place blue shells.
I'll be fine.
Just restart.
Fine.
I need to get the cannon.
Yeah, the bullet bill where you just teleport through everybody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Skip.
One, two, three.
All right.
Just do it like every other racing game like this.
Just stay behind everybody and wait till there's a major crash.
And then just slowly go 10 miles per hour by everybody.
Hey, we're fine.
I'm still here.
Always pass on the inside.
Hey, I want to stay in like fifth to 10th place until the last 10 seconds.
I already have the strategy.
I already know what to do.
That guy's dead.
All right.
We got a crash.
Easy.
10th place.
This is exactly where I want to be.
Good.
I don't want to be in first place.
That turn sucks.
It's not about going fast at all.
Just throwing.
Oh, I'm in ninth place.
I'm like halfway there.
All right.
Now punch it.
And then there's a huge that big turn here.
Okay, here we go.
We're going to lose two more people in front of us.
Oh, my God.
What do I do?
What?
My fucking God.
This is horrible.
Restart.
Not yet.
Once I know I once I can't see the car in front of me, I'll restart.
Does the fucking wheel even work?
I'm turning the car and I'm just going straight.
Yeah, it's a restart.
It has to be.
Holy shit.
This is ridiculous.
Okay, here we go.
New plan.
New plan is to cause a horrible, awful accident.
Just stuff myself into first place and just try to blow up like 10 of these cars.
Stay right here.
I'm going to just I'm going to just drive into the crowd like this, this group here.
Okay, well, it all did was take me out.
All right, I'm going to slow down.
That's unethical.
Well, I'm just trying to win.
Okay, I'm going to try.
I'm going to do very, very slow.
I have to drift and shit.
I don't have to start all the way back here.
That's so unfair.
I'm going to try some drifting.
Come on, stay with it.
These people are stopping in front of me.
They're actually holding their brakes down.
Dicks.
Okay.
All right, I'm going to be in 12.
Holy shit, we dodged that one.
Oh, most lost control.
Go with the crash, go with the crash, go with the crash.
I'm not in last place.
I'm in 14th.
Two people are dead.
So, how the fuck do you take this turn?
Use the brakes.
You can't use the gun.
I don't have a gun.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to go left side.
I'm going to try to pass everybody on the left.
I'm going to try to stay somewhere around 80.
Why is my car covered in fucking cooking oil?
Like, I don't, why can I, I don't understand.
What the fuck?
I was going slow.
The thing just spun out.
Bad traction.
Well, they have bad traction too.
It's not fair.
All right.
Let's try this again.
I was in like ninth or eighth place.
We're going to improve here.
This big turn is stupid.
And it gets rid of all the newbie players.
Slow down, omega low.
How fast do you think I was going right there?
I was going like 25 miles per hour.
We warned you.
So, is this one of those scenarios where this game,
when it was returned to Blockbuster was,
you know when you would buy a game or rent a game at Blockbuster,
it would have like a save file on it?
Was it just always on this save file?
You got to be fucking kidding me.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Lightning McQueen?
Why, we're going to do the same thing as that guy.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me see the mini map.
Can I see anybody yet?
Holy shit.
This is horrible.
This is what you guys are talking about.
Now he gets it.
Three laps, two.
What were they, why?
Why not just one?
Why do I have to do three of these?
Don't hold the gas down.
I'm not.
I'm being gentle.
Okay, we're good, kind of.
I guess, kind of.
That was very gentle, but I'm in last place.
Look, as long as I can see everybody, I don't even care.
All right, this guy is erratically driving.
I'm going a little too fast, but it's all right.
I'm just going to gain some ground.
I'm going to slow down right here.
Just coast, coast, coast, coast, coast, coast.
Come on, you guys are filling up the road.
Pass on the left.
Okay, slow.
Good.
All right, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good.
Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow.
Get out of my way.
He's connected to me.
You fucking connected to me.
That guy latched tires onto me and told me.
Hooked my tire with his tire.
That was better than the last attempt, though.
That was better than the last time.
He got stream sniped.
All right, here comes the famous difficult turn where every single AI can do it,
except for the one guy in the back who's the computer or non-computer player.
Nobody else has any trouble with that at all,
except for the one guy actually playing the fucking video game.
Famous.
All right, stay on the left side here.
Don't hook on to somebody.
We're okay.
All right, I'm doing way better than I was the last few times.
That's certain.
Slow down.
Get off of me.
Same guy.
Okay, that's always been the wall.
Still not in a bad spot.
Let's do this turn good.
Really?
Why are you guys all going so fast?
I think I'm the famous turn again.
All right, there's lap two.
I didn't crash yet.
That's good.
Jesus.
Dude, what the fuck is this mission?
What the hell?
Lower the difficulty?
How would that change the driving?
It's worse AI?
It actually is worse AI.
Classic is hard driving.
I'm going burger boy technique.
No, fuck all these tech.
No, screw every one of these.
These things you guys telling me.
Follow on burger boy technique.
Let's go.
The burger boy technique is you just don't give a shit.
Shit.
Here we go.
Right through.
12th.
11th.
Okay, we're fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
Yeah, full, full throttle.
Throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle, throttle.
Watch out for this jump.
All right, we're still a fine.
This is all right.
Could be worse.
Let's follow the other drivers.
Too fast.
Way too fast.
Pull it back.
Of course, look at how fast that guy's going.
No matter to him.
Nice.
How many people uninstalled the game at this point?
You remade the game.
Hey, let's remake the game and make sure we get to a point where everybody fucking uninstalls it.
You don't see the next 14 hours of the story.
Being filtered.
Yeah, well, what the fuck?
I'm not lowering the difficulty yet.
Not yet.
That was an anger bump.
Yeah, get the fuck out of my way.
Get out of my way.
Put this hay here.
I'm never going to get to fifth place.
I need like a TAS to be able to complete this mission.
I tried driving on the road.
Yeah, I have.
Dude, what the fuck?
Why?
Look at how much acceleration.
That guy went 5,000 miles.
Look at him.
I'm holding R.
I'm holding down right trigger.
That guy has...
He's going 10 times faster than me.
Ride the bank.
You tried going as fast as you can.
Yeah, your car spins around in a circle and every other AI driver
drives 500 miles per hour.
I'm the only one that has to drive the car.
Okay, at least one idiot I get to pass.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
We got a full idiot pile up here.
Easy, don't rip the wheel.
Look, there he goes.
Ride the wall.
I don't care.
I'm not going to sit here for five hours.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care.
I'm just going to beat it.
I'm just going to play the game.
What, I have to do the driving mission for four hours?
If you can beat the Simpsons hit and run.
Simpsons run at least had a car that made sense when you drove it.
And I know, oh, it's an old car.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm going to blow by these fucking assholes on easy.
This is grandma difficulty.
Get out of the way.
I don't care.
You can call me terrible.
You can call me shitty all you want.
I'm going to get in first place on easy.
Hand the controller to your mother game.
Even this is still hard.
Oh shit.
I can't lose on easy.
I got to first try it on easy.
Otherwise, I have to delete my Twitch account.
Get off me.
Get off of me.
Bank, bank, bank, bank.
I don't need to bank anything.
This is to win.
I know, I'm trying to kill that guy.
That's a threat.
That's the guy in second place.
I don't care.
I know people are going to be making fun of me for years over this.
Who cares?
Use the bank.
Guys, I don't even know what that means.
When I hear you say that, all I know to think about
is like withdrawing money from an ATM.
I don't know.
Use the bank.
I don't even know what that means.
I'm going to win.
I'm in first place.
I'm doing fine.
I don't tip over.
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm embarrassed for him.
No, you're not.
It's fine.
Whatever.
What do you...
What does it matter?
What?
Everyone...
You know, your resident sleep...
Fine, I'll put it on classic mode again.
I can't lose my Twitch account.
It's going to get fucking deleted if I don't win.
I set for a bank.
Come on, this guy's smoking.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm good.
How embarrassing.
Get those resident sleepers out of here.
I don't want to see them.
Get the resident sleepers out of here.
Fine.
You want me to turn it on classic?
Where's the end of the match?
All right, fine.
Let me just get to this next turn
and I'll put it on classic mode.
Where's the finish...
Where's the finish line?
Do it now.
Not yet.
After I ride the bank, I will...
This is all the sleepers.
Fuck, man.
What the fuck?
Come on.
I don't want to...
That's all right.
Look, I'll beat it on classic.
How does that sound?
All right, we did it.
I'm getting booed, but I won.
I'll take the booze.
Think you underestimate
how much patience I have for that.
Relapse on classic mode?
No fucking way.
Stream would turn off.
Oh shit.
This is the most spam
I've ever seen on my channel.
Holy shit.
It's every single person doing this.
Every single one of you is doing this.
Holy shit.
I must mean it's true.
No, no, no.
Take off emote only mode,
and I want everyone to spam that.
I want you to break my chat.
There was 10,000 people there.
I deserve it.
Hey, remember when we said that?
What it would look like
if you had bots in your channel?
This is it right here.
Now I can just play the game.
Well, I just want to play the game.
I just want to experience the story.
Whoa, did you say
you just put it on easy, Tommy?
I wasn't paying that much attention.
No more.
I'm done.
I don't want to see it anymore.
No more.
Okay.
Put it into cool guy mode.
Put it in.
All right.
No more of that.
Making me feel self-conscious.
Yeah.
I'm feeling a little self-conscious right now.
Where's Polly?
Here's the funny part.
The people that come into the stream
that see that I've only been streaming for a few hours
are going to be like,
holy shit, he beat that mission in like an hour or so.
Pretty good.
Top tier.
What?
Polly.
Looking for Polly.
Yeah, I'm realizing right now
I just did the unforgivable sin.
I made it.
I put the game on easy.
On stream.
On Twitch.
That was very bad.
I never should have done that.
Yep.
Polly, where the fuck are you?
I could have put it on normal
and got away with it probably
with enough explaining and enough gas lighting.
Easy though.
No.
It's going to be about a year
before you guys get over that one.
Polly.
I don't know what Polly looks like.
I felt like I was holding a microwave.
All right.
Let's continue our playthrough of Mafia.
There's Polly.
Hey, Polly.
Eat.
Okay, he's going to eat.
There's the cafeteria over here.
Probably right here.
Polly?
Eating?
Somewhere?
I think I might put it on easy to find him.
Yeah, he'll probably show me
an indicator on the map where he is.
Not a bad idea.
Polly?
Where the hell is he?
There he is.
Polly.
God damn it, man.
Why aren't you Polly?
For the love of God.
It's as if he was eating.
He's the guy that looks like Jimmy Fallon.
They all look like Jimmy Fallon.
It's just Jimmy Fallon everywhere.
Polly?
You look like Jimmy Fallon.
Everybody looks like Jimmy Fallon.
Oh, of course.
He's the guy all the way at the edge of the map lying down.
This is show some respect.
Jimmy Fallon?
That's true.
But I'm saying you gotta go home too.
He does look like Jimmy Fallon.
Okay then.
I guess.
Let's go, Jim.
He's about as funny as Jimmy Fallon.
You know, I haven't seen Jimmy Fallon
do anything in, I don't know,
probably seven or eight years.
He says he hosts the Tonight Show or something, right?
You know what I said?
What did you say, Polly?
I said this guy.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's not true.
I ate his Ben and Jerry's ice cream.
Yeah, that was like probably a year ago.
So I have consumed Jimmy Fallon content.
By the way, it sucks.
It's really not that good.
Half-baked best Ben and Jerry's ice cream.
You don't even need a celebrity on that one.
Or Chunky Monkey.
Get out of here.
What do you mean?
I love Chunky Monkey.
He's the best.
Chunky Monkey without the walnuts
would be the best ice cream ever made.
I don't like nuts and ice cream, really.
I love pistachio ice cream,
but I don't like the pistachios in the ice cream.
I just like the pistachio-flavored green ice cream.
Kind of getting in the way.
I usually just go around them.
What happened?
What am I doing?
Fish food.
Yeah, fish food's pretty good.
Take me to the blue tropics.
I didn't take you home.
The bridge.
Take the bridge over to the island.
Take me to the ladies.
Pauly, get out of the car, please.
Go lie down for a few hours.
Way to drive in movie.
Get the fuck out of the car, Pauly.
I feel so good.
After complete.
We had some subs, by the way.
We had Nepsi gave five community subs.
Chungy, Chungy Scrungey gave five,
and then Malcolm X2 gave five as well.
Let's go, Tom.
You want anything else?
No, I'm heading home.
Hey, Tom, before you go,
I ask you maybe a small favor.
Sure, Luigi.
What do you need?
Zombie Eater, $50.
5,000 fucking bits.
Sarah.
Thank you, Zombie Eater.
Yeah, I hear it.
She doesn't need any kind of-
Huge money.
You owe us a chubby bunny,
but seeing as that you committed the card,
I'll set up changing the game's difficulty to easy on stream.
Don't you think we deserve something else?
Maybe.
I'll think about that.
I gotta piss.
Watch the cut scene and relax.
I'll be right back.
Luigi, I'd be honored.
Sarah, time to close.
What's this then?
Tom is...
Tom's gonna take you.
They're right.
Hey, I just work here.
Make sure nobody bother you.
Fine.
If it'll make you feel better, Pop.
Hey.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Let me get my coat.
I'll wait for you outside.
You okay?
I don't need anyone walking me home.
Hey, we were talking about meeting up tonight anyway.
Quit goofing off.
Okay.
I'll wait for you, I guess.
You with me or not?
AFK.
Hey, welcome to stream AFK.
Ow.
Oh, cookies.
Hey, guys.
What is it?
What is he gonna think?
He treats me like a kid sometimes.
Hey, I get it.
He's protective.
He's seen things.
We've all seen things.
What am I holding?
We gotta talk about you stealing food.
Hey, I cook it, so I get to say where it goes.
We won't say.
Wait, is it-
Are we gonna go on a date or something?
Well, maybe tomorrow's finally gonna be the day he fixes his own food.
He's hoping it.
All right, now let's run.
Hello?
Yeah, oh, it's not as much as last time.
It's enough.
No one thinks you're an angel.
The dawn hates being food go to waste.
And this, this has gotta be Tommy.
This is Tommy.
They told us all about you.
Isn't that right?
Your famous race driver, Tom.
Everyone talks about you.
Yeah, she's right.
They talk about anything in particular besides that I just won the race?
Nothing about how hard it was?
No, not yet.
Not that I've heard.
I'll see you at church.
Good.
All right, Sarah.
We had a wonderful date.
It's been really fun.
It's nice you do that, Tom.
Well, three people on this block.
Trump voice is the lowest form of comedy that you have.
What?
Who's-
One of the-
Donald Trump?
What are you talking about?
I was-
This is this guy.
What are you talking about?
That's all you got?
You spend all the time with a lady killer like Sam Trepine.
Just because you go like this doesn't mean it's Donald.
I have it automatically, Donald.
I was doing his voice.
I wasn't doing Trump.
No.
Is there gonna be a fight or something here?
I mentioned it to dad this one time.
And all of a sudden he gets you to be my knight in shining armor.
No, no, Sarah.
Don't worry.
These are all actors.
All of them.
Well, like I said-
Every single fucking one.
Please, there's no problem.
He said you wouldn't want other guys I dated.
I'm trying to save Tommy and all.
These guys over here playing dice,
they're gonna do the exact same movements over and over again.
Pictures made.
They gotta make sure they stay in the camera.
They did blocking earlier.
Check that out.
Sarah, this camera's in every fucking direction.
Are you stepping-
Piss off.
We'll let your boyfriend watch.
What do you say?
We going to have trouble here.
Trouble started back when you tried to steal our girl, chief.
You saps aren't careful.
You'll end up in wooden overcoats.
Last chance to walk away.
We ain't for ales.
We know who you work for.
Sally Erie might have been the big six when he was younger,
but he's all washed up now.
It's only a matter of time-
Zoomer hair.
I need Sally Erie.
Or anyone else.
Not for this.
See what you got, cake eater.
All right, so I just kicked their asses.
This is where we let off to.
Uh, I just pulled a grenade.
Weapon.
You still want to fight me?
Okay, at what point would you run?
Okay, I run now.
Oh, no.
He changed the difficulty to easy.
This is supposed to be a fist fight.
Let's get out of here.
Ooh.
Okay, am I gonna get in trouble for that?
Push me?
Stab him.
Holy shit.
Oh, boss.
Fuck it.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
This guy would be out in a second, dude.
God damn it, man.
How many running hits do I-
That's what I got, you little bitch.
Do I kill him?
All right, get to Sarah.
Give me the bat.
All right, they're all actors.
You got a good right hook.
I'll give you that.
You're bleeding.
Come up to my place.
I'll take a look.
Am I, though?
Is I supposed to be bleeding?
Yeah, their blood is all over my arms.
Where?
Oh, on my-
It's supposed to be on the arm.
What do you got?
Compliments of the done.
Nice.
Take another.
I mean, I get-
All right.
You gonna grin and bear this?
Is this like the 1600s?
Yeah, I'll be okay.
Good.
You were like doctors and you didn't just like drink alcohol to do-
take care of wounds and shit.
Think about it, will ya?
It's gonna take as long as it takes.
The sloppier the stitch, the uglier the scar.
Yes, you did.
Am I right?
You stitched up a lot of fellas.
Getting rid of scurvy.
It's just duct tape.
Yeah, you're in a full suit.
You wanna-
No, no, no.
This thing never comes off, ever.
I shower in this fucking thing.
Sarah.
Hey, Mayo, thanks for the five community subs.
And also Rip, Alex Trebek, thanks for the five community subs, too.
He has a drop in subs today.
Thank you.
She started working here before she could see over the bar.
I don't have a daughter of my own, Tom.
I'd do anything for Luigi's little girl.
So would I.
We all would.
That's right, boss.
Anything for Luigi and Sarah.
Do those bastards think this is fucking Luna Parker?
I'd just say Jimmy Fallon.
That's all I-
I'll rip him apart with my own hands.
Just, I'm waiting for him to start laughing and look into the camera and giggle and shit.
But who's gonna pay up when they learn we can't even protect one of our own
as she walks home from work?
So what do you want us to do?
Teach these boys-
Yeah, I would do anything for Sarah.
I would do anything for Sarah.
Put them in their bodies.
Put them in wheelchairs.
Bust their faces up so bad even their mothers can't look at them without screaming.
We know where they're holed up.
My friend on the floor says we should start looking in the Chinatown.
Then Big Biff will know something.
Tommy, go to Vinnie, get us some gear.
Meet me at Biff's place.
Yeah, okay.
Leave these punks laying in the street.
I want everyone to know.
We do not allow mad dogs to run wild in our neighborhood.
You got it, boss.
Some of these sons of bitches could still be on our turf.
Go.
I'll check the neighborhood.
Make sure they're gone while you see Biff.
Good, huh?
I'm gonna take a selfie with an anime character filter.
Okay, so when you're done with Vinnie, come find me-
Uh, I don't know what that means.
Like a Snapchat thing?
I don't have Snapchat.
All right, talk to Vincenzo.
Like, get in the car, talk to Vincenzo.
You got a new weapon for me?
I can- give me like a grenade or something.
Hey, hey, here for some heaters, Tom.
Nah, I'm already going and healed.
All in me.
We gotta give a beating to some punks who've been on our turf.
I don't want to pull this and piss in our own street.
There's something to bust heads.
That's all we need.
Why is this guy the-
Sam turned over some guys' ware house.
1930s Q from James Bond.
Gotta grab that babe roof himself, the guy said.
I mean, that's horse shit, but they bust heads.
It's just baseball bats.
This is not something-
Oh, yeah, what an elaborate thing.
You could just go buy these at Walmart.
Why do we need a guy for this?
Just go get some baseball bats.
Anywhere in the fucking whole world.
We really need a guy for that?
1930s mafia James Bond.
Hey, here's a bat.
Oh, cool, this is a normal bat.
Does the top open and a little gun comes out,
just a little knife that shoots out and stabs somebody with a dart?
Nah, you just hit him in the fucking skull and they die.
Oh, okay, it's corked.
I can't drive past this.
I like the rain, though.
Nice touch.
Why even shape them into bats?
Just buy wood and give-
Just go to like Home Depot and buy a bunch of 2x4s,
cut them in half and use those instead.
It's probably cheaper.
Why does it have to be a bat?
It does the same thing.
It's a piece of wood that's heavy you hit somebody with.
Break?
Well, bat would break, too, wouldn't it?
All right, Polly, what are we doing?
I want to get my bat.
Follow Polly to Biff's pawn shop.
I gotta keep following Polly.
There's a bear in here.
Name Billy.
Pals with a prissy chump and a boozer with a bald head.
Right, right, I know them.
They're set up in the old service station in a block over.
They hock some gear every-
I want to- I would like to walk.
...small time.
Here to come to you, Biff.
You're good with small time.
Out the bed, cross the street.
You'll find them there.
Thanks.
See you around.
Hey, Polly, about that dough?
Axe is waiting for my guy to come through.
Okay.
Next week, just sit tight.
I feel like I'm having deja vu.
I really am.
This is like mission four in a row, besides the racing one,
where Q gives you a baseball bat,
and you've walked into a store with it.
But I don't even use it.
Let me go back to the car racing.
No, I'm not doing that.
I already beat it.
It was really hard.
But I did it, though.
All we gotta do is find the other guys in Chinatown who look like we do.
There it is.
There's what?
A.S.T.A.T.I.A.N.?
It's sub one hour?
Yeah, it's true.
Can we at least run?
This game is really fun and it's really cool,
but they really do like to slow down to L.A. Noire levels
in some of these missions.
Kick the door.
Tell me a nicest A.S.T. I've ever seen in my life.
Synchronized cigarettes is what I was gonna say.
It's a Marvel movie?
This guy's got a bat, too.
Captain America.
They are doing the Marvel movie one, two, three sequence.
Punch, block, punch, punch.
Block with one arm.
Punch with left arm.
Block, punch.
Into the stomach.
Into the chest.
Into the head.
One at a time.
Yeah, it always makes this really crazy sound.
Like this, like, when they punch.
It's like, oh, wait, I have to run around.
Let's go this way.
Jump over it.
What?
Oh, shit.
Oh, that guy's on fire.
I didn't even do this.
I feel like I didn't do anything.
I keep shooting this guy in the ass.
Is he dead?
What?
That was right in the fucking head.
We're good.
I have two bullets left.
Oh, it's not on easy.
This is on classic mode.
The health chair.
Wait, who's who?
Who's who?
Was that guy a friend?
I don't know.
Is this a bad guy?
I think we did it.
Is this hot?
Can I go in here?
He's not good either.
It's okay.
We both got surprised.
He's the one that opened the door.
How is he so surprised to see me?
Hands up.
Catch up to Billy.
Oh, shit.
Fucking whack-a-mole.
He dropped it.
Nice throw.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
I get him.
One more guy.
Where is he?
Who's shooting?
You're aiming the gun at me.
On me.
Look out.
What?
Stupid idea.
Very stupid.
Completely out of your element there, man.
You can run straight at me with a gun.
Random crit?
Oh, not this shit.
Don't let the punks escape.
Sure, I'll get it.
I have 21 shots.
That's not a whole lot of ammo.
It's raining too.
I got to be careful.
Oh, boy.
Oh, look at...
Shit.
Road is so slippery.
No, I'm going to lose him.
No, I'm okay.
We could have just chased him on foot
and would have been better.
At least we could have snuck down alleyways.
How did he pass the racing mission?
That was pretty tough.
Took me a while.
I really zeroed in though on the menu
when I made it easy on dude.
Seriously.
Jesus.
Oh, it's all right.
We got Luigi.
This is a bit...
They're going to wake up with guns.
Through the game.
That car is mangled.
What did they crash into?
We weren't going that fast.
Ah, shit.
He disconnected.
I'll wait.
He might come back.
Game's fucking multiplayer sucks, Tommy.
I swear to God.
Where to get used to it?
He was in the pause menu setting it to easy.
That's pretty good.
That's really good.
Simple straight.
Nice.
Very nice.
I can't afford this life no more.
Just getting lucky.
I'll give you a chance to win your money back.
You want in, boss?
We have business to discuss, Paulie.
We're in it now, boys.
One of our associates at the court
in this office sent his over.
Corpse's name is Joe Ortiz.
You recognize him?
Sure.
That's one of the punks we ran out of the neighborhood.
Now we got the bullet in the back of his head?
He did it.
Jimmy found it.
Well, the cops ought to thank us.
We did him a favor.
The guy was a rapist, boss.
Yeah?
Well, he was also a city councilor's son.
You want to drive a politician into Marella's arms?
There's no better way than killing off his family.
That gets worse.
You left another guy in the wreck?
In any piece of media, is there ever a senator's son
that's not a bad guy?
If you're going to do a job, do it right.
He made it?
Yes.
He spent the week in Santa Mary's, but...
You killed that guy.
He was a senator's son.
Can he point a finger at either of you?
He was a murderer, rapist, killer, drug addict,
and he like beat up dogs for fun.
Look, Senator's son, by the way.
Galati's funeral's today at St. Michael's.
Sam, you're going to attend.
Sit in the back and try to spot the lucky bastard.
How will I recognize him?
He'll be the one who just crawled away from a car wreck.
His arm is broken.
Look for a sling.
Sam's going to need a little distraction
if he's going to clean up your mess.
He's sending Tommy to dip his wick?
It's a brothel?
A gentleman's club, just down the street from St. Michael's.
Madonna's invested a lot of money in it over the years.
So are me and Sam.
Sam, regardless, the owner has suddenly decided
to do business with Morello instead of us.
You want me to go remind him of his obligations?
Yes, then blow the place up.
What?
Morello wants to take businesses away from us?
He'll inherit craters.
Look, Tom, we can't send Paulie and Sam since all the ladies know them already.
Are we trying to not have so much heat put on us?
But you can walk right in.
Okay.
What about the manager?
Like I could syringe somebody.
If any of the horse see it, well, it'll be a warning.
Once he's out of the way, head to his office on the top floor.
Grab any documents and money you find there and place the explosives.
Vincenza will see that you have what you need.
And you think the blast will be big enough to give me cover?
Yeah, but be smart.
Only take a shot if you know you won't get made.
Tommy, one more thing.
One of the girls is passing Morello information about our operations.
Before you blow the place, you'll need to take care of her, too.
You want Tommy to kill a twist?
Come on, Frank.
It's just bad luck this falls to Tom.
But we gotta protect the family.
Her name is Michelle.
Wait, I have to-
She's usually working one of the upper rooms.
Gonna kill some lady?
Her photo is in the folder.
You boys clearing everything?
Yeah.
Tom.
Pay attention.
I got it, boss.
Then get it done.
What a reaction to have a thing that you're watching.
Do I have to kill some lady?
Yeah, man.
You probably should already know why and who that is.
And it's not just some lady you're killing.
What are you talking about, dude?
Are you even watching?
Am I playing, like, Candy Crush on my phone during every cutscene?
Sometimes it feels like that.
But I'm not, though.
I'm just staring blankly into, like, the colors.
Okay, what do you got for me, Q?
Thank you.
Not that special, just electrical tape and dynamite.
Thanks, Q.
Uh-oh, we're gonna get some exposition.
Hey, don't kill her.
Give it to her and make sure she gets far away.
A hundred bucks.
Okay, sir.
I'll see what I can do.
A hundred dollars in 1930 was, like, ten grand.
That's a lot of money.
This show, she's the one from the racetrack, right?
Tom, that was the last time we're ever gonna talk about her.
Ever.
I told you.
We won't tell the Don about that one.
Uh, hey, uh, Polly, was that her?
Hope not.
Oh, yeah.
Tom, that was the last time we were gonna talk about her.
I told you what I had to ask and you listened.
You gotta leave it there.
Okay.
Oops.
Okay, we're fine.
Keep your head when you get into the hotel.
Find your mark and don't act suspicious.
Is that for the gunshot?
One hundred was about 1.2k.
That's a lot of money.
You say about it.
If the bomb goes off, I'll do my thing.
Got it.
What's with you today, Tom?
What kind of world is it?
I want to ride a motorcycle.
You get sent to a cat house.
Well, I have to clean up.
Shit, wrong button.
Isn't that a cop right there?
Anyway, what was I saying?
Oh, yeah.
What kind of world is it that when you screw up, you get sent to a cat house?
Well, I have to clean up your mess at a funeral.
You see the justice in that?
I see you.
Unhinged.
I was just trying to get the fuck out of the way.
Just try to finish your job this time.
Come on.
Are we going to get everybody standing up on the high ground here?
What?
In GTA, you never ran over a pedestrian before?
Of course not.
I stopped at every red light and I used my turn signal.
It's the funerals, Tom.
That's all it ever.
Not me.
No, of course not.
Anyone ever wants to do is point guns at the family and shoot.
In point, there were so many funerals.
I actually do.
That's how you make GTA, like, a 500-hour game.
That's a shame.
Seen as you're always dressed for the occasion.
Great gag, Tom.
Write that one down.
Thanks.
I'll do that.
Say that in court, German.
Here's your stuff.
But stand up and be like, what?
You're never in GTA.
You're in the family.
Good luck.
You too.
Yeah, I would be my own defense.
Your Honor, in Grand Theft Auto, you can run over people.
You never done that before, Judge?
You never ran over an old lady in the crosswalk in GTA?
Maybe we'd get flustered.
But well, case dismissed.
Please.
OK.
I didn't say I didn't do it.
See?
It was not necessary.
I didn't have to do it.
There was no reason to do that.
I was trying to get out of the way.
Enter the hotel.
I have a bomb, don't I?
Oh, shit.
Do I have to get searched?
Send a message from Don Salieri.
Find Michelle.
Find the manager.
Know where I can find the manager?
I just watched the door, pal.
Nobody cares.
OK.
Find Michelle.
Hey, handsome.
You know where I can find Michelle?
And I got some business with your manager, too.
A girl?
I can help you with that.
Wait.
Hold on.
Somebody had a gun.
Get that away.
Oh, shit.
OK.
He's hidden.
Find Michelle.
Michelle.
Because you're not the dame I'm after.
No, Michelle.
I'm new here, baby.
I don't know a thing.
Why don't you just walk up to everybody and say, Michelle?
No, Michelle.
Yes?
Or just yell, Michelle.
Somebody's head's going to turn.
Yeah, what?
Hey, I need you.
I need to speak to Michelle.
We can just talk if you don't want anything else.
What's a handsome man like you doing in a place like this?
Looking for a girl named Michelle.
She's busy upstairs, but I need to...
That's all I needed to know?
Can I get a drink?
I need to talk to the manager.
Look at that droid.
...straight through the lab.
Yeah, I'll take a large espresso from the Golden R2-D2, please.
All right, let's just go upstairs and find Michelle.
You're looking for a good time in this way, sweetie.
Michelle?
Michelle.
Sure, y'all.
Come to my room and tell me all about it.
Uh, okay.
I just want to talk.
You know, I get to hear that a lot.
I bet you're not like all the other guys either, are you?
Nah, not really.
Okay, kill the manager in the lounge.
Why did this become Hitman?
What?
Whose room is this?
Hey, put you in your place.
You know Michelle.
She's in 208!
Get out!
Sorry for the intrusion.
It was that easy.
Okay, 208.
I don't even need you anymore.
Where's 208?
This is 101.
I don't even need to be in here.
What am I...
No, this lady's gonna poison me.
I'm gonna say she's gonna poison me.
I know it.
I guarantee this lady poisons me.
You're gonna poison me!
I know I'm gonna get poisoned, I swear to God.
Is this 208?
What's in here?
Everybody is a threat right now.
It doesn't matter.
People are gonna kill you.
They have guns.
They have knives.
I'm protecting myself.
Psycho.
See?
Everyone's a fucking threat.
Look at these threats.
I'm telling you.
Wait, who's who?
Wait, is this a bad guy?
Who's the bad guy?
I don't know.
I don't know which one was the bad guy.
I have no idea.
Okay, easy.
Do you know where Michelle is?
You're the bad guy on my chest.
All right, I need to go up.
Where's the staircase?
Why is nobody getting me in trouble for doing these crazy things?
2-0.
Where is it?
Bible?
No.
Shoes?
Car down there.
Can I change?
Oh, 2-0-2.
Wait, wait, wait.
What's this?
Yeah, 2-0-2.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Find Michelle on 2-0-8.
2-10.
Where's 2-0-8?
2-0-1.
2-0-9.
Okay.
2-0-8.
Oh, it's just on the...
Okay.
This is where I have to be.
Should I knock on the door?
You, Michelle.
What's it to you?
A fella named Sam is one of your regulars.
Maybe there's a lot of guys named Sam.
You know him.
Works for Don Celieri.
Maybe you got him talking about...
Excuse me.
Do you know where Michelle is?
Don Morello offered you some money to spill what you heard.
No.
Sam, trust me.
I don't say nothing.
He knows that.
Well, the Don's losing a lot of money because someone can't keep their mouth shut.
Hey.
I didn't kill everybody.
The first lady I thought was gonna...
The door was gonna close and she was gonna stab me or poison me or something.
Second room.
There's two guys in there.
One of them was beaten.
One of them I choked.
One of them.
Then I punched the other guy.
Because if you ever show your face in this town again,
they're gonna find you with two in the head.
Do you understand?
What about the security guard?
Yeah, that's true.
I can't, uh...
Get dressed and make tracks.
I have no excuse for the security guard.
I just kind of did it.
Just don't come back and we're square.
All right.
We're good.
Kill the manager in the lounge.
Killing everybody besides the manager in the lounge.
Don't I have a bomb?
Back downstairs.
Oh, it's okay.
Someone's just jumping on the bed.
Psycho.
All right.
Don't hurt anybody.
There he is.
All right.
How do I kill this guy?
I guess I just go walk up and put my hands on his neck.
But I don't think that's gonna work.
Can I talk to him?
No, this is gonna be some weird hitman thing to do with this.
I'm gonna drop a chandelier on him or something, right?
Poison?
Why do I think there's poison in this game?
It's not showing up at all.
Why did I think I was gonna get poisoned?
Like, here, have a drink.
And I was gonna die.
Why did I think that was gonna happen?
I actually just have to kill this guy, I guess.
Uh...
Oh, he'll go to the bathroom.
He's gonna go to the bathroom eventually.
And we'll just chuck him out of the bathroom.
Shoot him.
No, I don't want to shoot him.
Why is there blood all over the place?
Oh, it's me.
He's not gonna move.
Just shoot him.
Everyone called me a psycho when I punched that lady
and when I choked that guy to death.
I don't want to be the psycho anymore.
I want to do the correct way.
Run, run, run, run, run!
Run!
I don't know if that's a good...
I don't know if that's a bad guy or not.
Reach the manager's office?
What?
What's the go...
I don't want to be the psycho.
I wasn't.
I was running away.
I did what I had to do and I ran away.
What is happening?
Oh.
I don't want to...
Um...
Don't listen to chat.
Just go and reach the manager's office.
This guy...
Okay, like the concierge just ran in with a shotgun.
And you're telling me that not everybody here was a threat?
That was the bellhop.
I gotta go, uh, game mode for this one.
All right, reach the manager's office.
Let's go.
I'll take the shotgun.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right, let's go reload this.
Oh, shit.
Where is he?
Oh, give me the...
Oh, yourself.
Neither one of us knows who we're aiming at right now.
Is there a heal?
There's no heal box, is there?
Where?
Oh, back in the kitchen?
I don't...
Where?
Sick.
Thank you.
There we go.
Now I got tons of ammo for the shotgun.
We're good.
I just like skimmed him.
Nobody left, all right?
I have no idea.
Oh, my goodness.
Everybody's a threat.
Even the naked guy.
Whoa!
Where is he?
Any health in here?
Oh, shit.
Remember, this is not a kill everyone scenario.
This is a get out scenario.
All right, that's cool.
Just run.
Your game reward is causing lag.
Where's his office?
I was right there.
Shit.
Oh, god damn it.
That was so close.
It actually worked for a minute.
Why are you playing with a controller?
Because my game reward's gonna get in the way
and it's gonna hurt if I press W.
Because when I press W,
it's gonna scrape against the E key.
I mean, the mouse.
The mouse...
No, it's not even...
That's a wrong hand.
I got a checkpoint, though.
Somebody else shot him in the head, not me.
Oh, shit.
Into the hallway, that's it.
I'm just gonna get to the end of the hallway.
I was doing like covering fire.
There's another guy right there.
Jesus, that's why I don't want to run.
Did I shoot myself in the side of the head?
Did I lean forward to peek and then shoot myself?
Dude, give me a fucking break.
Where is this guy shooting at me from?
Shit, that was a loud yell.
He did not fucking hit me.
I'm just saying bullshit.
I had explosive right here.
Ready?
Fucking come on.
It's lower the difficulty to regular.
Don't be on classic mode.
I'm not gonna put it...
No, I can't do that more than once.
You know why I hate video games so much?
Because you have to put your mouse sensitivity
down to like 0.5 in every fucking video game.
Do you guys realize?
Do you guys notice that?
Who the fuck play...
Why would they ever have a like 5.0 sensitivity?
What's the point of having that even be an option?
It's a little too low.
Why does this feel so laggy?
I think it's because it is.
All right, the same stupid...
Get up.
It's gonna explode.
Just get rid of it first.
Someone's gonna shoot that.
It's gonna kill me.
That's just ducking in plain sight.
The controller was sitting on my lap.
I put it on the desk.
Turn on aim assist.
Wouldn't I want to turn it off?
Is it like pulling me over to other enemies?
Fucking die!
Game's at...
It's bugged.
Turn on v-sync.
I don't think...
Is that real?
I don't think that's real.
You're alive?
You gotta turn vegetation on...
All right, this...
Same fucking doorway.
There he is.
You can't be serious.
Same guy.
He shoots me in the head every time.
Why is this guy so impossible for me to kill?
I shot him right in the neck.
What was that?
Oh my fucking God.
Why is it like this?
Here's the gamer instinct.
Oh my fucking God.
Are you...
Are you kidding me?
Because I replaced my gun in the beginning of the level
when I choked out the fucking bellhop
and I took the shitty gun.
Really?
No.
All right, I gotta replace this gun.
This thing sucks.
I'm like shooting BBs at these guys.
Give me your gun.
What do you have?
Thank you.
Oh my God.
What the hell was I thinking?
What was I doing?
What was wrong with me?
What are you doing?
The guy in the hat.
This guy's in my head.
This dude is in my head so bad.
He really is.
Yeah.
I shot that guy.
Okay.
I don't even know what happened.
That guy exploded.
No, don't.
Use your grenades.
I don't have any grenades.
Get up.
Shit.
Come on, dude.
I don't have any bullets.
Oh shit.
Give me the controller.
I don't know what to do.
Do I have anything else?
Give me another gun.
Give me a gun.
No.
There's one more guy.
There's no bullets in any of these guns.
What are you doing?
I don't even know where he is.
Where is he?
Holy shit.
What an idiot.
Get the safe.
I'll take this one for sure.
This is a sawed-off shotgun.
Why does this guy have a spotlight all over him?
Can I get him out?
Clown?
No, I'm not going to kill this guy.
Okay?
I am not going to do that.
I've done enough.
I've done enough like punching and fighting and shooting and stuff.
I'm not going to do it.
Not going to happen.
Not right now.
Shoot the chair.
All right.
I might shoot the chair.
Can I shoot the chair without killing him?
You're going to blow up the what?
Oh wait.
This guy's...
Yeah.
How do I...
I'm going to blow up the whole building?
Take money and documents.
Okay?
Get that document.
Money.
Documents.
Land the bomb.
Does it matter where?
That clown guy really is just kind of still in there.
He's just tied up.
Okay.
I blew out an office.
I didn't blow up the building.
Oh, we're good.
Get to the roof?
Are those police shooting at me?
Why does it look like my body was on backwards?
Can I find a way up to the roof?
All right.
But where are they actually shooting?
I don't think I can get rid of these guys.
I have a shotgun that I'm going to shoot into windows
that are like 500 feet away from me.
Restart chapter.
Oh my goodness.
I am going to have to just run.
Slow down.
Go, go, go, go, go.
What difficulty is this?
Classic.
Hide and just heal.
Do I have any other guns?
I don't.
I just have a stupid shotgun, man.
I can get them.
Oh, shit.
I get them?
I got them.
Go, go!
While they're distracted while they're shot.
I'm in trouble now.
Why did I switch to the dumb shotgun?
Because it was on the ground
and I thought it might be fun to use.
All right.
What am I going to do?
I think I have to kill these guys.
Are they gone?
I saw the guy in the eye.
That guy doesn't have an eye.
All right.
One's dead.
One of them is dead.
This is my actual opportunity here.
I'm going to wait till they reload
and then I'm going to run.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Okay.
Ready?
Let's count.
Three, five, six.
Two, three, four.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Five, six.
And one, two.
Come on.
I'm not going to fire.
Okay.
I'm all right.
Nobody right here.
I don't have a gun.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There's a guy.
There's a guy with a gun
but this is a health pack right here.
Move these boxes.
Get out of my way, please.
Can I zip line?
There's a dude right here with a gun.
I didn't.
Holy shit.
I'm okay.
I got one more bullet.
Which guns?
I need that gun.
Where is it?
All right.
Well, I'm headshotting his hand.
Headshotting the fence.
Kind of, but not really.
Don't do it.
It's not worth it.
Hide, hide, hide, hide.
Dude, what the fuck are you doing?
It's not worth it.
Give me your gun.
I want ammo.
Shit.
Guy right here.
Oh, okay.
We're safe.
Spike's on there.
I can't jump over that.
I thought it was a jump.
Cool.
All right.
So far so good.
All joke?
No.
I don't think you can fall off.
Even if you tried.
Try, try, try.
I can't.
I can't even fall down.
How far we've fallen.
We can find redemption in death.
This is just going on now.
Okay.
Now, William.
He was a sinner, yes.
But he was also a loving son.
Oilus from Mafia.
You're here right now.
In real time.
I just wanted to pay my respects.
Watching it.
Billy.
I never said this.
But I consider you my brother.
I can't even count all the times.
You saved my ass from a beating.
I don't know how I'm gonna-
Sweet.
Wait.
That's the guy.
That's the guy who killed Billy.
No.
Funeral?
Excuse me.
I'm telling you.
Everybody's a threat.
Everyone just has a gun.
This whole-
Everybody just stood up with machine guns and shit.
Kill Johnny.
Johnny?
That's Johnny over there.
All right.
Got him.
Give me that.
Wait.
Pocket revolver.
That sounds cool.
No.
That thing sucks.
The guy threw a molotov in a church.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
I'm sorry.
Everybody was doing it.
So I thought I would do it too.
Everyone was doing it.
I'm just such a creature of being able to be easily visually manipulated.
This is what was Billy involved in.
Get over here now.
Playing a game with a controller without any aim assist on.
That's another issue, I think.
Damn.
I'm just realizing that right now.
Take care of this guy, Fart.
That was sick.
Warming him up?
Who?
Oh, he's right there.
Why did the game just slow mo for that guy?
See?
I told you he's doing it.
Look it.
I have enough bullets.
What's going on?
Is my computer overheating?
Oh!
Fuck!
The shotgun was on the ground.
He punched me over the thing twice and I got stun locked.
Who's next?
Come on.
Yeah, cool.
Is that just Fortnite, that guy?
I think I got him.
Is that him?
What's with the gun, man?
Over here, right?
There he is.
Okay.
Let's go.
Leave vault on keyboard.
Hand grenade.
Holy hand grenade.
What?
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Give me this.
This is the way this city works.
It's out of ammo?
I don't know how to punch.
How do you punch?
I don't know how to punch on the fucking keyboard.
I'm swapping between the two.
Is left alt?
Stop reloading.
You're wasting your ammo.
Oh my god.
That guy got shot like seven fucking times.
You did not get that off.
You motherfucker.
I can't believe you got it.
Stop fucking.
It's such a habit.
I'm sorry, it is.
This is the way this city works.
Oh, there's a machine gun right here.
Give me that thing.
Where is he?
That's it, right?
Okay, let's go.
Please, I'm enjoying this.
What have you done?
Murder in the house of God.
These men were criminals, father.
Thieves, rapists, killers.
And God would have embraced them if they'd asked for forgiveness.
That's hard.
Now, which one of these men might have sought redemption by working with the poor?
Which one might have saved just one life?
None of us, father.
You bastard.
Wait, didn't...
Do you have any confessions to make?
You better do it quick.
No more bloodshed, please.
I'm gonna just fill him with like eight rounds of...
I shot him with a machine gun, didn't I?
Consider this an act of divine retribution.
That make us even.
Sure. For now.
For your trouble, father.
Still alive.
I don't want your blood money.
You took theirs.
Not a lot of difference from where I'm standing.
There should be enough dough to patch up the bullet holes.
And keep you quiet.
When the cops come, you tell them the gunman who did this had East Coast accents.
We're really doing this to a priest?
I've been out of town, right?
I won't lie, but I won't say anything at all.
Good. Be ashamed if we had to come back here.
Am I gonna the priest?
Were you?
As soon as I walked in the church, the crew recognized me.
Followed me straight back out.
Holy shit, man.
My spot.
I'm not sure.
I'm just...
Where's the car?
I gotta get in the car.
Oh, shit.
Okay, it's all right.
Stay here.
Get over here and don't move.
No, no, no, no, no, no, Polly.
What are you doing?
Stay back here, Polly.
We need a car.
Can you steal a car?
No, that's illegal.
How you doing?
All right, get out.
I'm getting...
Oh, there's a million police right there.
We did that real close.
Returning to the scene of the crime.
Yes, there was a stolen car.
You're right.
Well, today didn't turn out like I expected.
Oh, they know it's me?
I don't think they know it's me.
Whatever you did at the cat house got the cops plenty pissed.
Yeah, it was messy, but I got everything done.
Everything?
Yeah, everything.
Right into the car.
Right into the train.
Shit, I want a bike so bad.
We both ride the bike at the same time.
They giving up yet?
I don't think so.
They must have called out every cop in the city.
Move.
I'm doing it.
All right, get out of the car up here.
Into the park.
Get out, get out.
Run, run, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Get this way over here.
He's behind the newspaper.
No, I can't...
I can't just punch people.
I already punched my quota of ladies in the face today, okay?
I'm not adding to it.
I want a motorcycle though.
He has a quota.
No, I'm just saying...
I just want to go, all right, let's punch this person.
Let's punch this lady.
Let's punch this guy.
Is he a bike?
I've never seen anyone do the mission like this.
Did he shoot someone?
All right, come here.
It can't be reported stolen if nobody knows it was stolen.
All right, we're in the clear.
Bike, bike, bike.
It's all right, it's okay.
If you see another one, let me know though.
Can you get on?
Oh, he can't.
Oh my god, Sam, please hurry up.
That's annoying.
Really?
You can't get on the bike.
You think we're cute?
Yeah, sure.
All right, we got no police on us.
We're good to go.
Let's go straight on.
It's time for a pee break, by the way.
I'm gonna get some water too.
And think about all the crimes I've committed in this game.
Update the driver.
I don't think it's even necessary anymore.
Yeah, ever since I turned up the graphics, it's been fine.
All right, let me get some water.
I'll be back.
After this cutsie.
In a fit of paranoid rage, I thought this lady was gonna poison me.
She just wanted to show me where her friend Michelle was.
And I punched her in the face eight times.
It's a strange thing.
Nothing really came of it all.
I always figured Celia repaid off someone somewhere,
because it wasn't even in her papers.
Which store can you find this game?
Thanks.
Uh, Wal-Mart.
Target.
Amazon.
And Frank caught wind that Morello was helping Galati get re-elected,
hoping he'd go after the Don.
Well, I covered some account books for Morello's offices.
Sturdy Tree was a pretty good year for him.
Best didn't know we were bleeding out before we did.
While we were busy keeping our heads down, he started moving in on our rackets.
Quiet at first, a few trucks go missing.
Uh, Top Burner has one too many high balls, drives off-
Did anybody in the 30s eat food?
We haven't seen anybody eat any food.
We've seen them drink a shitload of coffee and cigarettes.
I think maybe Polly smelled something.
Oh, there's a Morello circling.
No one's eating.
Who was still making good money.
And with the Don worried about keeping the heat off,
we didn't have much to do.
Except drink, have a few laughs.
Every time I went into Salieri's, there was Sarah.
They literally just ordered their food.
They're not going to eat it on camera though.
Frank, Galati, the Don's consecutive.
Yeah, that's right.
He set me straight.
He set us all straight.
There's a lot of buzz around town about you guys.
Yeah, we got into a little scrap last night.
It's no big deal.
I don't care about the bar fight, Tom.
I care how it looks when you walk into a club
and buy everyone around.
We got to do something with our dough.
Then blow it at the track on Sunday.
All right, food recommendation time.
You want me to become one of those Wall Street boys?
Don't sass me, Tommy.
I'm trying to teach you the ropes
so you don't get strangled by them.
You ever have a dog, Tom?
Stonks?
Sure.
A little mud when I was a kid.
I don't think I can eat those.
When I was eight or nine, before I came over from the Ceasley,
I had this beautiful, skinny Cernico de Letna.
Like a little gray out.
Fastest dog you've ever seen.
That's how I met the Don.
We started setting up races together.
Pedding on her with coins and rifle shells.
There wasn't another dog that could catch her.
She never lost until the day she did.
We were only out of pocket knife, but
I never saw the Don so angry.
She got old on you?
No.
Pregnant.
She went into heat, got out of the yard,
and every dog in town had a turn.
You're like that dog, Tommy.
Every time you flash your money around,
you're a bitch in heat,
and everyone in that club is now looking to fuck you.
I think there's a
and once you get fucked
from where you could describe this to be.
You're no good to us.
What the hell are you doing?
You understand.
You made your point.
Good.
But you need to think about your career here.
Look, police at his ceiling.
It's a germatyr analogy.
He's not smart enough to run anything.
Sam is loyal, but he has no vision.
But you, Tommy, you could run this town someday.
I'm considerably more hateful than mine.
So what happened to the dog?
Don't tell me you're like Saturn.
Out in the atmosphere.
And me, I'm like Jupiter.
And the dawn, the dawn is like the galaxy.
You're not going to be careful.
You don't go too many revolutions around that sun.
You can let me off here.
That would be kind of...
Yeah, I could see that.
That's kind of what I would do.
Give Sarah my best, Tommy.
Jeremy, you just missed the moral of the whole story.
Don't show, don't flash around your money
and don't act like an asshole.
I think that's pretty much the whole story, right?
Back then, everything went through Frank.
The plans, the orders, the money.
You could get the call day or night.
Frank says to wait for him in the garage out in the back.
You got the job, I think.
Thanks, Luigi.
Sarah's cooking.
She's bringing something over.
Don't put the game on easy.
She's a good girl.
Right.
Pretty good moral of the story, I think.
All right, where's Frank?
In the day.
About to pee?
Oh, right, it's all right.
Oh, this has been kind of one big, long cutscene.
Thanks for waiting, Tom.
The Don and I had to go over last month's numbers again.
Sure.
So what's the job?
I want you to help Sam and Paulie with the shipment
we've got coming in tonight.
The good stuff?
Straight from Canada.
Where do you need me?
Sam's going to meet our friends from the north
at the farm outside of town.
Paulie will oversee the trucks
bringing the shipment into the city.
But I want you to go with him.
Oh, shit, this isn't an open world game.
Make sure it all goes smoothly.
Okay.
Get the car from Ralphie.
Meet Paulie at the warehouse.
What does it feel like it is?
In case you run into any trouble.
Sure, Frank.
No problem.
Good.
Now bring the Canadian home safe, Tommy.
There is already a case you're marked for the Don.
You can do free roaming?
All right, let's go.
All right, it's not let's pee.
We'll be back in like two minutes.
Beer B?
Okay, hello.
The order is yours if you want it, Tommy.
Thanks.
Going in.
Welcome back.
All right, I was looking at chat.
Drive to Sellier's warehouse.
All right, let's move on.
Drivers, I don't need them.
I'm good.
I need to make a turn here.
Holy shit.
I am intact.
Cool.
I'm not going to lead the cops to the job.
There's a guy on foot chasing me.
That's it.
I'm going to be fine.
Through here.
Mm-hmm.
Let's drive.
Yeah, I'm going.
Shit, that's a lot of noise.
Just hang out for a sec.
Drive slowly to the next checkpoint.
We're good to go.
Hop right in front of me.
All right, we're good.
I want to drive a motorcycle around.
Ask and you shall receive.
He hates the game.
We're getting that idea.
All right, now this is very slippery, but it's pretty cool.
I do wheelie.
I can ride like Batman.
That's cool.
And three, two, one.
Fly over the handlebars.
Oh no, it's the concussion sound again.
Fuck you.
Can't jump over that.
Can you see me?
Okay, now what?
Is he going to arrest me?
He's looking for me.
Wait, what was that sound?
I heard a vooga and then it exploded.
Okay, which way do I need to go?
Back to the bike.
The bike is right here.
How did I do that?
I don't because I was driving too fast with the motorcycle.
I crashed into somebody and then the guy chased me into the bush
and then I got shot by five cops.
Do I actually?
Okay, I'm not fucking around.
Get me the fuck out of this.
Who cares about the bike?
The bike is stupid.
You just crash and die.
The motorcycle doesn't go faster or anything.
It's just more vulnerable.
But it looks cool.
It does.
You're right.
Okay, and back to fast.
This guy's just in the way.
All right, no cops.
We're good.
Um, somebody said look at that link.
Hold on.
Is that the water doing that or is it me being an idiot?
Cops.
Why is everybody standing over here?
Because I looked back at the car accident?
What?
You nearly hit a guy.
I did not.
We're safe down here.
Okay, we're good.
Uh, he's coming back this way.
Oh shit, it's this dock.
I gotta go over the bridge.
No, did I just get the cops called on me again?
Because I fucking beeped at her.
Just take the ticket out.
No, but yeah, I mean there's no in-game currency.
That doesn't really do anything.
It's not a problem.
I don't think it takes money out of your account in the game.
All right, I'll just go turn myself in right here, right?
There's like three cops here.
Here, I will pay.
I will pay.
I'm paying my Skyrim debt.
What just happened?
Okay, we're good.
Don't tell me I could get you in trouble for that.
Oh, and uh, officers, excuse me.
Actually, were you just beeping at a pedestrian in the crosswalk?
I was crossing the road and you beeped at me.
I thought you both arrest yourselves.
Was I a pedestrian in the road and did you beep at me and scare me?
Why are they speed matching me?
I don't like this.
Seriously.
Oh, I can't play these games.
I like, I just can't.
My attention is so bad.
Like I look at chat and just read what you guys are saying.
I'm gonna straight away.
It's just like, I'm just, I'm looking over and just, oh, hey, hi guys.
Oh, fucking God.
Just get there for the love of God.
Holy shit, man.
Okay.
It's not Grand Theft Auto.
It's not GTA.
Stop playing the game like it's GTA.
You can't just like smash into stuff and just drive over people and drive into things.
There are rules.
There are laws in this game.
Lighting is pretty good.
Yeah, it is.
I mean, the game looks great.
It really does.
Ride the bank.
Okay.
Here we are.
Same exact spot.
Graphics are pretty good for the 1930s.
Yeah, they are.
This game is ridiculous.
Illegal speeder.
Sharing the road with this thing would be so hard.
I'm glad I don't live in a city that has one of those.
That would freak me out.
Normal driving RP or riot.
Fine.
Raining out today.
I thought I was going to break.
I thought I was going to crash through it.
Joke ruined.
Oh, well.
What is this place?
This place is across the whole game.
All right.
Take off the limiter.
Overclock the car, please.
All right.
Now it's back on.
When you get a straightaway like that, you got to go for it.
If there's no cops around, you're fine.
In front of that car, it looked like it was made of tin foil.
You know this place?
Oh, yeah.
We've done a few pickups at the farm before.
Don't worry.
There ain't nothing but cow shit and shine out here.
It's going to be an easy few clams.
We'll load up the trucks, we'll come straight back.
Yeah, let's make it quick.
I got someplace to be.
The skin is really good in this game.
You can see like all the random little splotchies.
How do you even do that?
Detecting the girl's virginity one day and taking it to the next.
How do you do next day after a shave looking?
Come on.
It's crazy.
I'm just kidding.
She's a good girl.
You settle down, she'll straighten you right out.
You're going home to a couch.
Yeah, the bumps.
The bumps look really good.
Now I wonder what kind of story she could tell about her old man though.
Cold killer back in the day.
Where are we driving?
Are we driving off the road?
Where are we?
You know, she's been helping out behind a bar
since she was a kid.
We're driving under water?
I bet she's seen and heard a few things.
Probably knows more about our business than we do.
She knows enough.
Where's this car?
How many questions?
That's good.
She won't ever make a liar out of you.
Christ.
Go to Mario just for that.
Watching a movie would be hell with you.
Damn it.
No, no, I put tape over my mouth.
Sam should be waiting here but I don't see him.
Something smells off.
Don't let your pecker get all shriveled up.
Probably just trying to get out of the rain.
The only thing you hear is
So if you turn the volume up loud enough
to like maybe seven or eight on your TV
you won't even hear that.
Okay, let's go find him.
Bastard.
It's just three sheets
and I'm wrecking a new suit for nothing.
I swear I'm gonna kill him.
Here.
Just in case Frank was right.
I'm gonna go grab them boys.
Get them sorted out.
You go ahead see what's what.
We'll catch up with you.
Jot gun.
Search for clues.
So the last mission was hit man.
Now this is like a detective game.
This game is everything, huh?
One quarter out of work.
Find Sam.
I'll be sneaking around.
Somebody here.
What is this?
A little target.
Oh.
Arlo Falcone.
Oh, it's a collectible card.
Okay, cool.
Investigate the truck.
Somebody in there.
Are they sleeping?
Hey buddy.
He's dead.
Jesus.
Drop your weapon.
You first.
We don't have time for this.
Sorry pal.
Guess we're doing this the hard way.
Okay then.
All right well he got one for me.
I didn't even have to aim.
I'm glad.
Into the house.
I shot the two glass bottles.
More than I could shoot the guy.
I'm getting collapsed on.
Oh come on.
I shot three times.
Right in the chest.
Put up the keyboard.
All right keyboard time.
Keyboard mode.
Yep.
Doesn't really help now does it?
Okay.
Is there ammo in here?
Yes there is.
Meet at the usual place.
Whatever that means.
It's a Wiimote?
Use a Wiimote.
You know I wish I could.
When I play games sometimes I go damn.
This would be so much better with a Wiimote.
Use a VR headset.
Hey glad you brought that up.
Tomorrow.
Going back to VR.
I'm gonna play multiplayer VR.
With some friends.
I leaked it already but I'm not gonna leak it anymore.
That's not gonna happen till late tomorrow night.
Very late.
8 am pacific is when that stream is gonna be a late one tomorrow.
All right let's go find Sam.
How much ammo?
Nah I'll keep the shotgun.
Any more ammo though?
I want a bunch of ammo for the shotgun.
Here we go.
Okay now I feel confident.
East coast?
Yeah that's gonna be 11 pm start east coast.
It's late.
The latest stream I've done in probably a year or two.
Should be a lot of fun though.
And that starts the beginning of a lot of VR.
FTK obviously is gonna be this weekend.
And tomorrow I'm gonna start the stream a little early tomorrow.
Yes so I can get VR set up and we're gonna talk about FTK.
Yes a little bit maybe like before maybe 20 minutes before everyone kind of shows up.
Because that's happening this weekend.
So holotov's over here for what?
Oh shit what the hell is this?
End of the stream voice?
Yeah probably.
It's getting to be that point.
I'll be back tomorrow though.
Tomorrow's gonna be high energy.
It's gonna be in VR.
Is that a bad guy?
Oh no.
Today was pretty high energy too.
The last few streams have been pretty high energy.
High energy?
Why can I not say that together?
Pretty much always high energy.
The only time I'm not high energy.
I think we found him.
All right we got him.
We found the bad guys.
Throw Molotov in here?
All right I'm gonna throw Molotov in there.
Nobody in here.
All right I got the back.
He's never gonna finish this game?
Um I don't know.
I might.
Once VR is set up it's not being teared down for a while.
I've got like a dozen VR games I have to play while that's set up.
He won't.
Yeah I you know let's just say I won't.
What?
That doesn't mean I'm not having fun.
Is that?
Oh shit that was I think that was one of our friends.
Well there he is.
Is he dead?
Gamer mode come on.
That guy's still on fire.
That's not a red barrel.
You guys can you just shoot him?
Get it off!
That lightning just distracted me.
Shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot him shoot this guy.
I'm fine.
What a grenade grenade grenade grenade grenade grenade grenade grenade.
I need another gun.
Did I pick up grenades?
No I didn't.
Shit okay I'm gonna go for it in one two press the wrong button.
You shoot me through the wood?
All right now I'm not gonna fuck around.
I'm just I'm not gonna fuck around.
Let's go.
Are you gonna call me a dead prick?
What aim?
The aim is unbelievable.
That landed right at my feet.
This is on easy?
No this is on like the realism game mode for some reason.
It's only easy when I want it to be.
Yeah that's right.
Where are you?
This is aiming oh okay.
Oh my god he's made it out of metal.
Chubby bunny.
I'm just gonna look like I had wisdom teeth surgery.
I should put him in.
Put a bunch of gauze.
Around my mouth.
Just kind of lean back and be like I just had true surgery.
You chubby bunny I will sub.
Welcome our newest subscriber next week.
We survived worse.
Wait were those two named characters or was those two just friends?
In quotes.
I don't have any ammo.
Oh my god.
Defend Sam.
Okay where are they?
Where are they?
Ow!
Can you move over the other way man?
Like can you just throw a molotov on keyboard?
T-R-Y-A-X-G?
I feel like I'm just playing Left 4 Dead.
Another game this game is.
Where are you?
Up the stairs.
Uh all right Daenerys Targaryen.
Oh no I'm realizing it now I'm on fire.
He was turned like cringing at that guy being on fire.
Oh it hurts.
All right I'm done.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Oh come on really man?
That was just somebody went into gmod and moved that face around.
That wasn't even me doing that.
I'm just gonna sit right here.
There you go.
Oh holy shit that guy's climbing the wall.
No.
Oh this is the best wooden fence ever.
Oh shit he's coming up here.
He's coming up he's coming up he's coming up to reload.
Hurry hurry hurry hurry.
Back on Sam.
Good Sam.
Nyaners.
Nyaners raid coming in.
Another huge raid.
This is like another monster raid.
This is a huge raid.
Another one.
Welcome guys.
We are playing mafia renewed edition.
Hope you had a good stream.
Nyaners.
Oh give oh go give these two people a follow by the way.
Nyaners and Kitboga please.
Right on time.
I can't.
Yeah Kitboga raided earlier too.
Oh no I have to do this.
All right we're going full gamer mode right now.
Check this out.
Why am I in permanent third person?
I don't know what I did.
How do I get this off?
Press X.
Check this out.
Silent.
Silent gamer mode.
What is happening with my gun?
Nobody cares about style points right now.
All right any more machine gun?
Yep get all the machine gun ammo.
What's that?
Card.
All right we're good.
2k viewers dropped.
Yeah that's all right we're all good.
We're gonna end soon anyways.
All right I get it back in gamer mode for a sec.
Absolute full blown gamer mode coming up.
I can't believe Jax ignored my gifted sub.
I'm sorry hold on.
Nice.
That it?
All right thank you to Tinfoilboy for the 15 community subs.
It's a lot of subs.
Mayo gave another five.
You guys just shower me with money.
Hopefully you think it's worth it.
Thanks guys seriously that's a lot of money.
Fucking massacre.
Thank you.
Sing the song.
Well he ain't any worse.
No.
I'll go get him.
Keep an eye out.
Mitchell thanks for the five subs Mitchell.
Thanks a lot.
We all know that German needs a shower right now.
I'm fairly clean right now.
I took a shower like six hours ago.
Seven hours ago.
I'm fine.
Okay we got more company.
Of course we do.
Jax mode three all right.
You wash behind your ears.
Yes.
When I shampoo I go behind both ears.
Like I did?
Is this car driving itself?
Here comes the armored truck.
I think that was just a guy on a motorcycle.
I don't think that was even a cop.
Tesla?
Tesla car?
You clean your...
Yes I do.
I clean my clothes.
I got him.
I don't know why I just read this.
I think I thought somebody just said centrist truck.
Like how what does it even mean?
Come on get the driver.
Driver driver get the driver.
What?
Okay it's all my the truck's already dead.
You died to centrist wheel.
Um where are they?
One down and there's one down.
The truck is about to explode.
Oh we're good.
Going to clear?
More.
That guy thinks he's he-man right now.
That cop couldn't even believe it himself.
Am I soft-locked?
Come on.
Did I not kill the guy behind there?
He's still there.
I think we're good.
No apparently not.
There's another one.
Okay armored truck versus bread van.
I wonder which one's gonna win.
Dude it's tires.
Shoot the gun.
It wants me to shoot the gun.
It kind of sounds like Barry from American Dad.
Steve's friend.
Holy shit.
Okay shoot just duck.
When they reload shoot it a little bit.
Duck shoot a little bit.
Duck shoot a little bit in the gun.
I know I know.
That's what I'm gonna get it.
Shoot the gun.
I know.
God take out the what?
The windshield?
Oh my god this is gonna be so hard to shoot the lights out.
Did I get it?
Yes.
Tommy take out the trash.
The trash?
Why are you saying it like that?
I just dropped him.
I'm playing like Blinko on the Price is Right.
I'm not even aiming.
This mission is really long.
Holy shit.
I feel like this guy would be dead by now.
Toilet bowl gaming five community subs.
Thanks a lot dude.
That's a pretty cool name.
I like that name.
I really do.
You didn't?
I did everything.
I want like five grand or I'm walking.
That was a five grand kind of play there.
All right.
That is where I'm going to end the stream tonight.
Thanks for watching everybody.
I will see you tomorrow for VR.
I think that's a good stopping point.
Sorry I put it on easy.
Sorry I punched that lady.
Sorry I shot that guy.
Sorry I strangled that guy.
Sorry I strangled the other guy.
Sorry I shot that other guy.
Sorry I ran that whole bunch of people over.
Please forgive me.
Actually kind of a big map.
No not forgiven.
I also blew up the clown too.
Oh well I didn't actually do that.
I think he was still alive.
Thank you everybody.
We'll see you soon.
Tomorrow at 8 p.m. Pacific.
I'm going to be playing VR.
I'm going to be setting it up and doing that all over again.
Half-Life Alex will be shortly after that.
Probably next week.
And after that maybe I will come back.
At this point probably like another six to seven hours left in the game.
Maybe one more full stream of this game.
Maybe.
It depends.
I'm looking forward to Half-Life Alex.
It'll be a lot of fun.
But thank you everybody.
Thanks all the subs.
There was a lot of gifted subs today.
A couple of huge raids too.
Kind of one hour or two hours apart from each other.
So thank you Kitboga.
Thank you Nyaners.
Still going to be looking forward to that Mr. Slime avatar stream.
You know it's coming.
Thank you though.
So I...
Where am I going to put you guys today?
Let's see.
Let me see who's live.
Let me see.
Who do I want to raid today?
Raid Mr. Slime.
Raid the debate.
No I'm not doing that.
Critical is critical.
Yeah critical is online right?
What's critical doing?
Raid the debate.
I'm not going to raid the debate.
That's a mistake.
What's critical doing right now?
Oh shit.
Hey this game...
This game...
Maybe you might see it real soon in virtual reality.
He's playing Phasmophobia.
Which is exactly what we're going to play tomorrow.
And when I say we I mean some mystery streamers.
Go tell Critical hello.
I'll see you guys soon.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
See you tomorrow night.
The mystery yeah.
Good night guys.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you again for watching.
Well that was just me linking his channel.
Let's actually raid his channel.
See you later.