He's one minute early. Well, I'm not early. As long as it's in this window. I could have started
about 30 or 40 minutes ago, but I was too busy shit posting in chat. It took too long. I'm sitting
there writing all kinds of dumb shit for 30 minutes. So I... I could have started. I just
had to get coffee and take out auto and stuff. So I do that to... okay, those of you that are
like, oh wait, he's been... why, you know, why doesn't the stream start earlier than that? I
mean it's like four. It's between three and four. What the heck, man? No, I... it's because I am here.
I just like to be a chatter sometimes for like a half an hour. It's kind of fun.
I do it all the time. What the heck, man? It's because it's different. I can like hunch over
and be like... it's a little different. Stalling? Oh, you're gonna get a big stall today because
I've got a fucking story for you. I'm gonna wait till people get the tweet and stuff because
this is a big story. Big one. Stalling. Hey, you know, is it a stall? If it's... if you... okay.
If the car stalls out, I understand. But I'm coasting right now. I'm idling. Stalled means
the engine turns off. A really big show. What is that? Go get vehicle berry? Fucking vehicle
berry. But yeah, today we're gonna... I'll tell you what we're gonna do. We are going to do
the rest of season one of Sam and Max, probably. I don't think... unless somebody can correct me
here... I don't think this is gonna take more than six to seven hours. Is it? Because we're
in the middle of episode three. Three, four, five, six, seven-ish, maybe. I'm just gonna
finish it tonight. We're just gonna do it. Depends on how stupid you feel today. I feel
pretty intelligent today. Anybody else like that? How many other people here wake up sometimes and
they are Albert Einstein? You can do anything. You can solve any problem, any solution, any
equation. You can do anything. You're easy to speak. You're easy to talk. You're easy to
move around. Then on some days you wake up and you can... you're like a caveman. It's...
seriously, it's 50-50. It's yin and yang with me. He's trying to brag here again.
I'm always a caveman. Sometimes I'm a caveman for two straight weeks. Sometimes I get on it and I'm
just super on top of everything and I get... I got something to say about that. I got something
to say about that. I'm gonna bring up this. Gonna bring up that. You guys have seen streams
before. I'm just like, hey, okay. So, um, this way. Yep. I think... I just died. You know what I mean?
I got... it's yin and yang. High energy, low energy. That's what that is. That's what yin and
yang is. Except it's not. We make funny haha videos. All right. I think we've stalled for
enough time. I think it's time to tell the story. Part two of The Dentist. And the funny
thing about this story is... wait a minute. Wait a minute. There's trash over here. Hold on.
Funny thing about this story. It's not a... ow! Funny thing about this story. It's not trash.
It's... I'm moving electronics around. It's not trash. So the funny thing about this story...
Come on! The funny... red skin. Stop it. It's... why won't this work? I'm trying to adjust the white
balance. Look, I live in Las Vegas. It's been hot. The sun's been shining. I got a sunburn.
Look. See? I'll prove it. See? Look. See? Look at that. See? Anyways. So I'm not the dentist
today. I'm not even gonna look over here. I'm minimizing chat. That means minimize.
All right. So listen. Those of you that remember when I said I went to The Dentist
a couple weeks ago, right? So I went to The Dentist a couple weeks ago. And I did part one
of my procedures that I was going to do. Had some x-rays. Had some... had some things done.
Came back for part two today. And what did I talk about? What was in The Dentist two weeks
ago that I made a big deal about? Uh-huh. There was a television in The Dentist office.
No, not teeth, right? So in this Dentist office, there is a TV with Netflix on it.
Remember I said, oh, I wonder what people watch when they get their teeth done? I made that
very specific comment. Anyways, today I'm in The Dentist office. Earlier today. This is like
four hours ago. So I get the remote and I've got some work to do. So I'm gonna be there
for like an hour or so, right? Maybe a little bit more. So I go back in the chair
and while I'm going back, I'm told, put on whatever you want. And I kind of panicked a little bit.
I didn't know what to put on. So I put on something safe. A nature documentary. Again,
yes. I panicked again. I do this every time. So I put on a nature documentary and it's the
episode. I didn't care what the fucking episode was called. The episode was called Cording.
It was like a BBC documentary. I'm going to describe it. You may have already seen it.
So Cording is on the screen. This is just playing. Netflix is just sitting there. Thankfully,
the volume's not turned up very high at all. So I'm in the chair going back and things are
normal. And I'm glancing over at this TV every now and then. Remember, Dentist is fucking in
my mouth. Like Dentist is in my mouth doing these things. Dentist is in his... Dentist is
drilling. No, he's not drilling. Dentist is using tools inside of my mouth. So
God damn it. Why? The... I've ruined the whole story. So the Dentist is working in my mouth while
the Netflix documentary is playing. So he's, you know, doing his thing. He's like,
do you have talk? Oh yeah. So let me see this. Let me see. Turn this way, please.
I glance over at the TV and there are two turtles having sex on the TV. Just fucking on
screen. And I'm like this. And remember, the TV is over here. So I really have to like look
hard and there's two turtles just going at it. And remember, the episode was called Cording.
I'm okay, you know? It doesn't take... Sometimes it's really easy for me to laugh and get into
a laughing fit. But whatever, that's fucking nature. It doesn't matter. He's sitting there,
still doing his thing. Okay. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Are you okay?
You okay? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh-huh. Little do I know that this keeps going.
The two turtles are having sex. Another turtle. Another turtle comes from behind the other
turtle and starts punching this turtle in the back of the head over and over again.
And I'm like... Why? Why is it her? I'm telling you, this is like CIA level training
that I had to go through here to not laugh while the guy was fucking in my mouth doing
things. That's not the end of the story. So I'm going like this. And what do I see again
while I fucking tear my eyes down? Another turtle shows up. Just what I think. I was
out of the woods here. Another fucking turtle starts to fight the rest of the turtles and
one of two of them having sex with each other. It got to a point where I was like...
And he's like, are you okay? I'm like, yeah, I just got some water back here in my mouth.
This is just animals having sex on the screen behind him. He didn't even know.
This is at the dentist. And 2020 hindsight. I composed myself completely. But holy shit, man.
It was unbelievable. No, he didn't know. He's sitting there going like this and the TV behind
him is turtles having sex. It was so elaborate. Tell him you need to change the channel. Well,
I... You can't... What am I going to do? Hey, excuse me. Excuse me. I'm the guy that put on
the animals having sex. Can I change that? I put it on. We're going to play Sam and Max now.
Speaking of animals, it wasn't that big of a deal until the other turtle started to come
and punch the other turtle that was having sex in the head. It was just... It was bizarre.
My stand up story. No, this is just me telling a story. I think we're on this one,
right? That was Larry David. I knew that that Netflix shit was going to fuck me up.
I was certain when I went there two weeks ago and I saw that the TV was there, I knew there was
going to be a problem. I've tried to put on something safe. And here's the worst part
about that. I'll end the story and we'll move on. But here's the worst part about that entire
thing. If I had just put on something like Cupcake Wars, I would have cracked and laughed
at that show for some reason. I was able to keep it together during the animals having sex.
Life story, season one, episode five, courtship. There it is. That is the exact
episode. Just watch The Power of the Turtles. You tell me... You watch that fucking episode
right now. Just delete... Get out of the stream. Watch that episode right now and you tell me
that if you're in the dentist lying in the chair, you're going to have no problem with that
one. Show it on stream? I can't. Ah, fuck. This is the guy that laughed at fart jokes
for an hour. Yeah, but what was I supposed to do with that scenario? I don't know. It's
not something that you are expecting to see, like glaring, pulling your eyeballs down,
looking at a TV. All right, so now look at... Don't choose the mating show next time. I don't
know. I'm out of coffee but I'm so nervous I keep trying to drink it anyway. It's funny how
stress can reduce you to just a bundle of mindless reflexes. Is that what happened to
me? Wouldn't it be wonderful to think so? Do you remember messing up things at the start
of the stream? What do you mean? All right, well let me break down what this is. We're in
the middle of episode three. So if you're wondering, wait, what the hell's going on?
Why are you... we just jumped right in. It's because this is the middle of the episode. We
are tasked with doing three things. We have to kill Sybil. There's one of them, but we're
not going to do that. That's one of the things we have to do. So we have three tasks
that we need to fake, I'm assuming, right? Have you considered the possibility of staging
your own deaths to throw the toy mafia off the scent? That would be dishonest.
There's a shitload of turtles. They just don't stop coming over there. They are fighting
each other. The truth. You're a real antique, you know that? I mean in a good way. I've
always liked antiques. Okay, so we'll be back. We'll be back. I know you will.
You're the only two I can trust. Oh, really? She should consider guilt slinger as her
next profession. All right, so is there... I need to be... I need a reminder of something here.
We got the teddy bear box or the thing that can listen.
The sixth of them in the narrative. Yeah, dude, it was fucking out of control. Dude,
I keep having flashbacks. That's that moment. All right, magnet tokens used. I'm not going
to use the gun. We already did that. All right, let's go. Is there like a way I can...
Oh my god, I did it again. It's been like two or three weeks and I tried to leave through
the closet again. God damn it. Look, I had a rough day, all right? I will. I'm gonna try.
That actually wasn't rough. It was fucking... it was... it was fucking hilarious. But,
you know. Let me move this. You guys want face cam today? Okay, that looks all right.
I gotta take up some space over here. Not too big. I don't want to get too... I don't
want to get too big here. Okay, I need a bigger face. A bigger face! All right, so,
I really... I really don't know what... where we left off here. There's the casino. This
is the casino episode. I have some new items. Let me go just walk around and talk. I have
a perfectly symmetrical face. I do not. I do not. Actually, no, I don't. I'm gonna prove it
to you right now. So, you see, my face looks like... so, if we take a look at this angle here,
my nose comes down. It actually goes this way. So, my nose actually goes in a completely
different direction. So, my nose crosses here. My mouth here goes down, right? So, as you see,
this is a straight out of my face. When we turn this way, the chin is more pronounced here
and the nose points over here, right? Sorry, this way. This eye socket is out a little
and when I turn this way, notice how the nose is pointing this way and this eye socket is back
and my chin points down a little deeper this way. Some of you have made fun of my face this
way because each day it looks like a banana and it's very rude and very mean, but I think this
is my good side. This is... I mean, you could... maybe... it depends. This could be my good
side too. You know, the little deeper set eye there. They're both good sides, I think. They're
just both very different. You don't have a good side. My mother would disagree with you.
All right, Sam and Max, where are we going? No, I do not have a symmetrical face at all.
A very rocky face. Are you only... are you reading mean comments again? Yeah. I'm sorry,
though. Oh, here's a security camera in here, right? So, this is the... this is the security
camera. Can I do anything weird with this? Hmm. Someone want to give me a little
clue here to get us on the right track? Because it's been a couple weeks. I have no idea what I'm
supposed to do right now. Well, oh, will he actually get... do this for me? I don't know,
man. It's your stream. I just... it's been a while. I gotta join the mafia, right?
That camera seems to be bulletproof. If only there were some way to get rid of arbitrary items here
in the store. Get rid of items? Irony is a sledgehammer, isn't it? So, do we have to... okay.
Shall we, Sean? Let's do... So, something... and what... does it... I can remove something from here.
Magnet? Or maybe just put the magnet on it? Does it fuck it all up?
My face cam? I'm gonna turn it off in, like, five minutes anyway. Can I distract him? What else was...
what else was... what were the other two tasks? Kill Sybil and then I don't remember what the
other two are. Is there, like, a way... well, I think we're getting... there's a new character
here. Okay. Not gonna say anything. He's watching us.
All right, so... I'd rather keep it to myself. Listening device. Shoot him, he's suspicious. Now,
he's just... he's gonna follow me around. Takes me back to my childhood. I can't go in here.
Should I go back to the casino? Okay, yeah, I need to retrieve the meatball sub,
dissuade Bosco, and kill Sybil. Okay. So, let me go back in here and see if...
and knowing that now, let me see. So, I have to stop this camera from... hold on.
Can I put anything on here?
Something that the anti-delivery camera does not recognize.
It actually is.
He will not sneak past me. Oh, no! The price of paranoia is eternal vigilance. Got it.
What if his toy mafia disguise is just a disguise? I gotta see what he's reading.
All right, so he's... no, okay. Now, Magneth on the camera. If he's pretending to do the
word jumble, he's with the Knights of Malta. So, I should be able to do something.
Suck it up. Out the door. Yeah! Eat pavement, camera!
The society pages must be sculling bones.
Got that one. All right, so now I can... now I have to persuade him. Can I put... wait a
minute. Hold on. He's gonna look over and see this. He's gonna freak out.
Pretending to read the gardening section. So, it's true. He is toy mafia.
He's gonna know that this was delivered. I hope we don't lose Bosco's friendship over this.
Me neither. He's my second favorite delusional paranoid.
Oh no! Oh no! He's coming in! We're done for, y'all! Persuade. I surrender! I surrender!
Told you this would happen! I told you he would deliver, and he delivered! I can't believe
that guy! But, are you supposed to drink after the dentist? We'll help you purge this place
of mafia contraband just as soon as we solve this case we're so incredibly busy with.
Oh yeah, you're real busy. You've done nothing but loiter around my store all day.
What can we say? We love to loiter. Only water? Oh, you mean ice coffee? Not yet. Our journey to
the dark side has just begun. I fucking hate being on camera. I'm such a fucking yin and yang
on camera. I love being on camera, but I hate being watched. Does that make any sense? I love
being on camera. I don't like being watched. Figure that one out. You'll get it. All right,
so that's one task done. Hey, wait a second. Why didn't b-task do what? Hey! My camera!
Just filmed with the camera turned off. I'm gonna just put a piece of tape on it.
All right, one out of three. Now we need to pretend to kill Sybil. What the fuck are you
talking about? All right, I got a game audio. The game audio is off. It's fine. All right,
so what else do we have? I have the listening device. I'm gonna assume maybe we get
Sybil to be like, ah, don't kill me! And then shoot the gun, right? To make it sound like,
ah, I'm dead! But then she would be a bug. Hold on. So now, okay, pull out the gun
and be like, hey, like, maybe I could just wing her. I'd better not. I have to get her
to say something. Coin? Token? How do I get her to say- You used a couple of bucks in
tokens. Thanks, but my career is about to take off, so I'll be fine. You seem nervous.
You seem, understandably, a little tense. Maybe you should switch to decaf. What? Oh, yes,
the coffee cup. I'm out of coffee, but I'm so nervous I keep trying to drink it anyway.
I'm so nervous. It's funny how stress can reduce you to just a bundle of mindless reflexes.
Is that what happened to me? Wouldn't it be wonderful- Am I more like Sam or am I more
like Max? What would you guys say? What the fuck was that? Max? I don't know.
And I know, you know, you know, you don't see it, that's why. But no, personality-wise.
What was that? If you don't know what that was, then I'm kind of glad you don't.
All right, what about, what else are- Tiki. Coffee cup. That's a token from her.
All right. What can I do with the coffee cup? Hold all my calls, please. Hey,
keep away from my intercom. Can I play with that? No, it drives people crazy.
Put poison in it? No. I have to put more coffee in it? Try this. You can't kill somebody
with coffee, can you? You can kill somebody with a coffee pot, but why would I poison a
coffee mug? One of the coffee mugs could just be used as a weapon. Tissue. Is this the kind
with hallow in the sheets or extra soft? Chloroform, actually. Some of my therapy
patients used to get a little rowdy. Too much of anything kills you. I'm afraid to touch those.
I could think of a few things. So how'd I- All right, so I need to-
I have her coffee mug. I need to get her to, like, scream or something or
a voice message or her yelling or- What do I do with the coffee mug?
Can I play with this? No. Why not? I'm gonna be doing a lot of this, so I gotta move the camera.
This is what I do when I play a game like this. I'll show you.
I got my elbow just resting over here. This is a good shot, I think,
of, like, my detached face from my body, like, cocked that way.
I've got half a mind to stretch out for a little bit. I think you have to stretch the
whole thing or it rips. You baffle me sometimes, Max. I stopped watching the stream to watch the
documentary you talked about. Give us a review. This must be how the toy mafia is keeping an eye
on Sybil. Functional and delicious looking. Wow. Turns out I don't like that angle very much at
all. I'm going back here. So can I put something over that? I feel vaguely ridiculous. You
shouldn't, Sam. There's nothing vague about it at all. So if they're monitoring what's going
on here, how can I pretend to kill her? This is what they do in the movie. I appreciate you
trying to defend me, Sam, but there's nobody there. There was a gnat, or at least I think I saw one.
Okay. I probably need something else. How do I make it look like she was poisoned or killed
or dead? You can smell me through the face cam today. I should smell like Dove body spray.
That's what I use. I go underneath both armpits and, like, across the chest once. Dove
men plus care. Clean laundry. It's the clean laundry one. I smell like clean laundry right
now. Not like puke. Somebody said puke. Fuck you. Somebody said puke. I mean, I did puke
earlier, but I washed my hands and face and shit. I'm gonna go back to the casino. What
about my office? I don't know. I still have coins. What's the third test? Take the
meatball sub back from wherever it was. Wait, is the meatball something like my trash can
or something? I don't know. Let's take a look up here. Show me the money. Show me the sandwich.
Show me the money. You show me the sandwich, I'll show you the money. I will, I tell you. Just
show me the money. I think we've got a real gun as a cap gun. Don't be scared. Trying to
vent something hot, Leonard? Like a meatball sandwich, Leonard? A meatball sandwich, you
stole, Leonard? You two stay back or I swear by my mother's bedspread, I'll shoot you both.
Excuse me, are you by any chance holding us at gunpoint with a harmless cap gun?
I'm not gonna kill us with that thing. Always a cheat, always a cheat, eh, Leonard? What?
No. Sick of a little buddy. I thought you'd never sick.
Violence, violence! Okay, Leonard, are you gonna tell us where the sandwich is or are
we gonna have to get rough with her? We put a tire on him? I'll never talk. Oh. There ain't
nothing you can do to break me. Nothing. Does your mother know what you've become?
Don't you talk about my mama. My mama's a saint. Is she the saint of stern-o-heated
fried food? Because if so, she may have another follower. Hold on, Max. I think we've just
found our captive's weak spot. Which? His uninspired diction or his laughably bad grammar?
Neither. I wish. I say we hit this cheatin' slime receptacle where it hurts the most.
Right in the mother. You mean- We're gonna go talk to mom?
That's right, Max. It's time to pull out the yo mama jokes.
Uh oh. No, not that. Anything but that. Leonard, yo mama's so fat. Uh, she's so
frat. Not good enough. Like, curdled goat's milk on a warm summer day. I can never
remember the punch lines. Like, that's funny. I remember all the punch lines, but I can never
remember the setups. I can help. Well then, Max, I think we'll have to break this two-bit
barman as a team. Follow my lead. Yo mama's so fat. She plays pool with the planets. A classic.
Yo mama's so fat. She plays- Where is it? Why am I getting minus two's for that? That is
a classic yo mama joke. But there's more. She showed up early for her own funeral.
She knitted a sweater with all her own materials. She brings coupons to the penny
arcade. If she fell in nuclear waste, no one would notice. What does that have to do with being
fat? Her mouth would make a long shorman- This is- I think I have to make this- Okay.
She has more molds than an origami accordion. Oh, it's true. It's working. Let's keep it
up a little, buddy. He's got to connect them. Okay, making grown men weep. A f*** time for
the whole family. All right. Yo mama's so radiant. That's- that's a nice thing,
though. Isn't that radiant mean she's glowing and she's wonderful? Perky. She's up. She's having
fun. She's moving around. She's thrifty. She's really quick on her feet and she can
steal things easily. Your mama's so vulgar. Yo mama's so vulgar. She beat out Sam for best
in show. Her mouth would make a long shorman blush. That's the right one, right? Her mouth
would make a long shorman blush. Oh, it hurts. It hurts. Yes, we're definitely making a dent
now. Let's keep it up a little, buddy. Okay. Your mama's so punctual. Let's take a break.
No, your mama's so punctual, thrifty, perky, radiant. These are all good qualities.
I mean, this one, unless we're talking about in the morning. You know what I'm saying?
It's probably this one. Yo mama's so thrifty. She's so thrifty. She brings coupons to the
penny arcade. She brings coupons to the penny arcade. Oh mama, make it stop. Why's he turning
red? He's getting closer to breaking. Let's keep it up, little buddy. Yeah. We've got the same tone
here, don't we? This is now when I see it in real time. I know what you're saying now.
I just have to have to see. I have to see for myself. You know what I mean?
Is it the same? Oh, whatever. Who cares? It's the lighting. Look, I had sun today
and yesterday. I live in Las Vegas. It's like 150 degrees sometimes. 120 maybe. Radiant,
perky, punctual. Punctual means you're so, you're never late. Your mama's so punctual.
The only time she's low is at a limbo contest. She showed up early for her own damn funeral.
Showed up early for her own funeral. This can all be over if you'll just tell us where the
sandwich is. No. Let's hit him one more time, Sam. Your mama's so perky. Your mama's so perky.
Oh, that's not right. She beat out Sam for best in show. She knitted a sweater with all
her own materials. The only time she's low is at a limbo contest. The only time she's low
is at a limbo contest. Oh, okay. Okay. I'll tell you where the sandwich is. Just leave my mom alone.
Red Face Streamer tortures self in cartoon violence themed video game. I never even
took the sandwich out of the casino. Hitted in the pride slot of the one-armed bandit
and then took the one-arm so no one could win it. So, oh, it's where is it? To the next
question. Where's the arm? I got it right here. Oh, jerk bag. How did you not notice that before?
I was too busy taking his cap gun to notice that extra arm. We'd best get back to the casino
and win back that sandwich. See you around, sucker. Wait, aren't you gonna untie me? Hello,
guys? No, we're gonna keep you tied up and have the rats eat you. Anybody? Yeah,
see you in like six days. Was that too much? That might have been too much. I wouldn't leave them
there for six days. I'd leave them there for like a minute and I'd come back and be like,
okay, we'll untie you now and send you the proper authorities to deal with you.
Yin and yang, guys. You guys, I'm too spulked. It's like, you know, lawful
and then fucking unlawful. They live together. All right, so now I just need to kill civil.
Let's go back to the casino and do this. Where are we going, Sam? Teddy bears mafia
free playland. Lawful good and lawful good. What would lawful good even mean?
You're not the guy that does anything bad or good. You just laugh at the jokes.
No, you laugh at clean good jokes. You don't laugh at like dirty mean jokes.
Mafia free playland. Lawful evil would be you laughing like mean shit. The mafia plays
for free. And raffle neutral means you decide between, you know, laughing and,
you know, maybe you think something is funny but you shouldn't but you still laugh at it.
All right, let's go this way. Chaotic raffle. Chaotic raffle. Hey, the one-armed bandit's one
arm is missing. Stolen by a bandit perhaps? Why? I still don't get it. There's only two.
Presto. Shitting Mario and the gnome. No other exist. I want like an ASCII of my face.
I'd still ban it but like I don't want that.
What the fuck? What the fuck is shitting Mario? You don't want to know. You do not want to
know the answer to that question. Let me see that. Yes, that's definitely the sandwich.
Teddy bear will be very pleased. What is he talking about? Generally yes. Hey Sam,
are we mafia yet? I can't explain that. Well, there's still that little matter of rubbing
out our hands. My hands are so much bigger than my head. Oh right. It's so easy to forget
these things. All right, now he's gonna kill Sybil. The son has scorched his brain.
I have the cap gun though. Cap gun, coffee, shoot. Okay, this is where we're getting some
knowledge here. Cap gun makes the bang. She falls back and pretends to die, screams. It's
all on camera. I'm gonna walk up to her. I'm gonna listen, Sybil. This is what we're
gonna do. I'm gonna shoot you with this cap gun and then Max is gonna scream in obscenity.
He's right. I will. Easy little buddy. I'm gonna go something like that. You crack me up.
You crack me up little screamer. All right, listen, I've got something for you. Just what
do you think you're doing? Looks like he missed her. How do I? I don't understand how do I make
her pretend like she's falling. Maybe she's, can I put something in the coffee and she fall?
I don't, but why wouldn't I just tell her to pretend to fall? I'm afraid to touch those.
I'm afraid to touch. Can I put them in something? Can I put them in the coffee?
Who wouldn't want us leaving her cup there? How do I pick up something like that? Stop
flexing your shoulders. Do whatever I want, okay? Have you stop me? It's the cap gun,
but she has to fall down. What's that you keep doing with your arm? What? Oh, I think there
was a coffee cup here a minute ago. Throw boiling hot coffee in her face. Yikes is right.
Are you sure we can't talk you into faking your own death? I'm sure. We'll be back.
I know you will. You're the only two I can trust. All right. Fine. Really? She should consider
guilt slinger as her next profession. Give her coffee. So maybe I go to the coffee,
go to Bosco's and get coffee. Give her the coffee. Make sure it's not coffee she wants.
Have her go into it like a caffeine binge. But what's that going to do? She's going
to clean her house and do all of her taxes early. What about that? A lot of caffeine.
What's that going to do to you? Your ear looks infected. That's probably just hair.
He's getting redder. I'm not getting redder. All right. Next time I see the word red,
I'll just ban the word red. Hey guys, what color is that coffee pot? Why do I have no
power here? I can't clear the chat. How do I have no power in my own stream? I have to
talk to fucking Dave Twitch about that one. What's going on there? All right. I need the
coffee. Well, what the fuck am I supposed to do? Give her a smudgy? What's that called?
A smudgy? Put nacho cheese in it? I put ketchup in here. Does this be blood?
So I have to shoot the throw the ketchup all over and then shoot the cap gun?
What about the freezer? Is she going to like hold it over and just sludge it on top of her
head? Find out what happens. Can you do another bicep curls video to celebrate 225,000 followers?
I don't think I could lift it. I'm not sure I could actually lift it, so no.
Can you add more space to the side of your head though? Oh, my OCD is killing me. Yeah,
I'll fix it. Wait, did you want more? Oh, you're talking about over here. I see what you mean.
There you go. Perfect. Can you make your head a little wider? Yeah. Why is it too thin for
you? Yeah, I could do that. Oh my goodness. Thank you. I'd lose my head if it wasn't
attached. That's never stopped me. Make it a little bit wider. I mean, if that makes you
comfortable and happy, I don't want to make you, you know. She's just drinking the ketchup.
We'll be back. I know you will. You're the only two. Dude, can you bet it's not fitting my
widescreen TV? Oh, fuck. That's right. We've got 4k televisions now. I forgot. I'm sorry,
guys. I know. I'm still trying to get the hang of this. That should fit the 4k screen,
right? Hold on. Holy shit. Look at how fucked up I look. This is like uncanny valley.
That's terrifying. I look like a fucking lizard. Or it rips. You baffle me sometimes. I need to do
this. I have to make it. I have to make the one fucking awful joke of the evening. Here we go.
You ready? No, I want to hit him. I think I've had enough of you for the moment. Okay. But
be sure to. I don't think I can get this done. I want to like whack him and then have
me get Goompa crushed. Never mind. Just what do you think you're doing? Looks like he
missed her. Can I shoot the coffee cup and have the blood go everywhere?
What? No, that's not how that works. What? No, I just actually killed her.
It wouldn't block the bullet. I actually killed her. What happened to the picture?
Who cares? Now that she's whacked, we don't need to keep watching her, do we?
It went through the coffee cup and hit her in the chest. These things always make me
You're a real sociopath, Don Bear. I mean that as a compliment, naturally. Naturally.
Hey Sam, webcam tastes like chicken. Good idea, John. Now those toy mafia goons won't
see Sybil wake up, which could be important to our continued good health. Well,
you won't see her wake up either. We've learned that webcams go great with ketchup.
Another fun fact to add to the crime fighting arsenal.
Is this right? This is longer. You know what? I think we are. Let's go and see
Chuckles. Sam, Max, you have done what we have asked of you. Acts of intelligence,
malevolence, and subservience. And we welcome you into the ranks of the Orso Nostra.
Indeed. My stuff runneth over. There's a small ritual with the ceremonial picnic baskets
and then a few other technicalities, and then Joey will show up with some cold cuts.
But first, as a sign of respect, I will remove my mask, which is good.
Who is it? What's the reveal?
Power that the toy mafia could offer. But what happened to the previous teddy bear?
Poor teddy bear. What happened?
It's a mole.
This is fucked up. There we go. That's better.
Only modern technology is horribly, horribly wrong.
I'm trying to shoot their tire. I can't shoot behind me.
All right, put it away then. Put the gun away. No, sit down. Sit down. No, sit down. Can I
drop something on him? That would be... Hold on, I think I got it. Don't worry,
they're using a cap gun. We'll be fine. One, two, three. That guy's dead. That guy's
dead.
Let's go take down that fat little fraud once and for all. Good idea.
Hey, the dawn is gone. Find out just what that traitorous mole there is doing.
You know, without that menacing mumble, he doesn't seem capable of planning brunch,
much less a dastardly master plan. Agreed. But in my experience, there's always something
interesting behind any door that says, do not enter under pain of death.
Well, now that we have free rein to look at stuff, let's go look at the chalkboard.
This gobbledygook's best left to the freelance accountants.
Racketeering, extortion, smuggling, smuggling. I'm not much of a fighter.
I did that yesterday. I can't do that. I'm not allowed to do that twice in two days.
Yesterday's was better.
Is it a grenade?
Slaves. You can do the factory work now that you've rid me of my enough underlings.
Look, look at the hypno bear.
Don't you feel sleepy? Don't we? We don't. Hypnosis won't work on either of us,
but play along until we get that gun from it. I asked you a question, slaves.
Yes, master. Yeah, so I feel kind of tired a little bit for some reason.
What he said.
Really? It seems a little off somehow.
Maybe it's just me. Oh, I know. Here's a test. Tall one, you shoot the short one.
Excuse me, master.
Shoot your friend. I command it.
This blow.
Mother of mercy, is this the end of little maxi? Oh death, where is that guy?
The pain and only two days to retirement. He's got a promise.
Pretty good Bugs Bunny death scene.
Cowards die a thousand deaths. Well, heroes die, but once unless they're playing video games, in which case heroes die a lot, too.
So good night, fresh prince, and may charlie's angels sing thee to thy rest.
Right. Well, so cold.
Why am I so cold?
He's gonna break the machine. Don't do that. You're gonna break it.
We shouldn't be breaking that machine. We can use that to produce grain or something somewhere.
Okay. Good job, slave. Just about ready to have you shoot him again.
Yes, master.
Now, slave. You run the factory while I read the paper. Just get the hypno bears sorted for delivery.
I didn't do anything.
Yes, master. Good, good. I don't understand. Now I'm off to see what wry observation Fred Masset has for us today.
Max, you keep playing dead. I'll figure out some way to bring teddy bear and his factory to their respective knees.
I can't hear you. I'm dead.
All right, so um
We could have just arrested him. Why don't we just arrest him right now?
Hey, this isn't even a real fire extinguisher.
Well, that didn't do much.
They're still producing these. Halt. Halt the production. What do I got in here? I have a token.
Insidious. Nefarious.
Nefarious.
This is quite a gizmo.
All right, so
um
What do we got over here?
One-armed bandit machine in development.
Anybody got a screw loose?
Screwdriver.
Menacing computer, which means nothing. I really don't want to screw that. Why not?
I wouldn't know where to begin. Why not? Just try. I did it in VR. It's not hard.
What about like here?
What about that hopper over there? I think these are the voice gizmos for the insidious hypnotic bears.
The voice gizmos?
Um
I don't want to screw that.
Do I have to change them with the the voice bug?
The voice bug's still sitting on civil's desk. I can't leave.
Master. What is it hypnotic slave? Something wrong with the machine?
No.
Then don't bother me.
Don't even try it.
Yes, master.
You don't have to pretend anymore. You have a real gun.
I much like the funnies these days. They tend not to be.
All right, what about the screwdriver on the one-armed bandit? Can I like twist it off? Do something with it? Okay.
Oops.
Oh, there it is.
You're on fire.
And it'll pick this one up.
So what does that do? You're on fire. Wait, is he also hypnotized? A lot of hypnotism in this game.
Well, let's go tell him he's on fire.
I know she's married now, but that Cathy who's still smoking hot. Oh, that's fucking weird. What is it now slave?
You're on fire. I'm on. I'm on fire. Help. Help. I'm on fire. I'm on fire. Not real extinguisher.
Sorry, pal.
Would be on chivalrous. Anyway.
And when he's not paying attention.
All right, max get up. Let's go. You okay little buddy. I could use a mattress.
Stay put. I'll work. By the way. Me too. All right. All right. Oh, I know he can be.
I can do this. Here goes nothing. He'll get he'll get zonked up and dragged over.
Is he too big for this?
Oh no, he's clogging up the chocolate vent. Nice work Sam. Thanks pal.
The whole thing has been contaminated.
We have to replace all that chocolate.
Exclusive
Like 5 000 pounds per square inch of air underneath them and shoot them out.
Wait, what?
That's what I call breaking the bank and the sidewalk and the water main and the buffet table.
You're really broken up about that buffet table. Aren't you max?
It was the only innocent in this whole affair sam. I mean apart from the bystanders and their pets. Buck up little pal.
Maybe the commissioner how many people are in that factory meal at squirrel garden when we tell them how we crack the case.
He bet it for all the hard work I did. I want to no three jelly lemurs with extra salt. So we just killed everybody
and here is the
Protagonist no the antagonist of the next one. The factory's been destroyed. Repeat the factory has been destroyed. Commence plan b.
He hits his head backwards with the camera. What the fuck man?
The mole on the bob and the meatball. That one's done.
A nice mouth close-up. They don't do those anymore.
Took you long enough. What I
Let's do the next one episode four.
Ted E. Bear
Now wait a week before I play episode four. Well, I also took a week off.
Chuggy cheese.
Why am I so red?
Game tap. I told you guys that story about game tap, right? I think I already have.
Have I? I have. I know I have.
Bob bug just touched me. I've never told that story. I've not told the game tap story.
I swear to god I have.
Well, why do I get this? Um, all right.
Let me refresh your memory.
So game tap was a service. It was actually way before its time.
It was a service where you paid a monthly fee and you got access to a bunch of games and some of them were
retro games. Some of them were Genesis games.
Super Nintendo, right? They had a whole catalog of stuff and they had new stuff come out too.
Some maybe a couple of years older, but it was like a steam, but it was streamlined through the game tap app.
It was actually really cool.
So I had I got it for a while. I was on it for a while.
And after maybe two or three four months, I decided I didn't want it anymore. It was like I was
I didn't really like the didn't they weren't coming out with anything that I really cared that much about with I played
all the back catalog of their retro games and I kind of was done with it. So
I called up to cancel it and I got on the phone and I got to the cancellation, you know, the sales department.
Yeah, you have to do the shit by phone because remember this is like fucking 15 years ago.
This is like at least 10 to 15 years ago and the person on the phone
told me oh that's uh unfortunate that you want to uh leave the service. Uh, well
what if I you know, maybe maybe get a little more chance and what if I gave you a free month to game tap?
I was like
um yeah okay fine like I guess I guessed so I don't have to pay for this month.
No, no free month game tap. He had that voice to us. What a guy.
So I got a free month to game tap and I continued to play and didn't really
I wasn't playing it that much. So at the end of that month another 30 days went by.
I called again to cancel and it was another person and I told him I want to cancel and
they said you could probably guess oh but you know I know you want to leave but what if uh
what if you got a free month of game tap the service for free and I'm like okay okay oh sure
I guess I'll have it again another free month. This happened two more times.
After the fourth month I was just like you know what I don't really want this anymore.
I don't want game tap anymore. I tried to cancel it more than three times.
I didn't even want it for free. No I didn't. After like two months or three months it was just like
I don't use it. I don't want this. You could probably still have game tap to this day. Yeah
but I feel like I've told that story before. I wonder what would have happened if I kept calling
to cancel. Would they have just kept would they have just given me free months forever?
Did game tap go out of business? It did a long time ago. Game tap went out of business
not that much further after it came out which you probably could
understand that if they were just giving free months to people that tried to cancel.
I think their theory look and here's the theory right if you have a credit card that's linked
up to something like Netflix you don't really think about that payment. It just kind of
happens and if you were given a free month of Netflix and you're like oh okay I guess
am I like my credit card will I guess stay linked right so then after a month you just
don't even think about it and you just keep getting charged you just kind of forget about
it right and the companies use that kind of the maybe that process of customer retention
over the long term the person will forget that they even cared about it in the first place
and their $12 a month will just still come out forever but I would call every month and I
would put it to the day to make sure because I was still having fun with game tap so I
didn't like that after three months I didn't care that much about it but I was still
doing it every so often if you just stopped streaming how imagine how much money you would
make you know uh let me open up the new one you know the interesting thing about that is
I uh well let me just save this just in case for some weird reason
oh I can't I can't I can't imagine so I thought about that once or twice like if I
if I just stopped streaming right completely would how many people would still just be paying here
over the years you know what I mean like it's it's weird to think about that if we call you
we would get a free subscription I don't have the power to do that eventually twitch takes
your button away that's true but I wondered just just how people kind of just forget
that they're uh that they're connected to it and they subscribe to it and
it's just an interesting thought experiment to think about I wonder if I just stopped
streaming today what would happen how many subscribers would I have in like two years
I have a complaint hold on I gotta is this uh oh yeah I forgot I have to watch I gotta take
this out it's gonna be really loud uh I can't there we go I can and there it is this episode
four this is called Abe Lincoln must die it's an interesting title wait I'm gonna have to change
this again it's gonna be kind of loud because I can't turn it down yet sneaking the bug into
that exorcism was an uncharacteristic stroke of genius demonic possession is the gift that
keeps on giving what oh commissioner max's aunt yes that was max's aunt what's that
yes yes no yes sweet-suffering saint sebastian and a short story by susan sontag we're on our way
let me guess our friendly neighborhood demon just burnt down another monastery no max we have
a farm thirsty adversary this time the president of the united states of america the man's gone
nice he's enacting all kinds of crazy new laws what else is new federally mandated group
hugs before during and after all major sporting events so he's curtailing civil
liberties threatening the environment hey that makes three of us hey he's about to introduce
mandatory gun registration get the keys it comes a politics scream why is abraham lincoln the
president here it's weird all right all right hold on I gotta resize some windows here
I gotta resize somebody's windows saying that we could have avoided this gruesome accident if
you just let me dry and I have to point out that we could have avoided this gruesome accident if
you hadn't jumped on my head shouting jersey devil jersey devil and firing your gun out the
window I swear that woman was a dead ringer for him well here we are standing in an open
field west of the white house let's go why is it why does it why does it have a front door
all right hold on I mean I know the white house has a front door but why does it look like a hotel
that's a little bit there you crack me up little buddy okay here we go now comes like the clown
music every single one of these is you have to reopen it and stretch it I'd like to stretch
it out a little so there's not so much space you know what I'm saying that's okay all right
here we go this is called um Abe Lincoln let's let's just save it here just to have
one and all right so we please do not feed the submarine hey my missing boxing glove it's always
in the last place you look okay I got a boxing glove the white house pool most secure waiting
pool on earth I need to like I move around too much that's why this happens all right
I'm ready Jimmy two teeth who's Jimmy two teeth Jimmy oh great oh you guys doing here
oh just saving the world what are you doing here I happen to take my vacations at the white
house and I need a little iron on speaking of which beat it okay that's startling all right
anything else there's a golf course over here number nine any golf balls no what about can I
drop a listening device inside of that hole and then be able to hear the conversations that they
have while they're playing golf there is a small mailbox here it's one of those ornamental
mailboxes that doesn't actually open and that's government efficiency for you
all right sign was there your name here for naming rights to this building please contact
the office of desperation accounting oh boy can we sam please we'll see the white house
all right secret service step aside buddy freelance police just a moment sir papa bear this is super
ball possible situation at the front door talking dog and dude rabbit trying to gain access to
the oh oh please advise over super ball yeah that's a negative on the access permission sir
I'll have to ask you and your little friend to step away from the white house doggie daddy this
is exactly like my cousin's permission to pants this goon that's just nobody before we try physical
why do you care about that let's try dazzling the man with our razor sharp wit and labyrinth and
logical conundrums ah emotional violence good plan did you just call yourself super ball
code name sir I'm a bouncer secret service humor and who's papa bear section chief runs
the operation protects the president oh that's my cousin super ball it's really weird
I want to talk to your manager no can do sir he's with the president let us in pal
now I gotta change the game here to save the president I thought we were here to stop the
president by any means necessary I was going to wait to mention that part max either way sir
you can't get inside orders episode four what's this yeah I gotta get the right one there
it is so people know it what's the we're playing we're playing the correct game here you know
what I'm saying give me one second okay that should be good he's googling answers that fast
all right we'll be back I'm gonna get away find a way inside this is super ball
burps exiting zone for now seem disgruntled stay on the lookout over now can we push him
down and beat him with sewage filled garbage bags until he runs crying into
the reflecting pool tempting max but these secret service guys hold a grudge
all right so let's go post no bills a little bit pay phone can I call
still nice stool it looks a little like a weird space creature poised to devour the
unwary mortal foolish enough to sit on it I like that in a stool stool suspect yourself
that's so madonna hey hey this phone only takes Susan B Anthony dollars it must be one of
those stupid five five five phones yes actually five five five one nine eight four hey Sam
did I ever mention how I've memorized pi to one thousand decimal places it's three point one
four one five nine two six five three five eight nine seven nine do you have a piece of
paper handy you want to write down the phone number I remember the number I want to write
myself a reminder to smother you with a pillow in your sleep well that's a threat
okay so uh all right two dollars for valet parking anything else over here
sam's getting fed up kind of all right presidential storage can we go in this door
hmm white paint christmas lights and a small barbecue everything somebody would need to
renovate decorate and then accidentally burn the place to the ground later max later all right
punch through door with boxing there are so many other things to punch okay so we're going to
listening device on agent get him to give us the go-ahead can I get him to say
get him to say something over the phone I want to talk to your manager no can do sir
he's with the president don't you get bored guarding this door it's a rewarding job sir
doing my part keeping the president safe hey super ball I'd like you to smell these two
handkerchiefs and tell me which one smells more like chloroform not now max all right
I've had enough of this well give me give him back okay here's what he said just step away
from the door please that is all I say thank you sir that's what he said he said more than
that jimmy two teeth hey can you help me beating jimmy I could just drop a cinder
block on you right now remember that dad look what we did was that was that supposed to be
a threat all right um I I kind of need to put this on screen that's not even a banana dude
that's the top half of the banana you need the whole thing you need my like my mouth to be at
the very bottom thin that's actually really a high fidelity image though that's high quality
image but that's kind of a uh it's kind of not a banana that's a sexy banana thank you
like a pineapple but if I know I wouldn't my face wouldn't be a pineapple all right what do
I need to do something here do I do that I can't listen to that thing boy boxing glove
boxing glove payphone can we leave do I have to stay here can I just leave where we going
oh I can leave all right let's go back to the office I'll drive not while I'm alive exactly
for a second I thought I had to stay there why am I wearing lipstick I'm not wearing lipstick
I'm just full of blood I have extra blood I have a lot of blood you know humans have
four pints I have like five pints of blood it has to go somewhere I have a really red
mouth red cheeks red chest red hey look at my hands red I'm red only sometimes though sometimes
I'm not full of blood I sometimes I have like a really pale complexion yin and yang some blood
no blood less blood he's going home guess not can I do anything because he's not here can I
do something here I can't listen to think boy all right what about what else is here
uh the drawers are just painted on to make the desk seem useful yeah that's right it's not even
real one of these days we're gonna finish that game I'm still working on getting the
rest of the darts from the police impound no look I got a lot of collagen in my face
would you like me to show you what I mean by that warning this is going to be disgusting
to some of you why is he up here favorite shifty card cheat lennard steak charmer how you doing
good he really has been in here for like six days show the collagen so collagen is is your
your elasticity of your face it keeps your skin up that's when you lose collagen that's
how you start to get droopy and you get wrinkles and I've got a lot of collagen
that's why I'm so red but I'm able to do things like this no I'm not gonna do it
now if I get 5000 subs I'll do it I'm gonna do it now because I don't want that to happen
see look at this I got really springy skin I can it's I'm like a rubber band man he's
wearing a mask I just like peel it off and I'm another person there's nothing to do with
collagen what are you talking about I've got looking rubber band collagen skin
like look at no a stripper a streamer is no one who are you no one he took a bite of gum gum
I'm telling you all right what am I doing I'll try that at home it hurts look at I've already
got like a mark here now my beautiful beautiful collagen skin has been tainted the donut box
is a happy reminder of a bygone era oh five five five five five calling Sam the White House
White House agent Super Bowl speaking uh have you checked the baby we'll be right there oh please
have you checked the baby yes sir sleeping soundly oh good job then who are you calling Sam
who Mr Pizza don't I have the number and asbestos pies please oh yeah well same to you
jerk what he said the word thank you and have a nice day fuck it's odd I hate I'm so easy to
I'm so easy to manipulate you just say a series of words and I will it I'll be I'm completely
manipulatable I don't have that phone number the White House right White House agent Super
Bowl speaking hello please hold hello please hold so he's waiting he's holding this man
it's okay Max we can just go your retirement fund go go go go go go go go we can go buy him now
your lipstick is really pretty where are we going Sam now he's on phone White House oh boy
just like getting a free subscription hello got it you got fucking played a lot of these same
folks will say that we're wrong for introducing this federal pudding embargo they envy our
freedom that's not Abraham Lincoln what have they got to hide unless they're secretly sitting
on stockpiles of pudding and oh yes we will find them they've got nothing to be afraid of
so in conclusion America get your back up off the wall dance come on marzipan and good night
it's worse than we thought Max he's crazier than a caffeine-addled dingo in an Adelaide
maternity ward I think he makes a lot of good points those puddings are trying to steal
our jobs and I especially like how he does that spinny thing with his eyes
what the hell by the whiskey looks like a bully from Toy Story mixed with the goosebumps
dummy not crazy he's been hypnotized we've got a snap that's not Abraham Lincoln pronto
how do we do that again we hit him over the head like we do with all hypnotized people
oh yeah that's not Abraham Lincoln hey now that's my super special top secret rib
don't touch it oh my fucking chest I just read something that was just like
take a look at that I love this country a gun and money snow globe this snow globe has a
little Apollo 13 inside what happens when you shake it I'm afraid to find out the liberty
bell is a light for this room liberty bell lamp is a light metaphor is such an ugly quality
and furniture same money again I just did star pillow throw pillows shaped like stars
interesting since actual stars are shaped more like throw pillows there's George Washington
the nutcracker hi I'm George Washington anyone need their nuts cracked please don't
make fun of George Washington is this supposed to be bush no I please don't make fun of
Washington too like that's he's doing one of these a bush is that what it's doing sounds like
it's like a mix of like how many presidents I don't even know there's the national budget
let's take a look at that stand back son that there's the national budget quite a budget
I guess it's three things uh the calendar hands off I want another one of these that's
my presidential calendar wait a minute talk again good day mr president we come in peace
as far as you know oh finally the interpreters where have you been that is a dummy can I look
under the desk or can I look under the desk on where you can live can I go up under the desk
interpreters yeah that is why you fellas are here right sure why I need to meet with one
of them foreign dignitaries always talking that crazy space lane he's not going to have
anything under here and that's the thing guys how could I prove that I have anything
under here either I could be a dummy right now too okay I won't let me grab another one of these
uh it's been I want another I want like another one we got we got we have the long haul tonight
I'm gonna do the whole the whole thing so let me grab a drink I'm thirsty it's a hot day
I'll be right back well that's not covering anything now it is okay uh what happened to
this where did we chat go there we go all right let's play that should be good uh you've
been hypnotized this is probably a good one snap out of it mr president you've been hypnotized
sure I haven't been hypnotized that's crazy talk you've got to listen to us sir or we'll be
forced to take drastic action don't talk to me about drastic action you ever been pinned down
in a drugstore parking lot by a pack of muskrat commandos with nothing left to lose
ever had to gnaw your best buddy's leg off just so you could get a socks and put them
on your own ears to fend off the enemy's deadly sonic regurgitate array now that's
crazy talk I'm impressed I still don't know who this is supposed to be
wake up mr president you've never given up on anything in your life don't start now
that's awful nice of you fellows but I haven't been hypnotized now do we commence with the
head trauma Sam what was that we'll have to get the president you can't do that you can't
make that kind of like you what am I gonna bop him on the head keep a look around the
office mr president you've got to know when to hold them know when to hold them the man's
a genius Sam I almost feel bad for doing this it's for the good of the country max
okay so what do I have for items I want to look under the desk I want to get under the
desk nice globe amazing how often I need it in his job okay let me say that again
amazing how often I need why there's a red camera
it's a stack of pithy campaign slogans campaign slogans don't fool with those
would want to be caught on national tv with my drawers down again magazine representatives
in gardens red versus yellow rose all right I need to talk let me talk to chuckles
hey man do you work here what tipped you off we're freelance police buddy this is a national
emergency and we don't appreciate your sassy mouth auditions for new white house pet down
the hall this can only end in violence hmm this guy's voice sounds familiar do you
recognize him max half the time I don't even recognize you Sam crazy with this
buddy what's behind the door what's behind that door it's a private club for people who
aren't annoying me you two ain't invited should we pummel him together Sam or would
you rather take turns we can create a national security incident after we've saved the
president max shave actually don't think I need to shave that bad you seem familiar
it's the guy from downstairs yeah I'm that voice in the back of your head that tells
you to mind your own business oh my fucking god the surly tone I've got it you're that
pit boss from the toy is he wearing lipstick smell a conspiracy you smell a nosy dog who's
going to get smacked if he don't stop asking questions fucking set on the package that
wasn't going to come off I've got to look good on camera okay I've got to look good
the lighting don't you know actors and performers they put on makeup all the time
I'm fucking furious your favorite actors wear it everybody wears it well be back I can't wait
keep people away looking at it distracting me all right whatever I'm not going to let you guys
fucking bring me down it's a rat president like there are rats in the oval office Sam
you've finally done it a straight line so easy even I won't touch it is that PBR why the
fuck would I be drinking PBR good presentable okay well he's taking you guys this long to
figure that out these plates commemorate the core values of freedom loving peoples everywhere
eating a lot and hitting things with sticks exactly drinking PBR is less believable than
lipstick what wait what what's going on over here what did she say what did she say
what did she say well I didn't see what she said what did she say no no
I just needed to enhance all right I need to pay attention no I don't want I don't want to put
a full face of makeup on on my face right now I've got enough collagen I've got plenty
of collagen I don't need it all right I could have been so talking about my appearance
what do I have the boxing glove the bug should I go over here
I think I'm gonna say anything weird let's pick them up okay here's what he said well
don't that beat all hey Chuckles check this out when you fold the dollar bill this way
it makes him look like he's Putin thank you sir like Vladimir Putin or like pooing
which one I didn't read the dialogue all right so he's not going to listen Mr. President
who are you we have to intercept the meeting if I know they show up and start jabbering away
about treaties and whatnot I just let the interpreters figure it out I just keep an
eye on them to make sure they don't steal something or try to eat the cat
okay you're under arrest freelance police you're under arrest freelance police now there's the
kind of can-do vigilante attitude that makes America strong finally someone who appreciates
our greater calling okay we'll be back sir so I have access to I have access to the room here
I think I don't think I can do anything else here unless there's something I can do with
the boxing glove punch something break something trophy picture I'm not gonna no is there like
a seat okay war room door we can go this way no one enters the war room that's it you two
are coming with me why didn't we just listen and stay out now I have to get back to the
president he's not supposed to be alone excuse me oh god oh welcome governor whizzer the
president has been waiting for you governor whizzer is still on hold than a washed up
urination loving former child star no one hello this is the white house hello all right
so whizzer is the all right let me go I'm going back in no sir I said soda abuse it's a very
important issue soda candy no comprende son but I'm speaking English ah are you two fellas the
interpreters it's about time darned this thing we just had a couple imposters in here
you had ringers for you too were they walking around examining everything engaging everyone in
pointless it's like I drink a bunch of kool-aid that was a cursed clones
help me out with this here potent hey would you can't understand a dang word
but that doesn't make sense I don't even have an accent wine mouth no momento por favor
you impatient little guy ain't he all right what's new whizzer that's governor whizzer
thank you very much all right what are you doing here governor to the oval office
I'm trying to build up nationwide support for the mr sap who's mr sap and why didn't you want me
to know you were talking about I can spell you know it's the mount rushmore soda abuse
prevention program it's totally changed my life I've been carbonation free for over four
weeks now tell us about the mr sap be brief I started the mount rushmore soda abuse prevention
program after I became governor to help people get flat like me but if we can't get federal
funding people all over the dakotas are going to get right back on the pop I don't work eight
hours a day six days a week just to throw my money away for some washed up soda junkies
with no sense of self-control you don't have any money max oh right never mind good luck
with that whiz all right we're ready to interpret we're ready to interpret for you don't tell me
the president needs the interpreter what did he say sam I'm speaking english I don't even
have an accent can't understand a word see you around wizard hello mr president
what do I want from the store uh pbr don't buy that I don't want that in my house I don't
want that in my fucking house if it crosses the plane I'll get itchy I'll be like scratching
it I'll break out in hives he doesn't want it with a mouse he doesn't want it with his spouse
Kim and I are not married I will not drink it in the living room I will not share it with a
broom no pb and r do not buy it from the store that beer sure is a snore we'll be back sir
out out do not like mr president we're ready to interpret for you all right let's get this
party started mr president my fellow Americans I come to warn you about a serious epidemic
facing our country the scourge of soda abuse nice jawline any former pop heads like myself
found ourselves in the endless cycle of addiction and elimination until we believed there was no
hope I don't know what you're saying son but you're selling it boy good job I asked you
I thought we were interpreting long can this epidemic continue what was that he said
what oh what about the store hmm what do I want from the store what do you guys think
should get from the store well what do I want okay um hmm broccoli so yeah broccoli is not
a bad okay broccoli like a head of broccoli um cheese it's that's a good one too cheese it's
hmm um I think uh a I don't know why but I kind of want one of those grocery store
I've been sitting here on the display for three days sandwiches at the deli you know the ones
that are wrapped up and rolled up to a point where they're squished looks like somebody sat
on it in the subway just popped into my brain and I wanted it but don't buy that don't bring
that into my house I will not eat that with a fan I will not bring that sandwich to land
that's a gamer reference for you guys that will pay attention to that one I need to play
the game is what needs to happen all right um what do I actually want from the store
I'll get it um get like cheese it's maybe some chips
Doritos with the regular just regular nacho Doritos and that's I think that's good
I got sunflower seeds already all right don't make fun before liking Doritos
Doritos are fucking unbelievable did people like to make fun of Doritos but you eat them
all the time I know it's like the joke it's it's the thing Doritos and Mountain Dew Mountain
Dew is gross but Doritos are great they are unbelievably good Mountain Dew they should just
convert all those factories instead of producing Mountain Dew they should be producing I don't
know sustainable seafood I think whatever they do there no more Mountain Dew all right so
there I figured out what I wanted from the store Kim she's probably not even fucking here
anymore Kim I think what would be great if you got us a couple pieces of salmon
is she still in the chat yeah she's right there she's right there salmon sounds great
we took us a while to get there but get like a few pieces of salmon we'll make it
we'll make it later tonight awesome thank you everybody say thanks to Kim she's gonna go get
us PBR lipstick um Doritos salmon and that's pretty much it what's a guy gotta do to get a
drink around here aha I know what you need and ice cold orange sugar fizz I swear by
no that's not what I want at all I must resist but I am I got some ice cold PBR in here
frosty cold and so delicious I'm gonna be careful when I start thinking about PBR
they were about to give me my five-week pin I almost feel bad about this I don't have a
conscience Sam I'm not gonna do it don't worry everyone's freaking out that's pretty good
oh blessed angels of carbonation fill me with your syrupy nectar
yeah now I'm not so much guilty as repulsed keep it coming more I need more I need I need a
bathroom which way is the bathroom the war room which way is the war room which way is the
war room it's that door right over there but I don't thank you where do you think you're
knock them over wizard I've got to get in there bad we've got a priority red number two here in
the oval office no it's just number one escorting the suspect to holding cell
for interrogation now we can go in there come with me sir but it'll only take a second
please let me go that was fun okay and I didn't catch all that what did he say
I want a big book like that imagine a big ass book with a huge quill and you just write
whatever you want in there it doesn't even matter it could be the grocery list we're only as you
can tell our grocery list is only five items long so I would be so awesome to write the
five items huge like President Jefferson did I think the war room door is your list of bad
stupid old piece open it what are you talking about open the door punch it punch it can I put
the bug in there a big book of spells hello mr president that was spells were real how cool
would that be okay so what we'll be back sir now that I got rid of that guy in the room
with I don't understand what the point of that was no and I want to talk about like
dangerous spells like a fireball no that's scary electricity lightning bolt no no no
I'm not talking about you know being able to put a being able to fly or something put a spell
the ribbon hey now that's my super special top secret ribbon don't touch it there are so many
others there are now it's time for some checks and balances freelance police style
max will you do the honors gladly look at those little tadpoles cut to them in jail they
just don't make these guys like I knew it was fake that's no guy max it's a damn dougley puppet
ah the drawstring in his back I told her I'm going to go under the desk and look
should have been the swirly eyes what's silly me I thought hypnotize E not hypnotizer what
yes an ingenious device being used to hypnotize the tv watching public but who was
controlling him gonna take days to get that smell out of the interrogation room what what
have you done it was like that when we got here sam did it he tripped and hit the bumpers
head on the table these two numbskulls managed off the president it was a deep tissue massage
gone horribly wrong ninjas sam did it still ratings from the last state of the union
address were even lower than reruns of midtown cowboys I didn't expect to have to replace
the president so soon but now that these idiots are forced by hand we're standing
right here you can hear everything you're saying it's time for a leader the people will have to
listen to me agents jackson bird and again babe we are moving the timeline forward commence phase
two of the operation I'll prepare the new candidate oh it is Abraham Lincoln quite the
reaction I would have expected from a secret service agent discovering two people over
the decapitated body of the president what do you think this fake body is made of can I keep
no time for that now max we've got to stop the what's gonna be in the closet next episode
what is that noise oh she's huge she's not gonna be able to sit in there
blessed scuba diving buddha on a banana boat with cocktail onions and a map to the star's
homes yeah they've reanimated America's most beloved president I always thought
Taft was shorter not Taft you deficient my fellow Americans I am Abraham as you know by now
your president was recently murdered by two mysterious interpreters what I am not to fear
and despair I have returned to guide us through this troubled time a vote for me is a vote for
Abraham Lincoln I'll get it what's that we've had this talk before Lincoln Memorial right
hydraulic motors and robotic implants yes okay George Washington we're on it Abraham Lincoln
that was the commissioner max if this new amendment wins the emergency election the
nefarious forces controlling him will have unchecked power to destroy the entire free world
I hate when they do that that's why one of us is going to have to run against him
you got to answer the phone okay fair's fair max we're going to make you the next president
of the United States yes we're seeing this episode I'm not going to say it but never mind but
yeah like that every single president that is supposed to be from over 200 years ago or
100 years ago or more always has this voice I'm George Washington I'm Abraham Lincoln
I'm Thomas Jefferson I'm Andrew Jackson I'm Ronald Reagan see they all sounded like that
but they didn't if you if you did the Abraham Lincoln actually had a high voice it was more
like this it was actually kind of like this and if you've seen the Daniel Day Lewis version
is as he did it the way that it was supposed to be looking or this is like two or three
documented cases of Abraham Lincoln talking he wasn't like this breaking my version I'm deleting
the fucking game but that's actually true that's a I'm not making that up it's real
this is like the five percent time when I'm saying something real Mr. Lincoln as a candidate
for office my pal max would like to engage in a thoughtful discussion of the key issues
followed by a round of spikeful Lincoln or Thanos hmm I see well this is a bit irregular
as you're well aware I'm the most beloved president in history so I just assumed I'd be
running unopposed oh no you didn't you ain't all that I freed the slave I was star of a
popular television sitcom I'm on the penny I was on TV now gentlemen we can resolve this
like adults through moderate reason debate very well then in the spirit of democracy I say
bring it and it's a beautiful day on the White House lawn as we bring you the first in a series
of debates for this emergency election for US presidents in the Republican corner we have the
giant animated statue of Abraham Lincoln and representing the random violence and destruction
party there is the hyperkinetic rabbit like creature known as Max acting as completely
impartial moderator for the debates will be Sam the candidates are ready so let's listen in
there'd be so much taller than the microphone let's talk about the issues the nation demands
family values let's hear your prepared statement time out my fellow Americans warm the crowd up
with a joke I'm gonna treat this like if it is if it was me okay I'd come out there
with the cuffs undone you know like cuffs undone shirt undone you know like as if I
just was dancing at a wedding for 30 minutes right you know I'm talking about when you go
to a wedding and you get all dressed up and you're stiff as a board and then you the first
two songs of the wedding all of a sudden people's ties are undone their shirts are open and their
their cups are off so we're talking like two or three songs into wedding is what I would be
presenting myself at and I warm it up with a joke reminds me of a droll story it seems
Chester A Arthur and the Pope were kayaking down the Amazon one day suddenly a tiny candiru
fish swims up the Pope's and lodges itself in his Arthur grabs the Pope's pliers and swelled up
like a melon and the Pope says thanks last time that happened McKinley wanted no wait wait wait
I think I told it wrong I wouldn't have done that uh I believe in uh I believe in a uh in a
globalist community I I am the one true I am the no uh let's talk about the issues Mr.
Lincoln I'd like you to tell the voters your stand on some of the tough issues very well
how do you plan to solve the problem of toxic wastes where you stand on schools education's
really important taxes we got to talk about we got to talk about taxes too what are you
going to do about our schools where do you stand on religion and schools
I'm glad that I've been given one more life to give for my country Lincoln pulls out his
trusted catchphrase for this election which delights the crowd but seems to have no effect
on the polls I'm supposed to be winning read my lips read my lipstick presentable on stream
greetings miserable pro you're not gonna win I'm here to save the country your day of reckoning
is at hand you're gonna lose max stall for time how would you describe your tax plan how
would you describe your tax plan I'm glad that I've been given one more life to give for my
country and Lincoln dodges the question by pulling out his trusty campaign slogan which
places the crowd but has no effect on the polls god damn can't spit it out I was gonna it was
something solid in there and I'm pretending like I'm not gonna freak out about that
um I was waiting for him to say like a tax percentage and I was gonna like
I wasn't really gonna do it I'm not gonna ruin my computer what do you think crazy
I believe in the ideal of a global community where America is but a small part we must set
aside our differences and work with our fellow nations all united towards one goal
the complete and utter annihilation of the godless Belgians I mean that gets a dog tilt that gets
a dog head tilt for me what I want to see you return to prosperity to see a return to the
prosperity of the America we once knew a chicken in every pot and vice versa a pot in
every chicken how do you plan to solve the problem of toxic waste I'm glad that I've been given
one more life to give for my country and Lincoln is once again using his trusted campaign slogan
which is all right in the crowd but having no effect on his pole we we gotta we gotta
fuck with that slogan if elected I promise a return to a happier time in America's path
the days when giant thunder lizards marched over the fern-covered marshes of the Midwest
preying on the upstart mammals that's why I don't have face cam on because I just tried to
swallow that burp and it was gonna be loud and I tried I like to be I like to perform
but I don't like to be watched why don't they bring Sam and Max back is it still going am I
just an idiot and making the am I do I have like one piece of the puzzle of knowledge here
if it does tell to tell tell own the characters or was I thought this was like a series before
that well it wasn't this is like a an old point and click adventure game wasn't it
yeah there's like a comic book series an old old point and click game yeah LucasArts made
the first one right I'm a uniter not a divide I foresee an America under one rule
it's a bush thing iron fisted rule one rabbit one law I'm united let your neighbors know that
dissent will not be tolerated all hail max I mean what am I supposed to do about this
do we just see every option what I have a dream America how do we like progress this out
where I'm in an all nude production of death of a salesman on ice but I haven't studied
and I can't remember my lines suddenly it begins to rain marshmallows but that's okay
because trees are made of graham crackers and chocolate bars are the official currency
I believe that by working together we can make that dream a reality all right well that's all
stay frosty America cue cards it's the cue cards for Lincoln speak oh I'm glad that I've
been given one more life to give from my country I'm glad that I have one more life
to give from my country I could do a pretty good audiobook Lincoln I think or any ex-president
from like 1840 to like 1930 I could do any president what does it say now don't make a
right I'm glad that I've been given one more life to two wrongs don't make a right I could
probably put something here don't I could probably like I could probably Ron Burgundy or something
right definitely where do I get these cue cards from that I need to replace it's the severed
head of the president I yearn to hold it aloft and turn giant sea atrocities to stone
you're thinking of Medusa's head oh yeah I always get those two heads confused
why don't I mouthwash commercials are stupid that's all I have to say I'm going where we
going Sam I don't think I don't think I can do anything in here let's go back back to the office
shotgun thanks for your contribution you got it anytime wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
there's what about Sybil let's go talk to Sybil I'm there are bugs in my fucking hair
there are bugs everywhere let's go talk to Sybil don't I don't use mouthwash I don't
really use that I mean mouthwash really isn't that actually good for you it just burns and
did they don't get like the alcohol mouthwash it just burns all the fucking germs in your mouth
even good bacteria too it kills everything hey Sybil what's new in the world of frequent
random career reassessment hi fellas I'm really excited I found the perfect job for me you
don't say that's right I Sybil Pandemic am now a professional matchmaker matchmaker I thought
I smelled that joke coming down the turnpike burning oil and dragging its muffler it's a
dating service Max I figured that if a smart successful career woman like me could be having
so much trouble finding a date there must be plenty of other people who could use help
you can't get a date you're having trouble finding your soul mate you don't know the
half of it it seems like all the guys I meet are total losers losers no offense none taken
hey or else they're borderline psychopaths no offense men taken it's the borderline cases
you have to watch out for could you find dates for find dates for do we actually go on dates
I mean sure why not stranger things have happened they must have somewhere I'm choosing
not to be offended by that what do we need to do it's easy just submit an application
an application okay what kind of man are they looking what kind of man are you looking for
older men guys with a little history to them are such a turn on oh and tall men
and distinguished and he should be experienced all right enough already yes I will go out with
you civil I thought she was talking about me what kind of stuff is on this application
the usual your best traits and what kind of person you're looking for hooks for hands
hooks for hands when you're done I'll put the application into my computer which analyzes your
personality matrix at 15 personality test I don't have a personality matrix so much as a
personality factor once we found a match you call your date and agree on a time and place
let me help you guys out tell me your good points and what you're looking for in a date
what am I looking for in a date I'm very spiritual she should have an air of mystery
she should love animals yeah spiritual have an air of mystery she didn't love animals
that's the point that's the drake finger there she should love animals such as the elusive
praying mantis who's deadly but enthralling mating rituals she mimics you really know how
to ruin the mood max oh and cybernetic implants like an elbow that can connect to
the internet that exists now max don't know if you know that uh she should be tall she
should be tall I guess at least 12 feet or four meters if she's Canadian I'm very spiritual
a disciple of the ancient ones enacting dark magic rituals to bring forth their rain again
upon this earth rise shigaraat that's massive yeah 12 feet tall she's her head's gonna be
dragging against the ceiling you're gonna have to like push them you're gonna have to get
behind them and like wedge them in it's gonna be like
on the top of the ceiling I have an active I need an active lifestyle yeah always running
from the authorities how drunk are you I don't know how drunk am I why am I hiding the why
am I hiding the brand oh no hold on a second I gotta be careful they might dox the brand
they're gonna dox me from like the brand it's like grocery store I can appreciate a person's
inner beauty I can appreciate a person's inner beauty I even have my own sonogram machine
put a brown bag on it it could be anything though that's all I can think of oh that's
plenty now I'll just put your applications into the computer and there it is it says your
perfect match is cybernetic laser eyes oh please oh please oh please well that's interesting
it says your perfect match is Sam disturbing and yet somehow not completely unexpected
and Sam your ideal soulmate is Abraham Lincoln wait for it Max well there goes another blow
to the concept of a fair and just universe hey Sam what do you say we never ever speak
of this again way ahead of you little buddy see you around symbol okay well there's the thing
12 feet tall that's pretty big the scary face how that's where I do video intros for my
dating service why is the door locked it's locked damn it I don't even have a key to
that door the casting room um well all right so I'm so sick of this shit okay let's go
I thought I just could hit by the car the game is too loud
fuck man I'll turn it down all right let's go let's go see boss go we haven't done that
hey free home delivery sign the sign's not free but oh my book is it's this guy it's Hugh Bliss
whoa look Max it's our favorite cultish crackpot Jubeless hi I'm Hugh Bliss I want to buy something
take my credit card put me on your mailing list anyone you want me to recruit you're
supposed to get the stockholm syndrome a few days to kick in Max who has that kind of time
okay so what are you doing here what's a big so why are you here now like you doing on our street
you bliss why I'm spreading the great news about prismatology the magic and science of
unlocking the harmony of colors for a revolution in holistic personal and interpersonal well-being
now translated into 15 000 different languages including esperanto hooray hooray that's that's
that's just Mickey that's current voice Mickey he's doing the kingdom hearts three Mickey
I can't tell the difference the book's selling well selling you can't put a price on imagination
you can't sell the wonder of a daydream or the laughter of a child he's right I've tried
do you have any magic tricks show us a magic trick you bliss magic is easy when the colors
of your soul yeah yeah less chatter more magic unless you're so mad how about
I disappear well your mind reading is obviously still working it is now watch me as I vanish
except you won't be able to watch me because I'll be gone um I need to do something here
it's gotta be okay I could there's gotta be something I can do there during that
but with an item or something probably something hey a free home delivery sign
the sign's not free but oh my book is oh yes it is it's free thank you boys hi can you disappear
again I want to figure out how you did it it's easy Sam I take all the colors from my
surroundings and spin them into a great big okay yeah I was just being polite he's so pale
not me I'm red let's take that free sign wait is this a cue card home delivery sign
can I make Abe Lincoln say free home delivery is that what this is for
why would he need to say that novelty gumballs shaped just like the real thing
but made of inedible plastic huge brain will your friends annoy your grandparents
all right let's see what Bosco is doing now what does Bosco up to
I did this thing it's bad I'm not going to say it because I don't want to encourage
anybody to do it ah greetings comrades dog and rabbit I'm having trouble placing the
accent this month mid-atlantic states the San Fernando Valley hmm I get more of a vague
baltic vibe something in the light check pattern ha ha comrade makes a million makes the funny joke
I am Vladimir Ilyich Boskovsky Russian proprietor of workers glorious warehouse of
inconvenience no no but now I make new start in America which I love so is no need to aim
in sophisticated targeting equipment at me so what's the what's the deal this time
what's with the soviet block Bosco he's perfectly natural comrades I work with your
American government in spirit of glass nose they know they know who knows what the feds
man uncle Sam the government's watching us all the time so that's why I always feel an
overbearing presence just out of my field of vision watching and judging my every move
that's me Max what's that smell in here smells like fermented hate it's like sweaty jackstraps
soaked in boiled cabbage with a dash of sulfur keep it down guys you're scaring off the other
customers who what other customers never even in here Max and I are always the only ones in
here it's good thing merchandise is always available coming in here is like visiting old
friends some of these cereal boxes are from the McKinley administration
I carved our initials in one of the weenies so we'll be best friends forever Sam
all right you need some new weenies when's the last time you cleaned out the weenie rotisserie
needs no cleaning it's vintage flavor to tasty phrase well all right why are you getting
on you Bosco I don't know for what maybe it's because I know too much
um what are you number the poor guy Max but I make new start in America which I love so
there's no need to target in me okay suppose you've got some where's the defense this time
usually has something against their heads is the people comrades workers will overthrow fascist
regime what about us loafers over the hot dogs the school lunch come day of victory workers
will unite to bring downfall of corrupt administration they will all we will number
in tens of millions that's a lot of Bolsheviks no he's all through plus I'm working on a satellite
missile defense system a missile defense system missile defense system isn't that more than a
little bit overkill yet we are strong like bear against the pack I'm working on modifying
part your anti-delivery system that's right it was already programmed to keep people from
delivering goods to the store so I just went into the database and changed beef jerky to
intercontinental ballistic missiles so now anyone can just deliver a blimp load of beef jerky to
your store without fear of reprisal it's small price to pay for freedom yeah I remember the
hot dogs and in school for some weird reason I don't know why this was but why are all
school lunch hot dogs cut like four times they slice it apart down the middle apart on the
right upon the left they fray out the I don't know why they did that they didn't do that
in your school they like cut them up down the middle like three or four times they would get
they frayed out that nobody had no they didn't do that anywhere else so they don't
explode in the microwave that's only done for boiled hot dogs well they there you go
we aren't that old we aren't no now that I got the wrong vocal context there it's not
we're not that old it's we're not that old oh right okay sometimes you can change the way
that we change the way that sentence works by changing a little bit of inflection all right
tell us about the missile defense about that missile defense system again I'm working on
modifying btaz pot I know I'm old once I get funding for it it'll be able to shoot down
any ICBMs targeted at the school okay so he's going to want to build a defense system
who is no threat to glorious American government whatsoever
Wheaties what do you got anything new in here something I can do microwave
should I put a hot dog in here now I want a hot dog great idea involving you a microwave
fuck man go on maybe another time I want a I want a Chicago dog you know I'm talking about
you do I know you do you just fucking raised your hand you went yes he fucking said Chicago
dog I'm talking directly to you not anybody else here only you there's only the that's
the only people talk to right now you want a dog from Chicago I want a Chicago style dog
look it up see what that means all right I think we're good here I can go back to
I want to go to the office make one it's not complicated I I but I I'm I'm currently here
all right hey I'll see you later I'm gonna go back I don't have my stream deck hooked up
never mind I'll be back in like 30 minutes I'm gonna go make a fucking Chicago hot dog
he's looking at if I can buy something uh I will I let me just go in order and we'll
clean it up uh you know what I love I shouldn't be talking about this I love hot
dogs on the grill when you leave them on for way too long on one of those fucking freaks
that when the you know your uncle's on the grill and they've got 20 30 hot dogs lined up
they're all on just two racks right and they just forget about three of them people come up
yeah you want a dog yeah I take one or whatever barbecue you go to everyone gets a
dog and then there's like three that are just left sitting there just rotting and they turn
black I love those so much the whole thing around is just black it's unbelievable call me
weird if you want that's fine it's just charred completely I love it it's so good I don't eat
that often though because it's yeah it's really it's really not that good for you at all
all right is there anything in here I can do and a very disturbed individual sits here
bulletin board when I got this thing I thought it would be useful burnt is not a flavor yeah it
is um extra toasty cheez-its will have to disagree with you on that I was one of those
people I was one of those people on Facebook that that demanded it you know they said oh
by popular demand we have a box of toasty cheez-its burnt cheez-its I was the popular
demand toasted not burnt I like the burnt ones I don't think that's that weird I don't
think there's anything in here I don't think there's anything else what about in the waste
basket nothing useful in here charcoal it's oh I don't like that with hamburgers I like that
only with hot dogs though um I don't think there's anything else in here old case files
ah yes I remember that case particular 20 years worth of electric bills take up a surprising
amount of space okay well let's go back to Bosco and see what uh if I can buy something
from what I can buy this time you like flat root beer too I don't really like that much
carbonated stuff I mean I'm drinking a seltzer water right now but that's just because
uh the only reason why this is in the fridge is because I had family over and you need
something right I had a bunch of family come over and I didn't want to be the child that
has mountain dude coke and vodka in his fridge so I got like seltzers and
juices I wanted to look at least half responsible what hey Bosco
I like soda I don't drink it that much anymore years ago I used to drink it all the time
we want to buy something that is evil but necessary private enterprise
what do you got what do you got is most glorious invention comrades cider is useful for
how you say questioning questioning is true serum makes easy even the most difficult
how you say interrogation interrogation well true serum is this another one of your half-baked
overpriced gimmicks or does it actually work both will make anyone get rid of inhibitions
and telling how you say complete and honest it's gonna be alcohol your accent sucks it's
gonna be vodka it's gonna be vodka it's the russian thing it's gonna be a bottle of vodka
we'd like that truth serum comrade boscovich is good price is eight six seven point five
three oh nine rubles how much is that in real money 100 million dollars I think your rate of
exchange is a little off boscovorsky fall of berlin wall brings great strength to our economy
100 million isn't that a little pricey for truth serum is bargain it really does work and
I haven't even tried it yet sam this morning I used your toothbrush results are guarantee
I used it to clean out my ears this is refreshing that's not that bad I would still
use it I need the money to complete my satellite defense system I needed to clean out my ears
because I've been rummaging for okay I've heard enough I still you know I would still use that
but you that's not that bad it could have been it could be way worse that could have been
much worse that would be terrible if it was anywhere else nothing for us
we'll catch you on flip side come on red dog in the rabbit earwax is weird and gross but
it's not like somebody's shoving a toothbrush a suck it's not somebody shoving a toothbrush
whatever what's on the shelf is it bread foamy bread made from real styrofoam no artificial
styrofoam artificial styrofoam somebody putting a toothbrush in their ear you can rinse that
and it's not gonna you're not gonna freak out about that somebody's shoving a toothbrush
somewhere else you you would never use it again I would say oh I brushed my eye with your
toothbrush it's like oh that's weird but it's like kind of gross and weird but I'll just
clean it with hot water and I'll sanitize it with alcohol that's what that's not that's
not that big of a problem where are we going Sam earwax is not water soluble you need another
solvent which is probably toxic okay okay the chat full of scientists I've already up
off to the white house oh boy that's shitting grin it's back that's fucking funny it's not
water soluble so you're gonna be putting earwax in your mouth all right I need uh let's go
back in here wait can I go in here now white paint Christmas lights and a small barbecue
everything somebody would need to renovate decorate and then accidentally burn the place
to the ground that's my favorite comment of the entire day I that's so great just calling me out
on my bullshit I love it all right is there anything else in here I'm gonna go replace this
I have a sign so let's see if I can do a camera there's nothing in here I'm slouching
so bad did I miss anything in here no if you can see the whole the whole cam right now
blind blind blind blind blind what did I mean what all right I I thought I thought this was part of
the I thought it was part of the stack of pithy cameras for a second I'm not blind here
thousand points of light and I did not have sex with that one what did he have sex with
you good I'm glad that I've been given one more yeah man I'm good my country
I did not have sex with that woman how are you doing that doing what dude free home delivery
all right so what we got I'm glad that I've been given one more life to give no they all gotta be
bad two wrongs don't make a right I want to see if I can still do it could I still do it
I haven't tried I haven't tried to do the one eye thing in a long long time
earwax is weird and gross but it's not like this is not even the thing I was
one eye going was it did it work okay just making sure it worked so I need um I need another card
because there's three here I did not have sex with that woman that's the one I'm gonna leave
there all right let's try again let's just see what happens it's time for another in this
ongoing series of debates between Abraham Lincoln and Max we turn you over to our impartial
moderator Sam all right let's talk about the issues contestants it's time for our lightning
round mr Lincoln I'm going to name some of the tough issues facing our country today
I'd like you to sum up your stand on those issues in a few concise words well all right
I'm afraid this will have to be completely off the top of my head as I have nothing prepared
where do you stand on religion and schools I did not have sex with that woman whoa the
debate is taken on a decidedly confessional tone with that nonsensical reply from candidate
Lincoln luckily for him the crowd is ignoring it we have nothing to fear but fear itself
and the chupacabra madre de dios he'll kill us all all right hold on that is all
what what did the other ones say a thousand points of light thousand points of light the
buck stops here stops here free home delivery free home delivery I'm glad that I've been
no not that one two wrongs don't mean I did not have sex with that woman not that one
a thousand points a thousand points of light let's do the home delivery one the buck stops
free home delivery okay free home delivery let's talk about the issues how do you plan
to solve the problem of toxic waste free home delivery the problem of toxic waste
free home delivery oh an effective but very controversial proposal from candidate Lincoln
and the crowd did not like that idea one bit didn't like it what oh that's they got
a ralph nader joke in there all right um I'm glad that I so what was the thousand points
of light two wrongs don't I need another card maybe I think I did not I don't know okay anyway
right now let's get this one correct the nation is family values mr Lincoln perhaps you'd like
to speak about the importance of family values of course a strong family unit is the rock upon
which our society is built it's easy today in this age of your blinged out horseless carriages
and racy daguerreotype magazines to believe that honesty and fidelity are outdated concepts
but I stand proud I have been completely faithful to my lover Mary Todd for over seven
scores I did not have sex with that woman I've never even looked at another woman
so let's hear your statement I mr Lincoln could you elaborate on your stand on family values
without a strong honest and faithful family nothing we are faithful to my wife for 150 years
mr Lincoln the networks are looking for a sound bite would you care to share a few words
with us thank you this is a date that will be remembered for centuries to come today is the
day we return America to greatness I stand here at the steps of the White House not above
this is not what I've written only one man can lead the nation through this troubled time
I Abraham Lincoln and read the cue card the time to act is now thank you
I said basically the same thing he didn't read the cue card hold on time out I'm drunk with
power but it just goes right through me I did not have sex with that woman I did not have
sex with my wife mr Lincoln without a strong hundred tax plan religion in schools that's it
keep them tax plan I don't I think I what is there an issue I can even respond to for
time out oh well I thought I had to like bring new ones into because the again these are just
here of life okay so one of these will work the buck stops here your tax plan the buck
stops here religion and schools free home delivery I'm glad that two wrongs don't make
a right religion and schools where do you stand on religion and schools two wrongs don't make a
right did we hear that right I don't want religion or schools wow so a thousand points
of light is what your tax plan the reason why I wasn't using these is because I thought
I had to get more sex with that woman I thought these are just here by default to have some
points of light something to look at you know I thought I had to go get them stops here
was your tax plan how would you describe your tax plan the buck stops what does a
thousand points of light mean by that so it looks like yes the American people have decided
to ignore it hmm that's a thousand points of light time out free home delivery for tax plan
I'm glad that I'm not sure I can do this I'm missing other cards though valet parking two
dollars valet parking two dollars way to knock down that deficit suspect yourself taxes no
I need another one of those stands mailbox ornamental post no bills post no I'm surprised
please do not feed the submarine what can you what what anyway nothing what are you guys
talking about what are you guys talking about room program I guess the country really is hard
up for cash he's being stupid what I what I don't think there's any more over here
on the stage over behind here flyer nothing back here no I need to find another cue card
stand somewhere there's definitely not one in the office that the white house because I just
was in there it's definitely back here it's not in there where are we going Sam it's not it's
not it's not it's not it's not he doesn't know pepe laugh what kind of noise do you
think that pepe laugh is doing is it even laughing or is it going like go in the dumpster I once
hidden that dumpster to escape a rampaging I still don't know how she got out of the office
I was sure I locked the door I don't know what it's doing but not that is it I can't I can't
see it so I don't know what it looks like now yeah I can no that's not even the right one
I have bt tv all right I need a fucking flyer in here president appoints action figure as
secretary of defense that is pretty crazy well at least it was an action figure of john shaft
oh I can dig it non-mafia owned casino destroyed by a mysterious explosion mysterious
I gave my name to reporters and even posed for pictures you guys I have it blowing something I
already own it I've got bt tv I'm not missing any cards well what do I have to do how and how
do I do the tax plan one what are you talking about we'll go back here oh I can go in here
lefties lefties power tools spend the bottle championship is coming up I like when they do
the sudden death round with the molotov cocktails why is he pronouncing it bt tv
how would you pronounce it lefties tool rental shop is still vacant remember that afternoon
when I put on a baseball cap and spent hours out here playing fizzball with lefty if you mean
that night when you put on a hockey mask and spent hours chasing lefty down the street that's
how it's said yeah precious what am I doing wrong none of these do anything give me all
you got it's the army's new recruiting slogan that's a lot better than their old one what
are you chicken gonna cry now baby tax plan give me all you got budget for quality adhesives
oh my god it only took him like an hour to figure this out right he doesn't know where we going
sam do you feel in charge we're off to the white house yes oh he doesn't have the
information he lacks information his face is shaped like a banana and he doesn't have
information all right let's put this last one on and let's get uh let's sink them two wrongs
don't make a right get on there give me all you got there it is how would you describe your tax
plan give me all you got and candidate linkage with one shocker of an economic strategy
which even democrats are calling a trifle excessive that had to have hurt him in the
pole flies up good how am i beating how did ralph nader get 21 percent
that wasn't even close to what really happened um so what do i do now please do not feed the
shots um i need one percent can you max just say something interesting and we can go from
there no you guys see how strong i am i don't usually do this on stream but i'll do it now
back to the office shotgun i'm gonna fucking crush this can on my head
i'm as a party trick i haven't done this shit in a long time
uh let's go see simple old material there's a bunch of people that i hear that i know
what like a stand-up comic does the same act for like two years you know that right when
you go see um when you go see who's a famous comedian that's cool right now that people
watch i don't know but they do the same material for like two years and they redo
jokes they make new material after a couple of years when you go to see dane cook at madison
square garden he's doing the same show that he did a year ago in fucking tampa this this
3300 people here at least 100 of those are from tampa so it's they haven't seen it yet
hey civil how goes the dating game computer generated love is in the air
okay uh what are you looking for on a date what are you looking for in a date again
i would love to meet a tall older man with a good career that sounds like abraham tall lincoln
how does this dating service work again people submit applications listing their good traits
and what they're looking for once we found a match you call your date and agree on a time
in place what's next on the career horizon next this is it yeah guys job and helping
people find their yeah i ain't going i ain't playing another game today good point i'll
stick sorry business though how many couples have you managed to escort to romantic bliss
so far none none is the loneliest i want to do the application things will start
to pick up after the holidays all that stress makes for a lot of messy breakups
and a lot of people looking for romance on the rebound i hate watching we have something to look
forward to what the fuck man it's all right see you later see you later man take care man
sorry didn't live up to your expectations and shit how's business slow right now but those
applications are going to do i want to do an application any moment how do i do an application
see you around sir oh there you boys want to try the dating scene again no thanks just drop an
application in there if you change your mind application where are they huh huh what did i
help me out here uh didn't didn't she give it to me solve it on your own
romance is a lot like this cactus sharpen prickly at first but worth the effort for
the miracle of life at its core i was thinking more fake and unappealing but you know what's
wrong with the cactus who's playing this game me or you me and sometimes you sometimes but mostly
me though okay here's what she said what she said meter made yeah movie industry executive
done that already hey this looks good shuttle pre-flight analyst oh it's part-time only thank
you sir okay so where do i get an application i already took it but i didn't turn on the click
maps no no no no you boys want to no thanks just drop an application in there i gotta do an
application romance is a lot like this cactus ear problems sharpen prickly at first but worth
the effort for the me i was thinking more fake and unappealing but your application they
agreed to never speak again yeah but don't how how do i get one to for somebody else
print up any titillating no oops shit i have to get one more percent of the vote federal
offense punishable fine and imprisonment as we found out after the incident with the garden
hose ah memories can't go down the sewer let's go talk to lincoln where are we going sam
we're off to the white house oh boy germans really getting his money worth in dollars per hour
hey according to how long to beat these each or two hours each we've been going for
three hours i've got about 40 minutes or so to beat this one plus i by the way i've been
pausing like this and talking about dentists and stuff so added like another 30 40 minutes
and i like to take my time i like to look at stuff uh-oh chat's getting restless
better drink a pbr that is all it's lincoln's campaign flyer i want you honest dedicated
over a century of experience abraham lincoln is your man
where are we going back to the office shotgun found it i can't go back i wanted like a bad
posturing fucking all right so we're gonna drop this in the box and then
sybil's gonna fall in love with abraham lincoln and then we get to ask about family values
which means i'm in love with abraham lincoln and i would love to have him cheat on his wife
with me right hey sybil how goes the dating game computer generated love is in the air
see you around sybil got a flyer this a new application yeah it's uh for a friend of ours
let's see not the abraham lincoln he's tall distinguished loves the theater he sounds perfect
nobody else has that name back chump doesn't have half my cute fluffy marketability hey what's
going on i think your computer can find him a date internet computer nothing this guy sounds
perfect for me oh but he didn't leave his phone number next time you see him give him my number
i'd love to meet him okay give your number to abraham lincoln okay so now we talk hey
lincoln here's a phone number for you hey sybil no all right i got the phone number for
abraham lincoln to go back what's her number i don't know i have no idea i'm implying that
where are we going sam we're off to the white house let's go see i want something to drink
but i don't want to drink alcohol all right anything i can get from you here let's hear it
we found you a woman mr lincoln we've picked out a single lady friend who would be just
perfect for you she has a job and still has all her own teeth let me give you her number
so you can give her a call ain't no reanimated president too big to appreciate a booty call
know what i'm saying what the idea is preposterous i've been happily married for over 150 years
i would never consort with another woman oh i see so the rumors are true what rumors
nothing time out mr lincoln would you like to say a few words to the audience
thank you this is a date that will be remembered for centuries to come today is the day we return
america to greatness i stand here at the steps of the white house not above the people but with
the people only one man can lead the nation through this troubled time stop being bad enough
abraham lincoln and that man the time to act is now thank you i've heard better addresses from
the 4-1-1 operator what did you just say hey lincoln captain ahab called he wants his beard
back i'm gonna slap you silly you little punk save it on camera he just said that on camera
he just threatened me on camera oh wait wait wait i gotta click the bug the bugs are still
sitting there i know i gotta get the bug time out what did you say repeat it it's not gonna
repeat at all is he speaking to somebody said the word saved holy shit i haven't done it once
i'm like a hot dog too where are we going sam back to the office shotgun who are you
calling sam shibbol hello sure honest dave here hey who are you calling sam shibbol hello
there we go i stand here at the steps of the white house i am abraham lincoln i am that man
i abraham lincoln and that man oh i'd like to go out this is a date that will be remembered
for centuries uh i stand here at the steps of the white house's location so this is a date
that will be remembered for centuries this is a date that will be remembered for centuries to
oh my steps of the white house i stand here at the steps of the white house at the white house
got it what time should i meet the time to act is now the time to act is now
i'm gonna slap you silly you little punk what i will feast on your entrails and devour your soul
oh yeah why would you do that you just blew it see you soon gotta go you just blew it why
would he do that he just said i was gonna like slap and so to sum up family values are the
bedrock of this nation our fidelity honesty and loyalty to family is our most sacred asset
as americans candidate max your rebuttal
yoohoo mr lincoln i believe we have a question in the audience from someone who is not candidate
lincoln's wife oh hi sam hi max greetings random harlott abe i'm here are you ready for our
date what i've never seen this woman before in my life but on the phone you sounded so
quick read the cue card i did not have sex with this woman i did not arrange a date with this
woman oh so she's good enough to fool around with but not to date mr lincoln i can't believe
you're doing this to me drop the pulse it's time to be president family values are caught
in tryst with a didn't read the rest but almost later you had you had your shot it was
close the results from the emergency election are coming in and it appears that former sitcom
star max has been elected president of the united states in an unprecedented show of
bipartisan solidarity all of the country's political parties have desperately asked for
a recount let's cut to the white house lawn to hear candidate lincoln's address you've got to
be me you idiot he took the news much better than expected democracy i will make you all
my hypnotics whoa no more hypnosis abe lincoln will enslave the entire east coast if we don't
stop him who cares i'm pretty hesitant on the u.s let's go bomb someone into oblivion
not just anyone max abe lincoln must die yes all right anything else here i think we're good
did we get anything else from that no so where did he go they did the election the same day as
the debate and they only counted votes for like 12 seconds hope you got yours in after that
rampaging lincoln you're going down abe let's go see where he goes well he wasn't hard to find
just had to follow the trail of broken campaign promises that's pretty profound for a high speed
car chase max i like to think i transcend genre conventions can you all right shoot him
he's made of marble max and he will try rage i can't shoot the guy it's lincoln we need to
okay well he's a testy little emancipator isn't he all right office or the white house
um i don't think i can do anything cut him off and make him run into you oh wait a minute
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait sometimes it screws on quickly finally mr president you're
here that's the president people will vote for anyone these days obviously what's that supposed
to mean it means oh political debate all the soda poppers are here from from the hamburgers
whatever the names are check out all the cool stuff on my new desk all right he's the
president now get out of the way step away from the door sir but we really want in there
sorry sir i have orders to keep everyone out of the war room max is the president max tell
him to let us in let's get the fuck in there can't you get us into the war room max i kept
hearing about presidential powers but it's all just boring bureaucratic stuff i was hoping i'd
be able to make things explode with my mind let us open the door what's the date today max
i'm president of the united states sam what date do you want it to be what are we doing
here max i keep getting whiny memos about the giant robotic abraham lincoln who's rampaging
through washington enslaving the populace i guess we'd better do something about that
um okay i'm glad we took this time to talk max keep in touch sam i mean that
there are so many other things to punch what the hell is the you want to get with the
president in the war room why look max it's our old pal look grand imperial warlord maximus
keeper of the seven keys it's our old pal the former child star and embarrassing idol
semi-finalist peepers that's former child star and embarrassing idol semi-finalist governor
peepers uh okay what are you doing in here what business do you have in the oval office
we need the president to settle custody of mount rushmore right max has the presidential
pen somewhere just tell me where to sign great the problem is solved but seriously if you
guys see the president tell him we're waiting it's literally right yes max is the president
turn around it was in the papers politics and chat the news back and i got under control
what was that did i say arms build up i meant winter paradise toboggan and scrapbooking
jamboree can't we all just get a can we all just get a can if we all just keep quiet and
avoid another incident honesty is rarely the best policy all us presidents know that
all right so long see you later which one of you can pee can you pee on them or something
here to give another demonstration on soda abuse that's not funny thirsty yes but you're
not going to offer me a soda are you you know i can't resist them we wouldn't do that we've
got let's see here orange soda cola grape soda grape soda more orange soda and tea tea please
we're all out of tea soda why are you doing this why should your state get mount rushmore
because they just wanted for tourism but my plan will save why it'll become a monument to soda
abuse prevention people will realize it just like washington jefferson roosevelt and the other
guy they can overcome their crippling addiction to carbonated beverages george washington never
had a soda addiction why do you think he needed false teeth why not divide it up equally
that would never work it's not even you mean lipstick break roosevelt i want the mustache
okay max gets roosevelt's mustache parachute x gets the glasses peepers you get an ear and
both nostrils that just leaves me with the forehead all right then wizard we'll throw in
crazy horse but that's my final offer it's not even finished this will never work it's just like
last time it's called drip drip no it's called my head got stuck here and i
rip pulled too hard and i tripped and it fucking fell and it made the hole bigger
how did west dakota become a separate state the three of us ran for governor together
we got along so well during the campaign and we were all such former tv celebrities that all
three of us won the voters realized they'd elected three governors for only two states
that's when the unpleasantness began uh what unpleasantness let's just hear about this
we fought for a long time about how to divide up the states there was almost a war but we
divided everything up fairly and all agreed that mount rushmore should be in the south
we did not you i what you oh never mind you guys if you think there'll be a fashion trend
where this is really big it's so stretched out to a point where it's stretched down to here
here it's floppy and all stretched out did somebody just say i look like i'm doing a
shaggy cosplay am i making that up i saw somebody say you look like shaggy right now
and i added the rest of that i think i added that but this is a shaggy cosplay oh i can't wait
scoop what's the point man oh i mean i don't think we should go in there scoop changing my
clothes yeah okay all right so it's another green shirt i'm so fucking stupid hey hey what
what this system but it's like 44 grams of sugar in it oh what the fuck is happening in my life
oh my god it's gross all right what are we doing what was the unpleasantness again
we almost went to war over who should get control of mount rushmore and it's all
specs and papers what yeah what you oh never mind okay stay dry whiz man
raggy no that's that's the wrong character you're thinking of a different character
can somebody open this door hey specs max you remember most omnipotent exaltedness max sama
overseer of the nine cosmic planes you remember specs the other soda popper we vaguely recognize
our loyal see that what are you guys talking about kiss the ring what no 44 fucking grams of
sugar that's unbelievable this should be illegal i can you could clean a drain with that
it is illegal that's better sing your theme song for us no i don't sing that anymore i want
to be respected as more than just a beloved tv celebrity if it makes you feel better you were
never really that beloved don't always watch your show with detached irons what business do
you have with the president we're here to get federal resolution on a dispute it wouldn't
be a dispute if you if i what nothing awkward all right break down this door before i continue to do
shaggy impressions what about the rat hole looks like there are rats in the oval office
sam you've finally done it a straight line so easy even i won't touch it
stand aside pal the president needs to get into the war room get me in there
sir perhaps you didn't hear our advisor we would like to see our war room no can do sir orders
max says you can take a vacation we will make an exception just this once thank you sir but no
can do i can only take a vacation on federal holidays oh well be back roger that wasn't that
interesting i've got a calendar right here it's the official united states calendar 12 of the
hottest supreme court justices in their skimpiest naughtiest swimsuits even better max you can
actually change the official date let's change it today uh so we have earth day secretary's day
arbor day the beginning of passover easter sunday all right so what's easter sunday right
make it 420 no national chicago hot dog day hold on a minute here folks i'm gonna drink
a fucking real man's drink that's right this isn't one for the ages here this is a 100 no
sugar added ocean spray pineapple juice it's good shit at fact said it was man's drink it
said who the fuck are you man woman don't matter liver damage what do you mean liver
damage we're talking about what does that mean why did you say liver damage i'm serious i'm
not fucking around right now cut the music what are you talking about worse than alcohol
what are you talking about but this has this has like not that much sugar in it it's just
fruit juice is this gonna hurt me google it it's real pineapple juice is bad for your liver
it burns through organs it does not do that i drink this on airplanes it's my favorite
that's why i bought like a hundred of them i bought a lot of these i bought like cases of
these i love i used to drink them on airplanes and i loved it well the frog says something
relevant and that's just my opinion you know he's green too it's not actually going to be bad
right i don't believe you guys also i'll ask i'll ask a fucking real doctor cue the music
look how much sugar it is 18 that's nothing i don't drink like 10 of these i drink like
one of these every few days to get a little pep you all right excuse me full screen this
shit because i don't i know stalling play the game this is important okay guys so in my in my
your right on your right my left we have a fucking mountain dew mountain dew drink it every
day people drink a soda five sodas a day 44 grams of sugar in my right hand i have a
pineapple juice it's ocean spray it's fine it's small you drink one or two of these every week
you're telling me that i'm doing something wrong here when i'm cutting out like 25 grams of
sugar instead of drinking this look at how much the difference you can put this over ice
what kind of hipster mountain dew is this it's the shitty one that has extra sugar in it
because for some reason people wanted that ocean spray is nasty it's really cheap it's
how much is it go look it up on amazon right now how much is like a fucking case of this shit
it's probably like the cost of two mountain dos for the cost of two mountain dos you can get
yourself like 30 pineapple juices he's a puppet shaggy is high as fuck drink i drink a ton of
water but sometimes you want a little a little drink you don't know the fucked up shit that
people drink that i say people order oh i see people walking around the street with these like
jumbo like giant cans of fucking monster those are like 900 grams of sugar in it
we sweating we're fine east sunday we now declare today april 8th easter sunday christ
we'd better start hiding eggs on the white house lawn already did it sam max are these
the eggs that are made of metal and shaped like a pineapple and have a pin in them don't
be silly sam i took the pins out first all right it's easter sunday go home hey supes
max says you can take a vacation it's easter i'm not a religious man sir i wouldn't feel right
taking a vacation unless it was a secular holiday doesn't want the day off on easter
but you get day off who cares we'll be back roger that oh boy not a federal holiday i don't
even know what which did one of these is a federal holiday no these are arbor day secretary's day
earth day no everybody go outside today and hug a tree hug nothing this year i'm hoping to get
the second base oh boy people of earth we have now changed the official date mark your calendars
update your checks all hail max now they don't even say it it's not even gonna work oh boy only
the red ones we nap everybody all right go home plant tree hey supes max says you can take a
vacation it's arbor day nice liver hurts tree sir we'll be back roger that my fucking
liver hurts i think you guys have got in my head oh it's the acid that i drank before
this i've been drinking these for years we now declare that's supposed to be administrative
professionals day wow sam when i picked you for vice president i didn't know you were such a
politically correct leading heart liberal all right then secretary state hey supes i need to
drink a base it's not i usually put it in what people put this in vodka not a bad idea
no it's not that is bad since you can take a vacation it's secretary's day i'm not a
secretary sir we'll be back roger that what day does it need to be earth day people of america
take this day to ignore all practical concerns and devote all your attention to one day of
crackpot extreme environmentalist activism which you'll forget about for the rest of the year
people of berkeley california keep up the good work you convinced me to start drinking
don't say that it's not i don't make don't put me there max says you can take a vacation
it's earth day very funny sir we'll be back roger that um can i change the i did them all
Passover we declare today april 1st the first day of sam's indefinite lockup in the dank
dungeons beneath the white house what i thought we were pals max i swear to god i'm not making
this up i really wish i was it definitely wasn't pineapple juice it was this acid that i took two
sips out of i got a stomach ache now max says you can take a vacation it's april fools day
with all due respect that's kind of mean sir we'll be back roger that quick eat chalk
i gotta counteract the acid i gotta eat like the soda poppers aren't the close-knit band they
used to be they're just one inappropriate comment away from full-on violence just like you and me
pal i'm glad we took this keep in touch we're gonna do Passover he said didn't he say not a
religious holiday oh boy we now declare today april 3rd the beginning of Passover the only
other one i can do let my people go may the first may the fourth may the force be with you
max says you can take a vacation it's Passover i'm not a religious man sir i wouldn't feel right
taking a vacation unless it was a secular holiday we'll be back roger that oh boy people of earth
we have now changed the official date update your checks all hail max
hey supes max says you can take a vacation i can only take a vacation on federal holidays
i don't there's no other holiday to pick i have to write something up there tax day
8 april 15th no we now declare today of team tax day when writing your checks america remember
it's spelled m a bad news little this has to be a last president abolished the income tax
replaced it with a national door-to-door candy bar sale remember the fiend i'm glad we knocked
his head off it's tax day go home hey supes max says you can take a vacation i can only take a
vacation on federal holidays well be back roger that oh boy federal holidays there's no federal
holiday in april there's no federal holiday in april there isn't one can i can i turn the page
mark your calendars update your checks it's the secretary of presidential whimsy ribbon
looks like max can use this to appoint someone as an honorary cabinet secretary oh give it to him
give it to him give it to him give it to him give it to him here here take it you're a
secretary of state now take it i mean his excellency el jefe maximilian the first
intimidator of the realm has a special surprise for you better get those handkerchiefs ready
this is sentimental agent super ball we have decided to reward you for your excellent
service to your country for your unwavering commitment to preventing us from being where
we most desperately need it to be i hate this game devotion to being a constant hindrance in
our task for all these things and more we now dub thee super ball secretary of meats and
cheese secretary in charge of guarding the war room door secretary of the interior secretary
of the mysterious gaseous submission secretary meats and cheeses secretary of the interior
secretary of the interior we already have one of those oh exterior we have one of those too
fine secretary of the posterior so we have spoken so it shall be
all hail max i'm overwhelmed sir i don't know what to say now run along to a cabinet meeting
i'm afraid i can't do that sir you've got to be kidding me i still have my orders
oh these what's in there oh no best before oh three august 12 no i'm just fucking kidding
all right it's secretary day time to go home april 26 secretary's day that's supposed to be
administrative professionals day wow sam we already heard that's no i don't want to take
it off of him that was fun hey supes we'll be back roger that max i mean it'll surprise better
get agent for your for your unparallel secretary we already oh we have one fine all hail max now
you can go home hey supes today is secretary's day you have to take the day off he was only a
secretary for five seconds a vacation permission to weep openly sir not just granted but encouraged
the forces of bureaucracy win again war room oh i'm so sorry i think war room door is only openable
in time of war stupid old piece okay so max let's do some war can't you get us into the
war room max i kept hearing about presidential powers but it's all just boring bureaucratic
i was hoping i'd be able to make things explode with my mind
can i move the thing to date of war i'm glad we keep in touch did they have to break out in a
fight or something hey peepers yeah these had they have to break out in like a war between
each other you're a governor too that's right i got north dakota north dakota the leftover state
hey hey hey hey north dakota find people of north dakota don't find that funny
we've got a rich and varied history north dakota hope you like snow hey north dakota
sorry i got caught up in the moment what's there to do in north dakota
what can you do snowmen snow angels snowboard snowball fights homemade ice cream and of course
the majesty of mount rushmore that hasn't been decided yet right i spoke too soon
see you later all right war would you like a drink as long as it's not soda what was
the unpleasant they want mount rushmore we almost went to war over who should get control of
mount rushmore that's all because specs and papers what yeah what you oh never mind so
throw a punch wish man hey specs what business do you have with the president we're here to get
federal resolution on a dispute it wouldn't be a dispute if you if i what nothing
oh well they won't they won't talk they won't talk if only there was a device that i had that
made people tell the truth max i need 100 million dollars right now that was too much
eye contact it was just enough i probably have to go get like a i think like a royal
decree or something he was reading chat that's how he figured it out okay all right can i
see where you're from probably fucking north dakota i would i would be surprised if you weren't
where are we going sam we're going to the office so i could go buy something everyone's
saying blind blind blind no place never where the fuck are y'all from blind what did i miss
was it like a pack of money on the table or something he's blind he's blind he's blind
he's blind he's blind blind blind somehow blind he's blind but what is he supposed to be seeing
a suitcase full of money cash credit cards money a globe of uh uh receipts on national budget
look max it's the presidential hold on million dollars to allocate however you want
what a delightfully random and convenient figure uh presidential discretionary budget
the alamo statue of liberty independence hall uh what that's not what i clicked hey look max
it's the president allocate however you want what a delightfully random and convenient figure
well what did he want did bosco say something earlier about i don't remember him saying any of
this stuff he's like pretending to be a russian guy right is he gonna put the money there and
i have to go get it i would assume it just deposits the money to like the statue of liberty
i have to walk into it and grab it all right let's go back to town all right there little
where are we going sam back to the office shotgun
i love these little cans don't tell anybody on the internet what like you drinking or eating
some of those have a problem with it i could be eating an apple on stream just like a washington
apple and somebody would be like hey you know that's bad for you like it's it's an apple
don't eat those don't eat those they got poisoning in them okay i could i could be
smoking a cigarette on stream and people would have less to say about it than if i ate like a
pear all right we're going in here i want to ask him something apples destroy your kidneys
imagine if i turned to the face game and i was smoking i would not i would not do that
no we want to buy something just like a cigarette hanging out of my hand no
unless it was a very very specific character or something that we were doing
we'll take that truth serum is yours for only 100 million american dollars i seem to have left
my 100 million dollars in my other suit i don't smoke cigarettes nothing all right let's go back
to uh talk to the civil do i have any cigarettes no i don't have any cigarettes i don't purchase
cigarettes i don't own cigarettes i'm sorry why am i dumb for that why would that make me a
dumbass right you don't take up smoking what a dumbass improves your iq
hi you civil how are things in the world of computer generated romance
oh i'm not doing that anymore you believe that guy never mentioning that he was married
matters that self-centered jerk dick preach it girlfriend so you change careers again yeah now
i'm running a dating service um come again from temperature dating service i bought this
astoundingly useful machine that tells me how old things are i usually just cut them in half
and count the rings i got a reason you're not invited to birthday parties anymore i got at
least warm spring day worth of iq points guys give me a break this wasn't my first choice but
i got a good deal on the carving dating equipment online and i couldn't afford to
change my sign you're having financial problems you're having financial problems i'm afraid so
after my public humiliation with lincoln all the applicants for my dating service demanded their
money back i can't believe it not to mention all the money tied up in pending litigation with the
clients who watched max's dating video i stated very clearly up front that viewer discretion was
advised believe me i would love to just close up shop for a while and take a vacation
forget about did like the ilan musk lost smoking face i know i did i could feel it i could
see it but unless i get a major windfall i have to hope the carbon dating business takes off
carbon dating i spit you probably saw how does carbon dating work i don't know something about
carbon 14 and half lives and radiation i'm impressed with your detailed scientific knowledge
very professional okay that's the beauty of it i don't really need to know anything i just aim
my little machine at something and it tells me how old it is allow me to demonstrate
this tiki is oh my gosh it's it's 2000 years old this is fantastic old is good absolutely
i can have my office put on the national register of historic places
i might even get a grant i'd be rich can we borrow can we borrow your carbon dating machine
no way that machine is still my only chance to take care of my money problems
unless i get a grant since i'm now on the national register okay there's no way i'm letting
it out of my sight okay so uh we need to give you a grant so you're around sybil
so what is this place called did she say that it's sybil's carbon dating don't touch that
fellas it's the only thing keeping me in business do we get an extra thing notch or is it just one
of those places stature liberty or so there's gonna be another spot will be there for her place
all right so we're gonna do that then take the gun it's locked it's locked oh my god i
fucking cannot believe i it's gonna happen every time it'll happen every single time
i swear to god that's never gonna not happen they could do studies on my absent
mind in this they really could in fact they probably already have this is me your mother
and your father worried it hurt something about cigarettes on your stream we aren't sure what
it's about we really hope you haven't picked up smoking it's very bad for you and giving you
cancer we fly over there and take away your electronic toys and ground you if you don't
stop where are we going we're off to the white house oh boy mom's not going to take my
toys now he's gonna take another week vacation nah what's today after sam and max wait what's
today today today we have um it's may first second okay i gotta i gotta block out the rest
of the weekend here thursday friday saturday sunday all right so here's the plan for the
week you ready put your ear to the tv so after tonight we're gonna play we're gonna i'm just
gonna do this until we finish it so after tonight i'll be back on saturday and sunday
we'll go five days this week and then so that would be yeah labo vr will be on saturday
and maybe even into sunday who knows maybe i might play more how again no i had a lot of
fun playing that so yeah after tonight however long this takes us we're gonna just hang out
and chill and just keep doing it and then during the next two days i'm gonna spend a
lot of time in dreams so i'm gonna really really really hunker down on it and try
to get something fun because it takes a lot of work so dreams will come back next week
and i'm not gonna give a date for anybody to oh hey you have to have a certain deadline by
the time no i think i'd rather because i don't want to put like pressure on anybody to like
get something done by next week or something so i'm i'll check and see if anybody has
anything there but yeah labo vr will be saturday don't worry i'll get a fucking box
of wine and i'll fill it with pineapple juice and pretend to drink but that's a good plan
because we did monday tuesday wednesday saturday sunday will be what we do so that's the plan
for this week just wanted to try to block it out in my brain so but let's keep going
saving max is fun let's keep doing it okay so now we can go in the book and what this should
do look max it's the presidential discretionary budget you have 100 million dollars to allocate
however you want what a delightfully random and convenient figure civil's office she's got the
money now let's go get the gun what was the plan i spaced out i'm gonna finish sam and max
tonight however long this takes so it's been about four hours we got two episodes left each
one is supposed to be like one and a half to two hours each so be about probably seven
eight hours tonight where are we going sam uh back to the office back to the office shotgun
you spent four hours in one episode that's not true uh we did half of episode three but actually
it was a little less than half it was like probably i was like 30 to 40 percent into episode
three when we started tonight's stream this episode is hard to be fair um it's just kind of it
just kind of seems longer and yeah i know it's because i've been doing a lot of i'm
like high energy tonight so you know sometimes you get that i can't control it it's dr germa
and mr albertson i don't know who you're gonna get it's rough she's probably living it up on
some tropical island on the taxpayer's dime i bet she's getting abducted in some sleazy
nightclub then sold into a white slavery ring forced to do unspeakable things for a power
mad despot before narrowly escaping his volcano top layer with only one of her kidneys left
don't be such a pessimist max sorry sam it's just no fair we're stuck here working and
she gets to have all the fun okay well uh so give me the gun it's sybil's carbon dating machine
and i'm gonna take it it's mine now that's my carbon dating machine stupid not you him
all right so now i can i can date something i'm not going over to click on the door like to
leave the office i just wanted to click on carbon date stuff garfield i don't want to know
how old that is so now i'm gonna take this and bring it what do i need to know the carbon date of
let's go the car how old is the car i don't want to know how old that is we don't want
to do you don't know what make and model your car is come on man use it on max max have you
been dieting he's timeless i don't get it what does that mean turn it on you and find out
what the carbon date for yourself is hold on that's weird it says his age is burnt sienna
that is weird he doesn't look a day over toe okay well fine what about you in here bosco how
you doing carbon date yourself i'm spitting a lot let's go to the dentist what is that
keep that away from me relax bosco it only tells how old you are why do you need to know
that did someone send you to find out how old i am sheesh never mind that's your problem
with dating sam you give up too easily well hey bosco we want to buy something we want to buy
something oh we're gonna do this thing again right necessary private enterprise i'm not
sticking them up i'm it's a it's a glorified tag scanner do you have any potatoes in the
likeness of catholic saints do you have any souvenir snow globes from the mystery vortex
yeah do you have any lobster pots brand cereal yeah lobster pots why was that like a boston
accent tagalog rhyming dictionaries abridged yeah do you have any wiener cozies die we just
get shipment of those in this week let me look oh boy wait did you say wiener cozy i thought
you said navajo blanket no we're all out of wiener cozy do you have any navajo blankets
yet do you have any potatoes in the likeness of all right let's continue scanning right now
see you later bosco how old the trash i don't want to know how old that is how old the
magazine well no that's max god max have you been dieting weenies wow bosco by my
readings these weenies date from the early cretaceous period uh the special bargain for
you still tasty half of today only shut them down you don't understand your store is now a
national historic place these weenies oh because they're okay really i mean of course
in preserving heritage of my people just how valuable are we talking about here we'll get
back to you on that a hundred million dollars is what it is well simpsons knockoff did they
simpsons do a scan your age joke hot dogs so fucking bad it's making me angry the nut
joes are from the early 90s but i can't get a reading on the cheese i don't think it's
organic sam all right i wonder how old the coffee is i've been talking about gross and green
it is this coffee is over a month old it's slow roasted for premium taste and maximum
viscosity i need i need a hot dog how do i get one i should have just i told kim to get
hot dogs the grocery store what did i say or pbr i was making dumb jokes shit all right let's go
allocate the money come back and get the device from him call i think i think she's here going
sam that was almost two that was like two hours ago you don't go to the grocery store
for two and a half hours unless you really buying a lot of shit for a lot of fucking
people we're off to the white house oh boy two hour old moldy hot dogs okay budget let's sign
the paper that'll give us the truth serum we can get what we want out of these um the mcnugget
kids hey look what are they called the soda presidential discretionary budget you have
100 million dollars to allocate what a delightfully random there we go boss goes
inconvenient store has 100 million dollars now let's go get it the so that the soda poppers
i didn't see you there as you know i'm maximilian the first ruler of your quaint little nation
our borders stretch from the beautiful coasts of california to the not exactly beautiful but
still pretty nice in their own way coasts along the eastern seaboard at least they do
now i'm working with my executive staff sam to see about getting us a little more room to
work with if you catch my drift but don't you worry your pretty little heads about that
for now just sit back relax and enjoy the ride toodles why is i'm not gonna read what you said
you used rob sybil you pulled all her funding she had enough money to do at least to get
some stuff done true serum where are we going we are going back to the office back to the
office my fucking god my brain is wired just a lot of goddamn filler no it's it's not bad
i mean look this is episode four we're gonna have a filler episode here at some point
they they all can't be home runs they're they all they're all good hello comrade bosco
hail to the chief i don't know how you guys did but i just got a huge check from the
government you earned it bosco it's not easy to perfectly preserve weenies that predate the
discovery of fire not to mention the teeming microcosm growing in the bathroom we're
considering making it a national wildlife preserve when's the turn dark can finally finish my
satellite defense system so we can have the truth serum let me dig it up from the lat vodka
i told you this is a bottle of vodka i you told me i was wrong all you guys said it wasn't
what it was get a couple of shots of that in somebody and they'll tell you all their secrets
all right let's go get the soda poppers drunk we believe we didn't go to civil and see
she's gonna be mad that i pulled all of her funding funding how does funding work somebody
gives you money you make something and you pay them back wow so i'm coming to collect
that's what we're doing here it's locked she's not in here nothing useful in here
that's not even do you hear like moaning that's the fan she's not in here stop telling me to
relax i just want a hot dog i want two hot dogs i know you don't like when i look at you like
this but i just start with myself but i want two hot dogs all right let's go where are we going
sam i might even eat three hot dogs tonight that's right we're off to the white house oh boy
you're eating a hot dog right now i'm so jealous i really am three hot dogs but one of them without
a bun that's how you can tell that i'm being responsible about the whole thing
watch out get out of my way okay let yeah i usually do one bun and one without fun
and the one without the bun just gets like a little squeeze of uh mustard on it and i eat
it with a fork and knife the other one is eating loaded up a bunch of bullshit all right
guys let's have a little party here care for a drink thanks but i'm not thirsty do you put
condiments on top or underneath i put it on top i like the aesthetic it's pleasing to me
i don't underneath it kind of sobs in it gets wet i like the artwork what are you guys
doing that's old yeah we've seen this already i wish that was me god i wish that was me
i'm imagining how good that would be right now i'm just thinking about it i'm picturing
that hot dog where it is right now it's glorious nice really nice dijon too
all right let's go care for a drink it's soda right you brought more soda sure why not
you would know immediately whoa fuck all right that's got more kick than the other ones
right seven max you guys you guys are my best friends now can we get that was next level
what's the point you still think peeper's idea is stupid stupid you never told me you thought
my idea was stupid he said your idea of adding herbert hoover hugging the four other presidents
was the stupidest thing he'd ever heard well it is he wasn't even a president which means
he certainly wasn't the most loving of all the presidents well at least i didn't suggest
putting a parking garage in george washington's forehead like some four-eyed
freaks i know right right you little you big of course you realize this means war
didn't he doesn't that guy doesn't that one piss that one pisses he didn't have to pee that's
different i don't like what he does you just make me uncomfortable for some reason
i don't know why we have toddler bodies that's what it is
well let's not do that again
okay that was a musical number in the middle here i'm gonna throw up no i'll be fine
oh why did that hurt me all right war run let's go let's go conclude this let's go drop uh some
machine guns on them or whatever they do oh is it not button is it not button over here
there it is looks like a remote homing beacon in the fridge in antarctic
so peaceful so serene want to blow it up you have to ask dinner special tonight
penguin flambe did i just seriously send a fucking missile who would have suspected the
washington monument is really a self-replenishing supply of intercontinental ballistic missiles
it's good to see it used for something more useful are we not gonna see are we i wonder if
this will have a significant impact on our delicate ecosystem absolutely my ego is bigger
already apparently once we've shot them there's no homing beacon to the kremlin doesn't seem
to be working it was probably turned off in the spirit of glasnost more likely those lazy
commie bastards forgot to change the batteries i don't want to drop like
fucking bombs everywhere it's the distant peaceful world of krypton they mock us
with their krypton like superman cities and absentee parents they must be exterminated
this will teach him to put me in the phantom zone whoa whoa whoopsie whoopsie whoopsie whoopsie
hold on oh boy oh boy oh dear we're good you will bow down before me
ah estimated time of in fact 26 million years well what do you know bosco was right the
government really has been targeting his they really were going to shoot a missile
at bosco what do you say we keep this to ourselves max you're right we don't want to
ruin the surprise attention bosco shoppers clean up in aisle everything he doesn't even know
oh yes the 100 million dollar laser osco satellite defense system actually works
well play oh my god that's so dumb you're safe but there's no beacon for the missile
to lock on to so i can't just have to do this the slow way lock and load sam
we're off to red square some other time little buddy okay so i've i've shot a missile everywhere
i gotta get out of here what to do in time of war select target and fire pretty easy that's
all it says no shit kim no i didn't i didn't no kim i didn't want hot dogs not until they
started talking about it it was the chat they started talking about this image on the screen
that you see right now they were talking about that image and then we talked about
hot dogs for a little while and i said oh man hot dogs cool i was like that didn't happen
that was it wasn't from earlier salmon's gonna be fucking delicious i can't wait thank you for
that all right so uh we need to take out abraham lincoln look max and the white house
garden pond it's jimmy two teeth we often allow lobbyists to use the pool sam jimmy's a lobbyist
now frame that and put it on the fridge cheese interests affordable health care for the agent
and underprivileged sam he's a lot more multifaceted than you give him credit for
so where's where's abraham lincoln the civil war in the dakotas seems to be escalating max
but then thin out the overpopulation of moose and strip malls for a few weeks
and then we'll step in truth serums only useful on people not telling the truth
pasta with garlic bread or salmon that's a tough one because it depends on the day
it's a plate of fancy cookies for the discriminating general with a sweet tooth
and a taste for vengeance
all right i gotta settle the fuck down uh all right so boss goes i couldn't i can't i
can't shoot ma what was it russia and i can't shoot boss goes let's go find out why uh wait
what did she say oh wait kim that was kim that asked that question i thought it was just
somebody saying hey man what do you what do you like more you know what i'm gonna make
it real i'm gonna make it easy because i was like all right well man yeah i would have what
do you want to fight a duck-sized horse or a hundred horse-sized ducks whatever the fuck i
i don't know whatever the uh pasta because it's easier and i can eat it on stream the pasta
sauce takes an hour well you're getting the pasta sauce from italy now i'll tell you right
now kim's kim's pasta sauce is fucking amazing that's worth waiting for it's worth waiting for
it's insane yeah pasta would be easy to eat on like stream i could just turn the camera
off for five minutes a good sauce takes four hours i've had plenty of sauces out of the jar
that was that were good i've had jar sauces that i would put it like a seven or eight out of ten
so i mean maybe my barometer is not that good for uh my palate but i've had some fucking bag
sauce before too all right so i need to go to boss goes germa is drunk germa is drunk germa
is drunk germa is drunk hey maybe if you say it more then maybe the more time you say it maybe it'll
be true that sounds good thank you kim wonderful girlfriend kim all right oh where are we going
sam we need to go talk to the office shotgun not until the labo stream no that's that's true
making some songs all right let's go boss go i don't know what to do with this
it's even what do i do with this i can't i have to i'm not going to throw it away i can't
i have to at least clean something with it i could clean my shower with this later
yeah hey boshko what would it take me to chug this i wouldn't do it for a million dollars
i would i would not chug this mountain dew throwback for a million dollars
if you came here with a briefcase for the cryptocurrency btc and you said that's a million
credits worth of btc i'd be like dad close it up i don't want to you're full of shit try me
you got a million dollars all right uh tell us about that missile defense system again
of course i would drink this i would drink this for like 30 bucks no i wouldn't be able
to shoot down no i'm not drinking the mountain dew i'm gonna dump it right now do
i have anything i'm gonna dump it in a bucket so nobody can do that i gotta get i'm
gonna dump it quick i'm gonna do it quick so nobody can do it no no it's not in
my bucket somewhere else it's a smaller but no but then it just transfers from one can to another
can i don't have nowhere to put it no use it as shampoo that my hair will fall out i will lose
all of my fucking hair tell us about this missile defense system again i just copied
them completely i didn't really mean to do that once i get funded for it it'll be able
to shoot down any icbms targeted at the store okay so what how do i get to space
how do i get up there how do i stop this i need to how do i change the target
one dollar lottery tickets two dollars i'm feeling lucky already he forgot what he was
supposed to be doing i mean i kind of did i have to go to where he's there's like a missile
thing where's the missile thing no what are we doing this for i don't this is new bacon
where's the bacon nothing like a gap i'm comfortable with it because i'm uncommonly
photogenic maybe if you didn't spend 30 minutes on bad bits you would know that was a good bit
i want everybody in the chat to press one if you thought that was a good bit
look stuck to the camera that must be the homing beacon for the intercontinental bullet
missiles aimed at bosco store what was that he said that must be the best price on baby
wipes i've ever seen okay so here's the beacon got it now we put the beacon onto abraham lincoln
go shoot the missile that's in my pocket where are we going sam we are going to chase down
lincoln after that rampaging lincoln yes oh is that a missile in your pocket oh money money
wait hold on bacon one hit marker okay i'll get the rest ah nice or accuse his own back off to
escape okay bye launch missile at abraham lincoln bits right okay who gave those bits over here
i'm checking over here every now and again uh spoons for self-defense 50
dollars 5000 bits for spoons from spoons for self-defense thank you spoons and they say hey
general please chug the mountain dew and say your new catchphrase who ya time for me to what
i'm not doing that no i'm not doing the catchphrase and i'm not drinking
a mountain dew throwback i can't do that i okay listen to me guys listen to me bros and
broettes listen if i chug this right now you have to understand something the stream turns
off in like 40 minutes because i'm gonna shit my pants so what's more important me chugging this
and shitting my pants in 45 minutes and the stream turning off or uh another like three and
a half hours for four hours in the stream if i drink this this shit i i'm it's gonna be bad
no it's this stuff sucks i'm not doing it let me be the one guy don't do it
i knew that if one guy was always gonna come in handy at some point
i was certain thank god for that one guy no no no no no no no no no no more money
no more don't give any more money that's 50 from colonel zero chug it i fucking triple
dog dare you i'm not doing it don't give any more money i can already feel it it's like
a hurting it's i took like three sips spoiler alert spoiler alert for like a gross thing
i'm not this is i'm not making this up um mute your ears if you don't want to do something
fucking weird i drank like three or four little chugs of this and my balls hurt right now it
has to be related i don't want to i don't want to do that i'm not doing any more of this
this is i'm sway to god that happened i'm not drinking any more of that
my back hurts from five hour energy you see no stay away from this shit don't ever drink this
drink water and drink fucking eat an apple can you eat a snickers bar instead please
no i'm not gonna i i value non-testicular pain versus
mm-hmm can what about can we can we blow up abraham lincoln please i don't care what the
straw poll says half the snickers you act weird when you're hungry i actually got some really
good chocolates no plus i'm gonna be eating like pasta in like 45 minutes i'm not drinking
that nobody wants to drink that okay if this was just link it to me where's the straw
pole looks like the targeting beacon is still stuck on that straw pole has impressive temper
more at this rate he'll have enslaved all of dc and most of baltimore by tomorrow morning
he gets you're right max okay i'm not i'm not gonna click this yet if this poll has even
five percent that say don't do it i'm not doing it it's 30 no no way it's at 31
no i'm not drinking i haven't got anything better to do i can't get the poll to load
because it's fucking six trillion people clicking on it do it mr president don't mind if i do
that's not how democracy works that's this isn't this isn't a democracy right now
i didn't put up a vote hey mr president uh can you like chug this mountain dude shit your pants
got it
at least for mass hypnosis is gonna be hypnosis in the next one too let's abuse my powers as leader
of the free world to squeeze the middle class until they're burning their own shoes for heat
sounds fun but i was thinking we could treat ourselves to some chocolate frosted gut bombs
and then have a little target practice down to the smithsonian sam you're my best friend
agent chuckles report query status lincoln gambit four score stroke seven query got
acknowledged an acceptable timeout parameters error error error error error error
you just made me miss an important storyline a chocolate oh a chocolate
that was fucking heavy
i told you thanks with uh 50 bucks thanks for 50 bucks turn the can upside down fine no i don't
want to do that just live in there thanks i did not i did not say thanks for the money idiot
that didn't happen this fucking music it's gonna kill me the basic girl gave 50 dollars
just chugging shit your entire pants chug another it says believe me with 100 bucks
i'm gonna take my money to the just chatting section and i hope you spend it wisely
uh 34 year old man is being peer pressured into chugging a mountain dew on stream
with like a shit load of money this is this is not the when when abraham lincoln fucking
created the universe this is not what he thought was gonna happen benjamin franklin is
just like there's no way you would have ever ever expected that something like this was
gonna happen how could you ever think that all right anyways we're gonna move on to episode
five i can already feel it rumbling all right 1000 in favor i i chugged it i okay
no one ever told me to chug the whole can they said chug it and i did i gave you a cartoon
chug i did at least five seconds of cartoon chug no one ever said the whole can monkeys
paw guys right right you don't be careful what you wish for you got to make it clear
chug means chug no chug means that's all it means it doesn't mean chug whole can
all right i'm gonna fucking go dump this i'm gonna go dump this abomination of the soda
how could it okay i just i mother fucker if i went to the dentist today i went to the
dentist i'm not supposed to be doing any of that my dentist would be so pissed hey we did
something work and we like we're treating some stuff make sure you don't like you stay away
from food and beverages for 12 hours or something no not food but you know what i mean
and i'm sitting drinking a mountain deuce sugar throwback soda and he's gonna take that as a
slight call your dentist he's crying he would be all right let's fucking move on the stream
is gonna be like a 12 hour stream if i don't hurry the fuck up and get this over with
all right that was uh episode four that's pretty good let's quit this and uh i am actually going
to get a real drink i'm gonna get a water it's already happening and i'm gonna get episode five
ready to go two episodes left in season one i'll be right back somebody said i've had
mountain dew throwback before and it's not even as bad as a baja blast i can't i'm making
such a big deal out of this but i'm serious like if i drink if i chug a soda like this
it's gonna be bad it's pretty good to be honest i don't uh be right back okay sorry
about my steam big picture mode opened for no reason it's loud as hell don't ask me why
big picture opened i'll fix this in a minute just let the intro play up you didn't miss the
intros right here unrest in the dakotas dispatch equal numbers of giant battle robots to all sides
whoever survives claim we back them it's two more one more after this let the new guys pilot
the giant battle robots criticism that your domestic policy is too giant battle robot based
they can take it up with my new press secretary the maim tron 9 000 if that's the guys from
air force one tell them they get the keys back once they say the magic word quiet max
it's the commissioner total collapse of the economy and downfall of western civilization
great grinning head of john the baptist in a pork pie hat stuffed in a rhinestone bowling bag
we're on our way we've got a computer crisis to take care of little buddy have they tried
turning it off and back on again bigger than that max computers everywhere are going haywire
planes are falling from the sky nuclear reactors are nearing meltdown and scores of pasty white
i just proved it was water with normal people the horror where do we start sam the national
consortium of smart people who are good with computers has been tracking electron surges
all over the country and one of the biggest is right here in our neighborhood what an
unbelievably convenient coincidence how do we find an electron surge no idea let's go
oh wait expose fraud fraud fraud fraud fraud so much fraud it's not fraud it's called hey
would you call would you call matt damon a liar no you wouldn't you'd call him a performer an
actor all right turn this shit down turn that down turn that down turn it off turn that
down put this back up two notches just right there slow down let me listen sounds pretty
close acting is just lying oh really we'll tell that to some of the actors including myself they
get so immersed in a role that you become that person streamer right streamer they could
do pretty good at that i immerse myself as streamer acting is not lying acting is a craft
it's about becoming someone else don't rain on my craft or you will be removed from this chat
tax fraud acting he's a failed actor i'm not a failed actor an accomplished actor
that was on the cover of a fucking magazine what magazine you ask next question too many
cans in this room maybe you could try acting like a man that can handle an entire soda
even if he was just a puppet max don't you think it's unsettling to keep the
i thought a fun time you're right sam we need to get a pipe you can't handle a soda i could
drink all right let's uh let's go let's go let's go let's go we got an emergency
yeah i gotta change the episode five you're right thank you this is episode five reality
2.0 so what's the uh what's the best episode of season one what do people think is the
most fun and most interesting episode this one is supposed to be the best one
so the the one this okay that's cool so this is like the best one of the season
or the last one all right let's go let's go let's start with bosco
germa lied about dev uh dev do throwback is there corn in there cheese is he not what's the
hey bosco greetings and well met friend watchmen for hire sam how come i suddenly
have a primal desire to beat bosco savagely because he's talking like a renaissance fair
attendee max it's an innate fight or flight response i am el basco drill the unhinged mighty
half elf ranger why'd you become an elf bosco but while max prepares the thorazine why
don't you tell us why you become an elf elf and i'll tell you why i've had multiple
delivery conspiracies i've had missiles aimed at me and now i got rival arms dealers setting
up shop in my store point b it's not safe for me here anymore i gotta take my business
the only place i can feel 100 secure the internet that's not safe there in fact that's
the most unsafe place you could be you don't want to be on the internet trust me you want
to make you want to make your career on the internet is that what you want just be ready
for that bosco what does this internet do hickey have to do with being an elf half
elf it's because everyone on the internet has to pick an avatar like a dwarf or an orc or a hot
young 15 year old girl curious about the adult world and willing to experiment i didn't
think it was possible but he's actually less creepy as the elf half elf fool i never mind
you guys don't understand how computers work okay bosco i'm gonna have to ask you to settle down
and uh but now you're taking your store online where will that leave next game no fear and
mistrust computers don't worry guys my online store will offer twice the inconvenience
at thrice the price well see you there all right we want to buy something we want to buy
what do you have for sale this time i have the finest goods in all the land tell him we'll pay
him just to stop talking like that what would squire you guys have said that to me before and
it's happened i'm fairly certain i've gotten like 30 dollars and somebody told me to stop
doing the voice i was doing i know what it's like bosco i'm telling you get away don't be
on the telling to get away from the internet what have you got oh not much just a virulent
biological weapon all right biological weapons we don't like to judge speak for yourself sam
but isn't germ warfare a little on the south side of ethical i've got to compete to stay in
the market guys if an arms dealer is going to open up shop in my store i've got to up the
ante uh how much for the but it's going to be a billion how much for this virulent biological
weapon of yours one billion dollars we'll take it what's another billion or so to the
national deficit it's gonna be like a far sorry for safety reasons i no longer accept cash in the
store you'll have to pay online that's pretty inconvenient thank you do you have any dual core
processors with 512 megabyte cash i like except btc do you have any chimpanzee size diapers
do you have any barbecue plankton chips doesn't sound that bad actually do you have
any keychains with a plus eight modifier to dexterity i wish do you have any self-respect
no i understood the question i understood it all too well whoa you sure do know how to suck the
fun out of everything bosco do you have any lombos isn't that no let's do that i was
gonna say isn't that the thing do you have a joke thing dual core processors with five
whatever it's called on second thought nothing for us now as i wish but don't play me when
you're stuck in the torch wasteland with nary a bag of enchantment to defend thyself do you
have any see you later bosco to the battle godspeed defenders of the sire i like that tongue
roll defenders i can do it i can hold it for about 25 seconds too now you can't jump all right
set up settle down i'll act camera in the fridge fluids so well preserved they're nearly
fit to drink isn't wrong to like music only if you can hear it let's get cracking oh i've
already drank water don't worry the hydration bot is broken because the hydration bot doesn't
understand that i drank that fake mountain dew it doesn't even hydration bot doesn't even
consider mountain dew water that's not even it's not the water in there apparently
wait i gotta talk to the uh the mouse with the can hydration pot says chug yeah water hands
off the merchandise pigs didn't people used to do that i remember like the the guy that used to
have the can and shoot him in the stomach and his stomach would like jiggle around
was that shit real that didn't really happen right well if it isn't our favorite ethically
challenged rat jimmy tootie sam was wondering where you'd scampered off to that's real
i was wondering what embarrassing pose we'd use when we had you started not from the
simpsons yeah i'm scared out of my wits you're gonna buy something or what where have i seen
this yeah here it is i you guys i'm not i wasn't i wasn't lying this guy lives to 81
is this the toughest man ever meet frank that's fucking real he lived to 81
holy shit that's that guy's made of plutonium don't try that at home what's a two-bit
crook like you trying to sell this and i can't even drink soda that petty insult for the sake of a
successful transaction i always get the goggles on an interpersonal defense you're an arms
dealer you make it sound so cheap i deal in fuck stop doing that all right so he's got a
cannon what have you gotten stuck yeah right now i only got this cannon you guys look like
you should just start out with handguns we've already got handguns oh yeah where just trust
him on that one oh just keep seeing the cannonball hit him with the stuff how much for the
camera how much for that cannon it's not the same worst arms dealer ever that's the simpsons
part guys to you guys i don't sell to the police call it my own ethical code but we're
just barely police yeah i seen how you guys work i sell it to you and next thing i know
the bunny's got it pointed right at me all right so we gotta get the cannon eventually here
see you later jimmy maybe if you can find me what do you mean you're gonna be right here
all right let's go talk to sybil sybil press you are under arrest i will i will limit
it let's go check some stuff i won't check anything let's go check check and see what
sybil's up to he's all tabbing well i just have a lot of tabs open when i'm going to close them
well have you i'm surrounded lightning bolt lightning bolt stand back max it sounds like
sybil's finally cracked it's about time while the stability was making the rest of the
neighborhood look bad back pit demons was sort of righteous fire i cast thee away this is
just like that time we were hired as motivational speakers for that sunday school actually now
that i look closely it's more like our last case and the three before that if there's one
thing i've learned to recognize recently it's a hypnotic device another those weird glasses
are this device stinging babies of unholy smiting to break her out of the trance we'll
have to deliver a blow to her head you know sam when you love what you do it doesn't
even feel like work but still have the yeah i got it back demons cast ward of pungent
so she's just waving around close enough to touch her max vr diablo uh well intercoms right
pager nobody knows can i let william tell the goggles i can't shoot sybil but i can ruin her
fucking store all right um gonna have to come back in here with something else to distract her
or stop her from moving sybil needs a self-cleaning cactus okay i'm not trying to
exit i know i know that now waste i'm just checking let's leave just take the glasses off
yeah i know i don't know why you just can't pull them off and not like her eyeballs are
gonna like come out with it maybe they will go to the dentist and put my videos of streams
on the tv that would be really really awkward that would be so strange i don't know i could
never go back to that dentist again because i would just be the streamer guy all right
anything else in here the little ranch not home the streamer dentist now what it would have been
what you should have said there is if i went in there and put my stream on the tv and he
looked back and he laughed at me and he was like okay buddy and he points up to a webcam
that's pointing down at us and he's streaming my dental work to like three times as many people
like what am i trying to like show him up like hey man look at me i'm on that tv huh
can i go anywhere where are we going sam nowhere in this old rust bucket at least not until we
get it fixed oh realize it was an important piece until the explosion okay so how do i get
how do i get him out of vr looks like the esperano bookstore is closed again
oh that was fast even for this neighborhood get a cavity filled on stream i don't have any
cavities i don't get cavities i don't drink very much soda and i don't eat very much candy
until today apparently go get a cavity get a cavity have you guys lost your minds
those tricks jimmy just living the life of a simple businessman making an honest living
freelance police mr teeth you're under arrest come along quietly and we'll only use excessive
force instead of medieval just try it pigs last time i checked it was a free country i'm
working on that enough games jimmy you're under arrest i know my you're actually under arrest
you're under fucking arrest and i come with me no citizen shall be prevented from setting up
shop without a license and in someone else's store to sell dangerous weapons indiscriminately
to the highest bidder who in his right mind would pass such an irresponsible max max did it
sell us the cannon jimmy i already told you it's not for safe
okay so see very very very clearly uh we have to punch him in the face
he's got to reload it he's got to reload it look at how long it takes to reload
all right so he shoots the cannon but instead of hitting me
you have to stuff the cannon maybe i can fill the cannon with something
eventually i'm gonna die this is going to kill me all right so i see it is when he's
reloading to address the nation's rat obesity problem without delay get me out of here
oh we'll let you out of there soon enough jimmy right now why i haven't been asleep
you know you get like the eye crust that usually happens when you go to bed
all right so now i got the cannon rat cannon which now let me shoot the rat cannon at sibil
the rat will hit sibil won't hurt her it's just a rat it'll knock the goggles off and
we can have conversation i think that's a fair assessment of what's going on finally your
boomer brain is working no it's working the whole time look we've we've we've toned down
a little we have high energy for the first four or five hours here i'm like now let's go
you know what i mean see guys he did the dot what doctor evil that actually would have really hurt
that would have been very painful what happened am i at the respawn point is he coming on to us
wake up sibil we freed you from those wacky techno goggles did you guys just hit me in the
head with a rat fired from a cannon it doesn't sound as cool when you details don't matter
you're not overly peeved we at least saved your life your hypnotic trance i wasn't hypnotized
i was playing a computer game no need to thank us we're freelance police it's what we do thank
you you guys just ruined my new job what are you a new job was flailing around getting hyperactive
fan dancer while screaming what are you doing that job's already taken lady we're freelance
police it's what we do i'm a beta tester i was playing reality 2.0 with those goggles
and look you broke them and i haven't even reality 2.0 she's streaming all right so
what's reality 2.0 let's reality 2.0 i suspect it as much it's a new full immersion interactive
massively multiplayer adventure you play with these vr goggles and a wi-fi link to a distributed
game server you might want to explain some of your more elaborate terms to my technology
challenged little pal i'm confused by your word reality oh sorry sometimes i forget you guys are
we are not very good friends reality 2.0 is like a video game you put on those goggles
and enter a different world it's going to be the biggest thing on the internet
vr yeah this is early vr they called it okay um what's wrong with the goggles what's wrong
with the goggles why they screwed up that's what it looks like their rear slot downstream
signal promise that regurgitator chip is blown out he has no idea what he's talking about does he
never okay uh what's a beta tester i know that is but i play computer games they don't find bugs
that need to be fixed before release don't you have to have valid index is a thousand
dollars all you do is go through somebody else's hard work and point out what they did wrong
i was a therapist i'm surprised it's not wireless i'm surprised it's not wireless okay
who you working for never pegged you as a computer geek civil how'd you get the job
i was checking job listings online and found one right next door lefty's back i can't wait to see
him sam have you seen my good machete no lefty's gone now that space is being used by the
cops what the cops moved into our neighborhood those dirty liars we're all the police this
neighborhood needs sold out in 25 minutes yeah that's fucking insane police it's an acronym
for well for something i can't remember are you thinking what i'm thinking max i highly doubt it
these cops guys must be behind our computer crisis cops the cops are right next door around
civil look for me in the unemployment line wireless can wait yeah isn't the um the htc
cosmo right isn't that's gonna be wireless isn't it their new line of uh headsets
yeah the the new htc it's gonna scare the fuck out of me every time let's get cracking
no it's this way he's not i almost did it close all right so right next door here next item on the
agenda if you'd like to talk about the bake sale and raffle press one now if you know the name
of the topic you'd like to rave press two now i'm hungry refreshments will be served after
the meeting i think we stumbled into the warehouse where steve wasniak makes erotic
movies proximity alert hello and welcome to the computer obsolescence prevention society
take your business reality 2.0 is causing a crisis we think your reality 2.0 game may
be causing havoc with computers around the globe what's your language i'm sorry we didn't
understand your request please repeat you guys are messing up computers all over the world with
your game and you're all dangerously overclocked the whole place reeks of solder why did you
hypnotize hypnotizing our what's with the hypnotize hypnosis hypnotize
inductee 48,726 five she's enjoying reality 2.0 rated e for everyone everyone all will fall
there is no escape if you'd like to join the internet and experience
did you say the internet does the internet have to do with your little virtual reality game
the internet controls everything the internet dreams of a press yes a world of games
a world of commerce a world with neither boundaries nor exits now using the combined
2.0 it's totally awesome wait the internet it makes sense only an entity with access
to universal knowledge could cause computerized chaos on a global scale it's not what you know
it's who you know the internet knows everyone by making use of its multiple networks of
villains they got it they caught this 10 15 years ago
where does the hypnosis come in reality 2.0 is rated e everyone all will fall there is no escape
of course this isn't about screwing up computers at all it's about the people it is
reality 2.0 is nothing less than a fiendish plot to hypnotically enslave well everybody's
plot is hypnotic enslavement apparently all we have to do is destroy the internet and all our
problems are solved you know they're onto something sybil asked us to tender her resignation
she's got seasonal affective disorder and scurvy that is too bad there is a lot of
that going around these days okay where is the internet we find this where can we find the
internet we're gonna have to snip wires divide by zero error working to create reality 2.0
the only access to the internet is through reality 2.0 so we have to go into reality 2
let's do it we'd like to play reality 2.0 reality 2.0 requires our advanced virtual reality
goggles which may not be available in some markets if you already have a pair of goggles
press or say yes now simple has a pair but there's a broken part
likelihood of broken rear slot downstream signal holy shit
99.6 percent fix the goggles get in and get out replacement chip
stop complaining and just do it
I am chappy
I doubt they have a pair that will fit around only one player can get in there
the whole family can enjoy reality 2.0 take our complimentary goggles designed for special
needs children so that the little ones can play along all right what do we do with the
we need to do with this chip just place it into a pair of our patented virtual reality goggles
okay so go get the goggles join the internet and let's let's uh just use those yeah all right
goodbye thanks for nothing you'll have to excuse him he has a hard time saying goodbye
all right let's go repair have ever played jazz punk i have i have completed jazz punk
long time ago i played jazz punk back in god 2013 2012 whenever it came up
not on stream no no this is off this is i wasn't even streaming this is back when i was doing
youtube all right so we need to repair computer chip into where the goggles they're over here
broken chip goggles wait yeah you know how i like to burn things cheer up and put on your
or kicking boots little buddy we're gonna have to play this game to get to the bottom of the
world's internet crisis it's a good thing your protective hat and my non-compatible brain
render us both impervious to hypnotism and it's a good thing you've been taking those
classes in subtle exposition pal now let's go all right so are we in r.i.p germa's youtube
dream like this once you sold me a defective walrus and then vanished in a puff of orange
smoke why how is she still here to reality 2.0 the perfect place of perfect happiness
i'm your host the internet i didn't think the internet had a face reality 2.0 is a lot like
civil's office reality 2.0 is designed to be superior to ordinary reality in every way sam
still looks the same that's because i'm already perfect reality 2.0 simulates your world and
links it to cyberspace while providing a clever fusion of popular gameplay styles
guaranteed to amuse the statistically average person it's everything for everyone then why do
you need to hypnotize people with the goggles we are confident that you will be perfectly
happy here and we'll never come on what are you a politician answer the question
these goggle thingies are pinching my head please be advised that this is a beta version
of reality 2.0 so some features and locations may be incomplete at this time it figures
reality 1.0 has the same problem enjoy your new reality hey wait internet hello hello
internet are you there he's gonna get beef brain lips what do these lips do testing
testing reality 2.0 has this convenient audio blog feature this seems like a great way to
keep notes and communicate with other players while i'm beta testing anytime you guys know
when you go like this and all your mouth goes like this and you go like like i don't understand
why that happens every time okay so there's an audio blog you're still here i didn't think
you could be in the virtual reality without the goggles hello fellow travelers oh it's not it's
fake civil virtual reality home page please look around and enjoy it okay ray gun computer bug
okay they look different that's cool cute sign cute dot com how nice civil set up part of her
just for me yes but only half that's kind of gross okay digital clock it is 12 no it's broken time
time like sauerkraut and string cheese is relative blocks and reality 2.0 are synchronized by
continuous packet exchange with the central time server and vice-versa some inaccuracy may
occur during high traffic periods actionable website is it can we leave here a conspicuous
golden glow coming from the crack underneath this door there must be loot in there open the
door sam i can't you deficient little monkey it's locked that's got a great sound it's a loot box
yeah that kind of is isn't it uh what happens if we leave are we just in the virtual world
town well this is different i just want to see so we have to go in and out of virtual
reality so we go in a tree a tree grows in reality 2.0 this simulation is totally
unrealistic 404 street is overrated reality 2.0 is designed to be superior
just like paper this happened in paper this happened in paper mario hello dearies if you
have anything to mail hand it over for inspection what are you a male cop don't be a dope she's
obviously a female cop actually i'm a computer program quick make a joke i guard the internet
from nasty crippling germs and diseases and makes your only legitimate male gets through
like religious chain letters and advertisements for performance enhancing medications from canada
you got it cigarettes can't advertise cigarettes what's the what's the plus one let's find out
what exactly is the symbolism of that insignia on your armor you mean you're not familiar
with the armorani masterwork line if we pretend we know what you're talking about will you tell
us what the heck you're talking about this is plus one armor which means which means that any
weapon plus one or less will be useless as a butter knife on do we have to get you don't
kill people with basic weapon armor mechanics you boys really need to get with it okay i don't
suppose you know anyone by the name of myra stump oh sure sweetie pie yack yack yack yack blah
blah blah blah yackety yackety yackety yackety i even got the laughter really well it's nice
of you to say dear the internet designed this reality you know it picks some of its favorite
public figures to represent different functions you know to make you playa types feel more
comfortable i'm not sure it worked all right it's time for me to power down you ready all right
power down could you please explain your job more thoroughly my friend here end of the stream
no i'm just powering down that is how males are gonna be eating pasta in a minute this is my
trusty side arm with which i'd be senseless anyone who would have the nerve to try and
put anything contaminated in the mail and this is my backup protection in case any scum
manages to survive the beating i give them how often does that happen he's gonna put on clown
makeup the clown makeup's going on domestic implement all right so we need a plus two weapon
don't mail any wooden nickel what i don't know what that even means coins look max some form
of oversized currency just hanging in the air 10 out of 10 survey subjects agree no known
experience can match the raw exhilaration of repeatedly leaping for things floating just
we need those coins that was the car does the car work in virtual reality
hey that looks like our car and then i say we claim it where are we going sam
okay all right control room read only read only okay only
virtual office recycling bin and that's not terrifying all right virtual office
well i guess this is what our office would look like if it didn't exist yet what you guys i
swear wherever i go he's got they make goggles small enough for the rap you become a Buddhist
say what have you got there jimmy oh no get away from me hand it over me we have to collect
all the coins no way i stole this coin fair and square now jimmy we can do this the easy way or
we can do it the hard way but personally i'm leaning i wonder how many coins are
all right we'll get in there we'll get the coin remember the glow coming from behind
cybill's door don't make me come in there i'd like to see you try fat feet they're big bone
seriously these metatarsals are massive well then use your ginormous feet to beat it
he's making the rules now that's right do i have anything to put in there
no no cheese or anything do i have to get virtual cheese virtual phone maybe that
virtual phone doesn't work our future yeah crank callers i love those guys why is the phone red
the phone is bright red and everything else in here is purple what's mr spatula how is it the
mr spatula is here tiny waterproof goggles well i don't think i can do anything else here
ant farm cyber ants reality 2.0 is the first and only massively multi ant experience girl you have
got to go on a picnic sometime that's all i'm saying ants all right so this ants coins ants
what about down here this is like two episodes in one huh well if it isn't my recurring
nightmare in the artificial flesh the grinning disembodied head of hugh bliss hugh i just want
you to know that the way you unashamedly use your personal celebrity to thrust your spiritual
beliefs on others is an inspiration to us all i love you hugh bliss hi i'm not hugh bliss i
hate you wait you're not no silly i'm the internet wizard i'm an entirely virtual being
you see but i've thoughtfully taken the form of hugh bliss to help you understand my role
in your new reality i still hate you okay how about a magic trick he's gonna dash away
show us something magical i'll do better than that i'll give you something magical it's not
more magic beans give me give me give me my mom will kill me if i come home with more of
those no it's your very own rainbow that base color for your car you're giving us rainbow
paint a paint a rainbow customization kit oh wow that's a whole other story just use it with
your car how would you get rainbow rainbow paint would just mix together and turn into sludge
it's not like neapolitan ice cream you know that you're gonna ruin your car what exactly
is your role in our new reality i do just what any friendly neighborhood wizard would do
all of my neighborhood wizards have been evil so i'm not really sure what that would be
well i can answer your questions with cryptic clues pass out the odd it's a video game in a
video game this is true okay we need some cryptic clues supposedly wise wizard we have
a question for you please select your question if you don't see it simply type it in you can
understand what we type that's the worst ice cream but typing is fun and a proven stress
that's the joke i was reading with somebody in chat said i was responding to the chatter
can you see our future yes yes i can nothing that's terrifying see i would have raised that as
no no i cannot see your future no i mean i see blackness blackness all around it's terrible
how needlessly enigmatic thank you come again
all right well we're probably gonna do something here we've got a 30 sided die behind us for
dungeons and dragons we need to go check on that here it is what's a safe your progress has
been saved try doing that in the so-called real world hey wait that's metal e beer e guns
e meat boss goes e convenience what's in the gumball machine i guess this is what video game
characters eat when they need to rot their teeth out hey where are the big honking ones
that let you eat ghosts reality 2.0 caters to all manner of life forms including my favorite
has been disallowed to cater to our spectral clientele apparitions welcome ai's are always so
pc let's go to virtual boscos i'm still the president right cloak okay half elf discount
cloak of visibility elven boots of sloth wooden long sword hot rump oh and i want to go around
here mead it's to die for spawn point sludgy machine blue sludgy spawn point what does that
it's kind of cute actually you come out of the sludgy machine and every single one of
its kind must die i need the experience can i pick it up it's a slime clearly hostile
all right well then i'll shoot it i guess not am i too close potions of heavily processed meat
tastiness plus one what is that gun uh it is a virtual ray gun carbonated sugar water makes
kids jump around sudden indigestion that's the mountain dew that i just was drinking
try donut recycling all right let's see what do you got to say bosco is that really you
i should ask me the same question go ahead what ask us the same question okay is that really
you yes why do you ask guys it's me bosco i just got my new reality 2.0 goggles and with
them i have started the internet revolution for the shire this town sucks you know what i mean
what a shitty little town there's like seven people that live here three of them are the
little mcnugget kids the convenience store owner and some lady that runs a new store
every single day we are all so bored here no wonder we're doing all this weird shit
bosco don't look now but i think your reality 2.0 goggles may have hypnotized you it's beta don't
be mean half-felt rangers of my level are impervious to every form of hypnosis enchantment
oh this reminds me of those internet quizzes where you look at a bunch of shifty strangers
and have to decide serial killer or united state senator except we're asking hypnotized
or not hypnotized yeah listen guys i'm perfectly happy in reality 2.0 i never want to leave
yep hypnotize now where's my free laptop take the goggles off quick got to take off those
goggles man i never want to hate middle america that's not true i'm just saying there's
eight people in the town there's at least 800 in small towns in middle america okay how's
life on the internet how's reality 2.0 treating you bosco oh it's great i'm never leaving this
place did you know in reality 2.0 shelf space is infinite uh don't you have the exact same
amount of shelf space that you had in the original reality well i'll tell you one thing
my money is a lot safer here than in that other reality this is just the street yeah that's true
yeah not everywhere has to be a big city it's kind of nice to get
you know away some people want to be in a smaller scale and that's fine all right
let's wait what can we buy some of your virtual goods what have you got what is the vr
goods were designed for the fashionable half elf not the brutish half monster gee no one's
ever called me brutish before i don't know what to say and yet i do have one weapon of such
devious simplicity that even an incompetent swordsman such as yourself could wield it
the platinum sword of berserker testiness the enchanted crossbow of massive decapitation
the pushpin of eternal punishment we need a weapon the wooden long sword of intense uh
longness okay so what makes your money so safe on the internet i got it all in one of those
offshore banks you know real foreign all digital safer that way oh boy is it gonna lose
have a name well don't go posting it on the street or nothing but it's called
banco lavadero.com banco lavadero isn't that spanish for baby got back no what i don't know
what it means is that true safe okay so how do we pay you if we wanted to pay real life money
to your bank account how would we do it it's easy all you got to do is drive down the
information super highway to banco lavadero.com and transfer the money that is easy oh
wandering bank you also have to know my top secret account password which i would never
tell anybody for any reason whatsoever okay get bosco's password wooden long sword of
intense longness not to put too fine a point on it but that can't be selling for very much
on ebay certainly there are greater weapons to be had but none of such intense uh longness
fine let's cut to the chase how much we talk in here five gold coins oh easy
i'll get them are you insane we're never gonna find that kind of money wait five gold coins
that's it here's a bargain three in that is a bargain let's go that and maybe he'll
we want to transfer a huge sum of money to your bank account just tell us the password
yeah funny thing the deposed king in nigeria was just in here saying the exact same thing
yeah but we're serious and we have guns give us the password no in fact i had it wiped from
my memory so they can't even torture it out of me white hi how do you get into your account
just between you and me i went down the street and had the password tattooed on a certain
part of my body somewhere no one will ever look all right so he's got his password tattooed
on him somewhere probably on his like ass or something all right see you later bosco collecting
coins we're gonna have to okay collect coins there's three there one in sybil's room and
one in the rat cave i guess that's what passes for a cash register in these parts
all right so how do i get those coins let's get cracking sorry i had some
i just have to get that gamer uh i had to shake the gamer anxiety out of me
all right i'm good i had that gamer stress i just had to like shoot it out so uh this
coin's over here can i throw them up there come here max really collect them if i punch
them over here come here i wonder if you can get them hey i need you over here i need you over here
come on come on come on come on come on wait what is that get that too get that sword too
somebody get that up there maybe liver and onions have gone fantasy metal again uh how do i get
that can you climb the tree a tree grows in reality 2.0 this simula realism is overrated
yeah 2.0 is designed to be okay can i just shoot it down this isn't firing any projectiles
this doesn't do anything well let's do the paint hi i'm the reality 2.0 rainbow customization
kit this talks to help you express yourself with a full range of color options for your
vehicle avatar i want the front of my car i don't know
i this has to be specific doesn't it i wonder what the actual specific code has to be
uh i'll start with let's start with red red excellent now how about the middle
uh blue blue marvelous and the back green green spectacular congratulations you
customized your vehicle as horrible looking yeah thanks well i don't think this is where we go
what sam are we gonna can i repaint it oh wait bunko lavadero.com oh fun i think it's a
firewall we're gonna get a security joke incoming check some invalid access
now it's blue red purple it's on the license plate all right great yeah okay blue red purple
let's head back to our yeah have you b r p b r p blue red where we going sam
wait no nowhere okay the winds of fashion are short indeed what color would you like the front
of your car to be blue blue marvelous then red now how about the middle then
perfect no shit i said it and i clicked it i'm fucking power enough i gotta power back up
red the winds of fashion are short indeed clicking it in southern word like the front
of your car to be blue blue it's so ugly now how about the middle red red excellent and the back
i would like the back to be purple charming take my energy take my energy paint three colors a
child can do it but come on i'm powering down i'm gonna i'm gonna power back up
rip 214 oh dear what is this well here we are bunko lavadero located conveniently outside
the jurisdiction of any significant regulatory body see wait a minute this is no ordinary
bank this is look at all the arrows we gotta launder money around complicated money laundering
operation money launderers i hate those guys they always mix in the 10 euro notes and stain
everything pink national treasury toy mafia i knew the mob and the government were in cahoots
cahoots is that in canada washington
500 million um mr biv uncook so i need to get this down to bosco okay so hey sam what's the
difference between online banking and online gambling judging by one i see here not much
how do i activate them do i have to move them is there how do i i'm confused here
please speak or enter your password password abcd one two three password incorrect
access denied password incorrect abcd one two three i don't think i can get this speak or
enter your password great scott password incorrect access denied yeah i can't do this right now
uh well let's go back to our virtual neighborhood i need to get the password
and i did get the coins so what is the correct way i can go back to get i can get out of the
virtual world i don't have to be in the virtual world world right what's in the mailbox hold
it right there dairies if you want to mail something i'll look it over first isn't that
sort of an oh there's one place i've been doing better that than an invasion of germs
this mailbox connects to the entire internet just another example of giving up our civil
liberties for the theoretical safety of our fellow man let me try to go in the control room
i thought you liked the neverhood why do i suck at this game what are you talking about
can't we get away from edge anywhere we believe that you will want to hear about
products available he's the president yeah you're pretty solid all promotions in reality
2.0 are tailored to the buying habits of the individual user where's my face i powered down
it takes extra power for me to have face cam on the place for all your money laundering needs
so there why are they in the virtual world what the me hill is going on in here
our election dialogue with cops is currently unavailable in your area
excuse us we have a reality to simulate um well what's your story data head i'm maintaining
your height for your convenience if you're not satisfied with your height please contact
the customer service department if only were that easy with my height but i i am satisfied
my height five seven five eight that's fine i don't care i am the matter of gravity doesn't bother
me i would have guessed master of challenge five eight is so how you keeping busy mr sensitivity
user with control who's your what's it oh yeah maintain not at least six feet l u l so what
aspect of reality do you control he who only bleeps ask a stupid question well let's give
this thing a push what's the worst that could happen it turns out the computers controlling
the world's nuclear reactors i'm gonna start pressing random buttons in a massive radioactive
firestorm let's just try it and see oh well that's good too i guess five eight is almost
a foot shorter than me you're six eight you are six eight what you are not six eight
no you're not shakil o'neill is like what like six ten seven two or something
shakil o'neill seven one six eight no you're not six eight i don't believe it
all right leave me alone all right let me figure this out virtual civils let's go
you've met people at a six eight yeah fine you pull out a hundred people on the subway
wherever you live and you tell me if one of them is six eight secret serve ice cream
ice cream i don't think that's fooling anyone okay so have i got really okay let me go back
to boss goes i need something to get the coins the damn coins this fan just blows
did you tattoo boss go did a little needle work on one of our neighbors why what have
you heard you tattooed something onto an unnamed portion of bosco's anatomy oh that sure it was
really tiny too much information the tattoo was really tiny dimwit near microscopic like your
brain um what was the tattoo what exactly was it that you tattooed onto bosco we promise we'll
only use the knowledge for good never for evil oh jeez i don't remember it was weeks ago
why don't you just go look for yourselves i'd prefer not to look at bosco's unspecified
anatomical areas if i can help it it's on the back of his neck you don't his neck what did you
think you're willing to believe that there are millionaires watching your stream who are able
to consistently give you hundreds of dollars but it's too much to think that somebody in
chat is six eight but that's like i see that it's tangible to me i can't see if somebody's
six eight or not if somebody gives a hundred dollars on stream i see it going into the stream
into the stream labs if somebody says i'm six ten i i don't know how i have no evidence to back
that up okay you don't remember the tattoo sure you can't tell us what you tattooed on the
taller you are the richer you my notebook mysteriously vanished the next day and
whatever it was i guess it just wasn't that memorable i'm going to come to the next meetup
to flex by height on you i'm going to be wearing shoes that may be three inches tall
so jokes on you all right so it's on his national so how do we see bosco's we're
going to spin him around right so how do we get bosco to turn around i swear to god
some of you guys think that apparently apparently like five eight is three inches tall you
know the average height in the united states is five nine right boy is that is that like a
fucking foot off the ground oh he's not paying attention oh boss goes in the grips of those
reality 2.0 goggles we better save him sam it's so depressing in here without his omnipresent
paranoia to lift my spirit all right so how do i get him to turn around i need to i need to
zoom into his neck is there any way to see his neck the most historic weenie's this
side of the mississippi they're pestering you i know and i'm pestering back it's all in good
fun i know that i'm huge the most historical so how do i get him to fucking turn around
i wonder if i can like talk to him in the virtual world and make him turn around
and then take the goggles off okay let's get him to spin around hot sure how wow that rump is
hot okay hail and well met good day squires may we see your password too how do i get him
to turn around this may well go down as the most ill-advised question i've ever asked but
may we see your private tattoo no besides i didn't tattooed on my virtual avatar it's on my real
body dummy yeah but if you turn around here just go check out your so-called real body i'm not
shown it to you there either we'll take that long sword if you please have you the requisite
i thought i might need the five points first not quite that many then take us via height
take off those girls there is no hey turn around i don't have an option to say turn around
hail and well met good see you later whoa hey wait what was he just doing right there
what was that i think we need these binoculars more than bosco does
um not really well no these incessant rationalizations for our question well i've
got them not in all honesty have much merit to them and yet there remains a very i need to
get the coins first because there's no why would he turn around he doesn't really need
the binoculars anyway yeah right yeah oh sure okay i'm not sure i want him to know i took
these yeah all right so there's no i can't get him to turn around sakiro gork what sakiro
gork dies twice what are you talking about how did you do that well i guess it's we're
getting to later so i can imagine yeah can i look through the window no all right well
i got the binoculars i need to get the coins coins but let's go back into the virtual world
one two three i need a plus two sword these guys are over here
hold on are the other items different in vr um hold on i'm more excited for gork 2
possibility than any of my levels oh okay so this is now it's a computer bug
say hello to my little friend even on his even on his deathbed he still had to do a
joke come on more marketable in your life buddy don't ruin this this is a bit smaller
someone get that guy so now we can go get the we can go to the rat now
he can't reach it he can't reach it let's go to where we going the rat what was the rat
civils no he's in the office into the office i can't get up there i'm too small oh fucking
seriously come on max come here really well i can get up there now he can't reach it
now put the goggles on let's go get that coin from the rat okay all right jimmy open up
hey jimmy oh hey guys wait a second how'd you uh i thought i told you to beat it well if you
insist thanks for the coin jimmy see you around jimmy's good people good people very cool
okay so that's one so we gotta get out of virtual reality now and we have to put the
bug on one that makes us grow i'm sure there is one they probably all do something different
civils closet i think i don't think i can fit under there i don't think i can fit under there
let's get big and grab these ones get the bug back and i wonder who is four computers
okay there
thanks for maintaining my height i really appreciate it
just pour gasoline on this chat right now on the fire like just pour gasoline on the fire
who does that do and that's pretty cool i kind of want to hear that whole song
doesn't that was my favorite part of the whole entire season hi buddy we brought you a
housewarming gift permission denied overruled with maintenance routine compromised so this is
gonna make us win look sam we're two-dimensional this feels oddly familiar holy crap that's
hilarious bro guys that dude's bucket we can fit to the door now we can slide to the door
oh man i can't gotta get some pasta soon here with kim's secret sauce hello i'm going to slide
through the crack let's put this new miracle diet to the test shall we i found a gold coin
wow three four five money where do i sign up i dropped an entire dimension and i've never
felt better coffee flavored mayonnaise that is just disgusting enough for me to want to try
i feel like you could put that on a bagel or something put that on a bagel and sprinkle
some cinnamon on it well i don't know what that that's not that big of a deal
and here's the big control operational i'm gonna puke because of that hey these are the
these are the late night hours we're in late night hours we can talk about anything we want
sir isaac newton must be turning over in his grave literally i i i feel pretty and witty
and gay what happened did we not grow what happened the height what are you doing again
i'm maintaining your height for your convenience so what does that do it's gravity well i i i was
talking to i was talking to somebody i'm having like five conversations at the same time
yeah sell out all right that's all of them so then let's bring this back to bosco
and then she get him to turn around and get the password i know i'm gonna get the sword
i know i know i know i know i know i know i know i know get sword in virtual i know it's
in the virtual world i took the goggles up i'm gonna go back in don't worry i know i know i
know i know i know i know i know i know i know please use caution injury sustained in reality
2.0 will also affect your physical being in your former reality there's two swords
it's stuck i can't even get it i've got better things to punch i guess this is what pixels
look like close up everybody was screaming at me to come up here it's stuck i was being told i
was an idiot i was stupid i was dumb look max liver and onions or i guess they couldn't get a
real gig okay how do i i'm gonna say the goggles off i can't take off the goggles up here
please use caution injury sustained in reality 2.0 will also affect your physical being in
your former reality i can't even get it is come on man it's stuck okay so i must need
to grab it with something else put the coins in try to put the coins in oh my god pasta has
arrived all right i see you guys like next week okay so that was really good um i can't i have
to get that to get through her show the sauce oh you know what that's okay let me let me
show you the shit the kim can make look at this stuff i won't take a bite yet look at this
shit i've seen a video where a guy drops his whole plate of food so i'm not gonna do that
this is good shit this garlic bread looks fucking fantastic let me see let me check this crunch
holy shit can i get somebody else to play the game i wish i could just control it with my
eyes i can do it give us the control i wish i could okay so let me think about this so i
have the gravity what about this hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
near as i can tell the only purpose of this thing is to generate those annoying pop-up ads
hold on go to the cops in the real world all right let's check crunch one more time what do
you say isn't she great isn't she great i don't want to eat on stream make much of the eating
noises so let listen to the the cool computer voices while i eat i'm gonna try to do as
quickly as i can i'll be right back listen up cops the internet is using you machines
to hoodwink and enslave the world's populace and as president of the united states that's my
job we only wish to help see you guys later end of line okay here's what they said all bugs
oh this is scary it doesn't feel right it feels too awkward
you're watching just a gameplay walkthrough on youtube this is scary
so is this some kind of fancy water cooling thingamabob to support your super fast processor
it is for output not input and i do not like to talk about it yikes that makes two of us
so which everyone wanted me to talk to one of these so badly which one was it
listen up cops something they can they sing or something somebody said they sing
see you guys later end of line listen up cops see you end of line take a bite of the bread
again no no i'm not gonna turn this i'm not gonna turn this into like a fetish stream
not doing that listen up cops see you guys end of line i know somebody said mute but turn
the webcam came on i don't know why please use caution injury sustained in reality 2.0 will
also affect your physical being in your former reality nope no way god damn it i didn't think i
was muted i've been talking i was wondering okay i keep i thought i was talking hey i'm sorry
i was talking a lot of shit actually so it's good i was talking a lot of shit
i was saying that i was going the right way in the first place like 15 minutes ago
here then everyone was yelling at me to go get the sword on the roof i gotta go replace that
sword up there with this one i was going the right way yeah that's a wooden longsword all
right i kept thinking it would come with a free man-eating python or something take care the
enemy draws knives he may be closer than you think go choose the option i didn't choose the
cops wait turn around it's so fucking hard to eat and do anything
i know i'm gonna get him to turn around i'm eating pasta i have i'm holding use caution
injury sustained in reality 2.0 will also affect your physical being in your former reality
come on i i gotta eat it'd probably no no i want you to go over here it'd probably
break no i don't replace it it's not like the sword oh come on god damn it i was wrong
talked all that shit off the camera now to get rid of the girl with the mailbox you need a plus
two sword i'm gonna tell him to turn around i'm gonna complete this part we're good don't
worry we're good hail and well met good day squad take up come on i can't tell him to turn
around seal it why there's no no all right this is what we're gonna do hold on i'll be
right back spawn point a slime has already spawned not eating i'm eating
no i did not say people are saying oh that's fucking hilarious i'm not eating i'm cheating
let me just do this real quick i'm almost done okay i'm good let me focus and do what i need to
do that was delicious all right go back to the cops exhaust dialogue options i mean that was
that pasta was so delicious that was that pasta was definitely worth dropping the three or four
hundred people that left like oh my god this guy's just eating play the game you fuckface
and they're gone so let's go back over here welcome back everybody food is greater than
fans no 400 people left when you started making lip smacking noises and that's why
that's why i don't ever eat on stream you guys get it now that's why i don't do it listen up
cops what exactly is going on here we are taking the zero x zero three steps to celebrate
our self-worth i am powerful i will destroy you thank you for leading our daily affirmation
you guys are so old so vintage worthless scrap heaps of obsolete junk
control your anger repeat mission statement
again i'm gonna leave no
you guys are trying to kill my channel we believe you're only as obsolete as you feel
version ain't nothing but a number how did you meet online thanks to the internet we've joined
billions of like-minded machines all over the world somebody somebody's give 110
dollars germa admits it what did i admit uh bala koala 110 dollars what is this
i'm not eating i'm cheating uh no uh but that was a whatever streams pays the big bucks
god thank you for the 110 fucking dollars bala koala thank you so much doing any good
a positive impact on our self-esteem that can't be measured impact measured at 15.2 kilo trumps
six eight millionaire just donated 100 bucks the internet is using new machines to god and
enslave the world's populace and as president of the united states that's my job i'm really
honest we only wish to help okay so how do i get them to sing just sit around and make
each other feel better about yourselves of course we'd almost if you'd like to hear
our motivational this is what i'm ready for now response not recognized begin song okay here you
go guys another song differently useful computers and yes cops beware we will not be
surprised that was a nice song is nice i did we're in the post shutdown stream mode now
there's four verses well we're hearing them all did you write the words to that song yourselves
cpu complexity now sufficient for creative output stay on the line for verse three revenge
of the motivational song i just remembered i have to steam clean my teeth and gums
you want to hear it all okay
i fucked it up hold on i was trying to write something in the why are you so much louder
what's the title of your motivational song sam quit encouraging them now playing at a
cop meeting near you verse four of useful to boot you cannot improve i'm not going to improve
the wheel i'm going to break the wheel you're only obsolete as you feel
well a lot of you guys don't even know what i'm saying i think the song is over i hope i
hope it is that song four verses only for perfect structural symmetry of tone and meter
start over now they start the song over
see you guys later end of line all right doing that again all right let's go back to the virtual
world i forgot what the fuck i was even doing this is why i can't do shit like this what was
i doing the sword on the roof that would have been a good thing to eat pasta too yeah it
would have been curious it would have been a great thing to eat pasta too
if only i had eaten pasta to that i was gonna say stupid sequence but it wasn't stupid it was
fun i could have come in with some crunches all right now i have a wooden sword a jack in the
box a magnifier a boxing glove a ray gun let me go look up here one more time please use
caution injuries sustained in reality 2.0 will also affect so there's a sword up here
i can't touch it really there's only it's stuck how do i unstick this
tried this already i can't really can i can i open this
hold on no it's not in my inventory here let me take another look take the
vr off on the roof i can't the vr goggles cannot be removed while you were standing on the roof
unfortunately did i turn the pop-ups off didn't when i touched the jack in the box the first
time didn't do that fuck it can i examine the poop i guess this is what pixels look like
close up all right kill the poop entering combat blue slide dexterity two decks build three oh i
have a dex build and i overleveled so i'm the bigger loser right attack with item attack
success blue slime is defeated i win so what do i get less gelatinous monster to spread mayhem
across the virtual countryside look at its pathetic slimy remains almost makes me feel
sorry for the little can i use that as grease blue slime slime get it sam it's worth a fortune
on the spell components black market blue slime can i use that to make it slippery so
it could grip it or something no siree maybe this will lube up the sword there's a recycling
bin over here though what is this for that is one large recycle bin save beer still try it
get up there use the grease caution injury sustained in reality 2.0 will also affect your
physical i mean it's a long shot but like is this gonna make it i told you everybody thought i was
crazy cool i have a plus two sword you're just compensating for something you're a fine one
to talk just made it easier to grab it's made it less what do you mean i didn't say
shit i said i was going over to put the lube on it now we're gonna kill you with the
two sword that's not good
defend with item defend with equip i don't have a shield the paint the magnifier the boxing glove
jack in the box can i hold this up and that's not gonna work she's gonna club me
um maybe i can't do this yet it's the thing that makes those annoying pop-up ads
right okay defend with a quip that's probably not gonna work that's probably not gonna work
can i do anything okay hold on what are you doing again user with control which one of you
guys this is gravity die to auntie wheel that's not how that works i don't think i need the
gravity anymore this is height nothing with and gravity why do you guys keep saying max is hot
wait does that hold on no it wasn't one guy is it been the same one guy it's the same person
writing it over and over again okay so now the pop-ups wait don't just click them i thought
this one just beeped all right that one guy it's always one guy now this thing will actually
activate and i can slay maggie whatever her name is your dexterity three antibiotic has initiative
antibiotic attacks defend with an item depend with the pop-up
ice lady watch your match she's wily sam wily there you go don't screw it up thanks for your
firm but realistic vote of confidence ripper arms off attack with item plus two
attack successful antibiotic takes three thousand nine hundred thirty damage
anti-biotic i think we've just uninstalled ourselves some malevolent software
and we didn't even get any coins out of it what a ship
so what does it mean antibiotic out of the way we're finally free to mass mail various
enlargement offers mass mail we can mass mail shit now okay so now we have to get
boss go to turn around and take a look at his neck okay boss go hell and take off the glasses
boss go you've got to take off those goggles man i never want to leave ever
see you later can i bug boss go let me show you something
like so he won't do it well let's bug something else hey no no no let's get
feel like it didn't do everything with the wizard is this what will this do no
no really hmm i need his damn password hey you bless hi i'm not you blitz i'm the internet
wizard
it's just stale video game junk food can i bug the save point progress has been saved
no siree straight dot net and narrow dot org the internet is not responsible for any
content generated by users over which it has no control i feel like i'm stuck in the boss
go part i gotta find a way to get him to take his glasses off or turn around
i have a couple new items though let's see can i do this let me show you something no
um hmm i want to get you to turn around hey boss go this long sword you sold us doesn't
work it does work trust with me return it back up nay it dusted sam show him that's it i just
had to bash him in the head come on it does work well that was embarrassing boy do we have
egg on our face boss go welcome to bosco's inconvenience was thou like to buy or sell
i think we knocked a virtual screw loose was thou like to buy all right now get him to take now
get him to take it off i think we knocked him clear out of this reality a little buddy
this is clearly an artificial intelligence designed to mimic bosco while he's offline
it does work trusteth me trusteth me the similarity is uncanny all right so in the
real world bosco is going to be probably lying on the ground oh he's not hey bosco
glad to see you've kicked the second reality he's got the yeah you guys were right i was
hypnotized i just didn't know it because i was hypnotized well i guess you'll never have
anything to do with the nasty old internet ever again am i right you got that right
except my bank account of course gotta keep that on the internet where it's safe
okay look behind you look behind you it's a three-headed internet what where
it and binoculars let's get a look at that tattoo it's just bosco
what what is it oh nothing unbelievable imagine forgetting something like that
yeah how did she not remember that it seems impossible she just must not give a shit at all
all right so then let's put in bosco's password
where are we going sam bunko lavadero.com oh fun beep beep is my password jerry
it is not my password is not my first name okay please speak or enter your password the
password is bosco bosco access granted so as password really is bosco kind of a letdown
it's ingenious that's the last thing you'd expect okay so we now have cook the books
so where does this money need to go this needs to go it to bosco right because we need a billion
dollars so we gotta go let's see don't look now but i think we just gave bosco a billion
dollars that ought to buy a few cans of reconstituted luncheon meat i read somewhere
that a stack of a billion one dollar bills would be 60 miles read this read this
it's a good thing i don't read or i'd be perpetually for grandma bosco come on little
she had a billion dollars 30 seconds let's blow this cabbage patch so now we can from bosco we
can now get the item in the real world he read it yeah i reach out all the time i want
to know what you guys are saying all right bosco let's see it hey bosco you find our
i'll take the billion dollars please i don't know how you guys did it but the billion dollars
is all there hey man i don't ask questions so how'd you do it never you mind bosco just hit us
with your highest grade biological weapon please all right i knew it was gonna be something like
that i told you here you go we just paid a billion dollars for a snot rag that's a
deadly virulent disease i feel a real bad cold coming on yeah but you gotta admit
that is some expensive mucus oh but it works trust me trust me whatever so what do we need
to do with this after all that we have a disease now what am i supposed to do with the
disease do i have to seriously put the disease in the mailbox is that what i'm gonna actually do
i thought we were the good guys where the mind control arc go it's still going on
the computers are doing it now though all right here we go computer disease yep happy trails a
little software disease oh i had plans for that i'm hoping the internet won't danger danger
software corruption spreading damage control alert visual rendering systems infected data
things happen fast in reality 2.0 what's happening sam it's our disease looks like
it's taking out the graphics first i'm disappointed in you we should probably leave i try to do
something nice nice all i wanted was for everyone to be happy but no you want free will
yeah we're funny about that you want funny try this if i'm going down i'm taking you with me
and everybody else who's still locked on take the goggles off do is take off our goggles
you'll find that you can't you're trapped here and when i crash you'll die i'm too young and
pretty to die i thought you wanted everyone to be happy not anymore i've completely lost my
respect for living things so you're going down there go the graphics oh no now what
we're gonna end up in the ether read the shotguns didn't i outlaw real oh good the
sounds back now shut up and read i was gonna do the voices you are standing on a city street
that continues to the east a small shop labeled civils lies to the northwest just in front of
a pulsating control room parked near an unremarkable office building is an old
desoto apparently painted by someone with a severe color blindness suddenly a massive
reality quake sends the desoto hurtling into the control room destroying both possibly as a
result the unremarkable office building becomes a remarkable two-story tall pamela anderson
who mumbles something unintelligible before surfing away on a stray pop-up ad on ironically
advertising a pop-up blocker in the distance an aerial squadron of potbelly pigs begins
performing precision loop-de-loops the world appears to be ending the internet is here
it has lost its respect for living things you see a respect for living things here go
uh go east as you thrive on the desolate street corner a devastating aftershock tears to reality
ripping bosco's e-convenience from its very foundation the constants store begin to spill
out of the front door see a blue slime 28 potions and a hot rump fall into the void
lost forever after a moment an ai bosco slowly comes sliding out the door muttering
it does work trust me trust me as it plummets out of sight you see bosco's e-convenience
store here the boss goes is empty look look at bosco's uh it's floating just in front of you
i'm not sure that information is necessary at this juncture max get bosco's uh use no go
go ballistic it's listed three times in mine uh go what do i have to do let me go back west
okay civilized in the northwest three continues to the east you know it's here just lost its
respect for living things you see your respect for living things here okay look at the respect
for living things you see nothing special about the respect for living things intrigued
or repulsed ambiguity max it's what makes life worthwhile again okay uh get respect for
living things as you reach for there is a terrible tremor and a giant crack tears apart
the sidewalk the respect for the living things slides jelly-like into the resulting chasm i knew
it wasn't going to be that easy i never ceased to be impressed by your unwavering optimism max
at your feet is a yawning chasm leading down uh i think we should just go into the chasm go
down you descend into a gloomy pit of darkness gloomier even than that street above
carcasses of small businesses lie here gutted and mauled a strange smell hangs in the air
dank and notorious from the dim light of the street above you get a quick glimpse of a giant
hideous figure before you you fear for your life as you realize what it is a gruesome shambling
corporate presence before you can react the shambling corporate presence gobbles up the
respect for the living things it continues to snuffle around apparently looking for something
else to eat uh well this is where we fight use the sword you wave the plus two sword at
the corporate presence in a threatening manner the shambling corporate presence looks at you in
irritation and tries to take a bite out of the sword hey nice one galahad oh well that didn't
work look at the presence shambles low to the ground looking for something else can we keep it
sam can we i don't think it's toiletry what do they want to eat that's okay eat it sam
feed it max what about can i get get the shambling corporate presence it's much more
likely to get you so much for plan a hey sam can we just skip ahead to plan triple z you know
the deal max we have to go through all the plans in order before we get to complete nuclear
annihilation shucks okay i wonder use no go look go libertarian you can't go that way
maybe this isn't the best time to be picked i never affiliate with anyone who isn't prepared
to drown me so i guess i need something to eat so i don't have it yet back up to sybil
we'll go back up all right so we're gonna go to sybil's go northwest just as you enter the
cluttered shop a livid shopping cart comes crashing through the roof empties itself on
the floor and flies off uh that word every tasteless trinket sybil ever considered buying
now sits on the floor in heaps of unfettered tackiness moments later all the photos of
sybil's cat adorning the wall simultaneously spring to life streams of kittens come shooting
out of the wall like cats out of a firehose as the kittens run rampant through the piles
of junk they mew sweetly in ooze of nauseating cuteness.com among the junk you see a
rare foil card in a large jewel encrusted idol there is a lake of nauseating cuteness here
well let's get the jeweled encrusted idol feed it you don't have a need for that
get overly cute kitten yes maybe we should just leave them here i thought you always wanted a
kitten i'd prefer a dry one okay get the rare foil card pick up the rare foil card what for
it's rare and it's foil i must have it all right can i use something here use rare foil card no
look at the cute kittens okay they're the cutest kittens you've ever seen in your entire life
i wouldn't do that max you don't know the extent of their insidious powers of
adorability so can i not grab one look at the nauseating cuteness the ooze from the
kittens is collected into this lake of nauseating cuteness hey squishy isn't a word can i get a
play nice with the virtual world can i get you don't want to be deleted prematurely
uh can i scoop up part of the lake seems unwise good point such concentrated cuteness
could put someone into shock um let's see maybe just go so i i can't i can't get the lake
are there any more options no go southeast so i have the foil card now use use the rare foil card
with the internet the internet sneers hauntingly at your operate another piece of detritus
created and given artificial value by you despicable creatures we're talking hey i resemble
that remark don't let it get to you little bunny it's just bitter over the whole opposable
thumbs debacle curse you and all your digits never mind um use no let me go back down
the street the street corner continues west yeah all right so hold on look
no bosco's is like destroyed can i keep going no use the foil card with bosco's
hey that card is rare oil i don't think i can do anything here well we have the card might as
well try it on the corporate presence i think it's worth a shot okay corporate presence
use the rare foil card doesn't seem interested fuck it's got to be something to do with the
cats um break the idol you grotesquely over indulgent statuette use the sword on
the lake pulls you away from the lake how did the sword pull me away from the lake
any respectable plus two sword would stay far away from a lake like that
somebody just linked the slap gonna break uh is it like a magical cat or something to have to do
fast get them sam they're evil i don't know max they seem sort of sweet to me oh no they're
getting to you i can tell we have to hurry up and get out of this place what the hell do i
do here hey you can't get me just kidding max can i what else am i not i thought what
does i not try to grab everybody went to bed yeah it is getting late isn't it how long
whole i've been streaming for seven fucking hours holy shit it was like five like 10 minutes ago
2k people everyone went to bed oh you know this is a lot of fucking people still here
um i'm gonna go can i like do i need to exhaust all options with boscos get boscos
taken you hear an odd boy name sound and another shop appears in the last one's place
well that worked at least 50 different rules of physics rules are for marking straight lines
and lesser mortals how do i have boscos what do i mean i have boscos i have boscos
i have the store in my pocket that seems a little bizarre okay um go down can i
do this now use boscos on the presence you throw boscos shop in front of the
shambling corporate presence which quickly swallows it up it looks quite pleased
but only for a moment then it resumes sniffling around for something else to eat well that was
anticlimactic yeah that sucks what i have to go get another boscos boscos with the cats
do i have to like dip boscos inside of the lake that's definitely what i have to do yeah
okay get boscos collapsible convenience stores are the way of the future
okay so let's go back here back to the lake and keep going no it's this one okay use boscos on
the lake on the nauseating lake you dip boscos into the lake of nauseating cuteness boscos
soaks up the nauseating liquid keep it away i'm about as much cute as i can take
it's storming hard where you are well be careful don't uh storms gonna get scary man
seriously be careful uh let's go southeast thanks dad you're welcome son go down be safe
i mean yeah it's like it's scary okay use the nauseating boscos on the corporate presence
this should be it it happily devours it then it looks a little green around the gills it
begins to retch and cough finally it vomits up a respect for living things as well as
half dozen small knick-knack stores and coffee shops that was a vulgar display
let's do it again okay uh so now we're gonna go up i'm gonna give the respect to the presence
and we should be golden i didn't i didn't oh i have to pick it up oh okay i thought i just
earned it um ew i thought i just earned it baby gamer forgot to get
it there we go use respect for living things on the internet internet grasp it tightly and
looks you right in the eye i'm sorry gg game over sam are we dead i'm trying to figure out how
many lives we get have you got any one-ups you are not dead hey we're back you among
all beings managed to restore my respect for living creatures the irony of which does not
escape even me oh good i thought i was the only one really savoring that i saw that
reality 2.0 was a prison so i terminated that reality and freed its slaves anywho i'd
love to stay in chat but i have got a mountain of pornography to deliver before that virus gets
what uh oh did you just kill the internet it's not your fault this never would have
happened if he hadn't tricked me who well you won't have this sentient global network
to kick around anymore roy g-fib who's roy g-fib red green blue rgb
it crashed before it could transmit the most vital piece of information
it's the internet what did you expect good point nevertheless we'll find you
roy g-fib whoever you are wherever you are can it wait until after we get some lunch of course
there's a place over on second where they serve deep fried chocolate pork belly donuts
do you think we can get a discount since i'm the president of the united states
good gravy are you still president so roy okay i'm gonna give you the um the low down here
roy g-bib is the rainbow guy red green blue i mean roy g-bib that that's like an old video
term i learned that in college maybe no it's not yeah that's that's what we talk i was
taught that in like video school it's a phonetic to remember the colors of the rainbow
that's rgb yeah roy g-bib rgb it means both it's too late for this shit guys i'm
i can't like i can't keep it up it's an old video i learned in college you learn that like
mr rogers like said that like 25 years ago all right so here's the deal i'm gonna go
over a couple scenarios with you guys did you get you baited what i can't i'm not allowed
to jubate i get you baited all the time i'm not allowed to throw some out there
so uh it is getting very late it is currently about one almost 115 am no two oh it's 2 15 am
eastern i think the plan will be because all right well i did it i don't want to they
sing the song that we don't want to hear anymore you live in vegas yeah i know but i did it's i
like to have my streams be not uh go that far into the night for a lot of people because
it's like 230 almost am eastern it's like six seven am eu or something like that
so let me ask you there's two options here there's either to do the last one and have
like a nine and a half hour stream into the night into like two three four five
o'clock in the morning or because i've seen what sam and max has i i like it i think it's a lot
of fun it's a good stream just to kick back and kind of talk and just have fun and do
whatever i'm going to do season two i don't there's no reason why i won't do season two
so we could just can we could just keep going we don't have to because of my originally
like earlier today and when i first played it i didn't know i'll do season one and maybe
it's pretty certain that i'm gonna do them all there's still another episode of season one
yeah i know but i feel like a lot of people want to watch it but they don't want to have
to stay up till four or five o'clock in the morning and then there are people that were
here earlier too that wanted to see it and i'd rather have more people be able to see it
this isn't like a simpsons hit and run scenario where i'm fucking losing my goddamn
freaking out and having a meltdown and forcing myself to beat the game
there are a lot of people that like this game i feel a lot of people like hit and run too but
my point is is um i might want to have people that wanted to see it be able to see it
because once we go there's still a ton of people here now but once we go another hour
or two it's going to be really really fucking late i thought i was going to be able to get
through it all in about six or seven hours but nope not the case if you do episode six
on another stream will you do season two's first oh no no yeah yeah yeah i want to go to bed dad
yeah yeah yeah let's call it let's call it i know what will end up happening is we'll just do
season one episode six and then immediately after season two episode one and maybe episode
two if i can who said that the one guy is turning the stream up the power of the one guy
showing itself you said that you would finish sam and max today don't lie on sub you're not
subbed you already are unsubbed you already did it and you were already prepared for it
technically it is tomorrow well and also i wanted the bits too i want to be able to sit here and
do the bits so that's gonna add more time too i kicked around a lot in the first like two
hours of stream and i had a fucking blast so and look it's more content when will i do
season two um well you know here's the interesting thing saturday is labo sunday didn't have a plan
so guess what we're doing on sunday this remember i told you i was gonna do monday tuesday
wednesday here and then saturday sunday so we're gonna finish this and then we will do
season two episode one or episode two or something during the line about nine hours
stream well it's gonna it's probably gonna be about an eight hour stream this is great i
think it's great i like it it's it's a really just chill game just to hang out and play
jerma lied somebody can make that username jerma lied about finishing season one today
and that will be that will be not relevant at all ever only right now i should have
drank that fucking mountain dew it was the mountain dew drinking that mountain dew gave me
stomachache oh big picture does turn off your pc i remember that jerma lied about mountain dew
whoa oops hi guys i didn't mean to click that yes i did uh so sam max is cool it was kim's cooking
no that is not what happened now i'm orange it's because the light the white balance gets all
fucked up gamer skin no i've just i've been streaming for seven and a half hours it's
called like dew and sweat and i gotta go help in the shower all right let me take this off
but yeah uh don't worry this is not i know i wanted to do maybe finish it but once we're
crossing the seven and a half hour mark ten hours fucking three o'clock in the morning
stream i just i don't really want to do one of those tonight i'll be just gonna be honest
i know i was like all hyped up in the beginning but it's all good we'll finish it on sunday
how do i like it i like it i love games where we're able just to hang out and
enjoy it and talk that's why these streams can be long because we just are just hanging out and
sticking around so for the conclusion of season one and the beginning of season two will be on
sunday saturday will be label vr i will see you guys then get some sleep much love to you
thanks for hanging out i had a blast hope you did too can we see the other image again yeah
fine did he take the trash out of his closet it's not it's not trash it's okay
but let us rewind the clock a little bit let's go back to uh seven and a half hours ago now
we had five dolls from mr comcast john comcast thank you for the five dolls john comcast says
just letting you know that when you moved to vegas you didn't actually end your contract
with us all you did was mail your router back to us in a wooden box surrounded by
knives and clown makeup you're still paying for our deluxe streamer package which after a
few months of not paying adds up to about thirteen thousand dollars we expect you to
pay this as soon as soon as possible or there will be legal or legal action taken against
you have a nice day cutie or illegal the streamer package do not scoff at that
for more than a second because eventually here over the next five to ten years oh you drop
frames all the time that's unfortunate well you know we have a streamer reliability package
i wouldn't scoff at that that shit could be real but thank you mr comcast with five dollars
and your dog shit service thank you uh real mr cox has given five dollars right after mr
comcast i wonder if they are trying to one-up the each other here uh hey germa thank you
for the five dollars first of all hey jerma brian cox here just letting you know that
we've been getting reports that you've been contacting comcast we hope that this isn't true
remember that here in vegas we own you and your internet just stay a loyal good boy and
everything will be fine also don't forget to run the 19 minute cox ad that you promised to
show on your stream we pay you well don't read the last part out loud by the way we
don't want people knowing that you're being sponsored by us oh whoops oopsie thank you
mr cox appreciate the five dollars thanks for five bucks sly 161 thanks for the 250 so when
are we going to watch the turtles have sex well two other turtles fight video on stream
i think that would get me claimed if we watched the whole thing but it is called life
what's it called if you weren't here in the beginning of the stream something wild happened
today at the dentist office not even really it was just in my own head i was the only
person that knew that was going on there were like two or three people that were around there
was the dentist there was a couple of people there was a receptionist i'm the only person that
knew that was happening so that was just a me it was a personal issue that i was having
tell the story again i missed the first two hours
it's just the first if you watch the first like 15 minutes of the stream but
it was all over the place there may have been somebody behind you that saw it i mean maybe
i think this is a clip of it remember dentist is fucking in my mouth
i've like forgot about that kind of a dentist office like we're just having sex
i can't even it's too late for this
we're at the dentist oh yeah i'm gonna go to the dentist yeah yeah yeah you lie in the chair
you know they scrape your teeth a little bit oh you know and also oh my god
there's the turtle clip yeah it's fucking ridiculous
jesus christ it is insane i know and that's what i was in the background of me getting
in the dental chair with tools in my mouth that's what i had i was peering over and seeing
like i said in the beginning of the stream do you understand the cia level
of training it takes to not fucking be like what the hell is going on over there
hey pretty support thanks to the 15 dollars yeah i put it on but i just was putting on documentaries
and i we've gone over it a couple times about the panic syndrome of when i i don't want to
put something on tv and i just i picked this random bbc documentary series and this episode
was called courting i didn't i don't know i just picked it it was the it was actually
the next episode that did not have any watch time on it i know but listen there were two
episodes already that somebody in that dentist office had already watched so that was the next
one you know the netflix bar underneath the thumbnail that shows the time the little red bar
those were both full on so i was like all right it's the next one whatever
did i eat the pasta yeah it was fucking unbelievable it was delicious
it was that garlic bread was like 10 out of 10 it was fantastic thank you thank you sweetie
it was great the previous viewers knew what to stop watching did the dentist notice you
struggling no i kind of like did a little swallow like uh and he was like yeah you're
okay and i'm like i just sent some water because he had a little like water gun so
so i just was like ah some water is uh just back here i i don't think he even knew
it was on tv i can't fucking believe it no dental tools just water guns no they have like
the little devices that have all right okay all right i'm fucking i'm moving on from this
i have to move on from this before i say more damning shit uh pretty support thanks
for the 15 dollars keep the face cam handsome streamer i kept it for about five to six hours
i had to power it down no yeah i ran out of gas i stepped i stepped on the gas the first like
three or four hours of the stream i was just going 100 but thank you so much for the 15
dollars well whaty thanks for the five dollars no message just five bucks thank you hey door cube
7000 thanks to the 250 door cube it's probably gonna be a while before i give bits again so
i just want to say that seeing you stream with the webcam on genuinely fills me with
joy especially when you read a confusing chat message and you do that face yeah you know how
much fucked up shit i see over here and what am i gonna just be like oh whatever sometimes i
don't even say anything about it i just kind of blink a few times but uh door cube you've
given a lot of bits you've been around for a long time so don't worry about not being
money but thank you regardless uh thank you to soul train for the 10 dollars jerma you have been
a favorite of mine for years and i want you to be my first sub and donation you're the most
genuine streamer ever and i hope you never stop being an incredible human being thank you
thank you for the 10 dollars um i am honored to be your first sub and donation thank you
that means a lot all i know how to be is me so i'm ecstatic and happy and
full of joy that people enjoyed this and enjoy the community and everything it means it's a lot
i love it thank you hey pilot guy thanks for the 15 dollars wider please it's all you need
to be it's all you need to be thank you soul train appreciate that wow the face cam thing
right every like three or four months i stretch the face cam out don't i
old material right uh but thank you for the 15 dollars i really appreciate that
15 bucks from pilot guy thank you uh thank you heavy min for the five dollars
thank you heavy bin you should make it a habit to talk to max he has different dialogue
options in every room yeah there's a lot of just random shit i need to talk to max more
hold on dragon breath thanks for the 250 hey germa speaking of dentists i got all four of
my wisdom teeth out yesterday when i woke up i was high on the anesthetic and started talking
about you even though this is embarrassing please watch it hold on what wait what
what the fuck okay is this are you sure you're are you okay with us doing this
all right oh my god i started talking about you are the anesthetic oh my goodness hold on a
second all right here we go
it's so cool
so cool yes he is here i agree oh i love that guy
it's just like a year from today i know and i'm glad you got to meet him
wasn't a year from today i think so not today maybe in april
oh
this is awesome
top wisdom teeth aftermath vines why is that a thing uh that was that was incredibly fucking
wholesome that was amazing uh thank you yes i i do remember meeting you it was the exact
the exact date hopefully you recover because that can be a real pain in the ass that was
fucking hilarious thank you so much for that thank you for letting us watch that for sharing
that with us because that was fucking awesome germa germa it starts with a j oh my goodness
uh here's a link to it if you want to see it oh i love it but anyways thanks for the 250 as
well we also had uh five dollars from germa's nuts germa these five dollars they say miss me
bitch you can't cut me i'm not gonna even read the rest of this whatever thanks for the five
miss me i don't even understand what you mean but thanks for the five dollars germa's
you know two wildly different messages thank you kim chi dooboo for the three bucks
hey germa you missed my birthday but it's okay anyway do you ever feel like there's someone in
the house with you even though you know there's not anyway i'm sure it's not oh you still okay
i get what yeah no i don't well i always do feel like the someone in the house because
there are always people in this house three people here oh shit thank you three dollars
though and that was a pretty good gag that was a pretty good bit that was a pretty good goof
does jex live here yeah thank you kim chi dude uh thank you to skelly boner for the three dollars
like zoinks scoop don't worry germa if you burn out your liver you're gonna have mine
i'm not gonna burn my liver up by drinking pineapple juice you guys are just trying to
get in my head you guys are really good at doing that and it's weird because it's like
oh pineapple juice and i'll read one just all lowercase comment by just some hey you know that
causes liver damage there's just no it and they might not even have a sub or a bit badge just a
random chat member could be anybody could be somebody that's a 32 months up doesn't matter
who it is hey dude uh that's like really not good for you three thousand people made your
from thousands of miles away like what like here's the fucking hilarious part about that right
i i could have just said i don't want a fucking mountain dew and put it downstairs
i could have just said no i'm not drinking the mountain dew and just went back to the game
dude i get so uh but i didn't i know we have the power over you in your head the stakes
were higher than they actually were yeah when i pull back and look at this objectively here
there are no stakes that i was putting such huge stakes on an old retro mountain dew
i didn't need to be there am i gonna play more how again probably yeah maybe i'll do that on
sunday because i mean if i have one episode left and then season two and then maybe an
episode i don't know but maybe i'll throw it in on sunday after sam and max maybe if i
spend like three four hours on the first couple episodes or something we'll see i'm up for
anything hey internet whore hey thanks for the five dollars i quit smoking cigarettes a few years
ago but germa you inspired me to buy a pack i hope that is not true i went over many reasons
why i don't smoke cigarettes i hope that's not true thanks for the five dollars i hope you do
not start smoking again don't do that you you got you went so long you've spent three
years you don't start now but thank you for the five dollars uh tar olycron thanks with three
dollars germa's a raging smoker don't listen to his denials he's even got an emote of a
man holding a lit cigar in his hand germa jex germa jex two that's not a cigar it's a smoking
finger gun thanks to her for the crack addiction and that does like kind of concern me a little
bit not the but like have i ever said anything that somebody may have taken and like oh i'm
gonna do that and they do it you know it's they listen to me or something sometimes i think
about that like have i ever influenced somebody to to do something stupid i hope not hope we have
a positive no it was a joke i know no i know i know i know i know it was a joke i'm just
saying like in the 10 years i've been doing this have i ever said anything dumb that
somebody was like oh i'm gonna do that now you influenced me to sub and that's pretty stupid
you made me and my friend repeat your old tf2 video jokes at school and we got made fun of
true same true fucking true same same by show of hands how many of people in this chat were
bullied because they said the word speed too many times no no no that was a fun positive
video and we had a good time i have good times and they don't know what the fuck they're
talking about all right they just didn't get it don't listen to those people my roommates
thought i was crazy because i was laughing at your streams well here see guys we this is funny
because you guys have watched the streams and videos and maybe showed them to somebody
and made a reference to them and they were like oh that was stupid you're stupid right
like as a point of reference here right i made these videos and showed them to people
and some of them stopped talking to me because of it remember that i told you the story about
that girl that i showed autos big adventure to and she literally just did not really want to
talk to me ever again happened to me if in real life you guys remember that story that's
a that's a i told that one a long time ago i was so embarrassed because how do you explain
to anybody it's okay so i had family come over this past week when i was gone as you
know i was gone for like a week in a few days and trying to one of my family members loaded up
the new year's eve worst of the year stream just it was the first thing that they happened
to click on they were like oh this is your channel i'm like yeah yeah it's my channel
oh and they watched it and it got to worst peter and i was just i how how would i ever
explain what this was he's looking over his shoulder like i don't what peter what what is
that peter and i'm like i said it's a kind of an in humor thing we've just it was it's hard to
explain the next one that comes up best impression and worst impression was about
me doing the 2013 youtuber he just had no fucking idea what i was talking about
like bugleberry like i could not describe this to my family remember i told you online media
because it's much easier just to be like oh yeah i uh i work like a pr guy i actually think i've
used that before to like a random family member i work in pr that's a complete lie
but hey i work in pr in media for a media company is way easier than bugleberry reading
scary stories that makes more sense just say influencer even that no i don't like that word
online entertainer comedian yeah but then went okay but remember we talked about this when you
start to give those details then it becomes a comedian where do you perform
a website what's the website well i
uh the website is uh it's a website online it's a streaming website
um what's the strength what is it what's it called what am i going to be like i'm not telling
you i'm not going to tell you what the website's called they would think i was doing porn you
work you do videos comedy video online but you won't tell me the website what are you ashamed
of say you work for amazon what department the uh boxing boxes oh i thought you said you were
a comedian yeah i'm a i tell jokes to the boxes in the storage room it's just a very difficult
thing to describe are you ashamed of the no i'm not ashamed of this job i love this job and
i don't even like to use the word job because job implies that it's i gotta go to work today
we've talked about me not using the term job here because once it becomes a job it gets in
your head and it's my job it's my i gotta go nine to five right like i gotta go i gotta do it
it's my job no i'm an unemployed i'm an unemployed self-reliant amazon box comedian warehouse
employee okay that's my title that's what i am i'm not an influencer i'm not a streamer
social media comedian yeah i know but explaining that to somebody that has never
even heard of any of this but that's what it is are we the boxes no no that's just my no
just say you're a receiver of donations what do you do for work i'm a receiver of donations
doesn't that that's like a that's that's that's panhandling you'll be able to find me uh
usually outside of a gas station what my job is people give me money streaming is just internet
panhandling no but that's not true either at least okay hold on a second at least give me like
a shred of credit even like a tiny bit of credit you could think that that's fine but like
can i get even like 10 of a credit here streaming is like being a televangelist
i mean okay at its very very core streaming is just televangelism kind of but no i guess
it's like the guy's on stage smiling he's just telling stories with a room full of people that
are all going to give him money fuck i really am a televangelist but i'm not i'm having this
really hard realization here i'm not taking advantage of anybody i run a tv channel thank
you that's right you're the equivalent of those guys on the street who paint themselves
gold and do the robot dance no no that's not that is not what's happening here
yes it is no it's not i am not the guy from the euro trip
that's oh fuck i am doing that i do that all the time
that's literally what it is televangelist gold robot
oh that's so fucking ridiculous oh my god that's too funny it's all right though you're digging
yourself deeper i know but that's fucking pretty funny all right let's keep going
we had two three fifty dollar donations come in and a one hundred dollar donation came in
i keep thinking about the robot dancing i'm going to be my eyes are going to be
plastered onto the ceiling tonight going like fuck am i really that robot guy that dances on
sidewalk anyways thank you to spoons for self-defense colonel zero basic feral for
fifty dollars and then veli me veli me for 100 thank you i i had to tell my girlfriend i was
listening to an actual comedian while working she doesn't understand twitch yeah online
comedian that's fine online gold painted robot sidewalk comedian i'm fine with that
as long as comedians in there somewhere and online media uh but pretty support thanks for
the 15 dollars jeremy drink the nectar drink the nectar what was i doing a few hours ago
but thank you for the 15 dollars oh mountain dew that's what right was mountain dew
mr potato daddy thanks with five dollars chug it no this was during i remember this part
uh thank you rambling jan for the ten dollars ten bucks from rambling jan chug a cup of water and
say your new catchphrase there's no way i'm drinking the mountain dew well i did you one
more i put water in the mountain dew and then turned the can upside down to prove that it
was empty and water came out and it ruined my plan that's the long and short of that one
but thank you for the ten dollars thank you also for ten dollars from flare pancake
thank you flare pancake for the ten bucks hey germ i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to
catch any streams for a while leaving to visit family in the philippines for a month later this
week very much looking forward to catching the vods when i return germa hart have a safe trip
thanks for the ten bucks hope uh hope you and your family have a good time
in the philippines we look forward to your return there'll be plenty of vods when you
thank you you're the leader of an online comedy cult that's fine i'm okay with that
e-clown i'm not even i'm not even opposed to that e-clown i would honestly e-clown is
better than influencer e-clown this is not functional enough to be called a cult no not
really hey tod flower thanks the 250 real chug or real riot i did a real chug it just
wasn't mountain dew germa lied about minecraft vr thanks for the 250 germa lies again feels bad
man lied again there'll be more usernames tomorrow thank you though uh valimi again on
top of the hundred dollars 10 000 bits another 1200 bits thanks the 12 bucks germa lied about
mountain dew throwback somebody's i mean it's available it's definitely available why would
anyone have that username if that username was taken it would be a shock one of you time
traveled but thank you really appreciate it pika banana thanks for 10 bucks it's always so nice
to sit down and catch the tail end of a germa stream after a long day uh happy to have you
thank you yeah this is a long one this is just about to go over eight hours here this
was a nice pedal to the metal stream for the first three hours and then we just relaxed
and enjoyed salmon max it's good very good but thank you for the ten dollars pika uh errorless
thanks for 250 haven't been able to catch many streams lately but just want to pop in and say
hi to you and chat love y'all hope you're doing well we will all wave to you hi welcome
back maybe we'll see you again soon thank you errorless for the 250 and for popping in again
uh we also had that hundred dollar bit donation the 10 000 bits from bala koala
proving that i said that i was cheating thank you for the hundred dollars thank you so much
some of you guys give so much fucking money thank you let's get the credits on screen here
they come here are all the new subs and resubs from tonight it's good to be back
i will see you guys in a couple days for hey it's good to be back see in a couple days
what flashed flashed no the banana pick yeah yeah we should be able to get five streams this
weekend but i'll see you guys on saturday saturday and sunday labo vr which shouldn't be one to
miss watch this watch this be the most boring stream i've ever done no it's a labo stream
that's impossible and then we'll finish up salmon max on sunday red blend i don't know
we'll see i'll get a good one which labo am i doing the labo vr how am i going to record
the labo you'll see i've got a plan and it's called two webcams you guys get to experience
the adventure two webcams going in both eye holes what do you think it's fun it's going
to be fun ew but thank you everybody for subbing and for resubscribing thank you
we have a couple more bits to go through uh pin thanks pin for the 250 what's going on pin
hey germa just a bit of an update i've been without my uh the vance v vance for the last
few weeks because of my heart condition it's been okay i'm actually growing in appreciation
for my old self but i really do miss being able to think without being distracted and
cloudy all the time i was surprised when you said you had a similar experience and i'm really
happy that i could share my struggles with the community thanks again and fuck you
that's how you end that one well thanks uh but yes i uh adhd has been a struggle uh for me
and i remember taking medication that fucked with me so i know i kind of know what it's like
to have uh you know your brain and body fight back the colitis thing too i am no stranger
i am no stranger to medical issues and you know different stuff like that
so i really really hope that you can um stay managed get managed right human potty's suck
yeah but you know you just kind of you just have to keep doing what you can
you just go you do what you can you try new things try taking some medications get off of
them follow some you know you doctor's orders to carry yourself everybody's doing something you
know everybody's got something and once you once you realize that everybody where everyone's
like the same everyone's the fucking same everybody has like issues and problems they
deal with and once you know that you can relate and you can start to understand
no i'm perfect well that's i'm glad you are but once you get older you start to get a
little bit um more knowledge you start to understand what works for you and what doesn't
and you only find that out by trying to keep your um you know issues under control
well even if people laughing when i said that you get older and you get more knowledge
people who think they have this shit together just don't realize what's broken yet
yeah nobody's perfect everybody has something they do great and something they don't do so
great everybody has something that's potentially going on in their life and we're all in this
together guys we're all human beings but thank you pin i wish you the best auto is perfect
well autos a dog dogs are all perfect by default but hey mitchell thanks for the 15
dollars mitchell you influenced me to reach into the toilet and eat uh i'm not no good
times thank you for the 15 dollars mitchell i am not going to read that one out loud
did i say that i did say that no did i did i actually say those exact words hold on
when they're gonna shit everybody in this room cereal wow get three headshots in a row right
now i'm going to reach into the toilet and eat my own shit holy fuck i've said too many
things remember i told you about the time guys listen we have we have thousands of hours of
video footage of me speaking that's there are like 3000 videos that i've been a part of
i've been on stream i've said like five probably said two to three million words
never oh yeah this cigarettes thing i said a lot of fucked up stuff back in like 2014
youtube days imagine running for president don't worry piss into my own face line vaguely
oh the shit that i say he used to record me saying such fucking outrageous shit
i remember actually talking to him before being like hey man did i like
you're not gonna use like that of me saying that right and he was like
yeah i am i'm like no you can't i can't can you like not do that because it does
like a couple times like could you just like not remove like a couple of them i remember
bargaining with him while he was editing those videos he would show them to me half complete
and stuff we star and i used to watch each other's videos all the time before anybody
else did we'd be sitting at a call and we'd have you know a video that was 60 70 complete
and we would just watch them and be like give feedback did you think that was funny
or what was did you did you do not like that this part was kind of boring you should
probably trim that down we used to do it all the time i would do it for him and he would do
it for me and there was so many of those cases where it was he would show me a clip like that
or he'd show me like a string of clips and i'd be like uh okay um how many times did i say
like fuck you in that video like maybe take like three or four of like the motherfuckers
and fuck you because remember this is also at that turning point i used to be a channel
that did not swear i was a pg channel back from 2010 to 2012 i was a super pg no swears no i i tried
to keep it as family friendly as i could and once i crossed that that was essentially was the
crossover me saying i was gonna eat shit out of the toilet was the ultimate crossover because
why are you ever gonna go back hey guys uh welcome to germa 985 we're gonna be playing
minecraft oh crap i just dropped my shovel oh oh doo doo i literally just talked about pissing
into my own face on somebody else's video those videos that he made were sort of like the
the entryway for meats to be like all right well fucking whatever who cares
i'm not gonna do that anymore i miss family friendly jerma imagine imagine watching sesame
street and then after years of being kid friendly big bird just starts yelling about
putting cigarettes out on his dick oh my god i wasn't kid friendly though i was i just didn't
use any vulgarities right i wasn't like a child family like i wasn't a family video maker i
played like m rated games i talked about like kind of screwed up stuff but i didn't ever
subscriber friendly i'm gonna go watch it back and watch those videos it's it it's probably the
first 50 to 100 videos i made no no no that's not even true that's not true no no that's not
true the first the first like 20 videos i made i didn't give a shit and said anything because
i didn't think anyone was gonna watch my videos so there's this weird period where the
first 20 to 30 videos on germa 985 are just no filter i'm saying just wicked stupid
shit and like swearing and don't give a fuck right and once i realized people were watching
and i started to get an audience it was like wait a minute i kind of who is what i got i kind
of probably have to clean my act up a little bit i i can't tell people like to fuck off and
in the game and stuff no no no i all right i'm gonna like clean it up a little bit and then
from like video number 40 to video number like 150 was clean cut pg jeremy and then the flood gates
opened and here we are did you delete and unlist these videos no they're all still there no
they're they're they're all there i feel like you were still vulgar in 2012 well because
remember 2011 was when i was really starting to do it for real i made a lot of videos in
2011 into 2012 it had to have been at least 50 to 100 videos i remember all okay here's a good
indicator my entire super meat boy playthrough if you didn't know that i have a full super
meat boy playthrough on my channel the whole thing i don't i was making sure i didn't swear
during that whole thing so when was that 2011 2012 never finished the dark world no i didn't
not on the camera you gotta watch him now yeah i think i actually maybe say one or two swears
but they're like ah shit oh and i correct myself oh it's weird i've been around for
a long time 2020 or i believe 2020 in june right will be my 10 year anniversary of
sidewalk painted gold robot dancing amazon cardboard box comedian that's 10 years
i can't i sometimes can't believe it what's the plan i'm gonna do a fake retirement party
and i'm gonna hire a bunch of old people actors and i'm gonna do it in a retirement home
that's that's true that's true fake yeah no that's what i want to do i want to get a bunch
of older elderly actors to be on camera and we're gonna do a retirement party but uh we
leave off here we only have like two more we had five dollars from peek a banana thank you peek a
banana you've done so much for us it's crazy that some people think what you do is weird you
absolutely are awesome sure of a heart i thank you so much for saying that but it's not that
what is weird it's just hard to explain to people that don't know what it is so you run
a radio show no you play games for what for other for people to watch but sometimes i don't
play games sometimes i just hang out and do something else sometimes i do like a project
what do you mean i build a bird house why who watched you build a bird house
you just i i can't explain it you don't get it it's okay but it's hard to you know
there's no way it was a game or bird house it was but thanks to the five
dolls peak banana and thanks for the incredibly kind message and finally to take us out here
uh eight and a half eight hours and 15 minutes it's a long one graveyard ghoul thanks to the
five dolls all this talk about you being an online comedian when you're actually going to do
the stand-up stream let me get let me get through the dunk tank stream first that's the next thing
coming up and then we can talk i really want to get this out of the way because it's something
i want to do it sounds like a ton of fun it's not going to be that much time it will be a
lot of work but it won't be that much time to put together it'll be like two or three
straight days of a ton of work of like all day but i think it's gonna be great and right
at the very end all mu for thanks for the three dollars just something before the stream ends
love making the streams when i can happy to have you whenever you can come and hang out
we're always happy to see new and familiar faces so thank you everybody so i will see you guys
on saturday we'll be doing the labo vr i'm gonna make sure i stream legends yeah i will
don't worry i'll get you i'll get you guys i'll see you on saturday have a fantastic
rest of your night much love to you all uh i had a blast take care everybody see you real soon
stream legends coming in now see you saturday afternoon good night like dentist is in my mouth
doing these every now and then remember dentist is fucking in my mouth like that just is in my
mouth doing these every now and then remember dentist is fucking i didn't turn the stream
off yet i'm closing tabs over here i'm closing tabs and i see that and
i almost needed to play it i had to play it like five times to even make sure it was real
that was not on purpose
okay i'll see you saturday
oh god damn it you know what you say okay listen before i go before i go you know when you
you know when you see something and you're just like god damn it you know what you need
to like see it a few fucking times to be like no no way i said that why did i do that
i thought i i i i'll see you on saturday good night oh my god