American Family Insurance gives you, I don't know, I have no idea how their coverage is, but I'm not gonna read that.
Odd Watchers skip 30 minutes. Why? Because I, every time we start a VR stream,
I cherish the fact that I'm not stuck in a virtual world for 20 minutes.
I can exist out in my own space and hang out and see what you guys are really saying in real time.
It's not 30 minutes, it's like 10, but you did that all day.
Hey, you don't know what I did all day.
For all you know, I could have been sitting on the toilet for an hour. How do you know?
Did my, did my make Jerma, what? Did my make Jerma, what?
He's still on the toilet. I wish I could get away with that. There's no way I could though, you know it.
There's no way I could do a
accidental face cam, the whole computer's in the bathroom, and I'm sitting on the toilet.
I mean, I guess I could, but not the way that I want.
Just like old times, yeah. We need the bird's-eye view. Wait, the bird's-eye view in the bathroom?
Why would I have all that?
Why would I go through the pain and suffering to set up like five cameras to do a look at me
I'm on the toilet joke. Make it the next event. No, that's not the next event.
Can I just drink my coffee for a second?
Can't wait till he does that. Chat, I'm not gonna cut off a finger. Not one. I'm, alright, I'll do one.
I hate that fucking coffee pasta, but I'd love it at the same time.
Just one finger. No, I'm not gonna do it. I'm not going, alright, two? Two sounds good.
I hate it.
Look, Chubby Bunny is not gonna happen before a VR stream or during a VR stream.
You know how horrible that would be?
Hey guys, I just got out of VR. I feel like shit. It's been like four hours.
Let me stuff my mouth full of marshmallows until I throw up.
No, that's gonna be, that's gonna happen on like a gaming stream.
Okay, S. This is a gaming stream. I mean it is, but it's me being put inside of the video game.
Thought I cleared my throat with much more than this before I unmuted.
Apparently not.
Okay, see? I'm not old. I'm just like you. I'm in my early 20s. I'm young.
Real voice.
Just like me.
Oh, he just drank blood.
What is this? Is this an iteration? Look chat, no, there's no way I'm not gonna cut my dick off.
Holy shit, dude. Alright, that one's fucked up. That one's wicked fucked up. That's, that's like a not okay one.
That's, that one's not okay. That one's not one we can paste as like a funny copy paste up.
Yay for Jerma. And paste a pasta, paste a post a post. What do you want me to say? Good hair?
It's, it is okay. This part I'm not happy about. If I just go like that, it's fine.
Amazing hair. Where did you get that shirt? Uh, from, yeah from Jackbox Party Pack.
This is not official merch. Uh, I like, I missed out on that one big time, I think.
We gave like Jackbox like fucking 12 grand.
Whoops.
Look at this, dude. Where can I get that shirt? If there's like, uh, look, I'll, uh, alright.
Long time ago, I was gonna make a fireman t-shirt, but I, you know me with merchandise. I suck.
I like just, I don't even, I just don't care. You know, I do like one shirt every three years.
I know, I know everybody like wants it, but like I just, it's, it's, it's too much for me to do and that's stupid.
I know.
We want it. I know, I know, but like I'm just such a loser. I like, I can't, I don't do merch.
That means when, when a merch does come out though, it's rare as fuck. Make an official one, maybe.
You know, here's the thing, you know, glue man, the glue man shirt originally, here's some, some lore for you guys.
Originally the glue man shirt was never going to be made ever again, and I think only like, I think like
1,400 glue man shirts existed. That was it.
So for like five years straight, you, if you owned a glue man shirt, you were one of only like 1,400 orders.
That was pretty limited and then I, obviously that didn't last very long.
Now you can get any, you can get any, I got, I got a t-shirt store on Teespring.
One of two shirts you can buy right now.
This is not one of them.
This is not one of the official shirts.
Now we got glue man, we got the night sky,
and coming soon, we've got the three singing rats for Christmas.
They're going to be, their heads are going to be up like, singing, one, two, three.
They're both going to have Christmas hats on, all three of them.
Heads up, singing, and you can see like the bottom, like the little part of their mouth right here, like one, two, three.
Fuck, I have to do that now.
What time is it?
Not November, right?
It's October.
Okay. Let me, let me look into that.
Ahem.
That was a monk of ets.
Let me look into that, monk of ets.
Fucking play already.
I get to, he just made me kick my fucking VR headset right in the glass part too.
Man that person.
I just kicked the glass part, my heel went ding.
I'm just trying, look, I'm going, I, we only got like another three hours in the game anyways.
That's not on me.
This is, why is this a Reddit mug?
Because it says the name J on it?
Which is the first, the letter of my first name?
That's not an egomaniac.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
I'm an egomaniac.
What, what if this said number one best dad in the world?
You don't think that's an egomaniac?
Number one best dad in the world.
That doesn't say that.
This doesn't say number one best Jeremy on earth.
I don't drink out of egomaniac mugs like that.
I just want you to know who I am.
This doesn't, this doesn't say Jer, this is the best Jeremy currently drinking this.
And why am I stalling?
I'll tell you, because I don't want this to have any liquid in it before I start to get in the
headset, because this has coffee.
Is it, look, look, I don't want to spill this, but look, am I going to dump this on the
fucking go XLR?
I almost just did.
Look, can you see?
Here, here, have a sip.
See, it looks, it looks like a fucking slush.
That's ice.
It's ice coffee.
Okay.
I don't want that to spill.
I'm going to hit the keyboard and this thing's going to fly in the air and dump all over
the ground.
It's ice.
It's loaded with ice.
What about my wrist?
How do I feel like I'm a VR character holding this in VR?
Why does it, why does it look like that?
Okay.
That was weird.
Why, why do I feel like I can't hold this now?
Why is it like, why is it weird to hold this now?
Like that?
Okay.
That's better.
All right.
Let me just finish this.
There's a lot in here.
I don't like drinking in front of people.
You know that?
You notice that?
I hate drinking liquids in front of you guys.
I don't know something about it.
I don't like it.
I don't like people watching me eat either.
Bod watch or skip.
You said 30 minutes.
That was a lie.
Stop stalling and drink.
It's coffee.
I don't want to just chug coffee.
You've seen me what I look like when I don't have coffee.
You want me to drink this as fast as I can?
I'll be like, I'll be bouncing off of walls.
It's cold too.
It's too cold.
Man discovers coffee.
I drink coffee like every day, bro.
I almost just like burp puked into the microphone.
Okay.
I have a question.
How many, how many upvotes on like fuck face Reddit, right?
On like, this guy sucks.
Like, on like, holy shit.
Freak out.
Like what, what do I, I don't even like the weird fucking freak out Reddits.
Right?
Like if you saw them, if the microphone was right here and I went like, oh yeah, bro.
And I like burp puked all over it and went like, oh fuck.
Like what, does that have a thousand upvotes?
2000 upvotes.
How many upvotes?
It would be on live stream fields.
Oh, well, whatever.
No, it would not have a hundred thousand upvotes.
Donald Trump could stand on stage and just piss his pants.
Just pee.
And you see the pee forming and going down the leg.
Just going, and that would not get, that would get like 80,000 upvotes.
That would not get a hundred thousand upvotes.
Oh, it would probably get like 20,000.
Are you doing political satire?
What?
Has it said the president pees his pants on stage?
80,000 upvotes.
Oh, he's getting political.
Hey, hey, wouldn't it be funny if Donald Trump peed his pants?
What's that mean?
What?
Why'd he say that?
I wonder.
He might be a Democrat.
No, no, no, no.
He might be one of those Republicans.
He must be.
Politics Andy.
Omega O.R.
Dude, you're freaking me out.
That's VR streams.
I let loose on VR streams because I get to stand up and move around.
You guys understand that when I'm sitting here like this
and I have to sit here with a mouse in my hand, I cannot, I cannot unleash.
See, I have to go like this.
Okay, let me move my mouse.
No, I don't get to fucking like unleash.
All right, let's go.
Okay, there's just ice in there now.
If I knock it over, I don't care.
Time for Half-Life Alex.
He's unhinged.
I can't stall 15 minutes for me to get ready.
We only have like another two hours in the game.
Anyway.
Okay, so we last we did, we did Jeff, which was ridiculous.
That was probably top 10, like worst things ever in VR and not in a bad way.
In like a holy shit.
I hate this every second of this.
It's real life.
I don't like the glass.
The glass shattering makes me, gives me nausea.
It was insane.
You know when you want to look up stuff about a game, but you're not done with it yet.
I really want to look up like, oh, what was the scariest chapter in Half-Life Alex?
And why?
I can't do that yet.
I can't look up like, oh, wait, what are the secrets of Jeff?
Nope.
I want to.
Oh, then put the headset on.
Just hold on a second.
Okay, that's right here.
Look, you're going to give, I'm going to unmute the game.
It's been 15 minutes.
It's been like two hours.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, head to the end.
I think Alex, it's comfy, a little tight, a little tight.
It's pissing me off.
I hope it's do this.
Why?
Okay, here's a pro tip for anybody developing a virtual reality headset.
Make these different colors.
Like, oh, left is yellow and right is green.
Okay, I see green, right?
Not like the tiny, teeny little R that's etched on the grain of rice down here.
That's L.
Hey, finally, finally, finally, finally, finally.
All right, this is chapter eight.
It's called Key Activity.
Welcome, everybody, to the stream.
Hey, strap in.
You've got to, you notice how my voice is different
because the headset's like pushing on my nose.
So if I sound different, that's like why.
People say, why does it sound so weird?
Because I have a huge fucking nose and this is just crushing it.
Okay, this is where we left off.
This is still broken, by the way.
So going left is almost impossible.
Thank God it's not used for anything else
because I have to fucking crush it and it doesn't work half the time.
Let's go.
Where was I going?
Kalanja of captivity.
Fuck.
What was that?
Oh, resume.
Everybody, okay, when you play a lot of VR, anybody else get like this?
Where, even in your real life, shit feels like weird being alive in real life.
I do.
This is why you can't be in here for that long.
Like, when I was pouring my coffee this morning, it was like,
and then like the trash came and like flew at my face.
It doesn't look right.
Do not tell anybody to skip.
Not yet.
Is there a third one?
Heck, yep.
All right, what do I got?
25 resin, that's yes.
What do you, what should I do?
Shotgun?
Oh, double shot.
That sounds kind of good.
Adds the option to fire a second shot immediately after the first.
So like, ba-boom.
Fucks.
Renade launcher?
Holy shit.
It's, don't, don't, don't.
All right, I won't.
Otto?
Was there a dog out there?
Okay, okay, Otto.
Otto, you want to come in?
Lie down on this blanket over here.
What do you want?
He's lying down in front of the door, just wagging his tail like,
yeah, I just want you to open the door.
I don't care.
Come on, let's go in here.
You want to come in here and lie down over here?
What are you doing?
Well, I'm just going to leave the door open because,
what's, why, what are you doing?
All right.
Oh, he's just sleeping out there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What am I doing?
Okay.
I don't know where, where was I?
This way.
I'm going to save the resin.
That's dangerous.
Um, he usually just kind of sits in the same spot.
So, and like, here's the thing.
I'm kind of like, I'm like a bug.
Like, I can feel the vibrations in the ground.
Like, on my feet.
If he, if that door opens, I will feel it.
It's like a spider web.
Like, I can feel it in my, on like the bottoms of my feet.
All right, we need a power source.
All right, power.
Cool.
Looks like you're going to have to go all the way to the antlion cave.
Or not.
It's literally right here.
Need any, any resin?
That was easy.
Derma, get the gun.
Derma, gun, gun.
Don't tell him.
What do you mean get the gun?
Gun.
There is no gun.
Power.
Unlimited power.
Total corruption.
Total power.
Yeah, I play hearts, Dylan.
Whatever, man.
That's an antlion, Russell.
That's an antlion?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
I do know what antlions are.
Yes, they're leggy.
God, the fucking.
Wow, that would have been a disaster.
Is it a grenade?
No, it's a rotten apple.
Same thing.
All right, if I were to leave this, would I ever be able to get it back?
And in there.
Okay.
Antlions.
Oh, wait.
Oh, click.
Egg.
Well, there is, there are antlions in the game.
I hate antlions.
They're terrifying.
Hold on, I'm going to make this little smile off my tiny head.
I got my flashlight's gone.
I don't like that.
I'm afraid of bugs.
Oh, no, I thought Jeff was supposed to be the scary chapter, not the antlion chapter.
Who isn't afraid of bugs?
I feel like that's just a universal thing everybody agrees on.
Fuck are you?
I don't know where he is.
He's up there somewhere.
Where is he?
What is it?
In the fireplace?
He's like, he's over here.
I need to pick a gun than this.
Fuck.
Are you Rex?
Are you Sorus?
Something like that.
Uh, I need to store this.
Oh, I still have a bottle.
Okay, um, let's get rid of that.
Jeff fucking sprints down this hallway.
Okay, I think we're good.
Gotta be ready.
I'm going to examine over here because there's probably shit over here.
This motherfucker is going to sh-
He's going to be in the fireplace.
I know it.
Here?
Oh, gross.
Oh my god.
What is that?
That's a different-
What the fuck is going on?
All right, good.
That guy was going to jump scare me in the other room.
All right, is this-
Is this-
How does this go in?
Oh, free.
Cool.
All right, that's how that works.
Oh, well, that's good.
I got 90 shots in there.
It's ready to rock and roll.
Don't move.
I'm a slug.
Hey, Jerma, I've been-
I missed it.
Throw the vodka.
I did throw the vodka.
This is a pretty cool exhibit.
This is supposed to be like Jurassic-
This is Jurassic Park.
This is Jurassic Park was in Half-Life.
Yeah.
I don't touch the glass.
See?
They ran around here and shit.
And they-
There was like a speaker that talked about them.
That was right here.
I think it's-
I need ammo, which is a good thing.
I want to go over there.
But watch out for that antlion nest.
Okay.
Come over here then and say it to me.
I forget-
I don't know anything about antlions from Half-Life 2.
What are you-
Where do you shoot?
This sh-
Oh!
Okay.
You're gonna shoot their legs and then shoot them in the head.
Yep.
I was trying to be cool and it made it-
I was trying to not be scared.
Oh.
Shit!
All right, we're gonna drive-
Is it-
Oh.
Oh, this increased, dude.
Thanks, man.
Load this shit up.
We got fully loaded.
Fully loaded.
Let's go.
Is there any, uh, drink it?
Here.
Okay, so I'm assuming that the next thing I do
is gonna be one of the last upgrades of the game.
Should I get the grenade launcher or should I get, like,
super upgrade the pistol or something?
What do you think?
Grenade launcher.
Grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade launcher.
Max the pistol.
Max out the pistol.
Uh, that depends.
Oh, we got on-
Okay.
That's-
Is that where, like, I got that noise from?
I think that is the noise.
Yeah, it is.
That's some deep lore that I-
I didn't even know about.
Is that healing sound from Half-Life?
Is that sound?
This place is-
Whoa!
What the fuck?
Yeah, that-
Oh, shit.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's an exhibit in there.
Hold on.
I'll deal with you later.
This exhibit is currently closed for root-
It's gonna break through the glass!
I knew that was gonna happen.
The second that they give you this to look down at-
Oh, glass.
What's that?
Smash!
Of course, I knew that.
Right when they showed me that shit, I knew it.
Yeah, that's what that's for.
Uh, this place is awesome.
All right, this just reminds me of just, like, every single, um-
Every single, like, lizard or snake or tarantula exhibit you go look at, you go-
Oh, cool!
What's it say there?
Oh, giant fucking poisonous evil lizard!
Oh, I can't wait to see him!
Where is he?
Oh, oh, he's under that rock over there, sleeping.
And they sleep for 17 hours a day.
Oh.
Okay.
Cool that you have this here.
I think- Is this live?
Wait.
Why do you sleep?
Let me watch you.
And guess what, guys?
I felt my-
I felt my spider web.
Hiding down right there.
Close your eye.
I can sense anything.
Fighter senses.
Yeah, that's how-
That's what spider senses is, guys.
It's vibrations.
Okay, so let me go-
It's this one.
And yeah, and a lot of time when you do this shit too, it's like-
It's the stick over there.
Oh, wow.
Uh, self-
Self-
Um, self-Tennessee rattlesnake.
It's like that.
It's just that little piece right there and it's coiled up over there.
And you're looking over here trying to find the fucking thing.
You're like, oh, where is he?
He's huge and scary.
No, he's like that little blob and he's just like sitting right there.
South, south, south, south Tennessee.
Yes.
Really south.
I'm talking like on the border.
Right before you cross into Oklahoma.
I don't know what's in the bottom of Tennessee.
I don't know.
I don't know what Tennessee touches on the bottom.
The bottom part.
It's not Oklahoma.
It's Kentucky?
Top of Kentucky?
I don't fucking know.
I want to see the lizard!
Where is he?
Don't get so close.
No, but I can't see him.
Is he in here?
Is he in there, mommy?
Don't go in there.
Mommy, hold on.
I want to find the lizard.
Hey, any news on the data pod?
Ah, your dad's head's down.
He's working on it.
He's got to be close.
Great.
Where's the lizard?
I don't know where he is.
It's like the back room at the zoo.
Oh, this is just dog food.
Lizard.
No.
I'm going to find the lizard and I'll be back.
Get back here.
Oh, I found the lizard.
Oh, there's a tiger in here.
Hold on, mom.
I'll take care of this.
Oh no, it's a squirt gun.
It's a squirt gun.
Help, help, help, help, help, help, help.
Oh my god, that's horrible.
Oh, I shoot him.
Oh, shit.
Oh no.
Someone help him.
What is going on in the back of the zoo?
Oh, fuck.
Timmy, worst Alex player on Twitch.
Fuck, get out of here.
I'm in chapter eight.
It's been like eight hours.
Hey, Jeff Keighley told me,
not personally, but through Twitter,
it took him like 20 hours to beat this game
because he was engrossed
and he thought it was really fun.
Okay, do you trust Jeff Keighley?
Because I do.
Oh, that sounded really unhinged.
Let's do that again.
Jeff Keighley told me
that this was like a 15 to 20 hour experience.
I trust him.
Don't you?
That's better.
Okay, use that one instead.
Not the one where I was unhinged.
Nice acting.
No, give me that mask.
It's mine.
What the fuck?
This shit is actually hard mode.
Get it off.
It's too hard.
Bye, gameplay.
I don't need to kill that one,
but I do want to get rid of this one.
No, I don't.
Hey, bird in there?
Bird's in there.
I knew I saw something.
Oh shit, now we're getting into it.
Now we're getting into it.
This is actually Jurassic Park.
And wait a minute.
Why did somebody make a Jurassic Park VR game?
Are you kidding me?
Why has nobody done that yet?
It's like the perfect platform
for like a scary watch out for the raptors.
They're going to chase you.
This exact environment.
It really is the Jurassic Park.
I love this.
I forget I'm in Half-Life right now.
That's how you can tell
that the devs just did such a fucking good job.
I'm getting immersed in Jurassic Park
and it's not even that game.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
It's one shot, one kill.
Oh, a grenade.
Open.
He sounds so sad when you take it.
He's like, oh.
Can I have another one, please?
That again?
That again.
Chrono trigger.
That's the sound effect from Chrono Trigger.
That's the sound that makes a lot of enemies
make this like.
It's that exact sound.
I think it's the same sound.
I guess no one's talking anymore.
Oh, grenade in there.
Oh, there's a lot of grenades just everywhere.
I don't know why.
Let's.
Goodbye.
I threw them and it scared me.
It doesn't matter.
Why is there so much?
Why are there so many of these?
Maybe there's something fucked up down here.
I know it.
Uh.
Oh, shit.
Go on, pop.
Pop.
What the hell is even in here?
Why is all this shit blowing up around me?
It's the story.
I got something.
Yeah.
What is it, Bob?
Story?
It doesn't look like they actually built the weapon.
It's like they brought it to an old apartment building in the QC.
But instead of going in to get it,
they grabbed the whole building and built a vault around it.
Wow.
Holy crap.
They must have been terrified of this thing.
I'm trying to figure out whether we ought to be.
All right.
That was a good story.
I'd like to hear a little more.
Oh, he's got a mask on.
That's.
Oh, we lost it.
Lost it.
But, um.
Now's not the time for you to do this.
Now's not the time.
I don't want to waste ammo.
Give me it.
All right.
I got it.
I didn't want to waste a bunch of ammo.
That would have been like 10 shots.
I hear something.
Oh, now you want to give it to me.
Not when there's danger around.
Oh, my goodness.
Where did he go?
Oh, it's so easy.
No voice.
Oh, there's a bunch of supplies in here.
Thanks for telling me to go back.
Imagine if I didn't get this supply.
Fuck, no way.
GTX 780?
Dude, I'll be able to play at 60.
Hang on, over here?
780, that's trash.
780 is not trash.
You could still play a decent amount of games on 780.
Guys, not everybody wants to play every game at like 4K.
I can't get up there.
What ADP?
Um, no, no.
You could definitely run like Counter-Strike at like 1080, 40.
But does it really matter?
Some people don't care.
Guys, if you think people really care that much, where are you?
If you think people care that much about like frame rates and resolutions,
we played on the fucking PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4 for two decades.
That shit was running like 25, 1080, to the 60, 720.
You think people really care that much?
I mean, I do.
And you do.
Human eye can't even see past eight frames a second anyways.
My doctor told me.
What the hell is this?
Russ, do you think a headcrab could turn a gorilla into a zombie?
Honestly, if there's a gorilla on the loose, I'm not sure a headcrab can make it much worse.
Is this foreshadowing?
Are we going to have to fight a giant gorilla with a headcrab on him?
Oh no, that would be bad.
That would be very bad, actually.
Is this why you wanted me to come in here?
I saw the gorilla, cool.
How is this lore?
I skipped lore?
It's just, hey, look, there's a statue of a gorilla over here.
No, no, I didn't see like 10 minutes of extra dialogue and lore.
I just saw, I wasted 10 minutes looking at a statue.
It's precious time playing Half-Life.
Birds, I love birds.
I really do.
I love birds, especially crows.
I love crows.
I think they're the smartest, most awesome animal next to a rat.
I'm seeing a pattern, though.
I like fucking crows and like rats.
I like all the things that the Bible tells you to avoid
because they kind of possess you and kill you.
Why?
Isn't that weird?
I don't like crows and rats and all kinds of,
aren't they like the dirty animals in the Bible?
Don't they like, don't they like?
Satanist, you're a Satanist.
All right, is it Satanist or is this Satanist?
I'm a Satanist, I don't,
I don't like, why you think I like to worship Satan?
No, why would I do that?
Stuttering, because he's a Satanist.
Okay, telling me that I'm a Satanist
doesn't mean that I practice Satanism.
Like I turn the lights off
and I put a bunch of red candles around me
and I sit in the middle
and I start asking for fucking like plagues and shit.
Like what does that mean?
I don't, I'm not a practicing Satanist.
I don't care, what do you want me to tell you?
Okay, Dark Lord, around me are my enemies, who I really am.
My friends, I'm worth it.
Give me the strength.
Hopefully you give me some kind of superpowers
because that's really what I want.
So, fill me with your fear and yeah,
you know, I could really use, you know, like venom.
I would love the venom symbiote,
like to be in me right now
and we could like go on adventures and shit.
You know, if you want me to be your,
come on, I've produced the superpowers
if the intercom isn't working.
Okay, I'll try next week.
Another series of candles.
Oh, an offering.
No way, dude, it worked.
Okay, I'm gonna tell the world.
Ooh, fish.
Dude, Satan coming through with a clutch.
Why am I carrying this around still?
But no, I thought I don't practice Satanism.
I don't practice anything.
I don't practice setting up my streams.
I don't practice the drums.
I don't practice religion.
I'm practice-less.
I don't do anything.
Okay, it's like eating Cheetos on the couch.
Me practicing anything and like watching Netflix.
Does that count?
I'm a practicing Netflix viewer.
It is.
Practice me.
All right, ban that guy.
Ow, why am I carrying this?
This is like a stress ball at this point.
Like, it's okay, the antlions can't get me.
Ow, who are you?
I actually really like this area, though.
You don't see very many, like, zoo exhibits.
I know they're all connected up here.
Can I, like, put the grenade up and over into his chamber?
Oh my god, okay.
I knew it.
I'm just waiting for that gorilla with the head grab.
I know it's gonna happen.
You guys made me go look at that for some reason.
Sorry, whatever animal is in there.
Thank you.
I'll take that.
All right, I'm ready.
Wait, they were shooting at the aliens.
Why did I just do that?
They could have helped.
Kind of gross, whatever that is.
Oh, this is broken.
I'm gonna have to get it.
You know what?
I think this is a good indicator
that I'm just gonna get the knuckle controllers
because this is actually broken.
Wait a minute.
This is the T-Rex scene.
This is actually the T-Rex scene.
This truck flipped over
and the kids are watching the drink.
Right?
Oh, Anto, you wanna get out?
I felt the vibrations.
He wants to get out.
All right, go on, go on.
The gun was not...
Holy shit, that was so horrible.
Not prepared for that.
It's not even on my head.
I'm underwater right now.
I can't even see what I'm shooting at.
It's just blurry.
I held my eyes underwater in a chlorine pool.
What?
Get the fuck out of here.
Okay, can I please put my headset
back on normal right correctly, please?
All right, we're good.
Fucking pause the game.
I don't have to.
Oh, now there's like...
Just like...
There's gross stuff in here now.
That's another thing that sucks about VR.
When you take the headset off,
the sweat from your hair drags across both lenses.
And then when you put it back on, it's over.
You have to clean the whole thing.
Pause the game.
I'm good.
I can see them.
Like, I have the stream preview right there.
Oh, dude.
Game of Grease.
That's disgusting, but I'll let it pass.
Well, you know what?
I'm in the mode for five minutes.
It's disgusting.
That's just...
That's gross.
Don't say gross things in my stream.
We have to keep it...
It's PG-13, remember?
Don't do this shit.
This is a PG-13 stream.
I know you clicked on mature R-rated content,
but that's how I act.
You have to act a certain way.
I act like R-rated and you act PG.
And if you act R, then you get banned.
Right?
That's how it works on Twitch, isn't it?
You say something gross, then you get banned.
If I say something gross, look at me.
That hit somebody behind...
That hit somebody...
Somebody was just sneaking up behind me
and it hit them in the fucking face.
Thank you.
I got it.
I don't know how I got ammo.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I...
All right, we got to get this shit.
Oh, we got five community subs from Nukeable.
Thank you, Nukeable.
Thanks to the five subs.
Welcome, guys.
Hey, we love our subs here.
Thanks.
We love our subs here.
Is that all we got?
I love this area.
This is my favorite area of the game so far.
Oh, it's smoky in here.
This is the best area of the game.
Yeah, for sure.
I love it.
Moon it for me.
I like this better than kind of just the city 17
corridors and buildings.
I mean, it's cool, like nostalgia purposes,
but this is new shit.
This is new shit.
I like it a lot.
From a moon rising?
Oh, okay, we don't want that.
I would have just walked into that.
Good thing I'm hyper intelligent.
I suspect neutralized.
Call off entire investigation.
Order me number one on Postmates.
And drop it off at the door where the electricity room is.
Don't come in.
I'm busy.
Oh, my God, there's an explosive.
No, bring this in here with me.
He's going to walk into the ship.
He's going to close the door.
Don't touch it.
He's going to walk into that.
It's not going to explode.
Okay, how do I?
Can I take all the air out of that thing?
Can I just like go?
What about the door close?
I'll pass out.
It'll fuck me up, won't it?
What do I do with all this stuff?
It's the Postmates guy.
Hey, hey, dude.
Yeah, I know you drove by the house like four or five times.
Just leave it out on the curb.
I'll go get it.
I know it's hard to find.
Just leave it out on the curb, dude.
He leaves it under the curb and another car drives by
and just runs over your lunch.
Oh, stop.
Oh, I'm fucking out of here.
Don't throw that.
Where is he?
How do I go like, can you hear me?
I don't want to use it.
What?
Okay, over here.
Just leave it at the door.
He's stuck over there.
I just turn him off.
He's not going to get over here in time.
Wait, maybe he is.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
I'm realizing this right now.
Give me this.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
It's going to blow the room up.
I got him.
Okay, we're going to...
This is like happens in every like movie where there's a prison scene.
The little thing opens.
Here's your lunch, you bastard.
Okay, I think I'm safe.
Where is he?
Let's go anywhere else.
Wait, let's go somewhere else.
Holy fuck, don't touch that.
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off.
Wait, where does this go?
There's something else here.
Let's see, whatever, fuck it, let's go.
Where is he?
Where did that guy go?
Okay.
Hammer mode activated.
Bladed.
I think I did it too early.
And that's so many times.
I can't do the like, hoo-hoo thing every time I kill somebody.
I'm going to make a compilation of that and it's going to be...
Oh, drink it.
You have to.
No, I don't.
Oh, there it is.
I don't even need it though.
I really don't even need it.
Put on ammo.
Good, good, not good, good, good.
Okay, we're good, good.
Better.
I really like the SMG.
I feel like the grenade launcher is cool and it might be fun, but
how many grenades am I going to find from here on out?
I don't think very many.
Will they make a dead space in VR?
I've never played them, but I know how they work.
Imagine like a dead space VR.
Those of you that have played the game, I'm just pretending to be a fan.
That's how it works.
I told you he was alive.
He was alive.
I told you.
Everyone that tells me that I shouldn't have been doing that all game.
Right?
He was sitting there waiting.
I shot him in the head and I killed him and he dropped the grenade.
Beth, you can thank me.
Thank me for being fucking aware.
Dead space is third person.
Stop pretending to be a streamer.
What the hell would you call me then?
What else am I?
Bill's here.
Bill's...
No, this is it.
This is the correct reference.
Bill's here.
Use that part.
When you make the video, you get a quick cut.
So it's just like, it's so crazy and then...
Bill's here.
Back to the action.
It's a prison.
They didn't build it to keep us out.
They're trying to keep something...
Keep what in?
I don't know.
I'm not sure if this data part even knows.
But they got something trapped in there.
Okay.
So if it's not a weapon, are we still doing this?
The way I see it.
Whatever's in there doesn't like the combine very much.
Whatever's in there?
So we got that in common.
Are we gonna turn up to be the gorilla with the, uh, with the head grab?
Are we still doing this?
We've come this far.
I say we keep going.
And if you find out it's something we really shouldn't mess with, we'll call it off.
That's my girl.
I'll let you know when I find out.
They're keeping the gorilla in there.
Oh.
Explosive.
I'm so far away right now.
I'm so far away.
Alica?
What song?
Who, who sings that?
Is that Metallica?
Shoot them.
What a waste of ammo.
What is that?
Does God smack?
Why did that pop in here?
The word I haven't heard that toast two words.
The light.
God smack.
Oh, wait.
That's just to turn on these lights?
Hold on.
No, no, no, no, no.
That goes up here.
That there.
Goes up there.
And then it goes down this way.
If I turn something on.
Goodness, don't fall.
Jeff better not be here anymore.
Livid.
No, I crushed, I crushed Jeff.
He's not coming back.
Button, yes, I can't press it.
We can go in there.
Here.
There.
Shit.
Okay, so what the heck is going on here?
Power for this?
We gotta turn the power off here.
We don't, actually.
Am I missing something here?
All right, so where the fuck does this go?
Green wire.
Here.
Oh, my God.
How do I get up there?
What?
Are you?
Do it already.
Pop.
Connect.
Now this goes.
Here.
Blue wire.
To.
Okay.
Blue wire connected to.
Blue wire up there.
Wait, I need to follow the.
Yeah, but what the fuck?
Blue.
Blue wire.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Power on.
Power activated.
That was tricky.
Don't do it.
Don't jump.
All right.
I'm not wasting any fucking time here.
Why would I waste time?
My fucking God, what happened?
Here, go home.
No more animals.
Oh, I mean, it's my birthday.
Is it here?
Here, all right, go.
Oh my God, I thought that was a real tiger.
Holy shit, that would have been insane.
Can you imagine?
Can you imagine if that was a fucking.
A tiger just chilling.
Just waiting for me to show.
Look at him, he's like.
He's huge.
Oh, that's silly.
That's just silly, Val.
I wish it was a real tiger.
Throw your face.
Throw yourself.
Okay, we're in this room now.
Grenade.
So, uh, it's gonna be another puzzle.
Wait, we have a little force of the power.
Oh, look, here's your auto.
Here's your auto.
What's this?
You.
Right there.
Yeah, gross.
Gross.
Yeah.
This is delicious water.
Thank you.
Wait, more toys.
It's me and auto.
Hey, auto.
Are you a good boy?
Yes, I am, Jeremy.
Oh, let's have a go on an adventure together.
Yes, let's go.
Okay, let's go together.
Hey, can I have a hug?
Yes.
Okay.
It got a little weird.
That was not my intention, but you know.
I wanted to just struggle with my dog, okay?
That straight up derailed.
No, what we're supposed to be is supposed to be like,
look, me and auto are like,
who doesn't give their dog like little kisses, okay?
Please.
You.
You made that weird.
I didn't.
I could sense you.
Where are you?
Can you see me?
I could sense you making that weird.
That's why I freaked out.
I gotta play the game.
Just kill this motherfucker up here.
I'm not a furry.
Okay, who cares?
Oh shit.
Reconnect the power.
Oh my goodness.
Something happened over here.
Wait, that just redirected the power to here.
A bus access this.
That's in the monster.
This is what I was working towards.
A TV joke.
They're giving me access to a TV joke.
Holy shit.
That's what exactly what.
In break.
It's in break.
It's okay.
In break.
God's wanted this to happen.
Oh, thank you, Satan.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
Not on me, motherfucker.
Not on me.
You fucking asshole.
Okay, that's active now.
Well, the red wire is now active.
This is a pain in the butt.
Red is now active.
I don't even power this shit on.
And.
Oh, wait.
I knew it.
Why was this perfect opportunity to TV the fuck out of this guy?
Hey, eat this.
Break.
Fuck this TV.
It doesn't do anything.
Did green vent there?
I already made that.
I made that joke three days ago.
I don't know.
How much health do I have?
Not very much.
Wait.
Isn't there a healing station over here?
Fuck it.
Take it.
I want that grenade.
That's why.
Okay, folks.
Let's go.
Fringy.
Fringe.
Wait, what?
What's going on?
Why is everybody saying fringy?
The joke sucked.
What joke?
Did I make a joke?
When?
What'd I do?
Autumn minus two is before I.
What happened?
All of them?
All of them.
The lever?
Crack.
Career ending.
Play with being guy pig.
What?
Ban him.
Sell now.
Baste cringe.
I don't even know what's going on.
What did I do?
Hold on.
Me like playing with actually little figures and dolls on the counter
and being like,
is not as cringy as saying green vented.
I just want to be completely clear about this.
Correct.
Baste.
Okay.
Oh, all right.
I just want to be clear.
I just want to know what's going on.
All right, let's get out of here.
Get out.
Wait, can I draw on the walls?
Oh, come on.
I can't do like an elaborate painting.
That's unfortunate.
How do I get the fuck out of here?
How do I get out of here?
Close.
Do I actually have to?
I don't.
Do I really?
Do I have to open the door with this shit?
I have to redirect the power again.
No, dude.
I don't want to redirect the power.
Wait, I turned it off, right?
So that doesn't matter anymore, does it?
Where are you going?
It's okay.
I turned the power off.
I pulled the lever.
I just turned it off.
Yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Baste.
I want to jump over the fucking barrels.
I was wondering why.
Boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Oh my God, that hurt.
Oh my God, they're scary.
Oh my God, it's loud and scary.
How did you even hit me?
Nice hit registry.
That's all you guys had.
Just one measly little clip.
I just threw up.
Whatever.
Where's the healing device?
Isn't it right here somewhere?
There's a full heal somewhere.
I don't remember where it is.
Here it is.
I don't have a thing.
No games.
I have a thing.
That looked so well.
Thank you, Valve.
Good devs.
Okay, come back and use it if I need to.
What are you doing on ammo?
Not bad.
Good.
Oh, eye's head right there.
Ooh, good.
Imagine healing with the right hand.
Insert the next disc.
Loading in 2020.
It's a VR game.
You know how intense this shit is?
I'm actually surprised how much they're able to do
without a loading screen.
You guys have to remember most VR games
they're one room
that you just exist in for like an hour.
This is a full...
We're going down hallways.
We're opening doors.
This...
Most VR games don't do this.
One room.
Still fun.
Anything on you?
Don't do it.
It's not even worth it.
It's wasting ammo.
Cool.
All right, let's go.
After 10.
Attack of the Clones.
Good luck trying to lock out someone wielding an Alex.
Oh.
That's the gorilla.
Don't say that.
I'm inclined to believe you.
Oh, shit.
Whoa, Russell.
Oh, they got it.
Substation.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, it's coming down.
Come down to our substation.
Break this down, Alex.
It's gonna come down.
I can't check.
Rats.
We're rats.
So where's those beams?
We're the rats.
You see that?
That's gotta be the backup station.
What's that, Alex?
Nothing.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
Uh.
Oh.
Did I press this button?
Welcome, all of you, to the Hunger Games.
I'm President Davidson.
Tonight.
You've never seen this movie before,
but you just think this is how it started.
You imagine this is how that movie starts.
You haven't read the books.
You haven't seen any media of it.
You've just seen on the side of buses
Katniss going like this with a bow and arrow.
This is how it starts.
And all the subjects are down there.
And you know the name.
Davidson, huh?
You did, Mike.
All right, this is gonna be a fight here.
I'm asking you guys.
Well, um, this is the time to use this shit.
Don't you think?
No, I think so, folks.
Oh, Mike.
That's a lot of people.
Holy shit, he's coming.
Oh, shit.
That's heavy.
Tonight.
Last push.
Shelf.
I thought it was the shelf.
It's you.
I'm sorry.
It was you guys.
I just backed up in the desk.
Okay, I'm ready.
Everything's loaded.
Everything's primed.
Everything's ready to shoot.
Everything's got plenty of bullets.
Let's move on.
Thank you.
Thanks, dude.
I appreciate it.
Appreciate you, man.
Appreciate you.
Hey, okay.
This is just because I leave a two-star review.
I'm sorry.
Is this because of the 10% tip?
Oh, shit.
10%.
Don't ever make your head.
If you're going to shoot for the king, don't miss.
Miss.
If you're going to go for the king, make sure you, uh,
fill him with like 20 bullet holes and not eight.
That's how I'm going to be alive.
I need help.
Hey, fellas.
Back up there.
Never mind.
Everybody needs to practice in DM servers.
I just did fine.
I just defied like 10, 20 enemies at the same time.
Looking for like health pack or something of some sort.
Why is that open?
Health pack.
Something.
I can feel my heart pulsing here.
DM instant respawn 24-7.
You know what's bad about 24-7 servers is you'll get in there and there's no map change.
The timer is at like 16 hours.
You know, you look up at the clock.
It's like, oh, yeah, there's like 845 minutes left.
Okay.
And you get trapped in there and you can't leave.
You look at the clock after like six hours.
You've been in the same map, shooting the same people.
You can't, it's like being in a casino.
There's no clocks in a casino.
You're just stuck at the slot machine.
You don't even know where you are.
That's why I don't like to play those.
Just your mouth just stays open and you're just like, oh, right.
I used to drink a 12 pack of Code Red Mountain Dew every other day.
Just sitting there doing that.
On original Team Fortress Classic, I forget what the map was,
but there was a map where you could go.
It was, I think it was well.
I would play well like every day.
The original well.
I don't like the casino.
There's somebody up there.
That's not a combine.
Maybe a scavenger?
Be careful.
Oh, don't throw a grenade in there.
I need that.
Just throw this out.
I'll take it.
Oh, any of you guys that have ever lived underneath somebody in an apartment building?
You got to listen to this fucking TV every day.
Okay.
Do you really have to have the TV at 10 volume?
You can't do it at like seven or eight.
Where are you in your house that you have to have the TV that loud?
I never got that.
I never fucking understood that.
Are you in the bathroom with the door closed with the TV at max volume,
trying to listen to whatever's on the TV 10 rooms down in your house?
I don't understand.
Why do people do that?
Good joke.
I'm not making a joke.
This sucks.
Don't do this to people.
I'm just getting like flashbacks.
No.
Wait, I am my own supervisor?
I am my own supervisor.
Okay.
Is it going up?
Were we about to like sneak into this lady's place or something?
What am I doing here?
Where should I go?
Wall dad.
What's she listening to?
I wonder what that is.
We used to love this show.
Wait.
Finally, we need to move the box or this thing is going to be black Mesa all over again.
Black Mesa.
Well, now I'm telling you it is black Mesa.
Oh shit.
It's one of those worms.
When she gets there, he's gone.
What in the history of today makes you think it is Elmer?
But this guy who got in there survived black Mesa.
He raised holy hell and then just disappeared.
We finally caught him and you're just going to let him go again?
Talking about Gordon Freeman.
Survived black Mesa for weapons.
God damn it, Rusty.
Gordon Freeman.
Wow.
That's good, right?
This is sick.
All right.
So let's go save Gordon Freeman.
Wait, we have to save Gordon Freeman?
Incoming.
Hey, give me a second.
Thanks for the exit, idiot.
Still there?
No, I'm not.
Grenade room.
Look, I figured out that you have to blow up the wall.
I had to do that.
I just was too slow.
It's Gordon.
Holy shit.
It's Gordon Freeman.
I can't wait till the last frame of this game.
Is you're in a room and all of a sudden you see we're going to be the start
of Half-Life 2.
Gordon Freeman, we're going to be in that room in the very beginning.
Gordon Freeman, we're going to be like hiding behind a fucking barrel
and we're going to look up and see the start of Half-Life 2
and he's going to look right back in the camera.
You know, he's going to be like, and then he's going to keep walking
and right that first beginning, he's going to pick up that can, right?
That's going to happen.
Let's go save Gordon Freeman.
It's going to be seamless.
Hey, give me a second.
All right, incoming.
All right, blow it up.
Blow it up and blow it.
Where am I?
And action.
What?
What happened?
I stubbed my toe.
Why did that happen?
Hey, there was a...
What?
I didn't jump the gap.
I didn't know there was a gap to jump.
Let's go save Gordon Freeman.
All right, just go.
I'm in here.
Hello, I'm in here.
Incoming.
Hey, give me a second.
I'm just blowing it.
I don't fucking care.
Let's go.
Okay.
So this little chimney right here.
Come on, really?
Okay, so the plan is to get to that control room and get Gordon.
And as people talk about him a lot, but I always just assumed he was dead.
Me too.
Hey, Dad, are you there?
Yeah, what's up, Alex?
If Gordon survived Black Mesa, where has he been?
I don't know.
Who were they talking about?
Wow, did you just...
Who, Gordon Freeman?
I didn't play Half-Life.
This is a new VR game.
It came out, like, sorry.
Blame me for, like, them not making a new iteration for 12 years.
I don't know who that is.
I just bought a new VR game.
What the fuck?
Pig fan.
No, I need a silencer.
What shall do?
I need to actually use this.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Do what I like to watch.
Ow, oh, yes.
Ow.
Can I get in there?
Oh, yeah, wait, can I get in there?
I say you got it.
Okay, I thought that was one of those explosive tripwires.
Can I jump on there?
Actually, I might be able to glitch that.
That's really possible.
There's a box up there.
Is that a box?
Not a grenade.
All right.
Oh, by the way, those of you that are wondering why I have to always put it in my right hand.
My left hand hitting that top button and holding the trigger at the same time,
I can't do it.
My fingers can't do it.
It hurts.
Like, I physically can't do it.
I always end up dropping it.
Electricity mini game coming up.
Nothing under this.
I know, I get it, man.
Do it to you too.
Oh my god, I fell.
All right.
I don't think I can do that.
What do you think they're doing in here?
Looks like they're moking the leggies.
What the hell are they doing that?
Are they jumping too?
Almost got it.
Almost.
Where do I go?
I can't go down there.
Wait a minute.
Why up here?
This is weird, right?
What am I doing over here?
Why am I removing these?
Nothing, actually.
I fall?
I'm so scared of falling down a gap.
I don't go down?
I don't know if I should.
I die when I fall.
That happens.
Fall joke.
Stop pretending.
I don't...
Okay.
Every time I've ever done something like this, I've died.
Hey, you stop pretending.
To pretend...
To tell me that I'm pretending.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Shit, buddy.
Not again, can't I?
My eyes!
That was fucking scary.
Right in the eyes.
This game's really fun.
This is one of the good ones.
Oh, no.
Can I get in there and open this from the other side?
Can I get in there?
Yes, I can.
Hey, cop, kiss.
Now what?
Somebody tell me.
Oh, right there.
That's not gonna crush me, right?
Get down here again, please.
We're gonna get in the toilet and it's gonna bring us up.
If we get Gordon back, we can really get a vicious.
Don't you think, Russ?
Maybe we can take him and split it up.
Well, he saved humanity once.
No!
And this time, he won't have to do it alone.
She knows, too.
Oh, for the explosives.
Can I kick this down?
I can't, like, like in that game that everybody preferences, including me.
Every single time I play any video game.
It's not.
I'll take the free heal.
Not yet.
Okay, bugleberry.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
There's a guy.
Hold on.
Take care of this guy first.
Okay.
Now, give me that.
Where'd that go?
Okay.
Come here.
I'm so afraid of this smash into the Reddit shelf.
Where am I?
Okay, I got it.
Russ, what do you think they're doing to Gordon Freeman in there?
That's a good question.
Are they, you know,
sucking his brain out?
Hey, Bits.
I don't know who they were.
Thank you.
Whoever gave you a bunch of money.
Handgun Harry.
I like the handgun.
It's like my favorite weapon.
I have 56 of these.
I have 56 resin.
Oh, my goodness.
I can do a lot of stuff now.
I don't know.
What should I do, though?
Look at that.
That's not fair.
How do you get that?
Probably get it later.
Does it hurt?
Um, do this.
Rick, do the joke.
Oh, I know what to do.
Thor, good for you.
Smart guy.
Hey, smarty.
Smart guy here.
Come up here, then.
Not even that scary when you know you can deal with it with a shotgun blast with Jeff.
Get back here.
Wait, what happened to him?
Russ, what's the deal with the throw bar?
Oh, you mean Gordon Freeman's throw bar?
Yeah.
Alex, he fought his way out of Black Mesa with nothing but that crowbar.
True.
Well, it's true that that's what they say.
You know, nobody knows for sure.
Gordon Freeman's crowbar.
Well, when I get him out, let's give him a gun.
Yes, but not much.
Dude, I can't wait for...
Upgrade station.
Is that a queen?
That's fucked up.
Crazy.
What am I going to do?
Should I do more upgrades?
Should I do a grenade launcher?
Oh, I don't know, but this is...
I don't want to do this.
I'm only doing this because I'm live.
If I wasn't live, I would have taken a break here.
I don't fucking do this sometimes.
String joker.
Okay, let's see here.
I want to take a look.
I got a lot of rest.
Probably one of the final upgrades I'll do in the future.
Burst fire.
Oh, don't need it.
Okay.
Aid launcher.
Auto loader?
Auto loader sounds really good.
What about my favorite gun?
The common fire.
Although, it's because I always have no place to put grenades.
Oh.
Potentially it's going to store them, right?
I can put it on a resin.
This is like six hours worth of resin.
Auto loader is new.
Oh, that should come in handy.
Oh, shit.
Push handle forward to ready grenade launcher?
Or fire to attack normally?
Oh, shit.
Press to launch grenade
or grab grenade to reset launcher.
That's the grenade.
That's not grenade.
Okay, it's ready.
That kind of looks dumb though, doesn't it?
This is like ugly.
All right, what else can I do?
How much is the laser sight for this?
Reflex is 15.
I'll wait for 25.
I want the laser sight.
Put it up.
I got my upgrade.
I'll store it because I don't need it.
Oh, people, people, people.
Is this in the same universe as the movie WALL-E?
Imagine if that was true.
Could be.
It's got the same color scheme as WALL-E.
It's blue, gray, and white.
That whole movie is blue, gray, and white.
So I see what you mean by that.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I activated the fight.
I got to go down, don't I?
Okay, I got to be ready for this.
Let's go.
My loaded.
I'm loaded.
Get down.
Who else?
Where are you?
Oh, nice.
Blox, come here.
Don't you spawn?
I know you're going to come over here.
You're going to spawn over there.
I know you are.
You're going to make a loud noise.
I'm going to freak you out.
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet.
No.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Dick.
Help me.
Where's the grenade?
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
Where is he?
I don't know where the fuck he is.
Right there.
He just threw a grenade at himself.
What was wrong?
I knocked out the fucking clip.
Okay, I got to be ready for this one.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Tighten these straps up.
Kind of like pretending to be bad.
All right, let me ask a question.
You got a guy shooting at you over here.
You got two monsters behind you and a guy spitting acid across the map.
Sorry that like priority number one is not like, you know, like.
Oh, yeah.
It's I'm dead.
Scary things are happening surrounding me.
Not, hey.
Oh, yeah, nice.
Oh, hey, what's going on?
No, it's terrifying.
Just win.
All right, fine.
Okay.
Stop.
Eat shit.
I don't know the trajectory.
I didn't know the trajectory.
What's this aim you got in front of you?
A fucking throw?
Open.
I want it open.
I can't open it.
How do you know where I even am, dude?
Give me that.
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck?
Why?
The top button.
Press the reload button.
The controller broken.
This hitched down tempo slowed down doom music.
Oh, my God.
All right, now reload.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Oh, my God.
Okay, see you in hell.
Oh, shit.
What's wrong with it?
How many bullets?
I need to...
What am I supposed to do?
Holy shit.
Get away from me.
Get away.
Don't come in here.
No.
This is...
Valve.
I can do it with this.
Why can't I do it with this?
I was hitting the wrong button.
Not anymore.
I was hitting this one not to grip.
Give it to me, duck.
Valve.
Oh, that's not why I was valving.
That's not...
I was valving over this.
Got it.
Oh, shit.
That was crazy.
You want to swap in here?
Nah, I would probably die in the...
Same shoulder as that arm.
Oh.
I...
That's a matter.
I've done that before.
Ready?
All right.
Well, but now it's working.
Like, it does like...
It works when you don't...
It doesn't work when you don't want it to.
I don't understand.
Like, you've seen me do the same motions.
Every time.
Well, it changed.
Nothing.
I just...
It's just...
I can't show it to you.
Valve.
Valve wants to work.
They're watching.
Valve.
Last three.
Three shells left.
Valve.
Valvin.
Last two.
Out of shells.
I need to...
I want ammo and stuff.
I'm not gonna fuck around.
This is like the end of the game.
I got like an hour left in the game or something.
I got like one chapter or two chapters left, right?
I want to make sure I get everything.
We're just gonna expand.
All right.
Nothing.
Let's go.
That's the monitor.
That's my monitor.
I just hooked it and almost pulled it down.
Okay.
There's only one point of entry.
Wait, do you have to...
Does it all...
Does it have to be on...
I don't think it has to be on them all at the same time.
I thought that's what was going on.
Okay.
Oh.
It does.
Oh, are you on?
It's gonna take him 20 minutes.
Took me five.
Odd Watchers already skipped.
And guess what?
That's on them.
Because they sat there probably for that five minutes going...
Oh, no, no, no.
He's gonna...
It's gonna take him 20 minutes.
They just went...
And ended up...
Whoa!
The final boss.
And they just spoiled the whole thing.
So you know what?
You just...
You did that.
I didn't.
I'm just playing the game.
Breaking and entering.
After is this?
After...
After we're in.
After 10 out of 11.
Oh, shit.
All right.
We're almost done.
I don't know what I've been screaming for.
I can't even tell.
I have no idea.
Chapter 10.
Somebody is just lighting up antlions.
Okay.
Kill...
Oh, hi.
I see.
Okay.
Are so good.
When do we get to see Gordon Freeman?
I'm actually excited for this.
We are gonna get a Gordon Freeman appearance.
Did I wake them up?
Wait.
Um...
Holy shit, dude.
I don't know.
I'm...
Just a stick.
Off the AC.
So good.
Hunts are fighting.
Why?
I'm gonna store this.
I already have one stored.
I have too much HP.
Okay.
I heard something in there,
and I'm gonna fuck off real quick.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
I've got a lot of shit on you, man.
I've got like 60 bullets on you.
Not that I'm gonna miss, probably.
I thought he was alive.
I thought he was queuing up for an attack.
God damn it.
How many can I have on here?
I can't do a double.
I have to use it.
Get under there.
Hold on.
Reload this, too, by the way.
No!
Push L's left.
This rolls to somebody.
I don't really even care.
All right.
So, if you take down that,
that thing's gonna come down.
If I climb up to this, I'm assuming.
Okay.
Help you?
Bored.
Bored penis.
Okay.
I wasn't expecting that.
Bored penis.
Okay.
I'll...
What am I gonna do?
I...
I'll be there.
Oh, fuck the grenade.
Thought I had it.
Oops, sorry.
I...
Watch this.
You just, like, pull the thing out?
Okay.
Did it work?
Oh, shit.
I did it, kind of.
Okay.
Now what?
God, I am supposed to get up here, isn't it?
Move this.
Come on.
Just get out of the fucking way.
Okay.
Stay open.
Oh.
He's...
Okay, the box is a distraction.
It worked.
I shot at the box.
Oh, Chad.
We're crying.
What's going on here?
I can't even spam.
What do I...
I'm...
I'm stuck in VR.
What do you want me to do?
F.A. hands.
Mods are fighting.
This is a bad Chad.
I don't know what's going on.
Attention to us.
Escape the Matrix.
All right.
I'm about...
Listen to me.
I'm about to get to the end of a game that's pretty good.
I want to enjoy it.
Cease this fighting at once.
Holy shit.
This is hard.
No.
And again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again, again.
I need to get to start.
Why?
I don't even get to start.
I think it's just to start this thing.
Put it in emote only mode?
Throw it in emote only mode.
Teach him a lesson.
Shit.
It's like...
Get out of here.
All this for...
Oh, that's actually quite a bit.
I already have two hit...
No.
I'm gonna leave that.
I don't want it.
Fuck that thing.
What's in emote only mode?
All right.
Now, cut it out.
Cut this out.
Cut this nonsense out.
Cut it out.
Arranged.
Okay, let's move this.
Okay, that does that.
I'm about to slip it out?
How do I move that?
Another control?
Oh, sick.
Did it.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, you're angry, but that's too much.
All right, let's go.
You're angry.
Oh, you're angry.
Where'd you even come from?
Progress.
It was worth it.
That was close.
That was fucking close.
Holy shit, I almost died.
Wait, this way?
All right, let's go.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Alex, we're getting close to the vault now.
I want the dot.
You don't have any more chances to use your weapon.
I want red dot on this.
Good point.
I'll see if there are any upgrades I can use.
The last upgrade.
I can't believe my pistol's made it this far.
I was thinking about giving it to Gordon.
This is the final upgrade of the game.
I want the red dot sight.
I want red dot on this.
Yes.
I did it?
No, I didn't.
Wake up.
It's time to wake up.
Laser sight.
Boom.
Final upgrade in the night.
That's it.
Let's see how good that looks now.
Now I can finally aim this gun.
Thank God.
It only took to the final 20 minutes of the game.
All right, are you going to?
I don't want to be on the wrong side of that.
Nice.
Hey, whatever.
Let him sleep.
Don't wake him up.
Be careful.
I love the red dot already.
Thank God.
Can we test it?
So good.
Oh, it's so good.
I can actually know what I'm doing.
It's still resident sleeper.
I mean, I might as well just use it.
Wake up.
Oh, I know it's why it's on emote only mode.
I get it.
Because everyone was spamming,
but they're probably telling me the end of the video game.
I'm just realizing that now.
I think it's in emote only because like there's
going to be a big thing here.
And I don't want everyone's going to be spamming like
Gordon Freeman.
Right.
I figured it out.
That's why.
All right.
I get it.
I think he's behind this door.
It's going to be Gordon Freeman.
White Gordon Freeman, but be back.
Hey.
Three left.
Ow.
Oh, shit.
He had the same idea.
That it?
Nothing in the car.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Damn it.
Okay.
Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me.
Here we go.
Direct hit.
Got him.
What?
Come on.
Three cells left.
Oh, what the fuck?
Get the fuck out of here.
I hit every single shot on that guy.
Every single one.
This is full.
We're good.
Yeah.
We're going to need this.
My goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
Just wait.
Now.
I'll do it.
Don't come in.
I'm warning you.
I tried to tell him.
Fuck.
I'm dead, man.
I'm dead.
Healing station.
Do it.
Gordon's going to be behind that door.
That was a full heal.
I think this is the only time in the whole game we've done a full heal.
Let's take a second here.
What else we got?
Nothing else?
Are we doing an ammo?
Good?
Good.
Full.
Everything's full.
Full health.
Full ammo.
We're good.
Let's do it.
Get the stuff over here.
I don't think so.
All right.
It's still in E mode only.
Holy shit.
That means something big must be about to happen.
Something huge.
Nothing even in here.
Okay.
Is Gordon going to open this door?
Does he talk?
Alex Scott.
So good to see you.
My name's Gordon.
I know.
I hope they do that.
I hope he talks.
Yeah.
Combine's really up.
Really creeping up on our ass.
That will be an oh shit moment.
I'll tell you that.
Get out of here, you fucking toys.
Let's go.
I got all the way up to the top of the tower.
Oh, we're going to get attacked by the drones now.
This is great.
Okay.
Just slowly go through this.
Out of here.
How do I get up here?
Oh shit.
Okay.
I'm going to jump.
There.
Here.
Don't fall.
Oh, you lucky bastard.
Three left.
Last one.
Still E mode only.
Oh, fuck.
G-Man's going to be on the top of this tower naked
by the amount of how long E mode only mode has been on.
Hello, Gordon Freeman.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Holy shit.
He put his hand down.
Oh, hello, Mr. Freeman.
It's me, G-Man.
And by the way, G-Man is Gordon Freeman.
I'm ready.
I don't need it yet.
Oh, he hit behind the force field.
Cheater.
Another one.
Another guy.
I hear a loud sound.
I think it's a big guy.
It's a big guy.
Huge guy.
Big guy coming in.
Who's the big guy now?
Vampire.
There's only one way you can go.
You son of a bitch.
Get the final electricity puzzle.
We're like 12 hours into the game.
You're going to put like the wood in front of the door still.
You're still going to put the wood in front of the door?
Alex, you there?
Yeah, dad.
It looks like you will be able to get into the vault from up there.
There's a terminal that extends a bridge to the entrance.
What's the security like inside?
Security.
God, it all laid out in front of me and I tell you, there is security.
But I've never seen anything like it.
It doesn't make any sense.
I guess I'll have to improvise.
Don't worry, honey.
I'll figure it out.
It's kind of satisfying when you pull the things off.
They don't even need to do that.
Well, we're like going way, way up here.
We are.
Alex, get ahead.
Those controls dock the vault to the station.
Mike, I've came to the inside of a piano.
What should I do?
All right, time to go rescue the savior of humanity.
Oh, we have to go in there?
You haven't been doing it.
All right, looks like the bridge is fully extended.
Just need to gently dock the vault to the bridge.
How far can that be?
How do you do that?
Oh, okay.
Well, one of these has to bring in the vault for Donnie, right?
Almost certainly.
Just pick one.
Immediately.
Four, five, six, nine.
Okay, we're going to do turn on nine.
Maybe.
No, not that one.
Eight.
Alex, the bridge isn't moving.
Why is the bridge not moving?
I know.
Russ, I can see it not moving.
Four, five, nine, eight, five.
Got it.
Here he comes, here he comes, here he comes, here he comes.
Come on, shh, shh, quiet, quiet.
Oh, it's not, it's a loading screen.
That was crazy though.
L-U-L.
All right, here we go, here we go, here it comes.
Alex?
Alex, are you okay?
Jesus Christ.
I think I just killed Gordon Freeman.
The vault's right there.
Just go in and get him.
What is that thing?
Why is there a stretch Armstrong that's stretched way too much?
Holy shit, I'm dead.
Reload to safe.
Reload, please.
I don't want to waste that.
I'm probably going to need it.
Why is everybody doing that?
That was a, that, this is like a checkpoint.
Yeah, see?
We can start freaking out.
Alex?
Alex, are you okay?
I think I just killed Gordon Freeman.
The vault's right there.
Just go in and get him.
That's what they looked like up close.
I'm on my way.
Healing station.
Yeah, I wasted my injection.
I didn't even need to use it.
And here it comes.
Here it comes.
Where is he?
Make sure we're all loaded up.
Well, so.
I'm ready.
Even deeper.
Look at Earth's core.
That's that.
Oh, damn it.
Assessment shot 15 times
right in the face and chest.
Oh, that's not.
Fuck.
Full ammo.
Okay, we're even deeper now.
I thought that was Gordon Freeman for a second.
I was like, well, there he is.
Fuck.
I just showed him a firework.
Damn it.
Out of cells.
A strider.
Deactivated though.
Lucky break there.
Could you imagine that?
Strider.
Blocking your way.
Extra ammo.
Jinx me.
Dumb.
All right, what are we trying to do here?
In that room somewhere, apparently.
Broken.
The lift is fucked up.
Okay, let's keep going.
Sneak in there?
Crawl?
What the fuck?
Can't get in there.
Get rid of me.
Okay, I got it.
Wait, no, I have to prop up the door.
All right, I got to prop it up.
Made it.
Or this shit.
Okay.
Power up there.
Active.
Power's on here.
Other power cell activator.
This one goes...
Oh, what?
Power on.
More trails.
Okay, now the lift works.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look at this.
I almost missed this shit.
Um.
Take it.
One left.
Oh.
There's a lift.
Wait, did I kill this thing?
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Get out.
How should I shoot him in the face?
Oh, fuck no, fuck no, fuck no.
Oh, fuck that.
Fuck that.
Um.
Fuck.
What a shit face.
Holy shit, that was insane.
Okay.
I didn't even use anything.
I was all the way out.
Alright.
Still.
Oh shit, it's a person.
Oh.
Kill him, entry, kill him, entry, kill him, entry.
We're gonna be right there.
Shit.
This game is insane.
It's just, it's like a, it's a, it's a, it's a stimulation.
Just stab you.
Stim simulation explosion guy coming a giant alien shoot those guys watch out watch out for the guy. She's an alien. Oh
Nuts, I feel like I downloaded into my brain every scary haunted house if I've been into and every
Theme-park ride I've ever been on at the same time
This is like going down the apex of the Superman ride of steel while somebody is putting screamers into your face
It's just a huge amount of intense reaction
And let's go
Unplug something. Oh shit the power cable. I have looked at power cable and the USB
So what happened to my arm? What what what happened?
Wow, give me that give me that thing fuck you fuck you
I
Lost chat I don't have chat anymore. I
Gotta do it without chat
I've ripped on the cable. I hope I have nothing anymore. We got to do it without chat
Love chats encouragement
Okay, let's go. I got a shit little like I got a shit little errors on my computer right now
I'm not gonna open them. Okay, let's go. Oh, I'm gonna get a bath after this one
This control is broken too. This control is broken too. They both broken. I can't move
Shit I can't walk perfect, bro. Fuck, please walk, please walk
Slowly get by like broken body to the end of the game
I see chat. I see chat. I just the turn the controller. We really fucked up like this
Restart the game. All right, what happened?
Restart the game. What did you restart?
Which controllers?
Yeah, no, I know but this is sorry, I got don't worry I got take a second reload
Why?
Okay, if I do it really lightly it works
car
Over there, right? I'm gonna take it with me
He's for the love of God open
Um, I don't know
I'm just gonna I gotta leave it. I have to leave it. Here we go. No fucking way, dude
I don't want it anymore
Don't kill me I asked nicely
Oh
My back is killing me right now. This whole area is gonna be inflamed. Oh
Hit the rage timer, dude. Oh
I'm gonna have to go in one of those medieval devices that stretch you out and like rip your bones in half
Fuck me
This is it. All right. No, no more three VR days in a row. I can't do that again
I
Get over there are
Wait, wait, hey
Alright Alex let track to be a movie. It looks like it'll get you up to the vault. Got it. Oh shit
Maybe I should have done that. Oh my way. Wait. Oh, yeah. Okay
Then you'll come out with course sound everything is gonna be everything will be fine
Talk to you soon
All right, let's get a mid-roll ad right when I fucking press right trigger
Holy shit, dude. No way
It's Gordon Applebee's has 25 ribs for $25
Okay, this is weird
What world's floating around?
Hey, I'm a dream your dream world
I don't know. Excuse me
Excuse me. Oh, dude. Yeah, get a banana and spin it around into space. Oh
Did that like right into the camera? Didn't I I got his brief? This is g-man's briefcase
What's in it? Oh this nevermind. Okay. I don't hear a clock. Is there like a
I don't have any weapons or anything. I swear to God
It's Peter Molyneux is inside of there. I'm gonna be really mad
Final opportunity for a television joke. Oh my god final opportunity for a television joke. I love attorney for a television joke
I don't even care. Fuck the TV joke
Fuck the TV joke never doing a TV joke again. Hey
This is some inception level shit right now, okay, that's gonna fall off
I
Honkers I must just fell off. I did fall off. I did. Yeah, I fell off. I fell off
And my life I soft-locked myself. I soft-locked. Oh, no, I'm not
Mailroom
Okay, um open
This didn't go in
Okay, if you want to do something weird
Take a mirror that's long enough for you to hold up against your chin
And if you hold a mirror long ways like this flat, so the mirror is facing up and you walk around
It actually looks like this you walking around on your thing
Be careful though, cuz you'll like bump into shit
That was like in Nickelodeon magazine like 25 years ago, I remember reading Nickelodeon magazine
Whose house are we in?
Who is this person?
Crack the plates and smash the plates. That's what Bilbo Baggins hates
Crack the plates and smash the plates. So carefully carefully with the plates. Oh
Don't do that. Watch out for that. Oh
No, you idiot. Oh, come on
Jesus man
Stuck in the bathroom. I'm stuck in the bathroom. Oh
Weapons
My god, what is that a drink? Was that a drink? No, thank goodness. It wasn't a fucking drink
Go down there my brains gonna explode
And kill me in there, please
Bathroom another bathroom. I love the bathrooms. I'm doomed
What is going on right now?
What is this level where am I inside of the machine I don't understand
Okay, we're going here
Or don't open I have to go in that one. I don't have to go in that door. Do I?
How the fuck am I gonna get up there?
That's the right idea I think
Up on there. That's right. Do I have the right idea and jump on that?
No, nae nae nae nae nae nae nae. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right, which one opens I don't open
Doesn't open this one doesn't open
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, what what do I can't get in here
I feel like this is what I have to do
Fuck. Oh my god fucking VR man. Just lock me in a cube
In a padded room
Well, this is not right died
Fucking sofa, I guess it was just like fuck. Okay. I at least I have the right idea
Boom
There's the door
Get the door open. Oh shit
Over there
I don't know. I have no idea what I'm doing right now, but I I can't help it. Oh, I can pull them off. Okay
Holy shit
Next oh you don't think I can get in this door
Oh
Where'd it go?
I have board in here. Wait, I need give me more of those. I don't have any more of those. What do I have?
Holy shit. Okay
The shot that grenade in my mouth what happened to it?
What else think they should make these controls out of fucking taffy or something? Why they made it a plastic?
It should be made out of stainless steel
Why are these made of plastic?
Oh, they're gonna get
Fuck you, buddy
What do we say
There's no more power when
Gordon i'm here to save you Gordon. I'm here to save you
Gordon i'm here to rescue you
It's me alex vanes
All right. Yeah, this is the end. Wait, we just released g-man. That's what's going on. We're releasing g-man
I might have this motherfucker trapped
And we we just let him out. That's g-man and then that's not important for him
We're the bad guys
Holy shit
This changes everything
This changes the whole story
All right, gordon
Let's get you out of this. This change is literally the entire story
Holy shit. Okay. All right. I'm ready
Uncle festers vibration machine on maximum. I told you I told you
I told you we let that fucking guy out impressive work
freeman
Mr. You wouldn't need all that
to imprison
Gordon freeman
so
Who are you?
Perhaps what I am is not as important as what I can
in exchange for coming
Shut up
Some believe the fate of our world is
inflexible
lawyers
They authorize me to
Nod things in a particular direction from time. Would you miss vance?
Combine off i want the combine off earth
That would be a considerably large nudge
To given the interests of my employer fast
What if I could offer you something you don't know?
you
Dad
Is that me? What is this?
What's happening? We are in the future
This is the moment where you watch your father
die unless
What?
Unless what?
unless
You were to take matters into your own hand
Hey, I oh release your father
The trick dirty trick
Uh, it's the trick
As a consequence of your action
This entity will continue
and this entity
Will not right
So he's okay
right
He lives
My dad lives
You are aware that you've proven yourself to be of
Extraordinary value a previous hire has been unable
Or unwilling to perform the tasks laid before him
we
Struggle to find a suitable
Replacement
Until now no
I just want to go home
Send me home. I'm afraid
you
misunderstand the situation
Wait
Hey, wait, wait
Wait, fine. Hey, so
Alex vance has
fired
Hating a sign man
I thought he doesn't elive ants die
What happened?
what
Hold on a second. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
So we did we just like stopped that from happening, but it happens because this takes place before half-life two
What the fuck happened?
Wait, what?
Feel like what a different like time. Are we like a multiverse?
Keep watching. Okay
That was awesome that that last 45 minutes was in fucking sane
Okay, let me tell you something if you had if you had
Like a gigantic living room and like five lighthouses and you had an index and you had the knuckle controllers
Yeah, that last sequence would have been the most intense moment of your whole life
If you're if you were able to actually sprint around your living room
You gotta be careful though because you could like literally sprint sprint sprint and smash looney tune style
Into your wall and go right through it and leave a imprint
It'll be like boom through the door. I'm like the thing that looks like this like oh I look
It's a it's a person's body went through here
That was fucking crazy
There he is. There he is. There he is. There he is. There he is
Just glad robin walker worked on another fps
I am
Oh, that was great that was very good double db game audio of water brothers
I don't think that's good
Yeah, it's same g-man. Yeah
It tells you to know that g-man is the spy
Also a very talented actor probably can't hear a word i'm saying the music's coming very loud
It's an actor credit scene
Gordon gordon wake up gordon. She's gone gordon
She's gone
Son of a bitch in his unforeseen consequences
I knew it
When I get my hands on him
Oh
Listen to me, don't let me pick this up and then go back. Oh you're gonna end the game now
No
I got to touch it
Okay, so
You know advance is alive
That was the very those of you that have no idea
It's been like 15 years kind of pieces together too. So you live advance dies at the end of half life two episode two
That's where the that's where it's left off
this game
Where are you guys?
spoilers
what
You just watched him die on the ground
This is this is this is the third half-life game
What are you doing here?
anyways
so
Let me get this straight
You live advance dies at the end of half-life two episodes. Okay, this game takes place before half-life two
This is in between half-life one and half-life two
But so if that's the case when you play half-life two
He's to he dies in that game
It's not like and you know, you know, it'd be really fucking crazy
Here'd be crazy crazy valvy eliciting
How crazy would this be if they patched half-life two episode two and he don't fucking die now?
What a mind fuck that would be
Imagine they patched that shit
it was like
Alex vance went back and then messed with the timeline and it messed and it messed with your computer
Awesome. Oh, that's cool. I'm so but how does that work?
It's retcon so what so but half-life two episode two still is happens
That means this time travel that means that but but that well, but that also means
That somebody fucks up later in like half-life four which causes him to die anyways in half-life two episode two
Well, they've got a real can of worms to play with here whenever they do that
wrong
happens
And is a time traveler
Half-life two never happened
No, but that but right there that was
Okay, i'm gonna i'm gonna have to go through quite a few reddit threads after the stream ends. I'm gonna have to watch
Half-life alex broken down
It's all fiction
Reddit theory. All right, let me get out of here
Oh
That was awesome
All right. I'm gonna have to give it an official score
An official score. My camera's lagging again
Definitely higher than eight
Definitely higher than nine
Definitely higher than a 92 higher than a 92
It's 94
done 9.4
Fantastic i'll tell you a little bit of the drop issues over the shoulder I had
Well, that's that's that's one little millipoint
two millipoints
and
The electricity kind of minigame thing where you switch the wires
Uh, I mean there's a little a little lot of those
9.4. That was your fault
end user problem
All right. Fine. We'll add two points, but then I take an extra two millipoints off for all the electricity puzzles. There you go
It's 9.4
Literally like the highest score i've given a game in like four years
Just say 10
What was the last time I gave a game higher than a nine?
I gave uh
I gave outer wilds an eight nine and eighty nine and people like wanted to kill me
House flipper vr. Yeah, we'll do that
That's the 22nd, right?
I still do
Now that was awesome. That was very very very good that exceeded my expectations and I didn't have any expectations
I told you i'm not doing that anymore
I'm not giving games expectations anymore
Because if I was going to be sitting here looking up shit every single day about half-life alex like I would have done
I'm not putting games on pedestals anymore. I'm just going to let them play
I didn't look up anything. I didn't even care about this game
I'm like this is like three and a half months late for what four and a half months late playing this
I didn't I just I just said you know what just it's gonna wow me if it doesn't
I'm not gonna look up anything. I don't want to like put it up higher because if I put it too high then it's not
Good enough
It was great
It was six months. Yeah, pretty late
Seven months late, whatever same deal same. It's within 12 months. It's okay
I'll play bone works. That's the plan
but
Uh, we're gonna move away from vr for a little while. I want my hair to grow back
I want my hair to grow back bad
Uh, we've been doing tons of vr
We're gonna move away from vr for a couple of weeks. We're gonna go back to playing a video game
That's not in a headset
I want I want if I saw two
Gotta do chubby bunny
We still have a bunch of 3do stuff that has to be done
We'll go back to vr
When we get close to halloween
Because then I have like three or four scary games we'll do we'll do like a halloween vr week. I play scary shit
Sounds like a plan
All right. Here's the ultimate question though
Is half-life alex worth getting a vr headset?
a lot of money
That's it's a shitload of money
I would say yes if there was realistically even
Like one or two other games
That with at this caliber
If you buy a vr headset for alex you're gonna be really fucking disappointed because every single other game you play on vr
Is way worse
So I would wait till there was another couple of these before you dish out four or five six seven hundred bucks
Now just because they're I mean look that you don't have like valve behind you make it your game
Well, let's be honest any vr game that is out now
I mean, you can't really compare you just can't
That doesn't mean they're not fun
And yeah the pc required to do so but uh, hold on a second though. Hold on
My pc is really not that good like it is but it's not
I have a 1080
and an i7 like 6800
so
I have like five or six year old hardware and it still ran it fine
780 can run it
Probably. Yeah, I mean I didn't see very much slow down and remember i'm streaming this too
So essentially like this is going through twice
Like my cpu is running double time because it's like encoding all the vr shit
source 2
Source 2 is pretty optimized. Yeah
My 1050 ran it fine with no problems. Yeah, you don't need like super crazy hardware
And it is still a high tier
I still think it's pretty good. I think it's done pretty good for me
Oh, all right
Let's do a hair check and then i'm gonna get out of here
pretty bad
And it is good enough right now. It's four and a half years old. Yeah, it's still it's still good
See
It actually looks kind of styled
Elvis what am I doing? Uh-huh. Ooh
That's that's like bargain bin. Elvis. Whoa
Look at that
No, i'm one of those angler fishes, you know, like the big teeth
And like the light bulb
All right, that's I gotta get out of here. I gotta fuck off
Uh, let's take a look and see what happened over the course of the stream. Let's do let's get the credits rolling
Thanks for watching everybody half-life alex awesome 9.4 out of 10. Wow
Thanks for subbing everybody
Speaking of which we had five community subs from prono varrox. Thank you
Five community subs from nukeable think we got that already
Fifty dollars that I missed this somebody said big bits
And here they are
Uh when I was in the headset, I couldn't really see
Uh pripro prep, thanks for the fifty dollars
The large amount of money you are by far the most enjoyable streamer to watch and i've been watching your videos for about eight years
Can't afford to give you the amount of bits. I would want to for entertaining me for years
Thanks for being you and doing what you do
If I ever have children i'm going to make them watch your videos to learn how to be funny as I couldn't educate them better
On that myself
If you uh show your children my videos, they're gonna end up in detention over and over again
I would hold off on that until they are at least probably at least until they're 18
You show your kids my videos
Uh, I think you might see some bad behavior coming through
What do you want me to say, okay, wait wait till they're 12 before they show you a video of me in minecraft
I don't know. This is what you want me to say. This is an 18 plus stream
Oh, yeah, yeah
God damn x rated no x rated the r rated r is not rated x rated r is rated r
Oh man, what the fuck is a germa? I don't know man. It's me
It's me
All right. I am going to get out of here
Immediately my whole body hurts. I'm in so I am like actually in like physical pain
Three vr days in a row is not so I don't don't I don't think that's a good idea anymore
I'm okay though. I'm all right
I am gonna just run away right now. I'll see you guys on wait. What's today's date?
I'll see you guys on friday or saturday, probably saturday. We'll do saturday sunday
I'll see you guys on saturday do a raid. Oh, you know what? You know who I want to raid
I want to raid boxbox because boxbox rated the stream with like
4 000 people last week or the week four and I just fucking ignored it completely
It was like an absolute. I didn't even it was a total ignore. I didn't even know what happened
So it was like oh boxbox raid. Here it comes. I didn't even know
And i'm just sending uh, let's go back and say thanks for the raid from two weeks ago
Sing the raid song
Wow, you're a piece of shit. I don't how did I even miss it? I don't even know what I was doing
I felt so bad afterwards. I was like wait. No, that's
Boxbox is awesome. I mean there was like a lot of people too
They're playing team fight tactics if you're into that. I don't even know how it works. Oh, and i've tried to watch it before
It's just 10 enemies line up and then somebody presses the go button and they just run into each other
I don't know how it works. It's apparently it's hard
Team fight tactics not team fortress tactics
It's hard well, all right, I I liked I played uh, hearthstone battlegrounds i've come in first place 10 times
Yep, I did
By the way, i've come in fourth place or higher almost 100 times
I am currently rated about
That's not bad for somebody that's bad at everything
But i'm not bad at everything. I just say that so then I can surprise you
Go say hello to boxbox
Thanks for watching everybody. I'll see you on probably saturday
We're gonna move away from vr
No, you are bad
Stay hydrated. Yeah, i'm gonna go get some water because the food take a bath
I need it
Have a great rest of your night everybody
See you in a few days
Good night