Oh, we got like a director over here, apparently, like giving me like a handshake or something.
Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with a very special guest. You know, you all know this guy, maybe, potentially.
Hi.
That's Burger Boy. We're doing this via satellite from Burger Boy's house. I mean, we're actually in outer space right now.
But no, we're gonna be doing Scare Saturdays over Burger Boy's house.
I tweeted this out, like, a couple hours ago, and everyone was like, you gotta have Burger Boy in that friggin goddamn video.
So here he is. And we're gonna play. What the hell are we playing? Black Death. Black Death.
The Plague.
Yeah.
Is this kid ready to go? Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Scare Saturday.
Let's do it.
Barrels, get out of here. Barrels, get out of here.
All right, we gotta find the lantern. Burger Boy has like no idea how to play these games, by the way.
And neither did I until like a week ago. So we have to find the lantern. I know that. Let's just open the door.
All right.
Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Is there anything? There's gotta be something in here I need to pick up.
There's an exit right there. Don't think that really matters. Let's just go.
There's voice acting in this one.
Holy crap.
Nothing under there.
Ooh, ice.
Beware when standing in the eye. No insanity. I get you.
To whoever finds this means. I probably didn't make it. I had to go back inside to get my brother.
We got split up in there. If you're reading this turn back now, that ain't gonna happen.
This is Scare Saturdays, baby. We push through no matter what.
Except for last week when I rage quit.
Second floor key.
All right, I got the key.
Go in this room.
In there.
Another note.
I have a headache. Yeah, you're giving me a headache game.
Gonna throw up. I'm gonna throw up.
God damn it, man. It's a fucking statue.
Yeah, just wait till you're doing this. It sucks.
Come on.
It has to be another way past this door. This door won't open.
Where's the lantern?
I can't open this. So did I go down this way yet?
No.
Okay, maybe it's because I didn't go down here.
God damn it!
All right, so for those of you that have no idea.
Okay, so me and him were just trying to figure out where the hell we were going.
And that thing just changed. Great. Fantastic. Thank you.
Thank you, mod.
I still don't have the lantern.
Got a key, though.
Great key.
That scared the absolute shit out of me.
Oh, is Burger Boy gonna like die because he saw that?
Hold on. Make sure I don't miss anything, man.
I feel like I'm missing so much stuff.
Maybe not.
Okay, this is the chamber.
Can we knock it in here?
Okay, no, here's the key.
I cannot use the item in this way. I can't use the key.
Where's that key go then?
Maybe the first floor door.
Okay, right, right, right, right.
Black. It's pitch black.
I hate that shit so bad.
All right, let's use that key.
What about if we go in here?
What just happened?
A loud noise was in my ear and it threw me back a thousand feet.
Hey, okay.
I'm assuming there's something on this desk.
Hey, look, a note.
They're watching you.
Oh, are they?
Kate, give me the Kate.
Third floor exit and the true horrors of this castle lie down in the chamber.
They're rapping at my chamber door.
Let's go.
Hi. Hi, guys.
Oh, you want to, like, scam me?
Get through all your heads.
One, two, three, four, five.
Who wants to go now?
You want to dance?
You fucking...
Let's go.
Wait, what key do I just get?
Hey, pay attention.
You got the third floor exit key.
Okay, let's get out of here.
I'm going to turn...
You know, I don't want to run into lamp oil.
I'm just going to run out of here like this.
Okay.
I don't like the frigging blood everywhere.
Oh, that's the second floor.
Did I miss anything in here?
What about...
No, I can't go in that door.
I already tried.
Okay.
Let's go.
To the Chamber of Secrets.
Get off me, bro.
Welcome to the Chamber of...
He's still right there.
He's still next to me.
Get the fuck away from me.
What?
He's right there.
No!
Did you just seriously puke?
Did you seriously just puke?
Oh my god.
Live on camera, Burger Boy just puked.
And swallowed it.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I can't believe that just happened.
You better keep that in.
Oh, that's staying in.
There's other people there.
You can't see them.
Hold on, wait.
Alright, I gotta go to the chamber now.
Alright, we got a live puke from Burger Boy.
The best part was he chased you until he got wicked close to you and then disappeared.
Dude, he chased me through the whole freaking hallway.
The whole point was to scare the ever-living shit out of you.
That's like never happened.
I think, you know what?
I think a lot of people are probably gonna say in the comments,
that was from using this light and walking around with the light out so we could see where I was.
Makes sense.
Alright, I gotta go...
Do I have a key?
No.
Okay.
Can I open this?
I can't open it.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, key, key, key.
Chamber exit key.
And this is my last letter.
Be careful.
I saw some unhuman creature lurking down in the chamber.
Oh, that's fantastic.
What?
Hi.
I hear the music.
Where is this guy?
Get away from me.
Get away from me, you prick.
I should have closed the door.
Hey, look it, we're back.
Your turn.
I can't believe you fucking threw up.
I cannot believe you fucking threw up.
Let's see if like, Jerm is just like a baby or if this is like really scary.
No, it's definitely really scary.
I've played this game before.
Yeah, I'm running.
Where?
No!
What?
What just killed him?
What killed you?
It killed me from behind.
All right.
Well, I recant my statement.
It's not so easy when you're in a driver's seat, is it?
That's probably going to happen again.
This is probably the right way to go.
I just like freaked out and ran away.
No, it wasn't.
The key.
How long have you been in this room?
The Enchiridion?
With it?
You're pretty low on lamp oil.
Yeah, good point.
Okay, well this is the right way.
Apparently.
Those chairs didn't jump for no reason.
Arm?
What else we got here?
It's definitely this.
Yeah, again.
Oh yeah, baby.
He's getting ready for a scare.
Oh!
Oh, he's smart.
Always got to shut the doors behind you.
Have you ever seen a horror movie, Jerma?
It's like the key.
Sanity what?
Dangerously low.
I don't know.
I'm in like hell now.
I made it.
I...
Try moving.
I made it.
I am.
That's it.
We did it.
We beat the game.
Woo!
Although Burger Boy was only there for like 30 seconds.
Well, it was a good 30 seconds.
Thanks.
Hey, Burger Boy's channel is going to be in the description.
His channel sucks, but like just go like subscribe.
Wicked bad.
You can like watch me like sleep on camera.
Alright, well thanks everybody for watching.
Uh, Burger Boy you want to do an outro?
Alright.
Thanks everybody for watching.
This has been Scare Saturdays with Burger Boy and Jerma.
And as always.
Take care everybody.
And don't puke like he did during this whole video.
Bye.