Hey, what is going on, everybody? Derma here with some live Dermalicious Man gameplay commentary.
Tonight I'm gonna be playing with the new items, the new demo items, because, you know, I haven't really had a chance to sit down with them consecutively, so let's go.
So I have to try to like figure out how this stuff works. It's been a week or so since I've played Team Fortress 2, but we're gonna give it a go.
So, when I first saw the sticky launcher, I was under the impression that I was probably going to like it, because you just shoot stuff and explode.
Shoot stuff and explode. Is that spy dead? I have no idea. Does anybody know if that spy is dead? Can I please hit...
You wanna go ham on ham? You wanna go ham on ham? It was a big mistake. You never go ham on ham with a demo.
Oh, you were a demo, so don't ever mind. You are a spy. If I've ever seen one, you are a goddamn spy.
No, he wasn't. He was a regular player. Look at you. Oh, no, don't. We can't lose. No, you fucker. Oh, I saw that happening too.
I legit just watched that happen and didn't do anything about it. I just kind of, my brain turned off and he's gonna get to the point here with crits.
Somebody do something about that. Oh, good job. Good job, Pyro. You flamed him. Nice job flaming him.
Now we lose. That guy charged on it and we lose. Alright, let's just restock the video. Hey, what's going on, everybody?
So, you're probably wondering why we're on cold front, and the answer to that is quite simple. It's really, really cold right now in the northeast.
There's like a big cold front passing through, and I figured why not show the implication that it's chilly out.
And it's like five degrees, and I'm sure a lot of you guys from really cold areas are probably like, wow, that's nothing.
You're telling me you're gonna close schools for like five degree weather? I walked to school in like negative 15.
What does this guy think he's doing? Oh, I didn't get anybody. I'm gonna wrap around.
I still don't understand this item. This item is like, what, a combination of the lock and load? Should I be treating it like a lock and load or what?
It's like lock and load in the default, kind of as one. I'm not even entirely sure how I should be playing with this.
But all I know is it's good for stuff like that, because it travels really far.
And that's what you should be using it for, at least in my opinion, is to launch stuff really far very quickly.
Well, let's try to get this capped. Hey, hey, that's two spies. No, it's not. It's just one. Where'd you go? Show yourself.
Give me this health. I don't feel like dying right now. Is he dead? All right, he's dead. We're gonna get this.
These rounds are going super, super fast. Yeah, I mean, direct shotting with this thing. Is it as fast as the lock and load? I just don't even know.
What the hell do I even know? Got that guy.
The one thing I don't like about this new sticky launcher is the point, the point, the thing. Can you say words? Say words.
It's not that difficult to produce vocabulary. Do we have a medic? I don't even know. Is the short detonation time?
I don't like that. But I guess you kind of have to give up the fact that you're able to shoot things across the map in like less than two seconds like that.
So we're gonna wait for this health to spawn. Please spawn. And you are. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry about that.
You could have used that health instead. I took it from you. Do we have this many snipers on the team or is that like a spy or something?
Get rid of that thing. Where's the medic? There's too many snipers. I keep thinking you're all spies. No, no, no. One more hit.
I would have had him. Still got him. I'm good. It's good to go. Good to go. Good to go. Good to go. Not really. Here comes everybody.
I should really pull this out. There we go. Oh, I just barely didn't get that guy with the long range shot.
Give me a medic. Holy shit. Get me out of there. Let's recharge. We need some health. Give us the health.
Oh, damn. Was that a crit screen or did he just get a random crit? Shit. I wanted to. I wanted to win this video game.
They got it. Damn it. All right. I got to like set up in my chair. Let's set up in the chair.
Let's take a sip of our crystal clear. That guy just lost an uber. Shit. That's no good. Can I stick?
I can sticky jump. Yeah, I think so. Right. Yeah. That's a sniper that's going for my. You know what? Screw it.
I'm going to use this thing. I like this thing more than the. Holy shit. Did he really just launch that across everything and hit me?
Damn it. Now they're going to cap it. No, I didn't. And you know, I didn't even sit up in the chair. That's problem number one.
I'm still like slouching back like a fucking sloth. There we go. Now we're sitting up and we're just going to go for this.
Let's see if we can get somebody right now. See if that just hit somebody. It did.
That's too bad that that didn't kill somebody. That would have been pretty funny. I'll pop it. He popped it. He didn't drop it.
That's too bad. And I'm still taking damage of one HP spirit.
Spirit of Halloween. No, we're in the middle of January.
It's like, what is what is this? Halloween only comes once a year and I would I would accept Halloween
anywhere between late September to early November. But in January, that's pushing it and I need health.
We're getting just swarmed right now. Oh, my God. I'm using this thing like a shotgun. If I could just hit this medic, that would be fantastic.
But I can't actually maybe I can. I'll just babysit up here at least for now until I can get some health.
There we go. The spirit of Halloween go through. I just saw a candy pumpkin. That was a candy pumpkin.
Oh, my God. You're you're no longer among the living over here. Where the fuck did you come from?
Oh, I got a winter crate. I got to do some shit. I'm not doing so well right now.
You got to arc these differently, I think. Sort of. You're not getting away with that.
Damn it. Come on up here. Come on up here. No, get away with me with that shit.
Oh, there's a lot of people coming down there. I need some help. Give me the heals.
No, not quite. Not quite through the hall. There are a bunch of people in here now, especially that spy.
I don't want that spy to wrap around. Yeah, there he is. Where's he going? Where is he? Right there.
Get out of here. Get out of. Damn it. Come on, we got to spawn. We can't lose right here.
What's going on? We having like a fucking tea party and spawn, guys? Let's go.
And there's a spy that just opened this door because the invisible man.
Nobody can open doors like that unless. Holy shit. What do we got here? You.
That's a crit. Come on, hit somebody. That didn't hit anybody. It was like three people just standing here.
You know, wrap around this way. Well, I got the medic of all people to get.
Oh, damn it. You're going to run right into me, aren't you? You didn't think that spy was going to get you.
I hit him with two. Can I hit him with that? I'm just going to go for the sniper instead.
Screw that guy. Sniper won't even know I'm going to do this because I can shoot at super long range.
Good thing I detonated before it even got to anybody. Holy shit. Bye. I didn't even kill him either.
I did not even kill him, but I will take credit for it nonetheless.
Damn it. I'm so bad with that thing. No, nobody on it. They're all over here.
You know, there's definitely a sniper here. Yeah, of course there is.
Can't even hit a guy standing still with this thing. Can't even hit a guy standing still.
Goodness. OK, well, sort of made up for it. Sort of.
You need a medic, don't you? What? What? It's OK.
I will take this medic and maybe we can push in. That would be great.
That would be fantastic if we could just push in right now. Oh, don't let him get over on that health.
You've got to cover all your bases when there's a health thing. You've got to put one here, you've got to put one there, you've got to put one over there.
This is not good. OK, well, we've got a team. Whoa, somebody's going to cap it.
Somebody was just about to cap it on our team. And we've got a Kritzkrieg.
Ooh, a Kritzkrieg. I bet you if you use it, we win.
I bet you we win. Oh, my God.
I got two people. Perfect timing for me to be good at the game.
What's happening? Just, you know, screw it. I'm going for it.
I made up for it. I made up for my two kill Kritzkrieg.
I did the sticky jump over and got the point. I did it.
I just heard a spy decloak. Is that you? That was you.
That was you. I got him. OK.
Well, OK. So got a spy. Got ourselves a spy there.
They're flooding the point right now. Oh, don't stop and drink.
Don't stop and drink your fluids, your Gatorade or your Powerade.
Whatever the hell you were just drinking. Dear.
Nobody there? Nobody there. How are our sentries doing? Good?
All right. Well, we only have to push through four points or not lose it.
Oh, there we go. There we go. Thanks for the speed boost, dude.
We're actually going to push out. Would you look at that?
Here comes a scout. I thought he was going to open the door.
He kind of is going to open the door, is he?
This is what we're talking about here. What we're talking about like long reds, a crit.
Was that a crit? How am I not hitting anybody?
I can't hit the backside of a fucking barn door.
Oh, that's a lot of damage. At least I got somebody.
Hopefully it was the heavy. If it wasn't the heavy that...
No. Spy. Where is he? Watch out for the spy.
Dude, I'm going to wait here because there's no way I can let that happen.
Because he will come over here and just sap this thing.
I got to give this guy a little bit of protection, at least. At the very least.
No, you're real. There's a sniper. Sniper down.
That's a lot of people.
No, I got him. Let's push out. Push out, boys.
We've got places to be. Guy's on the right.
Oh, he's still alive. There he goes.
What about this guy? Long range.
Too bad. Too bad.
No, get away from me with that.
Now I'm on fire. Heal up.
We actually, surprisingly, we were back on our toes there.
We're back on our heels.
Is that whatever the expression is? Is that even an expression?
I don't know. Probably not.
We're going to pretend it is, though.
And we're going to hope that the spy did not just walk right by my ass.
Which he probably did.
That scout just almost ate me alive.
Here comes the Uber.
Don't you even think about it, you two.
Die! Did I get the medic?
I didn't get the medic. I didn't get the medic.
We're in trouble now.
We still got the sentries?
If we still got those sentries, we'll be in pretty okay shape.
But I'm going to assume.
That might be enough to prolong this.
Oh, no, we got two. We got two. There's one right there.
Don't worry about it.
Nobody worry.
We just got to make sure this heavy medic doesn't roll in here
and just destroy everything.
I'm going to try to shoot over the heavy and kill the medic.
And I was sort of successful.
Kind of. I did damage.
Don't turn around. Don't turn around.
There's nobody behind you.
Oh, I should have paid attention behind me.
I was too busy hamming people.
Oh, well.
Shit. Well, that's what happens.
I'm going to try one more time.
I'm going to go balls to the wall.
I'm going to try to just cap it quick.
Hashtag cap it quick is what I'm trying to do here.
But it's probably going to end in my own death.
Considering I didn't do any jumping or anything.
I didn't like sticky jump or anything.
But here we go. Cap it quick.
Middle point.
We got a couple of people going about.
Oh, we got. Here we go.
Here we go.
All right, we got two or three down.
Two or three down. What we got? One Demoman?
Where's he at?
There we go.
No, not quite.
You bastard.
You just killed my medic.
We're going to cap it.
We just got it.
Oh, my God.
Hashtag cap it quick.
It's actually a thing.
No.
Shit.
Cap it quick.
Yes.
You see what happened?
See what happens when you use a hashtag in a game?
You got to write it.
You got to know what's going to be written.
Hashtag cap it quick.