Oh, hi, didn't see you there. Yeah, I did actually. How you doing? I'm doing okay. Where should I sit here?
Or sit here like this? So you can get like a full-on like face reaction to my fucking d-
Oh, look at all the cool stuff and game rewards. How- what- what's- why is there no uh stream?
I don't understand. Oh, they usually have like a big like 25 advertisements before every one of these?
I missed it?
What do you mean I missed it?
No, it says live December 10th. I didn't miss it. Hold on. I gotta tweet this.
I missed the stream.
That would be embarrassing.
It was yesterday.
Got a bunch of- got a bunch of community injured here. But what is today?
What is actually today?
Actually refresh though. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Why is this so- this doesn't make any sense. Why does it look like this?
Oh, okay. There we go.
Okay. So hold on. I don't have to follow the- refresh the page.
Is it going? It's not even going. What's this?
Jeff Q&A.
Riot Games. Chat Choice Awards.
Game Awards. No, where's the actual live stream?
Why didn't you shave? I don't know.
Click that one. Can I stream that one? What's the rules here?
What are the actual rules?
This- um, this is why I only want to get here 15 minutes early. My pre-show- you think I have anything for my pre-show?
No, I played like three games that have been nominated this year and one of them I played for like an hour.
I- you don't want to be here for this- for me. I have a terrible sense of what is cool this year.
I took like three months off.
I played like 12 video games. Spit just flew out of my mouth. That's how you can tell I'm really rabid tonight.
Is it- what can I watch? Sing the pre-show song.
Hot Chocke? Oh, man, it's hot. No, it's not. Oh, look at my gross mouth spots.
Oh! Can you see this?
How am I drinking this coffee?
Am I going like-
Look at this like a bunch of like mouth like spots and like water.
There's like a lipstick on here.
I think there's actually lipstick on this cup.
Can you see the like lipstick mark?
Ew, ew, ew. Evil lighting too?
I didn't show any nudes on stream. All right, everybody relax. What time is it? 324? When does this thing start?
Okay, so
Let's think- let's think about you're handsome.
Not anymore!
Yeah, but on- I don't know. What's my good side?
Let's find this out. I don't know who gives a shit about the game awards.
Let's talk about my- me and how like got my appearance. What's my good side, you guys think? I don't. Okay, so this is me.
What's like the good side?
Both? What's worse?
I think this side's probably the bad side. If I would take a- if it would be me in the mirror.
All right, I gotta talk about like video games. This is getting weird.
This is like I'm like a weird guy that's like obsessed with himself.
You know, one of my good sides over here, but I don't know about this one. I think this looks okay this way too.
Like it's the fucking game awards tonight. You know, what did I play this year? I'm gonna do a pre-show.
What did I play this year? I came out this year.
Put your head on the statue. This is- I don't know, this feels weird. I played Doodle God. Hades, yes.
All right, if I want Hades to win something, I really do.
Hades came out this year.
Um, Bug Snacks? What else did I play?
Watch Dogs? Watch Dogs is not gonna get nominated for anything.
And if it does, like if Watch Dogs is on there for game of the year, I don't even look, I don't even care.
Half-Life Alex, but that didn't come out this year, did it?
Did Half-Life Alex come out in 2020? Half-Life Alex came out in 2020?
Oh shit. All right. Why is that- that was probably the game of the year.
Is that not on game of the year?
I would say that would be game of the year for me. It's not even on the list.
Why the fuck would that not be on the list?
How is that?
It's a snub.
Well, because nobody has VR.
It's because like only like 2% of people have VR. That's kind of weird.
But it's like it's probably the best game that I played this year.
So why wouldn't it, you know, are we judging it based on the merits of how good a game was or judging it based on
how many like Twitter followers the social media account has?
Like how many Twitter followers does like the fucking Ubisoft Watch Dogs account have?
How many active Reddit users are inside? Yeah.
I mean how many active Reddit users are current- are like voting?
But that doesn't make any sense because Val- Half-Life Alex is like a huge Reddit game. What are you talking about?
Everybody loves that game.
If that's the barometer, it's not right then. It's not- it's not accurate. It's a popularity contest germo.
The Valve is wicked popular up the stream. What time is it? 328. What else we got?
All right, so Half-Life Alex is probably my game of the year.
I would say.
Well, let me get like a couple more clanks in there so you can like really tell I'm sitting down having a coffee with you.
I think um, no, that's ASMR shit. I'm not gonna do that. I'll leave that be.
Hades was good too. I'd say Hades. No villain hair. No, I did. I put- which is my hair recently has been really like wavy.
I tried.
I put a bunch of water in it and like I've really like tried to like get it to go back, but it's too short.
So it won't stay back. It just won't- it won't stay back. It's gonna be like this.
Wait, it hasn't even started. The game awards haven't even started yet. I got time.
I just go throw water in my hair and get ready.
I gotta get ready for the game awards, man. I gotta like slick my hair back.
Do it on camera? I don't have a sink in here. Where do you see a sink?
Dunk your head in water and come back here like-
All right, I'm ready. I'm gonna look like sweaty. Why am I sweaty? No.
That's just the light. I got a little light in here now so you can like illuminate my face for you.
You're in the bathroom right now.
You're always like this. I know. Look, I'm a pretty sweaty guy, okay? Look. You got like sweaty lips.
I've got- I've got like sweaty teeth.
See? There's like sweat coming off my teeth.
Lip gloss. It's fucking chapstick. Sit down.
Relax.
You got Gary Busey teeth.
Hey, they're big and they can chew through food very quickly.
Oh, you know, you're at the burger place. Oh, man. I really can't like bite into this burger. It's like it's too big.
It's too much. I go like-
And when I bite into this shit,
meat and cheese goes out the sides and like splats on the walls and stuff and everyone's like looks over they go
Holy shit, that dude- that dude's teeth must be on point. They look over and I go yeah, they are.
You ever need me to bite through metal?
I'll do it. Excuse me, sir. Sir, I noticed that you bit into that hamburger really well.
Could you- could you break this copper for me?
That'll be $40. Fucking show gonna start already. Is it live?
Hold on. Wait. I didn't even put my head in the water.
It did. It's live. It's live. It's live. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is it actually live or are you lying to me?
Offline.
Liars. Liars. All of you. Press the refresh on the page. Hold on. I do have to- I already did.
You missed the show.
Okay, I'm refreshing the whole page. Oh, it's Pepe Laugh. Pepe Laugh. Pepe Laugh. We got him. Pepe Laugh. Pepe Laugh.
I'm laughing at this guy because he thinks he had to refresh the bucket page. I got it. I understand.
But now I have to do this again.
You have really slow internet.
It's 3 32 right now.
Should be on.
No? Oh, wait.
Oh.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, it's an ad. Wait, it's an ad. Okay. It's an ad.
Okay. All right. All right. By the way, 5G. That's never gonna roll out everywhere.
You'll be able to do 5G in like five places. That's why it's called 5G.
It's gonna be in like five major cities in like a 200 yard radius.
The following program may contain content that some viewers might find offensive.
Can you hear it? Are we good? Are we live?
Good men here coming to you live from Los Angeles, California. From Las Vegas.
Damn it. Damn it. And please allow me to be the first to thank you for setting down cyberpunk for a few hours.
As you can probably tell the game awards are going to look a little different this year.
Our venue may be smaller, but the show itself is as gigantic as ever.
The awards and world premieres won't be changing except
I guess the only people clapping will be me and probably a few crew members. Oh, right.
We'll bring us musical performances from London and Tokyo and one positive of tonight's mostly digital gathering is
we'll get to see more faces in the talented teams behind this year's outstanding games. What the hell is going on here?
As for us here in the pre-show, we'll be setting the remaining minutes before the game awards kick off with brand new trailers,
mercifully brief integrated marketing, and Lin will be performing a song from Persona 5 Strikers.
Oh, you guys be excited about that one. The big reason we're all here.
Awards. Our first category tonight is best score in music. It's just going right into it.
It's a particularly strong contest this year with five standout nominees that could on their own
represent the best of the generation. What's good music? Here are the nominees for best score in music. Best score in music. Doom Eternal.
Nice, Doom. Play Doom OST. Final Fantasy 7 Remake. No, I don't know. Hades. Yeah.
Ori and the Will of the Wisps. I didn't play it, but sure. And the Last of Us Part 2. Didn't play it. I don't know. And the winner is?
It's gonna be Doom Eternal or Hades. It's gonna be Hades.
Final Fantasy 7 Remake. We already know those songs. We already heard them 20 years ago.
All right. The music's good. It's good. It's good.
All right. Now the music's good, but we already heard those songs.
As I said earlier, you'll be seeing a variety of different world premieres throughout this pre-show.
Oh, give us some world premieres. Strangely enough, we've decided to show you our most important one first. Here it is.
What?
Oh, the digits go. Elden Ring. Come on. Welcome to the Devolver Digital 2021 Game of the Year Award.
Sponsored by Devolver Digital. And now, your host, Devolver Digital CEO,
Nita Struthers.
Oh, guys.
Okay, shush it. So yeah, tonight we are here to celebrate this year's most memorable video games.
Let's not overlook the unrelenting hype, not for this,
but for next year's as yet to be released games coming at you hot from what many believe to be this industry's most ridiculously
overrated publisher. While most of these games are months away from release, we at Devolver Digital are strong
proponents of awards for awards sake. And with that, the nominees for the Devolver Digital 2021
Game of the Year are Shadow Warrior 3 by Flying Wild Hog. It's from, yeah. Oliya by Skeleton Crew Studio.
Card Shark by Neria.
Family, like a baby.
By Dane.
Devs, Baby Devs.
Lupiro by Developer Four Quarters.
Kind of wish the baby like burped cute through the camera.
Well, just now, really. Let's have a look at Lupiro.
Your world has been cast into a dark spiral.
Place enchanted cards along a heroiney path.
What am I supposed to say?
Just build cathedrals and remember your world.
Scrounges for weapons, armor, and mystical items to level up your hero.
Expand your camp, customize your card deck, and uncover secrets.
Feast the lich, break the spiral, and see the world.
Lupiro, coming in 2021.
Hey, here's every single one of these streams you're gonna watch on Twitch.
Thank you. See you next year.
Whatever
Every year the Game Awards do our best to highlight new games from all sorts of developers from AAA big shots like Devolver
to smaller independent studios.
Our next world premiere is the debut of a new game from Awaseb, a young studio started in New Caledonia. Enjoy.
Here we go. Another world premiere. Let's go back to back world premieres. Back to back jacks.
Back to back jacks.
Crap.
Oh shit.
You can fall from really high places. What the hell?
You can be a coconut.
Oh, that's all right. Let's go to coal. How do you get out though?
This next award category is for one of gaming's most popular genres, action adventure.
The breadth of what is considered an action adventure game also leads to this regularly being one of our most competitive categories.
Incidentally for the past three years the game award winner for action adventure has gone on to win game of the year.
This is a big one.
Here are the nominees for best action adventure game.
Assassin's Creed Valhalla
Ghost of Tsushima. I haven't seen one second. Marvel's Spider-Man Miles Morales. I haven't played it.
I want to play. Hori and the will of the wisp. Should I be doing this? Star Wars Jedi fall in order.
I didn't play any of these. And the last of us part two. Holy shit. I haven't played a single one of these the entire year.
What kind of comments are you gonna get from me? The last of us part two.
Wow, we won. This is awesome.
We want to thank the game awards for choosing us as the best action adventure game. Oh the best of known beforehand.
On behalf of the directors, which is myself, Anthony Newman and Neil Druckmann.
They definitely knew before it. We want to thank the entire team at Naughty Dog who poured their heart and souls into this game.
It's really their talent. Oh, they probably all did one. It merges you in that world and really makes you feel like you're on this journey with Ellie.
We want to thank Evan Wells our president.
Also everyone at Sony and our partners for really helping us put this game together and get out the door.
And especially to our fans who
supported us and
really helped make this game something special. You guys make it worth it. So thank you again.
So you have to assume that every single one of these people has to do a we won.
Oh, I won. We have many more awards coming up in the pre-show.
But first, so you can understand like oh we won. Yeah, but you don't know you won.
But you're like pretending you won in case you do.
Interesting. Hello everyone. I'm Connie. I'm the CEO and creative director of my games company called Yo Mai in beautiful Berlin.
It was such an honor to be nominated for the games
for impact category at last year's The Game Awards. It's held due to the Golden Globes. Our most important project today
called
Sea of Solitude.
I'm very happy to announce that Sea of Solitude will be coming to Nintendo Switch this winter.
But it's not just a port.
We fully reworked the entire game. We're calling it The Director's Cup because it's a version that truly
represents what I wanted to convey about the topics that are especially
important in today's difficult times. We can't wait to share it with you until then. What game is this?
Enjoy The Game Awards. The Game Awards aren't even on yet. See you soon. The 17 minutes till The Game Awards start. What?
This is the pre-show.
You missed it. No, I didn't this is I'm way too early monsters. You know them too, don't you?
What the fuck? They're waiting for us to capsize.
To drown.
We'll face them.
DMCA?
Oh shit. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Oh, who cares?
We should just safe harbor together.
I ain't mutant.
You want to shut me down? Like fuck you. I'm not mutant. You told me I could frame this everybody on earth that was here doing this.
No, I ain't mutant shit. All right.
You're gonna get banned. I'm not gonna get banned. They said we could do this.
I ain't mutant shit.
Telling you. What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to do?
The algorithm doesn't care.
Let me show you how I fucking deal with algorithms.
Let me show you how I fucking deal with the algorithm.
We've had some great world premieres already, but we recognize there may be some fans of elegant Shadowgaze puzzle games who feel left out.
Oh, let me show you how I deal with algorithms. It's called select all delete button.
We've got something for you too.
Oh, then what are you gonna do? Come at me?
Here is shady part of me.
You're just a little bit of code motherfucker. You're just a little bit of code.
There once was a girl who was trapped in the dark with naught but her shadow for company. A journey to escape
She did embark
And her shadow followed distrustfully
Girl found no hope in life
I'm gonna get like shut off like mystery. Not so tough now. Are you jeremy?
We break free i'm gonna get shut off midstream and you're gonna get us apology tweet to like twitch. Hey, I mean, i'm sorry
I was just like kidding around. Oh, like I really want to respect everything
You're gonna get like a a follow-up like backtrack tweet if you're just joining us now welcome
We're in the middle of what has turned out to be a jam
Do a cry tweet awards. We've just premiered two trailers back to back
And now we'd like to take a moment to announce the winners of three awards
First is best family game a category that did a lot of heavy lifting this year
Super mario, uh, no, not that's not ever like this year and chuck e cheese went bang
Family games were always there. The nominees are did you say?
animal crossing new horizons
Crash that was kind of low. It's about time. Chuck e cheese is like here ultimate knockout
Mario kart live home circuit. No, that was bad dungeons and
Paper mario the origami king wait and the winner is when do these come out?
animal crossing new horizons
Next paper mario came out like 10 years ago awarding best community support
This category debuted last year and it represents the game no bugs snacks. Yeah
Demonstrated through communication and respect here are the nominees the best community support apex legends
Destiny 2 okay fall guys ultimate knockout. Okay
Fortnight, okay
No man's sky, okay
And valorant all of these and the winner you probably top reddit comment of all time is like fuck this game. They're ruining it
We get to acknowledge the winner for best debut game
This of course goes to nominees that represent an independent studios first ever release
It's an award for fresh perspectives new ideas and distinguished bravery. Oh guys
The nominees for best debut game are best debut game carrion is that's good though. That was good
That's cool
Raji an ancient epic and play it and
Roki I didn't play fast before it was fun. It's gonna be fast before you're right or carrion
All right. All right. I'm on board with that one
That one does it for me. That's five trophies down and the game awards haven't even officially started yet
I'm gonna I agree with that countdown timer says we are minutes away
So i'd like to take a moment to let you know about a few ways you can interact with tonight's big show
All night long fans will be predicting the winners on twitch using a special voting extension powered by verizon
5g built for gamers
Lock in your picks throughout the night to see if you guess the right winner and whether you're watching on our official channel
Or from one of the music this is a mirror
Megadrops will be activated for fortnight
Over the last few days fans have visited our at the game awards tiktok channel and I think it's so loud
Which the last of us part two team they support team abby or team ellie the votes are in and team ellie won the vote
Thanks for your vote and be sure to follow us on tiktok if you haven't yet to catch
What did what who won an award it was a tick tock only award to see what their pick is for 2020
Is game of the year and the winner?
Is go to tsushima as for the game award for game of the year
We obviously won't learn that until the end of the night for now
We're about to take a super short break but coming up on the other side
We've got winners for each of our esports awards a persona five strikers performance and of course
more world premieres sure
It was a reddit game. Hey, thanks sydney
Listen, it's hard for me to believe that it was 27 years ago
That my brother robin and I watched players venture into the ages of mist for the first time ages of mist
Anyway, today I am so excited to start a new chapter of mist
With the release of an entirely reconstructed vr version that's available now on the oculus quest platform
We've got something special for anyone who purchases mist they'll unlock a mist themed oculus home environment
I'm so thrilled for you to experience mist in vr and thank you so much for your continued love and support
I ain't gonna be playing that one
Have you noticed that all vr games for some reason I don't know what I don't know what this is
It seems like all vr games decide that aesthetically they're going to use like the big mickey mouse glove hands
for like your hands
I feel like this in a lot of games
Is that intent is that like a decision for is it easier to see or what why why is that?
To the game awards pre-show for the first time you were polygons. Okay, so there's a reason okay
Right here in the pre-show and i'm not sure there could be anything better to jump off with performing
Here comes the dmca
Okay, every streamer during this portion game awards, yeah
No, no, no, no, I can't we can't we can't do it guys. We can't we can't I we can't
We can't do it. We can't do it. We can't do it
Just how about you you open up on your on your own stream open up your own and we'll listen
Like just get to my i'm at 17 minutes and 41 seconds get there and we'll listen to it together
Oh, well, I can't put it on
Oh look, this is pretty catchy
Oh, and here comes the drop
we go
And then we sing
Everyone and blah
I'm fucking whatever. I don't care. We're listening to it
Look look we'll fuck with the algorithm ready
Fuck with the algorithm
Audio jungle
Oh god, just select that line of code and delete it
Oh
Audio jungle good i'm safe. All right. I'm like kind of scared. Oh, this is my favorite part. I love this part coming up here
Oh, that's my favorite part. I love it, especially when they do that. This the breakdown is the best
Here it comes again. Oh, yeah
When they die, I love this song so much
and cool
See right now. I wish there was a map of like every stream being dmca'd right now. We're dropping like fucking flies guys
The stream is gonna get like 40 000 viewers because it's like oh dude. Did you hear like this guy's stream?
Just fucking died. He was watching r e o and they fucking killed him
And i'd be like, uh announced an update to 2010's near replicant the prequel to near automata
The actual title of this remake was of course another sick joke from director yoko taro
But the game awards pre-show
I'm moving around a lot today tonight. I am both happy and unafraid to introduce the gameplay debut for near replicant version
1.22
4 487 139 dot near really
Okay, i've never played one second of any near game
I just pretend to be uh cool about it and think it's awesome because people like it
So I pretend to like it
Near let's go
I'm excited because you're excited. You know what I mean?
That's like cool. Yeah, cool. Yeah
DMCA
I'll fix it
I'll fix it. No, I won't I won't fix it
I won't fix it
It's been a special night already and now I get to share with you another game awards first the world premiere
Of a new band you heard me correctly. They're playing their debut single follow unfollow. Please welcome for the first time ever
Ofk
I
Hope it's good
They have to be fucking with us now. You know what I mean?
Who the fuck is this?
Wait, this is a new band
DMC i'm not gonna get dmca. This is a new band. This is like a new world premiere of a new band
But wait, are they signed yet?
They're not signed yet. I'm okay
Should I wait hold on i'm not gonna do
Okay, I i've muted it for a few seconds
This is the end boys and girls this is where we go
It's been a really good run on twitch
But like it's not it's gonna be hard for me to it's gonna be hard for me to fight
Um, like seven different radio labels in court, you know what I mean? Like i'm they're coming after me
I'm just gonna get up like it during the courtroom. They'll be like give me give me like some statements to make mr
Albertson everything. Yeah, of course I do entertain and inspire of the 30 different game awards categories
The judge just throws the case out. He's like
But I may need to call in some help to get through them all we'll see
Here we go for best esports game. The nominees are
Call of duty modern warfare. Why?
counter-strike global offensive
fortnight league of legends and valorant, I don't know and the winner is
league of legends just wins every fucking year
best esports coach the nominees are best esports coach, okay
grab rambo
zepha and
zonic
And the winner is it's gotta be zonic. Come on. Yes
I love the name zonic the nominees are
Blast premiere spring 2020 european finals call of duty league championship 2020
Iem kato vc. What about a chin like this?
league of legends world championship
Would that make me more handsome overwatch league grand finals 2020 and the winner is
league of legends world championship 2020
For best we all read the nominees are
dash
golden boy
machine
And the winner is
shocks to esports team the nominees are
dallas empire all righty these damwon gaming
g2 esports san francisco shock and team secret like team secret and the winner is
g2 esports
Congratulations to all of the winners
And now to announce the winner of the best esports athlete
Here's the host of espn's first take and the new espn plus show steven a's world
steven a smith wait didn't espn talk about how like
Esports wasn't real or something. Did they just bring steven a smith to the game awards in an effort to legitimize esports as something equal to
Athletic sports. Oh, I think he's he's
That's not the point
League in the nation shut down
Esports just kept on going
With that being said i'll say this much
All of the esports athletes nominated are without question more determined
That was a pretty good intro and definitely win more than anybody on the dallas cowboys
now for our nominees
crimp six
show maker
canyon
shot z
Zai wu. I turned it up and the winner is
Showmaker
Thank you
You can definitely sense it right the game awards are about to begin
steven a smith just handed out the final award of the pre-show
And now it's time for one last premiere before the main show begins and it's got something probably went like we could all use a little more
Of dragons fighting dragons. They're never gonna take over. Here's sentry. You gotta fill the m.o.b
Oh world premiere shit, what is this?
Oh shit, this actually looks pretty good. What is this?
Oh shit, I'm actually into this. What is this?
Oh fucking shit. It's like
Is this painted dragoon?
multiplayer dragon fights
Sentry age of ashes. All right that whatever man. That looks pretty fun
Is it a mobile game? No, it's not
It's on steam. What are you talking about?
I mean god that looked I i'm not i'm not gonna look kind of cool
It means i'm about to sign off and hand it over to jeff
Look forward to performances from eddie better and the london phil harmonic orchestra
We'll be playing the traditional game of the year medley as well as a special surprise. I love surprises
There will be world premieres from fall guys dragon age super smash brothers ultimate
Oh, we're gonna get a new character surprises little surprises, of course. That's my prediction. I'm signing it right now
Travis touchdown, that's my prediction. I'm just saying game awards that game's coming out now soon
I think it's gonna be traps touchdown signed it
It's already a costume. Well
Never mind. It's gonna be a fortnight character, but no, it's not gonna be a fortnight character
Here hello everyone the world and welcome to the game awards sneakers are awesome 20
We are so happy to have you joining us tonight
You know this year of course will be a little bit different
Uh, it's been a tough year for everyone. I know and normally with the holiday season
We'd all be gathering with our friends and family and I know that can't happen for all of us
But tonight we can gather here
And connect around games something that we all love games connect us and i'm here in los angeles and whether you're watching
Live right now in china early in the morning in europe america my native canada wherever you are
Uh, even in india this year all over the globe. We are coming together tonight to celebrate our love of video games
Uh now to keep everyone safe tonight nominees are going to be joining us live via zoom from all over the world
You can see them there. Hi everybody. They're all joining us from their homes and their studios
China europe los angeles
We're gonna be joined also by some very special guests kiano reeves gal gadot bree larson tom holland christopher
Nolan john david washington christopher nolan is here chef
Reggie and more and we also have a very special performance by eddie better here pearl jam
Uh, he will be in seattle and the london philharmonic orchestra did they just like contact a bunch of hollywood agencies and just say hey
Who the fuck's available on thursday amazing show and as always we've got bring them in we've got first looks
We've got new game announcements
All of the things that make the game awards special will be here
And what i'd love about this show is that the entire industry comes together tonight to celebrate games
Everyone is here or at least I thought everyone was here
Wait a minute. It does sound like we're still expecting someone else to arrive
Reggie
Okay, who's gonna be it's gonna be it's who's not in the game
captain crunch, uh scrooge mcduck
travis touchdown
Dr. Robotnik
Steve carell from the office
It's really it's sephiroth
Sephiroth is it now?
Sephiroth
And remember best music
Because
There's some final fantasy fans
Whose their house their house just fell over because they fell over so far hard in their chair
like their house fell backwards and landed on site because they fucking flew to the back of their room and went
boom
I just pulled my headphones out
Well, I mean if you're that's cool if you're excited about that, I mean everyone's been
Do you guys remember?
when people used to make
Fake bullshit never gonna happen smash things
Characterists and it was hilarious because there's no fucking way sephiroth
Mega man pac-man and like solid snake were gonna be in this it was a joke. It was like, holy shit
What a hilarious joke you just made
Back in like 2008
The people that made those smash character lists that were like i'm telling you guys no, this is gonna happen
That's like the guys that bought btc when it was like fucking four dollars
And everyone's like dude, what are you talking about? You're crazy
Just wait to see no way man. You're out of your mind
All right, i'm gonna do it I don't care if you flip it
The fun is just getting started but of course this show is also about
Indicated activists
I am honored to present the award for best performance
Among the nominees is an inclusive group of talented actors filling vastly different roles in games that are nothing alike
however
These artists are nominated. I could do any song by the way clear dedication to their craft
And an extraordinary ability to bring humanity and empathy to their roles here are the nominees for best performance
Oh, so all right. All right. All right. Okay
Deserves to suffer
Stupid boy, you shall never reach the surface. Yeah. Yep
Okay
Let's do this
and the game award goes to
Laura bailey as abby the last of us weren't
Oh, wow, um
wow, uh, I
I was such a fan of the original
Last of us and of troy and ashley's performances within it. Um, I fell in love with joe linelli
so it is
No surprise to me that
abby's role within this story has been met with such
Uh passionate responses
but um
To have been able to play but she's incredibly talented like she just did such a fantastically challenging character
Who through her story enables the player to find?
Forgiveness and empathy is something that i'll be eternally grateful for
um
Oh, man, I told the team on the day that I finished filming
that what I wanted more than anything was for my performance to
To give a performance that honored the impact that the original game had on me, so
This award means so much. Um, thank you to neil and tally and the entire team for giving me the opportunity and for
All of the support and the guidance along the way
to patrick and ian and grace for
uh
Everything you did the the story and abby would not have been as impactful without you by my side
Um that was a that was a I that would hear that ding that wasn't me that was on the screen that was like
And every single time I work with you I come away better for it
Thank you. I've been doing that. You know to me if I if I was like really good friend
Somebody that was like fucking best voice actor award best voice actors
Um
Other than um, I think you should probably be giving the speech right now. I think you're amazing and
Your your strength and your power and your vulnerability and your performance left me speechless
Um, I love you marry me
to my husband travis who spent countless hours just listening to me come to terms with what this uh
game's journey has been
um
And to the fans
Obviously to everyone who voted. Thank you for your support and for your love and for your passion and for
Allowing yourself to go on this journey with abby and with me
Thank you. I love you. She's insanely talented. She's good at everything. I messages coming in she can do anything
She's very good to have everyone here celebrating an amazing year for games
All right
We are streaming on every platform tonight including twitch where we have drops for among us and fortnight who both have world premieres
Coming up later in the show and throughout the night. We will also be interactive on twitch
Who you think will win using a twitch extension first up best ongoing game?
So go and vote now lock in your prediction. I didn't um, I didn't turn that on going on
It's been one of those special years that sees the launch
Don't have that here next-gen consoles with that brings a whole new generation of games tonight. We are on where's my drop?
I don't care. I'm not gonna what do I team of veterans reveal?
The very first details about their ambitious and exciting new project right here at the game awards. All right, let's go. Let's see
Pretty much since the day I started there has been a really clear turn it on
I can't I think the thing that that makes it different from a lot of first-person games is it's not just about shooting
Eco sci-fi is a term that we use future fiction, but from an ecological focus
There's been this ecological disaster these corporations came in and they developed new technology and on the surface everything's
Everything's pretty great. We're still early in development, but we're really excited with where things are going
We wanted to share a cinematic piece that helps set the tone for our world
What is it iberpunk
You don't have twitch integration
No, I I am here it's me
I just I turned I turned my fucking big screen tv on and you guys all pulled into the driveway
And you're just looking through the screen. I have a microphone that has speakers outside the windows
Like i'm about to do twitch integration and whatever you're just in my driveway
The corporations gave us solutions
Yeah, yeah, you want drop?
I like lift up the window and i'm like, hey here comes a drop
It's like like an old printer that I don't use anymore and i'm just like
Boom
There's no ink in there by the way, you're gonna have to get that yourself what they're hiding your fly
The flight of the fly
So i'm gonna stop talking i'm like probably pissing people off find the answers you were looking for
Agent dark is the beginning
Oh
Bro, shit. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on
Oh, that's a big deal
That's a big that's a kind of a big deal
It's perfect. That's okay. There you go. Perfect dark from the initiative xbox very exciting to have that announced
All right
Well, we're gonna go right into another game announcement for the first time right here at the game awards. Check it out
Okay, that's i'm actually kind of excited for that if they do it right
Oh
roll rock, okay
This is left for dead three
Yeah
But not left for dead
Well, I hope it's good
Yeah, so they made uh
Yeah, so this is the spiritual left for dead successor, right?
It actually is called something like that too. Isn't it like dead for
Us or something. It's called something like that
So they made evolve
Right and then evolve was like almost like a catastrophic failure
So they're like, you know what?
Valve is not releasing left for dead three
This is pretty exciting for all us left for dead fans
Of course, uh, you guys are known for all the amazing work left for dead and now you're let him go for it
This i'm building on the legacy with this new zombie co-op shooter. Uh, what's new? What can you tell us about it chris?
Well, we wanted to do more and bigger right we wanted to have more playable characters
Uh more missions more story
But we also wanted to have a bigger variety of zombies to fight, right?
But also we wanted to go bigger. So now we've got these 20 foot tall
Uh zombie monstrosities that are definitely gonna take
You know the help of your friends in order to defeat more more more great to have this game more more more sounds like
I think you've prepared a little surprise for everyone watching, right?
The terminators in the game movies are cool, but uh gameplay is king, right?
So let's see some of that i'll can terminators in the game. Here we go
Here's the gameplay reveal of back for blood. Okay. Never mind. Never mind. Okay. All right. Okay. I stand correct
Is the safe house safer room, right?
I'm actually excited for this because like who's who doesn't want to do this again
Hey
Just go kill some
Na aim who doesn't want a a next generation left dead like everybody does
Yeah, how many hours just melted away with me and my friends playing left for dead left for dead, too
But you don't have friends anymore yo
Excited what are you talking?
It's fake gameplay. Of course it is
It has to be non-stop special infected attacks. Otherwise, you're not going to buy it
You have to be puckering your lips and your ass needs to be stuffed into the bottom of your chair
This entire gameplay reveal you're not going to pre-order it. You're not going to buy it
He's like he just modeled himself
You get you get kicked for that the vote kick thing would just pop up right after that. They didn't show that part
There you go back for blood june next year
Alpha next week crazy. All right, very exciting. Well tonight we're celebrating games and we've got awesome discounts
On many of tonight's nominees with the game awards sale across xbox playstation Nintendo e-shop epic game store and
We also have the game awards festival a chance to play upcoming games like little nightmares, too
The playstation 5 the nintendo e-shop instantly with g-force now
So make sure to check that out. You can stream on any device with no downloads on g-force now
Well, we also have a lot of great stuff coming up. We'll have performances from the london philharmonic orchestra
Cool eddie vetter, but right now two years ago. We announced at the game awards scavengers from midwinter entertainment
Everyone has been wondering when they'll get to play it shoes on that. Let's hear from
Oh
It's like what's happening. Oh, no, I do have a really exciting update for you
But first I just want to thank the many thousands of players who've been testing the game with us over the past year
Your feedback and your support means the world to us. We couldn't do this without you
Today where's the swedish chef big news to share
Is it a swedish chef cooking game? That would be incredible. I would pre-order that right now
That's a good link
Get you back alive. This is where the real fun starts. I've been preparing this for years
Now I need is in place
Your test begins
now scavengers
Coming 2021
Closed beta starts now
All right. So there you have it the pc closed beta for scavengers starts right now
If you're part of our community, you can play with your existing steam key
But we're also opening up 50 000 slots for new players
So go to play scavengers.com sign up for free and we'll see you in the game now what?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
No, this is held in no time
Is it no
So this actually would be a pretty interesting experiment that some of you guys can keep track of during the course of the events tonight
Ads versus awards that have been shown
I know they're all ads, right? But like i'm curious
This is okay. You know when you go you get a magazine
Any major magazine publication that you get at like the grocery store or like the gas station and you just you really it's half
It's more than half ads like for like colognes and shit
Game awards are seriously just like a fucking gas station magazine
stardew valley
Is a game
Cuphead also a game
And these are cool overcooked to these indie kind of showcase
These are all really good
i'm more excited about this than
These are all very good. This look at this. Look at this list
You thought you could get rid of me, but you can't
His instagram and the game awards have teamed up for six new arfx
You can share two instagram reels. I played with them yesterday at home and posted to the game awards profile. Check it out
You can transport yourself to final fantasy seven's train station transform into the doom slayer
Don the mask of the ghost of tsushima sneak through the last of us or even become zagreus from hades
To create your own just head over to the game awards on instagram
Click on the effect icon and share to instagram reels instagram
I'll be back later to show off some of your beautiful creations
I should I just take a picture of me with just the default dog filter
And be like oh game awards like
like
dog nose and ears
Don't even use the filters
I have a punk cyberpunk went out of my button. I can't why can't I turn my mic? What's going on with my streaming thing?
There you go forza cross cyberpunk and later kyanu reeve johnny silverhand himself will be joining us to present the best direction awards
So stay tuned for that. Uh, but welcome back now coming up next
We're gonna present the best ongoing game award and the twitch community thinks fortnight is gonna win that with 47 percent of the votes
Well, let's find out the twitch community is right
We're about you guys. What do you guys think ongoing game which recognizes five outstanding titles that continue to deliver for fans
Here are the nominees. All right, it's important. Is it is just how many updates there are ongoing game?
How many patches they how many like localizations they do in one week or something? What is it go?
Oh duty what this is just every multiplayer again, that's currently like the servers active right now
And here are the nominees for currently active servers for multiplayer games
Who's gonna win? All right. Well now it's time to reveal the winner. The nominees are joining us here. Hi guys. All right, here we go
I love them the game award goes to no man's sky
Hi
He was just like it's not gonna be us they're gonna talk a bunch of shit about us again
Shit, thank you so much
We're really lucky, you know, we get to come to work every day and make games
No man's sky is such a wonderful game to work on, you know, didn't they it's not always easy though
Uh, so moments like this
They mean a lot, you know, this means a lot to me means a lot to the team
Thank you so much. Thank you to the community for continuing to support us
Thanks
Okay, didn't they do a ton of work to try to get that game to a good place?
Now every year it did right it was like they tried they were like we're gonna try to fix this and make it good and
And they did right? But they're always a few you're not deserve them
But I think don't give it a fortnight. Check out this world premiere. No, they they put a lot of work into it from what i've heard so
They were under a lot of pressure for a long time too, you know, they were a small team that's good on them
All right good on them deserved
What the fuck this is black irons to transport ship karon you are cleared for landing
Callisto protocol
Yeah, I thought it was uh
I thought it was dead space as well. Look kind of dead spacey with the thing in the back and everything
I'm feeling some dead space vibes and there's little wonder why you know him from his work on dead space and call of duty
The ceo of striking distance studios glenn scofield. Hey glenn
Hey, thanks jeff
Well, the crystal protocol has been in development for uh over a year and a half with a team of well over 100 people on it
It's a single-player third-person story-driven survival horror game set in the year
2320 on jupiter's moon of callisto
Our goal is to make the single most scariest game for pc and consoles
And we're so excited to be able to show it here tonight. Yeah, that's awesome. Thank you very much glenn
We're looking forward to hearing more about that. I would be next year
All right announced back in july warhammer 40k dark tide is a four player co-op game from fat shark
The developers behind warhammer vermin tide 2 well tonight. They're sharing a first look at the gameplay check this out warhammer dark tide
Okay, i'm excited for this. I love warhammer. I played as the tau
I was a huge fan of the tau
We ain't ever gonna see them ever again
So it seems
all right, this is
Is it weird that i'm kind of more excited for this than I am about?
the left for dead one
Kind of looks like to me this kind of looks better
Is that weird for me to say now?
It's time to recognize some other winners in the category of best art direction the nominees are
final fantasy 7 remake ghost of shima
hades
Ori and the will of the wisps and the last of us part two
I feel like it's been the same five game award goes to am I losing my mind? I feel like i'm rewinding shima
Congratulations, the sucker punch. I rewind i'm like rewinding for best action game. The nominees are
doom eternal doom eternal hades half-life alex
That one that one and streets of rage for it better be that one
And the winner is don't tell me what it is hades which one was relation super giant
It's hades. I heard it. That's all right. That's okay. That's good. Good dreams half-life alex marvels iron man vr
star wars squadrons and the walking dead saints and sinners iron man vr when the game award goes to then
Half-life alex congratulations to valve
For best sports racing game those nominees are guaranteed to win that five f1 2020
fifa 21
nba 2k 21 and tony hawks pro skater one and two half-life alex game award goes to
Is in a category with like hawks pro skater one and two watch out look down there are bugs at your feet
Hey, look at your hands anticipated game voted on on twitter this year. The nominees are
Elden ring there. I said it god of war sequel
Halo infinite horizon forbidden west
Resident evil village and the legend of zelda breath of the wild sequel. It's gonna be your most anticipated game
I'll be honest. It has to be god of war
Elden rain. Okay. All right more people. Congratulations to front. I thought it was gonna be god of war
All right
It was big this next game comes from the creators of gone home in tacoma the fullbright company and anapurna interactive present one part road
Trip one part mystery with two familiar voices. Check it out
Oh
My name is test divine and the world is passing me by
I guess as I get a little older i'm starting to feel how things
change
They decline and go away
That's how it was with my grandma same joke andy
I just I hear it and I feel like it fits some places we found
Hints of something she never told us about a man who wasn't my grandfather for a second
I thought she was driving the car and I was like what the fuck is happening some sort of lost fortune
We can't ask her about these things anymore. So
We have to go looking for the answers ourselves
My mom and I are searching
I don't know what we'll find but
Whatever it is
I know we'll find it
together
Open roads
All right that I didn't get very much info there. It was just we're in a car and you had a book
Didn't get very much. But okay, we'll see again this year
We're excited to share some stories about people around the world who are making a positive impact on the gaming community
These are our global gaming citizens in partnership with facebook gaming
Our first honoree tonight is latin x in gaming check out this important story
It's worry. We somebody said wario. Where are you serious?
When I was starting are you aware of games industry as a latin x better be
I felt quite invisible. It still feels like i'm the odd one out
I felt alone
I was often the only woman and the only latina woman in the room. I think about how hard it was for me
To get where I am today
To go through that anymore and welcome to latin x in gaming our content
Our voices latin x in gaming is a group of people that are dedicated to supporting
Other people of latin x descent in the gaming space the past three years
We've just grown from a really small group
into thousands
This was no longer just about game developers. This is about streamers and students and journalists and marketing and fans
Pave the way for people like me pave the way for people in our community
Just knowing that there's somebody out there doing what you want to do empowers you to to chase it
It's a really beautiful thing. I'm trying not to cry. I was this close
Okay
Hey everyone, my name is anna donlin
I am the executive producer of valorant and I cannot believe that it has been only half a year since we launched this game
Our valorant community has shown up in such a huge way
Helping us take this tac shooter from an idea to a home for tens of millions of players around the world
To celebrate this we've teamed up with the game awards to highlight one of the most vital pieces of our community
Honestly, the ones that got us started in the first place are valorant streamers
Together we ran a fan vote. I'm not one of the best emerging valorant streamer from our global community list
We'll announce the winner before the end of the show and then we'll all go raid their stream together
What if I just turned on like valorant right now valorant and i'll leave you just a taste of what we've all done together this year
I'm just like the potential of valorant. I love it
Guys i'm never gonna get nominated for an award ever
I would never get nominated for anything. I'm like a house flipper streamer. There's no house flipper category
Plus I would run on stage
I would I would go on stage with like a go-kart or something. They wouldn't want me to be there
I would like drive into the fucking podium with a go-kart
And get out in the clown makeup be like
No, they don't want they're not gonna they don't want me there i'm not gonna get on the invite list
Earlier today we tweeted out that there is a special event happening right now in pokemon go
Well now's the time to bring out your phones and start catching because we're officially on
A whooper watch and they are so whooper watch
We've partnered with our friends at pokemon go to keep an eye on the water fish pokemon and throughout the night
We'll let you know when large numbers of whooper will appear in the wild
We've also been told you could encounter a shiny whooper if you're lucky
So open up pokemon go and catch some whooper while you watch I didn't get a whooper
I got another charizard
I don't know. What the what is a whooper?
We're on whooper watch
Disco lcf the final cut at the end of the world is waiting
So get out there
Solve the murder with a unique skill system at your disposal
Of your own path across an award-winning open world
In this groundbreaking role-playing game
Welcome to reality
The base what lead the way if you could only find your gun
That's okay
With full voice acting for every single one of the city's beautiful people
Yes, i'm going to unplug the microphone, okay
And leave a bigger mark behind you in new quests. You're big boys. You can handle it
Okay
Fucking play this uh, is it looks like kind of cool. That's right
This looks like kind of fun
Enjoy the definitive edition of this hit rpg
Disco elysium and i'm not saying that i'm not look. I know we just watched a guy punch like
That kid in the face. I'm not like oh nice. He punched a kid in the face. Um, this is for me
That's not what i'm saying. I'm that's not i'm saying let's be clear by that
I'm just saying that it looked like it was kind of interesting the egg maybe
I would like want to check it out
That's not why
It's like a big thick book
Okay, it's too much story for you. Well, all right
Okay. Well, whatever
Welcome back to the game awards. That's so exciting disco elysium news. You may remember last year
They were I think the one the most awards out of any game last year at the game awards. So I did yeah
Well now we're gonna talk about bioware's dragon age franchise. It is known for its story and its characters
And right magic kingdom bioware wanted to dragon age magic kingdom preview of what to expect in the next game and where it will take us
Enjoy really face tyrants and would-be gods
Seen friends lose life and limb
But there's always someone bent on breaking the world
I omega low where
You knew people were gonna start to say it
hero ancient prophecy
The person's heart is going person. They'll never see coming. You don't do that and not be scared
You've got your back. I've got your back
box balls
Even the dread wolf
This is your story
This chat is now on whooper watch
I don't really follow dragon age at all. I don't really all right. We're back and i'm
I'm trapped in our set now. I don't know what's going on. All right
Next we'll have a look at an exciting new tactical squad. Those are fucking deadly lasers set in the endless universe
He knows that you don't new game announcement. He's like, yeah. Oh shit. Okay, i'm gonna have to like dive through that
It's closing in. Oh, I shouldn't have picked the deadly lasers for the set
Get off get off camera quick
help him
free him
Uh, sorry guys, I I picked up the magic item on the podium
Uh, they told me not to touch it, but I mean it was shiny and I had to see what it was
Is it another left for dead kind of game I don't think so
Is it not every co-op pve game is left for dead
It's called endless dungeon
On xbox series xbox one ps5 ps4 ps3 super nintendo sega genesis
That was a lot of consoles. All right, uh endless dungeons. Very cool
Our next world premiere comes from south korea crimson desert the new open world action adventure game from pearl abyss
This next gen game offers in-depth story driven single player content in an mmo setting what you're about to see includes
Actual gameplay footage. This is the beautiful and merciless world that actual gameplay footage
Is the new like made with real cheese?
On the fucking front of your cheese product the cheez-its and shit. I feel like that we're getting there organic
free range gameplay
Okay, I was gonna say this it kind of just looked like looked like a visit minnesota
Hey wyoming
It's like a tourism video
Wyoming we've got stuff here. Come on down to a beautiful wyoming and they have some celebrity that may have spent a weekend there
That does the entire video the whole ad
Wyoming I had to change flights here at one time
It's cool though. Really liked it. I thought he was gonna just blast him in the face
That was like a i'm gonna fucking a haymaker. You know, it wasn't okay. Shit. I missed it. I was gonna
Damn it
Okay, here we go
Come on a little too much grass. I think
Those particle things like you have like a firework in your hand
I mean I can't think with a little bit more time in the oven. This looks like it could be really good
I think a lot of devs really want to show like look at how many particles look at how many pieces of grass we can put
on the screen
But seriously at some point it really does look like you're you're like a fucking aquarium
You know what I mean? Like look at it's like deep sea shit everywhere. It's like coral reefs and shit like it's it's like
I don't care about that
I'm interested. I'm interested though. It looks like it could be pretty good. It looks
I mean i'm into like the third person kind of sword
gameplay, but you know
It looks like it could be all right
I mean, it's not coming out tomorrow. So they got a lot of time
Holy shit, okay. This looks this looks pretty cool. Okay, i'm gonna say it could be pretty good
What the hell is going on?
Okay, I mean
That's a lot of effects
So many effects going on. It's just it's just the finale of every firework show you've been to
And i'm talking about the grass does that too
He's walking through the glass the grass and there's like big exploding firework effects in the grass
Glass too sure
crimes
On the of the desert crimson desert
I was wrong get all the latest news of crimes of the desert. I love having new ip and new teams on stage
South korea that one looks so good desert. All right now to present our next award
He joined me in fortnight earlier this year the star of tenet you got to play fortnight washington. Hey john
Hey jeff, thanks for inviting me to the game awards as you know in christopher nolan's latest film tenet
I played a character called the protagonist
Very literally named narrative and I thought that was cool name for a character
It reminded me a little bit of playing video you just like start saying spoilers for all the
Protagonists helping to tell the story of the game with our choices
Great narratives and games are the perfect balance of that feeling of being in control
But also being guided by brilliant storytellers and so these are the nominees for best narrative
Didn't a lot of people complain about tenet that like you can't hear what anybody's saying
Again it's hades ghost of shishima last of his friend. It's the same five games a touching reunion. It's the same five games
Did anything else come out in 2020 the game award goes to
The last of us part two
First off, it's such an honor to be nominated with so many incredible games that came out this year
so truly truly
Of course, i've got to thank my co-writer and the director of the last of us part two neil druchman
Who was courageous enough to tell such a ballsy story?
Um, and a big shout out and thanks to pogchamp
Other writers josh share and ryan james and of course the entire naughty dog studio
This game is what it is because of the collaborative nature at that studio and their love of narrative
and of course
Thank you mostly and always to the fans these characters meant so much to us and were really touched that they resonated with you as well
So, thank you
Right now we've got a very special
News for all you virtual chefs out there joining us all the way from his kitchen. It's the swedish
I understood every word
Little
Chef i'm so sorry to cut you off and you're looking sharp in that tux by the way and my swedish
It's a little rusty, but I think there's been a little bit of confusion. Honestly
No, no, no, it's for the win
No, no chef i'm so sorry that you didn't actually win a game award that trophy you've got honestly
It kind of looks like leftovers. Anyways, you're supposed to be sharing an announcement here
What's the announcement?
No co-op game like a fun cool new game with a playable character named
I want him to bite the thing set up
Wait, it's I what's I that is why you're here for a world premiere
Co-op swedish chef game. I'm not going off cam for this one. This is like this. Oh
It's just overcooked like it's an overcooked costume
But it's a new game. It's a new game
That's a new game. There you have it. What do you think chef? Oh shit, that's a new game
Inferno
Oh my uh, all right. Well, congratulations to the swedish chef this time
It's real swedish chef is playable in overcooked all you can eat on ps5 and xbox 3 dex and he's available
Right now coming up gal Gadot is presenting our games for impact award
And we'll head to abbey road studios to celebrate mario's 35th anniversary with the world famous london
Philharmonic
But right now let's hear from dr
Lupo about a new initiative at the game awards that was your class that was like whatever like that was dr
Lupo and tonight i'm honored to partner with gilette to introduce the game awards future class
A group of future class dreamers and pioneers who represent the bright bold and inclusive future for video games
Games have really changed my life to be honest with you
My name is royce payne
I'm a senior computer science major at mario's college and i'm currently playing on the mario's maroon tiger gaming team
We see other big colleges are able to have these gaming teams and they're winning scholarships for us not to have it
We were like this is a lack. We need to get rid of this lack
We're just a collection of hbcu's who have different passionate gamers who want to compete against one another
We've played against some good competition so far
Just being able to really break into that space and open the door for others to come behind me. That's huge for me
That's cool shit
Oh, hi everyone. I hope you're enjoying the game awards. I'm alana pierce coming at you live from my mansion
I've had to find some unique ways to deal with
2020 situation like maybe I go for a swim in my
Olympic sized, but that's not olympic the the olympic one is indoors
But I know that there are some people out there watching this that are depending on things like vaping to try to calm themselves down
however
the high levels of nicotine that you can be inhaling can actually worsen your anxiety and just kind of fight against the mental health battle that is
this year not that I would know because
I'm a vape. I've got but that doesn't mean i'm not trying I don't vape
What are you what are you talking about for those of you who are looking to quit vaping, which I hope we're talking about
I don't this quitting is a free text-based program with a free built-in support system. I don't think it was to 8 8 7 0 9
What are you talking about?
I don't vape
I've never vaped in my life
Oh mario party 17
20, I don't know. Oh
You have to accept it. I don't I don't vape. I don't vape. I don't have a vapor pen. I don't like
I don't I don't do that
No, you guys talking about like marijuana. Oh this guy this guy smokes
I heard he smokes weed. No, I don't I don't even do that either. I eat it
Correct yourselves here mario music back. That was fun. All right back in 1997
I wrote a story about two game developers coming together to make an unreal franchise tonight
And it's legal again for this here in las vegas. So what the fuck are you gonna do about it right now?
by the way
Whoa
Just kicked in about 45 minutes ago
I'm not I'm kidding. Don't take everything I say so seriously and not everything I say is real
I told you 90 of everything i've ever said is fake
This is new unreal. Holy fuck
This is unreal
That's unreal
What oh, it's what but wait, why are they doing the unstoppable killing spree? Uh, isn't that unreal?
Welcome back to the game awards earlier. I asked you to head over to instagram
Of the year arfx to your reel. Let's check out really looking forward to the new ghost busters game. Come on
On instagram and i'll share some more in just a bit now back to your house. It's too hot. I gotta get this off
I'm fucking steaming right now last month call of duty invited players to unravel a conspiracy decades in the making with the release
Of black ops cold war on december 16th season one kicks off free multiplayer maps more weapons and more operators and for warzone players
A massive update of content including a new close quarters map rebirth island
Here's your first look at the gameplay of season one. Okay, we're on the walk. We're we're on the whopper lookout
Yeah, this chat is in whopper lookout mode. It's too hot in here to wear this fucking bathrobe. I'm sorry
I gotta take it off
DMCA whatever actual dmca what?
Oh
Now it's not
Why can I not hear that now? What happened to my audio?
I like fucked up my entire mic setup
It's only coming through one headphone
kill the rest
Oh, there we go. Now I can hear it
35th this year super mario brothers orchestra wasn't going to be easy to pull off
But we had to try I know how much we all love video game music
Well, i'm really proud of what we've got for you right now
This is a little like a little like 30th anniversary of nintendo's all-time classic super mario brothers originally released in 1985
Here to perform a medley of mario songs from the legendary abbey road studios in london
This is the world-class london philharmonic orchestra led by conductor lauren balfe. Enjoy
It's loud. I can't do it. Uh, yo for this
I can't my voice is still fucked up
I can't do it
Oh
You can make it do whatever you want
All right, all right, but this is video game music. I'm fine
I promise I am not gonna do the i-e-o again
I want to be the conductor so bad. You just get to sit up there and do cool shit like
That'd be so much fun
Like I already I don't play an instrument. Can I just do it?
stop
Why?
You're fine. They what?
You're not fine. They just dmca'd two days ago
What this guy is just zerked out of his mind kind of makes everything better, doesn't it?
Wow, uh, thank you to lauren and the london philharmonic. They'll be back again later in the show and eddie better is coming up too
So lots of shows i'm just sitting here like lots of us are in lockdown right now
I don't like the guy the rave that's on like the drugs
Just going like lockdown and I know we all can't wait to go back outside to travel the world meet new people
Well until then here is a game where you can do all of that as you explore and record
Disappearing cultures in a strange beautiful world. This game is just stunning and it's coming to playstation 5 check it out
It's so hot in this fucking room
Why is it so hot in here?
I'm gonna start saying celsius. I think it might be like 50 or 60 degrees celsius in here. That means holy shit
He knows what celsius is and that's hot
190 degrees Fahrenheit
Oops, never mind
Might be though. I just turned the webcam back on and i've got i've got I got like grill marks on me
We have one season
Streamer tries to pick up chicks on stream by talking about celsius
Why would that be how it'd be so bizarre what?
Beautiful that's seasons. All right. Well now it's time to present another game award
She's the star of the upcoming film wonder woman 1984. Here is gal gadot. Hey gal
Thanks jeff i'm honored to be here at the game awards
Lots of video games are fun to play but each year a select few games deliver a deeper message
They focus on subjects that can be historical political or deeply personal
The games for impact award honors socially progressive projects that have the potential to inspire
real change in the world
Here are the nominees
Games for impact
Oh, what was that game stirring up old memories the game looked pretty cool choice about that
Resist matter that cost
And the game award goes to tell me why
Hi, i'm mary hall the community manager of tell me why and on behalf of the entire team from both don't not entertainment
And xbox publishing thank you so much for this award and thank you so much for all the love that you've shown tyler and alison
And their journey i'd like to express our team's deep admiration for all of tonight's nominees
Especially those that have used their platforms to tell stories about trans and queer people with sincerity and heart
Here's to a future where even more marginalized people can see themselves and their experiences truly reflected in the games they play
Thank you so so much
Congratulations, everyone's joining us live. The tech is working. This is amazing and it's so cool to see everyone. What was that frame?
All right. Well right now we've got another brand new game announcement for you. Check this out empty
Uh-oh empty. No, I want to be on camera for more than one second. Jeff. Give me give us streamers a second. It's about me
whoa
Wait, is it is that the vin diesel?
It's a vin diesel game
What is this?
This doesn't feel like this is even real
I feel like this is like a deep fake vin diesel is in this okay
Let's see what it is
They all run back and then they all like get into like a big like a ferrari or something
You don't even like get it
He starts just driving through the forest
What the fuck?
Okay, if you're talking about a third person you play as vin diesel against the dinosaurs
Um, I have to play this game
And I will guarantee it. I will happen at lunch
I will stream this game at 1201 midnight. That's how much I want to play this
He didn't make it. He didn't make it. He didn't make it
What the fuck
That was two things that weren't like mmm, you can't get us and then like the frienders or family member who just got just
killed
What the fuck was that?
This is that was that was like vin diesel's friend
Or vin diesel's like family member
Oh wait, that was an enemy
What?
I wasn't paying attention. I just saw vin diesel's face
I thought they were together
No, he just said old friend
I thought that was like one of vin diesel's friends
No, what the fuck are you talking about
arc two
Vin diesel is the character. I don't understand what we're watching here
That was a fan fiction made like they made that two starring vin diesel and the team at studio
Somebody made that in blender one more announcement for all arc fans. Check this out. Can you feel it?
The balance of me I have to play that day one there is someone out there who may change our fate
Could lead us out of that was an insane trailer
To survive. I have to play arc two
And there's an arc netflix animated series original. Oh my god. We're getting so many cool things today
Well, here's the thing guys. We all know that
We all know how much money the arc franchise has made
You know
The animated series
The fuck man
Oh, that's that's like I don't even know to say this is the biggest
I don't know. I have no reaction to this. It's just like I could not have like carl urbans in this
Russell crow, I thought it said with russell crow as vin diesel
I was like why?
And with russell crow
Crazy here for fall guys. It became a massive phenomenon and we all had fun with it
This summer, especially when we were all in lockdown this holiday season fall guys is back with a winter wonderland for season three
Here's your first look
It's the most
I didn't know I didn't that's different
This song's dmca too, whatever they want to come after you then i'll write up a letter
Just wait for like an hour from now
Isn't there like a twitter account that tells you when people are banned?
We'll see that before it happens and i'll be like wait
German 985 twitch channel has been banned indefinitely. Oh
I guess I am
The game festival is going on right now and you can stream all the game festival demos using any device
You own with g-force. I feel like i'm just turning the camera on to like prove to you guys that i'm still here
Games you can play all weekend long. Hey coming up next. How are you tom holland?
Nolan why again and the award for best multiplayer more awards and announcements. I'm just like peeking into your room like oh reggie
Keanu reeves plus eddie vetter from pearl jam playing his song from the last of us part two
But right now elite dangerous is a space sim mmo from frontier players have been exploring the galaxy for nearly four decades
Don't freak out is the gameplay reveal of odyssey don't freak out you explore on foot. I don't want to like i'll be like reggie
What's up? I'm a huge fan. I don't want to freak out. I don't want to freak out
Sorry, cool. Reggie's here
Hi reggie
More dmca super dmca
Oh, this is oh, yeah it is
This is actual control the major tom
Take your prozine proteins and your hands is on
This major tom's at ground control
I'm looking through the mirror
And everyone can see us through the b.a
The stars look very interesting today
This is
Look if I tear I guess i'll be fine
There it is. I fixed it
Imagine you just had to what if I like had something in the algorithm
Where like people found out they did some digging and holy shit like the germa 985
Ieo if you put at the beginning of your video or at the end of your video it fucks up the thing
every single video would start like
Uh
Hi everybody. Welcome back to the channel. We're playing uh minecraft tonight. Oh shit. Hold on. I realized that
All my life i'd been using video games as a way of nurturing my own well-being
And I wondered if other people could do that too. Hi, this is
And so I established checkpoint to bring mental health resources to the gaming community
What is mental health we use games as a medium to raise awareness and to reduce stigma
And to provide real tangible resources to people who are struggling that they can use in their everyday life
This is really good really cool above all else. I want people to know that
It's okay to be struggling at the moment. There are resources out there and it will help and it will get better
Welcome to enoch
If you don't want to end up as worm food what worked for you in the old world won't work here
Running and hiding are simply not viable options here if you plan on surviving you need to shift your mind into a higher gear
So let me walk you through the mantras of survival
Your attention, please
People can fly. Oh, I thought this was one of the things. Yeah, that's right. First of all, I want to let you know people can fly
Get on top of your roof right now. It's right. That's how you survive
Chuck yourself. I don't know why I thought that
Your powers are on tap. Don't do that
Don't keep them waiting three
You've got a kill to heal. There's no use licking your wounds
Want your health back get out there and take it violence breathes vitality finally
guiding philosophy to end
You have to think aggressive shoot people in the head
Take their fucking heads off with knives and axes
step four
Drown people's heads in water make sure they can't fucking breathe and then their last breath comes out when you watch it
Nudity step five don't ever show nudity even one nipple. Don't ever do it. Don't stop disgusting weird
step six
Gouge out eyeballs with a fucking knife
throw guy off bridge
Shoot in head with gun at point-blank range resumed in close-up
You got a kill to live and heal
Oh shit, this kind of looks good
This looks pretty good. I'm interested in this. What is this?
Fist that's a good name too fist
I'm sorry. I can't stop
And there's an amd chip in there
Nice, I can't wait to get my own risen like 64 cores
Hey, what's up guys? It's uh, tom holland here
I am in atlanta on the set of the next spider-man film, but I am honored to be a part of the game awards tonight
You know that for the past few years i've been working on the uncharted movie
Which did involve some extensive research playing the games. I'm honored to be playing nathan drake
What I can assure you is that we really want to honor naughty dogs amazing games
So this film tells you how nathan drake became the character we all know and love
It is now my honor to introduce my good friend nathan drake. Please welcome. Mr. Nolan north
I thought it was gonna feel like a cg thing and he was gonna like start talking
I could not be more proud of you
You know someday when someone searches for nathan drake on imdb and you are the first result. I will only be remarkably bitter
You know video games allow us to connect with friends family and complete strangers
We can share memorable experiences beyond the confines of our own homes funny or even travel to vast new worlds with our buddies
On the couch next to us of all the years. I've been grateful for multiplayer games
He's never been more important to us than they were in this historically crappy rotten. No good cursed year
These are the nominees for best multiplayer
All right
best multiplayer call of duty modern warfare fortnight
Um
I can't say why
When the imposter is sus you fucking guys and the game award talk about how much I hate this photo
And then you memed the fuck out of it among us
What who won?
Among us won
Oh I can do this. All right. Thank you game awards and everyone who voted for us
Um, and also congrats to all the other games nominated
Um is an honor to have won best multiplayer category our goal with among us from the beginning was to create a fun experience
amongst friends
two years ago among us started with
Local mobile and then um online and pc and the rest is history
They killed it all they really did like connect with friends is increasingly significant and we're so happy
Many of you turned to among us to play with friends and family big
Thank you to robot teddy dual studio and our other partners for helping us navigate all the excitement
Thank you to our moderators and the fans who have been on this journey with us for the past two years
And big thank you to our friends and family
You've helped us test and been incredibly supportive through it all. Thank you so much. Thank you
Yeah, that's really cool
Tonight you've been using instagram's custom game was on steam for like a year or something right before anybody really started playing it
Like you're real. Let's check out a couple of those. They just made a fun game. Whatever and now winners in my book
Keep making those trophies and i'll be back with more later now back to jeff two years. Yeah, thanks very much sydney
Later among us among us the new map reveal. All right. Now we've got another brand new game announcement
This one is fun. It's one of your favorite supernatural horror franchises
And it looks like a bloody good time. Check it out. I don't know why I was just like, I don't know. I'm a weirdo
I was gonna be like bloody good time is
Like that's how we're describing. I mean you can't wait
What in this one don't you love that a wonderful girl you love it linda like why do we care what's wrong with us?
Blood blood everywhere. Yeah, good. He said the word blood fucking everywhere. Give it to me
It seems an archaeologist had come to this remote place to translate and study his latest find
It was never meant for the world of the living. What is the book awoke something dark in the woods?
It took linda it's evil dead
Is it an evil dead game or is it dlc for dead by daylight for me?
Holy shit. Okay. Awesome. Yep. Cool
Plus one already
That's a full letter grade. I didn't even know that yeah
I'll be checking that out evil dead the game next up a classic game franchise
Is being remade take a look at this announcement another left for dead. No, that's probably like a little story kind of game
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait this power stone power stone
Oh
Oh, okay
When I say ghouls and ghosts ghosts and goblins, all right, this is my favorite game of capcom ghouls and ghosts. Oh, okay
Where's power stone?
We're gonna get a power stone three
We love ourselves some capcom arcade classics. We're now going to recognize some more winners in the category of best
independent game the nominees are
carrion
fall guys ultimate knockout
Hades
Spelunky 2 and spirit fire didn't smoke it to come out like a few days ago
Hades congratulations super giant
That's two wins for haiti's design. Those nominees are doom eternal go to tashima
Half-life alex resident evil 3 and the last of us part two
You gotta give that to alex and our winner is half-life alex the last of us part two. Congratulations. Naughty dog
And half-life alex was awesome playing game are they only going to win fresh vr game seven remake
It's unfortunate. That's what it is persona five royal wasteland three and yakuza like a dragon and the game award goes to
final fantasy seven remake
Congrats square in the category of best simulation or strategy game. Those nominees are
crusader kings three desperado's three gears tactics
Microsoft flight simulator and xcon right our squad is
microsoft flight simulator
Congratulations
And our fan category you can actually fly a plane
Tournament style to pick your favorite games the final five nominees were doom eternal goes to tashima
Hades marvel's spider-man miles morales and the last of us part two isn't that just the all the category already
No, we announced it online. Congratulations to sucker punch ghost of shima
Player's choice is just now we've got one more for was it missing for best fighting game and here to help us out
From netflix's cobra kai two great rivals from film history ralph machio and yuji okamoto. I hope they fight
Are they gonna fight? Oh, okay
Game awards. What's up? Hey ralph, you know who wins this? No, how would I I mean we haven't even read the nominees yet
Not you
That's a bedroom piano
He's got a piano listen, whatever, okay
Why don't we just read off the list of nominees, huh?
Best fighting game grand blue fantasy versus mortal kombat 11 ultimate street fighter
Five champion edition one punch man a hero. Nobody knows
Under night in birth
And here we go
the game award goes to
Sorry, it's
stuck
Somebody glue this thing. I got you macho
And the winner is he gets up and like leaves his room and opens the door and he comes in his room and they
Fucking start fighting guys. Awesome
aw
All right, uh, congratulations to mortal kombat and thanks to ralph and yuji one of the things I have really been missing this year
Is flying around the world
But luckily we have one of the most beautiful games of the year to help fill that void a little it just won best
Simulation strategy game microsoft flight simulator and next year it's coming to xbox
Here's what that's going to look like. It's an airborne view
By the way, uh, we just had to skewed up just because you know, we're gonna take a look at flight simulator now
Uh, you know just win
Best simulation category. We have the big screen behind us. Let's take a look at it. Why not? Let's see. Oh god. Damn it
He's a big dmc
What I what do I do
Uh
No more songs stop playing songs in my microphone
All right, uh microsoft flight simulator looks amazing coming next summer to xbox and now it's time to take a look
At another game coming to playstation 5 check it out. Can't wait jeff
PlayStation 5
This could be big
20k, holy shit. Is this the highest this most people that ever been here my end what is waiting at the beginning
I will go there now
Holy shit. Yeah, 17 18k was the carnival. Holy fuck. Oh, hi guys
Every time what is this?
Cycle i'm trapped inside
And it looks cool. But again, I gotta say it again with this particle effects aquarium and everything has to be lit up and exploding and
Lights have to be everywhere
Looks cool. It does
It's too many things too many like explosions
It looks really cool, but we'll be back in just a moment with a man. I mean a man a meme a legend reggie
He's gonna join us
We've also got a new look at a game from a guy you might remember from one of the craziest most unscripted moments
In game awards history joseph fares plus any better better is here reggie's coming up soon
And later jacksepticeye joins us from europe content creator of the year presented by adobe
Lots of great stuff coming up here on the game awards. We will see you right after this
Content creator of the year. What are you training for?
What will you do with this strength? It could it could be me
My answer to this question used to be simple
It's not so that I continue winning
I train
So that I never
Lose again
I should just put myself up there as a category and when I don't win just trash my room
Like put holes through walls and stuff and like break my computer and stuff
Oh and the winner for content creator the weird new here is
And i'm like
Yeah
Um meat boy
Meat boy
Oh, I tried to play this game and on my ipad and the whole game was black. I couldn't play anything
I was pissed and I looked up on the forums and everything and it was like hey
My game is like black too. There's all the graphics are black and I can't see anything and I was like
When the fuck are they gonna fix this?
But I just uninstalled it and never looked back
Like the mobile version is fucked up
Sorry, you're not gonna get my like eleven thousand dollars in buying like
different like colored swords
I was ready to give it to you
It's a spyware game. Well, you just made me say that out loud. Is that real? No, that's somebody's opinion
That was somebody's opinion don't take anything I say seriously, please
This is abby versus ellie from the last of us part two
I am team ellie ellie is probably one of the greatest game characters of all time
Yeah, and abby can beat her up. So that makes abby better team abby all day
What yeah, I want team edward if she gets a nap and some food in her
She could probably deadlift a small car and she's nice to dogs. Well, ellie is an artist and a beautiful singer
Abby could be a good singer. You don't know. Yeah, you can tell she's not a good singer points. Like there's don't make good singers
Fair enough win this round
Procedurally generated road trip are you from the border be careful with the people that give you a ride
Wait, what and don't travel with someone you don't know. What is this? We love you, honey
Okay, i'm interested thousands of roads. It's a car game
All right
Road 96 i'm ready for it. Let's go
Wish list it now. I will I will right now. I'm wish listing it right now
It's a whole letter grade
I like this. This is a gey song
I like it
I love gey songs. They're my favorite
What's the matter?
Where's everybody saying f?
Everybody say f back to the game awards and before we went away there
I might tell you that was a look at a new rogue coming to rogue company
So make sure to check that out this holiday season to press f. Oh, probably remember this next developer from a few years back
He is not a fan of the office this guy. Yeah of colorful language and our show
He's in if he's got a new game and he wanted i'm excited to look at his next game. Yes. Okay awesome
He really is my friend joseph farris. Yeah, i'm gonna shut up for this one
What's up, he's like a mocap suit back at the game awards as you can see i'm in the middle of a mocap shoot
Working on our next game. It takes two
Trust me when I say this hazelight's next co-op only experience it takes two
Yes a blend narrative and a huge variety of gameplay never done before and today we're gonna have a gameplay reveal
Our word exclusive. I know you like word exclusive, but this one is even extra exclusive my man
Anyway, we're also gonna have this guy
We call a friend pass which means you buy one copy you get one copy for free
You know if you play with your friend, you can play with free with for free. I mean with
Anyway, it's coming out march 26. Enjoy the trailer. Really? Goodbye. Boom. Let's see it. I'm so excited for this. I
Um the way out was awesome
This is the story of a magical king
one of wizards and
a big dame sent upon the high seas an odyssey through time and space
Also a bit of a winter wonderland bobsled sort of thing, you know
What is this?
Almost forgot they used to be humans. Ah, yeah
What this story is really about
Is this story of cool, why'd you look like a blob of play want to change back then you need to fix your relationship
What the fuck
Some of these environments look ridiculous
Oh, I love it, okay, it looks so cool
Oh, this looks so fun, I can't wait for this shit
What
What the hell is this? I'm so i'm into this
sometimes the screen is together and
Yeah, do we you're not feeling it no, okay
Are you entitled to your own opinion?
Holy shit
That's that's not that far away either
That's the game of the show right there for me an absolutely crazy game joseph showed that to me last summer when I was in stock
Home, I'm like we have to show this off. There's so much gameplay there. Thank you for that joseph
All right
I'd like to welcome a longtime friend and supporter of the game awards
He was there in vegas for our very first show back in 2014 and he's been back every year since we weren't gonna
I didn't tell you guys the retired president c.o.o from nintendo of america, but still a boss reggie fissame reggie
Jeff jeff, how you doing? I'm doing good reggie. Take it away
Absolutely
You know, i'm proud to present the very first award for innovation in accessibility
During my time at nintendo. We had a mantra
gaming for the masses
And we pushed that agenda with we nintendo ds and now nintendo switch
But today approximately one billion people around the world
Experience some form of disability that makes gaming challenging for them
This award was created to highlight the efforts throughout the gaming industry to make software and hardware
That enables games to be played and enjoyed by the widest and most inclusive audience possible
Because gaming is for everyone here are the nominees
Emperor of earth seriously
He's awesome
I have to pee so bad and the award goes to
the last of us part two
But if I leave I gotta go pee but if but if I leave
I'm matthew i'm gonna go pee right now. This is my fellow designer and neighbor amelia shots
And from everyone at naughty dog, we would like to thank you so much for honoring us with this year's innovation and accessibility award
Thank you as well to the game awards for choosing to add
This category and to all the other developers who have designed and advocated for accessibility in our games
We hope that together we can continue the momentum to push our industry forward as developers
We know how one small design decision can unlock the entire game for a player games are special for their ability
To blur the line between player and character providing a means for personal engagement with narrative that is unrivaled
And other artistic mediums. It's up to us to ensure that everyone can experience that for themselves
We'd like to thank our terrific group of accessibility consultants and we'd absolutely could not have done it without your your insight and your
Your uh detailed feedback. Thank you. We'd also like to thank our partners at worldwide studios
Our senior producer sam thompson the user experience research team and our dedicated accessibility qa testers
And we'd also like to thank everybody at naughty dog
This was truly a team effort and every department had a part to play in removing barriers for players with disabilities
Lastly, we'd like to thank you the players
Nothing makes us prouder than hearing stories from players who were able to experience the last of us part two without assistance
Using our accessibility features to remove barriers that would have otherwise excluded them from both of us. Thank you so much
Thank you
Congratulations to naughty dog such an important category and i'm proud that we're able to recognize innovation accessibility here at the game awards
We do that every year moving forward this next world premiere gives us our first glimpse at next year's big adventure for the elder scrolls online
I what if I miss elden ring i'm gonna miss elden ring
Elder scrolls online. I don't give a shit. I'll be back
From imposters in among us to the visual beauty of genshin impact mobile gaming has had an incredible year
Coming up i'll be revealing the winner of best mobile game presented by lg wing the world's first 5g swivel smartphone
Powered by qualcomm snapdragon
And later the first look at a brand new map from among us
The game awards will be right back
In between light and dark is so very thin
Let's cross it together
Fate comes knocking sooner or later
With this power we make our own face
What I missed what I missed. All right, i'm back
I actually dumped the water
I found a water and I dropped it. I got all over the counter
So I had to like I didn't have any there was no paper towels available
So I had to take the back of my hand and like scrape the water like into the sink
I missed elden ring. No, I don't fucking way. I don't do that
It's only been like two to three minutes
I did not miss elden ring. There's no way
I seriously did they always do you actually missed it. I'm not seeing any debates in the chat
I it's just I missed it
Okay, okay. All right. Yeah, you guys
Wait, this is star wars game
Five
We are going to make another star wars game without a fucking lightsaber mind there it is we get to see
There it is
I already saw this I should know better
Okay
I tell you I forgot I talked a lot of shit about how there's no vr lightsaber game and then yeah
I remember that. Yeah, I forgot whatever
It's only on oculus though
Omega oculus omega lull oculus
Available now on the oculus
Tonight go to wdblack.com to get one of the fastest internal ssds on the market the sn850
nvmes ssd with heatsink
Is a heatsink on at this time?
Why would there be a heatsink on a hard drive?
It seems kind of like why?
Gets really hot is he dumb. Am I I don't have a heatsink on a hard drive
Am I stupid?
It says these do get hot if they're fast enough. Well, just but does it need to be that fast?
We've just heard from our friends at pokemon go that there is another surge of whooper appearing
Another whooper watch
Bring out your phones and get to catching and if you haven't heard this is dumb recently implemented
Everybody's gonna get a whooper
We're all gonna get whoopers. They're not gonna be rare
You should have not said anything about it and then said by the way
If you were playing pokemon go during the stream like that whooper you got
And prokey are also we're all gonna get fucking whoopers
Not worth it. There's also a lot of bonuses happening now and it's never been a better time to play pokemon go
We're all gonna get them
Epic game store. They've always known you would come
Oh, I thought this is pokemon go
Do you know why you have?
secrets lies
This should be cool looking forward to this
If you are to face
What's coming you must find?
your full voice
Hot world
apes exodus
To present our next award. She's another award from ig n a long host for the game awards pre-show. This is sydney goodman
It's kind of weird were once defined by their limitations
In a way, okay
Mobile game came up this year
Despite their platform as technology has closed the gap releasing on phones is no longer a limitation
It's an asset
It's never been more apparent than tonight where the nominees for best mobile game have found massive audiences
No, don't say genshin. I couldn't play it here. They are that shit didn't work on my ipad
Better not be buggy and shitty. No, that should better not be
No idea no, no, no, no, no
It's gonna be among us it has to be and the game award goes to be among us
Among us, right? I mean, yeah, of course. That's like the most played game in the history of the universe right now
Thank you again game awards and everyone who voted
We originally designed our game among us to be played on mobile devices
Somebody just come out of the bathtub look around and like the outfit and be like, oh shit and like go back in the bathtub
We wanted our game to be accessible at any level of gamer. It's to be shared amongst friends and family and
Whoever is first and foremost among us would not be where it is today without you same joke
Whatever when it was mobile local only no for the first time just yesterday. Thank you from the four of us
Um, again, big thank you to robot teddy dual studio and all of our other partners for helping us
during all of this
Um, and thank you to our moderators and the fans who have been on this journey with us for the past two years
One joke and for our friends and family. We love you and miss you
Thank you for being so supportive. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
One joke and no not two among us second win of the night
Next up the monster hunter franchise is coming to nintendo switch in 2021. This is a new look at monster hunter rise
I was trying to rise
This is new shit
Is this actually new shit or is this they just remade it for the switch?
I know monsters in a giant stampede
They attack the village in a frenzied rage new. Okay, hold on. He knows why this happens
But it came close to wiping out our village last time
It was announced a while ago. That's still cool though
I've been training for this moment for our entire lot to protect kamara village
Okay
Come a lot of things coming out in march march is gonna be a big month
Play the demo cool. That's cool
Hmm. Hmm
That one looks kind of fun
All right over on twitch the next poll is for content creator of the year vote now for who you think is going to win
And we'll find out a little bit who wins that category
But next up he's one of our industry's great performers and he plays joel in the last of us here is troy baker
One day on the set of the last of us part one
Neil our writer and director asked me and ashley
What we would have been if we weren't actors. I thought about it for a second and replied that
I always imagined I would have been a singer
ashley just shrugged and
In her charming and off-handed way said dare you be so charming
Right, how dare you be the most charming handsome man of us into ellie and joel space
And music became major elements of their stories creating touching moments between them one of those moments now indelible in our memories
Incorporated neil's story as well. Are you making us all look bad not as a writer but as a father
It involved a song he would play and sing to his daughter every night
That song was pearl jams future days
One day neil asked if I was comfortable playing it in a scene. He was writing for the last of his part two
now I don't
Generally get nervous
But I understood what that song meant to neil and to the game and the truth is neil can play that song better than me
But nobody can play it better than the person that wrote it from seattle performing future days. Here's eddie vetter. This is okay
Hey, this is just like a song
And sometimes you succeed to make this man of me
Somebody just said is this the guy from the weird owl song?
I am way older than you
This are you serious?
That's how you know him
No, dude, what the fuck?
Come on
All right, i'm just gonna quiet
Earl jam is almost 40 years old. That's insane to think about
I'm 18. Who is this guy?
Start asking for prime why because there's a lot of people here
No, don't stop to this channel, what are you nuts
Break 20k. Hey everybody
I don't even have notifications. Anyway, so I don't even know I can't even tell
I said it somebody got me to say
But i'm not saying anything. I'm not i'm not doing any notifications. Nothing
Thank you for the subs. I appreciate but I ain't saying anything
Not during the game award
Start talking about crime
Do people do that I feel like that's so obvious and so it's like stupid
Like i'm i'm not on the game awards
Guys i'm probably on a band list somewhere
You're a brand risk
I don't think i'm am I?
I don't think i'm a brand risk
Could I no
I mean I did show like me and chuckie cheese kissing on stream, right? But like that's
Whatever that a brand risk
With dump truck ass, whatever
He's a powerful rat
All right, so that was the song future days and um
that that song you might recognize from
From the last of us and I really appreciate the way that was that was used
especially bringing
Joel and ellie together
connecting through music
And I and I thought maybe it was cool too that made you
want to perhaps pick up a guitar
Yourself and and write a song for your loved one
um, but uh
It is nice to be part of this
Uh show my appreciation and be part of this year game awards
and um, what a fascinating way to
Tell a story. It's just getting better and better all the time and um, it's cool to be part of it. So
Uh, thanks for having me and enjoy the rest of the show
Nice very nice doesn't get better than that. Thank you so much eddie better for being here on the game awards
All right. Now here's another brand new game to show you for the first time
Elden ring, this is it. This is it. That's not
You already very interested
What the hell is going on here been helsing
Evil west
That was the exact same font the exact same text just missing a couple evil dead
That's kind of odd
There you go evil west. All right on twitch
We asked you to predict the winners in content creator of the year and the twitch audience
Uh said valkyrie with uh, 44 percent of the vote they think is gonna win
So the award for content creator of the year is coming up next presented by artist boss logic
Use adobe creative cloud to create tributes to the nominees. You'll see those in a minute
We've also got announcements from among us and fortnight
But right now scarlet nexus is an upcoming action jrpg from bandai namco
Here's a look at the brand new let's check the hairline. We gotta check it every now and again. How's it doing?
It's okay
It's okay virtual brain link cable and now it's all right
It's it'll be all right for a little bit of 10 years more than I did in training be strong
Seems like you're okay
new recruit
mysterious scum
About last year's theme was constant conflict
This year's theme is constant particle effects
The resisting I will obtain the red strings
Yeah, this has pushed the hardware to 98 CPU usage 100 percent of the time you play
Change the title
I didn't see elden ring yet
I didn't see it didn't happen. We're waiting for elden ring on the all-new xbox. I did not miss it
It's coming up soon. It's gonna be a huge deal
I am often depressed when I look at the status
Of where we are in terms of depression and anxiety and inattention
We owe it to all the people that are suffering to be really creative and to try things that when you first hear it
You missed it. I didn't miss it. It's coming medicine. It's gonna be a huge reveal. I am a neuroscientist and a neurologist
It started for me 12 years ago
I became really interested in this idea of creating
Experiences as a way of improving brain function and this relies on a principle called neuroplasticity
The fact that our brain reshapes itself and modifies itself in response to challenges
And so that's how it all started for me to create a video game
That was carefully designed to challenge and reward the brain in a very specific way
And so it just happened a couple months ago
The fda cleared endeavor rx as a medical device to treat inattention in children that have adhd
This is the first time ever that the fda has cleared a video game for any medical condition
So what we're talking about right now is to have a video game prescribed just like we prescribe pills for conditions
And think about this as a new type of medicine
The world is a dangerous place
This
Only the best can keep it safe
Become a tier one operative
plan
position
And execute
Fuck the face cam. It's not on
It's not on man join the elite bring the thunder
Thunder tier one as gamers you are just generally better humans and the world needs you
Here at the peak humanity procreation facility gamers from around the globe are donating their superior dna
I'm donating i'm donating what I have powerful swim swims and it can be yours
transcend humanity
through gaming
What the hell is that?
All right too long on the end too long way too long in the end way too long on the end
That was like uncomfortably long at the very end there
Come on, are you gonna donate your gamer poop?
I read that wrong
Yeah, that's called I played fortnight for 12 hours went to taco bell and got one of everything on the menu because I hadn't eaten today
That's tomorrow. That's what we see tomorrow
There's the brand risk
whatever
What I see is you just saw ea play is available now on new consoles steam and origin it includes star wars jedi fall
In order one of our nominees tonight in a great game
All right now on to one of the biggest games this year was created by three developers in seattle now for you saw them
They've won two awards tonight interslot. They absolutely took over the internet with among us
Well, they sent us something special
This is the reveal of the brand new map for among us. Check it out crewmates
This map
With the layout of the top
Quit grouping up choose a room to start in after a meeting
We definitely have an imposter here
Whoa
Whoa. Yeah, I went like this team has another surprise. They've turned
My face into a mask and that drops right now on twitch for the next 30 minutes. That's right
The jeff keely mask have fun. Don't be sus. They they came to me. I said, all right
I was shattered on the ground
Content creator with over 25 million subs and over 13 billion views. He's joining us now live from the uk
jack septiceye
What's up, everybody loves jack. Come on, let's hear how's it going. Hello everyone at the game awards
In a year when so many of us were separated from our family and friends one thing remained the same
Our favorite content creators were still there for us
They're streaming gaming and sharing helped us fill the hours and feel connected unifying us all with our shared passion for play
Here are the nominees for content creator of the year content creator of the year presented by adobe
Are you proud of me dad? What? Who is this man in my face?
Hold on wait, hold on. Hold on. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow
And don't forget german on 85
Yes
And the game award goes to
Valkyra congratulations
Thank you so much to uh the game awards for nominating me and to all of my friends
And family and fans in my
loving community for being so supportive of me, uh the past
seven or so years of streaming and now to uh
Being creator of the year, that's crazy because there's just so many amazing creators. I can't believe I don't know. It's just
Unbelievable. Anyways
Thank you so much for the support. I am very flattered and honored to accept this is a reddit shelf back there. Yes, there is. Yeah
Yes, there's a reddit shelf adobe salutes the nominees for content creator of the year at the game awards and all gaming creators
Around the world tonight celebrate your creativity by downloading a free trial of adobe creative cloud at
Tgaxadobe.com and get creating
Joining me right now is the chief creative officer of epic games donald mustard. Uh, donald
It is great to have you on the show. It's a yearly tradition new fortnight season. What can you tell us?
Oh, man, it's so awesome to be here. You lost two k viewers. This is amazing. Jeff. You did this yet again, uh,
So yeah, I was so excited right now
New season just started we just all battled this together with our favorite marvel heroes
And and what that's done is it's left the fortnight zero point exposed and agent jones is
looking for all these hunters throughout all these different realities that can
help him stop anyone from escaping from fortnight and
Uh, we've already seen several characters come in and we have one more that he's bringing in somebody said, please talk
I can't stand the capitalism
What do you want to do
I can't solve that like I can't like suck on my
Solve like capitalism for you. What I would I I
Please help us
Master chief comes wait my master chief is in short
You know, it's wicked funny. Isn't that crazy? I master chief even in the chat too
Most favorite characters ever in anything and i'm just nobody kind of care nobody was like pog pog
I didn't even I didn't even hear it. I didn't care in in fortnight. It's weird. Nobody cared
The coolest thing is he's going to be available tonight
Uh in fortnight you can go and and get master chief like I heard that and I was like, you know
There's some pretty cool. Did I hear something my ear? Well, I heard and everyone in the chat was like, oh whatever
Yeah, so I think uh, you know, we didn't want to stop right there. And so there's something else
I think we should uh, we should check out and um, oh he's already in the game
Well, hello, sir. It's an honor
Hey sarge, did you hear?
Huh? I guess you already got the news what news master chief is coming to fortnight for what now?
It's only one of the most popular video games in the world. Is this kind of a big deal obviously?
It's where we are right now
Huh? Wait a minute. If you had no idea that we're in fortnight, then why do you have a cardboard cut out of master chief?
perfectly regular reasons
Whoa, you guys knew around here? No
The chief got eliminated by a sneaky blue. That's no blue. That's that's ninja
It's such an honor. I'm a huge fan of yours on twitch twitch. Is he twitching because he's blue
Stop making us look bad in front of ninja. We're sergeant griff from the popular web series red versus blue
You probably watched it about 10 years ago
What are you doing here?
Well, it's more than just the chief coming to fortnight. This map is too
It'll be in creative mode starting at 10 a.m. Eastern time tomorrow
Oh
Remember the time when I was in fortnight
I'm pretty sure it was called something
Hey, lord
Giving your favorite stop it. What's with the screen and maybe add your own personal touches to the map. Hey, wait
Does that mean we can have dance battles?
Come on ninja. What do you say?
Make it stop. I can't solve all your issues here. What do you want to do?
Oh, I got it. Oh wait that looked like I was versus blue donald
I'm here. Isn't that so awesome and so funny. Um, so what's awesome about that is that
Uh blood gulch was recreated in fortnight creative by this awesome creative team that call themselves atlas creative and
Tomorrow at 10 a.m. Eastern fix it or whatever. It's cool. Remember school is cool version of blood gulch
Oh my god, it's gonna be fun. Everything is in fortnight right now. So are you done for the season?
You know, I mean agent jones is uh, that really was a family guy joke
Remember the time that red versus blue invited us into fortnight and we played with ninja
It really is
I can't get over that
How many i've no idea where we're going next, but i'm on board
Thanks, joe. All right, are they taking a cue from smash brothers up in a moment?
Keanu reeves is going to present the award for best game direction. Just put in just put in everybody
Don't go anywhere right now
Are they because that we talked about that right when the three stooges get added to fortnight cascade then, you know
We're there and I am stoked to be welcome into rocket league's vibrant community in such a big way
I'm excited to work with psionics and monster cat to put together an ep for rocket league's music season
Fortnite is directed towards kids. Why do kids like all these older actors?
You can get the featured anthem in the item shop and grab my free banner all weekend long
Let's check out the season two trailer featuring my brand new track that I made just for you guys
I mean, I mean maybe a little bit. Yeah
What is this
This is the fortnight that this is the fortnight concert thing they did right and like big concert in fortnight
This is a dip. This is rocket lego. Okay, never mind wrong game
No, that's a germa 985 car
For every other one of us of like the thousands of us on twitch
I think cyan and pink looks great
you know
I love it. I love it
I work with teal and pink
It's my favorite color scheme. So how don't you dare say anything about it?
xbox game pass december 15
Your next favorite game is a game that came out
20 years ago. It's not really your next favorite game. It's an old favorite of yours that you liked a while ago
All right, does everybody kind of hope that like the source code for skyrim gets lost
I'll say it
So they can't keep doing it. Could you say something so controversial?
I'm just saying like it
They gotta stop make they got they gotta stop. You gotta stop it
I was so brave to say
So brave
I mean like oh my god lol skyrim keeps coming out. They gotta stop doing that. I'm so different and contrary at our time
Actually, the real contrarian thing would say I hope they release skyrim for ps5
So i'm gonna say that
I really hope that they release skyrim for ps5 like unlocked
with like
10 better shaders or something
That's the real brave thing to say
GTA 5 is the one that should fill those shoes now. Yeah, we'll see when gta 6 decides to get announced on my phone
And there's so we can officially declare another
Wooper watch
team go
Grunts are also appearing in balloons and at pokestops and you can save shadow wooper from their villainous clutches
Make wooper your buddies take photos of it with ghosts. I'm huge and battle with it in go battle league
If you're enjoying wooper watch you'll love pokemon go's december community day. The camera looks awful this weekend
And be sure to check for it after the show to see how many to hide all my like things that I have here
During wooper watch i'm never gonna upgrade my camera because then you'll be able to see like the blemishes that are on my face
This it's blurred enough where you can't see any of the problems that I have
Got one right here. You have no idea. It's kind of blurry
I've got a little spot right in my eye right here. You can't see that. You have no idea
I'm in forever 720 never going up
Take off slow mode
Uh, all right, if one of the mods is around take off slow mode for one minute
Just have to be just chaos turn it off
One of the mods just said
fuck
Fuck people are getting timed out because they're spamming
I can't even read the chat. It's impossible
You picked the wrong time to get a drink
All right, you can put it back on put it back on
Scribe of avalon fallout 76. Oh, don't care fighters fast, too. We already know one of them
there's steve
there's
from arms
pac-man
Cool smash bros melee. Yeah, they really fucked that up, didn't they?
We've got a lot of great show keanu reeves still to come christopher nolan and so much more and of course
We've got the game award sale happening on all the platforms including an awesome discount on
Destiny 2 so uh, make sure to check that out across all platforms
All right for the next 30 minutes on twitch you can get a free cosmic wrap for fortnite
There is a twitch drop happening right now. Let's check that out, too
This next game was announced last year right here at the game awards
Developed by airship and supported by riot ruined king and now they're back to give you a first look at the gameplay
From this indie title the first ever single-player console game from the league of legends universe. This is ruined king
The first ever single-player console game ever you're like that's weird to say cut throats
Spirits
Monsters
When you live in bilgewater
You see some things let's start the party
Queen of bilgewater looking to bring order to this twisted town
The priestess of the great kraken unmoved by fear
This is destiny
The legend is by riot whose strength is only eclipsed by his kindness
I mean, they're technically still like an indie studio, right? Even though they grossed like a billion dollars in revenue last year
Are they no they know that's right. No, not anymore. It's not an indie studio
Did they say indie before this came on
They did what
That's my blade small indie studio blizzard
What brought together nothing good? I reckon all right. I read this wrong. I thought somebody in chat just put in all capitals
Fuck turn-based chat
But there was turn-based combat. I read it like a fuck turn-based chat like what the fuck i'm gonna talk like slow mode
All right, I thought they were making a slow mode console and pc in 2021
Now to present our next award a man who absolutely needs no introduction here. He come, please welcome
He's gonna get on that stage and he's gonna say I can't wait till you guys follow new things
Thank you greetings everyone. Yeah. Yes. I'm honored to be here to present the game award for best game direction
This category recognizes the studio that demonstrated superior creative vision
Setting an even higher bar for the entire gaming industry. I love kiano. He's awesome over the past months
I've come to really appreciate all the fantastic creativity that goes into making a video game
A special shout out to the folks of team at cd project red in poland
Yes, I had an amazing experience playing johnny silverhand in cyberpunk 2077 spoiler. What?
Thank you
And now here are the nominees for best game direction. I love his I love his like energy. It's just so
He's this is a one-time gig. He's doing a reddit moment. We're done. He's going for a reddit moment
Wish things were different
And the game award goes to
The last of us part two. All right. I mean congratulations. It's half of alex is on that list
Half of alex is on that list kiano. That's a vr game real thing to say, uh
Shout out to our game directors kurt marganal once vr games are not toys anymore guys
I don't know how long that's gonna take man. What a year. Um
It's an honor to be in this category with such incredible games
Direction is nothing without a team to internalize it to make it their own and turn it into a game
And we're privileged to have such an amazing team cast outsourcing partners our partners at sony
Every single person that worked on touched this game helped shape it and a big thanks to my forward boss now partner evan wells
You guided us through thick and thin while we made this game
Uh, I can't tell you how much I appreciate that. Thank you to the game awards and to all our fans. Cheers
I I mean
Last of us, right? We've still got one last award to present the big one game of the year presented by christopher nolan
I'm gonna turn what a tribute to all the nominees performed by the london. I'm taking my headphones up for this one
Like I said when people still see vr is kind of this like tech demo toy thing
Where it's like it's not really games. It's not a real game
It's like, you know look at your hands and like throw the bottles on the ground, right until people kind of stop seeing it
As that you'll never see a win like that
Um very gimmicky until people get that out of their heads
Fuck is this gta? What?
Am I missing gta 6?
Put it in putting my fucking headphones in what the fuck?
Oh, no, no, no, no
Obviously going through need. Oh, it's yeah, it's just gta whatever gta online
um
Okay, I can hear it
Anyways, um the fact that vr is still a toy
an expensive toy
Was born about the gate like the ads was so well paced. It was such a fun game
It was a game of the year in my game of the year in the year
515 whatever after having federated the african continent she set out to conquer road
It was on witnessing the consequences of this terrible battle that she decided to impose upon her people as strictly a vegetarian
Diet and it's in 1082 following the unexplained death of the king that she was crowned empress of spain
It's in fact to celebrate this event that rock and roll was invented
What the fuck in?
Allied with the valiant japanese she discovered the real indies which had fallen into the hands of the bloody french
This was followed by the great devastation
The 100-year war that lucy adam ended before beginning the great reconstruction
And establishing a lasting peace by banishing all forms of currency and violence as well as the use of selfie sticks
in museums
Lucy are you with us?
Is this cg?
Is this a cut scene is this filmed in real life is this
Push was that a cut scene?
That looked fucking real with instagram's game of the year ar effects. Here are a couple more
Those effects are still available. So keep posting to your instagram reels and coming up
We'll find out who's getting a real life game award trophy for game of the year
Nose ears
You can't I don't even have instagram
How bad have things gotten the german occupation has turned every neighbor into a possible enemy
More resistant members, but that's much easier said than done
Drop your weapons make any move and we shoot
Please tell me you brought bazookas
Zookas vr experience the world war two
Okay, what that's a piece of shrapnel
We had to report for the dread was something we had to build
You want to hear the rest of the story
This is the game what's going to be a tough job ahead where's my sister
It's good for us to be together
That's all we can ask for
Medal of honor
What really?
It's available now
What the fuck that oculus get the fuck out of here. Come on is available for everything else, right?
Is it available for everything else?
Welcome back to the game awards. I'm so excited about that medal of honor for respawn in vr surprise
It's out right now. What an incredible. Holy shit game. I can't wait to play that hopefully this weekend
All right
When the show ends the games continue with the game awards festival
You can play upcoming games and stream them on g-force now. So elden ring is coming on pc mac
Or or shows over make sure to check it out. We got playable games available all through the weekend
All right. We've got one last world premiere to share with you
Check this out. This is this is it. This is this is it. This is elden ring. There we go
It has to be here we go
Doesn't look like elden
Mass effect maybe yeah, I don't know
That's effect four no
This better not be like destiny 2 dlc
better not be
mass effect
Four we're not sure what number but it's gonna happen at some point
Mass effect, I can't wait to see where bioware is gonna take that uh next. Um, very exciting
All right
Well to present our final award
This man has created some of the most iconic films of all time some of which screened this summer in fortnight and on december 20th
I'll be sitting down for a conversation with him on youtube to talk about the home release of tenet and his illustrious career
And if you've got questions for him, which i'm sure you do send them our way using the hashtag ask nolan on twitter
But right now without further ado to present game of the year. It's my honor to introduce christopher nolan. Hey chris
This guy couldn't care less about this whole show. It's an honor to be part of the game awards
I had bathrobe on i've always been interested in telling stories that that immerse the audience
I like movies that that unfold in unexpected ways and pull people into a world
When I look at video games, I see a lot of parallels with that kind of storytelling
How players agency and choice intersect with more traditional storytelling methods. It's uh,
Exciting to see and really quite groundbreaking
Tonight all six nominees for game of the year are true masterworks in immersive storytelling
To pay tribute to them, please welcome from abbey road studios the london philharmonic orchestra conducted by my old friend lauren balfe
All right game of the year
We're looking for i'm looking for a hades win here
Not that wouldn't I not this one. I didn't play this one, but I wasn't really that wouldn't really into it
Are there other nominees?
Is this it the only nominee?
Okay, here we go
People really like this doom right people really liked all these but I mean
It's hades angle. This is not let's be honest
This looked really fun, but I never played it. So I can't give a real opinion on this year. I really can't
Is this the favorite is last of us two the favorite?
Well, I don't know. Maybe there'll be an upset
I'll tell you who i'm rooting for i'm rooting for i'll tell you i'll probably rooting for i'm rooting for hades
If hades doesn't win
Yeah, there it is. Let's go
Let's go
I had hades doesn't get like half the screen time the final fantasy 7. Okay, I was gonna say what the fuck is that?
animal crossing I mean
hades doom
or animal crossing could be like
I could you know, it's been a while, right?
I want hades to win
Half-life alex isn't on this list, which is dumb
Like I actually can't believe that what a big step
In like the space if they were to win game of the year, but whatever we can't let's not complain
That sounded fantastic
And now the game of the year award
goes to
The last of us no two
It's the favorite
They won won everything
Won every award won best direction best game best fucking music
again, uh big congrats to all the other games we're nominated with um
Everyone at naughty dog
I I can't wait to hug and high five and get drunk with each one of you
Um, that's gonna have to wait till next year
um
I want to just thank every person that worked on this ambition game and within Naughty Dog and outside
uh shout out to our
Um sony partners again scott roadie connie booth herman drinking on screen
Your support and trust in us means the world
Um and more than anything and I know that I speak for the whole team when I say this
We'd like to thank our friends and family that stood by us and molding us making this game
You inspire us not only to make better more meaningful games
Um, but to improve how we make games on behalf of everyone at Naughty Dog. Thank you
Who won the people like the players choice award congratulations to Naughty Dog game of the year for the last of us part two
And congratulations to all our winners and all the nominees around the world
Thank you for joining us virtually and next year. Hopefully we will all be back together in person
But in the meantime, there'll be plenty of games to play
Congratulations also to plufle who is voted by the fans as their favorite emerging valorant streamer
Let's all go raid her stream right now on twitch. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't leave show. That's coming up right now
Don't go slash twitch gaming. I'll be done yet. I'm not gonna get my final thoughts. He didn't like in tonight's show
But don't leave my screen very unique here
You go there after one thing that never changes is our passion for gaming and the games we love
Thanks to our game awards team and all the incredible developers and publishers around the world who made this show possible
Under very trying circumstances. I did actually in this elder room. Take care. Stay safe. Happy holidays
Oh, that's so bad. I'm jeff keely. Good night. We'll see you next year
Oh well
427 000 concurrent viewers. Holy shit. That's a lot
Okay, here are my thoughts
Is there an after credits like thing?
Is there gonna be an after credits like secret after credits ending?
Um half-life alex being like nominated for one thing or like two things and winning one of them just because it happened to be a vr game
That's upsetting it is
But whatever, you know, whatever elden ring is vaporware. No, it's not
It's never coming out
Well, I mean george r.r martin's working on it. So maybe you're right
He'll talk about it for the next 10 years
And then we'll never see it
I've been waiting for the winds of winter for like seven and a half years. So
That's very possible
Uh, all right. Yeah, i'm gonna go that's it for me. That's all I had planned
I'll see you guys tomorrow
I missed the elden ring. I'm kind of annoyed by that. But you know, whatever look kind of tired today
Do I look tired? Maybe a little that was a show right? That was an award show
What are we doing tomorrow? What are we doing tomorrow? That's a really good question. We'll figure it out. I had fun
Look, I always have fun
During the e3s game awards and stuff. I actually didn't miss it. Oh, so my title is just fucking wrong the whole time
The entire oh my god
Donkey just come right when i'm ending the stream right now shit. Am I gonna get to 30k andy?
donkey
Thanks for the raid, dude
I'm a big fan
You're a funny guy. I like you. Oh my god. I feel like the brad pit just walked in
Donkey. Hey, what's up? It's like going on donkey. How you doing?
I've been a bit i've been a big fan since like 2000 like
2012 or 13 or something did I get the 30k? No, welcome guys. Thank you for the raid
Unfortunately, i'm like i'm turning the stream off in like 30 seconds
But I appreciate it. Nonetheless. Thank you
Welcome guys, you got to sing the raid song. Sure. I will
That's the song the wind song from um, what's the wind song from zelda
Don't leave i'm not a weirdo i'm not weird don't leave they left they all left
What about if I do the hair differently no, thanks, well, and uh, maybe we'll see you again soon
But I am like turning the stream off like right now. Thanks. Thank you the hair
Count olaf
I do I kind I do kind of look like count olaf
Right. All right. Should we raid? All right. Let's all right. Let's set let's send you all 30 fucking thousand people
Like that, I actually I can't believe it. That's insane. All right, so where am I sending you guys?
I gotta send you guys somewhere
There's so many people where are we going? Who's streaming right now?
Oh, we've we've cleared it. The end is like a week ago to go to italics. All right, let's just
Let's just dump like 30 fucking thousand people on italics. He's gonna be like, what the fuck are you doing?
All right, he's let's let's let's let's dump like 30k people on italics. He's gonna fucking shit his pants
He's gonna be like what the fuck are you doing jeremy?
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow
Have a good one. Have a good rest of your night
Take care guys
I will I don't know. What is he doing? Oh, he's doing game award stuff, too. Well
Give us who you thought was the best
Take care guys. See you soon. See you tomorrow. Well for a pre-stream chat. We'll figure it out as always
Thank you. Good night guys