Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here, and...
MLC stuff! Hey guys!
Woohoo! Today, we're going to do something a little bit different.
We're going to do a Minecraft timed build.
And I know we're not the best Minecraft players in the world, but that's why we think it might be actually pretty interesting.
So, how is this going to work?
We're going to give ourselves 10 minutes timed. It'll be on the screen.
And whatever we build in 10 minutes, we're going to try and build a person.
That's today's episode.
So, whatever we come up with... What are you doing? Hello?
Whatever we come up with is what we're going to end with, so let's see what happens, okay?
So, I have the timer ready right here.
And in a few seconds, we're going to start building a person.
So, in the comments section, before we get started, in the comments section, let us know how well we did and something else for us to build.
I want to try and make this a weekly thing. So, are you ready?
Yeah, I've never played Minecraft before.
Like, in browser Minecraft.
Let's see how bad I am.
Okay. And we're starting now. Go.
You build the leg. I'm building the right leg.
Okay. Let's make sure... I have the worst creative mind.
I'm the worst at drawing things.
Build... We only got 10 minutes here.
Build four squares. Four squares going up.
You absolutely can't tell me how to build my leg.
It's going to be, like, symmetrical.
Okay, hold on. Let me see this here.
Yeah, he needs a red shoe. Hold on. We need to put that on him.
Hey, details come later. We got to get, like, the structure down first.
Dude.
All right. How high is yours?
Dude, already, like, one minute is almost gone by.
We don't even have his, like, legs.
Okay, hold on. Match it up. Match it up. Okay.
So, that's your legs.
He's going to be like...
Go one higher. Now we connect the legs.
No. Connect them now.
Yeah.
Just...
Oh, my God. This is the worst person ever.
He's not doing the splits. Look how far away his legs are.
We don't have enough time to, like, do this now, so...
All right. Now we need, like, the pants end, and it has to come, like...
Look at how skinny this guy is.
Hold on. It needs to be... Oh, God.
No, this is, like, his belt buckle right here.
Hold on. Okay, you build the belt.
I'm going to try and build, like, to make it so he's not, like, a freaking stop sign.
This guy is, like, as wide as a stop sign.
All right. I'm building his belt buckle.
Looks like he's wearing a diaper. Hold on.
We got, like, Tommy Pickle here.
Oh, man. This is so stupid. Oh, God.
What is... Why are you building...
That's his belt.
Okay, cool. Cool. Cool.
All right. Two minutes have gone by.
Oh, dear.
We got... I keep on, like, falling.
All right. While you do that...
Well, okay. I'm going to build his other shoe.
What did you do? Red?
Or red blocks.
Most simple shoe ever.
Drop down. How many blocks did you do?
That's a... Oh, God.
All right. So he's got his shoes.
He's got... He look... What does he look like?
Oh, my God. He looks like a Dig Dug character.
All right. We need... Okay, we got his belt.
Now we need his shirt.
Orange blocks. Orange blocks.
Yep.
Orange blocks. Okay.
Why is he, like, so...
What's with that thing at, like, back here?
Did I not, like, make his belt long enough?
No. I... Because he was, like...
I told you he was, like, a thin bastard.
He had to be, like, a little bit bigger.
All right.
All right. We're good. We're good.
We got this. We got this.
Time. What's the time?
Three minutes. We're good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
He, like, pooped in his pants.
Why is his pants so low?
I know. I know.
He really, like, pooed his pants.
His body needs to be way bigger than this.
Ugh.
Watch out. Get out of the way.
I'm sorry. Oh, I dropped my blocks on the ground.
Go on. Go on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Why did he poop his pants?
That's something we can fix later.
His body needs to be at least twice the size of his, like...
He's gonna be, like, a weird freak.
His legs and his, like, butt are bigger than his body.
Like, are you kidding me?
Well, he could, like, make a perfect character,
like, on Hey Arnold or something,
where they always, like, already have screwed up proportions.
All right. All right.
Dude, we gotta get it.
We gotta get away from the body.
Four minutes have gone by.
We have, like, a lot of detail work to do.
Should we start the arms?
Finish what you're doing. I'm gonna start the arms.
He's just wearing a sweatshirt, right?
The arms are gonna come out, like, two or three blocks,
and then they're gonna go forward.
Wait, didn't we decide his skin was gonna be orange
and he was gonna have green pants?
He's shirtless. He's shirtless.
He's shirtless.
It's like summertime. He's, like, in his bathing suit.
All right, so come out. Let's see.
One, two...
All right.
One, two, three, four.
Come out four blocks.
And then go forward.
Go forward two.
What if I give someone a hug?
Yeah, he's trying to give someone a hug.
What is that, like, vanilla wafer?
Hey.
Let's, uh...
It's so hard to, like, stay afloat.
Oh, so I did my arm proportion wrong.
All right, whatever. Just go.
Okay, I'm trying to look and see what we got here so far.
What did you do here?
That's his poop.
Wait, he's fa...
That's the front of his pants?
That doesn't make any sense.
Why are you fixing it?
Because this is his forward. That's his, like...
When you poop in your pants, I'm sure it covers the front of your pants, too.
Okay, I'm gonna start on his head.
No, he needs to be wearing, like, a necktie or something stupid
to make it, like, so we can see where his head is.
All right, he's wearing...
This is, like, necktie.
Oh, Spongebob Squarepants, like, tie?
That's just that big?
There, that's good.
No, no, no. It's gotta be, like...
That's where, like, it looks like a tie.
I just broke his belly.
All right, good.
Now he's wearing a scarf, apparently.
Building a snowman, hold on.
We gotta add, like, the three...
Almost six minutes, dude.
We gotta, like, clean this up.
Oh, wrong button.
That's as good as...
Look at his, like, cocked to the side neck.
We need his eyes.
Okay, okay.
Did you give him, like, obsidian...
Those are nipples.
It looks like armpit hair.
Armpit hair, like, on his chest.
Okay, we're gonna give him these for eyes.
I don't even know what this is, but this is his eyes.
This is, like... Hold on.
All right, all right.
No, we need more... What is that?
What's that?
Oh, all right, all right. I see where you're going here.
Or I was just thinking mouth.
He needs fingers.
He can't just have these, like, sticks coming out for hands.
There's one finger.
There's two fingers.
There's another one.
Oh, great, like, alien claw fingers you made him.
Is he, like, the machine you get the toys out of?
What is he doing over here?
It looks like he's in the middle of a dance move.
He's like,
Yeah, let's do this.
All right, keep it going.
He needs... What else does he need? He needs hair.
Over seven minutes now.
All right, cool.
What color is his hair? How about...
Do we have, like, brown or something?
Brown wool. There we go.
Oh, it's going like nighttime.
I know.
We don't have any light here.
Whoops.
I'm giving him, like, a chef's hat
of brown hair.
What else can we do to him?
He looks like a total dumbass.
It's like
Chef Boy ID, the Pringles guy,
and, like, Spongebob Squarepants
had a baby.
And, like, this is him.
I was thinking Mr. Krabs a little bit.
All right, we only got, like,
a minute and a half left.
Let's clean him up a little bit.
We gotta give him a name, too.
Fix his hand.
This hand is such an atrocity.
Both hands are.
My, like, Minecraft is starting to lag.
I don't even know how hands work.
I'm opening my hand
right now, looking at it,
to try and, like, see what it looks like.
Okay, so this has to come out, like...
No, crap. I'm just standing here.
What am I doing? I'm giving him, like, a cane.
I'm looking at my hand again.
We're almost at nine minutes now.
Oh, great, great, like, bedpan hand
I gave him. Like, yeah, that's, like, fantastic.
Nice, like, skillet hand I gave him.
Oh, my God.
All right, feet. I forgot. We, like, have to come back to these
to make these better.
No. Dude, do your, like,
pants turn into your feet?
No, the boot has to come out like this.
Like, here we go, here we go.
Nice, like, Yoshi we made.
Super Mario Brothers.
And crab cakes.
Make it a little bit higher up here.
All right, crunch time. We've got about 30 seconds.
30 seconds to make this the best Minecraft
build ever.
This shoe is way too long.
We got, like, goofy.
An extremely goofy movie here.
Actually, I kind of like this character.
All right, what else? Make the tie,
short the tie a little bit. This is casual
Fridays. Make this, like,
that. No, that looks
like a tongue. And we're
coming down to, like, the final few seconds.
Three, two,
one, it's over.
There it is. Ten minutes.
And here he is, the
freak show.
So we've got to give him a name now. What's his name?
I don't know. How about, like,
Greg? Oh, hold
my line. He just, like, left the game.
Hey, you crashed at the perfect
time. I didn't want you to name our creation.
But in the comments section for anybody watching
this video, go ahead and give this guy a name.
As well as a rating.
Like, as to how well we did.
Like, one out of ten. So, still a one to ten.
How well did we do with this guy?
And I think that's going to be it, guys. So,
again, leave in the comments what you think we should do
for the next build. And, yeah.
Take care, everybody. And, Stealth, you got
anything to say? Yeah, just
take care, everybody.