Look, that IP is for Upward. I hope you- welcome to Upward. You're on your way to Upward!
And when you get on Upward, join Red.
Please be Upward. I have my fingers- no!
It's Asteroid!
I knew that was the joke, but deep down, I wanted to believe that this wasn't gonna happen.
You wanna do a 1v1 like the good old times?
You wanna 1v1 me?
Yeah, I do. I wanna 1v1 you as Demo Knight.
And this will decide who is the true reign supreme pizza.
This decides who eats the most pizza, okay?
Whoever wins this 1v1 duel eats the most pizza and we can finally settle it, okay?
Okay, because we haven't been able to figure that out since, I don't know.
We've been in massive arguments about who eats more pizza and I think it's me.
Did that not even hit you?
Did I say you could use- did I- did I- did- are you breaking the rules already?
I said Demo Knight.
I'm breaking-
Just wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I didn't even mean to pick that health up.
Just hold- oh, it's so funny!
All right, you ready?
Yeah.
So, I challenge you to a duel.
Challenge you to a duel. Demo Knight only.
No, like an actual duel. Like, you should accept.
I don't- I don't have notifications turned on.
So press like J or I or something.
That wasn't even you. I didn't even kill you. I like just-
See, that's why I was trying to-
It just hit J. Did it work? Oh, yeah, yeah, it worked. See ya.
Did I- did I win?
All right, I see you. All right, all right, you know- you know the drill.
Come, uh, not over there. Come over where I am.
Okay, I'm coming at you.
Follow- follow your teammates. Watch out for this guy.
Go up here.
Up- okay, perfect spot. There's a Demoman up here, but it's okay.
Hey. All right, so in the meat-
Why are we doing this?
Yes.
It's gonna-
All right, where are we going? Where are we going instead?
Did you get it? Are you out here? Are you coming?
It's that simple, buddy.
All right. There is a, uh-
Okay, your whole team is coming out at the moment. We need to-
Go over to the right.
You know, like the right where you can go down and drop to where the health pack is?
Yeah.
Go down there. That's where we're gonna do our duel.
That's where we're gonna do our back-to-back duel.
Ten paces, just like-
Nice. Nice. You come over here as a soldier?
Yeah. I thought it would be a nice duel to show the duality of man.
Why are you using the- Why are you doing-
The War Update? Remember the War Update?
No, no. This- No.
And whoever wins this duel gets the gunboats.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on a second. What did you just say?
Whoever wins this gets the gunboats.
Whoever wins this gets the item, the gunboats.
Yes.
Get me out there quick. Are you serious?
I get gunboats. I gotta get them.
Okay. Please go demo.
I am.
You haven't changed. You have not changed yet.
Come here. I think you can-
Yo, I'm not gonna change. Yeah, I'll show you.
I'm getting those gunboats. I want them and I'm getting the pizza.
I'm- Hold on. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up.
Do not screw this up.
I'm winning the duel.
You want to see what we do? He thinks he's so funny.
Oh yeah. Laugh it up. Laugh it up.
I'll show you how funny it is.
He thinks he's so goddamn funny.
You think you're such a comedian, don't you?
You think you're so funny, don't you?
Rage heavy, rage heavy, rage heavy, rage heavy.
So it's like an old school duel.
Like back in the old times, like get a vintage ambi.
Okay. Where are we doing this?
Where are we going to have like a minute over?
You know what? It's probably over here by like the-
Way, way far behind the spawn.
I'm just going to cloak through and die because I have the kunai.
So just cloak and dagger through.
We're going to go all the way back to this gray gravel door.
Gray gravel?
It says old geezer, draft beer.
Oh, that sounds pretty good.
And you're not going to do an MLC stealth and shoot me as I walk there.
No, no, no, no, no.
If only you could aim, you would have completed the joke.
It's time for the duel.
Don't do it. I made the stupid mistake.
You don't have to make it again.
Okay. So we're going to go back to George Washington times.
Okay. That's what happened to George Washington.
Back to back.
We're going to do 10 paces. Okay.
Okay. So right here.
So I would start like right here and you just hit W one, two, three.
So turn, turn, turn around, make sure you're turned.
And now we're going to do 10 paces.
Are you ready? Okay.
Yes. Ready.
Yeah. One, two, three.
You can't bullshit a bullshitter, buddy.
I knew you were going to do it.
I just wasn't prepared.
You turned around on two or three.
We both were at fault on that one.
Were you just waiting the whole time for me to turn?
Yes.
You weren't even honorable at all.
I didn't even do the first turn.
Can we do a real one?
Yeah. We're going to do.
We're going to do a real one.
Turn. I want to see you turn.
I look, I want to turn.
We're going to turn at the same time.
Okay. I'm going to turn and you're going to shoot me.
We all. Okay. We only have 30 seconds.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn.
I'm going to trust that you're turned as well as I am.
So you're ready? 10 paces.
Hit W 10 times. Ready?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
That was very stressful.
I got to say.
I hit a wall.
Here. You, you go on that side.
I'm going to go this way.
Yes. You go that way.
So turn. Okay.
I, I'm not turned right now.
I just want to make that very clear.
So you don't think that I'm trying to screw you up.
I just wanted to make sure that.
Okay. Turn, turn.
Okay. We're both turned.
Ready? Yeah.
Five paces. One, two, three, four, five, son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
New dual. No, no, no.
New dual, new dual.
Okay. Are you now turned?
I'm, I'm trying to bump into you.
I'm making sure you're there.
Yes.
Okay. You're there.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay. Make sure we're like, boom.
Count to five, turn.
We're having a real duel.
Okay. Count to five.
We're having a real duel this time.
Count to five.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready? Go.
One, two, three, four, five.
Are you shitting me right now?
Are you fucking serious right now?
You put on Uber.
Out of all the things you could have done.