Great. Okay. Hold on room name. Shut up for a second. Will you shut up for a second? I'm trying
I am going to fucking kill you the room name is
Okay, room name is Stern, I'm really stern and I put an N on it accidentally password is
Gerber you're being very abrasive right now password is burger
I
Everybody wants to see this happen
And boo is not in the call. I'm sorry. I think I can only do that. Okay, I'm gonna get you
I'm gonna get you you see my guy spazzing out. No, not yet. I think the time when the timer runs out
It's gonna do both of our moves
Okay
Close to sucking your dick. I had to remove the following dialogue because it was way too inappropriate for YouTube
I hope y'all understand but there was a lot of swears and a lot of bad words
Look at that. Look at this like ass on this guy. This guy's got like a nice ass. Oh great. Why did I just?
I'm gonna contract and I'm gonna like kick you. Okay. No, I'm ready. I'm not ready. Remember you hit space if you're done
I'm ready
I think I've got a hand on you at this point. Yeah, you got you got your left hand like grasping my hand
All right, but you want to go hand to hand? Yeah, this is some hand-to-hand combat. All right, okay
I'm gonna hit you right in the face
I'm gonna hit you right in the face. I'm ready
We're just holding hands here comes the hump you ready for the hump. All I'm doing is like contracting my like but
This is gonna be worse than the last one
This is a German versus star this is a German versus star at all this is this is turning to some weird weird shit right here
I'm like too busy like looking at this. I'm gonna lose
No, I want to do get contract that I'm dead. I'm my hands are off the keyboard. I like screwed it all up
Oh man, is it gonna be sick? Oh, I'm gonna shoulder tackle you. I'm gonna show the tackle you right now. Oh, oh
Oh, there's twenty nine thousand. I like tried to headbutt you and you actually figured out how to like raise your arm
No, no, I'm just dead. I'm just spacing you in I'm gonna I'm gonna fall too
I'm not gonna fall way before you do
Yes, look, I want to see this fantastic fight where I just put my face
Oh
All I did right there was flex I just like flexed my bicep and punched you in the face
I'm going I'm going all out like pelvic thrust into you by the way
Shit. Oh, I blocked I blocked
See the situation you just got yourself into this is the meta
I'm so screwed. I'm falling. I'm gonna fall straight back right now. Like I'm it's over already
I'm like I'm taking like a dive right now. Why does everything end up so dirty in this game?
Is your legs about to come across your whole body? Yes it is
On the ground and like full windmill kick you
If you like just stepped all over my foot, I think I might have this no, I don't think I have this
Remotely, but we're gonna keep trying to make it look cool. This is definitely gonna look cool
No, yes
I
Seriously think you might have just dropped me in one punch. You are going to one punch KO me right here. Hey, I
Just like spit out my gum
You just ransacked my face
Every animation is me falling down to the ground. It's over. You seriously just one punch KO'd me
Let it play out it's over
No, I'm gonna fall first because I have more momentum
Wow, you really you won and you told me to just let it play out like I was gonna like try and stabilize myself
But you're like, no, that's let him fall to the ground and I've wailed on you
Okay, I can't believe I won
I got okay in what situation in a fight
Do you get knocked out like in the face and you like win the fight in one punch?