Hey, what's up? How's it going? We missed you. I was live yesterday for very long. How's it going?
You're quiet? I don't know. Shouldn't nothing change. I mean, I might be talking lower. I'm
screaming and yelling like I was yesterday. Yesterday was a wild one. I'm gonna slow it down
today. Play some trip hang. Am I saying trip hang 2? Is it trip hang 2? Trip hang 2? Trip hang 2.
Is there a trip hang 1? I played the demo a long time ago. Back, what, like 6 months ago? Is there a trip hang 1?
The demo was crazy. The demo was a lot of fun. So I said when it came out I was gonna play it and
here it is. It's out. Hey, what do you mean that the game is quite violent? Uh, this game is quite
violent. That's pretty much all I need to say. Because, uh, I think it's pretty bloody. Violent
game. If I remember the demo, the demo was, uh, was, uh, was outrageous. It's like fear. Yeah,
I played the demo. How the sunflowers. We're gonna go over a few things. I did say that I wanted to
show the sunflowers today, but, sorry, uh, not gonna show them today. I know people were waiting
for this. I said Sunday was gonna be the sunflower day, but I want to make sure these photos look
really good. Holly and I want to edit them, make them look nice.
And I don't just want to throw up a random shit picture. Like, oh, yeah, like, oh, this one and
this one. No, we're gonna curate them and make them look really nice. And then we're gonna present
them. I'm also gonna go over the house flipper lineup of streamers. Uh, that stream is gonna
be really fun. Looking forward to it. Tuesday at one o'clock Pacific. Doing a stream where I get
tentatively because still there's maybe one or two people on this list that, um, you know,
depending on scheduling stuff, some people have stuff to do, but we'll see. I think it's gonna be
probably 10 to 12 people. Can you talk faster? No, I don't know. Tentative Andy. Is stir doing it?
Um, I don't know. Stir just might be there and just do one. I don't know. We don't have a formal
agreement that stir is actually making a house on Tuesday. He can, he's more than welcome to,
right? Like I said yesterday, uh, he's been formally invited and then formally uninvited
and then formally invited again. So yeah, if he wants to do it again, do you think that you
will take over the world one day? No, no God, no, no, no. If I take over the world, you mean like
have my own little farm somewhere and like raised chickens and goats and shit. Then yeah, then yeah,
that sounds nice. Like Thanos. Yeah, guys, like Thanos, no other person in any country, in any
form of media, no other person has, has had a farm before. Just Thanos, just the guy that snapped out
humanity. Only Thanos has done that. Nobody else has ever done that. Why do you, you quote him every
five seconds. I need to correct the record here. Maybe back in like 2019 or something, 2020,
maybe like 2021 when end game was really relevant, right? Like, oh, whatever. I don't even know what
year that movie came out in. So you did. Remember you reference end game for like five years straight.
So it was a big piece of media. That movie made like five trillion dollars. Okay. I'm going to
reference the popular media that comes out. It's like World of Warcraft. Yeah, I reference World of
Warcraft a lot. It was a major, major part of my life and it was like a cultural phenomenon.
I'm going to reference it sometime and I can already see the Batchesters and that's fine.
That's fine. But anyways, yeah. If you want to go over the list, I'm going to get this out of the
way so we can just play and hang out. It's going to be a chill night tonight. I'm going to hang out
and play for a little while. Okay. So the tentative list for the House Flipper Invitational. It's just
me. Nobody's involved. It's just me. Let's go over how this is going to work. I have to, I have to
stall, right? Each one of these people that I'm going to save right now on Tuesday at one o'clock
at the same time are all going to start making a house. They're using the same house.
It's the same template. They will not know what house it is until Tuesday at one. So there's not
going to be a scenario where it's like, oh, it's this house. I'm not going to give them any
opportunity. This list is a bunch of friends of people that you've recognized for years.
Maybe a couple of new faces you haven't seen on this channel. Maybe friends, friends, friends.
Yes, friends. Yeah, I got friends. Okay, here we go. We got Joel, Vinesauce Joel. Looking forward
to what Joel is going to come up with. We've got Seadog. Seadog. RT Game. RT. Vinny Vinesauce.
Poke. Poke will be joining us. Ludwig. Ludwig. Doug Doug. Italex. Italex is joining us on this
stream. And Connor Eats Pants. Those are the, those are the, that's the tentative list.
Possible one or two may be added. Still trying to figure it out. But it's going to,
it's going to be a hell of a stream. Dream Blunt Rotation. The other thing too is that,
so I was thinking about, okay, who, who do I think, who do I know that would actually want to do this?
And I asked all my friends, obviously. But the other thing is I don't want it to be too many
people because if it gets to be like 15, 20 different people, it's like, oh, we all,
you all have to give me tours of your fucking house. We'll be here for like seven hours.
But yeah, I think this, there might be another one or two people added.
Maybe somebody is like, yo, I can't do it on Tuesday. It's all good. That's the tentative list.
Still waiting on one or two confirmations. What is the prize for the winner?
Absolutely fucking, absolutely nothing. Absolutely zero. Nothing. But here's the thing.
You're going to be graded. It's not just, oh, make a house and whatever. And all these grades are
just, the grades are absolute horseshit guys. All right. This is not a real competition.
Can I, I got to make that really clear. This is not a real competition. We're just going to
fuck around for a few hours. You know, this is not a real competition. But if you want to know what
you're going to be graded on, I put a lot of thought into this. Contrary to popular belief,
the grading system is loud. Sorry, that was so loud. The grading system is going to be as follows.
It's going to be weighted, a 100 point scale from A plus to F. F is always 55 points. You cannot get,
you cannot go below 55 points in a certain category. Creativity is worth 35%. Complexity
and structure is worth 25%. Cleanliness is worth 15%. And philosophy is worth 15%. Now you're
probably wondering, that does not make 100% Jeremy. That's where you come in. Chat's grade
is going to be worth 10%. Because I know of like, some of you, like, like Stirr said, the person,
the person that makes the auto house, some of you guys are probably going to give an A plus to.
But I want to be the one that decides. What are you going to be doing while they're making their
houses? That's a great question. I haven't figured that out yet. It's only going to be like 60 to 80
minutes. So I don't know. It's possible. Maybe I'll just jump around and look and see what people
are doing. I'll do browser games. But yeah, everyone's going to have a slot. So people are
going to have about five to 10 minutes to do a tour. And this is where it can get pretty bloated,
right? If this is, I'm trying to think of, okay, who, who can I invite? I don't want to just,
and I don't want to invite a bunch of people and then have to take it back. Cause it's like,
oh shit, actually I invited too many people. And you know me, I don't really fucking know anybody
anyways. I know very, I, my circle on, on Twitch and in the kind of content creator world is
actually fairly small. So, you know, I try to include as many people as I can, if I can. But
yeah, it's going to be a fun day. You're actually lying? Wait, what? What are you lying about? This
stream is not happening? No, what? This stream is happening. I've, I got, I got a whole document
about this stream. Okay. But anyways, yeah, we're going to grade. Well, I'm going to grade and then
you're going to give the ending grade and whoever wins and loses. It doesn't matter. It's all for
fun. Anyways, this whole thing is for fun. I made sure to tell everybody like, Hey, this whole thing
is just horse shit. Just everybody should know that they're talking about how you promised to
finish breath of the wild. Oh, they're talking about something else. You're wasting everybody's
time. What? You can't just have fun. Not everything has to, what do you mean? We can't, we can't just
have. All right. That's a bait comment. That's a bait comment. You didn't even let me trickle in
first. Uh, well, it's been like 15 minutes. Yeah, it should be fun. And again, that list might grow
by one or two. It might also reduce by one. Like I said, but that's just a tentative list. I wanted
to wait to tell everybody that because give people time to figure out if they can do it or not. Yeah,
we'll see. We will see. It's going to be fun. What the fuck are the stream tags? I have not
typed in a stream tag ever. So whatever's there, I don't know. I didn't even do it. One of the mods
just did it. They're like to fuck with me. You should delete them. I honestly, I don't even care
enough to delete them. Is that, you know what I mean? I could go over here right now to the dashboard
because on my other monitor, I have my dashboard and I can, I'm hovering over one of the X's for
tournament arc. I could click the X right now. I could do it right now. But the effort to click
that X is just not enough in here. I mean, I just don't even, you know, I can't do it. I just, I
don't care. But of the people that I mentioned there, I'm very curious as to, because there's
one of two ways to take that stream on Tuesday and that's going all in and doing house additions and
putting up custom wallpaper and shit and doing a full redecoration of the house. And then there's
like, I imagine some of them just going to put like a nice couch in a living room and like put
a painting up and maybe not even paint the walls and just be like, hey, what do you think? It's
going to ask. I'm very, very excited about this. I think this is going to be really, really fun.
Last time Ludwig tried. Ludwig, I'm, I don't know if I would, I think Ludwig is going to make a
pretty good one. Ludwig has experience because if you don't, we did this on Ludwig's bros versus
bros, bro versus bro. So Ludwig has experience. Conradepants also has experience because he was
the one that graded it last time. So, and there's also a lot of people on this list have played a
lot of house flipper. That was part of my decision too, was have they played this before? Hmm. There
are some house flipper veterans that are on this list. When is this Tuesday at 1 PM Pacific? Are
you going to make a house? I don't, I don't know. I might just mess around in house flipper for the
60 to 80 minutes that people make a house. What the fuck is a Tuesday? All right. You guys ready?
Let's play. Uh, going to be just hanging out playing the game. Yesterday was kind of wild.
I'm going to dial it back a little today. What about Stirr? Stirr, that's what I mean by this.
Still a few people that I'm not sure if they're going to do it or not. Stirr is just one of them.
Stirr might just jump into the discord call and just be like, hey, I made one. And he's like,
okay, well, I'm going to grade it. You starting at 1 PM on a Tuesday is never going to happen.
Well, when there's 11 to 14 different streamers that are going to all be there at that time,
I better fucking be there because it's, it's my event. So if I'm not there, that's a big problem.
That would be bad. So I have to be there at 1 PM Pacific time. When like 10 to 15, like,
it's going to be like probably 12, maybe 11. It might be 14 though. It might be like 15. I
don't know. It's going to be, it's going to be a lot of people going to be late to your own event.
Yeah. Stirr's house could be the waiting house while you're waiting for other streamers.
That's actually not a bad idea. Are we going to, am I going to have to send a DM to Stirr to do
another five nights at Freddy's stream where he just discord shares me him making a house for like
an hour and he's not even being graded on it. I would just like watch him play the game and then
he'll just leave. He'll just leave after that. He'd be like, all right, I'm out of here. And
he'll just leave the call. He doesn't even care to be like a part of the festivities. So you're not
even streaming the, oh no. Yes, I am. I am. So how it's going to play out is after the hour goes by,
each person is going to have a, about a seven minute time slot and they're going to share to
me their screen and we are going to go through a tour. They're going to give me a full tour
and I'm going to be taking notes stalling. Well, I mean, this is an important stall. This is a,
this is, this is the big house flipper event I've been talking about the last few weeks.
I think it's an important stall. This game can be pretty loud even if you lower the volume.
That is great for me to know because I will drop it even further. Thank you.
All right, let's go. Trapang 2. Here it is. New game. Uh, I, I'm not picking rage mode.
Hold on. What is this? Easy? Have some casual fun. We won't judge. Oh. Recommended difficulty
players who occasionally play FPS games. Recommended for experienced FPS players looking
for a challenge. What about experienced FPS players that are not looking for a challenge?
How come there's not a normal plus? Uh, punishingly difficult. You will die a lot.
Ridiculously difficult. Expert mastery of the game's mechanics and exploits are required to
play on this difficulty. And then enemies have eyes in the back of their heads.
Instant reaction times and near perfect accuracy. Only some kind of sick and twisted person could
enjoy this. I was playing on normal. I don't care. What the hell? All right. Double headphones going
in. Normal. Omega low. Yeah, that's fine though. I've said this before. When you're over 35,
you can pick normal. It's fine. You can pick normal even if it doesn't matter how old you are.
Stop judging people for playing video games the way that they like to. No audio. I'll turn it up.
This is me. Face cam. We've been good. No, not today. Not today. No face cam. We're in the
chill zone right now. All right. Well, it actually is kind of loud. Still. Can you do a nose cam?
No. Did I just get shot in the head? That'd be so funny if it just started like that.
Audio is fine. I can see it over here. This needs to be changed though. 60% for everything.
Yeah, this is fine. Maybe turn the effects down. Bring this up. Bring the master volume up. Right?
Two cheats. I need to play the game first. Producer Andy. Here we go. This needs to be much
like six maybe. You still have a beard? No, it got way too hot. I had to shave it.
All right, here we go. Wait, the physics even work when you walk? What do I just do? Can I pick that
up? Have you seen the giant LED ball in Vegas? That thing is fucking crazy. You know what I'm
looking forward to? I'm looking forward to when that becomes a giant snow globe in the winter.
It can be anything. Is there a sprint? That has to change immediately. Input. That needs to be E is
where is it? Cloak. Okay, we'll do cloak F and then interact as E. Oh, there is no sprint.
Oh my god. They were moving way faster. It's getting ready. It wants to do it.
The dot appears in the center of the screen when you were in shadow. Oh, so the dot means that I
can't be seen. Do they have audio devices? Do they have organic audio devices on the sides of their
heads? Am I going to get spotted? You can be seen in the darkness. If they let you rent the sphere,
you should put an image of your face there. Oh yeah, this is your captain speaking. We're landing
in a nice beautiful sunny Las Vegas. If you look out your left window, you actually hear the strip
is in view as we're landing here. Take a look at the sphere today is the sus guy. I don't know if
any of you know who that is. Well, your answer to the question is no, I don't have like an extra
six million dollars. So no, sorry. Health pack, right? Why not? Is there a flashlight? Here we go.
Is it too loud? I have a feeling it's going to get very loud here in a second.
I just looked at the you're tripping. Am I? I feel like it's going to go loud. Just be aware.
It's probably going to get loud. Locked. He said rage mode has a warning if you click it.
Rage mode is insanely difficult. Basically anything will kill you instantly. It is not
recommended unless you have a minimum of 50 hours spent in the game. Our publisher even
asked us to remove this mode. Are you absolutely sure you want to proceed? Oh my God. That's so
funny. All right, so I got a gun. Let's do a shoot test to see how loud this is.
That's it's all right. I might need to drop the sensitivity a little more.
Maybe five. All right, let's go. Oh my God. Okay, that's going to freak me out. I'm going to keep
things behind me. It's an autosave. That's good. There's a jump. Cool. Jump and melee to do a
powerful kick. Oh, that's right. There's a big, there's a big jumping kick. What did I just hit?
I just broke my leg. Did you really just say there's a jump? Cool. Slide is alt. I think I
want to change that. What does Q do? I think I want Q is slide. What is Q? Focus. Alt for me is
weird because I have to take my hands off of, um, my thumb is like in a weird spot. I'll try it.
Middle mouse is not a bad one either, but I'll try it as it is because I'm going to hit the windows
key. Yeah, now I'm going to change it. Now I always hit the windows key if alt needs to be pressed a
lot. So let's change it. Let's make it something else. You press using your thumb. What do you
mean? Would you use something else besides your thumb? I know what to do. Watch this. Mouse four
for slide. Sounds pretty good. And then where's grenade? Grenade is going to be mouse. Uh,
mouse five. Let's try that. Yeah, that's much better. That's great. Pick up Intel site 14
security message log. Read it. Cool. Well, actually do I need to know this? Cool. All right,
let's go. This is a stamina bar. This is locked. There is a flashlight. Oh,
enemies can see the flashlight. This was the demo, wasn't it? I remember playing this in the demo.
He's so high right now. I'm not. We're just enjoying video game. Is this game like fear?
It has been compared to fear. Yes. Checking on the tunnel. Who's he shooting at? He just
shooting at his friend. They know where I am. Got him. Slide. Wait, somebody, somebody over here.
We're both stupid. We can't even hit each other. Oh yeah, that's right. I forgot.
I forgot you could do this. Is he dead? Wait, did I come this way? Wait, did I come this way?
I think I can this way. Okay. Um, this is where I just bought everybody. Where's the goal?
It's concrete. I don't know where I'm going. Uh, that's a rule on this channel. If, if the,
the walls are all concrete, I don't know where I'm going. I actually don't know if everything,
if the walls are gray, I'm not going to know where I'm going ever. If you're wondering why
game companies made the, for you to go like it hit the side of your head with your finger
and a line goes on the ground, it's because of me. Blame me. It's all my fault. It's my fault.
I'm the one that they do that for. Cause I shot and fought people in here. Is there a map? Uh,
I don't, maybe not yet. I'm sorry. I'm reading chat too. So the, the walls are concrete. I'm
looking over a chat every 10 seconds. Is this right? Going the yellow doors. Dude, you're going
backwards. Yellow door and then up. And that wasn't I just up here? Kick the red doors. Okay. I, I
found it. Oh, she that scared the shit out of me. Oh my God. Wait, that guy's a different gun.
There's no aim down sights. There, there's the slow down. Cool. I have full health, but on hard.
I might, I might, I might. Okay. You don't have to be sprinting to the, to the slide. That's,
that's cool. Shotgun. Ooh. Yeah. I, I always pick the shotgun. Intel. Where are they? Oh my God.
God, this is violent. This is a violent game by the way. Wow. That was loud. I can't see
anything. All right. Flashlight off. What's all over my gun? The oil. This is blood. It's blood.
That looks like a CS go skin. There's so much blood and guts all over it.
That's like a factory new fucking bloodstained weapon. That guy exploded. My God. What the
this guy live. What the fuck? That guy was climbing like Spider-Man on the wall.
Okay. That was crazy. Anything else in here? I'm going to have to get good pretty soon though.
There's a lot of things you can do with the slide. It seems sprinting costs stamina. Killing enemies
temporarily boost stamina. Okay. You're playing on baby mode. I might turn it up to hard baby mode
would be easy though. Actually you're laughing. People are exploding. I mean, it's, it's kind of
a wild thing going on in the screen that sometimes you don't know how to react to what's happening
in front of you. Geez. You know, there's a game mode you can turn on where it's confetti instead
of blood. I must want to turn it on for a little bit. Let's do actually let's do it. I'm curious.
I want to see what it does. Confetti pyro mode pyro vision. Yeah. I still might need to turn the
sensitivity down. Are we supposed to recognize this person? Oh, a big token. Can you take the
sword? I guess you can't take the sword. What the hell was that? They would definitely hear that.
There's nobody back here. Don't mind that. What just happened to the wall? The wall just,
that was weird. I got all ammo. Uh, let's go shotgun. What just happened?
I thought that guy was me for a second. Can I take a second just to understand?
I thought I pulled out into third person mode somehow and that that was me in the room.
The confetti is funny. I want to get one more person with the confetti and then we're good.
Wait. Secrets. No. Keep it on. Okay. I'm going to try to melee kill. Let's go. Turn up the FOV.
I think it's at 90. Fast movement and nauseous. Uh, is that 90? Should I go higher than 90? 100?
Go 110. Let's try 110. Oh, that is a little better. Okay. Also, I want to put the, let's
put this back on. Turn v-sync off. Turn v-sync off. Turn v-sync off. Turn v-sync off. Look sorry
for me. Oh my God. That guy just tried to do a roundhouse kick to me. That guy just roundhouse
kicked me in the head. We're going a little bit, we're going a little bit lower on the sensitivity.
Let's go. I don't have any throwables. No grenades. Did that screen shake? I turned the screen shake
off. I feel like I'm trying to score like a touchdown. Like, oh, he's got the ball. He's
jumping over the offensive line. Oh my God. Turn the difficulty up. Let's try it. Watch me die in
one hit now. Oh, what's up? I thought the chair was a person. Oh, I got grenades now. Grenades
explode on impact. All right. We're going to have to make this work. Use silenced weapons
to shoot out lights. Wait, where was there a silenced weapon? Oh, uh, go in complete darkness.
Get out of here. Oh my God. Who else? Who else? Geez. That guy killed himself too.
All right. This time, let me not do what I just did because I, I thought whatever. All right. I'm
got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Any more lights? Forget about all the noise in the moving
chair and desk over here. What? I'm just staying down. Got him. Oh, all right. I got a cloak too.
I got to use the cloak more often. I am just breaking everything I touch. Stop. What the
fuck? How do you miss when you're invisible? Open the fucking door. Open this. Open the door.
Give me all right. What do you got? All right. I got a good spot here. Uh, yeah, I'm, I'm taking
this. Give me this thing. Weapon part acquired laser. Ooh, customized weapon. Ah, um, that's kind
of cool. Enemies can see the laser. I'm ready to take the other part. There's another part.
I missed a part. Where was this other weapon part? Oh, it's the briefcase. Okay. I thought it was
ammo. Can I put two suppressors on this? So it's like a big long end of the barrel.
Bolded stock, higher recoil, but slightly faster reload times. I'll keep that. Can I put the
suppressor on the shotgun? Why do people compare this to fear? I just got her. I don't notice it.
I think it's mainly the slowdown mechanic. First person shooter slowdown mechanic.
Lots of, you know, crazy physics shit happening. How would you even see me? Oh my God. I'm
invisible. I'm invisible. I'm invisible. Got them. Oh, those aren't lasers aiming down the hallway.
I thought those were laser sites. That's just my vision doing that. What? It is lasers. What the
fuck? It is lasers. What? It is lasers. I, I, okay. I promise I haven't taken any fucking edibles
today. I thought it was just these doing that. Okay. Well, can I get in here? I don't want him
to see. The fuck is that? Oh, this is a good guy. Subject 106. Accessing user memories.
Successful uploading. Subject 105 termination. Upload complete. Incoming message. The cycle begins
again. Capture means you will be forced to complete your original mission. Exiting program. What the
heck? Where is my health? Just lower right. I remember this room. This is the crazy room from
the demo. Fuck. Get everything quick. Supermarkets sweep this shit right now. What the fuck?
I slide tackled that guy's helmet off. I tried to fucking hit melee him. I tried to melee him.
Oh my God. Okay. I'm going to, I got to run. I'm going to die.
What's that guy doing? He's still alive. Quick, quick, quick. More, more, more stuff.
Why did the, why did the grenade take so long to go off?
What? Is he still alive? Is he still alive? You've got to be fucking kidding me.
That was fucking crazy. Uh, no, wait. There's another door. Where is this one? All right.
Fuck face. This game is great by the way. This is wonderful. Wait, can I, hold on.
I, I need, okay. Here we go. Oh shit. Oh my God. It's right behind me. Oh man.
How the fuck? Oh my goodness gracious. Can they see me? Hey, stop firing. I got your friend right
here. Stop firing. Stop firing. I got your buddy right here. Stop firing. Okay. Nevermind.
Let's go. Okay. Where are they coming out? In there. Fuck you. Like a fucking cockroach.
I'm just like impossible to get like tilt. It's just like there. Where'd it go? Where'd it go?
Did it go behind the couch? I don't believe that spider go. I don't know. I'm dead. Okay.
You play like a rat would play. Yeah. That's what I mean. It's just like,
I'm like a squirrel that got in the room. What the hell? Why did a fucking bomb just go off?
How come I can't do my slow down anymore? It's in a queue. Did they take it away from me?
I have to fucking try to do this. Oh, I have like no ammo. All right. All right. All right.
All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm having too much fun being a fucking weirdo.
Oh, fuck. Okay. This is hard. So I said the assault rifle is terrible.
This is a gug at a game. You shouldn't be standing still. I, yeah, I know, but I need to,
I don't have any charge. I'm going to turn the brightness up as well too. All right. Hold on.
Why did I just pick this up? There's too many of them. There's too many of them.
That guy's covered in our armor. Get away from me with that thing on your back.
Get away from me with that thing on your back. Get away from me with that thing on your back.
I ran into fucking bullets. I'm just going this way. Fuck it. No, give me that. Blow up already.
God damn it. Holy shit, dude. Oh my God. Somebody help me. Oh, no. Give me your gun. Give me your
gun. Stop floating around. Stop. Oh my God. All right. Here we go. Close the door. What the fuck?
This guy's going to blow. Okay. I'm good. Was he alive? I thought he blew up. Hold on.
We get to go up a little bit higher. What the hell just happened? I got ammo. I got ammo.
What the fuck, dude? Dude, I just made popcorn. I didn't even fucking hurt the guy.
What the? Oh my. Okay. Can I put it down to normal for a second? Holy shit. This is crazy.
This is a boss fight. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm just going to sit right here
and I'm going to grab them when they get over here. Oh, fuck. Got it. Oh shit.
Okay. Got him. Where'd he go? No, don't die. Oh my God. One left. One left. One left. I got it. I
got it. I got it. I got it. Got him. Holy shit. That was fucking wild. 106 is approaching the
hell. I remember this part. I remember this is the demo and then I thought these were enemies.
I fucking shot this guy. We're going to get you out of here. Don't do that again. I killed this
guy. I thought they were not. I mean, after that, come on, do it again. Sorry. I did a lot of
screaming back there. It's time. I got to pull it back. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't. There's
an achievement. There are consequences. No, I'm not doing it. There was at least four or five voice
cracks during that as well and I'm very embarrassed by it. It happens to everybody. All right. I bet
you couldn't even point out where Tripp Hang is on a map. No, I couldn't. Okay.
So now that that's the kind of tutorial for zone, that's the demo. What do you do from here?
It's a very pretty game, I will say, and it runs really well. Something I think developers that
make games like this, it runs very well. It's like, it's pretty smooth. Do you have a 3090? Yeah. Is
it how is 3090 still considered like good? How much more powerful is the 4090 compared to the 3090?
Because I usually wait two or three generations. Should I wait till like the 5080 or like the 6090?
You don't stream in 1080p. Yeah. You know, that's going to change pretty soon here. The one thing
that sucks about having like a 1080p stream, the one thing I'm worried about is I just turning,
I would have to turn the bit rate up or I'd have to drop. I mean, maybe I'll just get like a
streaming PC or something. Which bit rate sucks anyways. Yeah. You have a 4090? No, I have 3090.
Do you play at 4k or 1080? If you're at 1080, you don't need more than a 3090.
Yeah, I don't play in. Well, hold on a second here. I do play in, this is, this is 4k, right?
Technically. Isn't that 4k? No? Wait, what is it? Two? What is it? 2k? That's not even 1440.
That's not even 1440. That's not even 1080p. Dude, that's better than 1080p. That's better than
1080p. Wait. Oh, oops. Okay. Now I'm playing in 1440p. Looks pretty good. Damn. Looks nice.
Yeah. That was a weird resolution. That's the kind of resolution that old, old games,
I remember like Warcraft 3, seeing some of those weird resolutions that they made for that game
that you could have for like probably eight people that had that monitor. All right. So
what do we do here? Cheats. Complete mission on hard. All right. So I have to beat all these
missions on hard and I get the cheats. Customize appearance. Oh, let's do that. Oh, hell yeah.
Okay. I mean, I got to go with the fucking red shoes. That's just a fact. Shirt I want to wear.
Can I see a preview? Whoa. Oh, these get kind of funky. All right. Let's go green. Green, woodland
and is there a green one here? Green. I got to go with the, we'll stay with the red. Cool. All right.
This is an awful drip. I'm not, I look there. I don't look somewhere. I'm like crocs. Combat
simulator. What's that? Should I do this? Oh, I just scared myself. All right. Where's the main
missionary over here? All right. Door Institute. We lost contact with our undercover agent in this
orazon. End of orazon. Like say the word correctly. Just do it. Prove that you can read that word.
Horizon. End of life care facility. Raid the facility and find him. I'm my own worst enemy
a lot of times because even if sometimes if I'm fucking around, it still doesn't matter.
Some of you will take away from this. Something's wrong with him. Can I take weapons or something?
I like this weapon. Tried. Tried what? This was testing the game. All right. Do I have a better
gun? I have a better gun to shoot that with. Dude, come on. I don't want to wait like another two
minutes before I can spawn again. All right. I got to disable that. Oh no. Look out. It's the guy
with the clown shoes. Grab him. Grab him. That guy's head was made out of glass. We shouldn't even
be fighting. You now. Go. Did he say hurry the fuck up? Where are they coming from? Oh, there he is.
Okay. Shotgun. Oh shit. Oh shit. Got him. Got him. Where'd he go? Yep. Oh, fucking. High value target.
Jackal. I almost shot the helicopter. What's in here? Ooh, breach charges. Now do I blow
the door? Oh, I like this song. It's dead. Oh, look out. Shoot out. Oh, in the room with the bottles.
Oh, oh, I'm in trouble here. Did he get pulled so fast? What sucked him down? He was magnetized.
Holy shit. Who else? I think we're clear. Can I go in here? Uh, where do I go from here? I came
through here. Um, the guy you threw was a, what do you mean? Earlier. I've thrown a lot of people
so far. Did I, I don't know where I threw that person. Did I throw in the pool? What about him?
The glass roof. Oh, okay. That was this way. Can I not go? How do I get out here? I don't think you
do. Wait, did I actually throw the guy? Did I need a key or something from the guy I threw over there?
That you mean over there? No, no, I don't think so. I think I just got on the wrong way. Wait,
really? Shoot all the glass? I don't think so. There's a breach charge. Uh, hold on. Keep going
up this event. Um, can I just? Yeah. Underground. Oh, wait a minute. The walls aren't concrete. You
don't have a, you don't have an excuse this time. Yep. I may have thrown the guy that had the item
I needed across the wall that I can't. Is it over there? That's a breach charge right there,
isn't it? Right there. That's a charge. Okay. Well, I'll just reload. Okay. We're good.
I'm all right. I'm going to fuck you up. All right. Where's the item? Let me in that room too.
Let me in that room. Oh, those are my friends. Shit. I'm sorry. Well, the grenade bounced off
the back of his head, so he's, he'll have a welt. He'll be okay. Ooh, I'll go with that. Any, uh,
customization options for the other stuff? Fold it up. Let's go. I need more gun parts. Whoa, dude.
Whoa, hold on. Nice. Ooh, what is that? That's a sniper rifle. You were the only person left, man.
I'm going to cover me. I got to get a no scope headshot. That's the only way I'll be happy.
Look at the DPS meters. He ain't doing shit. You all right? All right. We got to go in together
on with me and on me. One, two, three, go. Who's saying that? Oh, it's the radio.
I thought it was one of these guys. How's everybody doing tonight? We having fun or what?
You play video games like my dad, bro. I'm almost 40. All right. This is just the way it is. This is
how it's going to be going forward. And I'm sorry. This is the way it is.
He's here. He's trapped. What? No, I was going to stealth. There's one more person in here.
Yeah, whatever. Wait, this is, this is, somebody said this is Kickstarter.
Is it? Wait, what do you mean Kickstarter? Was this game a Kickstarter? You'll never beat me.
He just punched. That guy was jabbing me in the chin. Ooh, weapon parts, the presser.
What about the sniper rifle? Somebody's still here. Who is it? You? It's not you. Is it, man?
No way. Shotgun suppressor. I think that's the most counterintuitive,
counterproductive thing to put on a shotgun. Does this actually do anything? Does it actually
work? I feel like you can't suppress the sound of a shotgun. It makes it sound cool. This person's
been looking for me this whole time. Communicating on the radio. OK, let's, we have to examine this
guy for a little while. I wish there was a cough button. Is he in there? Is he in the what? No,
grab him. Is he in there? What do you mean mouse five grenade? Be careful here. That doesn't
consume your grenades, by the way. That's actually kind of crazy. I need more ammo. I'm for the boss
fight. I'm going to use the sniper rifle only. That's the boss killer weapon for sure. 100%.
I got one of those too. Yeah. Oh, that doesn't hurt you. It's just you two assholes left.
God damn it. How do I get rid of these guys? Oh, oh, these guys have got concrete bodies.
You didn't hear anything. Only they had a weak spot. Yeah, I shot the
fire extinguishers off their backs and they didn't die. I'm going to do this slow.
Why is he laughing at me? God blow up, blow up, please blow up, please. Oh, this guy.
Seriously, dude, the guys got a jet pack on now. Hold on, I got to take a sip of this.
Can you tackle them? I don't think those guys fall down if you tackle them too heavy.
All right. I'm just going in. Fuck it. Fuck everybody in this room. Watch out. I'm going to
hide in here for a sec. Oh my God. They get, they're going to get hit by those. They're going to be
stupid and they're going to walk into that. Watch this. What am I hitting in the way?
There ain't nothing in the way. What? You just aggroed more enemies.
All right. These guys are really hard. I got to kill those guys first. I thought he was going to
walk in and walk backwards and blow up. Okay. This one, I took that guy's helmet off too.
All right. We're good. Better. Oh my God. There we go. That's better. Show yourself.
That guy was just talking. Okay. He's dead. I need this health on them. No, I got,
I got a full recharge. I'm good. Is there any other ammo I can grab here though?
I feel like I need it bad. I guess I can just take this and run around. Does this help me?
Pistol's really good. The pistol does seem really good. Doesn't it? All right. I got enough.
Now don't die in here. Where's this guy? One more over there.
There's nowhere to go. Okay. Don't run around like that here. No way. I want to, why can I not?
I can't grab them. I was trying to grab them. Oh no. Charles. Oh no. What the hell was that?
Somebody rock across the tripwire. I, I don't know. All right. This is going to be hard now.
Who's here? Oh, I don't think I made out better than they did.
He's still alive. Oh my God. I thought that was the doorway. I thought that was the doorway.
I thought this was a hallway. I thought that was the ground and this was the wall.
Wiley Coyote bit. Yeah, seriously. Wait, there's still people here. Oh, that's the jackal. All
right. I got to be ready. Oh shit. They're going to throw grenades in here. I'm in so much trouble.
Oh God. What the hell does he have for a weapon?
I'm still sliding. It's not going to hurt me, right? Got him. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right. I had it last time. I'm good. I know what I'm doing. I know what I'm doing. I know
what I'm doing. You're going to think I'm stupid for this, but it's not stupid. Trust me. All right.
Now. Oh, this is hard. All right. Get me in the room at least. Oh Lord. I got nothing to do. I,
holy shit. Okay. Here we go. I'm going to go invisible and I'm going to run behind everybody.
I wish I didn't throw all three of my grenades like a dummy. There he is. He's dead. Oh,
that's so many people. Stop, please, please, please, please, please. All right. Stay right here.
I'm all right for now. Where are they? Are they in the room? I think they're in the far room.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. I think I killed one.
Whoa. That guy was just whispering to himself. I got it. There we are. These big rooms with all
the... Those are fun. Sliding under the flare was dope. Yeah, it's fun. I didn't even pick this up.
Hey, do that bit again where you get really mad and have a death counter that's really high.
No, you can only do that so many times. What's going on in here?
All it costs is a bit of your kindness. The Pandora Institute. I value... Oh wait, we're not done.
We're not done. Hey, I'm in here. You gonna walk over here? Hey, what the hell? What the
fuck was that guy in scuba gear? That guy was in a full scuba outfit. What the hell happened?
That reminded me of... I feel like I queued up a bunch of actions. We all queued up actions at
the same time and we all did them at the same time. That was like a strategy game. I feel like
I was playing XCOM for a second. Everyone just does all their moves at the same time. Is that
how XCOM works? I ain't gonna let you kill me. No way. Stop throwing grenades. How many grenades
do you guys have? Cease fire. That's right. Let's talk about it. Whoa! I snapped his neck. Are we
all done here? Is that it now? Can I keep going? Holy shit. Take this. He should have just shot me
in the head. At some point you don't scream before you're about to do something. Take this is
probably what you shouldn't be yelling. Take this. And then he goes for a kick. Is this kind of
fucked up? What happened here? One of those times I'm gonna get roundhouse kicked in the head and
it's gonna kill me and I'm gonna scream. Whoa. What's going on here? Okay. Now the music's
getting kind of strange. That was a scoring moment. It really was. You guys are right.
Instead of jumping off a cliff you can jump into his arms. What? Oh dear. 106.
Man of the hour. Oh hello. I'll get that elevator unlocked for you. Are you gonna die
right when this opens? I got it. According to the schematics this elevator is going to take you
straight to the basement. It's probably flooded with grunts right now but that shouldn't be a
problem for a super soldier. I gotta get back to my team. Good luck. All right well good luck.
Thanks for the help. Not dead. Yeah. Still alive. Still going. I'm just waiting.
Something's gonna. Yeah. Come on. It's an elevator in one of these kinds of games.
Of course something bad's gonna happen. What was that? Do not use elevators. Well I just used one.
That's a lot of blood. Don't use elevators. Don't use the elevators. Do not use the elevators. Do
not use. Take only one. Don't be selfish. What are these? Water? 550 for a water. What the hell
is going on here? Yeah. Amusement park prices. We're gonna disable this door. Can I grab that?
Oh. Take the health. Can I get through here? Oh health. Maximum over time. Okay. Wait. Didn't
tell. Patient exposure. Wait hold on. The effects on a human subject were catastrophic. Upon exposure
the subject's DNA was rapidly rewritten causing grotesque mutations and physical deformations.
The subject was immediately transformed. Its skin took on a sickly green hue becoming blistered
and swollen oozing a thick green liquid. Okay. Okay. Can I open this door? Abandoned move to
Maxwell. Darwin. Okay. Oh. That was so funny. Thanks. I really was hoping it was gonna.
Am I the visitor? You know what? I actually do prefer the pistol. Somebody said it. I actually
do want it instead. To Dr. Clark. Keep this off radio. It's impossible. Sterilization impossible.
Extraction impossible. We're already compromised. Relay orders to men. Enable lockdown. Procedure
disabled. Are we gonna get like a Satan face here? I would imagine a Satan face is gonna show up in
a second. We got one guy here. The one guy that had to come in here. What is that? A giant bat?
Okay. This just turned into a different game. I love how he's perfectly framed right here too.
He runs right in. Right center frame. Points at us. I see him. That guy's guaranteed to die.
Guaranteed. God damn it. All right. This just became a scary game. Conflicted scientist email.
The reality of our research pushes boundaries of medicine and science. It is essential that we do
not let personal things get in the way. Developable goals to save lives. Okay. Maybe I shouldn't have
taken the pistol. I want to go see the thing. I want to slow-mo that thing. Keep out. Does the
game have photo mode? I don't think it does. I don't think so. Did you just get me? A new special
infected or something? Okay. I was not gonna stand close to that. No fucking chance. It looked like
it was coming through the wall at me already. Mountain Dew Overtown. Doing that. Scary. Hmm.
Are we screaming? Sometimes during my use sound like SpongeBob. That's all right. Oh god. All
right. This is now infected. Got a mutated alien world or something. Jesus. Oh my god. Okay. This
is. I love how they bumped into each other though. That was fun. Get out of here. Wait. Can I grab
the enemy? Oh my god. Am I not killing them? Am I not killing them? I don't think they're dying.
Way to go. I'm playing Cod Zombies now. Sorry. I play it like Cod Zombies. Fuck you idiot. Why
are you doing that? Stop. They can't be right next to you. God damn it. Get it together. And
that works. I got an idea. Ready? That kind of works. Don't do it again. I can't be trusted.
Okay. I'm good. My accolades. All right. I think this only. They just keep spawning. So
good bro actually that time. Jesus. I didn't even know I threw it. I didn't even know I threw that.
There's a lot of enemies. I don't even have enough bullets to kill all these things. All right. All
right. All right. All right. Okay. Everybody relax. I'm going to take a sip of my pee. I'm not going
to sound like letting the air out of a balloon really slowly. I'm going to just do it. I'm going
to get focused and I'm going to do it. Oh my God. I missed. Oh. Somebody said, are those
trip hangs? Why is this guy just sitting here? What the fuck was that guy doing? I got it. All
right. What was that? You got to be shitting me. Really? Let me collect. I feel like there's a lot
of stuff I can get now. Can I do more damage on the handgun? I think those. Yeah. I think those
were trepang too. Those trepangs. I thought that was a giant laptop. It's you dude. You're the
trepang. Okay. I think I. Wait. No, I like the shotgun. Somebody was here. Go to the door. Blood
or no blood? I hear it. It's going to be another huge wave and I have no ammo. Thank God. What's
that? Oh, it's a shotgun. Is it better to take the regular shotgun or this one? Take the suppressor
off. Fuck the suppressor. Yeah. Suppressor lowers damage. I don't want to be damaged. It's the same
gun with layout. I'll take it. My mom wants to know if there's swearing in this game. I'm not
allowed to watch if there's swearing. I think there's this swearing in the game, but I think
more importantly, people's heads are exploding. So I think that's also something to keep in mind.
Jesus. It is a bat. Wait, we're just. There's. It's scary. What? Is it behind me? Is it right
behind me? There's no way anybody can do that. Oh, what do I go? How do I get out of here?
I'm sorry. I'm going to, I'm going to keep running. I'm not going to stop. Still alive.
Ooh. He has another gigantic coin. That's not what she meant. Okay. I thought she said, you know,
she said, destroy the subject. I'm like, okay, I guess does that mean, all right, where are we
going to go? You know what? I'm just noticing right now. My mouse is like, look at my mouse.
That's strange. Isn't it? I didn't even notice that till right now. Can you guys see my mouse
on the top and left of the screen right now? Or is that only coming up for me? Jesus. I'm
sorry. I probably scared you, but I scared myself. It is there. Hold on. Maybe I should put it like
exclusive full screen. It's not doing it anymore. But why did zoomed in over here? Hold on. Huh.
Wow. Is it doing it still? No, that was really strange. Has it been happening the whole time?
I think it has been. Not really. I didn't notice. No, it might've been. Okay. Well,
if you have a mouse show up on your screen, then just go exclusive full screen. It'll fix it.
All right. Now I have to destroy the subject. Anything else in here?
No. Wow. That's a lot of stuff. They are preparing me for a gigantic boss fight.
So let's go ahead and take, I want sniper rifle, sniper rifle, shotgun. This reminds me of that
VR game that stir and I played where our arms were wicked long and we were able to like put our arms
like behind our backs and like shoot ourselves in the back. We were like aiming the guns behind
ourselves. Oh, that was so fun. That game was so fun. That is so funny. Okay. Um, I can hear the
thing screaming in the other room. What about the sniper? Why would you pick a horror game for a
chill stream? Well, chill stream in the sense that I'm kind of just playing, just hanging out.
All right. I'm ready to go. Can you do, can you akimbo shotguns? I, can you, can you do well?
I don't think you can. Maybe not yet. You can? Not yet. Okay. All right. Uh, I think that does it.
Maybe is there any more grenades I can grab or no? He's, he's waiting for me to come in the room.
Okay. Boss area. I think I can hear his wings flapping running around up here. Shit. Anything
though? His brain. That dude, that's their full brain. Their whole ass brain is out of their head.
Not even in any more than one piece, their whole brain, the entire brain that was surgically
removed. That was not exploded or anything. Okay. Let's do it. All right. Cue the music.
Secure it. You want to read it? Get those laser gates turned on as soon as possible. Just heard
from the eggheads. Just one of those things get inside a reactor. This whole place is going up
in flames. Okay. Well, let's do it. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Here it comes. Maybe not
yet. Maybe. Throw them into the reactor. Is that a rocket launcher or something? No. Is it? No.
Okay. Let's do it. All right. Got one. Okay. Wait, this health over here. Just throw them out the
window. Did I? Damn it. I think I walked over it accidentally. Nope. Okay. There's like three or
four more of these. Another one in there? Oh my goodness. Oh, this one up here. All right. Get out.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Oh, oh shit. I have to run. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I just had to see.
It's going to be a checkpoint right there. It doesn't. Oh no, it's not. Don't do that again.
Don't do that again. That's me shooting the gun. Shut up. Shut up. I didn't throw that guy.
That guy jumped in on his own. I didn't throw that guy. That guy. Jesus. Get over it. Somebody
just. Okay. Go. I won't be an idiot this time. I promise. All right. I'm up. Go, go, go, go.
Slide, slide, slide, slide, slide. You fucking McDonald's shoe motherfucker. Let's go.
It's right behind me. That was actually terrifying. Where do I go? Where do I go?
Oh, we're fine. I don't know where to go. Chill stream. Hurry, get it. Fuck you.
Open, open, open. Where even is it? Man, that was crazy. Geez. Am I good? Did I make it? What's
the name of the game? Trey Pang 2. I'm alive. I made it. I have a feeling that thing's not dead.
Raven's on his way now. Maybe I did. Thanks guys. Okay. Let's get it. Don't walk right into it,
dude. What are you guys doing? What? Where to go? Where to go? Where to go? Goodbye. Where is it
going? Jesus. Got him. He's staring at me. There you are. There you are. There you are. All right.
Now I'm going to run this way and here we go. I want to get close as hell. Oh my God. I don't
have anyone slow down. Chill stream. Chill stream vibes. That's right. What difficulty? This is on
hard. I'm sorry. It was a good shot though. I have to pee. I'll be right back and we'll keep going.
I did unlock infinite stamina as a cheat. All progression will be saved on easy difficulty
regardless of your current difficulty. I'll be right back. See you in a minute. You guys ready
to go back? Continue. So what? What's next? Music's kind of louder than everybody else.
I keep thinking it's going to open automatically. It just isn't. I like sniper rifle a lot.
Okay. Okay. I tried to run. Is this a weapons cache? No. It's like a reactor down here.
It's fucked up.
Oh, he's so funny. He even blew up right there. Do the double drop kick wrestling move to it.
Press the button. Very well protected. I love somebody who just writes stop. Stop it. Stop that.
Are you even going to do that times 10 speed with the wild stream? Um, it's a good in theory joke,
but in practice, I'm not sure. It means no. Okay. Listening memories. She's not telling you
everything. Data package redacted. Upload complete. Not telling you everything. All right. Well,
interesting. Is this the only thing you're going to play tonight? I wanted to, I was going to do
browser game stuff, but this game is not very long from what I've heard. I heard this whole
campaign is somewhere around like four to seven hours long and I'm kind of into it. So I want to
play it. We'll do browser stuff at the time. Don't worry. What's all that? Main story is about four
and a half to five main and extra is seven. That makes sense. Hello. I want to get back in there.
All right. Appearance. This is the simulator. Go to the gun range to get guns. This is going to be
at least an eight hour stream. Well, how many, what do we have here? We've got one, two, we did
these two, three, four, but it's probably like five or six main missions. Yeah. See side mission.
I think we can get this all done in one stream. I'm not going to go as fast as I can. I'm not going
to just blow through it. It's definitely possible to do the main ones and then maybe one or two of
the side ones. Hack the servers and steal classified information. Hack servers in Horizon's
highly secure data center. Covered files from the Pandora Institute show Horizon is collaborating
with cultists. Cultists investigate the extent of their collaboration and destroy the cult.
Side missions are wave defense missions mostly. Okay. We'll do the main ones, but I do want to
I don't think I unlocked very much. Let's just go for it. Is this your favorite game ever? Check
the gun range. We got rifle, flash bangs. Hey, those are fun. That's why you're the super soldier.
Who's talking to me? Have some fun. Huh? Oh, thanks. All right. What do I want to bring? I'm
I like the, can I take the sniper rifle? I want the sniper rifle. It's my favorite gun in game
and that's why it's too bad I missed. Shotgun's fun, but we'll do SMG as well.
Resetting the range. It's fine. Folded stock and suppressor. Yeah. What does it sound like?
That sounds awesome. I love the way this sounds. All right. I'm ready. I guess I can take
armor and flashbangs. Why not? I get to keep these when I go on the mission, right?
Sounds like a paint gun. It does a little video. TF2 sniper. Maybe that's why I like it. It sounds
like that. All right, let's go outside. There's a bunch of fakes. You'll see what I'm talking about.
Does folding the stock give any advantage in a game like this? It's not like the gun is going
to bump into shit with the stock out. I think it was what? Recoil shooting, right? Here we go.
Faster reload. This is an interesting mission. Like a gigantic mansion or something.
Dwarfic Castle, Yorkshire, United Kingdom. Kill the cultist leader. Kill or capture
the scientist Dr. Kramer. Interesting. Plenty of ammo. I'm going to turn the light off. Okay.
Going down. I already have that weapon, right? It's a presser. Maybe I'll put it on the sniper.
Yeah. What game should I play? There's not much time left. This one. That's a lazy answer.
Is it though? This is a new game that just came out. It's very good. It's action packed.
It's not that long. I think that was a perfect answer. Okay. This brain came out. It's full
brain. His full brain is indestructible. What the hell was that? Eat shit. Oops.
Where are they? Where are they? What did that guy just do?
All right. That was pretty sick. I'm not going to lie. You're going to land here. What kind
of weapons do these guys have? Shotguns. Oh, that one looks different. No, it's not.
Enforcer 106. Take the brain with you. It's like left for dead gnome mission. Are they here?
Nobody here? Game looks sick. I would tell you it is sick. Didn't tell. Beware. Like those you
destroy, you too shall become. I'm having fun with it so far. I think the only real complaint
that you could have is it's not that long from everything that I've been shown, but they're
there. This is it right here. Can I get this right now? It's this guy right here. This is the guy.
That's the guy. Oh, wait. Yeah. Also, I'm also a proponent of length is not determined if a
game is any good. I would rather have a really fun, really polished, like six to 10 hour game
than a just junk filled slog of like a 20 plus hour game. Where are they? I didn't aggro the main
guy. So I guess I can kind of keep sneaking around. Nobody saw me come in here. He hates Elden Ring.
What? Here's the hold on. Elden Ring is like one of the best video games ever made. Besides millennia
and we're done. Pre patch. Today marks my first day as an apprentice. I've left my old life behind,
including my job at Horizon. I made this decision not just for myself, but my wife Martha and our
unborn child. I believe that the patriarch offers, the patriarch prefers something not that my old
life could not true. Somebody else can read. All right. They're here somewhere. That guy's still
alive. I only shot that guy in the groin. I could, that guy threw up in the balcony, did like four
Tony Hawk pro skater moves. Oh, I fucked him up so bad. He's up there. I don't think he knows what's
going on. All right. I'm going to keep going. His whole brain again. Got you. You dead? Oh God.
I'll try it one more time. Printer music? What does a printer music mean? It sounds like, what do you,
hold on. Listen, listen, listen. Oh shit. I still got it when it's still in the air. I killed that
guy. Okay. This sound, this you saying is a printer? Like an old printer? I guess maybe a little
Intel. Resets of 12 reps of pushups using the edge of a table. Resets of 12 reps of pull-ups using
the edge of a table. Resets of 12 reps of lunges using a stack of books. Resets of 12 reps of
military press using heavy books. That's how you become Saitama. So you become strong. That's the
secret. Masks and robes must remain on during PT. We do not stretch or warm up. We train as we fight.
It actually is bald. All right. Where am I going? I think it's this way. I'm now five days into my
apprenticeship at the cult hall. And I must say the schedule is quite rigorous. Rising at the crack
of dawn, praying for four hours, fasting and so on. It takes some getting used to, but I believe
it is for the greater good. The hall itself is quite impressive, but where are all the women
and children? Martha's not enjoying herself much here, but I'm sure she will accustom herself in
due time. I thought this was Thanos. Are you? What the hell? Are you? I'm going to die from this
motherfucker. He's going to kill me. What the fuck? This guy's super powered. That guy is super human.
He was literally unrecognizably fucking burnt. That. Okay. That was terrifying.
Holy shit. That guy almost killed me. What the fuck was that? He's stuck on them.
That was fucked. That was so loud. That hurt my head. We're just knocking a ton of shit over,
aren't we? Farewell. Farewell, brother. I once got to get killed by a chair, don't you?
I love this game. It's great. Okay. Now where was I going?
Briefcase. Please unfold this for the love of God. I'm fine. It's good. That's fine.
There it is. All right. What are you doing? The BLT stream? Uh, hold on. I,
hold on. I gotta pay attention to where I'm going. Uh, shit. Where am I going? I came down this way,
right? Yeah. Is this right? Yeah, this is right.
By the patriarchs. They're all still screaming. Hold on. I can get it.
You alive? This guy's so burnt. All right. I've had enough of that. Oh Jesus. They're spinning.
Oh, they were in like a carousel. That out of control carousel. Holding on
for their lives while the thing spun a million miles per hour. They're on a roller coaster.
Oh, I'm just going all the way. All right. Die. They're still alive. I'm just running up these
fucking stairs. Get away from me. Get out of here. Stop. That's the guy. That's the fucking boss.
This is the boss. This is fucking mayhem. All right. I'm just going up there.
Fuck it. I don't care. Follow me while I care. Come on. Oh Jesus. I have to relax because I'm,
I'm going to like fucking freak. Okay. Let's go. All right. Now go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That's enough. That's enough. That's enough. That's enough. He's right here. Dude. What's your head
made out of, dude? What is your head made out of? Did I get him? Is he dead? Oh shit. They're all
still here. I, oh my, wait, go, go, go, go, go. I killed him. I got him. I got him. I got him.
I don't know. Just go, just go, go, go. Just go. Just go. Just go. I already killed the guy.
Wait, he's still alive. Where is this guy? But he has magical spells. Whoa. You got a different
gun and this thing looks crazy. That was fucking insane. That was a lot of fun.
Man, get your hands up. Did we get him? God damn it. I can't shoot through this.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going. You sorry suck of shit. How do I get out of here?
How do I get out of here? How do I get out of here? Oh, they come to you. I can tell.
Okay. I got it. Can I do something with this gun? Two smart gun. That's funny. Kind of add
an ammo for this thing. Swap it. A ham, a full ham thing is still bloody. Can I eat it? Is that
gas coming in the room? Somebody said to do that. It was kind of funny. Somebody said, get really
close to a wall and throw them in. Kind of funny. Look at all this literature. Yeah. What are you
doing? That just didn't feel like shooting the gun because it was going to take too long to rev
up the gun, which was two or three seconds too long. And I thought I could just jump over it.
That's a bad place to spawn. There's a fight going on here. Here I come.
That was some Banjo Kazooie shit there. We're good. Don't do that. You just killed somebody
on your own team. Why are you playing an FPS? You've changed, bro. Oh shit. Somebody's talking
next to my head. That was weird. How was that? Did I just bounce back into it? I was going to say,
please don't. I need ammo. Ages ago, I left my old life as a soldier behind in search of something
greater. I joined not only because of my beliefs, but also because it gave me a sense of belonging
and fulfillment. Oh, sorry. I had a drink halfway through that auto fully automatic pistol. I'm
going to take it because I want to try it. All right. Where's game progress up here?
Where are you at? Where are you at? Oh, he's in this room. Who? What? What? What's that?
Like an automatic shotgun. What is this thing? Fresh. What's up?
Let's go. Who's on my team? Hey, you on my team? Are we up? No, we're not. Who's on my team?
What was that? That was a grenade. This is a grenade. Sure. All right. I get it. Who's on my team?
Hey, you're on my team. My precious. I get it now. All right. Give me that grenade launcher.
That's us. All right. Here we go.
Oh, look at this. How like orcs or something, but it's slowed down. I feel like playing
fucking Daisy right now. Just get him going in and kill him. Just like, can I get him?
He's across the map. Can I hit him? Oh, I'm not very good. This guy's still talking.
And in my absence. What? Oh, who's with me? I'm bringing one pistol in here.
Is the neti pot stream after this? What on earth are you talking about? What are you talking about?
I used a neti pot once when I was sick, like two, three years ago. What on earth are you referring
to? This is goofy. I like it. This is a goofy weapon now. I like it a lot. This thing's empty.
You are goofy. Hey, it's fun. What's that beep? I'm not standing on a landmine, right? I need a gun.
I'm not trying to be an asshole here. I'm sorry. I'm just, you're stuck on me.
I want to sneak up behind this guy and just, just to whip him in the back of the head once.
Can I do that? I hope I can. Bro, you had your volume up way too loud. That's like you thought
you were turning it off, but you turned it all the way up. Ooh. Can I do anything? Incendiary.
Incendiary what? Shotgun? Let's take a look at the intel. Dr. Kramer. I'm now supervising
the cult experiments. It's my job to gather data and assess if there's anything usable in
their insane methods. I report every 30 minutes if I miss one, or if my heart rate monitor goes
too high, a black ops team will arrive and kill everyone, leaving no traces behind. I must regain.
I must remain objective. Cultists are fanatical and delusional, but there's a chance that some
of the methods may prove useful. If your heart rate goes too high. So I can't exercise. I can't
watch. I can't watch tenant. I can't, um, I mean, there's a lot of things I can't do. It's kind of
unfortunate. You can't. All right, we're going to move on. Incendiary on shotgun. Oh, I don't
think I can do it. Can I? Oh my goodness. I can. How did I not see that? Thank you. This might be
hit. He's dead. Jesus. Uh, shotgun or, I mean, grenade launch. Let's just, whatever. I'm doing
grenade launcher. Can I pick up these knives? Ooh, cool. I'm beginning to feel skeptical about
the cult experiments. It's clear that their methods are dangerous and unsound and I've yet to see
any real progress. Perhaps they were not entirely honest with their promises. I'm kind of concerned.
I have no bullets, but it's going to make them count. A lot of health here. Okay. I have the
10 shots. This guy here. No, is it you? How do I get up on the stairs? Check the helmet cam.
There he is. Not just that. He's also a magician. Really? Where are they approaching from there?
Okay. What's up? That was a huge first shot. It killed almost everybody. Let's go.
Any more? Oh, they're across the way. I want a throwing knife. Somebody right in the head.
Wow. How many grenades are over here? That was like 10. What? Did you see the indicator? That was
like at least six. Whoa. You got to be kidding me. All right. Let's do it clean this time.
Where are they? Where are they? It's one guy just sitting in here in the kitchen or something.
Go back to the helmet. I think I might've broke it. He's right there. I think I broke it. Wait,
was it that guy? Here we go. Did you think we're good now? Yeah. Oh, right in the head.
He landed it horizontally with his back. Dude. Oh, I think that was a bug.
That was a bug. Somebody's still alive. How come your feet are glowing red? Because I got
the fire flower. That's why I just have a fire on them. It's a nice touch. They added it.
Where are you? Oh, there you are. Oh, Jesus. Oh, run. I got to bring you all the way around
the house. You're going to get stuck in here. Watch this. Hey, bro. He has no idea where I am.
Yes, he does. Don't let him grab you. Damn it. Oh, shit. I thought I was being sneaky.
I was being sneaky. All right. Well, now knowing that I need a different gun,
this thing has no bullets. Anything on the ground? I might be in trouble. Well, it's Dragon.
Gianni is carrying this entire mission. His work is so good. Oh, the voice work. Yeah. Oh,
you better believe it. How did that miss? It went right through his armpit. Where is he? Oh,
he's destroying this whole place. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. There's another gun on the
ground. Shit. Invisibility is so useful here. Where'd he go? Jesus. That's a lot of grenades.
Don't get stuck on that. Come on, man. Get out of my way, Ben.
Almost down to the last bullet. Final bullet. Nice. This game is intense.
I can't imagine doing this on something harder than very hard. If you die instantly in Rage Mode,
I feel like that's going to be extraordinarily difficult. Extreme was not too hard to do.
I wonder if Rage Mode is. I wonder what the strategy is to actually do this on Rage Mode.
What weapon is it? What series of weapons? Is that not the right way? Oh, um, wait though.
I ran over a weapon and I need. There it is. I already have a shotgun. Is there no other
weapon on the ground? I really only have one bullet to kill this guy. That's it. I swear.
I saw another gun. There it is. All right. Creepy. Jesus. So it's true. You really are
just like me. Question is. Oh, he slowed down time. You slowed time down. I get it. He's doing the
same powers that I am. That's interesting. It kind of sounds like somebody's listening to like a
really intense movie in the other room. I'll take this thing. Look at this thing.
Still doing browser games? Um, probably not. I don't think so. I think it's going to take me
all the way to the next hour or two to beat this. Dual Weld. I got it. Dual Weld Serum. I love how
you have to inject yourself to be able to hold two guns. That's funny. H. Find another weapon of the
same type. Will two at the same time. Boy. Uh, how do you shoot them both? They both just fire.
I'll try this for now. Two shotguns. How do I switch weapons? Dual Shotgun. I feel like this
would be great. Yeah. I'm, I'm all right with this. Can I even pick up? I don't think I haven't had
two shotguns here. I don't have enough ammo for it either. Yeah. I'm good with this. Dual Auto Weapons
of Insane Recoil. Find out. Don't fall down there. Who's shooting? I just kicked that guy's
fucking chin off. Come here. Come here. Come here. Holy fuck. Holy fuck. What the hell? Oh,
I don't even know who did that. I'm not even sure that was supposed to happen, but it did happen.
I'm not entirely sure what just happened. Got him. Oh my fucking God.
Okay. Relax for a sec. Don't you dare. Get away. Who's left? Dude, what the hell? Come on.
I was trying not to hit them. I was trying to have it bounce where their feet were. Somebody
said this game makes you really feel like a guggada. True. Oh my God. That was brutal.
I think he said, Oh no. I can't even react, dude. It's fucking too much going on.
Oh no. Geez. I'm all right. Fiddlesticks. Did he actually say Fiddlesticks? No, he didn't.
You piece of shit. That was so perfect of a throw. I hate your guts. I'm not even doing that.
I just did the fucking Luigi from Mario 2. I just pulled off a Yoshi midair. Oh, okay. Go now?
You want to go now? Wait, let me get all the ammo. I got plenty. I'm good.
I think those are going to fall down. Somebody's head came down here. Hey,
watch where you're throwing those. Somebody's arm. Oh no. Oh shit. Nobody else is going to come down
here, right? It's so dusty. What's going on up there? I think somebody just said, shut the fuck
up. All right. The dust is. Wait. Oh, two guys right there. Are you guys okay?
That guy was alive. They're getting too close to the edge. Those are our teammates.
Okay. All right. I think we can move on. I mean, it's still mayhem up there, but three stooges war.
What was that? What was that? That was like somebody's thumb. What is that?
It's somebody's shoe.
This is crazy. The loafers just got ruined. How much more men do they have? Oh shit. Are you all
right? I'm kind of hoping somebody lands down here and is alive. All right. They're actually,
they're starting to get smart. They're starting to get smart. What happens if they run out of ammo?
Can they run out of ammo? Where's my grenade? Hey, I got to get out of here. I have to move on.
This is going to keep happening forever. All right. That's fun. Sneaky. That was kind of fun.
Oh, they're done. Penetrator. Oh, what's that? Oh, no. Definitely keep this. All everything.
The actor is left. Yeah, that's true. Oh, that was very enjoyable. What the fuck? Somebody burped.
What the fuck is happening? Oh, those were my guys, were they? What the hell, man? What? I
didn't know they were my guys. There's the belt again. My game just crashed. What do I do now?
Hold on. I have to restart the game. This game is very good. I love this game. It's very fun.
What was that? What the hell was that? Was that the game? What's happening? Are we good?
Are we good? I think we're good. All right. Let's go. We're going to go all the way up. Whoa.
Come here. I'm out of ammo. There's so many people over here. What am I doing?
All right. Let's go. What are you doing? Get away from me.
Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way.
Here we go. Why has my gun forsaken me? It feels like I wasn't into Tom and Jerry, somebody said.
Dude, I need health so bad. I have no ammo. I have no ammo. I have no ammo. I have no ammo.
I have no ammo. I have no ammo. Oh, shit. Fuck you. Oh, I didn't get them all. Shit. Sorry.
Ready? There's way too many. Oh, fuck off. Damn it. All right. I got to get a different gun.
I'm using too many bullets. I got to conserve bullets. Here we go. Better. Keep going. Go,
go, go, go, go. We're good so far. I just launched my... Don't go off the edge.
Oh my God. Better. Okay. Assess. Assess. Get rid of that. There it is. All right. I'm going
to hold off for that now. Let's just use this thing for now. Autosave here. Okay. Am I going
down? High level target. Got him. Who's got the smoke? What? Shit. Oh, thank goodness. All right.
We're fine. Everyone. We're alive. Perfectly cut screen. It was intense and I did not expect it.
You know what? Oh, I thought those were green. Ah. Sorry. These are fine. You know what? Throw
these anyways. Get rid of them. What's up? Oh, he's right there. All right. Boss time. I could
do double shotgun, but there's not enough ammo. So, I'm going to stick with this. My funny this
ammo. I think I'm good. How far into the game are you? Um, I don't know. I could put a dual
weld on here. That's exactly what I'm going to do. All right. Let's go. Boss time. Today is a day of
grieving. You are the second brother I must kill. There's a lot of guns back here.
Where do you go? All right. We're going to just expel all the weapons. I just unloaded this so
much. I'm just throw. I'm just whatever I got over here. I'm just throwing. I just went through the
table. Get out of here. I just threw an axe. Good strat. Oh, it hurts. What the fuck did that guy
come from? Where did that guy? That is another one. Oh shit. We're right in the middle of this.
It's too much stimulation. This is way too much stimulation right now. I don't even have any
ammo. It's too much stimulation. I don't know. Is there enemies? Is that thing still alive?
Shit. It's all right. We're right here.
It's too much. There's too much going on. It's just carnage. It's just mayhem. Stop moaning.
That's not me. That's them. That's them doing that. Is that not me? I don't know. Am I doing
that? I can't tell. It's intense. All right. I got to do this. This guy's got to die right now.
Did he jump out the window? He's dead. All right. All right. We're good. I got it. I got it. I'll
get it now. He's alive. He's alive. Get me the fuck away from him. Freeload the gun.
Where is he? Yeah. Stop moaning. I'm going to be. You've been breathing.
You've been breathing so loud. It's an intense game. You have a microphone right next to my mouth
when you're sitting there gaming, when you're gaming it up real hard. There's no microphone
sitting right here. Just like, Oh, let's get every fucking breath that comes out of his mouth.
That was intense. That's one chill stream. I'm chilling out.
Stuff can be intense and still just be kind of operating at like 70% or so. I'm just hanging out.
What'd you do? You're screaming. We need to go on the offensive again. Yeah. But I don't know.
Chill mindset. Chill stream is a mindset. Yeah. It's definitely a mindset. I think when I say
chill streams, I think what I mean is usually no cam and just whatever happens. I'm just going to
play and not really paying attention to much else. Looking over chat every now and then.
The game is intense. That's fine. This means he's naked. I think I'm just going, I go into these
more when I say chill stream with the intention of being dialed down like 30% or so. And plus it
is 110 degrees. It's very hot out right now. So yeah, I don't have any upper clothing on.
Oh wait, I want to see the, I think I can do it from here. This site 83 Russia. So I'm going to assume
there's probably two missions left. The green from what one guy in chat said is these are wave
missions. I'm going to imagine another one opens up somewhere around here. Some of them are.
Let me, I'm going to go pee one more time. Maybe more than once. It's cool. I like these. These are
a lot like your older streams. That's part of the intention too is just kind of turning something on
and just hanging out and doing whatever. We do a lot of wacky kind of crazy shit here, but I don't
want that to be the only thing that anyone can ever anticipate here. If that makes sense. And again,
the whole off brand stuff kind of splitting up time between having a job and everything. I have
a job now. Yeah, I'll be right back. We'll keep going. Site 83. As long as you're having fun. Oh
yeah, for sure. Oh Megalel a job. All right. You're back. I am back. Oh, hold on. I forgot my drink.
All right. Let's keep going. Site 83 is the next one. Repurpose this former Soviet military base
into a research facility. Nearby civilians were evacuated earlier today under the cover of a gas
leak. We're sending you in with a small team. I do want to play around with the weapons for a second.
Where's that area to do that in? A deadly nerve agent. There it is. All right. Bolt launcher.
Rat bombs. Some of these you have to actually beat on high difficulty. Bolt launcher. That's what this
does. I thought this was a shotgun. Okay. It's not a shotgun. What else can you do? Penetrator. More
accurate and powerful non-explosive bolts. Single fire. How does that work? That was just a very,
it's like a magnum. It's like a Resident Evil magnum. Pretty good. It doesn't have a lot of
ammo though. Pretty low. I'll try it. It's a comedy gun. Does that mean I could have two of them?
You can't use two of them? Okay. I actually like these. Take the suppressor off. Try the two
shotguns. Yeah. Let's do that. Excuse me. That's an easy way to get them out of the way. I just died
in a place where you shouldn't, you can't even die. What just happened? I couldn't pick up the
shotguns on the ground. You saw me try at least a few times. I tried. My theory was I could throw
a grenade and they would get out of the way. And it was kind of true. We haven't done this in a
while. Ooh. Moody. Keep the red shoes. Let's do that. All right. Now let's go back to what I was
going to do. Shotgun. Shotgun again. There it is. So how does this work? Wacky. I kind of don't like
it though. We'll go bolt launcher and the double SMG. No suppressor, no nothing. But I do want this
to have the penetrator on. All right. Can you dual snipers? I probably not. Let's say it if I can.
Dual snipers would be strange. You could fire one of those quicker than just dual welding. Yeah.
That's what it feels like. All right. Let's go. Is there anything else you can do up here?
Or is it just these three things? Can I get in this room again? I somehow get this wrong every
oh there it is. All right. Site 83. Let's do it. I will say I do have a hard out in about an hour.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to beat the whole thing in one sitting here. I'm not going to
rush. It's a hard out. Somewhere around 830 Pacific I have to have to go. I think it's possible. Each
mission has been about 45 minutes to an hour. Ooh. But I'm not rushing this. I genuinely really like
this game a lot. So I'm not rushing to the end. I want to stream it again. Let's do it again.
And do the side missions and stuff. So don't worry. The next stream after House Slipper I
will finish Trippang. So what does the gas mask do now? This mission is pretty long.
And browser games. Well that would make a lot of sense wouldn't it?
Finish up Trippang and then do browser stuff. That makes sense to me.
Yeah. House Slipper is Tuesday. We're never going to see this game again. No, no way.
No way to what you said. Are you going to dress fancy? I might.
This mission is really good. Ooh, nice. They've all been pretty strong so far.
Sorry. I should be talking. What's going on everybody? Welcome to mission five.
We are ready. We're going to get in here. We're going to guns blazing. Make sure you follow the
stream. Intel. Emergency alert. All personnel must don gas masks and CBRN suits immediately.
Shelter in place and await further orders. Do you experience auditory or visual hallucinations?
Disarm yourself and report to security immediately. Jesus. Bro, you're watching TV.
There's no way you can see through that. You're watching YouTube videos through that thing.
I'm not going to tell on you, but like, come on, turn it off.
Does the gas mask mean I can't run for that long or is it my breathing different or something?
That would make sense.
All right. Who dies first? Phantom one one or Phantom one two?
Composer or Oracle? Who dies first? Me or me?
Let's, okay, let's get a vote. Is there a mod right here? Who dies first? Phantom one one.
This is Oracle. Composer or me? Who dies first? That's actually going to be really hard.
Bet or a poll? I think it has to be a poll because bet would be between two, right?
Let's do a poll. Bet? Can you bet with more than, you can add more?
All right, then make it a bet. Who dies first? Between the three of us.
Oracle, who is one one, composer is one two, and then me.
Well, now you got me all fucked up because now I'm gonna, I'm gonna be really concerned now.
The options are Oracle, who is one one, composer who is one two, and then me.
What if no one dies? Well, then everyone gets refunded. Yeah, they're doing it now.
Is it friendly fire? Yes, I believe that's correct. Part of me kind of hopes we open this door and a
grenade just kills all three of us. Then we're gonna have to go frame by frame and see who
exploded into guts first. People saying like, oh, what if we, we can just look it up? Yeah.
I'm in this too. I've died probably 40 or 50 times so far in this game.
In the, in the gameplay walkthrough, it does not say, hey, and then streamer German985 walks
down the hallway and gets hit in the head with an axe. All right, good luck. Imagine, imagine betting
on fucking Oracle. Couldn't even go through the door, right? I thought that just killed me
for some reason. What was that? Okay, I thought he disappeared. Hey, get out of the way. 31, 33,
and 36%. Wow. Oh, my fucking heart attack. That 83 was formerly a Soviet military base.
I still got everybody. Oracle, composer. This door is automated. See if you can find a generator.
We'll keep this always. I'm not gonna die at the exact same time. These motherfuckers set up flood
lights, but they don't have the common decency to change a fucking light bulb.
They're both going to die off camera. They're both going to die off camera. But who screams first?
Who screams first? It's going to be composed. It's going to be like,
and then fucking Phantom's going to be like, no, composer. One member of the security team
is unaccounted for. Here we go. The guy's running faster than an F1 car. That's scary.
I thought his name was Oracle. What'd I say? Phantom? I don't even have their names right.
Oh, yeah. Phantom. That's a pretty cool name, though.
Okay. I almost just lost it for myself. Oh, they're Phantom one. Okay, right. Phantom is
like the name of the unit. All right. That's what it was. I'm actually really intrigued.
Who gets grabbed by the monster first? Are we good? Where'd they go? Can we identify them?
Are they alive? We would have heard them on the radio. That's a lot of blood. All right.
Get the forensics. Is this Oracle's blood here? Whose blood is this? What time did they die?
I saw somebody. I saw a body on the ground. Jesus Christ. Don't run. What do you mean don't run?
Can't kill them. So I'm hallucinating. I think they're blind. Don't run. Move silently. Oh,
you got to be kidding me. Crystal physically pulling and absorbing several objects within
close proximity. I'm not sure where they're taken to. There's several cameras inside and
they continue to transmit from the location at least a thousand miles away. Thousands of miles
away. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? It's coming down.
What do I do? Okay. I know what to do. You just said run. That's the one thing it said to not do.
Oracle's going to go on the radio. I'm so glad I could see you. Phantom over there didn't make it.
Or whatever. Composer. I don't know. I met the guy yesterday. I don't remember what his name is.
This is composer. This is composer. I repeat. This is composer taking heavy enemy fire.
What the fuck did it come on? Did both of them die at once? I don't know. I don't know. We didn't
even hear a scream. We didn't hear anything. Am I going the right way? Yeah. Usually there's a
yowl or something. Yeah. There usually is a yowl. Access attempt successful uploading. Data package.
Upload complete. Incoming transmission. Bunch of swears. User identified. Subject 106.
Your mission is nearing completion. Will it end on your terms or theirs? Who is sending us these
things? Yeah. Usually there's a yowl. Can I move this? It was activated somehow. That's not good.
And it gets worse. PA system said there is some unauthorized activity in the loading bay.
Think we ought to check it out.
What the fuck is that? Don't let him near the console.
Did you say that? Don't. Hey. My last breath. Don't let him near the console. Uh oh. Is he
going to be okay? Yeah. They're going to be fine. I'm going to get jumpscare grabbed by one of these.
Wait. Who is that? I. How did you knock it? You know there's monsters around here. You should
be using suppression things. You're going to attract the monster. You guys are attracting the
monster. You are attracting the monster. You idiots. Why are you firing so? But okay.
Are they still alive? We don't know if that was them in the room. Hold on. We need to confirm this.
You died first. But we're not sure though. We're not sure. How's this for strange activity?
First confirmed death? No, no, no. That's not how it works. Not yet. Not yet. We need to know if
they died first. That's not how time works. They may have been dead from the very beginning.
I think one of them was on the ground. Possibly. We got to confirm it. I hear the whisperings.
Let's cope. Even if it is cope, we need to confirm it. I agree with you. It very well could be me.
What if they're MIA forever? I don't know. Is it confirmed? I hate this. Am I even going the right
way? No. This way? This room is so bright. It's hard to see. Oh, okay. What is that? Something
sprinting around? If he gets to the end and those two dudes are still alive, then he died first.
How are we ever going to know? Something is sprinting around out here. Okay. It's just that.
What the hell is going on? What's wrong with my bitrate? Do I have to do something here?
What the fuck just happened? Okay. So I'm hallucinating right now. That's what's going on.
Um, this is back rooms? Actual back rooms? Hold on. Do not enter. I'm going in. Nevermind.
Uh, what's going in here? I thought that was a really cool Fortnite weapon. These posters again.
Oh, fuck you. I can't go through this glass. I don't like this. Something is running. Come on.
What's that? Something's red over there. What is that thing? This actually sucks. This actually
is very scary. Oh, who is it? Who is it? Who is it? Do we have an ID? We have an ID. You still
died first. They died after you. Hold on. We don't know that. I don't know who that is. Oh,
it's just a radio playing scary Halloween CDs. Come on, dude. I'm never betting channel points
ever again. No, we'll pay it out. It needs to be confirmed. All right. Auto save. Holy shit.
This dude pogged his pants. Oh, what the fuck? It just knows where I am. I thought if I stop
doing that. Oh, it's that hand again. Stop doing that. Oh, yeah. All right. Get the intel.
Take a bath. Just paranoid that if I'm going to run. I've heard the sound effects this whole time.
Well, very obviously we got here. This is still fine. I like these weapons. I'm going to keep them.
Find me? The hell does that mean? Somebody just used that. When I find, what do I do? Okay. Where
am I trying to go? This way. Don't do it. Are you crouching? Uh, no, this is the character's height.
Phantom 2-1. That's Phantom 2-1. Do we wait? It's 2-1. I wonder if they're going to be down there.
We need 1-2 and 1-1. I pressed it, right? Is there no power or something? I do. Do you have any idea
where 1-1 and 1-2 is? I need to confirm if they died. I had a bet. He's got the autopsy report.
Oh shit. Phantom. Wait, it's not you guys. It was them. If it was them, that would have been so
fucking funny. That would have been unbelievably funny. I don't think there would have been another
funnier clip on this channel if I just unloaded and killed them both. Uh, all right. Now what?
Drop down here? No way, right? I guess so. What was that? There was somebody in there.
That was weird. Static. The expedition team members and all camera feeds were cut.
Gas lamps went off. Everyone's waiting to get gas masks. Weird. Oh. Uh, yeah. What can I do for you?
Boy. Somebody's in here. Erm, what's going on here? I like the erm. All right. I just
remember playing Call of Duty. Black Ops. And there would be people running around like this.
And they would be playing the way that this game is actually played. In fast motion. And they would
kill that many people in a room. Weird carpet. God. I'm thinking about just sprinting. It just
disappeared. Oh, stop it. What the hell was that? Did you see that? I saw it. I saw it. I saw it.
All the time. I saw it. You right here. Found you. Oh, let me play Call of Duty for a second.
Let me play Call of Duty for a second. Make sure I'm like lying down on the ground. Is that a hallway?
Okay. Did somebody just walk in? I'm here. I'm here. Kill me. I'm here. I'm here. Kill me. Pretty
good, Arnold. At least a 3 out of 10. I like it the way they are. Don't. That thing just keeps burping
in my ear and it scares me every time. Oh, I can play Call of Duty. Oh, shit. I got out ammo.
Our UAV is online. Our UAV is airborne. What's that thing that was in the sky and just went
baaaaaaam. Why would you throw that grenade over there? Explain it. Explain it to me. Explain it.
All right. We're gone. You and me. If that thing shows up, I'm feeding it to you.
I don't know if you're going to want to eat it though, dude. What happened? Well, get out of
here then. Oh, you're not allowed to come through here. Only the main character gets to do this.
I need one, two in there. I don't see one, two. All right. What do we got? Okay. Double laser.
Composer? Oh, it's a different person. One, two, cauliflower. Did I do that? Did I do that?
It was quite the Steve Urkel. Uh, okay. Subject 83. Let me in.
Do I have to sneak? Where's subject 83? How did you not get hit by goodbye? Wait, give me that.
Subject 83. I don't even know where it is. Where is it? Maybe I have to shoot this. Can I control
that? I don't think so. Something's coming. What the hell is that? Are they all going to turn into
monsters? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
When they're doing that, I think I have to go press the stuff on the walls, right? Uh, wait,
can I, I can't just do this. I think that's what I have to do. Um, I don't know. Oh, touch it.
If I can get them all. There's two more. Oh shit. Oh, die. Oh, right in his head.
Jesus. We're still firing. All right. I got to turn these off. This game is chaos. It's great.
What the? We're good. The Jerma die first. Why is the bet still going? Uh, cause it needs to be
confirmed. We've not confirmed it. It's eight 30. Yeah, I know, I know, I know. I got to, I got to
go, but not, I can, I can finish this. This is probably the boss. Uh, now what? Yeah. Low's almost
over. I can stick around for like another 20 minutes right here. Where's this electricity?
There it is. Composer two one is not our guy. Yeah. If I get, if we get to the end of the level and we
can't confirm it, then then we'll just refund everything. Oh, that's a lot of people in there.
We still alive. Whoa. Oh shit. In my pants. That guy has a machine gun. What did he say?
Thanks a lot. All right. Any more ammo and this should be it right here. Right. I'm stuck on the
stairs. All right. There's one more. I think it was the one that was up here. Yep. The last one.
Oh God. Damn it. I had way too much confidence running down there without any slow mo. It's okay.
It saves it right there. Thank you. Right. Oh, all right. Get away, get away, get away, get away.
That had to have killed him. Oh, quiet. You're so loud. Oh my God. You have a flame thrower of some
sort. All right. This is it. Perfect sleep stream. Uh, I'm not so sure about that, but we are having
fun nonetheless. All right. Let me just get everything. Cause this is the last wave where
this might be the actual fight. Maybe I'm definitely gonna have to shoot it with that. That's
without a doubt. Any more ammo or anything? Oh, whatever. Just don't die. Let's go. All right.
They come from over here. Yep. I think I did okay. I need a new gun. Okay. That looks good.
So now what? There it is. All right. Turn this shit on. Did it make it? Oh,
shit. I don't think we can confirm who actually died. Pay up. Somebody was lying on the ground
right at the beginning. I don't think we can confirm who it was. And then I died. Yeah. I
think we got a refund. Send it all back. There's only one line on the ground. We can't confirm.
Cool. Crazy shit in your last mission. It's what a Ryzen doesn't understand. Yeah. Just refund.
It's fine. All right. We got one more mission to do, but it is not going to be tonight.
I got to get out of here. I've got to do some stuff before it gets to be too late. I'll see
you guys on Tuesday. Tuesday at 1 PM Pacific. We're doing a big house flipper event somewhere
between 10 and 14 or so, 11 or 12 different people, different streamers. Everyone's going
to make a house at the same time. They have about an hour and 10, maybe minutes, hour and 20.
I'm going to get a tour of each house individually. Then after that, I'm going to be dipping out for
about four or five days. And you'll see me after Tuesday. I mean, you'll see me probably on the
weekend. We'll finish this up and we'll do some browser games. But 1 PM Pacific Tuesday, be there
if you want to see the house flipper stuff. There's going to be a lot of house flipper streams being
streamed. We're going to take the house flipper category, probably as high as possible, the
highest. I'm going to try to get it as high as it's ever been. We'll do the sunflowers on Tuesday
as well. Well, all right. Oh, squeaky voices. We're going to play with these later. Spooky mode.
Okay. There's some funny stuff here we'll do on this coming weekend. All right, buddy. See you
soon. See you tomorrow. See you Tuesday. Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out as always.
Sure, thanks. It was very fun. I highly recommend it. You can make this game as hard or as easy as
you want. I highly recommend it. BLT? That's right. I do have to eat the BLT still. Maybe soon. Maybe
later. Never would have thought I'd like it if you didn't show this game. Well, I'm glad you saw it.
Very fun. See you Tuesday. 1 PM Pacific. Write it down if you have to or not. You don't have to be
there if you don't want to. You can do whatever you do. Do whatever you're going to do on Tuesday.
See you soon. Take care. Call your mother. Call your father. See you Tuesday. See you later.