You ordering Chinese food? All right, you ready? I got it, I got it. You want me to tell you what
I want? Here we go. Crab rangoons. Spare ribs. Noodle. That's it. All right, let's open Elven
Assassin. Stop killing time here. I feel like it's been a majority of this stream. Sorry for
everybody that wanted some more VR for Mind Show. It's kind of hard to work with sometimes. So I
know a lot of people may have left. Uh, I'm sorry. Just do what I can, right? That's all I can do.
Elven Assassin. Let's try it. Spare ribs. Oh yeah, the spare ribs are the best. Elven Assassin.
This is an early game. I'm sure it is. Hey, but thanks for sticking it out. I say that a lot, but
you know sometimes you come across shit that you didn't know existed in the first place, so
appreciate the support. Let's go. I'm ready. This is an early access, so some things will
improve along the way if you find any issues. All right, well this is wrong again. Jeremy.
Uh, I gotta change this from Mind Show to Elven Assassin, unfortunately. ABCD.
I like cringed people out of the channel. Archery platforms don't match your play area. It should
be not be used to play. Okay, whatever. Single player is fine. RPG, I guess. What the fuck is
happening here? No, the same shit that happens every time you play VR. What was that one? Oh,
I put it in the chat. Oh, you did? Oh, wait. Okay, ready? Graduate goon. Okay. Spare ribs.
Okay. And some kind of noodle. Like mulling? Yeah. Okay. All right, sorry about that. No,
it's all right. It's all good. You're good. You're good. It's all good. And some kind of noodle.
That was Kim. Virtual reality. Hey, pay fucking $299 to not have this happen. God damn
consumerists. Uh, defend the Elven town. Sure. Get the fuck off me. This is pretty. How do I play?
I, I don't know how to play. Okay. All right. Ah, shit. I'm not good. Not good.
Fuck. All right, got it. Wave three. All right. I win. Wave survived. Wave four.
What? Somebody climb it up here. Breaking in. What? What happened? Oh, my face. God damn it.
I'm gonna break my VR. Oh, fuck. Breaking in. Whatever. He'll be fine. He's slow. Just
go around him in a circle with a rope. This is just mind show. They're breaking in. Come on.
All right. I've got it. I'm good. I'm good. Oh, that was good. Good. Breaking in.
Full of fire. Is this the whole game? Breaking in.
Shit. Who's left? Who's even left? Can I go over there? Oh, I'm so good at video games. You have
no idea. Watch this. Watch this one. Just fucking feast your eyes on this shit. Just zoom in on this.
Just fucking download that. Download this one. Breaking in. This giant jacket is killing me.
I'm not fucking this one up. Oh, you dick. Right in the head. Come on. Come on. Breaking in.
Oh, thank God. Right in the head. Come on. Really? Game's kind of good.
All right. Let's summon Jax for this one. Ready?
Fuck. Come on. This stupid giant.
All right. I'm done. I'm done with this one. I'm done. We're moving on.
This is fun. This is fun to do this. God damn it. I'm done. I'm off. Get me out of here.
Not anymore. We're done. Breaking in. Oh, I got it. Not yet. Not yet. Horror game? No,
not right now. You don't really... Horror? Ugh. Fine. Let's do Dreadhalls. Can I beat the game?
We'll find out. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR 5 community stuff. I didn't lie. I did do it.
All right. So the title of the stream is Improv Acting Workshop. And we're going back into
Dreadhalls. I feel like the title can stay. Let's get it open. You ready for some acting?
Are we doing sweat? Eh. It's okay. Uh, where is it? What the hell is going on?
Show sweaty. There you go. See how red I am. VR takes a lot out of you guys. It really does.
Where is my... God computers. Don't fucking buy them. All right. I've had a few drinks.
We can go into Dreadhalls. See if I can beat it. I'll give it a try. I will. Solid attempt.
I'm in the last section of the game. I should be able to do it. Let's get some courage here.
Dr. Steen 5 community subs. Thank you. I'm going to wake up tomorrow.
All this hair off. It's too fucking expensive. All right. Dreadhalls. I'm not afraid of no ghosts.
Let's fucking do it. Oh, it's so scary. Oh, two headphones in this time. We're almost at the end
of this game. I'm going to beat it tonight. Two headphones. Let's go. Oh, it's so scary.
Fucking horror games. Shut the fuck up. How do you move? I forget the controls, but who cares?
I don't know how to move. I'm serious. That's the map. Okay. How do you move faster? Okay. I got it.
I got it. I know what I'm doing. Let's go. Oh, so scary. Monsters. What the fuck are you doing?
What's up there? Oh, these shit guys. I'm sorry. I'm going to relax. I think I said wonka.
Open for a scroll. I sat down and turned off my lamp once more, but this time the shadowfall came
to me. I didn't run. I raised my gaze and moved to touch them. They blended with me, agony,
freedom, despair, understanding. Shut the fuck up.
What do you got? To be judged. To prove your worth. To satisfy your curiosity.
All to be forgotten here, like many others before you. I'm not picking my ass and moving to court.
How do I get the fuck? What is that for? Did I go the wrong way?
This way? Okay. All right. Okay. All right. Okay. Let's go. What does that noise mean? Watch it.
This way. Shit. Okay. That's quiet. Oh, okay. What is this? What is this? What are you doing?
What is it in these hands? Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Okay. Okay. Hold on.
Nothing. Nothing. God damn it. Who's the dog? Jesus Christ. That was the best YouTube reaction.
Let's go. You can only sprint for so long. I'm going to go right. I'm not going to go straight
ahead. Let's go right. I need oil. Fuck. I have no oil. How do I have no oil?
Oh, God. Nothing. Come on. What's in here? Oh, give it to me, please. I've seen the pillars.
They shine and chant. Fucking Jesus Christ. Give it to me, please. Burn him. Burn him.
Why did it go up? It's being left. Straight down. Oh, thank God. Okay. Checkpoint. I can see you
now, reader. You will not sit. You lied to me. Whatever. Can't you hear them, liar? It's the
pillars. They are chanting your name. Whatever. Get me the fuck out of here. Left. Oh, yes.
Got it. Got it. Fuck yeah. Let's go. One. Two more. Oh, that sucks. Okay. We're going this way,
then. That's it. Through here? Let's go. Is this right? I don't think it's right.
Didn't I already have one? Oh, I'm stupid. What an idiot. What an idiot. I know. I know. I know.
This way. Let's go. Two more. Let's go this way. What the fuck is that?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. This is
hard lock. Which way? Straight? What is this? Oh, fuck. What does that mean? What does that mean?
Oh, shit. I don't know what that means. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Is it the lady? Come on.
From here? I have no idea. What's it say? This is very loud. This way. What the fuck does that mean?
What does that even mean? Oh, shit. I don't know what that means. Oh, my god. I don't know what
that means. Oh, my god. I don't know what that means. I don't know what it means. How do I turn
this off? Oh, I don't know what it means. Oh, my god. Just sit here. Oh, fuck. Come on. Shit. Oh,
my god. I don't know what character it is. I don't know what it is. Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god. No fucking way. Jesus Christ. The same thing happened. So I check. There you go.
You're such a good actor. It's like you were really scared. God damn it. Let's go. It's hard
to talk when these are in. Immersing myself. Ay, ay, ay. Jesus Christ. Okay. Well, let's go.
Tuber reactions. Let's go. Speed run. Come on. Speed run. Not fucking around. Let's go.
Get to the eye. Right here. It's gonna be right here. Stupid game.
Come on. Just get there.
What is that? What is that? What is that? I don't know what that is. Oh, I'm gonna go this way.
Fuck. Shit. No. Wrong way. God damn it. I need one more eye and that's it.
Fuck me. Come on. Get it. Beat this game. Oh, god. Come on. Let's go. I've never seen that monster.
I know this. What is over here? Is it the dog? Is it the dog? Don't be the dog.
You hear that? Oh, shit. Oh, some creatures are attracted to your light. Okay. Let's go tell them.
Okay. I'll be over here. I'll be over here. Okay. What are you talking about?
What? What is talking? Who's talking? Holy shit. God. Give me a fucking. Jesus. Fucking Christ.
Holy shit. Oh, fuck. Please, God. Oh, my fucking God. Jesus. That was terrifying.
Fuck me. P-break? No, I'm good. No, I'm good. I'm good. I got water right here.
It's empty. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's go. Let's go. That was terrifying.
Turn your light off. What the? Jesus. God. This is the scariest game I've ever played
and I've had a few drinks. It's fucking terrifying even with like four glasses of wine. God damn,
man. Come on. How did I end up here? I don't know. Why am I playing Dread Halls?
Oh, I don't know. It just kind of happens, huh? All right. Let's go. Fuck. I have the hiccups.
Nothing. Of course. I will. I'm going to beat this game before the stream turns off.
I swear to God. I don't care. Open, motherfucker. Oh, is there a lady in here? Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Let's go this way. I got oil. Oh, fuck. Oh, God. Get out of here. Get me out of here.
Jesus Christ. It's right behind me. It's right behind me. It's right behind me. It's right behind
me. It's right behind me. It's right behind me. It's right behind me. It's right behind me. It's
right behind me. It's right behind me. What a dumb room. What a stupid fucking room.
Oh, close the fucking door. Oh, God. Damn it. What is that? Who is in here? Don't open the
fucking door. Don't. Do not open the door, please. Right. What is that? Oh. Oh. I found. I don't care.
You're okay. Let's go. Give me the eye. Come on. Oh, fuck you. Oh, fuck you. Oh,
fucking streamer. Fuck you, you know. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Twitch Prime is a thing.
Don't. Don't subscribe with Twitch Prime. Who cares? Just watch for free. You fuck me.
You know what? Fuck this guy. This guy sucks. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Get him out of here.
Oh, I'm so good at Twitch. Fucking subscribe to me if you want to. Don't.
Fuck you. What's up? Yeah. Fuck. What's the way to go? I have no fucking idea. What? Did it open that way?
I don't know what's going on here. Fucking don't. I think I'm with the right way. Okay.
Gabe sucks. Okay. Oh, shit.
Oh, straight. Oh, fuck you. Oh, okay. Let's go. Come on. I'm at the end of the game. The pillar is
the gate between the worlds. Not for you. No, you have been tainted. Like all of us, your place is
here too, bombed by the shadows. You can't escape. You belong here. Oh, god damn it. Fuck you. No.
What is this? What? What? What? Where do I go? What the fuck? I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Please. Oh, please. Okay. Get them both. Use the oil.
There it is. You ready? I don't know if I'm ready. We'll find out.
Shit, it's the brow noise. We're all going to shit our pants.
Why? I don't. Oh, I got to. Oh, yeah. Why? Okay. Great. Good job. Fuck off.
Fuck you, wall. Get out of my way. I'm going right to the portal.
I'm going to sprint to the portal. Ready for this shit? Watch this. What? I'm going to beat this
fucking game. Watch this. You ever seen a streamer beat dreadholes on the stream?
Line them up. Because it's me. Look at this darkness. Find me somebody else. Okay.
Find me somebody. You're one of them. All right. Get in there. Go. Get in there.
Ah, what? Oh, I did it. Yes. This game was good. Get it now. Download this fucking game.
Seriously. That's a great game. That's a good game. Random map. Okay. Yeah, for sure.
Let's go. Let's go. Fucking random map. Ready for this shit. My brain's melted.
Who gives a fuck? I'll see you guys in like two weeks. All right. No. I don't get very much
stamina. I'll be honest. I don't know how people fucking scream every day. I got no goddamn stamina.
Zero. I can do this shit for like six to ten hours. And I'm out of here for like a day.
I don't know how fucking people scream this long. I mean, like, I need like four days off. I'm kidding.
That's a joke. God, do you get it? Do you get it? Don't fuck this. Ready? Watch this shit.
No screams. No. Whoa. No. Whoa. Zero. Beat the fucking level. Watch this shit.
What are you stupid?
Only stream on Twitch. This fucking website right here. Only motherfucker to beat this whole game.
Find me somebody else. Anybody else do this? Any. I mean, anyone else on Twitch. Anyone. Ninja did it.
If you find me another person on Twitch, I'll give you a trillion dollars.
Hey, taxi. Taxi.
Oh, look at me. I'm like an alien from Aliens 2.
Suck my fucking thumb.
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I got light on you.
I got light on you. Fuck off.
Loser.
I'm going to kill you.
I got light on you. Fuck off.
Loser. Loser. Loser.
Inadequate. Inadequate.
Inadequate.
Okay. Please go away.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Okay.
What is it?
Who is it?
What's going on?
Fuck.
5.8 by the way. Fuck off.
You want to measure me?
Sure. Next Monday.
Ugh.
5.8. Get over yourself.
Get over it.
5.8. Get over it.
Ugh.
Please.
Get over it.
I don't think I can fucking see you.
Whoa.
Close the fucking door.
You terrible video game.
It won't do it.
Why won't you do it?
No.
Oh.
You're the man. I'm the man.
You're the man.
Hey.
TwitchTV.
What do you think?
I can't get by him.
I can't go by him.
Hey.
TwitchTV slash fuck you.
I don't know what to do.
Making jokes to make yourself feel better.
I can't get by him.
Ugh.
Oh.
He killed me.
God damn it.
More wine?
There ain't going to be. How am I this drunk?
This is like wine five.
I'm fucking crazy.
Pee break? Okay.
I'll be back in five minutes.
Not even.
Look at this shit. Hey, have you seen anybody on
Twitch?
You know, I want to apologize to the fucking
thousand people that left.
Ugh. God damn it.
I'm sorry. You thought it was going to be
a better stream.
It's alright. It was fun.
Fuck. Like 1200 people left.
It's okay.
The view count doesn't
matter, okay?
I, let me get you a full body.
Full body. I am having
a good time. Are you having a good time?
Are you having a good time?
Are you? Maybe.
See you in a minute.
You guys are fucking awesome. Thank you for
watching. See you in two minutes.
Alright.
2800 people.
Hey, how are you? I think.
No.
Fuck that. No, it's not time to go.
Fuck that. What is going on here?
What are these noises?
I just beat Dreadhalls. No, I just beat it.
I win.
Give me my chair. I got my chair.
No, no, no, no.
Here you go. You guys are fucked.
Jesus Christ. Come on.
I'm trying.
Okay? I can't do...
I tried.
I swear to God I did.
Whatever. Who cares?
Am I sponsor going to get mad at this video?
Alright. So.
What are we going to do now?
My stocks are dropping. I don't care.
Jet Island?
It might be time to go
to bed. In like an hour.
Going is not a bad idea.
That's a good idea. What do my stocks
look like? Let me see.
Let's find out.
The stocks are up. What are you talking
about? They're flying.
Look at this.
What are you talking about? Look at this shit.
Are you serious?
Let's go over this because somebody said I was dying.
Are you sure?
Let me see.
Let's see here.
This is the last
week. We got a jump
right here. I mean I've
been on the decline. It's alright though.
This is today. One
day. Look at that climb.
It's worth a million.
What's my all time high?
Over here. 27 bucks.
Oh. Shares
to buy? Let's fucking buy it right now.
Bought it. I got some of the fucking
people to buy. Hold on.
Where's Vinesauce? There it is.
Vinesauce? 38 bucks?
Okay. Hold on a second here.
50? 50 bucks?
What the fuck?
Let me get rid of that. I don't want this shit. This is going to tank
in like fucking six months.
10 community subs. Thank you.
How many subs? Wait.
20. 20
from Sroylet. Thank you for the 20 community subs.
Holy shit. There was a lot of subs
tonight. Jesus Christ. 20 from
Sroylet. KW. What the
fuck is this bullshit? What?
No. That can't be right.
No. That can't be right. That
can't be right. Where's Kraken? Kraken
not on here? What the fuck is this bullshit?
Where's Critical? All right.
All right. I'm doing all right. I'm doing okay.
Is that what? What is this? Just hanging out
you. Where is it?
Come on. 2300 bucks.
26 bucks.
That's how much I'm worth. I don't believe that.
What's up with that? 30 bucks.
Joel's worth more than me? What?
Joel was worth more shares than I am.
That's fucking. That's unbelievable.
That's bullshit. How do I sell this?
Let's buy fucking 130
bucks. Come on. I'm 26?
Sell it. Unbelievable. 30.
What am I? I've got a pretty good jump today though.
26. Where the fuck is my
jump? No. People are selling.
Who is selling right now?
Look at this. This is one hour. Don't
sell. People are selling me and I can't
fucking even believe it. People sold after
the AVC joke. It wasn't a joke.
It was an experience. Alright.
Alright. I swear to God
I'm not this fucking crazed.
Your hair is your most number one important
asset. 26 bucks. I'm
worth fucking 75. I swear
to God. Alright. Let's do
one more Dread Halls
map. Now that I'm getting the fuck out. It's cheap.
It's cheap. Oh, that's cheap
today. I knew it. I knew it.
I knew it. No.
Don't buy. I'm sitting down for this next one.
I'm sitting down. I'm not
standing. Fuck it. Buying
in a bull market. Whatever.
Do you see this name? Wait. Wait.
Wait. Wait. Give me a second.
Insider trading.
What does that say?
The biggest... Google, Amazon, Twitch,
Streamlabs, Mail, Yahoo, Login, Streamlabs,
Teespring. What's down here? Regular?
The biggest waste of time.
No annual fee. Okay.
Give us a fuck. If
my stock is not worth $5,000 tomorrow
I'm gonna quit streaming for the next
6,000 minutes.
You know what to do.
Insider trading.
How did I gain viewers doing? How?
Why did you come here?
What are you doing here?
Like 400 people showed up. What did I do?
I didn't do anything.
God. Fuck it. Did you want to fucking
subscribe? I hate myself.
Let's go.
Let me sit in my fucking like streamer
chair. More Twitter?
No. I already got who I need.
I'm gonna be worth a fucking trillion dollars
in like six weeks.
It's the IRS? I paid
taxes.
Whoa, Texas.
Don't get me started on that.
Get off the fucking screen.
Alright. Are you
chumps? No, you're not chumps. You're fucking
valued members of the community.
Where am I? Why would I call you chumps
that's fucking not nice?
Maybe like 5% of you are chumps.
Maybe. The people that like say that you suck
and your streams are terrible.
I would give you like a D-minus.
Get the fuck up.
I don't need this fucking
chair. Where is it? I'm standing.
Maybe like 1.8%
of you. Fuck off.
The other like 99.6?
You guys are fucking hell yeah.
You're stupid.
I know. I know I'm dumb.
I've lived 34 years on the planet. You don't think I
know this? You don't gotta tell me
I'm fucking dumb. I know this already.
I have 126 IQ
and a fucking 60
performance IQ. I know this already.
I gotta tell me every day.
What the fuck is
going on?
I don't know what's going on. Hey.
Hey. Hey. I don't think so.
I don't think so.
What the fuck is happening? Who is
who are you? It's a chair.
The eyes of a hawk.
Alright. Let's go.
Did I do something wrong?
What the fuck?
Say it with me. Say it
with me. Say it with me.
Say it
with me or I'm fucking
I'm gonna knock every stream
again.
I'm just doing the same
thing.
The next person that says E is
getting banned. I swear to god.
I can't handle that shit
anymore. It's just a naked guy.
I'm gonna fucking grab him by the fucking
Okay. Goodbye.
One more. Random.
Twitch.tv
What?
I don't know where I was going with that.
I just said the name
of the website.
What is this fucking dumb story?
Are you having a good
time? Are you having fun?
Are you having fun? You better.
That was embarrassing.
Whatever. Fuck it. Who cares? I suck.
I tried to catch it.
Okay.
Alright. I don't understand.
Oh shit.
God damn it.
Oh god damn it.
Don't move.
Why would you do that to me?
Oh my god. I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die on camera.
I'm sorry I have to leave. It's really hot in there.
Oh my god. Are you serious?
Why would you do that to me?
Why would you do that? He's trying to kill me on camera.
Why the fuck would you do something like that?
It's really hard to contain myself. My knees hurt.
Oh my god. What the fuck happened?
Why would you do that to me?
Why would you do that?
I can't.
Oh my god.
I just felt the hands on me.
She's done that before.
She's in trouble.
I'm gonna give her a lecture.
Oh Jesus Christ.
You can't do that to somebody when they're in VR.
That's like the number one fucking rule.
You can't do that to
somebody when they're in VR.
I'm done. I'm gonna sit here
and hang out with you guys for a little bit.
Jesus Christ. I can't do it anymore.
Fuck me. Give me the chair.
Get this out of the way.
I'm returning this.
I'm gonna return the Vive.
This phone for a while.
We made her do it?
Anybody got a clip? I wanna see it.
What the fuck was that?
She was in here for a long time.
Hold on.
Let's see it.
I wanna see.
She was in here for a long time.
Oh my god. Give me a break.
What the fuck?
Hold on. You guys can't.
Before that?
What?
How long was she in here for?
I had no idea.
Anybody have the whole thing? I wanna see the whole thing.
I'm gonna die on camera. Is this it?
What? She's in the closet?
When did she get in the closet?
What?
Why is she in the closet?
How long was she? What?
No, she was not.
She was in here from the break?
I don't fucking believe it.
No way. 30 minutes?
I don't believe it.
No fucking way.
She was in there for 30 minutes.
Why?
No, she wasn't.
She was in there for 30 minutes?
She's trying to kill me. Jesus Christ.
Go watch the VOD. I'm gonna bring up the VOD right now.
Why?
Why would you do this?
She's hiding in the closet.
This is what I get for not having the fucking chat.
She's in there here?
No, she's not.
No way. Hold on a second.
She's unbelievable.
I thought she was ordering food.
Let's watch this. I wanna see this.
She's not in there, is she?
No. What?
She's gotta be kidding me.
That's so scary.
I can't.
Alright, that's it.
Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me.
I'm gonna fill the closet with concrete.
I'm fucking muted.
What do the stocks look like?
What do the stocks look like? Let's take a look.
Did I go up at all?
I fucking have nothing to say.
She was here the whole time.
Jesus Christ.
I'm doing okay. I'm at 26 bucks.
That's better than fucking not marrying many people.
Well, I think that's gonna be it.
That's a good time to go up.
You took off the headset when she started to open it.
Too early?
Oh, let's hang out then. Fuck it. Let's go.
I'm selling my German stocks.
Look at this peak right here. That's a huge peak.
I mean, that's a sell point right there.
Oh my god.
What a scream.
Insider trading? It's okay. It's Twitch stocks.
Alright, I got money.
Let's go home. What do we got?
Uber Haxonova.
That's too much money.
Uber Haxonova is worth some money.
That's at 37 bucks. What the fuck?
I don't know who any of these people are.
Oh!
Trending! Trending!
Nine bucks?
That's a fucking steal.
What do we got? 30,000?
Alright, I think I got a good portfolio.
What's my portfolio? Account.
Let's see what we got.
We got Vinesauce, Kiwo, Dr. Disrespect,
Forsen, XQC, Destiny,
Uber Haxonova, Mizkif, Tylo and a Ninja.
Where's me?
Ninja's all...
I sold myself right off.
Fuck, you're right.
It's okay.
That's a good portfolio.
I don't think that's a bad portfolio.
Is there anybody who named Mike?
Nine bucks?
What are these gains?
What the fuck are these gains?
Dr. Disrespect for five dollars and twenty cents.
Okay. I got a lot of Vinesauce.
I got a lot of Mizkif.
I don't know. Should I have that much
of Mizkif? I don't know about that.
I think that might be too much.
I got a lot of Kiwo.
Kiwo on the rise though, for real.
Mizkif.
Grillmaster doesn't exist, guys.
Look at back here though.
9.48?
This is going to come back.
Tomorrow.
What the fuck? Are you kidding me?
No! Fuck! No! Shhh! God damn it!
Wait! Really?
I want as much as I can get a Kiwo. I'm serious.
Look at this. Kiwo is going to fucking explode.
Look at this.
Already on the fucking uptake.
Buy as much Kiwo as you can possibly fucking purchase.
I'm serious.
Come on. Look at this. Are you serious?
I can't even do it.
It's fucking parabolic!
Alright. What time is it?
Ten? Fuck it. Let's hang out. AMA.
Ask me almost anything.
Let's go to IRL. I don't give a fuck.
I'm not done. That's better.
Just chatting. No! Fuck you, Twitch!
Give me a break. I can't believe it.
That's better. Okay.
Alright. Ask me anything.
I'll ask me anything right now.
What's my actual height? 5'7.5".
With shoes on 5'8". I'll measure it if you want.
Favorite YouTuber?
Donkey.
Yeah. Probably.
What am I going to do? Breakfast tomorrow?
Yogurt.
That's it. What do I think of Growmaster?
He's a fucking piece of shit.
He's a leech.
Whatever it takes to get viewers from my stream.
It's unfortunate but that's just the truth.
Sorry to say.
What's my favorite casino in Las Vegas?
Now that's a really good one actually. That's a really good one.
I have a real answer for you.
Are you ready? This is no bullshit.
The Aria.
The Aria in Las Vegas
on the strip, if you're talking strip casinos,
is my favorite casino.
I love the Aria.
And Circus Circus because the place is dumb.
But it's a good place though.
It's fun.
People are like fucking juggling and flying around in the ceiling.
Circus Circus is number two.
Aria is...I look like
fucking insane. Hold on. Give me a second.
Jesus Christ.
I'm going to get presentable. My God.
That's not going to fucking do anything.
Oh my God.
How do I get a Chad face?
Like this.
Am I mad at Kim?
No. What? It's funny.
Comedy trumps everything. Okay?
If somebody does something at your expense and it's funny,
it's fine.
No. Why would...she's wonderful.
What? Why would I be mad at my girlfriend?
For like hiding in the closet
for 30 minutes. No.
That was great. Only Chads have
kids. I don't have any kids. I'm never going to have kids
and it'll never happen. Next.
What's my workout routine?
I'll show you. That's it.
This is that once a day. Favorite fruit?
Banana. Nah.
Banana sucks. Um...
Lemon. It's probably lemon.
Why don't I want kids?
Because you have to change their diapers and they shit all over
themselves. That's it.
Am I a vegan? No.
Never will be.
Hamburgers are too tasty. I could never do it.
Steak and cheese subs
are the reason I could never be a vegan.
Because of Philly cheesesteaks.
I eat them like once a year. But that's the
reason. Would I eat lab
grown meat? Yeah.
Why not? I would try it once.
If I didn't like it then fucking I would fucking
delete my Twitch Prime.
Longest gone without changing underwear?
That's a pet peeve of mine. Not even a day.
I change my underwear once a day.
You think that's bullshit?
How could I prove that? There's no way.
Longest I've gone without showering?
A day. One day.
One day! That's it.
That's it. You used to be such a
meathead. Did you really stop lifting? Yeah
it just became too much.
I walk every day because I'm a fucking boomer.
I'm 34 in September.
Do you guys understand that? I'm 34.
I'm 34
in like a few months.
That's fucking old.
I can't go like throw weights around
anymore. You understand?
I can't do that anymore.
I wish I could. What's my
birthday? August 4th.
I did, I, that was
the, I told you I didn't want to give the
it's in September. I don't know why I did that.
Any conventions or meetups in the
future? Well it's funny you say that.
There is a place
in Las Vegas called
the Level Up Lounge.
Okay. This place is really
cool. They got like games. They have like skee ball.
They got like fucking
it's pretty cool. They got like a bar.
There's Jenga.
There's whole, there's like pool tables.
I was thinking
now hold on don't quote me on this. I'm
about to say it but don't quote me. I might.
Don't fucking quote me on this.
I'll be very upset about it. I might
see if I can do a
private party. Don't fucking
you dare quote me on this.
Where I rent out the Level Up Lounge
and we just have a fucking good
time. Don't quote me on that.
But I thought about it. Seems fun.
The Level Up Lounge is in
the MGM casino in Las
Vegas. And I'm like fuck
going to E3. What happened here?
Fuck E3. Fuck
I was going to say the T word.
Fuck like E3.
Fuck like PAX West.
No. Let's do our own shit. Right?
Let's do our own thing. Come to
Germacon at the Level Up Lounge.
This isn't real.
Like I hope they don't piss off somebody
at Level Up Lounge. It's a great place.
The place is fucking great.
It's a really, really clean, wonderful
place with a great bar.
We'll see. Come to Brazil.
I don't know. I don't got any money.
Germacon at the Level Up Lounge.
You can do a private party. We'll see. It might be fun.
There's a karaoke. You can like do
LAN parties. There's like a VR.
There's an entire VR setup
at the Level Up Lounge in MGM.
If you work for MGM,
you don't have my phone number but I might
give it to you at some point. That would be a lot of fun.
To do a full on like meetup
but open bar
and like open
karaoke, open VR setup.
I would just pay for the whole fucking
thing. And we could have like a good time.
If you're in Vegas for a fucking weekend, come on out.
This isn't really yet but it might be
in like a few months. Open bar is a
bad move. No it's not. It's a
good move. It would be
21 plus. Sorry.
It would have to be. Get
Penn and Teller. I would do my own magic
tricks. Open bar with VR.
I think that would be fun. It would
be. If I ponied
up the cash to have whoever
I mean, here's the thing I didn't understand
before I moved to Las Vegas is there's a
lot of people that live
in Vegas. A lot of you guys live here.
And in LA. So
fuck it. Let's do it. I don't care how much
it costs. Fuck it. Who cares?
It don't fucking matter. That doesn't matter.
If I can afford it, oh
you better fucking believe we'll do it.
Fuck it. VR chat
meetup.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR5
community subs. Thank you. You could do that?
I probably could. I really
don't think that would cost that much money.
Is this drunk talk? Not really.
It's more like just hang out talk.
You can ask
Kim. Me and Kim went to this
place. And we specifically
it was like how fun would the speeders do with a meetup here?
Because I get you know
you can do a meetup at PAX. You can do a meetup at
E3. No. Fuck it. Let's do our own.
Let's do our big
bits. Oh Jesus. What happened?
Colonel Zero thanks for the 50 bucks.
Can you pay for my plane ticket?
No I can't. I can pay
for the booze at the bar.
And the space. But I can't
pay for plane tickets.
And he said this. Kim Dang
take a look at Kim Dang right there
talking about it. Let's do it.
I'll call these motherfuckers
no they're not motherfuckers. They're really great people.
I will call MGM tomorrow.
Yeah. Let's
do it. Fuck it. Let's do it.
Let's do it. Quote me.
Let's do it. Let's do
JermaCon at the level up lounge if it's possible.
Let's do it.
I'm not really that
tipsy at all.
I am but not really. I
swear to God this is something me and Kim were talking about
like last week. I swear to God this is for real.
I was
stone cold sober
when Kim and I were talking about this.
People saying flush?
That's the VR helmet. That's
not me. That's being in VR
for five hours. Yeah let's fucking
do it. Fuck it. I'm gonna
call them tomorrow. I swear to God.
What's the food situation? I don't know. We'll get
like fucking McDonald's delivered. Who cares?
How much water do I waste?
What the hell is that kind of? What?
I don't waste water.
Confirm. Did I talk
about this last week? Did I talk
about that last week? Did I
talk about that last week? We went for
my birthday and he did talk
about this. He did.
I have like pictures of the level
lounge and I made sure to take pictures and stuff.
Excuse me. Look at the space. We're gonna
witness corroboration right here.
That's Kim by the way.
Hi. We're gonna witness
corroboration. I'm sorry I scared
you earlier. Oh my God. My knees
started to hurt so I actually had to leave.
Like I was like I need to get out of here.
I need to get out of here.
I was like I gotta get. I was trying to leave
like well I was just gonna leave but then
I started laughing too hard so I was
like oh I'm just gonna scare him.
It was bad. You just get the shit out of me.
But yeah see there we go.
Story corroboration. Yeah we went to the MGM
for my birthday and a couple other things
and we had a lot of fun there so we think
that people would have really
a lot of fun like meeting
us and drinking
and the bar was really like the bar was
really nice. The bowling alley was
really nice.
They had like a virtual VR set like
you go into the room and it's like all VR.
Karaoke too.
They had a giant Jenga
table. They had ski ball
pool. If anybody
likes to play pool they have that
too and what else. They had like a
like really hyped this up. It's like not
real yet. They have like a ton of space invader
games too like if you like to
oh my God. We're like hey
look at how fucking amazing the MGM
level up casino is and it's like
oh yeah. Oh and they have a photo booth there too.
They got a photo booth.
Oh and they have a bunch of painted
cats on there. Painted cats!
Are you kidding me?
No yeah they do. I have a picture right here.
Painted cats. No it's a cool
place. See? Are you sold?
They're the painted cats. Hey that's
what it looks like. We're like talking
up this place so much.
But uh you don't waste
water. Everybody knows that
they're just talking shit. You use a lot of plastic
though. Gotcha.
I use a lot of
plastic? What the fuck does that mean?
Plastic? Like single use
plastic? I put it in the recycling unit.
Uh oh. I'm getting compromised.
I
put plastic in the recycling
receptacle. I do.
Come on. Talk into the camera.
Tell them. He does
95% of the time.
100%
Alright. I love you.
I'll see you when you're done. Bye guys!
I recycle. I do.
I care about the environment.
I recycle. We got recycling here in
Vegas. I put everything. I don't know
what that was even about.
Recycle 95%.
You can't recycle everything.
Some recycling cannot be recycled.
If you've got bubble wrap
it's gotta be...
I recycle. I do.
Who's my favorite streamer?
Oh. Are you talking about
talent? Are you talking about who I think is the funniest?
Or what's interesting?
What do you think? Who?
Vinny. Joel.
They're always doing something fun.
Always doing something different.
Vinesauce. The whole Vinesauce team
always doing something fucking different.
They're always trying to make something fucking fun.
Follow them if you don't know who they are.
Joel, Varg, Skeletor.
Skelethor and Vinesauce obviously.
Criken
is always doing something fun.
Italics. Roommate.
Like, roommate
Literally is right here. Probably fucking sleeping.
Who else? Wake him up? Fine.
He probably heard that.
He's probably like, what the fuck are you doing?
Who else?
Who else is a streamer?
Fun streams?
I don't watch everybody.
He just watches
his own VOD start to finish.
Fuck off. Don't watch Italics.
He's fucking not even fun.
He's not even funny.
Honestly, Kiwo is great.
She does a lot of RP.
She does a lot of fucking character work.
She does a lot of editing. She's fucking hilarious.
Hysterical.
Go follow Kiwo. For real.
XQC is funny.
He's really just kind of all over the place out there.
He's funny. He's fun to kind of see.
Who else is
I think funny. Interesting.
Dance gaming.
Just OG. Dance gaming is fun to watch.
He's talking about his
investments.
You got me. You fucking got me.
I'll take it. I will. I will take that.
You did catch me
in the middle of my bullshit.
Star. Star. I mean
what can you say about Star?
One of the funniest, most talented fucking people on YouTube.
Still going on Twitch.
Still funny. Still interesting.
Give him a follow.
He's fucking OG. For real.
Who else?
Uberhacks on Nova.
Nova has been around for a long time too.
Moved to Twitch.
Still fun. Still interesting.
Critical. Critical is killing it on Twitch right now too.
There's too many people.
You understand? There's too many people.
There's so many fun. Look. Okay.
Germa985. This channel.
Sucks.
Don't leave now. Don't fucking watch.
No I'm kidding. Stay.
But there are so many fun channels
that are always trying to do new things.
Trying to keep going.
Excel. But don't leave.
Because I need you.
I need you.
At the table I'm going to spend like 15 grand.
I'm going to spend 15 grand.
How much is it to rent out
a fucking level up lounge? Let's find out.
Level up lounge
price.
That doesn't do anything.
Depends on the year. Yeah it does.
Grillmaster?
I hope Grillmaster
fucking throws himself off
of a fucking plan of existence.
He has talked so much
and his fans are unbearable.
Grillmaster x BBQ.
And his fans are relentless.
I'm just trying to stream
myself hanging out in IRL.
And they come in here and they fucking
throw themselves into the camera.
What? Gonna have to ban you?
Gonna have to ban you for
threatening other streamers?
Grillmaster doesn't even fucking stream.
Old joke. No.
This guy sucks.
Fuck this guy.
Who is he? Don't worry about it.
I'm not going to answer that question.
Ban?
I bet Grillmaster would be saving city goals.
Yeah this channel sucks.
Who cares? He doesn't even have a stock. I do.
I have a stock.
Does he have a stock?
No I don't think so.
I do. What is it at right now?
Not even in trending anymore.
What the fuck have you guys done? He sold out.
This is fake bullshit.
It's not even real. Maybe I should
stream better? I try.
Do I have any cringey old art?
How about some cringey new art?
How does that sound? Let's go for it.
No I don't.
How? I was quiet for a long time.
It's not bad. Alright that's it.
What else? What else you got?
Vinny said he loves you?
Hey thanks Vinny. You're a pretty good guy.
Explain becoming a tree. Alright alright alright.
This is important.
Everybody that was going to leave
has already left.
We had like forty four hundred people here.
Like two hours ago.
They moved on. They probably watched
that's fine. But the twenty eight hundred
people that are still here.
What is going on with trees?
You cut their limbs off. They come back.
How have we not
figured out as humans
how to genetically
tap into that
complete regrowth?
Seriously. Trees they
fucking grow back. They last
thousands of years some trees.
Imagine in a hundred years
if they can tap into
the DNA of trees.
I'm getting made photo. It was
a thought experiment. Never mind.
No no no no no. Listen listen.
Besides humans.
Right? Did I eat any
edibles? No. No.
Not tonight. Not any night.
Oh they got a picture of the black hole.
That's right. They got a full on picture
of the black hole. Let's take a look at it.
Black hole. There it is.
It's not boring. It's a good donut. Let's see it.
So this is a picture of a black hole.
I mean it kind of looks like what happens when you go
underwater and open your eyes and look
at the light. That shit's coming for you.
And it's going to wipe out everybody.
That's the last thing you see before you die.
Yep. Like a blurry
like the ring three image.
Can I what?
What the fuck did you just say? Holy shit.
Why worry about black holes
when your stream is this derailed?
I made that up. Somebody didn't write that.
I said that pretending to be a chat member.
How long has this stream been
six and a half hours? Watch
an old video? Ah.
No. Not tonight.
Not tonight. Do a backflip. Sure.
Fucking easy.
Fucking easiest thing I've done all day.
Any other questions or requests? Do a
cartwheel? Fucking easiest thing
I've done all day. I'll do two.
You want two? Fine. I'll do two.
What? I'm going to kick
I'm going to kick that and I don't want to kick it.
Get this off! I'm just kidding.
I'm so self conscious about this
hair. It's so bad.
Will I ever go to Australia?
No. Probably not. Look at the link.
What link? I don't see a link.
I see. Where is it?
I just saved it. There it is.
Am I looking forward to Game of Thrones?
Yeah. I don't know.
Maybe. A little.
Wider? I can't look at that shit for more than
five seconds. Alright.
I think that's it. I've embarrassed myself
for a night at least.
Mine show was a lot of fun.
It just technically had some problems.
Thanks for the stream. Thanks for watching.
There's a lot of people fucking here. Thanks for
giving me your time. As much as
I think maybe. Thank you.
I put raw garlic in my head?
What? I don't know what you said.
No for real. You guys
there were a lot of people here. I hope you had fun.
Thank you. We will do the
bits. I'm
probably. I said I was going to
do three days in a row. I might be
a liar. Am I a fucking liar?
I don't want to be a liar.
Now we're not done. We're not done. We're still going.
What do we got?
Are there any other games? It's late
but who cares? Fuck it.
What is it? VTOL?
VTOL VR.
Let me look that up. VTOL
VR. What is this?
VTOL VR.
Combat flight sim game.
You trying to make me throw up?
V. Alright.
I'll buy it. Fuck it. I'll buy it
right now. Let's go.
VTOL VR. Fuck it.
Let's go. Don't push yourself. We all love
your health is number one. No. I mean I had
three days off. You guys know this
right? I told you guys this
a long time ago. And by long. I mean like three
days ago. I take a
lot of time off to like
be ready. So.
No I'm good. I feel great.
What did Kim say? What did Kim
say? What is she saying now?
I didn't even see it. I didn't
see it. VTOL
VR. VR Josh.
No I owe it to you guys for
a fucking longer stream. I do. I really
do. I swear to god. I just typed
in VR Josh into Steam. That's not
that's not it.
No I do because you guys
you guys are fucking great. Don't worry.
He doesn't know. She's not in there anymore.
Okay. Kim's not
in the closet anymore. Look
I just lived like 30
years. I went in there and like
I jumped into a fucking another person's
body. I just barely fucking
came out. It was like 30 fucking years of a person.
Acting fucking one on
one. Give me a break. I could out
act Brad Pitt. Fucking give me a scene with
him. Give me any scene. It
doesn't matter what it is. Did you see how good that was?
My god it was fucking fantastic.
Setup tour?
Yeah sure. There's
a computer. And there's the other
computer. And there's my fucking desk.
As you see there is a
wine. And there's
me. Nothing else here.
Is this game any fun? Can we
see a bathroom? Yeah sure.
It doesn't go that far.
Is this installing or what?
Install the game? What the fuck are you doing?
I just bought it.
I don't know why this is not happening.
I don't get it. Show tax returns?
Alright. So show my asshole. Okay.
Here we go. Where is that game?
I just bought it. VTOL?
I just fucking bought it.
Where the hell is it? In
add to cart. What did I just buy?
What did I seriously just buy?
What? I don't understand
what I just purchased. I just
bought it. I just bought it.
Purchase. Your account already
owns the game. There it is.
Let's go. Oh my god he
leaked. Relax.
BRB? This was
30 bucks. I hope you fucking understand.
The things I do for
love. Look at me.
Look at me. VTOL.
Alright. Did we get Chinese food?
Did we get Chinese
food like an hour and a half ago? What happened?
Where is it? I
could go for some crab rangooz right now. Why am I
like 15 feet tall? Should
I be this big? I don't
understand. Why am I like 15
feet tall?
What's happening?
VR Josh told me to buy this.
All of them accountable. Okay?
Where's the audio? No chat.
Don't scare me. What is this?
The Chinese food I ordered?
I didn't order the Chinese food.
You have spare ribs downstairs and
you have pad thai downstairs too.
You just want one?
I just heard. A little birdie
told me.
Mmm. Mmm.
Mwah. Mwah. Mwah.
Fantastic. Okay.
Well, I'm going to leave these notes for free.
Can you guys hear this?
Why did you tell me to buy
this? Help make preparations
depending on the dress for personnel?
I don't... Negotiations for
priests? No! This is not going to come through the ro...
Why did I buy this?
I don't know why I bought this. That crab
rangooz was fucking fantastic.
Okay. I'm ready.
So what do I do? Fly.
Okay. Fly.
Align your seat with the...
Align your seat with the virtual
grip helmet when ready. I'm ready.
Okay. Let's go. I'm ready.
Where's the audio? What the fuck?
I can't... This is... I can't
hear this. Why is it come...
What? Nav off?
Hover mode? HD?
What the fuck is this?
Grip? How do I get out of here?
Landing?
This is too much!
Grip? Jenison?
This is $30!
Just toggle flight assist?
What do I do with this?
How do I drive?
All? None?
Go? Navigation? Nav?
No. That's night vision.
How do I get that off? Get off!
I don't want night vision.
I don't know what this does. HUD?
Brightness?
Why did you tell me to buy this?
I'm going to be fucking forever in goods. I'm out of here.
Eject?
Where is eject? Grip?
How do I fly?
How do I turn it off?
Turn it off!
Turn off the...
What is this? Eject?
I'm gonna throw up. I don't know
what I bought that for.
Try tomorrow.
We'll see. I'm okay. I just wanted
to play when not
drunk. That was a
good walk going on there.
Well, thank you for watching everybody.
That's it. I'm gonna go eat some
crab rangoons. I did not think
this was going to be a seven hour stream.
What is going on here? I don't... whatever.
Thanks for watching. Thanks for thinking
around. I'll see you guys
hopefully tomorrow.
Unless we sit here and have another glass of wine
and have a few conversations.
I'll probably be
live tomorrow. What the fuck was I doing?
In actuality,
I'll probably see you on fucking...
on Friday, probably.
What an idiot.
What a stupid motherfucker.
Like I was gonna do three VR days in a row
like four to five hours each. This is like a seven hour
drunk stream. What a dumb dickhead.
But, regardless,
I actually
had a lot of fun. Hope you did too.
If you didn't, I'm sorry.
I can do better. I'll try better. I'll try
harder. If you did,
I'm glad you did. If not, then I'm
trying. I'll see you soon.
I'm gonna go have some crab rangoons, but
let's do the bits.
Look, I look drunker than I am,
okay? It looks like somebody fucking
shook me up and threw me and hit me in the
face with a shovel.
That's because of the hair.
Okay? Look, ready?
How do I look now? Probably pretty
good. But like,
it's the hair. The hair fucks me up. I'm deleted.
But thank
you so much for joining me. I'll see you soon.
I hope you liked it.
I did.
I had a great time.
But, let's do the bits.
See you guys in probably a day and a half.
Because
Jeremy's 34 and drinks
and has to sleep for a whole day.
Took three days off.
God damn it. What an idiot.
What an asshole.
Thank you guys.
So, we had a
meaty-matey. Thanks for 10 bucks.
Especially with wine. What a bad choice.
But it was fun. I had a great time.
I had a great fucking time. I really did.
What a blast. I really did.
Uh, meaty-matey
10 bucks. Thank you for
brightening all of our days with your streams
and being the only person I can watch on Twitch.
Uh, thank you.
That means a lot.
I hope you enjoy yourself here. I really do.
Regardless if I drink
wine or not, I hope you
have fun. Cause I had fun.
I hope that means you did too.
Uh, Superintendent Chalmers, thanks for the 250.
Please grow a massive
Tormund beard. It would be a scarecrow. It would be
terrible. You wouldn't want to look at it.
It would be ugly.
Uh, Smelly Boy, thanks for the 250.
Desk infested by Gamer God.
I don't know what that means,
but thank you. Bake me
home 250. Less than 20 days
till Avengers. Are we excited or what?
Yeah,
kind of. Kind of.
It would be a good movie. Hope it is.
What wine am I drinking? This is a Malbec.
Malbec is my favorite wine.
It is the best.
If you can get your hands on a Malbec,
please do. It's good shit.
Jerma lied about stream
legends. What kind of name
is that? That's not, I do that
every day. Every, of the stream.
What are you, what? What are you talking about?
I do that every stream.
You'll get it at the end.
I promise. Door Cube. Hey,
Door Cube, thanks for the 250 Door Cube.
You are screaming way too much. I did not
raise you like this. I did not raise you
like this. You scream too much.
I forget every
skit I made in that
game. I hope they were funny.
Hahaha.
Uh, thank you
Kombino for the five dollars.
Hey Jerma, it's me Kombine. My
account was stolen by
someone from Malaysia.
Can you make characters have sex with each other
in this game? Do it. I give you money.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that, Kombine.
I don't think you can.
Maybe if you really put your
imagination into it. Maybe.
Ugh.
Hey Flugboy,
thanks for the 20 bucks, Flugboy.
20 bucks. Hey Jerma,
I thought I'd drop you a good amount of bids tonight. Hope you
are doing well and having a beautiful Duwang.
Duwang.
Also, really
I'm hoping Keem comes down
and smacks you after screaming.
She did. She scared the
fuck out of me. Ah, that's a Jojo
reference. Okay. Thank you
though. Thank you Frodeon Weapon for the 250.
No message, but thank you Frodeon.
Internet, Jorge, thanks for the 15
bucks. Nothing makes me laugh
harder and my day better than
watching the stream and chat devolve into absolute
madness. Much
love, Jerma. Much love to
you. I mean, you just watch the guy
like drink wine and get like drunk
and play a
VR game. And I made
a fucking ton of money. Seriously.
Do you understand like how
much that fucking means to me?
I can't even tell you.
I really can't.
I wish there was another way
that I could tell you that.
Thank you for everything. And
as long as you're having a
good time, that's all I fucking
care about. That's the only fucking
thing I care about. Even if
I feel like I need to talk shit and make fun of
it. Of course, we're all gonna
prod at the stream sometimes.
Thank you.
You guys mean more than you think.
Seriously.
For real. Never ever in a million
years did I think that somebody would think it was fun.
To like watch me
drink wine and like make shitty
videos in mind chill.
I
am forever fucking grateful.
Thank you for everything.
Seriously.
You don't understand how much that
actually means. Not only
Jorge did you give me 15 bucks.
But that message.
I wish I could tell you more.
How much that actually
fucking really means. For real.
I wish I could. But thank you
so much.
VR Josh.
Six dollars from VR Josh. One of the
resident VIPs.
Sorry about the technical difficulties. You handled
it really well.
VR streaming can be extra rough
sometimes but I appreciate you trying to make it work.
Now I know that too. And like
look. Mind show
is amazing. It's a
great idea. The people behind it
they really give a fuck. You can tell.
So my frustrations
with the game are not
necessarily
take it with a grain of salt. Because
I mean we had some issues with it but it was
still a lot of fun. It really was.
I don't mean my frustrations
to be taken out on the developers of the
game. Because I do think it's
really great. I hope they continue
to improve it. I hope it's continue
I mean it's a great concept.
But thank you Josh. VR
Josh. I loved
it. I had a lot of fun.
I still think. I would still recommend that
game. Just because of what they're trying
to do with the platform. It was good shit.
For real. Hey pizza
bot. Pizza bot.
Five dollars from pizza bot. This is a fever
dream. Yeah. That's
kind of how it works here sometimes.
Peaceful. Hey Lee. Thanks for the 250.
Hey Jeremy. Just want to say you're such a funny
man. Keep being yourself.
Going to Texas tomorrow.
So I'll miss a bunch of the streams but I hope you
enjoy the rest of your week.
Love you Jeremy. And chat.
I'm sure they appreciate that.
Thank you for the 250.
Thanks for the wonderful message.
Hey Jess. You got it. Thanks for
the 250. This is how your fight
scene directing looked.
What is this?
This is the
Liam
Neeson jumps a fence.
I can't believe they actually kept this.
Why would you not
change that? That is so
absolutely disgusting
in a filmmaking sense.
And I really, I mean that.
Holy shit. That was unbearable.
But thank you Jess. You got it for the 250.
Hey Pilot Guy. Thanks
for $15 Pilot Guy.
I'm fine. Seriously though.
I haven't laughed this hard in a while.
Thanks Jeremy. Thank you.
Glad you had a good time.
Thank you for the $15 and your wonderful
and amazing message.
Thank you. Mostly lost.
Thanks for the 250. Hey Geronimo. I'm going to
leave this Academy Award nominee by Kiwo
here. And it's
sequel which is even better.
Sorry, not sorry. Kiwo, deal
with it. What are you talking about?
Cherry chapstick.
What is this? Hold on.
This is a Kiwo video? I mean we gotta
watch the whole fucking thing.
Things have been rough between us.
Jeremy wants you to come home. Jeremy wants you to do this.
I miss you. I know things have been rough.
I miss you too. I still love you.
I love you too.
Awesome Texas.
Where's the audio?
What happened to the audio?
Kiwo, we gotta make it like a fucking
real video together.
I didn't do anything.
I just like shut off. Blossom.
I just played the video.
Kiwo went to bed 3 hours
ago. I don't blame her.
It's late. It's like 2am
Eastern. Like 6, 5,
6am EU.
The vibe may have, the vibe probably
fucked it up. But thank you Mostly Lost.
Kiwo and I will make
content together I promise.
She's hilarious. She's talented.
Of course I'd want to
make content with somebody like that. For real.
Like it's gonna happen.
It's never happening.
Hey Mostly Lost, thanks again
for the 250.
We can probably piece together the ABC video
with the first person's perspectives
when you were filming it and the final
audio from the end.
I don't even know what you're talking about. I forgot it.
What an embarrassment.
Didn't I lose like 700 fucking
viewers during that segment?
That's embarrassing.
I lost like a thousand
viewers.
That's so bad.
Okay, if I was a marketing person
I would come to me and be like
hey dude, don't fucking
do that again. You lost
a thousand people.
You lost like 20% of your whole
audience.
That's a new record.
Who cares?
Who gives a fuck, right?
It's all good.
But thank you Mostly Lost.
PastaGlobs
250, bless you for putting up
with dumb technical bullshit for as long as
you could. We love you.
Thank you. I think it was worth it because
the game is worth it. I think so.
Demias, thanks for five subs.
Demias, thank you.
Jerma lied about Minecraft
VR, five subs.
Rin the cutest, three subs.
Dr. Steen, five subs.
Sroiliat, Sroiliat
give 20, which is unfucking
believable. Thank you Sroiliat.
Sroiliat,
Sroiliat won.
Jerma lied about
Minecraft VR, another 10
community subs.
I can't fucking believe you'd give this
many subs, thank you. That's a lot
of money, it's a lot of contribution, it's a ton
of fucking, it's a big paycheck.
I
can't even, thank you.
15 community subs
tonight. I don't
have much else to say. I can't believe
it, thank you. Jerma lied
about Fruity Loops, I lie about
everything. Jerma, what's up? Like the stream
but I think Fruity Loops would be better, I do too.
And a real guitarist
to be hired to
play the guitar on the stream.
I'm working on it.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR,
lying about a lot of things tonight.
Hey Benito, maybe in
your drunken stupor you'll reconsider your
weird authoritarian stance on enabling
the Pog emote.
Like really? We got this shit.
That's better than it, that's the best.
Do you need anything else
besides that? Man Bear
Pig, 15 dollars from Man Bear Pig.
Jerma, it's probably weird
hearing this with somebody on the internet,
but you helped me overcome depression with how
funny you are. Just want to say thanks
for everything you've done, even if you don't know
you did it.
Anytime somebody tells me that,
happens maybe once every couple
weeks.
Maybe like once a month
somebody talks about their depression on the stream.
And how like this community in the
stream has made it easier and fun
and interesting for them.
I can't even fucking
respond. I can't believe it.
I am so
happy that you can have fucking
fun here.
You can forget about the bullshit of the daily
life. You can come here and enjoy yourself
with this community, with these people
and this stream.
I will never fucking forget
that. I will never
fucking forget it. So
when somebody says something
like this, it
means a lot. It hits me to my
very fucking core. I
really truly hope the best for you. I do.
Thank you for the $15.
Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for hanging out.
I'm depressed that these fucking streams help
the ever-living shit out of me.
We've got a great community here. We really
do. Forget about like the
meta in-joke stuff that
people say. We all say it, right?
But at its very, very core,
this is a great, really
great fucking community. So
many people are
so great here. I am
so forever blessed
with this group of people.
Pin wrote a
paper on this shit. We have
like papers and like scientific
documents based
on this community. Do you understand?
God, it means a fucking lot.
I hope you fucking understand that.
You guys have given me so much.
I am completely
grateful and forever happy
that you can take something from
here too. God damn.
Like, I wish you the best, for real.
There's a lot of great fucking people here.
I wish there was more I could say.
So much money and so
much happiness and
acceptance and fun and
interesting things and interesting conversations
happen here. I couldn't trade
it for anything, even if I wanted to.
It's impossible.
I couldn't do that.
There's so many great things.
Look at the shit from fucking last
week. Look at the game. Somebody
made a video game
about this community. It's like
what? It's unbelievable.
Every fucking day.
Don't think, I don't think
about this on a daily
basis. Thank you for
everything. Thanks for hanging out. I'm happy
that you have a community.
You have an outlet. You have something fun to do.
And I'm gonna keep doing it. I'm gonna
try to keep this community going. I'm gonna keep doing
things that I think are interesting, that I think
are fun. If you wanna ride the ride,
I hope you do. If it's not for you,
thanks for coming out.
Anyways, thanks for watching.
Even if you don't think it's for you.
Thank you for giving
me even a fucking second of your goddamn time.
For real.
E-Dragon, thanks for the $5 E-Dragon.
I wanted to give you $5
for my birthday, but
now I think you should give it to Kim for that scare.
I'll give it to Kim.
Door Cube, thanks for the $2.50. This $2.50
is for Kim. She deserves it. I can't believe she's
tied in the fucking closet. That's insane.
Kim will get it. For sure.
Kim Bits.
PikaBanana,
thanks for the $5 Pika.
Kim is amazing. That was absolutely hilarious. Awesome
stream as always. I'm glad
you enjoyed yourself. Thanks for sticking around.
Thank you. Wilma,
thanks for the $2.52.
Cheer52, no message. Thank you, Wilma.
Unkind,
$5 from Unkind.
Hey, JermaBabe,
I had a really shitty day
preparing for my trigonometry
exam, but just popping in very
quickly at the end of the stream and seeing you
scream like a little girl
made my day.
Jerma Heart, I wish you luck on
your trigonometry exam.
I'm glad you got some happiness
from that. Thank you. Good luck.
The scare was very real.
I just, you don't know, when you're in VR,
the world closes in.
Nothing else exists,
you know? It's hard.
Thank you, Unkind
though. Have a great exam.
Hope you ace it. A minus.
I'm not gonna give you the A plus
here. Kim's the perfect match
for you. You two are the only people I know who would
be willing to stand in a closet for half an hour for a prank.
She's great. She puts up
without my bullshit. If you
find a girl or a guy
wherever, doesn't matter, I will
put up with your fucking bullshit.
She's great. She's fun.
She means everything to me, so.
It's great.
That's for real. If you get a
human, take him. Yeah.
Hold on to those that you love.
My sunflower seed block. What a
champ, huh? How does
one find that? Accidentally go to a Christmas
party and meet somebody and accidentally
hang out with them. That's what happened to me.
That's it. Sometimes shit just happens.
You can't plan for it, guys.
You'll never know.
It just happens.
I was single for like seven years.
It just fucking happens sometimes.
I would be the last
person to tell you that that was going to happen.
It was Burger Boy's Christmas party.
Well, that's not true.
It was a Christmas party I went to with Burger Boy.
She was just there.
Just be approachable.
Be yourself. Tinder
update. No matches.
That's it. No matches.
That Tinder shit was depressing.
Tinder sucks. Delete that
fucking app. Don't use that app.
That app is poison. Don't use
it. Kim, that's
amazing. Thank you.
Okay, Cupid.
Just be yourself and just try.
That's all you can do.
But error of paradox
thanks to the three bucks franker Z.
That's a dog. Thank you,
three dollars. Error of paradox
again, 250. Jerma, I'm going
to Vegas for my 21st birthday.
Can we please do the level up lounge
thing? It'd be the best birthday ever.
It's probably going to take a while
for me to get that going, but I want to do
that. People want
to do a meetup. And
hey, you're going to be at TwitchCon.
I don't want you guys to fucking stand at a goddamn
line.
Waiting for my signature. Like a
fucking Disney World ride.
No, fuck that.
We're throwing a fucking party.
You understand? Oh, hey, welcome to the
fucking meetup. Here's your signature, bye.
No, fuck that shit.
I ain't doing like a TwitchCon
standing fucking line meetup.
Some people have to do that because they have
so many people. And I
understand. But if I'm able
to rent out a place,
fuck it, let's do it. Let's just have fun.
Anybody's invited, 21
over. Let me see what I can do.
JermaCon. No, it'll be
a lot smaller than that. We
can like trickle into the casino and just dick around
for a little while. Put like fucking 20
bucks on a double zero. Why not?
Fuck it, let's do it. I'm done.
Should be fun.
21. Gotta be 21.
And only like four people.
You know what? If four people show
up, then that's
great. Thanks for coming.
I will treat you
like fucking royalty.
If you decide to show up. Seriously.
You guys don't even understand.
When I went to TwitchCon, there's a quick little story.
TwitchCon last year,
or like two years ago, whenever
it was in Long Beach.
One person
came to the
meetup that I put on Twitter.
It was Red Ranger. Not sure if they're
still around in the community or not, but regardless.
That's who
we hung out for like fucking
45 minutes.
I don't give a shit about
how fucking many
people are there, how big the line is,
oh yeah, policy.
I don't give a shit.
We sat and we fucking talked and we hung out
for like a fucking hour. One person.
I don't fucking care.
That person
watched the streams,
cared about this content,
cared about this community.
I don't fucking care if one person, I don't care if fucking
ten people, five people, I don't give a shit.
One fucking person
could go and it would like light up my
life. I don't care.
I don't give a shit about all that.
I really don't. I hope you fucking know that.
The one guy could
show up. That would be fucking great.
We would have a blast. I would do karaoke.
Who cares?
If 200 people show up,
I hope I can give you all attention.
Do you mind if I get drunk as fuck?
Get drunk as fuck. It's Vegas.
It's Las Vegas, dude.
What do you mean, do you care if I get drunk?
It's Las Vegas, Nevada.
Just be safe. Don't fucking drive.
Don't do that shit.
Get a Lyft, get an Uber to your AirBnB
or hotel. The hotels are all right here.
Get a room for like 30
bucks at fucking MGM. They're like
nothing. Does the open bar have
milkshakes?
Maybe. It depends. Staying in
an AirBnB in Vegas.
But for real, I don't
care if one person wants to
say hello or a thousand.
We've done meetups before. I don't do
Twitch or like YouTube
sponsored meetups.
The last time I did one, we just filled up a lobby
and just hung out for like fucking two or three hours.
I don't
give a shit about that.
I don't care about feeding people through fucking
goddamn line.
And I might be talking shit
right now. But whatever.
I don't care. Deodorant is
necessary.
It is. We're in. But
I'm not gonna stand on a soapbox
anymore. If I do it,
you'll know well in advance.
But each and every fucking
one of you has grown this channel.
Has stuck with this channel.
So why wouldn't I value
every fucking single one of you?
The reason why, oh you had
4500 fucking people watching?
That's like top 10, top 20 on Twitch.
Are you serious?
What? I'm not gonna give you the credit that you deserve
for that? Are you serious?
Like that's such a huge fucking deal.
A shitload of you make
this channel as popular and as
interesting as it is.
Never fucking forget that.
Never, ever, fucking
ever forget that.
Ever. Oh look at me.
2020.
For me to get up here and like
drink a bottle of wine
and like act out my dumb fucking
skits. And you're
watching. Like I don't
have anything else to tell you.
That's remarkable that somebody would do
that. But Superman,
thanks for the 297.
He's knocking shit over. Now that's an empty cup.
Jerma, I got a vibe.
I have to see how much fun you're having with it.
And I can't stop playing Beat Saber. What a great game.
By the way.
Also, my stepbrother and I are going to Vegas
next week. What's my favorite
places you've been to?
And where do you want to go? Best wishes.
Well, I told you
my favorite casino is the Aria.
It's just that everything is in the Aria. I love the Aria.
Downtown Vegas is great.
If you get to Fremont Street
for real. It's a great
place. A lot of good pizza.
Evil Knievel's got great pizza.
Aria. The Aria.
Like this, right? The Aria.
Like that.
There you go. The Aria.
If you want to walk the strip, it takes about
two plus hours to walk the whole
thing. So just the whole thing.
I've had a few glasses of wine. Give me a break.
Takes about two hours to walk the whole thing.
Wouldn't recommend it. Stay somewhere.
Go to Hash House
Agogo at the Link.
The Link is, I mean, the casino is alright.
And the drinks are alright.
And the place is alright. But Hash House Agogo
at the Link
has the best cheeseburger
I have ever eaten.
It is the best I have ever
consumed in my entire 34 years
on the planet.
Hash House Agogo. Fucking go there and eat their food.
It's fantastic.
That is not sponsored. It's just real life.
It's just real life.
Okay? It's great.
They do like a lace burger.
They flatten it out. I want to go there
right now. It's just fucking reality.
Streamer condones hash
consumption.
Well, if it's Hash House Agogo, then yeah.
But thank you Superman.
Hope you have fun in Vegas.
Enjoy it. Just don't let it consume you.
There's a lot to do in Vegas.
Just be responsible.
Hazy thanks to the $5. They said shave.
I will in a few days.
Internet Jorge. $15
Internet Jorge. If JermaCon
actually happens, summer will be
awesome since I'm off
and request to work off. Jerma, I'm challenging
you to drink off.
I read that so wrong.
It's not going to be JermaCon. I don't want my
name in that shit. I'd rather
it be like the hangout
session or something.
I don't know. JermaCon
sounds a little pretentious.
I'm going to
get in touch with MGM. I really
am. I swear to God this is real.
Grill MasterCon. If you can
make it, I'll talk. If it happens,
I'll talk about it a lot more.
21 plus. We'll see if I can get
a private party. It'll be fun.
Thanks for the $15.
Something or utter
thanks for the $2.50. Can't wait for
JermaCon. Hope you can handle your liquor better at
the open bar. I'm good.
Thank you Bingo Sunshine for the $15.
I'm going to charge back these bits
if you don't stream tomorrow.
Come on.
I might...
God damn it. I'll try.
I didn't think I was going to drink this much
wine. I might have to fucking
sleep tomorrow. What a fucking
asshole.
And I took three days off.
What is this, like an eight hour stream?
I'll see you in a few days. I'm going to take another
few days off.
God damn it.
I appreciate the fact that people
really, for the most part,
they don't care.
The more that you guys understand, the more that
I can do the things that I want to do.
You understand? We talked
about it a lot. I don't have like a schedule.
I don't want a schedule.
I want to just do it
whenever, you know? Whenever I'm fucking
happy. Which is a lot,
right? I never want to force
myself or push myself
to do things I don't really necessarily
want to do, right? I've been doing this
for a long time. I hope you
understand that every
single fucking time I press that start
every time, every
single fucking time
that I press that start
streaming button on OBS.
I want you to have as much fun as possible.
So if somebody says, oh you took like three
or four days off, I just, I
just know that that, I want to make sure
every stream is fucking good
and fun for you. And sometimes I
have to take that time. I was like that
on YouTube. I mean maybe I'm not,
I don't stream as much as other people do, but
that's just kind of the way I work.
He's getting sentimental
again. No, you guys fucking get it.
You really do. You guys fucking get it.
An actor.
No.
I couldn't ask for a fucking better life
and a better group of fucking people.
Like get it, you know.
God damn.
If only you guys knew. I say
it a lot and we've been talking about it for a long time
tonight. But my god.
Just wait, wait.
Another few weeks.
I got a lot of stuff planned.
Thank you.
It feels good to be funny. I finally found someone who can
make me laugh. I feel you.
Never change. Lord knows we need
more loving and well-meaning people.
Like yourself.
Fighting just a bunch of laughs and much needed.
I just want to
have a good time. That's all I
care about, you know.
In a world that's so fucking crazy.
We live in like a crazy fucking world.
The world is crazy.
In a society. In this society.
This is as much of an
outlet for me as it is for you.
I hope you understand that.
This is the Joker backstory.
We live in a society
where if you're fucking good at something,
fucking trees
regrowing. I'll never
be the biggest streamer. I'll never be the fucking most
respected streamer. Maybe.
But I got you guys.
I got this fucking group of people.
You all get this shit. You all understand.
I don't need anything more.
I don't need anything else.
I got a fucking group of funny fucking
people. I don't give
a fuck about anything else. Are you kidding me?
You think I give a shit about being
like the most popular?
I've got to make sure my post gets
20,000
thumbs up. I don't give a fuck.
Holy shit.
I don't care at all.
Hopefully this video can get
10,000 likes.
Please give. No.
I don't give a flying fuck about that.
Fuck that. Let's just have
fun. I'm getting worried about
him. No. Don't. Don't. Don't.
Don't. Wine gives him
the pot. I'm not going to swear for the rest of the stream.
I promise.
Not one more time.
Hey, Thevious!
Thanks for the five dollars.
I'm glad I got to
catch your stream today. It's honestly been one of my favorites.
Hope you play more VR
horror games. I had a
relationship and the other day.
And this really helped my mood.
It was only about a month long or so.
So I'm not completely torn.
But it was still rough since I'm dealing
with college finals.
Just wanted you to know that I appreciate your streams.
Thanks for great stream.
Turn my heart. I'm really sorry to hear that.
The one
thing you can take from that though
is if it was a month long, it
was, you know, you
figured out that it wasn't to be
and you moved on.
You're going to bounce back.
Just don't worry about it.
There's tons of other people in the ocean.
Just go diving.
You know. Don't worry about that.
Thankfully, you didn't figure that out
two or three years later.
Right? Tons of people are
drowning. I got my snorkel.
But, Thievous,
Thievous, I wish you the best.
Don't let it break you up too much.
Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for the five dollars.
Oh, Zalaski.
Thanks with three bucks. Alright, look here, boomer.
Olive Chat wants 2012
beef cake,
beef cake. Germaback,
take him out of the closet.
I'll never be that fucking Jack.
Guys, I spent every other
day in the gym.
Oh, that was a swear. You're right.
I was lifting four days
a week. Oh, it took
a 10, 20,
it took like 20 hours a week of my time.
Alright.
At Jexpo,
at Germa Jexcon
2019, I will
bench press 240 pounds.
Why did I say that?
I hope somebody can help me.
At Jexcon 2019,
I will bench press like
100 pounds and somebody can help me.
We're gonna have to need a spotter for that one.
It's gonna be
live streamed. Jexcon
2019 for the level up lounge.
Alright, I gotta stop saying that.
Because that's not true.
And somebody, MGM
might be like, that's not fucking happening, dude.
Like, don't say that shit.
But, hey, maybe
it will. Maybe it will.
Swear. Ah, it's alright.
Hey, broluck.
Thanks for the three bucks. They say nice hair.
Nice hair. What is it?
It says nice hair, apparently.
Let's find out what this means.
What is it? What's wrong with it?
What is it?
I don't get it.
Nice hair.
What's wrong with my hair?
Okay. Thanks.
Thanks, I guess.
Okay. Alright.
Thank you, broluck.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR
thanks to 250.
Plebs can't Jerma Venus, though.
If they sub, they can. But
you can Jerma Venus for them.
Thank you. Skelly
Boner. Oh, I read that.
You are, hold on.
Mr. Picklesworth says, you're honestly a huge inspiration
in my life. I look up to
you so much and I truly hope my future turns out
as good as it has for you.
You're one of the most genuine and loving people on the entire
internet. And don't change.
If you look up to me,
I hope you can take a couple
of things. Try your best.
Try to make as many people happy as you can.
And be realistic about your goals.
Try your fucking best.
Do what you can. And try to make as many people
happy as you can. You only get one chance.
You got one life here.
Try to do your best. Just do your fucking best.
Obey your thirst.
Hey, peekaboo in a $5.
We're blessed to have you. I'm blessed to have you too.
It's a symbiotic relationship.
So thank you.
Mithril Bong. Thanks for $5.10 Mithril.
And they say,
Jeremy, you're the man. I just hate
you a little for doing the ABC's
bit while I was in the subway
on the way home from work.
You can't win them all though. Laughing
my ass off. Keep it up your 35
and haven't peaked yet. You'll
figure something out. I have not even peaked.
As Dennis Reynolds says,
I haven't peaked yet. Come on.
I'll peak when I'm 45.
You know how much shit is coming up
in the summertime? You think I've peaked?
Don't even. Oh my God.
You have no fucking idea. I'm gonna
get in a goddamn clown costume. It's in a dunk tank.
And you guys are gonna control a fucking
pitching machine to dunk me. You think
I've peaked? I'll see you in a few months.
Not even like a few weeks. Fucking
whatever it is. Oh my God. Are you serious?
I'm a golden
goddamn god. Remember
that. All Mew thanks
for the three bucks.
Say it was the suit, Peter.
It was the goblin so that I can go to bed.
Hope he can go to bed now.
Jackatomic.
Thanks for five bucks.
Your butterfly effect is insane.
So many people go through life just hoping
to make a difference in the world. But you've done
it. Thousands of people here
plan our nights around you because you make us
happy. And it helps us get through
tough times. You're a gift to humanity
as a whole and we thank you tremendously.
Give yourself some credit.
As they say in Game of Thrones, the night is
dark and full of terrors. But
give yourself some credit. Right?
Minus two games. Come on!
It's coming back in like a week. Give me that one.
Thousands of people plan
their nights around you. But you do
understand that I plan my nights
around all of you.
You know? It goes both
ways. So
I plan a lot of my nights
around you guys. You know?
I want the streams to be fun. I want you guys
to have a good time. And if you're saying
that, it's a complete
symbiotic. I'm the hippopotamus
and you're like the hippo bird that
eats the fucking bugs.
You know? Or you're the hippo
and I'm the bird that eats the bugs.
We're in this together.
Forever. So don't you ever leave.
Don't ever leave me. It's kind of
a bad idea. It's alright.
I'll see you soon.
Chat doesn't know. The hippo bird.
I don't know whatever the bird's
name is. The hippo birdimus.
Doesn't matter.
Streamer forces...
But if I have a butterfly effect on
you, I hope you take something positive
from the stream. We fuck around
a lot. Look, we fuck around
all the time. But if
you take something from the stream and you
take something, inspiration or
positivity or
helpfulness or community,
it doesn't matter. That's such a
big fucking deal. When I go
to bed every night, I will lie
in my bed. I'll stare
at the ceiling. And a lot of times
I just think about
this world that
I live in now. And this community.
And I'm living in Las
Vegas. In a nice place.
And what I've
been given. Right?
I don't sleep on my back. I fucking think
on my back. I sleep on my side.
So whatever you tell me that I've
given you, always remember
what you've given me. You give me
that opportunity to lie on my fucking back in
Las Vegas and be like, holy, I'm in fucking
Las Vegas. In like a nice
place. In a nice area.
And I fucking can
pay my rent. I...
What?
That's why I take this shit so damn
seriously. Like I take fun
and this community so seriously.
I think about this shit all the goddamn
time. Paying rent?
Pogchamp? Yeah. I thought you bought...
Nah, I don't own in Las Vegas.
It was too quick.
Our vessel.
No, but it's true.
Think about that. Think about the thousands
of fucking people. Think about the thousands
of you that have decided to fucking
pay money to this stream.
It's not a joke.
It's not funny
to me. It's a lot.
It's a huge amount
of people. It's a community
of people. I can't
even fucking comprehend sometimes.
What else do you want me to do with spare cash?
I just hope you think it's worth it.
Yeah, I've had a few drinks, but you guys have heard
this before. I will never change
my tune on this. Ever.
Doesn't matter how many subs come into this
channel. How many bits come into this fucking channel.
I will never
change this tune. And if I do,
tell me about it.
If I ever change this shit,
if I ever start acting a different
fucking way, start acting like
I deserve this. I deserve something.
Keep me fucking grounded.
I hope you do. Because it keeps the community
fucking churning. Your tune
is raw.
You don't strike me as the type. I hope I don't.
I hope I don't. I hope you guys
think that I do this because I want to.
Otherwise, what would I
stream fucking six, seven days a week?
Every stream is turned on because I
want to turn it on. That's all there is
to it. And it's never
going to fucking change. Don't ever
let me change. Five thousand
subs, ten thousand subs, twenty thousand.
I don't fucking care.
Never let the dynamic change.
Otherwise, I've failed.
And why I started in the first
place is moot.
Don't let me fucking do that.
I really fucking mean
that. That's for real. That's actually
coming out of my...
We'll turn the camera on.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that.
Here. Clip this one.
No.
Jesus Christ.
That's all I'm going to say. I'm going to move on from that.
I know it might be about fucking rambling, but
drunk man's thoughts are superman's
thoughts too.
Because they're the same person. What the hell
does that even saying mean? You're going to say
the same goddamn thing.
Whatever that fucking saying is, you've heard it.
You look worn out.
I'm not, though. I'm just fucking
terrible.
Thanks for the one dollar.
I'm not supposed to be reading these.
But thank you.
Thanks for five dollars.
Look, Jerma, I really need you to do me a favor.
What's the favor?
You didn't say what the favor was.
You just gave me five bucks, which is a fucking shitload of money.
You gave me a five dollar bill.
I don't know. What's the favor?
Jerma lied about Steam Legends.
You never came back. You never came back.
What do you mean? What did I say?
I'll come back in an hour and a half and I'll do it.
I'm going to go eat some food.
I'll do it in an hour and a half. Do what?
Do what in an hour and a half?
I don't know what this means.
I don't know what I'm lying about.
What was I supposed to do?
Oh shit!
The loot! I never came back.
I never get
I never came back and gave the loot.
Oh god.
Wow, I never did. Holy shit.
What a terrible person.
Yeah, I was supposed to do that.
Oh my god, I'm so scatterbrained.
I'm so sorry.
We'll do it tonight.
Thank you Dorkcube for the 250.
If you still decide Jermacon is a good idea
after you leave the VR stupor,
just be careful how you plan it.
You have to consider how to handle
what could possibly be a large group of people
following you for hours.
No, that's fine.
We would go to the Level Up Lounge
in the MGM casino.
Beautiful casino. 21 plus.
I'd make it work.
It'll be fine. We'll do karaoke.
I'll sing like fucking Walking in Memphis
or some dumb shit.
No, I'm gonna play this by the book.
So don't worry about that.
Level! You're so dead set on
Level Up Lounge. I know
it sounds sponsored, but it's not.
The place is just cool.
It's not gonna be like that.
Don't compare me. I'm uncomparable.
I am an uncomparable streamer.
Do not compare me to other streamers.
As you can tell by
my fucking Twitch Docs.
Let's take a look and see how good they're doing.
Don't compare me to other streamers.
Let's see how my Twitch Docs are doing here.
Let's see. Trending.
Is German985 currently
trending? He's not.
There he is. There he is.
Okay, a little bit of a dump.
A little bit of a dump.
People have sold.
People have sold a little bit.
You gotta cool off after
a big gain like we've seen.
But yeah, don't worry.
Whatever the meetup will be.
It'll be a never...
Maybe I'll stream it.
If I can get permission
from the Level Up Lounge in MGM
Casino. Maybe I'll stream the whole
fucking thing. Somebody said
Jesus, this guy is wasted. No, Vance,
I'm not. You joined at a weird
time.
God damn it. How do I
tell that person I'm not? How do I tell this person
I'm not wasted? God damn it.
I'll see...
Hey!
You were right. It's fine. It's okay.
Mithra Bong, thanks for the
$5.10. Jeremy,
you're the man. I just hate you
a little for doing the ABCs on the
subway. Oh, we already said
Mithral, thanks for $5.
God damn it.
That guy's right.
Don't leave, though.
Did you just get here?
You know, there's a follow up button. Don't press it
until you find out you think that it's fun to be here.
We've got a great community.
We've got fucking fun people.
I'm gonna get dunk tank in like a few weeks.
Just wait till you see me in the dunk tank.
Twitch can... He's probably already gone.
Hey, Dork Cube, thanks for the $2.50.
Hey, Bro Luck,
thanks for the $5.
Hey, how many people in your community do you think have
murdered someone? I don't...
What the fuck are you talking about?
I don't... I'm gonna say zero.
I hope it's zero. Kim
Dang, Kim Dang,
22 minutes ago,
my girlfriend just sent
$5 in bits to this
channel. Why are you doing that?
Please eat your food
downstairs. Oh, God.
Okay. I'll be down in a minute.
Uh, only...
Let's get the... Oh, Kim,
you're the best. Here come
the credits. That's a lot
of subs. Thank you, everybody.
For this like dumb shitty
drunk VR, German complaints about
technology stream. I'm
watching from jail. I hope you get out soon.
That's a lot of subs.
Lightspeed subs and
Clueless Sniper, thanks for the $2.50.
I have to wake up early
tomorrow, but it's worth
staying up to hear you talk. Love the
stream, everything you do. Thank you,
Clueless Sniper. You're
a fucking huge part of this community. Thank you.
Thank you, Jesse. You got up at $2.50.
What if you do that same height party
thing where everyone gets a pair of shoes to
bring them all up to the
same height? I'm 5'8". I don't give a fuck.
Dorkcube, thanks for the $2.50.
I kid you not,
I have watched this clip at least once
every single day since it happened.
What is this?
You watch this every day.
What a joke.
I fucking love the internet.
Hey, welcome to the stream. If that person is still here,
I hope you followed. If you didn't, then
hopefully we see you soon.
Take care of yourself.
Hey, I just joined for the first time. Well, then
I'm glad.
I can't believe I lost like fucking a thousand people
during that like singing thing.
I'm going to look at that clip tomorrow,
that stream tomorrow, and be like, ugh,
what the fuck was I doing?
Who cares?
Whatever. Fuck it, it's all a good fun.
He hates his new viewers. What?
Post the fight.
Ugh.
I may have turned away a few people today.
If you're one of the people that stayed
after all that, hey,
some of the best fucking TwitchTV content
you could find.
A fucking 5.8 troll
screams at bad technology
and gets mad at bugs in games
and it makes a cringey fucking
13 second bit.
Hope you had fun.
And finally,
Frostro, thanks to the five bucks.
Jerma is a measured
experience, not a single stream that
lost some viewers.
Oh.
You guys are too much. Thank you so much, everybody.
5,000, 2,000, 10,000,
40,000, fucking 200.
I don't give a fuck.
If you thought it was fun, I'm glad.
Thank you. What a fucking blast.
I loved it. Tonight was great.
Thank you, everybody. I'll see you all
soon. I can't, I mean I'm supposed to stream
tomorrow, but I might wake up
with a hangover and then we're going to have
to, we'll see.
I don't know. I love you.
I'll see you guys fucking real soon.
Whenever that may be, in the next day or two.
Lots of water. I will.
Take care. Have a great one.
Oh god, I forgot about the stream
legends, you're right. Keep me honest.
Hold on.
I'll get it this way. I'll get it.
I'll get it. I'll get you.
I got you guys, don't worry. Hold on.
There it goes.
Stream legends.
Open it up if you have it.
If you play it. It's just a little
fun thing to have down there. It's free.
You don't have to pay anything.
It's just there.
Here we go. I will see you guys
real soon. What?
What the hell did I just do? Oh there we go.
Three, two, one.
Gifts gone out. Hope you got something good.
See you tomorrow
or maybe the next day if I
wake up with a hangover and then I might
have to go the next day. Ace Attorney's
out, that's true, but ah
how much VR? Ah, we'll see.
See you soon. Take care guys.
As always, have a
great day.