What is going on here? I just gave myself two redstone torches.
What is this like dog? What? There's a dog just like sitting in this room right here.
Information kiosk. Oh I know what I can do. It's a dog. Hello doggy. Hello little doggy.
Who's your good boy? Oh no! I didn't mean to punch you. I was trying to pet you.
Is there a pet button in this game? Uh, no. Can I like pet him?
Now he's mad at me. I'm sorry dog. By the way, by the way, I saw somebody comment on your last video.
They said, Jerma, you know that there's an engineer skin for Minecraft, right? You should get a TF2 skin.
Well this is Gino from Mario RPG. It's like my favorite video game thing ever.
I love Gino. I don't even know why I'm a pirate to be perfectly honest. I have no idea.
I thought you were like a king. I am the king of pirates, of course.
Is it nighttime again? Let's fix that. Geez, man.
I wish I could just make it daytime like forever. Now you're welcome.
That's where the gold block goes whenever you find it. Okay. All right.
Are you ready? I think I'm ready to play Jungle Race. Game one. So we just go?
We're going to keep tally and see who wins when all this is said and done.
I am ready. Ready? So the whole point, we're going to get up to the top of that thing, right?
Are we going? Oh yeah. Obstacle course time. Oh, go. Over the slow sand.
Oh, this is slow sand. What the hell? Come on, come on, come on. Run, run, run, run, run, run.
Oh my God. I'm going to like puke. This is like pulsating.
They got up here. All right. We're on the bridge. No. Oh, I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm all right. I'm good. I thought I fell down. I'm in the water pool. That's not where I want to be.
Swimming up to the surface. Oh, I see you. I see you. You're like right across from me.
Oh, I'm going to win. I am absolutely going to win.
I refuse to lose. I'm getting stuck on all the vines.
What's going on? Where am I? Oh, wait, the vines, right? Go, go, go, go, go.
The gold blocks are on the highest place of the jungle. Destroying leaves is cheating.
I don't even like know what this is.
Oh no. What is going on? The world is gone.
What? What? Oh, what do you know? Like half the
world is gone. Let me just climb up this tree. I'll be okay. Uh oh, I fell.
Okay. There's lots of handy ladders placed strategically
around these trees. All right. I see this platform. Probably supposed to go up there.
No, get out of the way. Up here, up here, up here, up here, up here. Come on, come on, come on, come on.
We're looking for the gold block, right? Yeah, there's like a
gold block somewhere around here. Ow. It's up here. Oh, there's a skeleton.
There's a skeleton on my side. Kill him. Punch him in his face.
Yeah, I'm not going to take time to punch him in his face when I could be trying to find the gold.
Oh, it's right there. It's right there. Oh my God. Go, jump. Oh, I got this in the bag.
I got this in the bag, I think. Wait, what? Are you already at the gold? Yeah,
I'm at the gold right now. Oh man. Here we go. Here we go.
Take only one gold block and put it in the Indian statue. All right.
I've already got the gold, son. I'm running out here. Wait, hold on. Where'd it go? Give me this.
Oh my God. Punch it again for another one. I got it. I got it. I'm good. Wait.
I don't know where to go. I don't know where to go. You gotta jump off the edge.
Oh my God. There's a creeper. You gotta be kidding me. You gotta be kidding me. Get away from me.
Get away from me. Oh my God. Okay.
I'm winning this thing. I am winning this thing. I just almost had a legit heart attack right there.
The world is ending. Where do I go? You have like a
chuckle. All right, all right. Jerma has
forfeited. He has died. I lost. All right, so we're gonna make a creeper.
You had a creeper? A creeper came right behind me and it freaked me out and gave me a heart attack.
985 and I'm gonna send... Hang on. Is this teleporting you to me or me to you?
I guess we're about to find out. Hooray. I don't...
Are you there? I don't see you. I'm standing right here, yeah. Hello. Go.
Wait. Wait, what? There's a second part to the challenge.
Oh, I do. Wait. Yeah, there's part two. There's part two.
This is the maze. We have to like climb. We have to like figure out
how to get out of this maze. How come I'm in yours?
I'm in your part of the thing. No, it meets up in
the middle so we're both like racing against time. Hey, hey.
But get away from me. Hold on. I just went
back. I went back to the place where I started.
I'm just like wandering around here trying to find the way out. Oh, it's definitely this way.
Oh, how did you get out there? I didn't make it.
Oh. I'm still stuck in the forest.
I can't like find my way. You're stuck in the... Oh, I found you.
Oh, you're already climbing up there. Wow. There's so many like things in the way. I can't see where I am.
I'm like in the maze. Oh, you're not. I can see
climbing that thing. Oh, there's an arrow. Oh, this is bad.
I'm gonna fall off of this for sure. Yeah, you certainly are, sir.
Are you already at the finish? Put the fire away.
Man, that was like the fastest scaling ever. How do I...
Do I just punch it? Did I win? Congratulations. Thank you for playing. I
won. I get a diamond pick. You win. And flint and
steel. You kind of won. You kind of like lost and
won. I absolutely lost the game.
I just failed pretty hardcore right there. I am bad
at jumping. Alright, so where are you? I'm still like failing at scaling this
wall with you so expertly like climbed up somehow.
I'm lighting the trees on fire. Is that bad?
Should I not be doing this? Is that gonna like ruin everything? I'm like
climbing up here just to see if I can. Just to see if I can...
Oh, you're over here. And I can't. I'm just a
complete failure. Oh, come on, Italics. I'm rooting for you. Oh, yeah, man.
Get out of here. No, my life.
I'm alive still. I don't know how, but I am. It's kind of dangerous.
Oh, God. Just a little dangerous. It's alright. We'll fight him off.
Yeah, I've got a gold sword. Fire. Burn.
Burn. Oh, I put you in the fire. Sorry.
Oh, it's okay. I forgive you. It's just a minor third degree burn.
So now we're gonna move on to... What's this one? Swedish Gladiators.
I think this one's gonna be pretty difficult though. Alright, that's
fine. I'm up for a challenge. I'm game. I'm game.
Two players needed. Obstacle race. So it's kind of like jungle race?
My specialty. Blue Gladiator is Notch.
Yellow Gladiator is Jeb. Reach the diamonds before your opponent.
If you fall in the water, you should start over. Okay. Sounds about
right. So do we have to push start or do we just go?
I think there's a start button. I think we just go. Is this pressure plate right here? Oh, no.
Okay. Step on pressure plate to make the game stop. And then I'm ready.
There's a button. You ready? I don't know, man. I'm getting kind of nervous. Getting those butterflies
right before an Olympic race. Oh, right before the meet. Here we go. This is it.
Are you ready? I'm ready. Do it. Do it. Go.
Running up the ladder. Here we go. Swedish Gladiators. Oh, yeah.
Alright. Jumping across an S. Oh, wow. That was close.
I'm not risking that. Oh, well. How do I get over here? Oh.
I was going to wait and see how you did that. Oh, you did it. Now what do you do?
I'm going through some kind of crazy obstacle course. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Okay. I get it. I get it. They're trying to push me off the edge now. They're trying to push me off. Oh, my
God. They pushed me off. I'm back on the track, but I'm at the beginning of it.
I'm already at that ladder. Alright. Alright. Hang on. Hang on.
Next time we both fall, I'm going to like spawn in some more bread
because I'm losing some hunger here. Jump. Jump.
Oh, no. Don't jump. Just walk. I have a feeling this is going to be just like a series of fails.
Oh, man. No. I'll get it this time. I can see what it's trying to do.
The pistons. The pistons that push you off are where it really gets me.
I'm trying to see the pattern. My brain is too slow right now.
Alright. Here we go. Boom. Oh, I made it. I actually made it. Okay. I got it. I got it past the
Oh, you're already up there. Oh, no. Oh, my God. I don't know what to do here.
Is it right here? And then you jump? There's water. Oh, no.
Oh, man. There I go again.
How did you see that pattern? I didn't. I like it. I got like
pushed off and it like didn't push me off and then I like glitched it out. I think.
I could be wrong. I might be really good. I'm probably not though.
Okay. There's water. I got it.
Oh, man. Okay. Don't get
trampled by the mine carts. How am I supposed to do this part? Don't
get trampled by the mine carts. Oh, here's another pattern. Great.
Go. Go. I don't know how to get through the second
set of pistons. You gotta just jump. I fell again. Oh, you gotta jump
and just glitch it out. That's the only way I got through. Water.
Water. No, no. Water slows you down. Whoa. It's pushing me off. Oh, okay.
Slow down. Slow down. All right. I'm back where I was.
Don't let the mine carts trample you. Okay. I won't.
Oh, man. No, don't go. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Go. Oh, it pushed me
off a man three times. You're gonna win this one. Oh, I hope so.
You've got the system down. You've got the system. Oh, my. Do you fall?
I did. All right. If I get knocked, I got back to this part again.
Come on now. Come on. I don't want to get hit by this piston.
Why'd I do that? Why'd I do that? Why'd I do that? Okay, I'm good. No.
See, it comes out the middle. Wow. This is just, this is gonna be a fail time right here. There it is.
Okay. Nice and easy. Nice and easy. Don't want to mess anything up.
Here. I'm almost at the end. You know what they should have? Oh, my God.
I'm not gonna screw this up. I'm not gonna screw this up. Not gonna
screw this up. All right. This one, I don't think I have to double jump for this one. I'm gonna
freak myself out. No, I didn't. Okay. All right. I'm gonna win it.
So, do you have to just tipsy-turvy on this thing or what? Oh, man. I don't know where you're at.
I'm sneaking. Is that gonna do anything at all? I have no idea.
Oh, for all the time it took. I completed it. Get some wool
and try to hit the basket to open the door? What? What do I have to do?
Oh, I have to throw it? Hey, Jerma. Oh, I'm trying.
Hey, Jerma. Yeah? Take a look around. Did you complete it?
You beat it before I did? Take a look around.
So, is this it? I'm dancing on diamonds right now, man.
You shut up, bitch. I can't believe it.
Look at this chunk error.
Is there anything after this? Because there's a chunk error right there. Yeah, there's like
the finish line is right here. So, the finish line is right there. Okay.
Make sure to right-click the button. Don't left-click it.
This didn't do anything. Oh, I just...
We are the champions of... You just
left me in the dust back here. You're like, ah, that's my button, son.
Apparently, there's a zombie doing it as well.
The obstacle. He's on my side. He's like doing it. Look at him. He's like, oh, I want to do it too.