Hello everybody. How are you? Good afternoon. Scam train level 5. Oh wait,
Poland. Can I do it right now? I'm gonna do it right now. I'm gonna change it right now.
I forgot to do that. I, yeah. Let me change that right now. Okay. Settings. Uh, okay. Preferences.
Okay. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Hype train. There it is. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Hard. Make it really hard. And make it 15 events. Done. Okay. Now it's, now it's very hard to do.
I just did it right now. Okay. Good. Now I just made it too hard. And now he's, he's, he's just
starting to scam everybody. Oh no. Now we're never gonna get a scam train. All right. But anyways,
how you guys doing? Welcome back. Uh, my voice is a little gone today. And I just figured out why.
And I remember the exact moment from yesterday that it happened. Um, if you remember during a
portion of the stream yesterday, I did this thing where I screamed without screaming.
I screamed very loudly, but I didn't scream. I cut it off halfway through and then I came back
and screamed louder. Um, that's what did it. And that's why I sound like this today and last night
too. Oh, there's only a limited time to earn. There's only a limited time to earn exclusive
e-boats. How hard is it now? Isn't it? It's harder to do this. I made this harder to do.
And I increased the amount of events that it takes. Everybody get your hands in the air.
Everybody, everybody hands in the air. Hands up. Everybody here comes up. I'm just a Skype train.
Like we're all going to get on Skype. Level one completed. Excellent work everybody. You did it.
You got us to level one Skype train. Is it actually harder to do though?
You're going to have to increase it a little more. What do we got? Hold on.
Hype conductors. Hold on. Here are your current hype train conductors.
You boy, pity. This is pay to win. Look at that. That greedy grinner is definitely grinning right
now. But we're going to do a community content night. And I know I say night, but it's day.
But that sounds like shit. Community content night rolls off the tongue better than community
content day. Oh, community content day. Now community content night. That sounds better to me.
Oh, I don't care if it's 11 o'clock in the morning. It's going to be called community
content night or let's call it EU night. But because we didn't do one last month,
I had to break it up because I didn't want to get sort of community content exhaustion.
And I'd want to spend time on people's submissions. I want to look at them and talk
about them. And obviously I have enough time on them. I don't want to just dump like 500
images on the screen and go, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. So we're going to do,
we're going to break it up into two. We're going to do two, one right now, and then one next weekend,
which the one next weekend will catch us up over the last like 25 days or so, 30 days.
What you're seeing here is stuff from November, from November into December. And there's some good
shit here. I've seen, oh, we got a hype train level two completed. Where's my lip balm? I don't
even have any lip balm up here. What a mistake. It never gets old. I pray, but on the lipstick.
No, I need lip balm. I really do. If I don't have lip balm, then get hype, get hype, hype.
It's just that it's the bar. I figured it out. If anytime that there is a completable bar,
somebody will do it. Always. It doesn't matter what it is. As long as there is a progress bar,
it's going to be filled. But I see this. I'm thinking about just contributing to make the
progress go up. I have to see the bar go up. We're just a bunch of mice. We're just a bunch of rats.
Like, bar go up. Yeah, eat. You owe Lord of the Rings subs. Oh, fuck. I actually do. I actually
do. I actually really do. Oh, how many? Look, I don't even remember. I remember like 15 minutes
of that 13 hour stream. How many subs do I owe? It was 40. Okay. All right. All right. All right.
Hey, I got to make this progress go up. All right. Hold on. Hold on. No, that's true. That is
absolutely true. Hold on a second. Yeah, because I said if I swung one time that I owed 10 subs and
I swung like three or four times. All right. Okay. Well, here we go. Let me gift subs.
Give gift subscriptions. Give. Can I give more? Okay. I have to do. All right. Here we go. 40.
$200. Now, here we go. Here comes 40 community subs. Okay. My mother does this thing. It doesn't
matter how inexpensive or how expensive something is. When she hears the price for it, she repeats
the price shocked and annoyed. How much is that? How much is that slice of pizza? Well, it's, um,
it's $2.80. $2.80. Jeremy. Yeah, it is. Oh, my goodness. That better be the best pizza I've ever
had in my life. Same reaction. If that pizza was $200 a slice, it would be the same reaction.
All right. Let me let's do this. Here we go. 40 community subs. I am a man of my word sometimes.
I'm making my own hype train go up. Wait, that doesn't count. Hey, hey, that doesn't. How come
that doesn't count? I can't increase my own. Hold on. So you can't just sit there and make your own
hype train go up. Oh, maybe you should try it again. Should I try it again? Wait, I ran out
of time. No, I didn't. There's still three minutes and 40 seconds left. All right. Let's get this
started. Community content night. Uh, this is going to be short stream. Probably going to be
a couple hours, few hours. It's going to be a quick one. We're just going to chill,
go over some videos, go over some artwork. And I do have something to tell you though,
something that you'll like. But for those of you that, uh, well, for those of you that think that
when Joel is on a stream, it's the worst stream ever. Uh, apparently, you know, the two streams
that we've done together, uh, the first one was nominated for worst stream of the year. Uh, and
the second one was nominated for best stream of the year because I nominated it for this year
because I loved it. Tuesday on Tuesday, we're going to do keep talking. Nobody explodes this
time. We're going to switch off. We're going to do a little longer this time and we'll switch off.
Uh, keep talking and nobody explodes part two on Tuesday. Just got the confirmation. Jesus Christ.
Hype train has been completed because, uh, not to be, uh, over not to be overshadowed by my 40
community subs, but it's just me. That's all right. Here's the, hold on. All right. Listen,
50 community subs just came in from Zyxia. 50. All right. That's right. That's five zero,
50 fucking subs. Everybody, every concurrent viewer is potentially going to be subscribed
to this channel. It's at some point, if you stick around for long enough and you do, and you come
to most streams, you're going to get a subscription. If this shit just is, this is out of control,
right? Like I mean, mathematically, how much longer can they be like two to 300 community
subs every stream? Like, see, you know, I see them saying to say, this is a 69, 69 subs from
phylactery. Jesus, guys. Oh my God. And they give the, they give the 69 number every time.
Level five completely gets over. We did it and I made it harder. All right. I'm going to make
this impossible next time. I guess I could just like, I guess I could just like turn it off.
Right. Anyways, but, but that's huge fucking money from both you guys. Thanks for the 50 Zyxia
and 69 community subs from phylactery. But what I was saying is all, whenever,
whatever somebody, whatever a streamer gives community subs to their own stream,
they're just deleting a percentage of money. You know what I mean? It's just like, here you go guys.
Here's 50 community subs. I just, I just deleted money. It's just gone. That's like, that's like,
that's like throwing like pennies away. You know what I mean? Like don't do that. Don't, don't throw
like a nickel in the trash. What the hell are you doing? You're crashing the economy. You're just
paying Twitch. Yeah. I just said that paying Twitch money was throwing money in the trash.
Oh, that was probably not the best choice of words.
Ladies and gentlemen, twitch.tv. If you want to hang out and have fun, remember I'm a streamer
here. I love this. This is a great platform to exist and you know, it's everything and it's also
nothing. Twitch, hang up for a while. That's all right. I just did that. I'm fine. I literally
absolved from all crimes at this point. Yeah, I did. I'm good. Anyways, all right. Let's get
started. We're going to play Stardew Valley OST. We're going to go over community content art.
So why don't we do that? Isn't it beautiful? Let's get it on screen. I'm going to just start with
artwork first. That's what we've been doing. This is the third time we've done it. I'm in the wrong
position. This is probably not the best music for the image that's completely, that's on the screen
right now. Is that guy naked? All right. That was, that was a good one. Oh, Stardew Valley.
Here's Saturn eating his children. Okay. What do you mean bottom right? You just freaked me the
fuck out. I thought there was something on this image that I didn't see. Don't shout this person
out. Why? I mean, it's down in the corner. All right, coming up. This is another doodles from
Core Monster. Please, if you submit art or anything, get your, get your, get your shit on the
bottom. You know what I mean? So we can know. So it's not just me. So it's not just me sitting in a
chair, taking what you've created and going, yeah, that's, that's good. Me. Nice. Hey, we succeeded on
the, I'm okay. Thanks for the, uh, 238 subs and the 7,200 and fucking like a hundred dollars in this.
Here come the emails. Free Skype account. Anyways, this is cool. Uh, this is, looks like some doodles,
which are always cute and interesting. It's literally $700. I know it's a lot of money.
I just want, I know it's a lot. There's plans though for that money going directly in a circle.
And it is just wandering because I'm just going to put it back into, into the Twitch stream.
Oh, it is going to Twitch, right? So if I get a hundred dollars and I put like $80 back into the
stream. Fuck! Here's another one from Cora Monster. Stalks her in a tumble. Ah, Cora, this is the
number one, Bia? Is this supposed to be the first Bia? Oh wait, no, that's Bugleberry. Is it Bugleberry?
Oh, is that Bugleberry's urns? I don't even know my own lore. Bia-berry. Bullshit. I wish I could do
even 5% of this, by the way. If I could even do 10% of just doodles like this, I, this is,
I would have drawn the like tiger eating the guy dream. You know what I mean? I would draw
so much shit. I would, there was so many random creatures and monsters up here that I just,
I would be drawing. I wish I could. No, I can't. I cannot learn. I cannot learn. It's no one. No,
I cannot. No, I cannot. I went to school for this. I paid money to an institution to learn how to do
this and I'm un, not teachable. I learned. I'm just too, I hold a pen, I hold a pencil like this,
guys. You know, I, I can't learn how to draw. I can't do it. And I know my limitations and my
limitations are, okay, here we are. This is what I'm incapable of as a person. Funny voices, noises.
That's it. That's all I'm gonna do. You know, we've got like noises. For instance, like you've
probably never heard anybody be able to go like this before. Like who can, who can do that that
you know? How about this one? How about that? I never get embarrassed on stream, but that just
did it for me. I don't know why. Cause I saw the, I can see the preview over here. You got, see the
chat is right here, right there. You guys are right there on this monitor. And then my webcam
and my preview is right there. So I look over at what you guys are saying and then I, who's that
fucking weirdo? You know what I mean? Like for instance, I'm looking at you guys right now.
Who's this guy? And I fucking don't like him. I can't put, this is why I don't do webcam.
Like I'm too distractible. I'm distracted by my own face. This is what happens to me in the mirror.
I'm not kidding. When I get out of the shower, I'm just like, I'm like, what are those, what are
those fishes that if they see themselves in a mirror, they get like angry? What is it called?
The beta. You know, if like your cat sees itself in the mirror and it's just like,
like that's what I, that's what I do every day. I'm like an animal that sees another like animal
in the mirror and thinks it's another animal, but it's just me. I just greased up. I told you,
I'm not lying. I told you guys didn't think I was mad at a sludge. You guys didn't think I was made
at a fucking sludge. Nobody believes me. Nobody believes me. Do you believe me now? Do you believe
me now? You believe me now, huh? What's he talking about? He said like he keeps slipping
his finger off off the A button when he's playing this game. Oh, I just touched this and slimed you
guys community content, but we celebrate all the wonderful things that people in this community
create talking about you. We're not talking about Jeremy being a cat or fish or a dog that sees
itself in the mirror and thinks it's another dog and freaks out. Um, very good work. Very good
stuff. These are a couple of thumbnails from the second channel. Might as well show them. They're
fantastic. Although do they have it in there? I think these are all by the same artist, by the way.
I love this. This image is fantastic. I think this is actually from the game itself. That's so good.
I know it is. It's so good. God, don't you like wish you were Spider-Man sometimes? I love how
it's just done. I love how just done with me Spider-Man is in these images. This is like what
it's like when you live in a city and somebody comes to visit and you take them around for a
tour. And this may have been like the like the 500th person that has done this and they're like,
and you're like, yeah, I've trained. This shit is real. This is this everything. It's all connected.
All connected. We need variety. We need different things to happen.
Me too. I'm talking about like the same thing happens. Those of you that weren't here. I'm
talking about the Han Solo wires in the ride at Disneyland. Some of you might not remember
this and maybe you weren't here, but I can't even explain it. Anybody get anything I'm saying? I
gotta be very clear. Does anybody get this? I mean even like three people. Does anybody get this?
Nobody can remember this? This is like the same thing as the Han Solo ride 50 times in a row.
Because I mean I need to like review this VOD and like bring it to the doctor. Hey, oh yeah,
it's like I got my physical covered up. Doc, what do you think about this? Can you just like go over
this footage for a little while with me? Can you just watch this VOD and then like then help me
here? This is a dream you had. This is from VR. It's multi trip. Nice work. I have this.
Yeah, this is the acid sludge. My body's just made out of it. Isn't there a superhero or a
supervillain or something that has like acid like ability? Probably me. Remember this manga sucks.
This is a fantastic image. How dare you say something so ridiculous? This is fucking awesome.
Oh, you're referring to the story. The story. I get it. This is great work, Bill. Here are some
doodles of the rat movie characters. Getting a little closer actually so you can see it better.
We've got, I don't think about this game. I don't know who these characters are
in the game. Like their actual names. They actually, the characters in 3D Movie Maker
have real names and they're wild. I used to know them all. Like Dick Dastardly Richard,
that's his name in the game is not that. It's like, it's like Gregory. I'm like,
we need that lore. Well, his name is Dick Dastardly Richard. Well, it's been amended, sure.
No, no, no. I'm saying like not in the lore, this character's name is not Gregory. His name is
Richard. The actor's name. Yes. But I like, I like this one. I like this one. I love the super
expressive artwork that people do. Although, it would be credited as Gregory. I like cartoon,
almost Looney Tunes style of overexpression in style. I love it. I wish I was capable of it.
That was a rumor, yeah. Let's zoom back out. Here are some more doodles. Get it all.
Get it all. Is that mustache hair? I can't help it. This is just how I look. You know what I mean?
Like, if you tell me to smile for a camera, like I just have like a goblin face. Like I can't help
it. I can't help that. I've tried. I, cause I can't smile. Smiling normally for me is just like,
I can't, I just, I can't do it. Like in a picture, me going like, no, I can't do it. I feel like too
fucked up trying to do it. Like, no, I can't. I feel like I'm just, I'm pretending. So I always
just do this in a picture. I always just go like, which that's fine. I can't do a big wide animated
like smile because I just feel like, cause every time the picture is taken, like for instance,
like take it, take the picture. Like, like I'm the fucking psycho in that image. That there's not a
good look reaction. Yeah. Yeah. Look, I'm doing it now. Like that cartoon villain. Oh, this is
great though. I like this. I like the, you got a lot of the, you got a lot of the nuances here.
This is over here. This is over here. Very good. But do we already have it?
Hold on. You already got it. Right. Okay. So hear me out on this. So this image, this image
is, that's how I look in pictures. Like that's the, that's the type of image where like you're,
you're on like vacation somewhere and the person's taking the photo. There's like three or four of
you in this photo. I'm one of them. And that's the face you make while the deep in the distance,
you're smiling and like the volcano back there is erupting. And you, that's you, that's the in
between from, I'm smiling and happy to, there's a disaster over there. And it's boom, right there,
right at that moment. I'm like that in every photo. Ask Kim. When we go out and we're like,
oh, let's take a, let's take like a selfie together. Kim will take a photo and it's just like,
she's like, no, no, no, not that one. Let's do it again. And I'm like, okay.
No, no, no, that one's no, no, no, you can't. And then I'm like, all right, let's, let me do it.
Let me do it. And I take, I take the photo and I'm just, I take the camera and I'm like,
I try to get it in the right spot. I took for me to take the photo because I know when I'm
going to press the button. Right. And then I just do, I end up doing this. That's real life. Go to
every picture I've ever been in. I, that face every time. Just telling you facts here. I put it all on
the table. You know, what do I care? Thermal bloat. All right. We can, let's get back to community
content. God's sake. What an egomaniac. Egomaniac is like airing out his insecurities. Isn't that
like the opposite of an egomaniac? Oh, what an egomaniac. He's like telling us about his insecurities
and he's like, he's showing us his real side. It is. Is it? Hold on. If I tell you, hey, I don't,
I don't like the way that I look in photos. I do the same thing in photos. I look, I don't like the
way I look strange. Wouldn't an egomaniac be like, I look good in every fucking picture. I am so
handsome. I'm the most handsome person that you've ever met. Isn't that what egomaniac is?
You're talking about yourself. We've seen this. We saw this before. It's stuck into the last one.
Look at that big brain up there. Look at this huge brain that's up there.
So bad. So bad. Idiot. Bald. Oh my God. Malding. Sour Please. Bold. A YouTube link. Now that's
completely accurate. It's just a YouTube link. Steve, follow me. LOL. What's going on?
This is fantastic. This is by SnoozingCopter. What's going on in this stream? Idiot. Bald. Bald.
No, this is good shit. I love this. Even got this. I mean, typically the camera would be this way,
but even got the foam to work. Oh, I sort of flipped this, but just go like this.
But actually I can do it right now. That's too much. Not quite wrong. Can you tell I'm new
at this? It's good. Actually, I actually like it like this. I think it's better like this because
the wine is pouring upside down. The wine is now the number one thing that you want to look at in
the image. You know what I'm saying? And then this is like his arm flowing down. I actually
like it like this. I'm serious. Wine actually is the front and center. Why are you drinking
wine out of a beer glass? This is completely judgment free zone here because I drink whatever
I want to drink out of any cup that I can get. Oh, you have to drink wine out of a wine glass. Why?
Why can't I drink wine out of a Pac-Man cup? Who cares? It's just a cup. It just holds the
thing that you then put in your stomach. Who cares? Because why? So you guys can look good
in a picture? I don't care about that shit. You know, I don't fucking care. This is great,
though. Seriously, thank you. I'm on a carnival. I got a good Clint Eastwood face going here.
This is the Wailord. Wailord is currently downstairs. Wailord has become another bed
for Otto to sleep on. Otto has been climbing on top of it and just laying on it and getting
comfortable on it. Wailord is now Otto bed number three or four. Get a picture of that?
Okay, I'll tell Kim the next time that she sees him doing it. Here's the thing. My camera sucks.
I hate taking photos with my iPhone because the camera looks like somebody spit on the lens.
Get a real phone. I want, no, I'm waiting until somebody releases a small phone. I want the SE,
but Apple decided that they were going to just kill the SE, not sell it anymore,
and make every phone three times bigger. I don't want a big phone. I want a small,
very easy to hold, thin, small phone. I don't want huge phones. I just looked over here and got
scared. Like, it just freaks me the fuck out for a second. Here, this is on the other monitor right
now. Get that off. I want a small phone. Carnival was one of the most fun times I ever had on stream,
and I loved it, and I'm happy that people thought it was fun. There's another image.
Well, we're doing community content tonight. Derma of the future. Derma of the past is probably
more accurate. Derma of the past. Gotta be young again. Derma of the future. Derma of the future
is gonna be walking around with a cane. Just like, I'm gonna be leaned over, hunched over.
Yeah, make this Derma of the, race that to make a Derma of the past, and to get swole again. I don't
think I could ever do it again, and look at this shirt. I used to wear those tank tops. I still do.
Gym stream. No, I understand now why you drive by all those old people, old ladies and old men,
that are just going like this when they walk down on the street. They just go for a walk,
and you're like, what are they doing on there? And they're just going like this.
I never understood why they were doing this. I didn't get it. Like, why are you doing that?
But you did, you're just, they're just moving around. They're just getting their arms and
their muscles and their blood flowing, and then they go home. That's what I'm gonna do.
I aspire to be that now. Rue crew in public. No, that's, what? Oh, okay, I get it. I get it.
That's, but this is good. Thank you. It's good shit. That's how I used to look. Man, I was
riding cheesy. Riding cheesy from Ike. Thank you, Ike. I like the nose. Very cute. Riding cheesy.
No helmet. Well, we don't know, we don't know that he's operating the vehicle.
He could be sitting still. He could be at a parking lot. We don't know that this is being
operated. By the way, it's not real. This is not really happening. Wait, somebody get a helmet on
him. This is an image of a cartoon character. What? This is actually pretty interesting
considering you go, oh, was that just the giant rat? Well, it is. But from the post, this person
has imported the giant rat into Source Filmmaker. And I have the link for that right here. This
apparently is the Source Filmmaker files for the, that giant rat. I don't know how you,
I don't even know how that was impossible. So I wonder how you did that. He must have had to
just model it, right? And then import it in. Rat movie three in Source Filmmaker. I just ripped
the model and ported it into Blender and ported it. That's fucking cool. That's awesome. I didn't
even know that, I thought they were made out of like bitmap images. I didn't even know it was real
3D. I thought it was just like fake 3D or something. That's, I guess it can kind of have to be,
right? I thought it was just like bitmap. Fake 3D. Yeah, like remember like Mario RPG? That wasn't
real 3D. It was just fake 3D. It was sprites. Yeah. Yeah, like a sprite image or something.
Well, look at like polygons. Like I didn't know they actually had like modeled polygons or
something. I don't know. 2.5D isometric view. Like Mario 64. I guess Mario 64 is 3D. I understand
you, Jerma. Okay, good. All 3D is polygons. Yeah. Yeah, that's true. 5G Jerma. I'm making a new
emote. It's going to be Jerma 5G. And it's going to be that image that I just took of me smiling
with like scan lines on it. You know, like, huh? But I don't fucking know what's going on.
I think this is used to support. That's really awesome though. I know it's the same exact face
because that's what I know. Screenshot that one. All right, coming up next we have. Oh, this is big.
This is a big boy here. Jerma95 gumball eyes. $4.20. I think we've seen this image before,
but not on a community content night. So I love that emote so much. It just, it conveys so many
different emotions for me. It really does. I love it. Worst emote. No, worst emote is JermaTV.
And weirdly enough, I don't want to delete JermaTV because it's, it's, it's just, I don't,
you can't delete an emote. You know what I'm saying? Otherwise somebody will be very, very,
very mad about that. If you delete an emote, people, there'll be somebody, I'll get a letter
and it'll be like, Jerma, why did you delete JermaTV? I mean, there was a JermaTV community
where we did that and we used it. And I'm going to be like, and then I'm going to have to put it,
but I don't want to, you know, you can never delete something. You can only add stuff. And
especially considering, well, your vault, vault coin is going to get deleted. And this face is
going to get deleted too, because there already is one here. You know, there's going to be two of
those. So that's getting deleted. But you can't, I just don't want to delete that many emotes.
I deleted next. Yeah, I deleted next because it turned into one of the most spammable things
ever. And you could, people were just saying next on every single thing that was on the screen.
I would look over and it doesn't matter what it was. It was just like, next, next, next.
It took over the entire chat. So I was like, I got it. I have to get rid of this. What a mistake.
This wasn't for me to add this. I have to get rid of this.
Those are the old times. Some old things need to go away. You know what I'm saying? Like,
German next. It was only around for like two months. It wasn't like it's been here for like
five years. It was here for like two months tops. And then I was like, I can't do it anymore.
That's true. I know, I know. Here's another, uh, doodleishito. I'm not even, what is this?
Is this a cigar? I thought I'm drinking coffee. Am I drinking coffee through the cigar? Is that
what we're supposed to be implied? No, it's just, it's just here. Imagine you had a chin
that fucking big. I feel like it would be a problem. How many of you guys lie in bed like this?
Like even if my chin was like an, I got a big chin. I do. I have a very large chin area,
like frontal chin. If this was even another half an inch down like this, an inch down,
when I lie down in bed and I hold like I'm on my phone or I have like my iPad or I'm just lying
there, you know, you go like this. It would be, you'd make a mark here. You know what I mean?
Like it would just, if you have a big, huge chin, you'd be pressing it down like into your neck.
You would just like hit your trachea and you'd be like,
uh, you couldn't put your neck down.
Anyways, this is good. This is my first time drawing Jerma. Oh, it looks great. What did you
do this with? Uh, we sit in them here. This doesn't look like a mark. This looks like, um,
like crayon wax or something. It looks cool. It's digital. Well, if it's digital,
it's supposed to be mimicking something. Like is it looks like kind of like wax, like crayon.
All the brush and Photoshop. Yeah. I know. I know. I know. I'm saying like it's like it's waxy.
Look, do you know what I'm saying? It's texture. Yeah. Like a crayon, like you and what is all
these, the animals from the Sims, the Sims for a second. I was like, is this the right streamer?
Is this like a different person? Okay. It's the drug dealer from the sim. Okay.
Buy drug, please buy drugs from me. Clip and report him. Oh, get out of here. This is, uh,
at the very least seven four confirmed. We're, if we're being honest. All right. So then yeah.
So seven four, that makes me how tall that's a, let's just say that's a full foot, right? Let's
say this is a full foot shorter, right? That's like six four, six three. What does it say? By
the way, where to pop this shirt? LOL. Asking for a friend. Um, I got that Nightwing shirt
at a clearance section at, um, I don't remember the store. It was, it was, it was the clearance
section. It was just like, these are things that are on sale. Hey, it was from some comic book store.
I don't remember what it was. I don't want to give you false info. It wasn't Walmart.
Walmart does not have Nightwing shirts. I could do it. Same universe as Nightwing.
Yes, they are in the same universe. It's a clown car, I believe. Looking good.
Uh, I got something to tell you guys. Caught his mic. Oh, these are doodles. Okay. I'm never
getting rid of that shirt. I hope nothing bad happens to that shirt. Really. You know, sometimes
you go into the wash and you take clothes out and one of your shirts is just like torn up for
some reason. You're just like, oh, what the fuck? I really hope it doesn't happen to the Nightwing
shirt. It's going to get caught somewhere and get torn or something. I'm going to, now, fuck it. I'm
going to start hand washing that shirt. That's, that's, I'm hand washing that. I'm not going to
put it in the washing machine. I'm scared. Go down here to the rat. Michael smells. There you are.
Look, I even zoomed in on it. Everybody loves Sheet Hill. You know, has it made an appearance
on stream in like six months? He's on vacation. No, he's on vacation. I'll come back soon. He's
on a long vacation. He's on a very, very long vacation. And I realize that's what you say
children when, uh, somebody potentially dies. But Cheeto is doing just fine.
When your fish dies. Where's, where's Mr. Guppy? Oh, oh, little Timmy. He's,
he's just on a long vacation. Oh, because you know that that kid's going to forget
everything about that fish in like two months. But that's not the case. He went on vacation.
Uh, huge money came in. Huge money. Mick Tavishes gave 10,000 bits. Thank you, Mick Tavishes.
10,000 bits. Yoruba, I swore a long time ago that I'd give you big bits once I got a full-time gig.
I did. So here's big bits. Thank you. Those are very big. Those are enormous bits. Those are,
that's a hundred fucking dollars worth of bits. That's a lot of money. Thank you for the ridiculous
bit drop. Glad to hear you got a full-time gig. It pays well. Did you eat Cheeto? Is he inside of
you? Why did I read that one? Excuse me. I like this, uh, kind of the neon look. I like this down
here. This is a Jojo reference. It probably is. Yeah, it is. Right. I've never even seen Jojo,
but I feel like I know the first five episodes already. Looks very good though. I do like it.
Those like blended neon edges. I went to art school. Failed, but I did.
It's Mr. Sneak Man. Look at, look at this neck. We got the, we got the same neck. I'm not looking.
Ew. Yeah. I look at some, I told you, I don't care. At some point you have to,
at some point you have to accept that you have a turkey neck. Or like a turtle.
I remember a couple of years ago when I still was like, oh, I don't like that. I looked up
and this is real. I looked up like how to get rid of the weird turtle lines on your neck.
I looked it up. Uh, it turns out you can't, you kind of can't. I started moisturizing down here.
This is fine. This is going to be fine for a very long time. This is going to be just fine.
This, however, is not going to be fine over the next 10 years. I'm going to be one of those people.
I'm going to, I'm just going to wear turtlenecks. I'm going to be like at the beach in a turtleneck.
People are going to be like, oh, wow. How old are you? You look really, really young.
Yeah. I, um, I'm, I'm, I'm 41. It's like, well, your voice fucking sounds old for that.
Yeah. I'm 41. And my, but my face is going to look fucking fricking like this.
And then I'm going to, I'm going to like take my shirt off at the beach and it's going to be just
like dusty and wrinkled and decrepit. And everyone's going to be like, holy shit. I thought that guy was
like 40. He's like 70. I'm going to have like a young face at like 60. You're a lich. Ego. Perfect
face. You, we all have perfect faces in the eyes of the Lord. Come on. Oh, this is, oh, wait, wait.
This one's a little more abstract. Who is this person? I, I need, who is this person? I don't
know. Like who, who is this imitating this, like this thing? Who is this? What character is this?
The character's name is Killer Queen. I got, I got to look this up eventually. I'm going to like look
up, I'm going to go to like the Killer Queen, Jojo's Bizarre Adventure Wikipedia profile fan page
and just read. I like this though. I'm a little more, I'm a little more jacked in this one,
the name of this one. I like how Bob, I got a nice, a nice, a nice buff look to me. Watch Jojo. No,
I can't. It's too many people have told me to do that. All right. You know when enough people tell
you to do something and they preface this always by going, hey, oh, you should really, you could,
you would really love Jojo's Bizarre Adventure, but skip the first two seasons though. No, no,
no, no, just don't watch the first like three seasons. Watch season four and season seven
and then they, and season six, halfway through season six. Don't watch the first two seasons
ever. Don't skip. What the fuck? Don't skip. What the fuck? Nobody says that. How many times? Hold
on. We gotta, we gotta go over this. People, I have heard not to watch the first season of Jojo's
Bizarre Adventure because it's like fucking different. It's not the same. People don't like
it. First season sucks. Don't skip it. Those are fake fans. Wrong. You see my eyes fucking scrolling
through this. Look at, I'm like, I can't even read, like, I feel like I'm reading a reverse teleprompter
and they have it at times 10 speed. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
I'll watch Jojo's Bizarre Adventure. That's my fucking, all right. You know what? Fuck it.
Listen to this. Listen to me. I'm gonna look you directly in the eye for this one. I am allowed
one anime per year. It's 2020 and it's not going to be Jojo's Bizarre Adventure. It's, it's going to
be back on Titan season four. Oh, I like, this is good. This is a great image. It really is.
There's Halloween mask Jerma. This is a great image for, I don't know if it works in an emote,
but this is like backseat gaming. This is backseat gaming the image. I fucking know everything.
I'm sorry. I know everything about you and you're not doing it. Let me help you here. Let me help
you here. You insignificant tiny fucking non person that's ever played the game before. I
know everything. That's good. I like it. What else we got here? Then you got the stomach,
stomach is, is very accurate. Why is the giant ride coming to kill me? He's got a knife in his
hand. What does it say? Chat is cute. Oh, I don't, I've got, hold on. Let me move the camera for a
second. I want you to see who made this. I thought it was about him. It could have been.
Pymations. This is fantastic. Thank you. I love it. All right. This image just makes me happy.
You know what I mean? This is one of those images that you look at and you're just like,
I'm happy right now for a minute. The oven mitts. What a nice touch, right?
Can we have any nice things guys? Can we have nice things at all? Get your mind out of the gutter.
I, I don't mean, I don't know. All I see in this image are a nearly Academy award winning actor
and a top 20 streamer on Twitch. I don't, I mean, I don't see anything else in this image that could
be producing anything negative. I don't understand. I mean, I, I, I see like a, a, a nearly
Academy award nominated actor and, and, and, and, and, and one of the top influencers on the
platform. I fucking hate that word. That word sucks. Remember we've, we've gone over that word
before. The influencer is so stupid. It's like they couldn't figure out what to call this group
of people because let's be honest. It's not like, it's not like we're fucking solving
like world problems. You know what I mean? It's just like, Oh, what do you do?
Entertainer. Oh, do you though? Are you Adam Sandler? And they go, no, no, no, no. You influence
people to do things. That's so fucking creepy though. What I don't want to be like influencing
you guys to do something that's weird. Hey guys, I just want to make sure you feel very influenced
by me today. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. This, this, this, this, this is going to get like, this might get
20,000 influence points. I said something and you clicked on it and you, you agree with it and I
influenced your opinion. I'm influencing you right now. You just don't understand it. You just don't
know. No, I prefer Eclan. I way prefer that because influencer makes it sound like I'm supposed to be
selling a product right now. Eclan, way better. You are selling a product. You're selling. Hey,
BRBs buying a night wing t-shirt. I just want to dick around on the internet and like have fun. And
I don't, no, no, no, don't call me an influencer or I'll ban you. Your actions have consequences,
Jeremy. Wait, what? Inside of two Jermas. Jerma lied about what? Jerma lied about 20, Jerma lied,
Jerma lied about sour in 24 hours. No, I didn't. I did that within 24 hours. That's, that's horseshit.
I did that. We got another huge bits. Core Monster gave $50 in bits. You're my favorite influencer,
Jerma. Eclan. Eclan, corrected. Uh, thank you for the 5,000 bits though. You know how bad
somewhere in my brain I want to get on like the fortune 500 list and I could, it would be a fortune
500 Eclan. Can you imagine having to read that as like a guy that owns like 600 fucking real estate
properties? Oh, let me see where I am. Well, I own, what do I own? I own fucking, I own Macy's Target
and I also, I have 500 corporate offices. What's the next page? Jerma985, the influencer Eclan.
He just like tears it out and the fucking rips it and crumples it up and fucking eats it.
Still an influencer. Fuck. What does he do? What does he, what does he even do?
How, how he is, he's at 1.6 billion. I'm only in 1.72 billion. I can't, I can't let this happen.
I can't let this happen. I can't let this fucking Eclan take over my empire. Anyways, if anybody
needed any more confirmation as to Eclan. All right, this is like hurts my head. Okay. Uh,
red germ redemption. I think we've seen this before. This is still good. Still very good.
Free views. What the fuck? Come on. Get the helicopter sound effect on the last one. No,
this is good shit. Betty White the goat. You know, Betty White has a slot machine in Vegas.
It's called, I'm not, I'm not making the, it's called, it's called Betty White's Fairy Tales,
a story time or something. And she has this huge comically oversized like medieval book in her hands
and she's just like, Oh, hey, welcome everybody. It's me, Betty White. Welcome to my fairy tale.
Isn't she like tells you stories while you play the machine. I don't know this by the way. I've
just seen it. I've seen it in advertisement. She like reads the stories to you. I've walked by this
before going, just walked by it. So am I, am I right? 2020. Am I right for 2020? What do you mean?
Am I right? Oh, am I right for 2020? What does that mean? Anime, anime for 2020. What does that
mean? For some reason, the one that I said makes more sense to me. Fireman. This is from Mikey
Loki. I love this song. What a great game by the way. Such a good game. Betty White slot machine.
What would you guys do if one day I turned on a stream and I didn't introduce anything?
I was sitting in front of the Betty White slot machine and just played it for like four straight
hours. And then I, and I turned to the camera when I had no more money left. And I just go like,
hey, can I, can I bum a 20? Hey, can I bum a 20? And then, and then a hype trend happens.
I don't say a word for three hours. Nobody would give anything. I know. And they should.
Casinos and slot machines are a category on Twitch and there are quite a few servers who make
bank on that stuff. No, I, no, no. All right. Here's the thing about streaming. Streaming
gambling to me is the same thing. If I were to stream myself full screen, smoking cigarettes,
just talking. It's like smooth. That's very smooth. Or like just streaming myself
drinking alcohol full screen without even talking. I don't, you know, it's one of those things that
it's like, it's don't want to like, I don't want to like promote gambling to anybody.
I don't want to promote like smoking cigarettes. It's not like I would be
influencer, influencer, influencer, influencer. Let's zoom in here. Uh, this is called
chair Montauk. Hi, let me be frank, Mr. Elbertson. You were never going to get the job in the first
place. This is an institution full of children. I called you here to ask a question. Why'd you do
it? Why'd I do what? Small pupils seems confused or concerned. Chat told me to Christmas killing.
Okay. I see. Even though he killed Santa, he needs to be, he needs to have friendly eyes.
Most of the time drew. I drew this. Don't steal original character. And I got the Aquaman shirt
on. Wait, don't steal original character. And this me, this is me. People's legs aren't that
fucking long. I'm sorry. Oh no. Stolen. That was fucking funny. All right. We got fireman with,
uh, what's that say? Anybody know what that says? It says, look at this dude. Look at this dude.
That's awesome. Look at this dude. That's cute. Very good. Wait till you see the one. What are
you talking about? It says watch Jojo season four only. This is very, very good. The, uh,
any watermark on it? No, there's not, but very good. I can't fucking take it seriously. I'm at
my limit. You're about listening to farts, slapping. Let me move my camera out of the way.
This is from sins. Sin Sue. This is very, very, very high quality stuff here.
Here's some donkey donut because you're epic. I follow like fucking 20 people on Twitter and
half of them are people that I followed back when I was like a machinima partner in like 2012.
I don't, I don't even use Twitter. This is great though. Follow them. Follow this account. They
post fucking good shit. It's pronounced scenes. Scenes. Okay. Oh scenes. Blocking his name. I'm
trying. I think there's another one too, uh, by the same artist. There it is. Season four. A good
one. Season four. All right. Let me give, we're not ever knowing and not ever seeing what this was
and not knowing what I was doing. This is a pretty damn good job. I would say for not knowing. This
one, not so much. This one pretty damn good. I don't even know what I was doing, but this is
great. Germ stranding. Awesome stuff. Never played this game, but heard it was very good. But I have
this thing where I don't play games that are a hundred hours long. I don't really do it. Uh,
I just don't have like time. It really, I, Red Dead Redemption 2 took me think like 40 something,
50 something. I don't have time for it. No, I don't have time. I don't have time. This is awesome
though. You beat it off stream. I did. It's like 30 to 50 hours. Let's get that artist over here.
Make sure I don't block their name. Evan Maple Syrup. 100 hour stream. Imagine the joke potential.
Uh, no, I think after like 40 or 50 plus hours in the same game, that's when I start reaching
and I go, man, I've been, I've been doing the same thing for like 50, 60 straight hours.
I should probably like come up with something to do, say, and then people guys is where I get the,
that's where I get the farming minus twos. All right. Why is everybody spamming it? I don't get it.
I don't understand. It's just maybe like a big mouth, like a big toilet or something. What is
this? Toilet bowl that you shaded over. I don't get it. Why is there no toilet seat? That's a
good question. I don't know. Derma peeve. Look at this dude. Nice to meet you. Somebody gets it.
I never get dehydrated. I recycle all, um, I don't know what that is. This is show face, please.
I don't get it. This is supposed to be you. It's supposed to be you guys.
And then I'm showing my face. Yeah. The nice touch fireman is put out because of how wet I am.
No other face. I only have one, man. This is great though. Thank you. I'm gonna get some more here.
This is, uh, Derma rumble. I got the artists there in the corner. Who's up here? Who's,
who's watching? Minecraft. Uh, I don't know. Uh, Mario and Luigi. Uh, Peter, uh, Peter Griffin. Yep.
Brover. Brover. Uh, that's the worst Peter. Bill Gates. I've never said Bill Gates before.
I don't think I've ever said it before. Look at how much bigger I am than these two puny,
puny combatants. I don't even stand a chance. Look, even you even need to bring a chair this
time. You got to bring a chair. This is the might that I, you know what I mean? I don't know. I'm
trying to think of the word for exudes. There it is. Thank you. Somebody said it. Uh, this is
great though. Thank you. From that one big chicken stream that somebody squished my face together and
just looks modern. Modern. Derma Warhol. Oh, this is impressive if it really is two inches tall.
That's kind of, that's very detailed for being two inches tall. Do you have like one of those big
magnifying glasses? Like the guys that fix watches? It's real life scale. Draw onto scale. Everybody
say it. Yell about it. Everybody yell it. This is really detailed though. It really is. Thanks a
lot Quinn. The Axe Fireman by Mikey Loki again. Look at the itchy eye. Sometimes this happens
where like the lining of my eye will just be itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy for not even like 10
minutes and then it goes away. Like, oh, it's horrible. It's just only one eye too. I want to
itch it. I know I try not to. Oh God. Oh God. What does this mean? What does it mean? What does this
actually mean? Anybody know what this means? It's just like, oh, horrible scratch. Itchy. Horrible.
This is great work though. Get well soon, Jeremy. And this is from Invaders. Doing my best. Doing
my best. Appropriate. How do they know about the eye? Spliceable spleen. Five immunity subs. Thank
you spliceable spleen. Look at eye drops. Eye drops are tricky for me because when I put eye drops in,
I know they're coming and I know it's about to happen and I just tear up. I start crying and
then it hits my eye and it's like just tears streaming down my face and it almost makes it worse.
It's, I can't, it's just weird to me. I can't, somebody else, I can't, if somebody else is
going to do it, not possible. I have to do it myself. Every time I'm outside in the wind,
I think it's just really sensitive eyes because when I go out in the wind, I will get these just
tears that just blow back like this until I get inside and then I have this like redness
from the lines of tears. Somebody's redeem a wink. Yeah, yep. Which eye? The irritated one?
You get to pick the eye. Which one? The irritated eye or the non-irritated eye?
Which one? Irritated? Irritated. Okay. I have to move my mouth when I wink. I don't know why.
You know what I'm saying? It's like the muscle that's here is connected to here. Is that odd?
Like, it's normal? Good. There you go. Excellent work. Whoa, this is, this is, this is busy.
This one's real busy. Let's get out of the way for this one. All right, we got the moon. We've got
Gloom Man. We've got Cheeto. We've got Pac-Man. Gloom Man. This is me. Beam Bag Sonic. That's the
air, hot air balloon. Nightwing. Why is everybody, what's with the Nightwing? How many times have I
worn that shirt on camera? Oh, it's Jax. That's right. It's Jax. Hundreds, you think? All right.
I just had a, you may have seen it in my face because the camera's on, but I just had like an
internal, is it on now? For a tenth of a second. This is fucking scary. What is going on here?
What is this? What? It's Fireman, but it is like a, what is the rat? What is this? Is this my room?
Oh, that's the door. Oh, the body sliders. Right, right, right, right, right. Okay. This is crazy.
This is crazy. I love it. An artist name? Any artist name on here? I don't see it.
I do not see an artist name. No, I don't. Thank you, though. Garfield down in the corner. I just,
I didn't acknowledge Garfield. I don't know what this is. It's a JoJo thing. I, I got, I got a question.
So, I've never seen the show. I don't know what this is. I don't know what that is.
What's the proper reaction to have to that image if I've never seen the show? Like, yeah, I know
those two people. That's, I don't know, for all I know, guys, this is, what the fuck is that?
Uh, okay. For all I know, wait a minute, I was going to say that, oh my God. Okay, I was just
going to say, for all I know, this could be Beavis and Butthead. And the image that I just showed on
stream was a combination of Beavis and Butthead. I was going to say this could be just Beavis and
fucking Butthead, and I don't know who they are. The ultimate streamer. Ask Joel about JoJo.
No, what is he going to say? Hey, dude, wait, what, what about JoJo? And he's going to go,
ah, it's a good show. You should watch it. Joel, are you sure you don't want to show me
these characters? Why don't you show me two of the characters on stream? Hey, Joel, what, hey,
Joel, what about, uh, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure? And he's like, oh, journal. He turns on his webcam
and starts like, doing like poses and shit. I'll be like, now I get it. Now I get it. But, uh,
long story short, I don't get it. Maybe some of you do. I don't know what this is supposed to convey.
There's no, no shoes on. No shoes on with a plastic bat. Oh, this is, and the, the picture
is going into the motion of throwing the ball and I'm not fucking ready. Oh, here's the back of the
card. Jeremy Elbertson, Boston Red Sox, hometown, Boston, Massachusetts. Positions shortstop.
After rage quitting tennis, Elbertson made his way to the realm of professional baseball
with an all-time batting average of 0.001, which actually means I probably got walked
once in 10,000 at bat. Oh no, batting average. That means I accidentally like,
bunted. Not on base percentage. Okay. Jeremy's only major league hit was a walk off grand slam
that won the Red Sox the World Series last year. Last year. When asked about the historic moment,
club manager Alex Costa said, look, this guy wasn't here supposed to be on the team. David Ortiz got
the flu and we just had to pick some dickhead from the crowd. Who even are you? How did you
get into the locker room? Did somebody link that video of me in the two grand slams? That's like
my favorite video. Where's the video of me doing the two big home runs? That's like, that's my
favorite video on YouTube. Where is it? I have to, I'm going to queue it up for the video portion.
I love that video so much. All right, hold on, hold on, hold on. Is this it? Sign in to confirm your
age. Oh, get the fuck out of here. Give me the real video. It's not it either. You guys are,
why are you guys so unhelpful sometimes? Right here, right here. No, that's not the one. This
is not the right one. This too. This too. I'm going to throw both. I love this so, no, I don't,
stop linking me this video. I know I said that 15 years ago. I know. All right, where's the,
where's the one that's the two? Unhelp. This is, what are you doing? No, you, I can see, I've
memorized the rickroll one now. Somebody please help me. Mods, mods, mods. I'm like calling my
mods like I call my mother. Mods, mods, mods. No, there's, there's, there's another one. There's,
there's one, there's two when I do the overhead swing. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong. Mods, mods.
No, mods. Soup has the right one. Soup. There it is. Okay, there it is. There it is. Oh my goodness.
This is like my favorite video on YouTube. All right. Okay, that only took fucking like
six straight minutes. Hi, bullet hole. Good shit. Show the video. I'm going to put it in this whole
video portion that's coming up in like probably 30 minutes. I'm not going to show it. I got it.
It's right. I got it. There's a whole video portion. Just, that one's free. Oh, I almost
instinctively just fucking clicked the X. Look at those. Look at those bumps. Thermobumpy.
All right. Click the X. Click this. Jeff, thank you. Thank you. Rhode Island, Jeff. Thank you.
Oh, this. Another one. Another one. Another one. I want to get rid of another one. I don't like the
veins in the eyes. I don't like the eyes. This is. All right. That's fucking really good art though.
Really good art by Iraqli. OD. Thank you. Outline Miami? Oh, look at this one. This one's good.
This is by Teens again. I'm going to get out of the way so you can see the whole thing. Christmas.
This is pretty much every major holiday terrain this year. In Germany you look like Harrison Ford.
That's a compliment. I'll take it. Motion blur. Yeah, that's a pretty good touch.
Those of you that might be new viewers, in point blank two, I did the bonus round, which is nearly
impossible for any humans to do. You have to shoot 30 targets that are in a line in five seconds.
Humans actually can't do this. I did it. You didn't do it. Fine. I didn't. Somebody else did,
but they live in my same body, so that's fine. The humans can't do it. They connected it to a
fucking computer and finally like scientists were all gathered around. They were like,
holy shit, we actually could do it now. And then I showed up. Or a person that lives in my head did.
That was not me. His name's Jackson. I love this. I want this. I want to sell this, but not this.
You know what I mean? You know, sometimes streamers and YouTubers do, oh, we're going to do pops.
Oh, yeah. I'm going to get a pop made of me, a little figure, and it's going to be me going like,
but like, I don't want that. I don't want just like a, no, no, no. I want this.
I want this to be sold. I want that to be me. I don't want it to be like a pop. I want to sell
something like this and have it just be supposed to be me. 3D printed. U2s it. What is U2s?
U2 sounds like, like, I feel like there's like a, like a, it's not like a dot com after that.
That's like a fake YouTube. Like accidentally have people click on something. U2s dot what?
That's like a, they make, they make pop vinyls for YouTubers. Oh, oh, okay. For YouTubers.
How expensive are they? Actual porn links in chat. I'm not clicking on anything.
I got plenty of links already queued up here.
Got the smirk down. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
I am going to personally come in here and time this person up.
No, I can't even, cause I can't do that. Physically, I can't even right click in here.
Like the broadcast software that I'm using. I haven't changed. This is my own fault.
All right. Very good work. Very clean. I'm hogging Jerma. Please relax. Hold it in.
Hold it until the video section. Jerma, please. What? What? What did I just do?
Hold it in. I thought like, I'm like, by my breath, I'm hogging. Hold, ah, whatever. I don't care.
This is good shit though. Really nice work. This is a depiction of the Halloween stream
when, uh, Fugleberry was doing something and that's fucking funny. Free me?
Some of you that might have not seen the Halloween stream, uh, there was a segment
where BF Fugleberry, who's a very well-liked character, uh, did a pottery class to YouTube,
to you, to the people watching. There was a segment on that stream and the stream had
8,000 or 9,000 concurrent people watching it. And after about 20 to 30 seconds of this character
being on screen doing the pottery, this is not a joke. This is not me making this up and embellishing
to like, oh, look how funny, that's fake. A 3,000 concurrent people left. 3,000 concurrent people
dumped me fucking immediately. It was an unbearable segment. It was the reverb. I know. It was a lot
of things. But yes, this is, I love this. This is by, uh, Needles and Noodles, if you can't see.
It was the audio and I didn't even know. It's all right. I'm gonna never forget that.
Somebody just shit my pants. Also from the Halloween stream when I climbed. I do remember that.
It was a very, very uncomfortable feeling. Did not feel very good. By the way, you know, like,
when you, when you look at yourself in pictures or in the mirror or something,
I feel like, I feel like that's what I see in the mirror. You know what I mean? Like, there are days
when I'm like, no, I don't have a bald fucking head. It's the way my hair is parted. I just
want to make sure everyone's aware. It's the way my hair is just parted for a second. Black.
Nobody can freak out. I know the people are going to clip that and go, oh, because that's what we
do on Twitch. If somebody's got a bald head, we fucking point it out every day. If somebody's
smaller than 5'10", we point it out every day. And that's what we do. That's what we do on Twitch.
Welcome to Twitch.tv. Oh, it's nothing, but it's also everything. By the way, don't be bald or
small because we'll hear about it every day. Anyways, someone just shit my pants. Bald, bald.
It gets funnier every time. The music just like changed to angry and it's like fucking freaking
me out. Okay. Back to normal. Back, back to what we were doing. Community content. Like, oh yeah.
All right. This is just like, this is just a spray paint tool. This is just spray paint.
This is pretty good. This is pretty good. Oh, did you buy this on Redbubble? You got your weird,
like, what are these, what are they called? What, you got it? What's it called? A Germanium?
A Germanium? Uranium? What are you guys saying? Uranium. I can't, the chat is going too fast.
I can't read it. It's going too fast for me to read it.
Germanium. Germanium. Germanium. Pretty cool. Pretty cool. What does it weigh when people come
over? I think this is farming dynasty. Just scroll chat. No, that don't work. If I scroll chat,
if I scroll up, scroll up, it comes, rips back down. Scroll up, rips back down. It happens.
Who made this? Me. I did. Me, me. I did. Me, me, me. Yeah. Okay, cool. Nice job, everybody.
This is from The Sims. He's sick of us. No. No, I'm not. I mean, that did come off. That,
that did come off as, like, like, over it. But I assure you, I'm not. I just, like, I know that's
what's gonna happen. I know I'm gonna look over it. I'm just, I'm saying it for you. I'm doing it,
I'm saying it for you. You don't have to say it. He hates streaming. Do not. You wink and then you
leave. Why are you stealing our jokes? I'm here too, man. It can't be me. I made this. I made this.
No, it was me. No, it wasn't. It was me. I did this. My eyes at you again. No, you know who actually
did this? It was Rhode Island. You didn't make this. Neither did I. We have to unionize now.
You guys are gonna unionize. We're gonna unionize. It was the whole state of Rhode Island.
Why is my eye so itchy? Oh, I'm gonna get so mad. Oh, I'm gonna get so mad. What? So, so,
he's going too fast. Take a Benadryl. Oh, take a Benadryl. Oh, I'm gonna take a fucking Benadryl.
Hell, my 6k viewers have unionized. What the fuck would that even mean? This is awesome,
though. I love this. Thank you. This is from The Thing. Oh, I keep having flashbacks of that
particular scene inside of the vent. God, that game was fucking ridiculous. I don't own Benadryl.
Benadryl is a medicine that your parents have in the house, but you don't. You know what I mean?
I don't have Benadryl. I have Tylenol and Nyquil. This is fantastic, though. I love this a lot.
Test him. Test that guy. Test him. Make sure we can see the artist's name. If we do, we can.
If you take too much Nyquil- If you take too- Wait, hold on. If you take too much,
you'll start seeing spiders. Omega lol. Take too much what? Giant enemy spider. Benadryl. Is that
real? Omega lol. What? Fog champ. Jax. I have a Jax pose. Oh, this is supposed to be my smile.
God damn it. How did you know I was going to do this? Thank you, Todd. Oh, look at this one.
Stay tuned. Is this Shito? Snowman. This one's interesting. Look at all this stuff going on
back here. All over here. Snowman and Fireman. Wouldn't Snowman melt right now? Be careful,
Snowman. Stay tuned. This is a comfy image. Comfy image. Get the whole thing from it. Good
stuff. So you're going to notice there's probably going to be a little bit of Christmas or a lot of
Christmas related stuff in here. I'm sure you've seen a couple already. That's because I didn't
do a community content night in December. So this is like all of November into like the middle of-
the end middle of December. So that's kind of where the cutoff is here. My bird likes
your background music. Your bird's a hyper intelligent thing. It says, Jerma, I warned you
not to watch. Really good teeth work. But that's- that's really like high quality teeth. Gums and
everything. This is- it's terrifying. It's very well done. Good teeth, by the way. A coat hanger
in the closet. Down to the most minute of all details. Yes. Nice work. Who did this? Who made
this? Not on there. Nice work though. Is it on there? Look at this shit. Now this. Oh yeah.
I love how shiny it is. I'm gonna pick- this is gonna sound crazy. I know it is. Anybody else?
It's too weird to say. It might be weird. Anybody else want to pick this up and smell it?
I know what this smells like. You know, it's like a- that like kind of new plastic kind of shiny
plastic smell. You right? New GameCube smell. Sure. I know what this smells like and sometimes
I need smells to like get like into a full package. Can't clip this so I can- clip this
for the doctor because this- this whole thought is going to the doctor. Anyways, this is fantastic.
It is very well done. It's very professional and it is made by this person here. Okay, I was- this
one wasn't gonna make it in. Uh, but I- I mean like come on. This is just- I had- this- I- it's like
I'm gonna- I got it. I got it. This is cute. I love you, Jerma from Lucas. You and me. It's just like
that's- I can't- I can't just skip over this. Nice job, Lucas. Going on the fridge. And then of course
we have the best boy in the world, Otto. This is so cute. And like this music is like making me emotional.
You know what I'm saying? It's like I'm getting- I'm getting in the ears. I'm looking at this. It's
like this is so- this is so- I love this dog. You know what I mean? And I got this like cute dog music
playing in my ear. Looks very good. He's recovering very well, by the way. He has stitches that have
to come out next week. But he's healing and he's resting. He's doing good. And this is great. This
is awesome. Very, very good work. I love the cookies. Who stole the cookie? Thanks for this.
I'm sure we can see who you are. Can you see? Yes you can. There we go. What a good boy. This is
somebody made the giant rat in Spore. It's pretty good. Pretty good work. This is a military land
vehicle. Play Spore. I tried to, remember? I'll have to go back to it one day, but nice job. This
is awesome. I like the tail. The tail just looks like a plunger. It might even be a pl-
Are there plungers in Spore? They might be. You're looking at us, huh? Is it because we're dentists
of the Outer Worlds stream? Arguably the best part of that game were the dentists that weren't
even actually real. We made them up. Fun. This is great, though. Thank you. Fast German versus
Purple Alien. Classic series by one of the green screen video makers. Fast German versus Purple
Alien. Always, always trying to one-up each other. I wonder what's next in their adventure if there
ever will be a third episode or fourth episode. It's a great series. Maybe one day we'll get
another episode. And look, Fireman's got his seatbelt on. We're about to find out. Not today.
Not today. This is great, though. I love the helicopter. He's safe. Well, he doesn't want
to fall out. He's just a circle. The germacopter, yeah. That magenta and kind of teal look.
Magenta and green. Psycho bubblegum eyes. Choco hair. Sweat check. Gum smile and nose.
Strawberry milk flesh. Stick and melting. Anatomy of a germapop. We made it. I like these things.
The Spider-Man. Sonic the Hedgehog. I love those things. Even if they're weird and they look like
shit and they're gross. I love them. I'm right. I got it. What's the music? This is the Stardew
Valley OST. Playing in the background. Don't rub it. What am I supposed to do? I can't.
Don't touch it. All right. I won't touch it anymore. What am I supposed to do?
Wash it. Pour water in it. All right. Well, we're getting. We're almost at the end of the art
section. Then I'm going to. I'm going to flush my eyes. I will rinse my eyes with some water.
In about 10 minutes. Very good, though. Jax versus Jerma. I know who wins this one. Jax
every time. Always. This is by Rain Loaf. God, I love those old light gun games. They're so fun.
It's just you can't. You have to play them on a TV. And that TV was such a pain in the ass.
Once that TV got in that room, I couldn't fucking ever get it out until I moved across the country.
It's so fun to play them. I wish I could have captured it better, but you just kind of can't.
Delete the Z-Mode. This is awesome, though. It's like painted. It looks like a painting.
Floating around the universe. What is that? Is this a drone? Why am I? Watch out for the blades.
This is gonna like slice my arm off. Farmer's Dynasty guy. Oh, OK, OK. Right, right, right,
right. This is the Green Goblin. The Flannel Goblin. The Green Grinner. Yeah, because I'm,
yeah, because we were trying to get it to fly. I remember, yeah. This giant rat.
Flannel Farmer comes to New York City to deliver fresh produce. This does look like the front of
a cereal box. Like if this is a strawberry, this is a marshmallow sugary cereal. And it could be
called like Flannel Farmerose or something. Tomato cereal. And we need like healthier options. You
know, I would I would eat like a vegetable cereal. I wouldn't. Why is this image? I don't understand.
Like, is it Duncan? OK, let's see. America runs on Duncan. Dungandonas.com. Rain low.
That's my hand. You just, hey, y'all just got influenced. What do you think about that?
Oh, stop, stop showing it to me. I might order it one time. One dime. Weird. This is good,
though. This is very well done. Very well made. This is by Appleshift. A small, incredibly highly
detailed animated short here. Take on me. This is very, very, very good. This probably took,
this probably took a very long time to make. Each one of these images is as high detailed
as the last one. Thank you, Appleshift. This is fantastic work. Why is he so mad? Wait, what is
this? Why are you clipping this? What is this? Why, why play this right now? This makes no sense. I
don't get it. Sad. So sad. So sad. Oh, right, right, right. This was during Monster Rancher.
Why is this so sad to this part here? Because this is where Monster Rancher 4 is when this happened.
I don't, that game doesn't exist in my brain. It's OK, I get it. All right. All right. It's
the last thing you hear before you die. Another animation here. I don't know what this is called.
Jirba is a blocked person. Really good NBA 2K face scan technology, because that's what it looks
like when you did that in any of those games. God, this is fucking crazy. Mom did not get me
an ice cream cone, except this time I'm a bowling elf. Apologize for this. The Roblox guy? Why?
Good stuff. This is the same image on the screen. This is the wire frame of this. You know what I
mean? This is the same exact image. You look like the guy from Gorillaz. Murdoch? New Gorillaz member.
Yeah, I get some Murdoch vibes from this image I do. Of course I know. That's like my favorite band.
Nice stuff. Changing energies a little from here to here. Why is Fireman wanted?
Wait, what? That's not on my screen? No, that's in the image. I don't understand why he's wanted.
Because he killed Snowman. Here's your real face cam.
Don't worry, I'm just winking in this image. I don't know why I thought for one second.
That this hair was photoshopped on. I did not think this was real hair for a second. I was
like, well, what's wrong with this hair? It's like you like pull the hair from like somebody's ass
and put it on here. This is the only part that's photoshopped. Wearing a wig. Nice work. Oh, look
at this. Coffee, Cheetos, and chicken. That's what they were for Halloween. Group costume. Hey,
that's easy costume, though. That's cheap. Doesn't cost any money. Well, I mean, yeah,
I mean, yeah, I'm just talking about like this one. It's just, yeah, no, yeah, it did. Now,
this is like a good expensive costume. I just saw the coffee with like a tag, like a sticker that
says coffee on it. Well, that was, that was a cheap costume. Guy in chicken suit. Left to right,
Jeremy. We go left to right. I love this stuff. It's awesome. I can't believe three German fans
know each other in real life. Say it. I already did. I said coffee, Cheetos, chicken. There you go.
I am, I'll be honest with you, though. I am absolutely shocked and floored and surprised
by the fact that people think this is so interesting or so funny or they've taken it and it's something
that they like to a point that they're going to do a Halloween costume based off. That's just like
fun. Thanks for that. Thank you for thinking that's that funny. Thanks for thinking that
that's that interesting because it's just makes me happy. I'm glad you think it's fun.
Jeremy, I just made lobster rolls. Nice. Good work. You got to do something. I got to get,
I got to get in touch with the person responsible for making fireman because it's, you guys,
you guys love fireman. There's got to be some opportunity to do something with fireman.
And not in a T-shirt, something else. Steal the rights from them. No, no. I actually talked to
the person that did that drawing and we already agreed on that it wouldn't just be, all right,
thanks for the fucking thing that everybody in the community likes. Bye. Thanks for the money.
No, it would be very fair to them. As fair as I could possibly make it. No, because I mean,
that is people that just love this shit, you know, make like a flush toy. I'll have to look
into these. That sounds like the mafia. I'm going to make it as fair as I possibly can.
Yeah, that does sound like bad. No, no, no, no, no. I've made it fair. I said I've made it,
hold on. That's bad. Yeah, yeah, no, no. I've already talked to him. I've already talked to him
and I made it real clear to him. Made it real clear. That's going to be real fair to them.
To let me use that image. Real fair to you. I made it real clear. Jesus. No, I mean, I mean,
they're going to get paid. Sounds fucking horrible. Paid. No, paid in money. Paid? No, paid in cash.
This is fantastic though. Good work. I love the bright, sunny kind of shiny look. Very good job.
It's like they, it's like they can hear us talking. I swear to God, I load these images up
and I just go, go, go. I put them in a row. I, I, I've not like gone through all of these.
I load them up. I, I, I don't know. I swear to God. Paid and laundered money. Well, here it is.
This is what it might could potentially maybe look like in the future. I don't know. Give us this.
This is not mine. Somebody, this is, somebody owns this. I love it. That's awesome. Iron Man
is a currency. Legendary. Yeah. Legend. The grin. Pretty good grin. We can see that who made it,
right? There we go. Say the line. Thanos? No, I'm not Thanos. I never will be Thanos.
And why would I want to be Thanos? I want to be, I want to be Spider-Man. This is from Spooky's
Jumpscare Mansion. I hope that's in the game. Is it real? I don't know. Is it
really funny if it was? Uh, Vilemi just, just dropped 30 subs, 30 community subs from Vilemi.
Thank you, Vilemi. Huge sub drop from Vilemi. Thank you. Congratulations to those that now
can spam Jirba TV. That's a lot of subs. So many fucking community subs. Team TV. Now I can't delete
this. This is what happened. This says, my five-year-old niece loves Fireman so much.
She wanted to draw him for you. Ella and Pitcher Cat. I love you, Jirba. Get well soon. Love Ella.
So precious. So precious. I just hope that, I just hope that she doesn't watch when I talk about
shitting my pants. Hope she just sees the Fireman content. Family content. You just ruined a moment
there, but now you have something in common with them. This is so cute. This is adorable.
I'm telling you, Fireman's gonna be worth millions. Fireman's gonna be worth millions.
That's a, that's a, that's a 500 million dollar franchise.
So cute. Thank you. panthaneevadestaxes.org. Nevada Republican Party. I'm fighting for you,
Dean Dingus. Imagine if your billboard was, your billboard to run for president.
There's even an Aquaman t-shirt. The Nevada Republican Party. panthaneevadestaxes. Oh my god.
This is so stupid. The crying face.
That's from one of the DOS streams when we played, what's it called, like Treasure Hunter or something?
Treasure Catcher, Treasure Grab, whatever it is. This is very zoomed in.
Video game time. Got my nice slicked back villain hair that I have at conferences. That's a good
at teeth. I'm telling you, this is like the third or fourth image that has really good teeth.
I like this. I got more hair than that though. It's not fair. I got more hair than that.
It's thinning, but I still have more than that. And finally for the image section,
you've reached comedy level two. Jeremy can now tell a knock-knock joke to other sips.
Pretty good. That's it for the art. We're going to move on to the videos now.
And I'm going to go just, let me just rinse my eye because we're going to move on to the video
portion. Thank you everybody again for your artwork. That was part one. There's still about
20 days or so of stuff that's from the last 20 days. We'll be doing that next week. So thank
you everybody for your contributions, your artwork, your videos, which we're about to see.
And yeah, you guys are fucking talented. I'm glad to showcase talented people. It's a lot of fun.
So it's time for a pee break. Time to wash your eyes and I'll be right back. Hello everybody.
We're going to move on to the videos. There are, let's see, 50, 40 to 50, maybe 50 videos,
40, 40 videos. Big bits just came in. Even more money contributed to the stream. Thank you.
Thank you to Chachooty Chabooty for $100 in bits, 10,000 bits. 10,000. Thank you. Grandma,
I love you and your community so much. I never want you to stop. This is the only fraction. This
is only a fraction of the money that you deserve. Oh, let me stop you there for a second. I don't
have any plans on stopping, right? But I've told you guys this before, you know, as long as I'm
having fun, then I'm going to keep doing it. That's it. I'm never going to force myself to
do any of this, you know, because then it becomes, it doesn't become genuine,
but I'm still having fun and I'm going to continue to probably have fun for a long time.
But just know, I need to stay interested. I want to stay interested because I don't want to just
do it because I want to where I have to. You know what I'm saying? That's like two more weeks of
stream. No, but that's, that means a lot. And then they say, uh, you deserve this for the countless
hours of entertainment you've given me and my friends. I think I have seriously watched ask
nicely for crits and pulling it off with the pump brothers 500 times each. Sorry that I'm not able
to make it here more often. Uh, love you. Wish you the best of luck with all your future projects.
PS chat has a nice booty. Well, thank you. Uh, hold on. We'll get away for the car drive by.
Never apologize for not being able to make streams. Some of these go very long and they go deep into
the night and they happen more than a few times a week. So don't feel like you're obligated to
have to be here. I know that's asked a lot. It asks a lot of people to be like, oh yeah, just,
uh, spend 40 plus hours, 30 to 20 to 40 hours a week with me. People have things to do. They
have things come up. I don't, you don't have to be here. You don't want to, you speak very fast.
Do I speak really fast? I slow down a little. All right. I'm just all right in the future.
I'm going to slow it down. So from here on out, my voice is going to be at a speed. That's minus
4% from here on out. Good. But no, thanks a lot to booty. Anybody that's watched the video,
like I've made that many times just, it surprises me every time somebody says
thanks for the a hundred bucks back to it. We're going to the video portion now, as you can see,
incorrect. No spoilers up top. I don't want you to see spoilers. This first one is called
stardew valley has to stop playing. All right. Here we go. I'm going to go off cam for these
because I'd rather we experienced it together rather than me have my face covering up a bunch
of it. So let's go. It's called animated. I mean, we're talking mainly bug. And when I say we're
talking bugs guys, we're talking like grasshoppers, ants, beetles, spiders. Would you eat a spider?
Good. I wouldn't see like ants are one thing, just regular black ants, not like fire ants,
just regular ants. I feel like I wouldn't be that huge of a deal to me. If I knew they were clean,
it was like they were three doctors and two scientists that were standing around in a
circle around me while I was about to eat it. And they all the all of them are just like,
yeah, that's delicious. You go ahead. The nutritional value is off the charts. And it's
great. It's better for you than eating an apple. Maybe. I don't know. One of those scientists
says it might not be a good idea. I'm it's gone. All right. Where is this supposed to be? Wait,
what? I mean, we're talking. What happened here? Oh, it's during that was a long time ago. Wait,
that was a very, very long time ago. I thought I didn't I talk about this like, like, not even
two months ago. Holy shit. What a weirdo. On to the next one. That was pretty good, though.
That was pretty good animation. Wait, hold on. Is it another one? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's another one. I'm confused here. Wait a minute. Mainly bug. When I say we're talking
bugs, guys, we're talking what is there another one of these like grasshoppers, beetles, spiders.
Would you eat a spider? I wouldn't. Why is this coming back? Why is this coming back?
Is your one and five teaser animation? Really? But when I say we're talking bugs, guys, we're
talking my ears. That was no spoilers. No spoilers. All right. That was this one's called
Jerma dream. Siri, take a note. No, no. What's the note? It's not a cave.
Sharing two sticks with a guy, some homeless guy threw up in his mouth. Mickey Mouse comes in
and drains all my battery from my iPod. I kiss him. Siri. I think this is a dream thing.
I think that's a dream that somebody did somebody have that dream or
I don't know. Take a note. No, no. What's the note? It's not a cave. Sharing two sticks with
a guy, some homeless guy threw up in his mouth. Mickey Mouse comes in and drains all my battery
from my iPod. I kiss him. You were talking about keeping a dream journal and how fucking weird it
is. All right. Yeah, I see. I feel you. This one is called Jerma in Star Wars. I feel like I'm in
fucking Star Wars. I ain't slowing down for nothing. Oh, what? You just put the V. It's just the music.
I think I just ripped out the code. Stormtrooper. All right. Moving right along. This one's called
1985. The ideal set up by the party was something huge, terrible and glittering.
A world of steel and concrete with machines and terrifying weapons. A nation of warriors
marching for the same thoughts and shouting the same slogans perpetually worked the same face.
Mike Tyson, the hardest puncher ever. Magic and punch in the face by Mike Tyson.
This is awesome. Machines and terrifying weapons. A nation of warriors and fanatics marching
forward in the same thoughts and shouting the same slogans perpetually worked.
Except for these guys here. Those are the two main characters.
Jesus Christ. This one's called the Jerma Showdown. I think we may have seen this
at the end of a stream. I think I put it on one time, but it's probably worth seeing again. Maybe
we haven't. Maybe something similar. You're going down. You're going down. This is so stupid.
What a loser.
Wait, it was an ambassador body shot? An ambassador body shot. Holy shit, that's fucking funny.
This one's called Just Waters of Nazareth. Whatever that means.
Pretty good. Pretty good. My first encounter with Jerma. My first encounter with him.
This is what it looks like if somebody were to make my whole face out of paper.
My entire body is made out of very delicate paper and it's your mother packs it into your backpack,
but doesn't really put the care necessary into making sure it doesn't get ruined.
And then you take this out in class and you're like, mom, what the? Mom, why did you put it in
here? I told you I wanted to carry it. And she was like, you're not carrying that. It's too delicate.
And then you have to have everybody see this. So you're implying that you're my homework.
In a sense. In a sense. This is called a crude pre-stream thesis. This is a song.
This is from Neon Genesis Evangelion, but it's a custom song. Let's see. Let's hear it.
I pronounced it correctly. Of course it is.
So it is custom lyrics too. All right. Let's see it. Let's hear it, man.
That was awesome. That was awesome. Y'all didn't want to give that one a chance until it got started.
Gift this person a sub for crying out loud. Nice work. That was really, really, really good.
There it is. Somebody did it. Clap, clap, clap, clap. Collapse all around. This one is called
German Wars, a Star Wars one. Hopefully there's not. All right. If you've never seen Star Wars
before, there might be a Star Wars clip in here. If you've never seen Star Wars, I guess it might
be a Star Wars clip. Am I gonna? Should I? Can I show this one? I think it's just like a joke,
right? All right. The Star Wars coming up. Here comes a Star Wars one.
Oh, this is like.
Is that a grenade?
Red group, go group. All fighters follow me. I told you they'd do it.
I'm going down. Here goes nothing. I'm going down. No, we're not. We're fine.
Oh, shit. Sorry. Sorry. Sir, we've lost our bridge deflector shield.
Intensify the forward. I don't want anything to get through.
Wait, hold on. You can't just end it like that. You can't just end it like that.
I fall twice. Okay, my stomach hurts. What happened? Look at the title.
German wars return to the two minute max runtime. This is going to be like five minutes long,
so I had to make some big adjustments laughing. That's the best part. That's seriously the best
fucking part. Oh, my God. Link link. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You want you definitely. I love porn tabs.
Oh, man. That was funny. That was by Coco Jam. Nice work, dude. Seriously. All right. This one's
called huge German shitpost, so I'm ready. I'm ready to mute this one. I got my finger on it.
Vaude. He was going to skip. I mean, I'm just standing around. Did I just lose my vaude?
Did my vaude just get fucking crushed? I mean, the title, it is titled huge German shitpost.
Did I lose the vaude? All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Moving on. Moving on.
Moving on. Moving on. Moving on. This is German the hedgehog 2019 movie teaser.
This summer. It's pretty good. Quality shitpost. Yeah. This is called. This is called
German destroys the cutest thing ever. And you have the money to spend. I already know what these.
I already know this video. I already know how this video ends.
You know, we've all we've seen the video. All of us have seen this video now, right? All right.
Listen, and you have the money to spend. I would get rid of one of these. I would make a statement.
And if you want to hear what I'm talking about here, I'm talking about a real state.
What would that be the cutest? What would this be the cutest fucking thing you've ever seen?
My god, this is called a rant wasp and the man rant wasp and the man.
So I think the thing about, um, I think eating going on a diet, it's not a bad idea.
Oh shit. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait till he lands. Wait till he lands.
Okay. He landed up in smoke. The roles have been reversed. Yes, they have no.
Who cares if I even show spoilers? You know, there's no spoilers to see.
Uh, we, uh, this is worth showing again. It is. This was shown at the very end of the stream one
night and it's fucking hilarious. So this is the, uh, this is a wager fulfilled pepper.
I got time. No, no, please. No, I'm trying to turn it. No, I'm trying to turn it. If I go into the
black hole one more time, I'm I'll eat a ghost pepper on screen. You know what I mean? Like
that's the kind of shit I need to make sure I don't do. Wouldn't that destroy my stomach? Yeah. So I
better not go in the black hole. This has to go up. This has to go up. Uh, this next one.
Whatever. Just play it. Play it. Oh no, my C drive. C, Jeremy downloads. Oh fuck. There is no sound.
What do you think this is? Yeah. Some mad man made this and also made this.
I'm not sure whether to be happy or to be very upset about this,
but now it exists in front of a green screen. So you can do things like this.
There's the trumpet or whatever, a horn, some kind of horn. She's a stupid streamer.
Jay Bum Bum said that you, how did you get that name? I can't believe that. That's the real Jay
Bum Bum that just said that. But yeah, now people can do shit like that. This one is called
Psycho Streamer Destroys Cybertruck. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Oh my fucking God. Well, oh,
maybe that was a little too hard. Should we try on the mirror? It didn't go through.
That's a plus side. Okay. It's beauty.
Maybe that was a little too hard.
Okay. It's beauty.
This is like, this might be one of my new favorite videos. It's just, it's just so stupid.
It's just, you find the perfect places to put these stupid things. Is it better than the
baseball? No, nothing ever will be. But that's still, that's still fun. Slate me. That was so
fucking stupid. I love it. This one is called Fireman's First Christmas. If you remember,
I believe this is the same animator from last time. Nobody say any swears.
There's a five-year-old that's going to watch this. That's a little too hard for me.
It's snowman. Their first meeting. Hey, that's not very funny snowman.
They're going to keep, it's a never-ending conflict. The unstoppable object versus the
immovable firepower, whatever it is. Why am I outside? What am I doing out here? Look,
they're friends. They found a way. Uh-oh. Do I get out of here? Help me. Do I not have a bed?
Look, it's Otto. I'm sleeping. What? I'm sleeping. I'm sleeping.
Fireman's First Christmas. That was so cute. Cast, Jeremy Albertson as me,
Fireman as fireman. Look at this dude. Snowman as snowman and sleeping dog is Otto.
What is going on there? That's not my face, right? That is not my face. It's not. No,
it is not. That's not my face. That's somebody else's face on my body or something. That's not
my face. It's not real. I know it's not real because I know what my face looks like.
That was fantastic. We're a little late. Christmas was a little while ago, but
uh, Kitchicat, that was again, fantastic. Very, very, very well made. Very cute.
We all love it. Coming up next, this is called Jirva at the Carnival.
Do we have audio on this thing? Oh, that was loud. Try it again. Do we have audio on this thing?
Let's find out. Does it have audio? Can you hear it? I got, I have no reaction to what just happened.
I was initially going to start laughing, but then I was just like, oh, I, I, I don't,
I have no reaction to this. It was just too much. Okay. The, the fact that it's stuck,
it stops when I turn around and it tails off killing me. Oh, that's fucking funny.
What else we got? This is called Jirva Loses His Sanity. Here we go.
I'm confused. All right. That was called
Insane or whatever it was. Um, have we seen this one before? I think we may have seen this.
It's definitely worth showing again. It's another Star Wars one. Don't sue me.
Oscar? Oh, I get the Oscar. Another Star Wars one incoming. I hope you guys have,
I hope you guys have seen the movie Star Wars franchise. Do we have audio on this thing?
Let's find out. That was a, that was a good clip. I liked that one a lot. It was very good. That
was really good. I liked that one. Nice work. Any more Star Wars? Now this is a Jirma's house tour
and already from the first frame here, this is accurate. This is very scary. How accurate this
is. I like this. They say, I hope you like it. By the way, there is no Jirma is small joke here.
The doors are big because I can't do proportions. The bed is a reference to a stream.
Let's find out. By the way, there's no short joke here. This room, this looks exactly like the room.
The music too. How'd you get the music in here? Kim, yeah. Let's see if it's accurate. This is
it's 100% accurate. It's my green screen room. What else? Where else we going?
Hang a right and this brings us to bedroom. Okay. Hold on a minute. Pause the video.
This is like kind of, this is a joke, but how awesome would this be?
This would be incredible. It's a normal bed. Now let's not look at the door. This is actually
really well made. Toilet. Am I going to piss? I'm going to have to close it if I piss.
I like, I would like that. I would like that. I really would. That painting, the paint job.
I want a weird ass room. You know what I mean? Eventually I just, I just want to have
just some strange ass rooms that have wild paints on them and fun. That was really well made. Nice
job. This one says this is secret dog ending is what this one's called. Secret dog ending.
Let's see what it is. There you go. Auto spotted. Bad dog. Bad dog.
Uh, this is very, I like the, the, uh, I want to see it again. I love the like,
hi everybody. He's like sad. All right. Let's watch it. There you go. Auto spotted. Bad dog.
Bad dog. That was, that was ridiculous. This is how I attack. That was a Garfield scream.
Holy shit. That was a Garfield scream. No, no, no, no. That's, that's, that's Tom from Tom and Jerry.
Right, right. Not Garfield. Garfield didn't scream. Since when does Garfield scream? Okay.
This one's called, uh, shut the fuck up. I'm listening to Bratz birthday mixtape.
Oh, there it is. There's like the guy. I really like lick my mouth every 15
seconds. Oh, I need lip balm. I got these dry ass lips. This is, uh, I've been showing this
before, but I don't think I've ever shown this on stream. This is called, I can't even save in this
game anymore. I don't, I don't really know the context of this, but he tries to fight him. And
all right. Like what's, what are these auto automatic fucking videos? Must watch. Yeah,
I ain't watching your shit. So what, what's that? What's that a reference to? What's, what's that?
I can't save in this game anymore. What's this? Is that like a CS go gun game or something?
I'm not going to watch that. I don't want to watch that. We've got like fucking 15 more videos.
It's a famous bunny hopping video and see if CS go. You can save your items at the end of the round.
Oh, it's a currency thing. Ah, I see. I see. By the way, the video has 300,000 views.
Currency thing. All right. This one's called parks and recreation, but it's German
parks and recreations, but apparently it's, it's me. No, careful.
People are still ending these videos with the earth exploding from rat moving.
I think I've said this before. That's the easiest way to end a video. It's so simple. If you're just
like, how the fuck do I end this video? Easy. Just have the earth explode. There's that's why I did
it. It was just, I don't know how to end this. I don't want to do that much more work. So let's
the earth explodes. Okay. I really love reading a book. Yes. That's another way to end. It's just
ways to make it so you don't have to do any more work. I think this, if this is what I think it is,
I'm shocked and kind of, I can't believe it. I played fear. I played fear a couple of months
ago and one of the things that I was doing was going around because just ADHD. Like I just
couldn't help it. I was breaking fire extinguishers and I think I mentioned to clip every time I hit
a fire extinguisher. I think somebody did it. Thermosphere of fire extinguishers.
I don't know about this one. Can I use this? Is it explode? Yep. All right. Here we go. Three times
bigger. This is going to give me a headache. I don't know. For some reason I thought I had to
use that. How is it already broken? Impossible. What? Oh, this is where I came from. Right. Thank
God. And that's, you guys wonder why I'm doing that. Why does he keep breaking those? Well,
because it's a breadcrumb trip and I know where I've been. There's nothing in there. There's
nothing in there. What are you doing? Oh, I don't, I can't, do I have him in a full retreat?
All right. Guys, when Dwayne the rock Johnson is standing there and he's like flexing in a
mirror, just like looking huge and awesome. And somebody comes up behind him and like grabs him.
He's going to go, you can't, nobody looks cool that way. It's true. Oh, here it is.
I haven't. Okay. This is the electric. That's the electric. Oh no.
I love this game and stay down. I cannot believe you did this. I feel so much more at home.
I can't believe you shattered his computer. So he freaks out. You know, he's had that monitor for
like 15 years. Fun thing. It's a really cool thing. Why am I closed? Oh, it's a different day. I did
it over two days. I haven't been in here yet. Right. Why did I not break that? I should have
fucking known. Really? That's the point. That's why I'm doing this. See, cause I know that I was
there. Missed lore. Missed lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip
lore. Almost two more minutes of this. This guy's doing a really great job of doing the random voice
lines that play when you spawn for the first time in a league of legends game as a champion.
Fucked up medical stuff. You should have seen what the guy did. He flew up. I, I, the guy was
going this way and then he got magnetized his face to the wall and blood splattered. He's going
to be like, what the fuck are you talking about? I'm lost. I'm so lost. I don't know what any of this
means. I thought this was like a Google satellite image of like a warehouse and roads and stuff. I
was like, wait, where is that? Holy shit. How many times did I actually do this? It's just available
for me. So I do it. It's just a, it's just a thing that I know. You know what I mean? It's routine
in a game with scary jump scares and all kinds of weird fucked up enemies. This is routine for
me. It's comfortable. I can't believe I used to do that shit. Embarrassing. I remember when I
thought that was fun. Memories. It's like looking at an old photo. Should I just give this to the
doctor? You know, like should I feel like this is just, this should be in like the, in the
folder of stuff I bring. I mean, seriously, that was crap. I can't believe you did it.
That's, you had to go through like, what? 17, 16 hours of stuff to find it. God damn. Well,
we got it. This is Pokemon gold, Pokemon gold, silver crystal battle, the giant enemy spider.
This actually is a music file, but there is some video to go with it. I bet you can never guess
what it is. See, a lot of people didn't know that there was a boss battle of this,
the giant enemy spider. Remember when I did all this? Feels bad, man. Old YouTube. Yeah, you know,
memories, you know, when you're like looking at an old photograph.
How long can you keep it up for? How long can you do it for? It's like, it's like passing an old
fire extinguisher. This is where it's from. I've never played this game. Why would I have that in
my head for any reason? Probably Smash Brothers. Yeah, definitely Smash Brothers. This is where
they got the Pokemon song. This is where they got that Pokemon song, you know? Remix? Well, I mean,
I know, I mean, of course it's a remix. It's really good, though. Very, very fucking great job.
Giant enemy spider. This is a remake. Yeah, what do you think? This is more music here. This is,
well, technically kind of. This is Sea Shanty 2, but it's German's pirate marching band.
I never played RuneScape before. I know a lot of people love it. I never played it.
That was, I think, I don't know what, what's the, hold on, let's go over here for a second.
I mean, I know this part because, I mean, like LOL, right? But what happens here? What is,
what's going on in this image here? Am I not, is this character not supposed to be here?
Does it get killed by a dwarf? All right. Can someone explain RuneScape to me in a small,
like three words? Is it hard? Do you, when you die, you're dead? It's, it's RuneScape.
You see like people die in RuneScape and it's a huge problem or something. You lose all your
items when you die. Okay. Stream RuneScape. I don't know if I want to do that. You just literally
respawn. Oh, well, I always thought it was something, this is hardcore or something.
No, I don't have any, but I can't get into like another MMO. No way. You respawn, but without,
so it's like Minecraft. Okay. I get it. Come on. Next is, this is, this is a one second video.
I don't even know how you get a one second video. You can upload it to YouTube, but here it is.
Jerma eats a lunchable. Good. Jerma get mad, then do stunt.
What on earth just happened?
Jerma get mad, then do stunt. I get it. I guess it is just the title, huh?
Regular show. Changed clothes, mid throw. Oh man. These are, I fucking love these.
This is a new Bill Crazee video. Another Bill Crazee interpretation of footage.
I'm going to see how long I can last. It's going to hurt like a bitch. You know what I mean?
I love all the, all the Gary the fuck up videos and Bill Crazee videos because
they're all a little different somehow. Sometimes it's a pool. Sometimes it's a
beach. Sometimes it's a bathtub. They're always just slightly different to a point where I like
watching them. I can't just let a video get to the end because I have ADD and I have to like,
I have to get it right before it ends. I piss off so many of my friends if I watch videos and stuff.
I'm just like, oh, it's done. I'm done. I got to click it too. I know a lot of people do that shit.
I'm one of them. It's called Jerma Boulder. We'd best leave till the weather's better. The rain
loosened some of this rock. I think it's Boulder wanting us to go away. I missed that somehow.
Is that supposed to be from the AI dungeon stream? Here is a mad tyrant Jerma kills his subjects.
Everyone's kind of baby. So this, wait, does that mean that I've been killing babies?
I killed them all. Is that what that means? And not just the men, but oh shit, I've been killing
actual babies this whole time. I think we saw this one. My favorite part is the bonkabonkabonkash.
oh here's another and we have made it to the mostly music well there's a couple of videos
there we made another giant spider joke oh boy oh boy quick somebody make a remix
of this remix no no no no no no i don't i don't this is not what i wanted to go back how do i go
back is that just a four second video two years alone in the world why did that end no no no uh
i've lost my account okay somebody said that sour place is a shitty emote that's why i paused
somebody said dude sour place really like sucks somebody said that and i was like oh it does and
then i freaked out and i pressed the wrong button i don't know i don't i don't have an opinion of it
i think it's cool i guess doesn't i know it's cool it's cool back to back tracking barry coming up
coming up on you this one's called uh giant enemy firebrand giant enemy firebrand more enemy
spider memes because they this has come back hard over the last month or two the giant enemy i don't
get it i don't get it but what is firebrand is that a is it the enemy in the game or something
we need you to do a ghost and goblin stream play super uh ghosts and ghouls and ghosts
ghost and goblins is so hard all right i'll do it i can't tell you i'm gonna beat it but i'll do it
uh that is the end of the videos for this one next week we're gonna do more but i wanted to
break it up a little bit so it wasn't ridiculous too much i wanted to give some time uh and that's
right we've got another one to watch there is another one to watch here's the here's here it
comes and we're going to watch this probably three times to the witsky a couple of doubles last night
he's hit intense straight and it's a right pack at hosel
and both teams storming for the
oh walk off
oh just you didn't think i was gonna catch it in the brawl to the way also the just the small
nuanced way the the shushing somebody back here let's get a couple of doubles last night
i love it it's perfect he's hit intense straight and it's a right pack at hosel
okay it's my birthday today of course new york
imagine i've said every time we watch this video i always bring it up but
like imagine tomahawking a fucking home run hold on there's another one i wanted so badly and
here's the thing about the baseball shit from the green screen i wanted people so badly to put me in
sports videos and shit and not very many people did but the one like i wanted these so bad
here is another one
i just love it's just so stupid you guys are fucking hilarious we have a little bit more to do
and by a little bit more to do i mean we have some music to listen to this is a freeze frame
we have some more music listen to we have uh this one here it's called a giant enemy spider
another one this is called germa spider's final boss
let's just hang out in a dark room and listen to this music the giant enemy spider
crazy into you crazy into you
oh don't even remind me of that oh i had actually did have drinks about that last night i hated it
worst noise of 2020 why this one's called rats rats i forgot yes i did now i remembered in real
time it's still itchy and i i i flushed it with water it's called rats rats rats
michael
i'm not gonna get an eye infection
yeah
what the dub is that true oh you got big guy what the love of dub is that true whoa you got big guy
i did it for you now nobody has to do anything let's go rats rats rats we've got two more songs
next one coming up is called guess who likes you and they say this actually says wait for it
so wait for it is what this says guess who likes you
they bite him in the bod wait for it is this just a song did they make this
it went back why does this work i don't know it does year of the rat in coming yeah
celebrate another on a birthday back and the final song of the evening
is called trap lord spider there was a boss battle in this the giant enemy spider
so turn this shit up i did i did turn it up it's loud as fuck
shit up turn this shit off upside down it's bopping you got there i pissed all over the
toilet i i had to clean it up it was bad i fucking it was out of control it wouldn't stop
let's bring that to the doctor too because that probably shouldn't be happening either
uh all right now that is the end of the community content stream you have a literal leak part one i
should say part one community content night part two will be next weekend and then next weekend
we will be caught up completely to the uh last 30 days or so so we'll be caught up completely on
uh saturday of next week replay the best video of the night i mean it's not a contest
this is not supposed to be a contest not at all this is never supposed to be a contest
the witzke a couple of doubles last night he's hit in 10 straight and it's a right pack at hosel
you're a boomer it's it's a baseball it's not a big deal at all at it in the same place
all right i'll see you guys later that's it for tonight short stream today i will be back on
tuesday or uh jill and i are gonna do keep talking nobody explodes again and this is gonna be we're
gonna switch off this time back and forth so there's gonna be a keep talking nobody explodes
stream on tuesday and then what we'll probably end up doing is we're gonna do tuesday wednesday
thursday of this coming week we've got a lot of other stuff to play we're essentially gonna be
we're essentially just gonna go and tick stuff off the list when is the green screen after i get
a shot of nerve blocking steroids into my ribs and i don't have a time frame for that yet because
that's it's apparently what i'm gonna have to do if you if you missed if you don't know what
i'm talking about i was going to go back in front of the green screen because obviously
oh let me just change the scenes here because this is the end um i was gonna go back in front
of the green screen and do six more hours of green screen content right just because this
this shit is so funny you guys come up with so much stuff and it's and even still a full year
later these clips are still used and still put in funny places that you guys have just have you just
it never stops so i wanted to give way more footage for you guys to use but i've come down
with a strange medical condition where my core kind of around my all in the middle of my ribs
in the back uh in my spine and back and ribs and shit it hurts and my range of motion is limited
i mean i can still move around i'm fine but i can't like throw my arms around and fucking
run around and jump and land like i did my range of motion is smaller it's tighter now
and we're still trying to figure out exactly what's going on but they think that i have to get
i think i have costochondritis i mean i have a hernia which i've said before
but i might also have costochondritis which is inflammation in your rib cage and this really
you don't do anything to treat it there's there is no treatment it's just do a thing that makes
your body not hurt anymore which is steroids like an injection in your like ribs but i will cross
that bridge when i have to but i'm good i don't think it's not like every day i can't walk or
anything i'm fine completely but turning my body more than probably 30 or 40 degrees to the left
or right ah it hurts but that's the reason why i haven't done it yet kind of waiting on to get
all that i want 2020 is the year where i want to get truly back to health because i have been no
it's not that i have been eating unhealthy or being unhealthy my body has decided to at this stage
the last like year and a half or so is to sort of revolt so 2020 i really want to get healthy
again whether that's you know find treatment for the back and rib problems i want to get back into
being healthy and not necessarily oh i'm gonna go to the gym every day but just not kind of feel
like bumpy two three days a week you know i mean if that makes any sense but uh let's do the bits
thanks for watching again the community content nights are always really really fun for me
because we get to watch and enjoy all the funny things that everybody makes and all the great
artwork that you guys do a lot of talented funny people here and i love showcasing it and each one
of these is the third time we've done this well technically fifth time we've done this where my
face hurts from laughing at at least five to ten of these you know what i mean drink water i drink
a lot of water don't worry it's not the water but hey let's go back fitting gave 250 quick guys
do a hype train the hype train did happen i have increased the difficulty on it and if i'm gonna
bring it up to its maximum we'll see what happens after that but i appreciate it nonetheless
ocean dweller thanks for 250 germany you made it harder but people still kind of do it we're
just spending more money now the smart move is to make it super easy so people don't waste
as much and it's over faster just make it like five dollars so if we get to level five instantly
something about that is funny but i feel like it would be annoying after a couple days but i'll
try it i'll try that next room yeah i'll make it like five bucks till i get to level five or
something or i might just turn it off you know it doesn't have to be there but back on soy and
mcdonald's and fast food i don't really i don't really like soy i don't like soy milk i don't
really eat soy products i'm not a big soy fan i don't really take that much dairy besides a
little cheese every now and then and some yogurt but i drink almond milk i have replaced almond
milk 100 with everything else that is dairy wait you're you're you're a chat if you drink almond
milk is that how it works oh shout out to the 4 000 doctors in the chat yeah shout out to all
these doctors uh but yeah potion dweller i'll probably just get rid of it it's a fun thing
to do maybe i'll turn it on every once in a while but i'm probably not gonna have it on every day
we've been it's been around for about a week i'll probably i'll turn on like the hype train like
once every few weeks or something maybe if people really want to do that not every day
peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 germy today i was thinking you remind me of courage the
cowardly dog it is a laugh i've heard this i think once or twice yeah it's pretty close it's pretty
close austin atlantis thanks for the 10 community subs lm man thanks for thousand bits ten dollars
germy you are king thank you for the ten dollars thank you pixel mike for the 1500 bits 15 dollars
they say bog clamp bog clamp i don't know what that means but thanks for the 15 dollars
stupid streamer you make me look bad
thank you uh 1500 bits jamie thanks for the five community subs jamie lm man again
for five dollars on top of 10 you just gave germa would you rather squee or xd
i would like to delete both of those from the dictionary if i had the power
kazi 101 thanks for the 10 community subs xixia 10 community subs on top of the 50 given
not that long after that thanks both of you lm man again 1500 bits on top of the rest
that's even more money 15 more dollars germa may your rats make all the rules
they do they always do rats run the world just don't know it thank you germa 985 for the 40
community subs appreciate that it's a lot that's a lot of money germa 985 autumn dragons thanks
to 250 germa have you ever had a they say there's a certain couple words in a realm then they say
whether or not you have i'm just glad i was able to make you say this out loud well you didn't
um i don't even know i i'm gonna say no i'm gonna say no i've never had a that before sorry your
boy thanks for the 10 community subs thanks your boy appreciate it your boy we also had
250 from zake here's the money can i please have my hamster back i miss him so much he was my only
friend some of you guys give bits every stream talking about how like i'm going to hurt you
you i'm not thanks for the 250 beaker thank you beaker for the five dollars hey germbo
do you know what the record is for your longest stream ever have you ever legitimately thought
of doing a 24-hour stream and then love from the frigid wasteland of northern minnesota
the longest stream ever was 13 hours and it was uh five days ago it was the lord of the rings
the two towers it was 13 hours and 20 minutes or something that's an easy question because
it just happened i've never thought of doing a 24-hour stream because it's very unhealthy
it's not good unless you are switching off with people for instance if there was three or four
people that were doing like a charity thing or it's really just not healthy to sit in the same
spot for 24 hours or more it's just bad for you i don't i could i know i i i was exhausted
i was physically beaten after that 13-hour stream that adding twice that in a way that's
just no fun that's no fun would twitch let you sleep on stream if it was pre-approved
now probably not but maybe but at that point you're like not even streaming at that point
the clock is just ticking just so you can have a 24-hour stream you know what i mean it's like oh
yeah though i'm doing a 24-hour stream except i'm doing 13 and i'm going to just lie down
in bed for eight hours no it's unhealthy i don't want to i don't want to do it the longest you'll
ever see truly is something like 10 to 13 10 to 14 max you know you nobody you can't you're not
supposed to just like sit down like that and just stare at us monitor 15 hours it's really just bad
for you go get a standing desk i don't think i don't want to stand for 15 or 14 hours
you need to as humans you got to move around you get i mean you if i was going to do a 24-hour
stream every every like two to three hours i would take like a 30-minute break but then that's you
know it's just not even at some point you're just doing it just to say you did it which i don't
really care but no no plans to ever do it dad regal thanks for the 250 i'm sick and tired of
all the bugleberry hate bugle boys across the nation are rising up and we're not taking it
anymore i am a bugleberry fan fight for the screams of every man all right can we get some
support here back and thanks for the 250 hey germa glad i could catch the stream after my 10
day stay at the hospital missed you so much that i had dreams of you streaming just random games
like mario odyssey and league of legends anyways keep doing you i'm not sure exactly what you're
doing in the hospital but hopefully you're good to go that is a wild dream to have considering
that i will never play league of legends on this channel i did make a league of legends video
but it wasn't it was grandpa it was me walking into towers that was it yanwen thanks for the
1500 bits 15 dollars from yanwen grima i know your face quite well i can teach you how to
draw i'm certain of it i'm unteachable nobody can teach me how to draw i can't even hold a pencil
right i don't have the patience for it i will draw six or seven lines and then be like i'm done i'm
done i can't i gotta get up and like scream i can't do it i can't do it i have no patience
i have no patience with it i can't sit there like do it no not gonna happen no i can't do it i can't
do it i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it no i can't no i can't do it i can't do it i can't
do it you have an art degree no i don't have an art degree i have the i didn't know what to pick
for a minor in college and art sounded like the most interesting liar you tilt brush vr i was
gonna it was on the list until i stopped doing vr again once i get this bullshit under control
that's one of the plans to go back to vr too but thank you yanwen you are incredibly talented
so please hire me as your art tutor i need a job seriously i can't do it i've tried i've had so many
people try i've had so many people attempt and then i just like i don't have time for it anymore
but this is a great picture let's put it on don't listen to chat you really can't do it
granko uh thanks thanks granko is trying to be realistic with me you learned pottery for a joke
yeah but that's different though you look at how how hard this is to do it takes a ton of time
i don't have i don't have time i don't have time this is fantastic image though yanwen seriously
killing it like always we also had 500 bits from siku 500 subs curls
you can't do curls anymore dummy bear thanks for the 500 bits glad to catch the live stream for
once glad to have you here thank you oh up upster narwhal thanks for the 300 bits
hey germa i donated last night about the germa auto emote and got a question for you
why are emotes not allowed for community content night is there an emote contest coming up soon i
have more 50 plus emotes on bttv and a hundred total that i've made over the past few months
you have just described the reason why that is the exact reason why because there's a lot
and if emotes there would be there would be an entire probably two to three hour section for
emotes what has happened in the recent months is they're discord emotes i will probably not
do an official community emote contest again for a while but what we've decided is open up
emotes for discord but that's kind of the plan for that the discord ones are cool like bits
yeah there's like a hundred emotes slots yeah but you you gotta remember for me just because it
exists doesn't mean i want to have them you know what i mean i want new emotes to be
important and different and i just did you oh well you got a hundred slots just upload a hundred
emotes i want them to all have their own individual value and not just throw up like
30 or 40 new emotes just because i have them and i know that germa tv exists but that was a community
emote you have a hundred slots actually i haven't even looked i don't know i actually i have no idea
how many slots i have and i don't want to look because i don't want to be i don't want to be
like embarrassed emotes to me are did was there something so significant that we thought was
interesting that it needs to be a way to express as a picture you know what i'm saying or just like
randomly something funny that happens i and it needs to have the test of time too because yes
i could have 50 different emotes of the same image but like a small change to my face
but i don't really want to do that discord emote slots oh that would be funny though
to the planets they're all very important to me there's only like one or two that aren't done
5g germa and germa psycho are the next ones because they've the test of time is there
there it is you need to be sure they can stand the test of time we don't want another bald coin
it's the most requested but no to answer your question community content night
emotes would just take up so much time and so many people would just submit them and then
afterwards it's like all right well why don't you why don't you have you have to add those now
it's like well we just looked at 150 emotes how i'm just gonna i can't
it's plating the stocks of bld don't use it buy now but we'll see that look all these things
are subject to change always because i'm gonna bump you here for a second because i don't know
that this as the channel gets larger and there's more and more people here there's more and more
things that need to be tweaked and changed and this is not the channel it was two years ago
it's a lot more people a lot more stuff going on you know i'm saying it the streams might be
very similar but the channel has changed a little like we've we brought on so many more people
this motherfucker's gone corporate we have the same emotes from two years ago
yeah we also have ones from this year like last year too corporate influencer it's all subject
to change it really is e-clown but thank you magpie for the 500 bits apparently the 3d
movie maker rat is named the breeze the wiki also has rocco from rocco's modern life for whatever
fucking reason but that's because there was a nickelodeon 3d movie maker extension add on
there is a nickelodeon 3d movie maker it exists it's the exact same game but with ren stimpy
tommy pickles and rocco and shit you need to stream that no bugleberry emote well the i mean
the book's still out on bugleberry i'm still gauging that one but yeah they had they do have
name another maple thanks for the 300 bits i just say love you jeremy thank you gray the color thanks
with 300 bits jeremy you look legitimately handsome whenever you smile and nod anyone calling you a
smalting goblin is talking pure shit you're like legitimately fucking good looking also
moo crew makes drew crew eat poopoo i did yeah i wouldn't say pissy shitty but i would say
drew crew eat poopoo so that just shows how i how i'm much of a fucking hypocrite i am
thank you though thank you tar alecran for the 253 it's time to talk about your being you're an
alcoholic it's a clip from earlier what is it what is it what do you mean i drink i drink
whatever i want to drink out of any cup that i can get
but what's wrong with that i drink whatever i want to drink out of any cup that i can get
what's wrong with that if you have just if you have like a coffee mug that's clean and you
want to drink a glass of wine put it in the coffee mug who cares is that it doesn't really
matter it's just a container that holds liquid nobody's seeing me do i'm just you know if i was
sitting here having a glass of wine out of of coffee mug no but none of you even would know
i was doing that unless the face cam was on so it's like what i need to show you my like cool
elaborate 40 dollar wine glass no and plus like i have the ninja turtle sippy cups are a godsend
because i can drop them and be fine you know what happens if you drop a glass of wine on the ground
it shatters glass goes everywhere and you ruin your floor forever if you drop a sippy cup with
wine in it on the ground it bounces nothing happens and you pick it up now explain to me
which one is this crazy person explain to me which who's the weirdo there it ain't me
it ain't me tar alecran thanks for the 252 i'm on top of your 253 please don't waste your time
watching a thousand hours of jojo's adventure the only reason people like that nonsense
is because they get stockholm syndrome through watching it for so long
watch ping pong it's literally the greatest show animated or otherwise to ever grace this earth
and it's only 11 episodes trust me i'm like a 100 month sub he's right he's right about it he's
right about ping pong actually true what's ping pong ping pong is actually fucking great don't
listen to that one guy why not there's a lot of one guys in here right now try what only 11
episodes just talking my language only 11 episodes are they 20 what 22 minutes yes okay cool
how many episodes are in jojo 500 500 500 no guys guys i tap out i tap out at extended edition lord
of the rings if i gotta be able to watch the whole show in less than 20 to 30 hours like 25
hours for a whole show like that's 22 minutes in length 30 minutes per episode is not 500 that's
a lie it's like 80 episodes not 500 oh well it's not 25 you buffoon wait why am i a buffoon
people are just lying to me hey how many episodes i i'm asking i asked a question
how many episodes are in jojo's bizarre adventure 500 500 there are five like 800 there are 500 500
oh there are 500 what are you an idiot i i asked a question i asked i asked a question
it's 152 surrounded by liars i've taught you well surrounded by liars
germa maybe there's a reason why they're doing that is you put forth a lies and then they think
that they could lie too no more lies no more lying we're turning over a new leaf no more lying for
you guys or for me you're a dumbass for asking and ban that person no more making no more making
mean rude comments either let's turn over a new leaf and that person somebody said fuck you but
i know they weren't saying it to me they weren't saying they were saying that to somebody else
because they know that if i if i saw that i would i would get rid of them i know you weren't saying
it to me to one chance to one warning you guys are just saying fuck you to each other you have
to be because why would you ever do that you guys with the the thought of potentially being
a internet protocol banned from twitch weird i you have to be talking to each other or something
it must be been an argument hey hank cheesecake thanks for the five community subs four monster
gave the 50 you're my favorite influencer thanks yeah i know mostly lost thanks to 250 i see short
influencer streamer on twitch i give bits thanks for the 250 appreciate it your boy thanks for
the 15 you're the most influential e-clown just e-clown please let me just drop drop the prefix
just e-clown please ocean dweller thanks to 250 i know who makes those slot machines
i've been at their offices in chicago for a luncheon i almost worked there that's crazy
that's awesome almost almost the dev of the betty white slot machine damn
you almost met betty white no guys betty white just like opened the book and read a few lines
and drop boxed 35 seconds worth of footage that's what happened hey spliceable spleen thanks for the
five community subs thanks spleen reaper thanks for the 250 germa why don't you take your one
anime a year to never watch jojo i feel if you were to watch even a single episode it'll open
the floodgates to even more jojo bits references etc it'll ruin the stream for the rest of us
please for the love of god never watch it don't give in this is correct this is correct based
based hey mr mushy thanks for the 500 bits hey germa you're my favorite e-clown
and i think you're very adequate thank you uh pugils thanks for the 500 bits looking cute today
germa chan uh appreciate it uh also thank you to dock d27 for the seven dollars 700 bits
i've been stuck in a metro system with what i can only assume is mr sneak man
the metro system what do you mean where i mean stuck in a metro system like i know i know i know
train but how do you get stuck what happened you missed the train hope you get that solved
hey seven layer wario thank you for the ten dollars i actually really liked bugleberry's
pottery stream please do more streams when you make us pottery and eat spiders just get your
makeup done to look like bugleberry and skip the mask fucking spiders volemy gave the 30
community subs thank you volemy more huge fucking money and speaking of which let us go ahead and
run the credits showing all the subs from today four hours and 20 minutes we're getting to the
end here i'll see you guys on tuesday stick around though there's still a few more bits to do or if
not take off if you want to it's up to you but again thanks for the support there was hundreds
of subs in community subs given today like there is i feel like i say that every stream
every stream i feel like i say thanks for the hundreds of community subs thanks for the
hundreds of subs you guys just continue to do it and it's wild so sincerely thank you
all of you we have a few more bits to do though we have shy void gave 500 bits five dollars from shy
void i just want to tell you not to be discouraged about trying to make art it's a new year's
resolution i wanted to be a better at drawing because of great communities like this one a lot
of it is just practice even if you're not satisfied with the quality you can always just keep practicing
and improving this is very true but also keep in mind that i spend a significant amount of time
doing this and even when the stream's not on a lot of my free time is based around this stream
and trying to improve it and try to make new streams and try to
big projects and try to get contacts with people and this is kind of this is my this is like what
i do instead of something like art and i think if i really really tried to dump dozens and dozens
and dozens of hours into something like learning how to draw it would kind of cut into the time
that i would want to spend working on stuff for the stream and i care very much about it
this do an art stream uh no no i can't i can't i love art i love art but i i'd rather be a
observer than a participant that makes any sense it does it makes perfect sense i say that a lot
but thank you for the encouragement rain low thanks to the 300 bits i'm glad that you liked
my art i've been watching your stuff since 2013 ish can't usually catch streams but i made sure
to tune into this one thank you for putting so thank you for all thank you for so much for all
you do you make me laugh so hard i cry sometimes love you germ also can you do a barney life
impression who's barney oh oh bar okay yeah
right let me see if i get this right
andy take both of you to come out for some keys you got the keys there andy can i have an apple
oh sure help yourself you guys this is like old tv i mean i tried my best
this they didn't even know what how to make tv back with old tv like the andy griffith show like
exactly like they they didn't have like back i've never seen a single episode of andy griffith show
but people are like oh haha haha i bet you if i turned on jerry lewis right now
it would be like holy shit this guy sucks come on who who who who no who who who who the fuck
ah no no i'm old i'm getting old no i'm old no no it happened it happened i got old no no
no i'm getting jerry lewis is getting hood so that means that's you know that means i'm getting old
and it's okay that's okay thank you appreciate the 300 bits i tried my best throw away
nine eight five throw away nine eight five gave a hundred dollars ten thousand
bits a few minutes ago actually like 15 minutes ago and they say in a sea of streamers playing
the same old content it's a fresh breath of air to find a streamer so consistently wholesome and
charismatic as you've been for countless hours you've helped people escape dark places made us
cry with laughter and shared pain both emotional and physical i love that i can donate in good
conscience knowing it'll go to something and someone worthwhile please don't forget how much
your community loves you even more than you may love it well thank you throw away nine eight five
i'm not sure who you know your true identity might be throw away nine eight five but i said
this a lot of times i'm not i'm not necessarily trying to be some bastion of content creation
you know that's not really my goal i just want to i just want to have fun i want to have fun
more than anything that's all that's my life how can i make this fun okay i how can i like make
like this more interesting for me that's it there's really no other ulterior motive besides
i just want to fucking laugh and have a good time there's nothing else here that i care about
in a streaming sense right now cry cry influencer i'm talking about no what about kim i'm talking
about like in a streaming when i turn on my broadcast and what my goals are you know what
my goals are but i like i live for those moments where something can happen on these streams and
collectively we all just laugh our fucking asses off i strive for those moments that's i care more
about that than anything and whether that we think it's funny or if not then that's cool whatever
but i i do this is circle jerky well that's i'm not trying i'm not trying to make it like a
i'm such grave circle jerky if you think that then maybe so but you gotta remember
there's a lot of people that that say stuff like this about this community and i i dress it you
know people say this kind of stuff all the time plus two to that guy let me tell you more about
me and how fun i and this community we're so much more fun and so much better than all the other
streamers out there that's what we do yeah but that i do you remember that time when we laughed
at the guy peeing in the sims true but that's another part of this equation right like i don't
want i don't want people to feel like that either right like oh dude this is kind of getting a little
fucking like circley like everyone's talking all this positive shit to each other like you're
getting a little circle jerky it's like i don't want you to i don't want that to be a thing you
think of either right i don't want that to be like the thing you take from the stream is like oh i
just chill i just jumped in and like well everyone's i tell you everyone's just pat
each other on the back this is kind of boring you know i'm saying joel is malding because of you
well he can he can shut his is he watching right now he's streaming now oh burning bridges that's
what we do here now long story short this is how i'm gonna end this is i'm just gonna do me if you
like it i'm glad if you don't then i'm sorry to hear that maybe maybe you'll find somebody you do
like that's pretty much it done all right we can speak it no more no more going around the circle
about it i'm sorry if it comes off that way i really don't mean it to thank you though grandpa
piss thanks for the 250 grandpa piss as it's my last year as a teenager i realized that i've been
a fan for all my teen years thanks for always saying staying so genuine it really does show
that you care we love you thank you grandpa piss appreciate that joe wait joe said not to watch
joe joe he should read it wait you can read joe joe's bizarre adventure is it a book
he just said he wished he could unwatch it so why the fuck is that any confidence for me to watch a
show jerma watch joe joe oh a person that you know said they wish they could fucking unwatch it
oh but go but go watch every 500 episodes whatever read it thank you for let me for
the 1500 bits jerma you in this community some of the best and most compassionate and uplifting
people around if it's not too much to ask one of my best friends marley is going through a really
rough time in their life right now i think it might help if they could hear some words of
encouragement from their favorite streamer tonight keep going keep going in a good direction
and make sure you get the necessary help you need i wish you the best life can get down you have to
keep trying though and this goes for all of you you know if anyone's going through something
horrible hanging in their life also try to take steps to correct it they try to take the necessary
steps seek it out seriously thank you marley i hope it gets better i really do i was watching
joe do a first episode and fell asleep and opened ping pong instead pretty good joke
catch a cat catch cats the one that made the fireman cartoon fireman cartoons plural thanks
for showing my fireman cartoons happy you guys enjoyed them means the world to me yeah hell
yeah they were awesome it's obvious that a lot of work went into it so for sure al store h2o
thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents this is the fourth time you've screened my baseball
highlights video on stream thank you for all the love that was the best video on youtube so
of course i'm gonna fucking watch it behemoth thanks for 250 mr germ the discord squad has made
a small project for you but doesn't properly fit the community content guidelines you think
you'll still see it absolutely uh somebody will send it to somebody who will send it to me
whether i see it in one of the channels or one of the mods sends it to me i will see it thank you
thank you eugene for the 300 bits i wanted to be a chad this year but i realize i don't have a chin
like you any tips uh no zero i don't have any tips how to grow a chin oh no no no this is i
don't have a chin like you i'm like wait what the fuck eat more bananas get adequate rest
no chin tips what did you buy your chin chew gum to develop the chad chin does that work
no wouldn't that just make your cheeks puffier no there's no way that worked silence surrounding
thanks for 250 you tap out at 30 hours that's like four germa streams yeah but imagine if each
stream was 20 minutes long fuck you actually got me there no you got me there are you got
me there real bad um i'm tapping out i'm tapping out i'm fucking out of here i'm tapping out
i'm tapping out man it's been too long i'm tapping out uh i i have nothing to say you just you just
absolutely fucking destroyed me on stream like you just humiliated me on my own stream so like
what am i going to say to that like fuck you like hey how dare you really though how fucking dare you
do that on my stream you're you're supposed to circle jerk me not damn no how dare you
don't call me out on my fucking bad bullshit we're supposed to do what
yeah whatever uh it's all right who cares who cares who cares who cares who cares i'm leaving
jeremy stay stay don't go i'll fix it i'll fit i'm gonna fix it i'll fix it i'll fix it i'll fix it
don't go don't leave i'm gonna fix it and like i'll i'll fix it in like a few streams i'll talk
about it some other time hey keith king crimson thanks for the 250 bits jojo is actually 150
episodes but who cares all right there you go don't leave i can fix this i love that but who cares
snoozing copter with three more bits to do actually let's get to the real ending screen
because it is the end you can't say jojo jojo is just like it just causes a cascade of stuff
it's snoozing copter thanks for the 250 stop listening to what anyone's telling you i have
the solution it's red line it's a fantastic anime and it's not a show it's one and a half
hour movie make this your anime of the year and you will be glad to have made the decision to
watch anime for one please watch this two minute trailer no no no no no no no more no more animated
video suggestions no more animes i'm gonna watch courage the cowardly dog for my anime this year
you know what i'm putting my foot down on this one no i'm gonna watch like seasons one through
four of spongebob done no no more no more anime suggestions put it in the recommended channel
the disco no don't do that because that's supposed to be for stream games courage sucks wow based
i'm sorry that's a word i learned a week ago and i've been using it in random places
anyways apollyon thank you for the 500 bits my boyfriend and i watch your stream often
it's basically where our humor comes from thanks for all the fun by the way if you want to
officiate our wedding by all means i can't officiate any wedding this most nervous thing ever
if you want me to officiate your wedding people said this if people have said that two or three
times i will sneeze in your face and ruin the wedding i'm not kidding this is not a joke
i will like i will grab the book the wrong way and cut my finger and bleed and shit and get like
blood all over you everyone's clothes at the dress and the fucking groom's outfit i'll ruin
everything don't want me at your wedding you don't want me officiating the wedding something bad will
happen to me and like i'll sneeze on you i don't know something bad will happen based wedding
that's not me saying that i just read that somebody just wrote that because it was just
so stupid all right i'm gonna i'm leaving i'm out of here you'll see me tuesday
uh just gave 500 bits you're gonna go to any future nfl games at the new raiders stadium
that's right because they're gonna be the las vegas raiders also since you're obviously the
scout i'm assuming you care about baseball what do you think about the astros cheating
they all cheat all of them are cheating i got some really bad sad news for everybody here
everybody in these sports is fucking cheating they're all doing something they're not supposed
to be doing and then eventually like three of them get caught every year it's like oh wow
cleveland was really doing all this really fucked up stuff last year oh the astros were cheating the
red sox had these apple watches and they were cheating the patriots spy on people remember
when the new york jets that everyone's fucking cheating they're all cheating guys you're talking
about a sport where people were on human growth enhancing drugs for five straight years like seven
thousand players do you don't think that they're just everyone's just cheating every day
everyone's just cheating i think you gotta we gotta look at like the fundamental reasons why
everyone's just cheating in all these sports to win hey who's winning we all are oh all right
yeah okay yeah sorry bye but yeah i don't ever the vegas raiders would be cool the golden knights
have done so many awesome things already they almost won the stanley cup the first year that
they were put into the nhl so yeah it's it's it's interesting i guess there's gonna be a more than
just football in that stadium so it'll be really really cool stuff i'm looking forward to it
so we had a raid we had a fucking raid definitely the best guy ever just gave a raid
welcome welcome all of you let's go let's go huge raid just comes in big fucking raid see you
tuesday goodbye news copter thanks for the 250 watch the trailer no no trailers 250 for mostly
lost well of course you think everyone's cheating you're a red sox fan and patriots fan yeah look
it up it's news and copter with another 250 watch the trailer i'm not gonna give you any money ever
again you're gonna make me end up under a bridge no no trailers no trailers i watched the first five
seconds no just me not you i i don't i don't want any influencer rector animatrix world record i
already don't want to watch it i didn't like animatrix that wasn't even the trailer is all
right i'll watch it i'll watch it off stream all right that's it i'll see you guys tuesday
thanks again for community content night as always i always have a blast on these streams
riot riot riot riot riot riot riot ray jol ray ray jol jol ray jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol
jol jol jol jol jol ray jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol jol just with our
adventure don't just with our adventure all right let's raid jol tell him i watched episode one and
i'm like pissed off that he gave me the recommendation because like make it make it seem like that he told
you guys to tell me to watch it but he definitely didn't and just make it you know just like just
you know fuck him up a little bit
good night guys i'll see you guys on tuesday have a good night