Hey guys, what's up? How are you? We're here, currently, live, technically live.
I cannot guarantee that we're gonna be live for very long. We've had cocks at the house for the
last like six straight days, and they may have figured out one of the issues. So,
it's just like the first Red Dead stream, that's right. We'll see how long we can go.
This is going to be one of those mystery boxes that you open. The stream might be two hours.
It might be 10 minutes. It might be six hours. I don't know. I can't, it's a mystery.
Just literally RNG the stream. I know it already already got already dead.
No, no, we're okay. Are we? No? Hey, I'm here. We just almost dropped though.
Hey, that's probably gonna happen like every 15 minutes. One minute. Oh, shit.
All right, when I press the button, it's probably, it's probably gonna do that.
So, let's ride it out here for as long as we can. I'll do my, do my best to.
Oh, this is getting ugly. Before he moves back. No, there's no going back.
Damn, it was just green for so long too. It was just so solid green and now it just doesn't
want to, just doesn't want to do it. Let's just, what's with the music?
You might be hearing the PS4 sound effects. Let's see. It's, it's there.
Moved on from Comcast and got worse internet. I have no idea. It's almost like a bad joke
at this point because this is a, this is a gigabit line. This is a, this is a thousand
megabits per second down. This is what we get for down. And they're, they just have some major,
major issues that are apparently, take a lot of work to solve. So, this is happening way
more frequently than it just was. Nice, already buffering, getting a buffering popup already.
Yeah, well, we'll let, let just, just hang out with me for a minute. We'll sit here for a moment
because we do get these spots of like a few hours where it's perfectly fine.
I'm getting back in a balloon. I'm going back to Boston. Let's see. What do I take
this screen off? What if I did this? Like you can see that, right? Because that's, that's
red dead right there. Come on, just like, just like feed me through the line that I need
to be on. So I cannot guarantee the authenticity of this current stream. And I'm, I'm so afraid to
press the story button. I'm going to press X and it's going to crash the fucking node.
What a social club. I think it's the rock star thing when you get online, right? Press X.
Should I? I'm so scared. I'm so scared that it's not going to work.
I should, here goes the node. I'm doing it. I care. I will fight through the frame drops here
because you guys wouldn't even believe this is nothing. We would lose internet for
12 straight hours. It would just be zero. All right. I'm going. I'm here. We go.
Wish me luck. Ready? One, two. I did it. Okay. Okay. I'll turn it up a little bit.
So this is, so this is red dead redemption two, by the way, if you weren't aware,
it's a new Western game that came out. I mean, is this supposed to be somebody talking here?
Spoilers. Well, what are you doing at a red dead two stream? If you're scared about spoilers.
I lived in Vinnie's dryer for a week. Well, that's not out of the ordinary though.
I pay rent and the age of outlaws and gunslingers was at an end. I have to turn this
up. There's like a volume control on this dumb thing. There we go. Turn it up. It's
got to do a cowboy accent. I've even the wish had mostly been tamed. That was until they showed
up. Bill, Bob, Barry, Borg. A few gangs still remain, but they were being hunted down and
destroyed. I can't read cursive. I got taught cursive. I don't know how to fucking read it.
There we go. That was a cursive. I would have been upset about that.
Rockstar games presents red dead two. Why does it look like horror movie text? Here we go.
I'm so excited for this. Give me my internet. I deserve it. I deserve an internet.
That's a lot of bird shit. All right, stop. I want to make a joke about a million birds
shitting all over them, but I can't stop it. Don't stop soon. We'll all be dying.
Whether it's May, I'm just hoping the law got as lost as we did.
There, Arthur. Any luck? That's me, right? I found a place where we can get some shelter.
Let Davey rest while he, you know, an old man in town.
Come on. Come on. Old man in town. 10 FPS with gameplay. You might be referring to
my internet. Chapter one. Byron. I don't know what that says. I'm not going to read the
subtitles at the bottom. I'm going to try to read it. Flash Schlistro. This game is like
an hour long tutorial. Hey, just long enough to us to make sure the internet will stay on.
Hey, welcome to the stream. Oh my God. Ms. Gaskell, get that fire link.
Javadab just gave 250 dollars. Mr. Pearson, see what we've got in terms of food.
Davey's dead. Thank you, Javadab. Nothing more you could have done. What are we going to do?
We need supplies. Well, first of all, you're going to stay here and you were going to get
yourself worn. And I sent John and Mike scouting out ahead. That's welcome. Thank you, man.
Thank you so much. See if we can find one. We can wait for some time to deliver these bits
to you. It's great to see you back in action, especially after you had to once again deal
with some internet issues. Still are. Listen. Still are at the moment. Listen to me,
all for a moment. Now we've had John a bad couple of days. I loved Davey, Jenny,
Sean, Mac, John, barf bag. We don't know. Something like that. But we lost some folks.
Now, if I could throw myself in the ground in their stead, I'd do it. Gladly. Quit
Comcast. I don't have Comcast. I have a different ISP across the country and it still follows me.
Everybody. We're safe now. There ain't nobody following us through a storm like this one.
By the time they get here. Well, we're going to be, we're going to be long gone.
We've been through worse than this. John McFar's stun. That was the guy.
Mr. Pierce, Ms. Grimshaw. I need you to turn this place into a camp.
We may be here for a few days. Now, all of you, all of you get yourselves warm.
Stay strong. It might be the modem router. Oh, no, no, no. Single option is being.
So they both must have headed down the hill.
Sure. Hey. Oh, are we like dead dead now? I had time to ask. Oh, boy.
What really went down back there on that boat? We missed you. That's what happened. Come on.
Hey, you need horses. Oh, yeah. Hey, Mr. Smith, get yourself indoors.
I know. I can see it over here. Get indoors, son.
All right. I get to play the game though. Need you strong.
Okay. It's deep snow. I ain't sure what we're going to find out here, Dutz.
We have to try. Is this game not on PC at all? Is it on PC now?
We'll do our best to stick to the trail. This goddamn weather.
It's been two days or more like this now. Yeah, I didn't think it was.
There's Jabba Dab's two hundred and fifty dollars coming in. Again, thank you so much, man.
I know I'm like trying to bounce and monitor my connection and play a game.
And thank you so fucking much, dude. It's a huge amount of money.
Big delayed money. Yeah, I don't know why that's happening.
I don't know what it is with Rockstar and not putting their flagship video games on PC.
The first Red Dead is not even on. Red Dead Redemption is not on
PC at all or some strange reason we need to get those people warm and fed.
At least we don't need to worry about Pinkerton's tailing us in this
a couple more days. You need to help me pick the others back up.
Okay. You're the only one I can rely on to stay.
I'm sorry. All I heard was crouch in the corner and throw rocks at people.
Is that what you wanted me to do with my Dalmatian horse?
Oh, that's snow, right? I thought it was like a giant Dalmatian.
Is that someone coming towards us? Someone coming towards us. Are they friendly?
Oh, cutscene. Bring it on.
Who's there? Guy on the left is going to be picked off with an arrow.
Micah. Gentlemen.
The audio is delayed. I think so. Found a little homestead down that way.
Okay. Anyone home? Sure.
Place is blazing with light and noise. Sounded like a party.
Let's go see. Follow me.
How's Davey doing? I didn't make it, nor did little Jenny.
Six B's. Bob, Barry. Davey was a real fighter.
Both of them calendar boys is.
Bugle. Was. Yeah.
And Mac, Sean. We don't know.
A business.
All right, Micah. Ask him if he's seen John.
Have you seen John? John.
He's talking about our John. My John. First game, John.
Let me take the rear.
Double tap and hold while pushing.
How is it to hold? It just disappeared.
Talk to Mike. Are you sure about this?
Let's do that.
Mr. Morgan. I never thought I would be so pleased to see your face.
Things always turn out fine. Except for in Red Dead Redemption.
Where's everyone else? Old mining camp back up the hill.
Hung for daddy to put food on the table.
Gotta love these graphics, though.
You said it before. We got too many mouths to feed.
Snow actually permeates.
So you should be happy.
That ain't fair, Arthur. I earn my share.
I keep saying people tell me to keep looking at the balls.
Think it's unreasonable to expect others to do the same.
I wouldn't do that in real life. Why would I do that in a video game?
If I was in this time period, I wouldn't go underneath the carriage like it was an oil change.
And lift up the tail and look at the ball sack.
What are you talking about?
You know me. I'm a good boy.
You look under your car and look for your car's balls?
What would be the car balls? I'm trying to think what it would be.
The car balls would be like the muffler, right?
Okay. Let's keep it down now, gentlemen. It's just up ahead.
I'm getting exhausted.
Turn it down.
Let's head down there.
I can't fall off this, can I?
Health is displayed in the lower left corner.
That tiny little thing is health?
That's so small. How am I supposed to see that?
Wait, is this like Super Mario?
Where there's like three quadrants?
Let's hitch up here.
The outer bar shows it.
All right. But that was like about an outer bar and an inner bar.
Approach the hitching post.
Let's get it on here.
Triangle hitches the horse.
Now we got our first set of action here, I think.
You don't want to scare these folks.
Follow Dutch.
I remember Dutch.
Sounds like quite the party.
This is a lot of snow.
You too. Get yourself out of sight.
One of them is a lot less intimidating than three nasty-looking degenerates.
My father?
In that cattle shed on the left.
Micah, get down behind that wagon.
Why does this have to follow me everywhere I go?
I don't understand.
I said get out of sight.
Go to the shed and press R1.
Take cover.
There's this shed over here.
Arthur, take cover in that shed over there.
Glad it took three weeks.
Blame Cox Communications.
Because these motherfuckers can't figure it out either.
And it's their service.
This is the shed, right?
There.
It's not.
We're in the cattle shed.
Oh, the cattle shed.
Like in this thing.
This is not the cattle shed.
Get up there.
Did I just take my glasses off?
How do I get out of here?
I'm sorry.
I haven't been paying attention.
Get in position.
What cattle shed is he's referring to?
In here?
This is not the shed?
Stuck because no blip.
No, stuck because I have to look over here and watch 5% of every frame drop.
Because it's taken this company three weeks to try to fix a problem.
Oh my fucking god.
It's infuriating.
Go back.
Go to the shed.
Is it the shed that's like straight in front of me here?
That looked like a cattle shed to me.
The huge yellow thing.
That's, isn't that where it just was?
Like isn't this, this is where I was.
Isn't this where I was?
Highlighted in yellow.
This thing here, isn't this where it just was?
I just did this.
Didn't I just do this?
I didn't hide.
A gentleman.
There goes Michael.
We can't help you, mister.
What's he going to do?
I got, folks.
Arthur, we got a problem.
Just me, so do you.
Protect Dutch.
Okay.
Is this guy going to fire at him?
I think you should go now.
Crap.
Bunch.
I just like, holy shit, this is aiming is a little weird.
What's with the aiming?
It's like, why is it pulling me?
I got to change the sensitivity here.
Great soundtrack, yeah?
All right.
Where is it?
This way?
He's not going to last by himself out there.
Now he won't last at all.
You didn't handle it.
I had to do something about it.
I'm not going to follow him.
Fucking internet companies, man.
Hold square near items to pick them up by searching the house.
Okay.
Medicine.
Whiskey.
They're going to open pots and shit?
It's just cabinets.
Hold near items to pick them up while searching.
A can of sweet corn.
Maybe they're hiding up here, too.
There's a big price on Cuomo Drisco's head.
Assorted biscuits.
Here's as big as a one on you.
Fruits.
You're probably the only thing me is.
Whiskey is not essential?
Wait, are you serious?
Your health core drains over time and is now empty.
Well, empty you will experience negative effects.
Do you need something now?
Get your strength up for the ride back.
Do you have to eat in this game?
Okay.
Slightly restores health core and moderately restores stamina core.
Interesting.
And then we have to go bake beans so that back in the middle is your core.
Slightly restores health core.
All right.
Let's just do this in the middle one first.
Let's just try it out.
Survival mode?
It seems like it.
Delicious, dry, warm, and inject down here.
Maybe we'll see how they are when we head back.
Better quality food will refill more core.
I don't really want us to split up.
Okay.
I got to refill my four cores.
Let's look around for some more stuff.
Just controls how fast you refill your health and stamina.
Better than nothing.
There's a lot of random shit on the mantle.
Examine the photograph.
Sure.
Let's get some lore.
Poor bastard was married to.
Okay.
Flip it around.
Secret code in the back.
Quake and Idy wedding.
Jett's tonbri.
I can't read it.
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
I'm just kidding.
Oh, look.
It's from the first game.
That's the cottage from the first game.
All right.
What's we got?
Two dollars and 43 cents.
Have we dropped a frame in the last, like, 15 minutes?
Can anybody tell?
Or do I have to, like,
or do I have to, like, scream as loud as I can?
I have?
God damn it.
Well, I say it now and now I just did right here.
I think that's all I can get.
Arthur, keep looking for stuff.
Arthur, go see if there's anything in that barn.
Okay.
Micah, you search the cabin.
See what we missed.
Sure.
All right, let's go.
Investigate the barn.
I'm going to go take a look and I'm going to go examine it.
No drop frames since the fight.
Now you can look at the current objective.
What's that?
Is that a bad guy, good guy thing there?
The atmosphere is great.
Yeah.
So far it looks awesome.
That guy just top roped you.
Ha, ha, ha.
Hey, what's happening in here?
That guy didn't get one hit in.
Should you kill him?
Interrogate.
All right, beat him.
This is just like the Punisher game.
Where is he?
Okay.
Anything else?
Thanks for the info, buddy.
What was the last time you shit your pants?
Joe!
When did it happen?
When?
When was the last time you shit your pants?
Let's try to grab him again.
He's like, come here, I'm not done with you.
Oh, there are animals over here?
What the fuck?
What's happening?
I have to restart the whole thing?
Oh, shit.
Wasted.
By walking out of the frame.
Oh, god damn it.
Well, all right.
Tell us, tell us again.
First passing hug.
I can't keep up.
His clothes changed?
Fiction to rob some train.
Gonna blow the tracks.
I don't know the net, I swear.
There were, that's his worst mission boundaries than in GTA V.
Well, I would say it looks like you have this, Arthur.
Do what you want with him.
All right, so now we get a second chance.
Should I spare him?
This guy, remember saving Private Ryan.
This motherfucker's gonna come back.
I don't want to do that.
But what if he comes back?
Where's my gun?
Focus on the horse.
Where are you?
In the barn?
How'd you get in here?
How did you get in here?
Well, I can, oh, I can calm the horse.
This is not my horse.
What, is this gonna freak out and start hitting me?
This looks animatronic.
I don't know if I trust it.
It's animatronic.
Don't ever stand behind a horse.
That's what I was told.
Check his balls, no.
All right, let's lead the horse.
Continuing to bond with your horse
increases its trust in you and improves its attributes.
The horse has now become your horse
as indicated by a blip on the radar.
Okay.
We still fucking drop, yeah.
God damn it.
This is like, I'm like really containing myself right now.
I'm like, I have like a, I'm holding back.
But this has been like an infuriating process.
Literally moved across the country
to a different fucking state.
Got a faster line and it's worse than it was before.
That's unbelievable.
With a different company.
A gigabit connection.
Thousand fucking megabits a second.
Eventually it's gonna get fixed,
but who fucking knows when.
Maybe you're the problem.
I don't think so.
I haven't had enough time to be the problem.
Turned on the modem, got an IP.
That's it.
Oh, what the fuck?
Get off me.
Okay.
Hold on.
Come in here, boy.
Let's go.
Just keep going west until you get there.
It is going to be okay.
We mean you no harm.
Miss, come on.
It'll be okay.
We need to get out of here and quick.
Come on.
Fire.
You okay, miss?
Three days ago.
My internet's acting up because I clicked on your screen.
Miss, you are safe now.
And you can't stay here.
I mean that fire wasn't bad.
You could just jump on that thing and roll around
and it would have gone off.
You come with us.
Of course.
Miss, it's okay.
We're bad men.
We ain't them.
It's okay.
Get on.
We'll keep you safe until you figure out what you want to do.
What's your name, miss?
Miss.
Adler.
What is it that Dory's been burning easy during a blizzard?
Mrs.
I...
He...
He was my husband.
Hey, somebody's coming.
Looks like it's Dutch.
Hey, everybody, Dutch is back.
We good.
How'd you get on?
Micah found a homestead, but he weren't the first.
Colm or Driscoll and his scum, they beat us to it.
We found some of them there,
but there is more about, apparently, scouting the train.
Thank you.
And that's the last thing we need right now, Dutch.
Well, it is what it is.
But we found some supplies, some blankets, a little bit of food.
And this poor soul, Mrs. Adler,
Miss Tilly, Miss Karen, would you warm her up?
Give her a drink or something.
And Mrs. Adler, it's gonna be okay.
You're safe now.
They turned her into a widow.
He might never be on PC, but the last one wasn't either.
That's like the unfortunate thing.
I need some rest. I haven't slept in three days.
You're over here.
Miss O'Shea will show you the way.
Mr. Morgan, we put you in a room over here.
Thank you, Miss Grimshaw.
Mr. Bell, you're with the fellas over there.
Well, how come Arthur gets a room
and I get a bunk bed next to Bill Williamson
and a bunch of darkies?
Get yourself to bed.
The rocks are a bunch of idiots for not putting it on PC.
Yeah, I don't know.
There's gotta be some reason why.
I think there's not, but I really wonder.
He ain't been seen in days where there ain't let up.
He's strong and he's smart.
Strong, at least.
Hello, Arthur.
Abigail.
Arthur, how you doing?
Just fine, Abigail.
And you?
I need you to...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry to ask, but...
It's little John.
He's got himself caught into a scrape again.
He ain't been seen in two...
Hours.
Two days.
Your John will be fine.
I mean, he may be as dumb as rocks
and as dull as rusted iron,
but that ain't changing because
he got caught in some snowstorm.
Please go take a look.
Javier?
Yes.
Javier, will you ride out with Arthur
to take a look for John?
You're the two best fit men we've got.
Now?
She's...
We're all...
Yeah, we're pretty worried about him.
I know the situation were reversed
and he looked for me.
Thank you.
Is he in a British accent?
This way.
Last I know, John was headed up the river.
We know he kept riding north.
Not like that.
That emote is making my chat scroll horizontally.
Wait, what?
Wait, hold on.
What are you talking about?
It's time to find John Mar...
All right, I need to like get happy.
I'm like sad right now
because of this internet bullshit.
I gotta get like excited.
This is Red Dead Redemption 2.
This is not like...
This is not an iPad game.
Hey, I see some smoke.
Come on, let's take a look.
Let's hope it ain't more of O'Driscoll's boys.
Seems somebody left.
All right, let's do some investigating.
Reporting here.
Did he do it?
Are we not going to like it anyways?
What?
I loved the first one.
The first one was great.
Let's inspect the camp.
There could be dust.
There could be fingerprints.
There's finger dust on here.
That's fine.
All right, fine, fine, fine.
I wanted to fucking dust for fingerprints
and you didn't want to do shit.
Watch out.
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Burning, burning, burn.
Burn my horse's legs.
Stamina drains when your horse gallops or jumps.
I can't see anything.
We had the money.
It seemed fine.
Somebody turn the antennas around.
Bounty hunters?
No, Pinkerton's.
It was crazy.
Raining bullets.
That lake was steaming.
Well, this is a beautiful mountain though.
Watch out for this crevice.
To change camera distance and perspective, press.
It wouldn't even let me do the YouTuber joke.
Come on.
Why?
Oh, sorry.
I got off track.
Let me just look.
Whoa.
Oh, you can't.
Hold on.
Wait, you can't.
Oh.
The horse wouldn't do it.
But you get off and you can do it.
Horse is smarter.
See, they continue up that way.
That fall was so stupid, too.
It was like he lost control of all of his body and function.
You tell me.
And that like, ah!
It was like Emperor Palpatine.
Let's just see where they lead.
Thrown into the thing in the end of the fourth movie.
He just did the Emperor Palpatine scream.
What really happened?
We had the money.
It seemed fine.
Then suddenly they were everywhere.
Hunters?
No, Pinkerton.
It was crazy.
All right, so I got the stamina bar.
The horse bar has the horseshoe.
Okay, so that's distance.
That's what I want.
Killed a girl in a boat.
FPS boat.
Bad way.
But it was a bad situation.
That ain't like him, though.
Okay, not gonna do it.
There's some tracks leading to the river.
It's not funny.
I'm sorry.
Wait, that was a bear?
What are you talking about?
A bear?
That was, I was trying to turn around
because I was making the fake.
It's not funny.
It is funny.
Whatever.
You were there, Javi.
It was a bear?
I don't think it was a bear.
We had the money.
It seemed fine.
Was it a bear?
Then suddenly they were everywhere.
Turning hunters?
No, Pinkerton.
It was crazy.
Oh, it's not funny.
Please stop.
I'm sorry.
Take it slow.
Big ravine here.
Get me, I'm not going over there.
Dutch killed a girl.
My side.
Bad way.
But it was a bad situation.
That ain't like him, though.
Tracks go left, down here.
Javi got shot.
I'm not doing it one more time.
Both shot too.
Sean, we don't even know.
I'm surprised we escaped at all.
By the time you boys showed up from the other side of town,
I'm only just holding my business all right.
Activate cinematic camera.
Hold this button down.
Damn, snow's coming in hard again.
That's cool.
We'll lose these tracks if we don't move fast.
Automatically follow roads.
Oh, let's see.
It's like watching an actual movie.
Nice.
Change cinematic camera, press R3.
All right, there's a lot of use cases for this, I think.
But am I still controlling the character?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I am.
That's hard to do.
All right, I'm going to play the whole game like this.
I'm going to be the first streamer on Twitch.
The first guy on Twitch to do it only in cinematic mode.
Looks like you know when you were 14 and you made that machinima.
That's what I'm doing right now.
I'm not going to turn it off.
Why would I turn this off?
Oh, wow.
Let's investigate.
Let's see if he can hear us.
He was riding this horse.
Help.
Where?
Up here.
I heard it from this way.
Is this the right way?
Am I going the fuck?
I gotta get it out of my system now.
Oh, shit.
Okay, don't.
Okay, no, no, no, no.
Just relax.
I'm not going to fucking do it again.
I'm sorry.
Do you think it's John?
You tell me tracks for sure.
But it could be anyone.
I have like the cinematic mode.
I'm trying.
I can't do it yet.
That's give me the money.
It seemed fine.
And suddenly there were everywhere.
It's five minutes to get fun though.
It was crazy.
I'm actually going to try to play the whole game in cinematic mode.
That'll be my schnick, right?
Like what the fuck?
Live stream replace entire Red Dead 2 in cinematic camera.
Okay, here we go.
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to jump.
I'm not falling off another edge.
That is a 100% guarantee.
Like I can 100% guarantee.
If I fall off the edge in the next like minute or two
in this like little tutorial,
I will do 100 pushups in a row.
On camera.
Take the germ attacks 30%.
It adds the bars to that support.
I'm not going to fall.
I'm doing the thing that's impossible.
You cannot fall like this.
It's not possible.
I'm holding X.
I'm tensed up right now.
Like you wouldn't believe.
I like this one.
How am I going to aim and shoot at people with cinematic camera?
Is that possible?
So close to the edge, yeah.
She has to guess.
I can't just guess.
This is beautiful though.
Let's get a different angle here.
Let's see if he can hear us.
So John is here somewhere.
All right, I'm going to follow him.
Up there.
Don't say up there.
Like I'm going to follow you.
Don't push me off.
All right.
Here we go.
Is it do I go over this?
All right, we're good.
We have to walk from here.
Oh no.
Grab shotgun.
Force weapons.
Okay, so our R1.
Okay, we can only have one sidearm.
So I'm going to get the shotgun.
So did I lose cinematic?
There we go.
It's back.
Wait, hold on.
Okay.
Oh, it turns off right when you hold the button down.
You can't do it.
But wait, is this an edge?
Okay, we're good.
It's on.
I'm not cheating.
I want to see from another angle.
I don't want to see.
Holy fuck.
I just that doesn't count.
I fell off a ledge onto another ledge.
I didn't die.
Stamina displayed in the lower left corner.
I don't have a cinematic.
Okay.
This doesn't count either because this is...
Oh god damn it.
Yeah, I'm all right.
This is the most stressful thing I've done in a long time.
Am I running the lip?
My stamina core is empty.
Square in this climb.
Get access to the shaft.
I need to eat something, man.
So I need some stamina here.
Classic oat cakes.
Is there just a stamina one?
Just canned peaches is fine.
I thought I just fucked it up.
That looks odd from cinematic view.
All right, we're doing fine.
Just eating peaches.
Canned peaches are where it's at, man.
That's good shit.
John?
John, we'll be looking for you.
John, the streetlights are on.
You're in deep shit when you get home.
Where is he?
He's in the game.
So he is in the game.
Wow.
I could probably do that if I tried hard enough.
All right, now we've got to cinematically walk him back to his car.
Oh, we actually do.
I think this is just supposed to happen, right?
If we go on the right, is this supposed to be okay?
Uh-oh.
Wildlife.
We're being hunted by wolves.
Who's going to distract them?
All right, we got to get to the horses.
Keep the wolves away from both of them.
That's just not going to work.
No, it takes it off cinematic mode.
Oh, well, we tried.
Get him on the horse.
You can see he's going to drive him.
Do first person mode.
That's actually a good idea, too.
Okay.
Where is he?
Oh, shit.
All right, yee-haw.
We're kind of going to yee-haw.
Please don't commit to this.
I'm not committing to it.
Now or later.
Are you going to die?
This is not very cinematic.
Up there?
More of them!
Get out of here!
Shit, there's more on the right!
That ragged off.
Do you see any more, Arthur?
I don't think so.
Jesus.
He just buried his face in the ground.
Just slid.
Just about.
You're going to be okay.
We have some shelter now.
All right, we're good.
Thanks for coming for me.
Of course.
Is this the portal soundtrack?
That bullet in Blackwater.
Now this.
I don't think so.
You had a hell of a time.
And Arthur always says,
I'm lucky.
None of us are lucky right now.
It's really crazy that John Marsden's in this game
and he just becomes Darth Vader in the next one.
You get to see his origin story here.
That's really cool.
Ride in the water for a bit.
Try to lose a cent.
Don't want to leave a trail right back to camp.
You know, we're going to need to come up with
a better story for that scar.
So, freezing, bleeding, starving.
Damn, they're getting even to death.
They're good enough for you.
Dude, oops.
We're good.
I did it.
I made it.
Super horse.
Can I scream too?
Does it help?
Help.
One, two, three.
Even by your standards.
Thank you, Arthur.
Thank you.
Any other lost maidens need saving?
Not today.
Have you and Dutch talked about how we're gonna get out of this?
I was just discussing with Herr Strauss
when the weather breaks.
I suppose we'll have to keep heading east.
East?
Into all that?
That civilization.
I know.
The west is where our problems are worse.
The west.
Come on, Herr Strauss.
Let's get warm.
Thank you, Mr. Morgan.
You've never seen this game before?
Is it on the Sega Genesis?
I was just gonna scream, yes.
But I'm not a screamer.
Events and interesting locations are noted in your journal as you explore.
Hold W to view.
Hold X for details.
Log.
Enter.
Pursue by memory.
John hasn't returned from an earlier scouting trip.
Arthur and Javier ride out into the snow to look for him.
Okay.
Checklist.
Kill all the wolves without taking any damage.
Complete what Elise 80 didn't do either of those.
That's all right.
Let's take a look at this.
Here's the journal.
That's very bad drawing.
You know when somebody asks you for directions
and you draw them a terrible map of intersections?
What's it just looks like?
Uh, okay.
I just draw in here, too?
What is this book?
Why would I not use this piece of paper on the left?
It's a waste of trees.
Is this the White House?
Oh, okay.
Blacksmithing.
I can't read this.
Oh, thank God it can be translated.
That's kind of cool.
Continue playing to unlock your bonus content.
Oh, I'm one of the suckers that spent $80
to get like the one mission that nobody else gets.
I feel real great about that part, just by the way.
All right.
Let's just go.
Let's just do some shit.
We got our mini-map here.
Got a horse, yeah.
Hold L2 to talk.
33-year-old substitute teacher can't read cursive.
Let's go.
I haven't been a substitute teacher in a long time.
All right.
All right, let's talk.
L2, greet.
Another cold morning.
What?
What is it doing?
Wait, why did it make me get off
for it to go to the bathroom?
Get over here.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Come here.
Come back here.
What are you going?
All right.
Relax.
Shit and run.
I guess we need to B or P.
Let's just do wits right here.
Let's just do P.
Couple of days on the lamb.
You lot have all turned yellow.
B or P?
Apart from you, of course.
Shut up, Micah.
I ain't never seen so many long faces.
I guess, I guess folks miss them.
I fell.
But when I fall, I don't want no fuss.
When you fall, there'll be a party.
A party?
Probably.
Funny, huh?
Sure.
I don't feel like being laughed at by the likes of you two.
Stop it.
Now.
You fools punching each other
when Como Driscoll's needing punching.
Hard.
You want to sit around waiting for him to come find us?
All of you.
We got work to do.
All right, I have the team mission.
You sure about this, Dutch?
Yes.
Folks been through a lot recently.
We hardly back on our feet yet.
The last thing we need is to get bushwhacked by Como Driscoll.
I know you hate him, Dutch.
He's here for us.
I doubt that.
No, you're just doubting me.
I would never doubt you, Dutch.
You always said revenge is a luxury we can't afford.
This is a right call, Arthur.
Take this.
Why does he just sound like a pitch-shifted version of him?
They were talking about trains, detonators.
Here.
Como always had good information.
Come on.
And you think now is the right time to hit a train.
Now you, my fancy living on deer piss and rabbit shit.
I'm getting too old for that life.
Mr. Matthews, Mr. Smith, Mr. Pearson.
Would you please look after the place there are Driscolls about?
Voice crack, voice crack.
How everyone laugh at him, right?
That's what you laugh at me.
That guy's way stronger than all of you.
Everybody pointed out in the chat, right?
We're going to go.
This is a robbery.
Automatic cinematic.
I didn't even do it.
Somebody turn on the AC.
It's getting hot in here.
Automatic cinematic.
I'll scold myself for that one later in the shower.
I promise.
I'm sorry.
I've been away for like three weeks.
I'm going to be in the shower being like with my hand up,
wicked hot water just going like,
fucking stupid.
Don't ever say something like that again.
It must be this way.
You good, Dutch?
Listen, I know you don't think much of my eyes recently,
but this is the right move.
Okay.
Debatable.
You know I'm going to be back.
Screaming in the shower.
You learned a long time ago that you hit Como Driscolls.
No drop frames, by the way.
I get to get out of meltdown modem into fun, fun mode.
This feud between you needs to be put to rest.
One way or things I can forgive, I can forget.
What he did to Hannibal, I can't deny it.
For me to pull off on another like audibly upset.
You know, like the difference when somebody's like,
oh, I'm pissed off.
What the heck, man?
Whoa, I can't believe I died there.
What's happening here?
Oh, damn it.
First, when you start talking like this,
like this fucking stupid fucking thing.
Like when you, that's how you know somebody's really angry.
They get like kind of internally,
they're so hot and they're nervous and shit.
Like they start fucking getting angry like that.
It's not like, what the fuck?
Whoa, I died in the game.
Oh, I'm so mad.
Whoa.
Are we birds?
All right, gentlemen.
This is it.
We goddamn ready.
Ready, Dutch.
Good.
That was very, very good.
That was like a classroom attendance.
Miss Morgan and I, we're going to head up here a little.
See if we can't get a sense of the layout of the camp.
Mr. Williamson, Mr. Bell.
You two take up a hidden position just outside the camp.
Mr. Summers, Mr. Escuela.
You two hold position here.
Let's go.
All right.
Throw haymaker.
I'm depleting.
This is absolutely beautiful.
You know, this is beautiful.
It's just beautiful out here.
That was at the same time.
Holy shit, this is what it looks like to look through his eyes.
I think so.
Got to go to a doctor, man.
Get into prescription.
You got astigmatism, bro.
All right.
Head shot from all the way back here.
What was wrong with that one?
All right.
So we're going to sneak up.
Metal Gear Solid 3, neck snap.
Two of them.
I was hoping I could see his big eyes.
Like Macaulay Culkin style.
Weapons not set on your load before dismounting will remain on your horse.
All right.
So we got new...
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Approach your horse to view store.
Hold L.
Do it.
Okay.
So where's the rifle?
Right here.
Long arm back carbine or carbine repeater.
Oh, that's just the slot it's in.
Okay.
I get it.
And I'll take the shotgun too.
Horse weapons.
We'll circle around the far side and go down that way.
Same as Micah.
Ten cents.
Yeah, that's...
I probably should.
I'll get it right eventually.
We can't afford.
Yeah.
Just wasn't sure you agreed with me.
Does it stay winter the whole game?
Arthur, have you completely lost faith in me?
Our needs right now are supplies, equipment, and a way out of here.
Everything else, including coal.
Okay.
There's enough of those bastards down there to deal with as it is.
All right.
So we're going to go carbine.
Not every area is snow.
Well, it's good at least that they put it in.
It's not just the desert and only the desert.
Take a shot every time somebody says okay.
All right.
No fucking around here.
No like look at how funny the streamer is jokes here.
You know what I'm saying?
And we already got that.
We got a cinematic mode.
Oh, LML.
And then, oh, I fell off three times.
And then, you know, I'm not doing that again.
Can they see us?
I should be crouched.
I can't do it here.
This is such a long walk down.
Wait till I get the game to open up for me before I do any dumb shit.
What a terrible stream.
Hey, what?
Why?
What happened?
I'm just playing Red Dead.
Just jump off.
No, one guy said that.
Yeah.
And he's the one guy now.
Why do I always read negative feedback?
Gosh, I need to make sure everyone's happy.
And if people are not having fun, then I want to make sure you're having fun.
I really can't fuck this up.
I got to be on point here.
No, like where's the shed?
Is that the shed?
Am I not dropping frames?
I don't know.
Is that a guy?
No, that's a good guy.
Take the lead.
He's giving me an opportunity.
Look at Dutch to give instructions.
Send in the gang.
I'll take the lead.
Wait, does the sniper elite thing?
Damn it.
Having R2 when not aiming.
Okay.
This is the last guy.
Up on top of the roof.
Don't fall.
Oops, sorry.
That guy was making a video.
I should have been quiet.
That guy was like recording.
He's definitely like laughing and like screaming right now.
Get over there.
Fucking sensitivity.
Lord.
I got somebody.
How?
I'm not sure.
Right through his hat.
One more guy.
Where is he?
Right here?
Oh, he just got me right in the mouth.
He shot me right in the face.
I'm glad you're getting shot right in the face like that.
They're really just walled.
Damn it.
I could just be dead.
What?
Why did I shoot twice?
Oh, that was the slow motion.
FP.
Oh, all right.
Is this 90 FOV though?
This just makes me want this to be on PC.
All right.
There's so many corpses though.
How am I going to get them all?
There is a slider in the menu.
Is there?
What?
A camera?
Or they aren't?
Okay.
Yeah.
It is there.
Get that fucking head bob off, please.
All right.
Cool.
Is it a fly immediately?
Actually, no FOV number.
It's just this one.
Bar.
Bar drag to the edge.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
More of them are coming in right now.
I didn't need a chance to loot.
First person.
Well, aiming sure is a thousand times better in first person.
I will definitely say that.
I'll say that.
Defend.
Is there?
Is there a dead eye in this game?
Damn.
Oh, there is dead eye.
I can even like see it.
Oh, shit.
Got that guy.
He's dead.
I don't have to worry about him causing any problems.
God.
I don't like that.
I didn't like that.
Holy shit.
Holy fuck.
That was insane.
All right.
New.
Oh, here we go.
Weapon wheel.
Dead eye tonics.
Fully restores dead eye.
Okay.
You release to use them.
Hides your identity while committing crimes.
Okay.
Let's bring it right back up.
All right.
Let's keep looking around.
I got this many bodies.
Do it with the shotgun.
Lord.
He didn't like it.
He loved it.
They're probably going to keep coming over here.
I guess I have to do it.
Is this like you can actually cut people's heads off in the game?
My lord.
Shoot the bodies with the shotgun.
Oh, man.
No way.
No fucking way.
There's like this.
That's that's insane.
That's it's just it's brutal.
Oh, man.
It's bruises brutal.
This game ain't coming out in Germany.
Like no way.
This game ain't going to release in Japan.
Is it all right?
Is it out in like Germany and Japan?
What do they do?
It is out.
Okay.
Blood confirmed it is out in Germany as is.
Well, hold on.
Yeah, I have to loot everybody.
You can't give me all these exes here.
Got somebody's belt buckle.
I will but just hold on.
There's a lot that could be money on everybody.
89 cents.
I'm just collecting bits right now.
What does this guy have?
What does this guy have on him?
Hey, thank you for the championship belt.
Big bits.
All right.
We'll look for like like come on.
What do you got?
No, that guy's not even that guy's not a sub.
Come on.
We don't even have like a sub.
What?
How many people here aren't even shocked?
All right.
I gotta cut that out.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right.
We got here.
He's onto it.
Because he's I'm just I'm not.
No, I don't I don't care if you aren't subscribed.
Don't worry.
Chewing tobacco.
Cool.
Pressuring fans.
No, you guys know that.
It's not I don't care.
Oh, there's an upper left.
Oh, there's a fortnight chest up here.
What's in here?
Epic.
Is it an epic?
Holy shit.
Somebody's hey, the great Lord Walden just gave out 20 tier one community subs.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, dude.
Okay, 20, 20 subs here from Walden.
Thanks, man.
Oh, my Lord.
No, no, that's not this is not what.
Thank you for the 10 subs after it.
Thank you.
Oh, here it comes.
I just can't keep my mouth shut.
But thank you guys.
Unnecessary.
But thank you.
All right.
I gotta search up here.
There's still things that I need to get.
Okay, that hurt.
What else is in here?
Sub.
Oh, there's a chest.
I told you there's a fortnight chest in here.
Take.
Is it a knife?
Two dollars and 12 cents.
And cigarettes.
Whoa.
What is it?
Is this dynamite?
What?
How would I even climb this?
This looks good.
What do you think, Bill?
Well, looks fine.
But thank you, though.
Those guys giving out those subs.
Really appreciate it.
Did we get everything?
Think so, boss.
Found this on one of them.
Thank you.
This is perfect.
Oh, yeah.
Interesting.
This is something about the train they was gonna rob.
Train mission.
I bought it.
It was 20 dollars.
Mr. Leviticus Cornwall.
Mount back up.
Let's keep moving.
What does dynamite smell like?
Alright, let's get out of here.
Proud of you, boys.
All of you.
Raisins.
No, that's tobacco.
Gunpowder smells like...
Not bad for some starving down in...
Uh.
They can pummel us.
Hard as they like.
It's hard to describe.
If you drop the frame, it's gonna happen.
I can't even get angry about it anymore.
You know, there's no sense crying over spilt milk.
Sorry, spilt.
It's just gonna happen.
Just, thankfully, it's not happening as frequently as it was at the beginning of the train.
You know, he'll come after us.
What do I think of the game so far?
Um.
Just like all the rest.
But we're gonna stay a step ahead of them.
Make sure we always know where they are.
It's very atmospheric.
Seems like it's gonna be really fun.
We allowed ourselves to get a step behind at Blackwater.
That won't happen again.
Even just that up there.
Looks great.
And we're just still in the tutorial, yeah.
There's way more going on.
Hang in, fellas.
Let's make some ground.
Cowboy Skyrim.
Yeah.
That's not a bad thing, though.
It really makes you feel like Spider-Man.
That's right.
Bring him back alive.
We got it.
Chase down and lasso old Driscoll.
So do I get the la-
Hold and get the weapon wheel.
This is gonna bring up is the lasso.
Okay.
Hold L2 to ready lasso and aim it at old Driscoll.
One of the most fun mechanics of the last game here it is.
Keep L2 held and dismount.
Press it.
Let's interrogate him in the water.
Let's drown this motherfucker.
He got out.
Where did he go?
Oh, he's uh, he actually is like getting drowned.
Give him a stone.
Yep, drop him on the back of the horse.
He might actually be able to drown.
Maybe.
Okay.
Yellow line in the radar is the shortest route.
In the yellow truck.
Press the thumb stick to pet the horse.
Yeah, I got him.
I pet him.
I gave him a little-
Hey, you're doing a great job.
Thank you.
Shut up.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Where is it?
Come on.
Trying to shoot the bird.
Can you throw dynamite at birds in this game?
Does it follow them like in the last one?
What bird?
The bird that was on the right.
Yes, that does-
That is still in the game.
You can try.
I mean, we'll eventually we'll try.
Seeing birds from other dimensions now.
204 bones to go.
Bring him to the fire and drop him in.
We're eating good tonight.
Hold near your horse to remove him.
I would.
No, I can't right now.
We can't do that.
I'm not doing that whole thing again.
I thought I was going to start cutting him.
Uncle.
Mr.
Williamson.
Tie this maggot up someplace safe.
We get him hungry first.
I got a saying, my friend.
We shoot fellas.
There's no need shooting.
Save fellas.
There's no need saving.
And feed them.
There's no need feeding.
We are going to find out what you need.
I can't believe it.
An O'Driscoll in my camp.
I ain't an O'Driscoll, mister.
I ain't-
Oh, whatever you say, son.
Well done, Arthur.
I'm just sorry we missed out on call.
Why am I still holding them?
Well, there's time enough for that.
Now, I gotta figure out if we can hit that train.
Okay.
That's a long saying.
Old friends complete.
Now we got P on the map.
Oh, excuse me.
I probably got an F.
Complete the mission without taking any health items.
One, two, three, four, five.
I got a 25% on the test.
Now, let's keep going through the tutorial.
No, I don't-
I don't even need to get on the horse.
He's literally right here.
Stu, I'll take you.
I'm gonna starve to death up here, Mr. Morgan.
We're okay.
We have a few cans of food and a rabbit.
For what?
Ten, twelve people?
That was in the Navy.
I do not wish to hear about what you got up to in the Navy, Mr. Pearson.
We were stranded at sea.
For 50 days.
And you unfortunately survived.
When we ran away from Blackwater, I wasn't able to get supplies in.
Idiot streamer.
Sometimes shopping trips need to be cut short.
We'll survive.
We always have.
If needs be, we can eat you.
You're the fattest.
I sent Lenny and Bill hunting and they found-
Ew, gross.
I mean, fucking disgusting.
Bill's a fool.
Unless those mountains are full of game they want to read,
ain't no wonder they found enough of this.
We'll go find something.
Come on, Arthur.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Here.
You're gonna need something to eat out there.
The sordid salted off.
Starving will be preferable.
Come on, let's go.
Is it weird that these gross shit items that are in these games,
the rotten can of beans and packed in spam that's four years expired,
I want to eat them.
If I could pull that out of history and eat it,
I would probably do it right now.
Nobody else does that?
I can't use it and you'll have to.
Bow and arrow.
Use a gun and we'll scare off every animal for miles around.
You're never too old to learn.
I imagine.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, man.
Let's head out.
Yeah.
Match the speed of your cockspill.
Stupid mistake.
It'll be fine in a day or two.
I just can't pull a bow right now.
Is that guy on YouTube that eats the old military rations?
Yeah, that channel's great.
I've put on that guy's channel and just fallen asleep to him eating old rations
and woken up at like 60 videos a player.
They'll be needing to feed.
I'm going to tap square when we're stationed from this move.
Oh, you can like hold it.
That's cool.
Is that just showing off?
I didn't wait.
I'm not saying what?
I didn't say that.
No.
I've done that to your videos.
Yeah.
Just happened.
Let's put this out on a tray.
Yeah, I know the line.
Come on.
You don't think I've ever seen it before?
Automatic cinematic.
Coffee instant cheetos.
Oh, God.
I wonder how big the actual map is when the game opens up.
It all is bad, but if it's too strong, they won't move.
Stay quiet.
Do a German impression?
Okay.
Stop here a second.
I see something.
I was about to just wildly make fun of myself.
Like just make fun of me.
No, I'm not doing that.
Why would I do?
No.
I've already done this before.
Recently.
How can you do?
I've already done it.
We'll track them on foot.
You're gonna need the book.
Don't leave it on your whole gun.
It'll scare everything around.
Approach your horse.
Don't use the gun.
So with Z, use L2R to select a stowed weapon.
Carbine.
Bow.
That's the one.
No point setting off without that bow.
You make less noise when you crouch.
And slowly.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna shoot him in the head.
You see the tracks?
I think so.
Maybe not.
I see them.
You can use eagle eye to highlight animal tracks.
Okay.
Focus on the track.
Enable eagle eye focus on the tracks to highlight them again.
Okay.
Yeah, I can.
I see it.
Your scent is also shown in eagle eye blowing in the direction of the wind.
Animals will flee if they smell your scent.
They'll remain downwind or far away when hunting.
So is this...
Is that my smell going this way?
Or are those those of his tracks, right?
He's gonna be up here.
It's top track.
I mean, I'm just gonna follow it.
22 miles per hour.
Top right.
Which way is it going though?
This way.
Unknown animal.
It's gonna be a deer.
22 miles per hour.
That would be very...
That'd be a lot.
I don't see anything.
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Am I close enough?
I'm gonna have to do like a...
Is it bullet drop?
Aim for the head.
A swing.
Do I not go get the meat?
Hunt another deer.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna...
I wanna get the meat here.
Select and call while aiming at it.
This will give you a chance of a clean kill
as they raise their head before fleeing.
So there's one over here.
All right.
Do I even need to lock that one?
I mean, we get the 21 stink meter up there.
Okay.
I haven't even played God of War,
the new one for PS4.
But I feel like this is the game...
Is that...
This happens in that game, right?
This is like the same game.
Something like that.
Yeah. Which way is it going?
I mean, is this...
Is it going that way?
Or to the left?
That I don't know.
The tracks.
I mean, those are tracks, right?
Or did I make those?
No, it's down here.
What's the button to call?
Fuck!
I don't even need to call them.
Why did I even call?
That was no reason for that.
I made these tracks.
Okay. There he is.
Got it.
Okay. We can stop this now.
Let's go!
Oh, it's actually...
Pick up the whole thing?
This is realism.
The compendium tracks what you have discovered in the world.
It can be accessed from the progress section of the pause menu.
We've found the realism.
And you can increase the distance that the horse will respond.
Come on!
There he is.
Shoot the deer in the head.
No!
I don't want to explode the deer's head.
All right. Let's go.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
I don't want to do it.
All right. Meet up with Charles.
All right, Charlie.
I'm coming.
I want to see its brains.
Jesus Christ!
So you drop off carcasses to Pearson
at the meat factory to contribute to gang supplies.
Okay.
Okay. You want to see the deer's balls?
Everyone's freaking out about it.
All right. Let's look at the deer's balls.
The deer doesn't have any balls.
Right.
Okay.
That's not how it works.
Seems to me.
You know, there are...
See? I told you they weren't going to be there.
I missed you guys.
I really did.
I unequivocally missed all of you.
We give the camp cook five minutes to grab the essentials and go.
And he doesn't even bring a crumb of food.
Good that we caught more than one.
We've only been up here a few days
and have already picked up two more mouths to feed.
One more.
I bet German doesn't even know me.
Boy!
What's your name?
Even me?
The one that makes fun of you?
Even you.
No, I'm not going to show the horse balls.
That's too easy.
I'm not going to shoot the horse's balls with an arrow like everybody wants me to do.
That's not going to happen.
No one said that?
Yes, they did.
Oh, shit.
Bears.
No, don't shoot him.
Am I losing...
What's wrong with my arms?
No, let it go.
Let go.
There you go.
You're going awfully fast.
Oh, the horse is...
The horse is spooked.
Okay.
I'm going to hold L3 to make the horse not...
Can he see us?
Fight bear.
Right in the fucking head.
All right, let's get out of here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right.
Cinematic mode.
He's screaming.
Where's my friend?
Come on.
Let's go.
Why is he standing there?
Is there a reason why he's just standing still up here?
The bear is gone.
Yeah, we're good.
I'm in combat.
No, I am not.
Let's go.
I have to fight the bear now.
Okay, I need to turn it off for a second.
Hold on.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Where's the bear?
I don't see a bear.
Give me the fucking carbine.
There's no bear.
He's not here.
Do you guys understand?
Do you see a bear?
I don't see a bear.
Wait, tracks.
Right there.
Where the fuck is he?
He's not here.
I see him.
No, you don't.
I mean, the red marker is over here.
Wouldn't he be over at the red marker?
I'm out of stamina.
I gotta eat.
Hold on.
Why did you guys make me do this?
I was so close to the end here.
Eat a can of beans.
Give me my horse.
You made you do this.
You did this.
There was never any bear?
Why do I hear it now?
Can we just leave?
We can leave.
Can't we?
He said, return to Charles.
He said, go.
Hurry up and return.
Where's my carcass?
Fucking carcass is on the ground over here.
That's what's happening.
I get it.
The horse is just as fucking stupid as I am.
All right.
This is why I couldn't move.
It has nothing to do with the bear.
See?
Everyone told me it's because I was in combat.
This isn't World of Warcraft.
We can just leave.
All right.
Let's go.
Fuck.
Who is this fucking bear?
I soft-locked the game?
No, I didn't.
Yeah.
We're fine.
Were you awake back there?
Yeah.
Just thinking.
We ain't ever talked that much, you mate.
Shoot bear with arrow.
And my toddler brain was like,
shoot bear with arrow.
OK.
I do think you say.
You think this?
What?
I'm a caveman.
Jerma, do that thing.
I do think.
Me shoot arrow to bow to bear head.
Me shoot bear.
Chat say good idea.
Me show balls.
Me laugh.
Me laugh at lowbrow joke.
Me stream on Twitch with bad internet.
Me try explain TCP IP to Bogo.
Bogo throw rock at head.
It's pretty nice and movie.
Well, it looks good.
But I'm streaming at 6,000 right now.
I mean, when it's good, it looks great.
Right?
When it's bad, yeah.
Who the hell is calling me right now?
But I cannot answer that.
So this upgrades.
Did they go a Fallout 4 route here?
Do I have to bring supplies and build stuff?
It's not forced?
That's good.
You earned it.
Have a drink.
It's urine.
Jesus, what is that?
Navy rum, sir.
It's the only thing.
The only thing.
Keeps you sane.
It does.
Seems to have done a treat on you.
You go rest that hand, Charles.
I'll be fine in a few days.
You mind helping me with the skinning, Mr. Morgan?
It's easier if we do it together.
I'll get to skin you.
You're always one with the jokes, aren't you?
Come on.
This really isn't a job for a man with a burnt hand.
I'll see you both later.
See, that guy has the quintessential haircut of end of the plate of spaghetti.
Oh, yes, yeah, yeah, you can take this.
I'm done.
Are you sure you're done with that?
Yep, yep.
Arthur, come on, get that knife.
Just get him.
Now shoot the deer.
No, I'm not going to fuck up the tutorial missions.
That was very quick.
That's what it looks like in there?
Not too bad, Mr. Morgan.
I thought it was wires and...
Yeah, we said you were a butcher.
Components and shit.
Looks like that in there.
I thought we just made animals.
They're like computers.
Well, if you catch anything else, sir, you bring it to me.
Sure.
Thank you, Mr. Morgan.
Heck, Arthur Morgan's first decent bit of hunting after all these years.
Yeah.
Well, we're on the run now.
Everyone's got to do their bit to survive.
You're not a Chuck E. Cheese.
The folk need it.
It's been a tough few days.
A few days later, you unlocked the Master Hunter Challenge.
All right, tutorial complete.
It's been a bad few weeks, but Dutch, being Dutch, he is busy making plans and
Dutch, being Dutch, those plans involve robbery and dreams.
Not yet, huh?
Who the hell is Epiticus?
I thought you was reading him his last rites.
Now I see you're introducing him to your other passion.
I'll mind you to show me some respect, Mr. Morgan.
Mind away, Reverend.
You're still here, then?
I owe you.
And you'll pay me.
For the moment, just rest.
Arthur, I think it's time for the train.
Want me to come?
Of course I do, but look out.
You stay.
That was always ugly, Dutch.
It's just a scratch.
Don't lie still, son.
What's that kid doing?
Get that kid out of here.
This is an M-rated game.
He's not allowed in here.
He's seen me now.
What's left of me?
What about you?
Guess I was hoping to see a corpse.
Bide your time.
You'll see plenty of them.
You're a rotten man, John Marston.
He is an idiot, Abigail.
We all know it.
Fix the D-sync.
Now, railway man.
Bill!
Tell me what happens here.
Ready?
At the water tower, just before the tunnel.
Ain't a problem.
Why are we doing this?
Weather's breaking.
We could leave.
I thought we was lying low.
What do you want from me, Jose?
I just don't want any more folks to die, Dutch.
We're living, Jose.
We're living.
Look at me.
Even you.
But we need money.
Everything we have is in Blackwater.
Of course.
You fancy heading back there?
No.
Listen, Dutch, I ain't trying to undermine you.
I just want to stick to the plan, which was to lie low, then head back out west.
Now, suddenly, we're about to rob a train.
Now it's too fast.
What choice have we got?
The Viticus Cornwalls.
No joke, Dutchie.
Who is the Viticus Cornwall?
That fix it?
He's a big railway magnet, sugar dealer, oil man.
Well, how good for him.
Sounds like he has more than enough to share.
Dutch.
Gentlemen, it is time to make something of ourselves.
Get your horses ready.
We have a train to rob.
Better?
Bad.
Everything's weird?
No, it's not.
We're riding with the gang.
All right.
Riding with the gang.
The street smells like pee now.
I'm gonna get hit by a train, I guarantee it.
Why is the audio playing backwards?
You know what?
Don't you be coming back here now.
I don't know why that just popped in my head.
That's when you go to jail in the Monopoly game for Super Nintendo.
I don't know.
That just popped in.
It just popped in saying hello.
I don't know why.
It just popped in.
You know, it just popped in.
Game or reference.
I wasn't paying attention.
God damn it.
All right.
Rob the train.
That's all I need to know.
So what's the story about?
Group of bandits.
Setting up camp.
Getting deer.
And fending off other bandits.
So far.
And John Marston.
Oh, he did?
He didn't die?
What happened?
That's a close one.
Well, this is pretty.
No, did we go to like zero?
What's that right over here?
This is what I call a crew.
Charles Smith.
Bartholomew Morgan.
Javier Escuela.
First man.
I was under the assumption that I was hopefully going to be live for at least a couple of hours.
Let's hope it's stable.
You sure you're ready for this, kid?
Of course I'm ready.
Just stay calm.
Keep your eyes sharp.
Holy shit.