Can you fucking guys see me? Am I live? Hello? What's happening?
Alright, that's really weird. Uh, my stream key. Something was fucking weird with my stream key.
When I was doing testing, remember earlier like an hour ago when I was doing like a test to make
sure we could stream at the same time? I got a stream key issue there. That was fucking weird.
But anyways, uh, hold on a minute. Hey, let's do the- just pretend I'm not here for a second.
Alright, so I think- I think I'm ready. I think I'm ready to play. Should be good to go.
Uh, let's just make sure that you can see that. And you can. Alright, okay, we're getting there.
I got a little cropping issue over here with my open VR. What is it? Wait, wait, what's this
giant warning? If the control buttons don't work, please check the game windows. What?
How do I get rid of this little fucking thing on the bottom left? Oh, I got it.
Almost there. Looking good. Door exposed. What do I mean door exposed? Door exposed.
Oh, hi guys! How are you? Welcome to the stream! I think that's good. No, hold on a
second. So today, as you didn't know by the uh, the point I did, we're doing VR tonight.
Isn't that better? Yeah, well that's what we're gonna do, a test. Are you ready?
Here's the test, because I couldn't really tell from- before- you're gonna- I'm gonna blow
your eardrums. Okay, so you guys need to tell me. So- so I'm in, okay? So I had the
chat program thing where you go like this and see the chat, but I couldn't get it to
fucking work. I tried so hard, and I'm gonna get that ready for tomorrow. But for today,
how does it sound? Does it sound like shit? Why is it that way? Why is the game that way?
Why is the game that way? I'm peeking the mic. All right, what about now? Desync low
quality. It's- it's desynced? Oh, wait, wait, wait, come on, ready? What do you hear?
Do you hear my- the clap first, or do you hit a cl- the clap after? All right, hold on.
How's that? Is that- can you still hear me? Are we good? Is that better?
Mine's gonna be desynced, but I couldn't tell. Hold on, let me move this shit.
Hold on, sorry, but block your ears. I'm just like grabbing onto your ears.
So- so that's better. So this is fine? You guys ever okay with this? Let's try some
tests here. Are we synced? Why the fuck is the game behind me?
I did like the point to your monitor this way. So there's still a desync. Let me try this.
That's fucking weird. A lot of weird shit. Oh, god damn it. Of course there's a desync.
Stupid fucking- I was playing PlayStation 3 yesterday. Everything's fine now.
Okay, so here we go. Look, I got my controllers here. I went like that.
Like I pointed this way to the monitors. Should I just recalibrate and point that way?
So I'm just gonna recalibrate. I'm just gonna point the controller this way.
I'm gonna try that because- what the fuck? All right, let's do a room setup. What's happening?
What the hell is that on the- oh, please take off the headset and follow the- you got it.
Okay, hold on a second here guys. All right, this will only take a second. All right, turn
the controllers, place the controllers. I just- I did this like three times. Why if I point this
way at my screen- fucking valve. Locate your monitor. Okay, let me locate the monitor real
quick. Found it. Well, I know where the floor is. I sure as hell know where that is. It's right
here. There's the floor. Okay. Now I'm gonna measure- I'm gonna do like the- here we go.
I did this shit like five times already. I wanted to be like prepared for the VR streams,
but you never are. They expect somebody to fucking buy this? You think like grandma's
gonna play this game? Okay, there we are. Let's go. Your minimum play area is not big enough.
I just- it was- what happened in the- is it because my monitor is over here now?
Is that the problem? My monitor changed its positions and therefore I don't have enough
room to play? Fucking virtual reality. Give me a goddamn Super Nintendo any day of the week.
Okay. Okay, there we go. Play area has been selected. Your play area has been selected.
Done. Setup complete. All right, here we go. I'm ready. Can you guys hear the game? All right,
here we go. How do- all right, I gotta open the game again. So what the hell is over there?
No game, no sound. No game, no sound. There it comes. I just have to- all right. What the
fuck is it opening? What are you opening? What are you doing? What the fuck is that?
Why is that on the screen? Why is that on the screen? I'm not even in that game!
I'm not even in this game! Give me a goddamn Super Nintendo. I'll take Donkey Kong Country 2,
please, if you could. I don't know how many people are watching. I think we got it. Here
it comes. Did it work? I think that's it, right? Yup. So I just want to make sure- I want
to make sure we're really clear on this, guys. I want to make sure you're damn clear on this.
I pointed my- please point towards your monitor. I pointed that way.
I think we fixed it. Technology sucks. Let's go back to fucking books. All right, I'm going in.
Yeah, the original virtual world. It's called J.R.R. Tolkien's The Lord of the Rings.
Are we good? I can't even drink my coffee. All right, I'm so excited for this. I really am.
Where's my predator connection here? Which one's right and which one's left? Can I see
that through here? I can't. Why would I be able to see that? Which is the left one,
which is the right one? I can't- where the- okay, the best part about the Steam VR shit,
and I- this is so loud. I get up- how do I adjust this? I'm only going with one. I don't
give a fuck. Until somebody figures that- there's got to be like a drink can thing that comes
down. How are you supposed to hydrate? That's on the- uh, that's mono sound in VR.
I can't do it, man. I'll throw up. All right, I'm getting my zone here.
I've made it to the zone, the play area, and I'm ready to fucking go nuts. I'm gonna turn
the game down a little. All right, I'm getting in the zone. I gotta put these down first so
I can get as comfortable- I don't like this fucking giant cable. How much is the wireless
thing? 300 bucks? Fuck me, I have like a giant rat tail. I have a giant rat tail
that's weighing me down. I've never even put it on. I wanted it to be blind. I adjusted.
I put the head on, but I didn't put like the rat tail on. All right, guys, I'm fucking ready
to go. Where are my hands? I'm supposed to be able to see my hands in VR. Where are they?
All right, let's do it! Something happened in here that I'm not, uh, gonna necessarily
aware. Okay, I think- okay, I got it. I got it. My hands- why? You need like fucking
four people- you gotta hire like three people to help you get into a game. All right,
I'm ready. It's nice and snug. It looks good. No, what the fuck are you doing? I don't- no,
don't go home! Get- what button did I just press? What, is there a button? No, don't turn the
system off! Okay, okay, guys, welcome to my VR attempt here to try VR for the first time.
At least in the Steam version of VR, which I've heard is quite fun and quite interesting.
We're gonna play this game called Blade and Sorcery. Came out, um, probably a couple years
ago, but I never had a chance to play it. Let's go ahead and create our character.
It's like got this- what? Wait, why is it giving me like a little cube indicator?
Get out of here! I know that I can't go that far. Why are you boxing me in? Stop it!
All right, we got, uh, hair. Uh, oh, you can select it. Let's go Mohawk. A beard. What
about- what about for a beard? What do you guys think? Oh, that's right, I couldn't get that to
work. Eye color. Uh, let's just go with like here. That's fine. Uh, I- is this game good?
Like, this is a highly requested game. I don't- I don't care what he looks like. Face.
Oh god, you're gonna do this to me right now. Why would you give me a character creator?
An elaborate character creator? That's so cool. Okay, eye size, eye rotation,
a mouth size. Uh, is this doing anything? Okay, I gave him a Mickey Mouse nose.
Somebody just like punched into his face. All right, you know what? Let's go with uh,
glutes. Oh, the glutens. I just heard my computer make a loud click sound. I don't
know if that's good or not. Am I still alive? Did my computer, did my motherboard just like
fry? Did I just fry my motherboard? I don't know. I don't know because I can't see. Who said that?
He's got like- he's got skin colored football pads on. This is like a joke. He went to the
party store and got this put on. Oh wait, hold on. That's too tall. You gotta be small
than that. Feet size. All right, that's good. I'm ready. All right, select this character.
I've got- is this play area too small? Am I gonna get yelled at for this every time?
Can you guys see these bars? Can you see these bars?
I might have to like sit down in a chair and just change it. I thought I told me I had
enough room. Select. Calibrate. Please stand up, look straight, and click calibrate to set.
It just made him- it just made him fucking this up. Okay, let's play the game. I can't
wait. Oh my god. What the fuck? Look at you. That's never- I've never experienced something
that fucking ridiculous before in my life. Like in my whole life. That's fucking so funny. Okay,
so I move around like- how do I move around? Did you know- I can't read any of that. I have
no idea what the fuck that says. Did you know you can sheath up to four objects? Do I
have to walk there? Okay, this is actually important because I will walk into a fucking wall.
I will actually hurt myself, so it's good that I did this here. How do I move? I don't- how do
I move? Oh look- okay, that's fucking weird. I'm sorry. Oh, you can jump? I don't like
doing that. It's too fast. How do I go slower? Okay, I'm starting to figure it out. Let's
see. You can sheath up to four objects and weapons on you. You can sheath up to four
objects and weapons on you by dropping them over your left or right shoulder. What? What?
So you can sheath up to four weapons by dropping them over your shoulder or on each side of your
hips. How close am I to this wall? Okay, you can practice this by doing it by looking at
yourself in the mirror in the home. Be aware that some objects are restricted to hips or
back only. How do I like turn around again? Okay, there it is. All right, that kind of makes
me want to die doing that though too often. All right, cool. So I practice with a sword.
How do I grab it? How do I get the sword? Sword, yeah. I want to grab it with like
what- which button? Okay. Can I hold it with two hands? Come on, use my force powers.
Ah, this is the coolest thing I've ever done in my life. I'm gonna hit the fucking wall.
I'm gonna get like a good stance here. I'm having more fun just doing this than anything
else. All right, come to me. How do I get it to pull over here? It's not gonna work.
All right, get it. Where'd it go? All right, how do I play? Let's go. So I can check it
right. It's right. It's the right one. So it's this one. There it is. Okay, cool.
I love this so much. I don't know what to do. Let's go over here. Let's take a look at
the books. What's that? What's that monster? There's a monster back here. Oh, it's okay.
It's a pottery thing. What the fuck is this? Oh, shit. I have to try to put it back in.
Get in there. This one. What the fuck? I'm pressing it, aren't I? It's right. It's right.
Sit on there. Come here. In. To the holster. Okay. My goodness. Is there a mission?
All right. Where am I in my room? Where am I? I'm looking to hit something.
Okay, that's not a real table. What's this one do? The market. Yeah, let's go. Let's
go to the market. Unknown location. Okay. What's that one? The arena. Wait, there's
a book over there. No one's ever gonna be able to do this. Choose destination on the
map to travel. Isn't that what I just did? The ruins. Oh, okay. These ruins have been
known to protect a mysterious cult practicing dark magic and human sacrifice. Make them pay
for their crimes. Am I facing the right way? I'm so disoriented. I'm ready. I have to,
like, move, otherwise it feels weird standing doing this. Is it gonna kill me if I let it
go? No, that's fine. All right, well, we don't need that right now. This is probably
a puzzle that I'm gonna have to do later. Can I just, like, can I just hit shit?
What's the distance? Right, like, here. This is the most fun thing I've ever done. I'm serious.
I'm serious. This is the funnest thing I've ever done in my whole life. I've been to Disney
World. I've rode roller coasters before. I've had teeth pulled. Uh, very easy. Wave one.
Uh, what's it gonna do? What? Here, put this away for a second. Okay. Oh, all right,
we got very easy. I just, I needed to know how to play the game. Start it. Fight in
progress. Oh, God. Oh, my God. Oh, I just hit my hand. Gotta make sure he's dead.
I'm gonna two-hand this. Ow! I went the wrong way. Oh, I dropped it! I blocked it.
Which way is he coming? Which way is he gonna go, huh? Which way is he gonna go?
Oh! What do you got? Give me a weapon. What do you got? What is this, stick?
Come with me, like, always. That works. Holy shit, why am I flying?
We got another one? Two more? Get in the low center of gravity. This fucking room
scale. My earbuds fell out. How do I pause the game? How do I pause VR? I don't have
any sound. Cut him in half! Ow! I'm gonna lie on my fucking, like,
resume here. I'm gonna lie on my SATs. That was fun. Where the fuck am I?
Uh, I'm gonna redo the room scale calibration and, like, pretend the room is bigger.
Need some coffee after that one. I put on the straps. Oh, yeah, I forgot.
I forgot I gotta put the straps on. All right, is the room scale thing annoying,
or is it, is that, okay, is that, like, not irritating to look at?
Because, like, I could just fake it. I'm not gonna hit the fucking wall.
All right, that's on. It's fine, it's fine. Okay. All right, just making sure it's not,
like, annoying to see. Move your arms in a walking motion to move instead.
Really? You can make it feel less intrusive in the settings, really.
Just like the Steam, like, VR settings? Hold on, let me just, like, see.
It's, like, crushing my eye. So, let me see here. I got the Steam VR right here.
Settings. Put this up. Uh, night mode, locked mode, DND,
suppress warnings and alerts when Steam's VR status is minimized. It's in the VR setting.
Yeah, I'm in the VR settings right now. That was so much fucking fun.
No, with your headset on. It's the settings while in VR. Oh, okay.
So, do I have to, like, go, like, is there a way I can get to, like, the Steam, like,
the VR menu? It's the bottom button. Oh, it is. So, it's this button on the side of the headset.
It's the thing that I pressed before. Whoa. I got to recalibrate. Recalibrate.
And then it's the settings in here. What the fuck is this button?
I pressed it accidentally before, and now I can't, like, find the damn thing.
There it is. Okay. So, settings, right? Stream. Okay. Night mode. Do not disturb.
It's the chaperone. Chaperone bounds. Opacity. Bring it down. Okay, that's better.
All right, that's cool. Intermediate. What's that mean? All right. Squares. Advanced.
Developer. Developer. Oh, okay. So, that, that did make some go away completely. I don't know
if I want to do that because that's, like, actually probably dangerous. I'm going to get
hurt. But maybe I don't give a fuck. We'll see. We'll see how annoying it is.
All right. Let's keep going. I'm going to put both headphones in so he can't hear us. You know
what I mean? He can't hear us. I'm so sweaty already. Yeah, that's much better. All right.
So, I need to, like, how do I, like, recalibrate this? This is not right. At all.
I might have to back to app. What did I do fucking wrong?
Click window on desktop. Holy fuck. All right. We're good. All right. Let's get back in one more
sip of coffee and we're going to do the next, we're going to do a harder wave, I think.
Let me get my fucking headphones back in. I'm so glad somebody actually made this game.
No, stop doing that. Respell. Respell. Respell. Respell. Respell.
I don't know what spell I did. Okay. Let's get this back on. All right. Let's go. Respell.
Okay. There's my sword, right? All right. Let's get this foot back where I wanted it.
Turn around here. They had some cool weapons though. Let me see what they had.
Some kind of stick. Seems pretty good. I don't know if it's that good though.
Doesn't even break any bones. This sucks. Give me my, no, here we go. Here's a new weapon,
right? Is this the same sword that I had before or is this different?
Like, hold on a minute here, fellas. All right. Who wants some pork? I'm ready for the next wave.
Fight ended. Okay. Return. Where's like the food game where you can like,
I just want to get like, I don't care about, is there a game with an onion?
Is there an onion in this game or in any VR game where I get an onion and just be like,
and the fuck, I'll just like slide it into the pot. All right. We'll do wave two.
There you go. This guy's got, jump over the rock. That would have been cool.
Just wait till he swims and then come in with a double. Just treat him like an onion.
I gotta get, what's on me? What the, why did I become the rock? Hello? What?
Give me that sword back. Where the fuck is hitting me?
You want to get the fucking chef? Eat this, you fucking celery bitch.
I'm wild. I'm like a caged fucking beast. I got both of you. Oh, would that hurt your hand? I'm sorry, ma'am.
Wait, how do I do anything? Can I grab? What? Oh my God. This is fucking a blast.
I'm losing my mind. I don't even, I don't even have my twitch dashboard on.
Sweat check. It's always going to get bad here in about like 20 minutes.
You can throw weapons? How do I throw a weapon? Hold trigger while using telekinesis. Okay.
Relevant controller. Drink water. Don't drink coffee. I got plenty of fucking hydration
room back off. How do I have like hair in my mouth? No, stop it. All right, steam. I'm
going to give you a fucking design choice here that I would change if I were you.
Don't have the button be here. Have the button be like up here somewhere. Like up here.
Because like everybody like puts it on like this. Or at least I do. So change it for me.
Okay, let's keep going. That was fucking I love this game. So let me get this straight.
Can I like throw a weapon if I like let go of this? That didn't really work. So but like this
with the force power, just kind of when I hit trigger, it kind of comes back to me.
So if I hold trigger and then do it, hold trigger and like I'm holding them both at the
same time. That was fucking cool. Hold and release when you throw it. No, that's what
I was doing. So I was holding the trigger down and then letting go. Not the trigger.
It's like this grip button. That's how you pull it up, right? Now I do have like spells
too. I gotta hold on. Let me do some like fucking fun tinkering here. So walk over here.
I got it forced right now. So if I hold the grip button down, there we go. Okay. So it's
the grip button. It's not the trigger button. Cool. Let me just play around. I got spells too,
apparently. So how do I do a spell? Okay, holding that jumps. This is walk. What is spells?
That's the other grip. I had it up there before, didn't I? Maybe it's like the trigger and grip.
Hmm. I didn't know that existed. What about down? Does down do anything on the,
okay, doesn't hurt me. Just wanted to make sure. Let's get that wave going again.
Oh, is it a spear? Hold on. I gotta, oh, come on. Let me, of course I can use the spear. Put this
back. And it's a spear and a shield. Thank you very much. Oh, this is, okay, now this is what,
this is fucking awesome. I can just be a fucking turtle dickhead and just be like this.
You know what I mean? I could be like the, what's the, what's the famous group of actors
that like took on the, took on the, the Persian, the Spartans. All right, I'm gonna do, I want
to do Spartan. Let's start it. I'm just gonna, I'm gonna, this is gonna be great.
Jesus. Use touch pad or thumb pad to stick, to scroll up or down. Use, select a wave again.
Okay, let's go. And let them know that 300 Spartans.
That's right. That's what you do. Remember they make the big wall right in his neck.
Get out of my town. They could give me like fucking 50 people,
doesn't even matter. And it's starting to hurt my back. Get out of here. Get off of me.
Oh, you want to play that way? Come on. Come on. Damn it. Oh, sorry. That was
dishonorable. I think I got him. What's going on? All right, let's go. I like this setup. Wave three
on very easy. Begin. All right, guy up top. My hands are covered in water. Oh, you get the same
strategy, but you didn't protect your legs. You didn't think I was gonna saw them. She's not
dead. Told you. Told you. Sorry, I'm being like silent. I have to. What the hell? How did
you get behind me? Oh, you got my eye like a movie. Oops. Something's in my eye. How?
Did like a piece of glass go in my eye? I just gotta get close enough to do like the sweep.
Now die. Oh, who's hitting me? I don't know. I don't know who is just hitting me.
How do I do the health potion? Oh shit. I need a different weapon. Where's my dagger?
Where's my dagger? I can fucking do that to me now, are you? Never fuck with a guy with
a spear. Just like Captain America. Let me get this straight. So can I like, I want to hold
this from a different angle. I'm letting it go. Holy shit. I got to do that to somebody.
This is like, oh, this is going right through somebody's head. This is definitely, oh,
this is so worth it. If you haven't played VR and you don't, and you figure about getting
a vibe, this game is $20, I think. Holy shit. All right. I need to get some like
backup weapons. I need to figure out how to do spells. All right. Can you come up for a second?
How much is the vibe? It's $4.99. And there are better games for free. I'm just getting a taste.
You know, I'm just getting a sample. Four dollars and 99 cents and all.
So I click in the touchpad. I was clicking the touchpad on the right or the left.
The telekinesis is going too fast. Is there like a menu I can look at?
You can grab people. Just pause and go to help. Yeah, I'll just look at it. No.
Let's see what we got here. I mean, is there? Oh, God. It's so hard to get back in once you're
out. I'm going to look like a fucking psycho, but am I going to move my hair? Holy. Let's take
a look. I just broke out of a coffin. You know what I mean? I'm not supposed to be
alive right now. I just broke out of a, they buried me like two weeks ago and I got out.
I wasn't supposed to be in there. I was still alive. Oh, there's like already like
grease on this thing. Fuck me. I can't hold it. Don't look my shirt up. I've already got like
face grease on here. I should have just got like a, like a buzz cut. Oh, I'm going to be
losing hair in front of this head. You bet you I will. All right. Let me try to get back in
here. Is there like a, like a wet wipe I can get for the vibe? There's got to be like
specific wet wipes, right? Somebody's going to make them. All right. Something's not right
here. It's going to go back around. All right. That's good. Okay. All right. Let's go take a
look at some stuff here. Back it up. So on this table, there's a health potion here.
That was delicious. Wait, I'm going dinner, man. Let's go. I'm going to do another one.
I'm just like drunk shit face guy at the bar. All right. Now we're going to go to
wave three is this one. So let's do this medium. Let's do, let's do like wave.
Let's just do wave three. Let's just try it. Wave two. All right. Let's see if I
can't fucking do something cool here. Didn't somebody say if I move my hands, I walk.
Oh, come on. What was I doing? I was grabbing him by the shoulder.
I just like did something there. It looks like when my hands were grasped.
Okay. So when you crass, okay, I got it. Lightning. So they went, okay.
So that's fucking loud. So I have lightning on my hand right now.
Is that, is that so loud that you can't even fucking hear it might be
I'm going to have to lower the fucking volume. Okay. I need a team of actors to help me.
I must just fucking tripped. All right. Let's try the wiping. So it's
grab, let go. So I only have, I have no spell here. So I have this one selected.
So let's just try it.
Give me that weapon. Oh my God. That's too much for me to handle.
Come on. Murderer. I got to do Diablo two style necromancer.
Oh my God. That was horrible. Don't let him do it. Do it. It's life or death. Which one?
Which one am I going? Give me the potion. No, don't give him the potion. I'm like handing it to them.
You idiot. You fucked it all up. No, that was pretty dramatic. I know. Grab. Yeah. I got to
get used to the controllers because it's kind of hard to. So for instance, when you like
grab, like when I press these buttons here, it's like, and you kind of have to tilt your
wrist a little because I can't really do it with my pinky. It's like, it's hard to,
I got to get used to the Vive controller. So I'm going to put, I'm going to, I'm going to
un-stop that potion. My back is like fucked up now. I've had like back problems for a while
and I have no idea what the fuck is wrong with me. All right. You stick in there.
You just stay un-stopped from my drink later. Let's get this out of my person here. Okay.
I got two daggers. Oh, let's get, okay. Let's try that again. Yeah. This time I'm going
to try to just work with this here. So bingo. That's so fucking awesome. I need to like
utilize, I got to start this and get up here. Is there, somebody has a bow. I have to crush
everybody's head with a brick. Let me just take a look. The axe. I like that. I don't
think I, I don't think I picked it up. All right. I like this one. This one's pretty
fucked up. Cool. All right. I guess that, okay. Yeah. Let's replace this. Okay. Just
make sure it works. Okay. Any more items that I need to be made aware of? Let's take a look
up top. That's so interesting. Cool. Uh, that, that over there, it looks like it could be
used. What are these bad, these oil barrels? Oh, fuck this. Just keep it here. I'm going
to be throwing these at people. Oh my God. This is perfect. Why wouldn't I come up here
before? Is it fall damage? All right. I'm going to go for like the throw shit if people
take me. I'm going to bring a potion with me up there. This one. Don't steal that.
What the hell? Why? Who's hitting me? Why? Who are you here? What? Ah, okay. Wave
three. Wait. Three stars. All right. Go. Get ready. All right. Get out of my way. What the
Is it my blood? That person. Get back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back it up.
Back it up. Give me that bow. Come here. Grab. No. What? Really? Really? There it is.
I got it. I'm taking people out. I'm fucking going to be like the Star Wars kid. Just you
wait and see. Fuck potions. We don't even need them. Stop letting go of it.
Come here. Get over here. Get the fuck over here then. Get over here then. What? What item
is this? Get off. Close the book. I'm creating a book in the middle of a fight.
How could we get that on the right track? No, it's spilling. What is it? Electricity.
I was like, am I standing in a puddle? Get off my sword. Damn it. This is fucking so much fun.
I thought, I was like, what am I standing in electricity? Absolute psycho. What? I'm fighting
for my life. I'm fighting for my life here. All right. I had a better tactic when I had this
shield and the spear. I'm actually, we're going to go easy. Like really, really easy
because God, I haven't even like grabbed the tip of the iceberg. Have I? This, this is fucking,
this is so much fun. What a broken record I am tonight about that. But my God, this is so much
different than the PSVR. It's like unbelievable. Has my stomach look fat? I mean, like not like
in the game, but me, it probably does. I want to try. I want to try just simply.
So I want to just grab this person. I'm just going to try to learn it.
So we got, okay, you're here. Can I like grab? So can I, okay, hold? Is it, okay, can you hold
this button? Do I actually have to hold it though? Yeah, you do. I gotta hold down the grip
and then, so you can do that. I can't, how do I do this? What? This is too, like what?
This is not how, this is not all right. It's not all right to like, let kids do this.
All right, I got it. You got to hold the grips down.
That was daunting. Look who I have. I have one of your comrades. All right, let's try that
again. I almost just fell backwards. Not because I'm like winded, but because I almost just fell
over because I'm moving around too much. All right, let's go back to my, my bread and butter.
I have to, really, the fucking objects just hurt. Ow, my face. Okay, that one's good. Okay,
that one's good. Wait a minute, can you? Can you? Can you? Really? I can't like drink that out of
the mug. Oh, that feels like, just that alone. Put that away. What's in here? I gotta hit
somebody in the fucking heaven chair. Like that's, yeah, I mean, where is it? I can't see it.
It's under the table. Okay, with me. Who will it be? Oh, hello, man.
Damn it. What? Did I catch the arrow? I think I just caught the arrow in the air.
It's too much fun to just experiment. All right, I'm going, I'm going for the real deal
I caught the fucking arrow out of the air. All right, give me my, give me my shit.
There it is. Let's do it. This is what I had the most success
with my setup with the protection and complete offense. My always on offense.
Let's go. They like, okay. Get out of here. Where the fuck did you come from? What?
You picked a bad place to spawn. Shoot it. Oh, I got it. Come on.
Pick up the dagger. Going up top. I'm like, I'm getting close to the wall. I gotta be careful.
I need that bow. Give me that bow. Come here. Come here. Does nobody have anything? What?
I'm stuck. I got, I'm wrapped up. I'm stuck. It's actually wrapped around my whole leg.
He put a target up for me and I hit it with extreme precision. All right. I gotta,
I gotta hold on a second here. This is on my leg. I can't, I don't know if I can show you
this. Can you guys see this? No, you can't. It's wrapped around. It's like a snake around
my leg. How the fuck am I going to get out of here? I have to just turn this way.
Whoa. Is it helping? Okay. I think that's better. That's good. Let's get it out of the way now.
The bow and arrow is fucking fun. Let me just come out for a minute.
Push the menu button for slo-mo. There's a slow motion button. Nice shirt. It's coming
through the shirt. Okay. So let me tell you a few things, right? A couple of,
a couple of important things. You know when like they have the VR set up
at the convention and they're like, Hey man, you want to check out the VR?
It's only gonna take like 20 minutes. Like, yeah, yeah, sure. No, that's why I always decline
because I end up like this and I have to go home. I gotta go back to the hotel after like being
in there for like 40 minutes. Check the face. All right. Hold on. Let me go, let me go grab
like some water. I've been in here for an hour and a half. Holy fuck. All right. Let's
check. I'm going to do like one or two more of these and we'll go on to the next thing.
What is on my face? You look like a homeless guy. I need to go look in the mirror and see how
fucking bad this looks. All right. Give me a sec. What is on my, what is on my face?
Why is it coming off on me? Is this poisonous? This is, this is from the fucking what?
Do I have an acid sweat? Oh my God. This is from the foam here. It's from the foam
in the visor. What? Are you fucking serious? Okay. Well, I look fucked up. I look like,
I look like the forward in a hockey game. I'm just like, oh yeah, let me take the break.
I just got thrown out of the hockey game for fighting. I just beat the shit. We just got the
shit kicked out of each other. Me and whoever else it was that was in the hockey game.
Oh my God. All right. Give me a second. I gotta like fucking clean my face up and
figure out why the fuck that's happening. All right. I'll be right back. All right.
It smells like Pop-Tarts in here. I don't know why. What is going on? Okay. I need to figure out
why the fuck this is happening. So I've wiped it off, but look, right? So I got a paper
towel here. Clean paper towel. It's like I'm doing a magic trick. What the fuck is,
why is it doing this? Is it just, is it, is that because it's a brand new or I mean like
that is very clearly like a bunch of shit coming off. I mean, I'm sweating in there,
like not like crazy. I mean, like maybe I am. Did I get like a defective model?
Of course. I always get the fucking like defective one. That's weird.
Did I do something wrong? That happened with mine too. Oh, okay. Well, okay. I've said,
there's like a, I swear to God, there was like another piece. It's going to keep
doing that to me. Did you put on the gamer socks? Get it. Hold on a minute.
How hard is this going to be like to put on? I think I already have one.
I think it comes with like another like thing to put on. But isn't this just,
isn't this just like a replacement? Hold on. Is this, do I need to put this on?
No, no. This is if you have, this is, this is for a narrow face. This is the same
material. No, it's the same thing. Well, whatever. All right. Let's see. I'm just
going to have to like get it. Somebody said it looked like I got out of the chimney.
All right. I got my, I had my water and take the last little bit of coffee in here. We're
going to do this one more time. I'm going to try to kill somebody with a rock.
I really want to kill someone with a rock. So I'm going to try. And then we're going
to move on to probably Beat Saber. Either Beat Saber or there's like, there's like,
I got like three things lined up for tonight. Each one will be about like,
maybe like an hour or two each. Because like I told you guys before, after like three,
four hours in this thing, I got to go like take a bath. You see it in real time. I'm
going to be horrible looking in like another hour or two. All right. Let's get back in.
Although make sure, cause I, is that in the right spot? Because I had to move. No,
I think it's good. I literally can't, I can't leave this room and have to move the
lighthouse to get out of the room. I'm pissed off and like annoyed that I have to
get this like warped, like paint shit on whatever it is. Like the smears, whatever.
As long as it doesn't get my hair, which it definitely will. Let me get this untangled.
This is so tangled. I must've spun around so many times here, but wait down here too.
God, I got to like step on this and twist it. One second. Sorry. Oh my ass. I can't,
I'm so glad that this is a waste up scenario here. Where, where levels are like,
I could get in trouble if this was like a waste down camp. It's like so sweaty and awful.
Not that, not that way. All right. This should be a little more full. All right. That's good.
Make sure I can move it out. I can. All right. Let's get back in. I'm ready to do,
I've got the bow and arrow. I'm going to have some interesting fun. All right.
Uh, all the levels are good. I'm good. Let's go. Spin this back around. Make sure I'm facing
the right way. Oh, hold on. There's so much water in here. Okay. I need to get something
to help clean this shit up. All right. Is this taking screenshots? Why does it keep doing that?
All right. Let's go. Audio, audio right here. I don't know which one is which,
which is the right and which is the left. All right, let's go. I got the, where's my bow and
arrow? Where's my, where's my bow? Wasn't there like a market? What? Is it a quiver? Give me
those arrows. Okay. What happened to my bow? I have a sword back here now. Am I missing
something here? Where'd my cool bow go? I haven't even done any environmental stuff.
Why is it all the way over here? Hello? Why is it in the ground? Whatever. It's not like
a fucking stick in the ground. That's great. Here, you know what? Couldn't take these then.
I'll just throw these at people. Fight ended. All right. Uh, I can scroll down.
How do I do that again? Right. Uh, that was a lot of money. Somebody just gave a lot of money.
I can't, I don't even know what it was. Uh, it was Freudian, Freudian weapon. Don't mind me
just derailing your stream. Ha ha ha. I saw it. Got it. Freudian weapon. Thank you so
much for the $50 and the derail special endless. No, thank you so much. I don't know
where you are, but thank, I think you're, uh, you should be like here. Thank you so much
Freudian weapon for the $50 fucking dollars. All right. We've got one V1 classic. There's a few
more things to try here. Enemies. Let me just do group one. What is this? Multiple enemies,
but only moan melee attack at a time. Cult versus bandits. Random cult enemies against
bandits. Am I just like the priest that sit here and watches the melee? Why is that guy
naked? We're supposed to be fighting each other. Why are you attacking the priest?
All right. Well, that's my friend. Okay. But that's how that works. My face is really itchy.
This fucking coal is on my face and it's itching my face and I can't scratch it.
Oh, get off. Remember what I told? Hold on a second. Remember I told you something was
going in my eye. This is like freaking me out now. Remember like an hour ago? Oh,
something's like in my eye. How? This shit is melting off into my fucking eyes.
All right. I got the edge scratched. Uh, I want to, let me go out. Let me go back out to
like the menu menu. What is the slow mo? Let me try slow mo of like hitting somebody in the
head. Get his weapon. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it. That was three people. That
guy's like, Oh, that was weird. I'm trying to like slit his throat. I gotta move on from this
game, but like there's more to do. I'm like having so much fun. I can't. I gotta like hit
somebody with another brick. Let's get like only bricks. I'm going to have plenty of cement
blocks. Okay. Get them all up there. So spell wise, right? Do I have to like go to town
and like buy shit? I've really only been doing this like weird arena thing. I'm going
to look into that in a second. Let's get this started. I'm going to try to just hit
people with fucking blocks. I'm going to rush somebody's head in between two logs. Are you
ready for this shit? This is so fun. It's too fun. They made a, they gave me,
they made a game that was too much fun to play on me. What the fuck is happening to me?
Give it to me. Put it in my hand. Hold an ax. I'm holding this like a fucking soda.
Come on.
God damn it. I hit myself in the back. How do you block that? That's not blockable move.
That's a non blockable move. Fuck. Put it in there. God, just run by it.
Come on. I want to give it a marathon. Give me the game right. Come here. Get over here.
Get over here.
Oh, no. Jump. Give it to me. Give me something. Give me the dagger. What?
Why did I just do that to her? Why did that just happen?
Oh, what happened there folks? Shit. Don't have to fucking game fuck me like that.
I was just sat on this fucking dick. What was that? This is intense. That was what? Medium level
three? I doubt I wasn't really using the slow-mo that much. All right. Let me go back to the,
like the menu. Look, I do that. What do we got here? Notes, controller, input,
all these tips. Go to character, go home. Let's go home. Cool. All right. Let's go.
Well, now I know I can do this. So fun. All right. Oh, we got this. More things here.
The market. Someone put a price on your head. Now you're ambushed in town with no way out and
everyone wants to bounty. It's either you or them. Okay. What about this one? This is the arena
and this is the ruins. So this is the arena. This one, these are locked.
Oh, these are work in progress. Okay. Let's go to market. Well, this is cool looking.
Okay. Interesting place. What's over here? There's like a little blacksmith table.
At least these weapons. Look at this. Oh, that's a big sword. That's like a bastard sword, right?
It's a fine blade. It's hard to kind of use it like this though, because you got to use both.
I'll give it a try. All right. What do we got here? Let's do, let's do easy wave two.
The well. You can probably throw people down the well, I would assume.
Do you ask? Two-handed is hard because the controls are so big.
No, yeah. Two-handed ain't going to work. The controls are too large. They just smash into
each other. I'm getting like wrapped up again in this cord. I'm like, step over the cord.
My God. I gotta like, how do you pause the game? I'm like wrapped up again.
Can't pause real life. Even if there is a cord in the back of your head that is
wrapping around you like going out and having a dog and having another dog meet you because
they're on the same sidewalk and then you get wrapped up by the fucking other person's leash
and you do the thing when you walk around in circles. The dogs are wrapping you both up now
and you're talking about like the fucking weather. That's what's happening to my
body right now. There's a dog down here running in circles around two people. Two dogs.
I'm going for the fucking thrust. What's happened? Did the game just lag? What's happening
right now? Where did you go from? Oh fucking God, dude. Like really. Look at this shit.
Getting a ceiling hook? I get like a ceiling tether. No, I gotta get the wireless thing.
The headset just has to come off because it's just been spun around too many times.
This cord is like such a thick-ass cord too. Hold on. I gotta get that ceiling tether.
It's like I'm playing, I'm doing a puzzle right now. Oh, I'm sorry. People are gonna
throw up from looking at this, aren't they? I'm sorry. It's almost done. Okay. All right. Yeah.
No, that's it. Have a nice day. No, you got a beautiful dog. Beautiful dog. Yeah. What's his
name? Oh, Ruff Ruff. Cool. Yeah. Mine's auto. Have a nice day. Fucking hell. All right.
Last one. I'm gonna go to Beat Saber. I'm gonna make this one count. This game is so
much fucking fun though. All right. Let's move. I'm gonna grab one more weapon that I haven't
used. No, I want the bow and arrow. Bow and arrow is so much fun. I have to use the bow
and arrow. What are you talking about? I don't need more. Okay. Let's get some slow motion
headshots and then I'm gonna call it. We'll go to Beat Saber. Just do like way three. Easy.
Go. Spoiled here. Okay. Let's get a slow motion headshot. Oh, got him. I need to get
a good shot from far away. Ow. I hit my face. Give me the arrow. Give me the fucking arrow.
Oh. Weapon. Weapon. Needed a weapon. Really? Worth potions? Oh fuck. I didn't hit the wall.
I didn't hit the wall. I hit the stand that's over here with the lighthouse on it.
That's all right. We're good. It's Beat Saber time. Too much like. Okay. All right. We're
good. I'm still seeing. Get some water. Dude, you're sweating. I've been sweating
this whole time. That's just the way it is. All right. Let's do Beat Saber. That was
really fucking fun though. So how do I go like this? I think I can just exit from here, right?
I think I can just quit the game from here. That's like I heard everybody at the same time
go ooh. Ding. I was like mining fucking coal over here. That's what I'm doing. That's this
one. Quit this really. Quit this reality. There we go. Play what you want to play. Yeah. I
want to play Beat Saber. Oh, I think this crashed. I think the sorcerer game crashed.
Blade and sorcery has not responding. Well, oh well. Let's open Beat Saber. Although somehow
I can still hear the game. Why can I still hear? Why can I still hear that? You hear the birds?
Why can I hear birds? What just happened? Oh, SteamVR had to like restart. Oh, okay. There we
go. Wait, what? Oh, this is like the home thing. Okay. SteamVR home has the birds. I thought it was
the other game. Let's do Beat Saber. Here it comes. We got a health and safety warning.
All right. Let's get back in. Playing Beat Saber is dangerous. So you're going to get hurt.
You're going to mine for coal on the pole. Then how is it? Hopefully I didn't fucking
cause a problem on that. Those things are expensive. I think we're good though.
Stay healthy. I'm good. I'm good. I'm healthy. Okay. Booting up. Here it comes. All right.
A small percentage of people might experience seizures when exposed to certain lights,
patterns or images. Oh, I'm going to change the... Is there a mod here that can change
the game to Beat Saber? Cause I can't fucking do it. I'm a little preoccupied.
Me, me, me. I can see. At least this one I don't have to move around. All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Those are going to make me puke if I do this like this.
Open new window. What the fuck is it then? This is Puke City. Okay. I did just hear it.
I heard who? I'm sorry everybody. But that was the first thing that happened. That was the
front page. All right. Here we go. Virtual world. There we go. Beat Saber. All right.
Update. If you want to refresh it, it'll show up there. Here we go. Beat Saber. Let's do it.
Get in the game. Let me show you some of my fucking skills. This time I'm not going to
ding over there. All right. Please read health and safety warnings in your VR headset
instruction menu before playing Beat Saber because you may be encouraged to perform
intense actions with your controllers. Make sure to review your surroundings and
clearing obstacles in your play area. AKA you. High physical activities of all the same
habits as doing a regular workout. Don't forget to stretch before playing and rest
regularly. Don't worry. I'll be fine. All right. We got free play. Party. Levels played.
Welcome. Thanks for purchasing our game. We're a small team working hard to bring you the
best VR and rhythm experience possible. Cool. All right. Free. Let's just play for free.
Let's do this tutorial. Holy shit. This is cool. Something about pork.
Max the color and the direction. This is just like Space Channel 5.
Do not cut or touch with sabers. Just like Fruit Ninja. Whoa. Make sure they're in the right spot.
How's the audio? Loud enough? All right. I can barely see. Do like a funny emote if the
audio is loud enough. I'm not seeing any funny emotes. That must mean. Okay. Hold on.
There's no audio. What the fuck? What the fuck is that? Why did it do that?
All right. We should be good. All right. I'm ready. Let's play Beat Saber.
Stand right here. Free play. Pop stars. This is the one from League of Legends.
Let's play pop stars from League of Legends.
What? Whoa. Hey, I don't want to join anybody's group. Why is this on? Why is this on here?
I'm losing the audio in my ear. Let's both fall out.
How long is this song?
League of Legends. What a fucked video game that is. What the fuck does that have to do with League of Legends?
Is this one of the characters singing the song?
I'm going to beat. I'm going to beat. I'll take a beat. B for boomer. Nice KD.
It's a little loud. All right. Yeah. It looks, it does look a little loud, doesn't it?
That's better. It was way too loud. It's all right. B for boomer. I'm going back in.
This is really, really cool. I mean, I kind of have to like close my mouth and just play
it, but this is fucking fun. You just like kind of zone in. How am I doing? That's a hair look.
Let's do it again. Another one. What's, what's like a good song? What would you guys say is
the best Beat Saber song? Let's take a look. Let's do, let's get it on hard and I gotta
get ready. Okay. This is let, no, get. Well, who made that? Okay. What does this mean?
Just single, solo, standard, one Saber. Okay. No arrows. Oh, I don't know about that one.
Is this this one artist? Do I, how do I play like other ones? This is all songs I have.
Let's try it. Make it a fuck for me on that one. Oh, God damn it. I don't, get out of my head.
Steam notifications. I don't know how many times you have to turn off steam notifications
and like delete it from your goddamn inventory, but it never stops. This one's
better. I like this one. Let's start it up. Come on. Damn it. They fuck with you a little
bit there. They fuck with you. A B? I'll take a B. Solo free play. Okay. All right. Looking
good. How do you get more songs though? What's the other one? What's the other League
of Legends song? Bring it on. Fucking expert. Let's go. You don't think I know what I'm
doing? Don't, what the fuck valve? This is hard. This song's not even good. I don't like
this song. It's a song on YouTube videos. This is a YouTuber song, right? Now this
one's on a, this one's like easy though. So this is like a, oh, I'm going to hurt
myself. I can do this on expert. Do I unlock songs? All right. We're going to do one
more on expert. I thought, I can't, you kind of can't do the expert ones unless you,
until you figure out like the muscle memory for the beat, can you? All right. Where's
like the custom shit? How do I do the custom stuff? What's happening here? It's
almost like for experts. This is really, really fucking fun. Songs, songs, songs.
You need mods. You need mods. You need mods. Okay. All right. All right.
Why do I look so feral? Go to the GitHub. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Does this have like steam workshop? I have to go to GitHub? Okay. There's no
workshop. Oh, all right. Well, how, let me just get this installed then. And then
where do you get the songs? From beatsaber.com? No, that's not real. That's a fake
website. Is it really beatsaber? So install them from in the game. Okay. So let me
just get this then. All right. How do I, they probably install custom mods.
This uses modsaber to get the latest approved and manually verified mods,
latest version automatically. Okay. So modsaber. This program currently supports
every approved mod on modsaber.org. Okay. Song loader, camera plus song
browser. There's a lot of shit here. Gameplay changes. I might, okay, here's
what I'm going to do. I'm going to hold onto this for tomorrow night. I'm
going to go get a bunch of shit. I need to like close the game. Let me
get this for tomorrow. Let me get like all the shit that's necessary for
it. And I'll like make sure it's, it's up and running and good because we're
going to do it tomorrow night anyway. So I'll get, I'll get a bunch of good
songs. Like country road. And I also need to get the mod that lets me
like look at my hand and I, I discord channel to suggest songs.
Yeah. I have the program. I have that VR drop program, but I couldn't
get it to work. I could get it to open up chat, but I was trying to
get it to like stay on my hand and how do I, you know, there's a lot
of me to kind of do before that. I look haggard. I mean, it's because I
have this, this shit on my face. All right, let's do, I'm going to do like
a couple more, just the default ones and then we'll move on to,
what's the other game that I got here? I got, I have, I have budget
cuts. Let me do a few more. Yeah. This super hot VR, I get so much
to play. I'm going to try to do like three, three games, three to
four games a night, each game for about an hour. And then we're going
to, I'm going to, I'm going like two or three days straight here, guys.
Let me do one more of these fun ones and we'll, we'll go to budget cuts
for like an hour or two. But I just, I just didn't know that you had
to, Jeff, stop, stop, stop, stop it. Let's go.
Fuck! I don't know how that, I don't know how that part goes.
Don't do it. I did expert first try on that, that's a C, but it's the
first time I've ever heard that song. I've never even heard that song
before. I, I started to get it. I started to figure it out. Let's do
that one on hard. When they switch it up on you like that. I think
I got to the place of no return here and I'll tell you what I mean
by that in a minute. So here's what I mean by that. Once you do hard
and expert and you, especially expert, certain sections,
certain sections of every one of these levels now, not on expert,
feels too easy and certain sections are way too hard. You know what I
mean? Like, I feel like I should have just done, but normal is,
easy is too easy. I went, I did, I got, I went, pointed on return.
All right, last one. Here we go. Did I already do this one? No, I
didn't do this one today. I definitely didn't. See, like,
this is too easy. You know what I mean? I've ruined it. Now I
have to play this on expert. Whoa, whoa, I got cocky. Don't get
cocky. I almost had a hundred percent. A B. How do you get a B
with 293 out of 295? That's an A, that's an A plus. All right,
now let me, like, eat my words. Do expert plus.
That's fucking hard. Do it again? Again? No, we'll do this
tomorrow. Holy fuck. I look like I'm supposed to be in a
Ghostbusters movie or something. I look like shit. All right,
let's, let's take our, let's take our final break of the
evening. I'm going to get some more water and then, and then
I'm going to open budget cuts and we'll play that for like
an hour or two. And then I'm going to take my, my actual
break from VR and we're going to go again tomorrow. So give
me one second. Let me get another glass of water. Coal
miner. Oh yeah. Well, first impressions of the Vive. The
Vive is a hundred times better than PSVR. I would
probably say safely. I'll be right back. Give me like two
minutes. Okay, so let us get back in. Look at my hair.
Can you imagine if I were to go, like I kind of want to go
sit down like after today or tomorrow and go to a barber
or a salon and just sit down and just be like, yeah, um,
you know, I'm not sure what to do with it. Maybe you
can have some suggestions on what I should do. Jesus
fucking Christ. It's like matted up animal hair. Like
that's, that's the kind of scenario with the lady or
whoever it is, whoever it's like, that's a salon cut in
your hair. You need to go to the doctor. Like you've got
to go to like a surgeon to get this fixed. I can't do
it for you. Get a hair net. No, I gotta get like a
haircut. All right, here we go. Let's get back in.
I'm not sure how this works, but I'm going to turn
this on so you should see me here. BRB needs to get
out of here. Budget cuts is this next game. This is
going to be the last one tonight. Wish me luck and
we'll be back tomorrow. What's going on here? Oh,
fuck. Right. Hold on. I screwed this up. I'm going
to move this back. The lighthouse has to move back
where it belongs. Here. It's good. Communicate
for a second. Uh, headset is not tracking. Not
ready. Not ready. Not ready. Uh huh. I know it'll
be ready in just a moment. There it is. All
right. I'm going in. See you soon. Space camp too
big. See you in an hour. Yeah. Ma, leave me
alone, Ma. I'll do my homework in an hour. I'm
currently in the oasis. Don't talk to me. Hold
both. It's a start. Figure my controller. Don't
you do it. In cords. Okay. Hold both pads to
start budget cut story mode. That's not what I
wanted to do. Hold both pads. What the hell
is that? Budget cuts arcade. Wait. Hold both
pads. That's an okay. Here we go. Room scale
360 tracking. That's what I got. Sound effects,
music. Okay. That's the one. Continue. Empty
slot. Let's go. Difficulty standard graphics
quality. Uh, I don't think it matters. Initializing
cat seat. Look at over there. Look right
there. Look at that. That's the one I hit
by the way. Initializing. Calibrating space
time. Please hold. I got battery halfway. I
can, I can hear you guys. Don't worry. I
got it. I'm in the oasis. Leave me alone.
Let's just take this along. Initializing.
Done. Calibrating space time. Please hold.
Can you take it? Come on. Dinner's in the
oven. Come on. This is supposed to take
this long. Okay. Jesus. Try picking stuff
up. Is it one of these games? Okay. Now
press and hold this tiny button in your
non-dominant hand. Bring this, bring,
bring tool handle here. Hold the trigger
to fire. Press any of the grip buttons
to translocate. So you, that's how you
move. Or is it? That's how you move.
Okay. I'm fucking nuts. Can I do it? All
right. Let's go. That's freaking me
out. No, no. Okay. So we got a light
switch. Turn it off. That hurts. What
did I just turn off? No. Put the
budget back on. Put the fucking budget
back on. All right. Back over this way.
Turn on the lights. Sure thing.
What do you want to do? Laser secure
anti-spy vent. Perfect. Okay. Can I sit
on the couch? I can go over there. I
can look at this. Computer. We got
some other shit here. What's that?
There's a wall right here. There's a
wall right here. I don't know which
one, but I know that it's there.
Nothing in this. What's that? It's
something. Is it brick? It's just
bricks. Come on. There's no smashing
sounds. Okay. You can't fucking leave
me alone. I'm assuming I can take
that off. Okay. Yeah. What's in
there? There's tape in that room.
Sure. And where's the wall? The
actual wall. Okay. Now what the hell
do you want me to do? What's that?
Key card? Hold this touchpad to open
your inventory. Use your other hand
to drop items into this bubble. Okay.
I got that. How many things can I
hold? Wall coming up. Did it take the
paintbrush? The tape? Caution, wet
paint. Okay. Well, I have the
key card to one. It looks like
we're going over there. Well, it's
two. Can I do something weird here?
Is there a one back here?
Oh. Oh. Well, I thought that the
one was that you got to use this on
one. You can't go on two until you
get the code for two.
Three hours earlier. Organic matter
here. Keep it. Alan! Alan! Alan! Alan!
I can hear you, Kate. I'm just
choosing not to respond.
Okay, then. Sure. Fine. I guess you
don't want to know about where all
our colleagues have been
disappearing to. Professional. Wait.
Okay, guests. I do want to know.
I did the YouTuber joke. You gotta
laugh. I'm divided attention.
Well, I heard from Tracy the
county that all the humans in her
department have been reported to HR.
They're human. Of course they're in
violation of HR. That's where the
phrase comes from. Human nature.
Did you even listen in our orientation?
Yes. But what you don't know is, is
that they never come back.
That's for you. You ain't going on
that trip, Dickhead. Are you sure?
Positive. They had a meeting with HR
and then, Poof! Never seen again.
Hey, you, too. That is worrying.
Back to work. I do hope they're all
right. All right. Okay. Open the
briefcase.
Press staple. All right. Hold that
there.
What are these drugs?
No, but I need this.
This pager was mailed to you. Enjoy.
The next challenge is disruptive.
What is it? Telephone? Hello?
How do I use the phone?
Do I press the button?
Okay, you gotta hold. Okay, I got it.
Ready?
No, not that. Not 1982.
Nineteen eighty-five.
Hello, can you hear me? My name is
Winta. And look, we can do the cute
introductions later.
You're in terrible danger. People
keep disappearing around here.
And I hate to tell you, but they're
coming for you next.
Now, I'm gonna help you get out of
here, but we have to move quickly.
See that locked briefcase? I hid the
key for it on your desk.
Wait, wait, wait! What's the objective? What?
Get out of the building as fast as you
can. What's the objective?
Put it in your inventory.
I'll ping you once you're clear. Now
stay low and hurry.
You can make it, but you have to go
now. Your desk is a key
under the pot and there's a
translocator in there.
And then you need to death bad
jump from the building.
From the elevator, go to the third
floor. That's me.
Hey, uh, hey, this is me.
It's me. I'll put that in your prayer.
All right, key behind plant. Key under
the plant. Key? There's a key over the
under the plant here.
Which plant? You scared me! Where's the
plant?
Did I call the number again? Hold on.
This is how the matrix starts. You
need to leave right now.
There's a key to the travel device
hidden on your desk. Grab the pager,
put it in your inventory, and get off
this floor any way you can.
Right, all right, so it was the plant.
It's in the plant.
Got it. How much money is in here?
Oh, this is not a bucket. This is my
walk. Beware. Do not do anything
weird. Top secret.
Move your controller to equip the
translocator.
Okay, uh, now it's time to go. I
gotta get to the... Let me take these
because I'm gonna, I'm scared I'm
gonna need them.
I'm gonna forget how to do
everything. Reading emails.
Okay. So, uh, your desk, go out,
find the elevator, go to the third
floor, and find me.
You got it. Third floor, elevator.
How about...
I can only show you the door. You are
the one that must walk through.
There's an open window. Fruit travels
through the air similar to a banana.
Okay, so everything travels through
the air similar to a banana.
What is considered great at one point
in time may or not have the connection
to something previously considered
small.
I made it. Every day is taco day.
Yeah, sure. All right, we're in.
Find the elevator, go to the third
floor. Itchy nose, hold on.
Every day is taco day.
What do we got? Soda?
Did you eat something? I don't know
you could do that.
Well there. No, no, no, no, no. Go back
out.
Oh, whoopsie. You know, fuck off.
Oh, hello. Get over here.
That was close. I can't kill him. I'm
trying. I'm trying to kill him.
How could you? Damn it, man. Give me
the fucking ashtray.
Hey, look over here. Your point.
This is a fucking ashtray, dude. How
many? Oh, fuck what I hit. I don't know.
Run out of time. Let's go. Get out
there.
Where is she? Tell me where she is.
All right, what do we do? Gonna go to
the elevator, right? It's like fighting
back.
I don't know where I am in my room.
No, it's okay. Another person throw
out a window. Cookie? All right, I need
the elevator. Can I get a water?
Where's that? Oh, there's coffee right
there. Give me that.
Give me coffee. I want the coffee. Well,
how am I gonna get fucking coffee out of
this thing?
All right, let's go.
Uh, what can you do for me? Anything?
Who is this handsome devil with the
death-set tones reaching out to me
over the tannoy?
Rex. Gold cup with ash or honey?
And there's plenty of ways to describe
me.
International business playboy
superstar. The writer is genius.
That's so funny.
Now 775 lost in time.
Uh, I need to get something from you.
Another day? Another dollar?
Oh, no.
Hello human. I am very busy with my
tasks. Can we be friends?
Uh, I don't know. You got anything
under there for Elbertson?
Fuck you. Here's the elevator. I found it.
Level three.
Do I need money? That's a wall.
All right, do I have a soda? All right,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Get rid of
this. I don't need that anymore.
I don't need this anymore. I need to
know what you look like, Phil. Let's
take a couple sodas.
Let's get some sodas. At least one or
two. I need to have a whole lunch.
All right, I got a whole lunch now. We got
apple, cookie, two sodas.
Perfect American lunch.
The wall. What am I gonna touch? I
don't know. Gonna be very slow.
Floor three, right? Bingo. Let's go.
360 degrees of fun.
Supervision Acquisitions HR COM team.
And that guy. That guy over there.
We got a new phone. Wait, mission
objective updated.
204- what the- okay.
2048. Isn't that like an iPhone game?
No. No.
Right, you made it. The quickest way to the exit is
via the acquisitions department, but
there are robots of the unfriendly kind
of head. TransCorp insists on using
military-grade assault robots for
supervisor duties.
So efficient. Not. Use the stealth
feature on the translocator to avoid
alerting them.
Stealth feature? You'll need an access card.
I think the manager on this floor
might have one.
Grab it and head to acquisitions. Good
luck. Okay.
So I have a- is this stealth?
Is this my stealth right now?
This is like a bug net. I don't know
what to do.
The stealth feature. Oh, I was probably
going to call you back.
Get to acquisitions. Might need a key
card. I have a key card, didn't I?
I have a key card. What happened to one?
Did I throw the key card down?
Okay, watch out. That first- that guy's
going to shoot at me.
And there is a stealth- I don't even
know what this does.
Use the stealth feature. You know-
I'm just gonna fucking go over there.
I'll get a tutorial right now, won't I?
All right, where's my tutorial?
Friends, I'm sure you
already noticed your brand new
supervisor colleagues have leaked.
I have a difficult enough job keeping
everyone
focused on the task at hand.
The setup let their bandits concern
you?
No, really. Don't.
I don't know.
I thought it was like a fucking scrambler.
Hope both paths to reapply.
All right, mission objective updated.
Yeah, but
how the hell do I do the thing?
Listen again.
All right, you made it. The quickest
way to the exit is via the
acquisitions department.
There are robots of the unfriendly
kind ahead.
Transcorp insists on using military
grade assault robots for supervisor
duties. They use a handout.
Efficient. Not. Use the stealth feature
on the translocator to avoid alerting
them.
Oh, you'll need an access card.
The stealth feature?
They didn't tell me this last time.
When portal is open, press and hold to
translocate silently.
They didn't tell me that before.
Friends, I'm sure you already noticed
your brand new supervisor colleagues
have leaked.
I have a difficult enough job keeping
everyone focused on the task at hand.
Just don't let their methods concern
you.
No really, don't let their methods
concern you.
Don't look, don't look, don't look.
I don't know if that is what I'm
taking.
Achievement unlocked. I got a crab.
Everything seems quiet. Maybe
too quiet. Is that a window?
Fucking gods, I thought it was an
open window.
I thought it was an open, I thought it was
and why would that have helped anyways?
How would he have even done anything
about that? He would have, I thought
he was going to look down like metal
gear solid or something.
All right, I got it, I got it. I gotta
turn it on. I know, I know, just look.
I'm gonna dial the number.
I know the fucking phone number already.
Lady, just. Okay, here we go.
What's in there?
Manager.
New supervisor colleagues have leaked.
I have a difficult enough job keeping
everyone focused on the task at hand.
Sit up. Let their methods concern you.
No really. Don't let their methods
concern you. Manager's office is right
there.
I watch all the things. I see all the
things. I shoot all the things.
See ya. Okay, I'm in the manager's
office. I made it.
Manager's desk? Okay, manager's desk.
Don't have the urge to throw a
fucking rock over there. I know you
want to.
Anything in the filing cabinets? No.
All right, manager's desk. Need a key
card.
Tuesday. Schedule meeting with Adam in
HR for that.
The stupid worker who left her key
card in plain sight in the yellow
section.
Stupid worker who left her
key card in plain sight in the
yellow section.
The yellow section. Is that orange?
We're gonna go to the yellow section.
Nobody in here?
Anomalous human.
That's blue. That's red. All right, I'm fine here.
Is that yellow down there maybe? I have no
idea.
Yellow's over here. That's yellow, right?
This is yellow. In plain sight in the
yellow section.
Can I get over there?
This is pretty yellow. HR. There it is.
HR. Yellow. What am I? I can stand
up. What am I doing?
I need the key card. Where's the yellow
section? Key card in plain sight.
Oh, it's already open. I don't always
let my guard down.
All right, what about over there? Right
down there?
Right into the desk. No, come on.
Better shot than that.
All right, I'm in. Did they come all
the way down here?
Doesn't look like it. All right, I'm
preparing a key card.
I've received a few notes about your
supervisors of late.
Please remember, any complaints will be
noted with Adam.
I heard of HR. He was always very keen
to know exactly who you are in
explicit detail.
Where's your key card?
That was the right idea. I was down
in the right spot.
I curled. You guys didn't. I don't think you saw it, but I curled up
into a fetal position.
I'm too immersed. Oh, thank god it just
puts me right here.
All right, let's go. Okay, there it is. Can I
scrap it through the portal?
Really? I can't just put my hand in
there? All right, wait till it's gone and
I'm going to come back and shoot it.
Ready? Here we go. One, two, three, go.
Oh, what are these cookies?
Please hold the text. What?
I've received a few notes about your
supervisors of late.
Please remember, any complaints will be
noted with Aria.
This very keen to know exactly who you
are.
Okay, I got it. I've never made that
kind of noise before.
A cartoon bird. All right, let's get out
of here.
Hey! What does this say?
Placeholder text for a lazy dev.
Forgot to replace the proper text
ring thingy. So you suck, whiz,
dev. Wow, it takes effort to write
more than a couple words for some
reason. I just wanted to fill
an A4 like, you know, with things. I
don't know. This is enough.
All right, I got the key card. We need to go to acquisitions.
Store that one. What? Oh, did I beat
the mission?
Pretty good. Why is this not fucking
Beat Saber? You know what I'm saying, kid?
Why is that? I don't have Beat Saber, kid.
All right, now where for? Interesting.
Welcome, everything's fine. This is a
very orange room. That's one single
orange.
Just give me a single orange, man.
Cool. All right, we got acquisitions,
distribution, cybernetics, public work,
statistics,
which is in here. So we need to go
to acquisitions.
This card doesn't work.
Okay, uh, right, right.
Uh, so how do I get up there?
Come on, Georgie. Come on down here,
Georgie.
I'm gonna bite your eyeball, kid.
Whoa, almost fell down. Attention. What
does it say? Attention.
Ventilation shafts ahead. This ventilation
connected to acquisitions,
distributions, lost and found, and
restaurants, okay?
So this ventilation connected to
acquisitions.
Okay, where's the vent? Oh, that's a vent.
Well, we'll just, let's go. Nothing else
I can do. Just go in here.
All right, we got fork, knife,
area to go, uh, the gas can of some
sort.
What do you want the gas can, you
think? Probably gonna need it down
there.
One, two, three.
That didn't do anything. Okay,
what else we got? Okay, go across
there.
Let's just do it.
Is this death? Yeah. All right, let's
sneak through. I'm gonna get jumpscared in
here or something, aren't I?
Okay, I can stand up now. Interesting.
We're gonna go that way.
It's not in. It is. Ah!
Well, this seems to be a dead end. No,
it's not.
There's no animals in here. The brush
is mightier than the sword. That's
what they're describing, okay?
That exploded. That thing was already
ready to blow up.
Nothing else I can do in here. Let's just keep moving.
Hey there, Georgie! Can you guys even
fucking see me right now?
I might feel like on camera. Button,
what do these do? I don't know if they do
anything. I have to do something with this.
Oh, hello. Bathroom, we made it.
Wow, you have an appearance. Whoa,
Twitter.
Ah, soap. I gotta play with the soap,
Spencer. I mean, it's a VR game. You
gotta click on everything, right?
You didn't program soap to come out
of the soap, Spencer. What are you
fucking kidding me?
Let's go in trash. Anybody in here?
All right, well, let's get in.
Oh, don't mind me. I'm just in the
bathroom.
All right, let's fucking get it down
here.
All right, I'm fucking ready. You ready?
Ah!
I gotta get out of the bathroom. All right, let me get out of the bathroom.
It's just like the other one. Need some
TP? Sure, I'll get it for you.
I gotta get out of this. I gotta...
All right, no fucking... Is there a wall?
There's a wall coming up.
Oh, I don't know where I am in the room.
I was slamming that on my knee. It was
like right on my knee. My knee was
right there.
It hurt. The stall's open out
this way.
There's gonna be a guy in here,
right? He's gonna be like, oh,
excuse me, right?
No, nobody in here. Nobody even in
the bathroom.
Oh, what am I gonna do about my fucking
alcohol moments?
All right, I gotta get out of the bathroom before I do something that I'm
gonna get in trouble for.
Get me out of the bathroom now. I don't
care about an item. Get me out.
Leave. Bathroom. Now. Bathroom. Out.
...meditations. You know, they used to hear me talk and think I was as good as a player.
Lost and found again.
But look at me now. Am I on tech empire?
Reading you this motivational note in my
favorite hand.
So remember, we all in the same boat.
75.
That is probably bigger and more expensive.
So what is our objective right now?
Something, right?
Home sweet office.
Hey!
Oh, the microphone doesn't work.
Can I be back? Can I get back here?
Well, I guess I can get back here.
Fucking secret. You guys didn't think I was gonna get fucked secret.
The early bird.
Look at this shit.
What's going on on my shelf?
Nah, I need something heavier.
Oh, excuse you.
Oh, whoopsie.
Okay, box.
This one needs a level one security code. I have that.
Give it a swipe.
What happened?
Oh, five, seven, and eleven.
Five, seven, one, one.
Hello?
Yeah?
I'm not sure if this line is tapped, so there's a package of
letterers waiting for you in the distributions department.
They're shiny, sharp, and stabby letter openers
that will definitely help you to escape.
Distribution center.
Let's just say that a manifest that said safe, totally harmless, and another manifest that said
sharp, pointy knives magically got switched around.
That's hilarious.
All right, I mailed you a box in the distribution center,
which is over here.
Here we go.
Should I like do more like VR?
Should I get like really into it and like have you guys see like for instance like,
it's pretty cool, right?
Like, it's actually got weight to it.
Would more viewers be here?
Might be looking in the right direction.
All right, distribution center.
The brush is money than the sword.
You've seen this already.
Can't do anything with this.
This is fucking daffy ducks.
Like three nephews or whatever they are.
Tweedle-lee, Tweedle-dum, and Tweedle-doo.
Fuck them.
All right.
There's nothing in here.
Wait, there might be an Easter egg writer.
No.
No, nothing in here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's that?
All right, distribution center is over here.
That's Joan T.C.'s office.
There's Nikki Hortense.
But that's not, I don't think going,
do I have to go into everybody's office and see what they have on the desk?
Wait, there's a no here.
Oh my goodness.
I, dear Nikki, I hope that your travels have brought you new perspective.
This is too, I can't read it.
Look, here, just take a screenshot.
Ready?
Take a screen cap and then you can read it later.
All right, let's go.
Distributions, continue.
Hello.
I'm just a bully.
All right, you need that notebook?
I just did the magic trick.
Would that take that?
Oh no, it's not coming in here.
Not gonna, no, no, we're good, we're good.
Two big cans of soda you got here
that transforms who is Dr. Gimbal Locke.
Cool.
All right, this is a secure area.
Level one key, I got that shit right here.
Distributions is this way.
Whoa, he opened the door.
Holy fuck, man.
Oh my god, he's gonna shoot me with the gun.
I thought, yeah, I didn't know he opened the doors.
So you guys are that way, right?
We're not.
You guys are over here?
No, you guys are this way.
Hey guys, how are you?
I wonder what that other thing is for.
It's in the door.
Okay, we need to go.
Right, that doesn't look right at all.
Where am I?
What year is it right now?
57, do I have to call the number again?
I have to call the number again.
Oh boy, we're getting some problems here.
Okay, I'm gonna open these all.
These are all open, right?
Get them all open, keep them open
because they're escape pods.
They're wasting me to get the hell out of here.
All right.
When you feel down, look up.
Can I not do anything about that?
All right, let's just get back out here.
Distribution center, give me that key.
Get out of the way.
What is this?
Did I save this?
The office, dear friend at the office,
I'm very happy to be live here on my vacation.
Please don't look for me.
Desk 132B.
He doesn't come down here, does he?
Does he come in here?
Shit.
Distribution.
All right, I made it.
Look at the knives.
Letter openers.
Hey, excuse me.
Okay, unbox pens, call mom, smile.
All right, what is it?
Up here?
There?
1598.
There's only two?
How do they work?
I'm not even holding it right.
Okay, why do you have like three microwaves up here?
What is it?
1598.
Seems a bit ominous.
Cybernetics.
Good luck.
You and then I have to go to cybernetics.
Oh, god damn it.
What did I hit?
The fucking wall.
Cybernetics.
Watch out, okay?
I'm taking a break.
I need to locate caffeinated beverage.
Hello.
I'm trying to put the head on you,
like in Skyrim and then steal from me, right?
That scared me.
Sorry.
All right, cybernetics.
Let's go.
Well, actually, hold on.
What's in here?
Any more letter openers in here?
That I need to be made aware of?
What key is that?
Just locked.
Got a phone in here though.
No, same 1598.
Come on, I need some more.
Any more letters?
Not that I can see.
Let's just go to cybernetics.
All right, here we go.
Can I not open this door?
Uh, I guess we're going over here.
Well, found them.
How many knives am I going to need?
Nice.
Okay, well, I kind of need all these.
Wait.
Oh, shut up.
All right, so yeah, you can throw the knives.
The knives actually have weight to them when they move.
Cool.
Let me try.
Cybernetics.
Let's make our way over there, what do you say?
Watch out.
This is one, right?
Give me that key card.
You got scissors.
Can I throw the scissors at somebody?
I have to be able to, right?
Like fucking gouge somebody's eyes out.
I thought that was the actual wall and it scared the fuck out of me.
I can't take these.
I'm just going to walk around with them.
Anything outside?
No, just keep going.
I hear somebody moving around.
There we go, okay.
There is somebody in here.
One of those bad guys.
Uh,
uh,
can I throw this at him and hit him in the face and knock him out?
All right, I'm going back to the first area.
I'm so confused right now.
Hold on.
This is the first area, isn't it?
I made it back to the first place.
What the hell happened?
Did I?
Did I do it?
What am I going?
Okay, I'm still going.
Okay, there are more knives here.
I gotta try to throw a knife at somebody, right?
I gotta hit this guy tonight.
What's that?
There's a wall here.
Back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up.
There's a wall right there.
What the fuck is going on down there?
Wait for him.
Hey, thanks buddy.
I owe you one.
No, turn the lights off.
Oh, you hit me right in the face.
That was a chimpanzee.
Should have used knives more often.
Yeah, how's the coal?
Splinter cell.
How was your latest session?
I was pretty sick.
Not as bad?
No, I must have acid sweated through the whole thing.
Angle the camera down.
What's it when I go like this and I'm like sneaking down?
If I angle the camera down, then you won't be able to see me when I'm like back here
or like over here or moving around here.
All right, I'm gonna give it another tap.
We're gonna go one more time and then I gotta take a break.
This is fucking fun though.
What a blast.
Virtual reality.
Turn the webcam sideways.
I can't like mount it.
All right, let's do it again.
One more time.
Let's see if I can get to at least the end of this little section here.
There's so much hair is bunching up and it's being ripped out.
Look at this.
Okay, remember those infomercials where it was the vacuum that cut your hair?
If I pull this up, it's all coming out.
Hey, how's everybody doing?
How are you?
Yeah, it's been rough, but it's all right.
I'm doing all right.
I'm doing good.
How are you doing?
How's everything going?
How are the kids?
Yeah, I'm like the guy that screens the people under the bridge now.
You know, that's what I do.
It's been real, you know, just get the job done.
Ow.
I'm gonna have to take a hose to this.
My poor hair was already struggling.
It's just gonna come out.
All right, let me get like a little sip of this, uh, just drink
and we'll try it one more time.
He thinks he's streaming.
So I see that there have been barely any drop frames in about
four hours.
So that's, that's a good sign.
He's been a patient.
Thinks he's in a stream in VR.
I need to get like a beanie or a goddamn haircut would do too.
All right, let's get back in.
I'll do one more death or one more attempt.
So tomorrow there's more.
I gotta think of a situation to untangle this fucking cord.
I'm gonna have to figure out a solution.
Is this left or right?
Okay, this one is left.
I expect you to die.
Well, I expect you to die.
It's not, it's the wrong game.
What's happening here?
Oh, right.
One, two, don't touch that one.
So the object, I might have it all the way back.
No, I have to be like a checkpoint or something, right?
No, this is perfect.
All right, I'm in a good spot.
I have, let's knife this motherfucker.
I'm not even gonna be scared about this.
Do you think I'm scared?
What are you gonna do about that one?
He's just like pissing over here.
No, that doesn't count.
That didn't count.
He was just letting it ride over here.
Okay, we're back in.
Do it again.
I gotta hit him right in the face.
Right in the face.
Do it again.
I'll do another, I'll throw a second one.
Please wait, please wait.
Give me that knife back.
What?
Oh.
Okay.
I'm making it through.
I didn't get fucking caught here.
Where's the wall?
Make sure I'm not touching a fucking wall.
Why did I just kill that?
Why did I do that to that guy?
This one's gotta count.
I'm freezing.
No, why did I do that?
He could have talked.
Okay, he could have talked.
One, five, nine, eight.
No, not yet.
That's two, I need two little two.
Work hard, get one access.
Everybody have like a key card over here?
Can I get in that?
No, I can't get in the production thing.
Stop that.
Maybe go back up?
Let me just check some desks.
If you go in here.
I guess I'm gonna go back up.
Was I back here yet?
I don't think I was back here yet.
Somebody's desk?
Anybody got level two in here?
Oh, that's where you find the money.
Beautiful.
Level two.
I'm gonna go for like a bouncing shot here.
Just like that.
All right, back down.
Where is it? Over here, right?
I'll get that later.
Level two.
Is there a wall?
Yeah, there is.
Be careful.
All right.
Gotta be prepared for this shit.
I'm almost out of this.
You can see me through the portal.
Fuck you!
Oh no, he's alive?
That it?
I don't mind if I do.
That was just fucking mean.
Hey!
Don't kill them.
Just put them up.
I'm gonna need these.
I'm gonna need these later.
Meeting room bull.
Something going on?
Is something happening here?
Hang in there.
Well, that sure is them.
We may need to move out of the way.
All right, so what we got?
We went through the front door.
Oh, come on!
I was trying to be so careful, too.
Where's the knives?
I just put them on.
It feels like a good day for a good day.
Should I go on over?
No, I don't.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I'm gonna hit that one over there
a shitload of times.
I need like a better solution to that.
I'm gonna have to move my lighthouses, I think.
Because I'm gonna fucking break that thing.
Okay, here we go.
Electricity, electricity, electricity.
What's in here?
Uh, huh.
Well, shit.
Hmm.
Maybe I have to go down this.
Should I go down here?
I'm just gonna go down here.
Fuck it.
Two, three, thirty.
The phone's ringing.
Really?
In the dog dog.
In the doggy door.
I made it in the doggy door, but.
Yeah, hello?
I admit it.
I knew this would happen.
I mean, you're holding a very valuable stolen prototype.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, don't get mad, okay?
I needed you to understand how bad things were here.
I need your help to find out what's going on.
Get a level three access card,
take the elevator, and find someone called April.
Her desk is in the production department.
Now, if you help me, I promise to help you escape.
Hank, you swear it.
Company to the pat-down station in the lobby.
Company will probably become a guest key in the lobby, whatever.
All right, so I gotta get a level three card,
and then I gotta go level fucking three,
and I gotta go level three, get a level three card,
and then get out of here.
Go and get out.
Sounds not easy enough,
but probably simple enough where it'll happen eventually.
What's over here?
It's locked.
That's it.
Okay, there's the elevator right there.
I need a level three card.
I gotta go in there.
What am I fucking running into?
There's a gun.
How do I use this?
Can I use this thing?
Can I use this?
All right, I got the card.
Let's go to the...
Let's get out of here.
Level three.
Let's go.
I did it.
I don't...
I only need the level three card.
It does everything the lower ones already do.
All right, let's go.
You've been in for too long.
No, no, I'm all right.
I'm going back in.
I'll be just fine.
Don't worry about me.
I'm gonna go back in.
Jeremy, you haven't shown up to work.
I'm going back in.
Jeremy, your school called.
That's all right.
I'm just gonna go back in for like another five minutes.
Jeremy, you haven't eaten in fucking two days.
That's all right.
I'm just gonna go back in.
Hey.
No number?
None of his company.
And he knows to work anywhere other than...
Oh, that hurt my head.
Can I use this?
Do I need to...
That way.
No.
8008.
Hello, you're listening.
I am very busy with my tax.
Backspot is broken.
Use John Smith's machine instead.
What the fuck is the number?
8008.
No, 8000.
I don't like this office.
I'm not coming into work tomorrow.
John Smith's office.
Let me in.
Map of pre-production department.
John Smith fax room.
Elevated lobby.
Mess hall production department.
Auxiliary.
John's.
Hello?
There's a wall.
Where's the wall?
Excuse me.
I need that back.
Uh-oh.
What?
Hey, what?
Who shot?
Is everybody behind me?
Who's behind me?
All right.
I think it's time to take a break.
Oh.
I'm having too much fun, but I gotta like...
I gotta like fucking rest my eyes.
Rage quit?
No, no.
I'll probably start with this tomorrow.
There's so many VR games though.
Oh, there's so many VR games that I have to play.
So we're gonna be tomorrow.
I'll see you guys tomorrow with more VR.
So we're gonna go three days in a row.
Just because I'm 1-0.
I mentioned like...
You can't even take me seriously with this like fucking toupee.
Oh my god.
Let's get a real talk going here, guys.
It's like this is a toupee they used to wear back in like the fucking...
It's 1800.
I gotta go get like food and just relax for a little bit.
It's like a couple hours.
I can only stay inside these things for like four to five hours
before like I gotta get away from it.
So tomorrow we're gonna pick up again.
We're gonna do more VR tomorrow.
So I will see you guys tomorrow
around three to four p.m. Pacific.
Get the camera out of here.
I doubt I could even go that long.
It really depends on the day.
Sometimes it's like one hour is enough for me to have to stop.
Sometimes like four to five.
It's still in the game.
Yeah, it saves it, right?
Don't have to do anything in particular to save the game.
That was a blast.
I'm very satisfied.
Kiwo can stream VR for like 13 hours straight.
Oh my god.
How?
How is it possible?
13 hours in the helmet?
Yeah, first impressions of Vibe is absolutely worth the money.
It was a blast.
I just I need to like take a few hours after that
and just kind of get my eyes off of it.
But tomorrow we're gonna pick up again.
I'll see you tomorrow.
More VR.
I'm gonna get some more games.
I'm gonna get some Beat Saber stuff.
But I'm tapped out for now.
By the moving sea.
This Discord link.
This coal miner link.
That's so stupid.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We got some bits to go through.
I'm gonna try a different...
I might move the lighthouses
because I don't want to break these things.
And I hit the lighthouse on the back portion of the room twice.
So see you tomorrow.
Let's get the outro on here.
Let's take that off.
Thank you for joining me.
What do you say we go down here?
Move as far as I can to the corner.
Yeah, the only problem is I have a big L-shaped desk.
And the desk is...
It kind of takes up a large portion of the back and left wall.
So trying to get the lighthouses...
I mean the room is big enough to do it.
And obviously I was taking at least
what?
Two or three steps in any given direction without hitting a wall.
Why do my knees hurt?
I have like red raw knees.
What?
Why?
Oh, it's from crawling around.
All right, so let's start a few...
Let's see, about four and a half hours ago.
We had a ton of gifted subs that came from Guild Hero.
I'm not sure if you still hear Guild Hero, but thank you.
There's like at least 25 to 30 gifted subs here.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah, I laid...
I did lie on the ground.
But thank you so much Guild Hero.
Let's start back here.
We had...
Hey Alec, thanks for the one dollar.
I got the starry night night sky shirt and it's epic.
Yeah, it's a great shirt.
I highly recommend it.
If you don't know what I'm talking about,
if you just have a teespring store,
a couple of shirts are there.
If you feel like buying them, cool.
They're very, very well made.
They're very...
The designs are very good.
It is available.
Wow, we just went to zero.
That was like a full-on zero.
Damn, okay.
Well, refresh, I guess.
That was weird.
But yeah, the shirts are available.
They're really cool.
I highly recommend them.
Thank you, sad Vega, for the one dollar.
So I did the idiot remark at Taco Bell while ordering food.
I said, I'll have a cheese Gordita Crunch, idiot.
They looked at me for a second in shock.
Then I repeated it and the manager came
and told me to apologize and leave or he'd call the police.
I apologized profusely and blamed you,
saying you were encouraging people to do it.
He looked at me and said,
if he told you to jump off a bridge, would you?
And I said, yes.
Here's the thing though.
I explicitly told everybody not to do that.
Because it was incredibly rude
and it wasn't a nice thing to do.
Sorry to hear that you got reprimanded at Taco Bell
for being what any normal person would see as being a dick.
But thank you for the one dollar.
Raise and rise, thanks for the three bucks.
Divus, thanks for the two bucks.
Dork Cube, thanks for the one dollar.
My dad always said, measure twice, cut once.
But this stream proved that sometimes,
even when you measure 10 times,
you may still slice your finger off.
I'm getting a feel for the room too.
Because remember, this is the first time
I've ever experienced VR, standing up with a Vive.
My only real experience was PSVR
and I had to stand in the same spot.
So you guys just, you guys watched live
my first real ever like room VR experience.
So you kind of have to get used to it.
Do I still have PSVR?
I do not.
I actually gave it to a friend.
So I no longer have access to it.
But now I have a Vive.
So there's really no reason I don't think I have it.
There are a few PSVR exclusives that look interesting.
But I have a Vive.
So anytime I want to do VR, I'm just going to use that.
But thank you, Dork Cube.
Good advice.
Superintendent Chalmers, thanks for the one dollar.
Andy say, hey, Jeremy, can you do a stream
where you just watch Willem Dafoe
talk about himself for 30 minutes?
Always eclipses the movie itself.
Willem Dafoe breaks down his most iconic character
for 35 minutes.
Well, no, 35 minutes.
I would watch that on your own time.
That's probably great.
He's one of the greatest actors we've ever seen.
But thank you, Superintendent Chalmers.
Thank you, Deviant XS for the one dollar.
Might be a good idea to put some straps on, bro.
Smashly, thanks for the four community subs earlier.
Tingy, thanks for the one dollar.
You had us in the first half of the most fun thing
you've ever done until you mentioned
riding roller coasters.
Everyone knows you must be this tall to ride.
You know that you could be like 48 inches tall
and still qualify for like the Superman ride of steel.
You know that, right?
So even if I was like four foot six,
I would still qualify for the Superman ride.
That's not true.
What are you talking about?
Five goddamn eight, five nine with heels on.
Thank you, trust no one for the three bucks.
Hello, Jeremy.
It's me again.
Last time we met, I was kind of obliged
to follow the same road as I had before.
That's all because of you.
Let's see where this road leads us this time.
Let's see where this road leads us.
This is 11 scariest germs caught by drones.
What the fuck is this?
Hold on.
I got to play it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me see.
Is Willem Dafoe's video still playing?
Oh, I see what's going on.
Okay, I have to get the HTC Vive.
I'm going to go to my regular speakers.
Okay, there we go.
Now this should be playing, right?
Shit, why can I not hear this?
Yeah, the Vive kind of takes over your whole setup.
It takes over your mic, takes over your headphones.
Let me just put this back to get that better.
There we go.
Okay, now I can hear this.
All right, we're going to put this on.
Let's do a browser capture here.
Let's just watch this.
Because I am just chilling right now.
Just trying to relax out of the VR.
Let's watch a video.
This is the 11 scariest drones.
Let's go.
11 scariest things caught by drones.
Watch it.
I'm not going to watch that.
This is going to turn into the same joke again.
Yeah, this is the dirtiest hit.
This is a great Buzzfeed video.
Is that a demonic?
Oh, come on.
How is that a drone?
Kid was testing his new drone in the forest.
He's given a terrifying man these.
That's not even me.
Loch Ness is famous for its myth of what it smells like.
I got to just climb in the fucking window
and just start using the computer.
The next drone footage is too gruesome.
While in the air, the whole balloon crew
would be eaten alive by this thing.
How did you, the crop, you, the frame by frame,
crop that shit up?
That was wonderful.
Jeremy, please forgive me if I got you upset
by using your image in such unpleasant ways.
I didn't mean it.
No, that's fine.
This got me.
Probably.
Hey, look.
I wonder what's going to happen in like a week.
News bloopers.
Uh, and no, I'm not going to watch that video.
So not going to watch the best 2017 news bloopers.
See you in a week or two when we watch another one of these.
I'm not, well, I'm not going to watch news bloopers.
The cycle continues.
That was fucking hilarious.
That was great.
Thank you for that.
That was really, really, really fucking funny.
Thank you, trust no one.
From $3 and that video.
Jess, you got it.
Thanks for the $1.
You look like a chimney sweep.
I gotta go like wash my face.
I gotta get in the shower and like condition my hair.
Thank you super seal for the $2.50.
Drink orange juice after brushing your teeth on stream or scared.
That's gonna ruin orange juice for me.
I don't put alcohol in my orange juice
and I don't brush my teeth and drink orange juice
because it ruins it.
I have something to look up how to clean the inside of your Vive visor
because it is disgusting.
If somebody was here and they had a cotton swab or something
or like a Q-tip and you just went,
you dragged across the front of that glass in there,
you would have enough to probably make
a whole nother like species of fucking mutants.
It's filthy in there.
But thank you super seal.
Thank you again.
Frodeon weapon gave $50 early.
Thank you so much again.
Big money from Frodeon.
Timmy Tim Tim, thanks for the $1.
They say crazy person.
Crazy person.
No, this is just somebody playing VR.
Very okay.
If I didn't have the VR helmet or the helmet hair,
I need a haircut.
Look at that fucking helmet bedhead hair.
No, that's somebody just playing VR.
But thank you Timmy Tim Tim.
Guild here again.
Huge amount of community subs.
Renix, thanks for the $5.
After you download mod installer,
you can download songs in game.
Okay, cool.
I'll get that set up before we stream tomorrow.
Thank you Gibbler for the three bucks.
Jerma, I didn't know that you were a coal miner.
That's the one we just looked at.
It's fucking wild.
Thank you so much, Gibbler.
Mentosium, thanks for the four dollars and 20 cents.
Hey Jerma, got you featured on the Yogscast Jingle Jam.
I was wondering if you've seen harder,
better, faster Jerma on YouTube.
I think you'll enjoy it.
I think I do remember the Yogscast thing.
It was green screen footage, right?
It was good shit.
I'm here.
I'm right here.
You don't have to beep.
I'm here.
Better, faster Jerma, I think.
Did we watch that like last week or something?
The name is familiar.
I'm not sure if maybe we have.
No, me.
I vaguely remember.
I don't think we did.
Better, faster, hold on.
What's it called?
Better, faster, harder, better, faster Jerma.
Let me take a look and see.
Oh, it's a green screen video.
Okay, I'm going to save this.
And I know I've said this a bunch of times,
but the green screen encore stream
is actually going to happen here
probably next week or the week after.
It's actually going to happen.
I've talked about it for the last three and a half weeks
and it's time to actually compile them
and do another encore green screen night.
So in maybe two weeks,
I'm actually going to talk to the mods about it.
We'll figure it out again.
But this one is not another submissions thing
as much as it is like a couple hours of ones
that have come out since.
So it's not going to be another.
All right, here's a ton of submissions here.
We're going to watch like 500 videos.
I'd like to keep it a little.
Maybe we'll do it at the end of one stream in particular.
Might be fun to do.
It's like Christmas morning.
My hair, if I grab the front of my hair
and if I pulled even with like a quarter of a pound of pressure,
the whole tuft is going to come out.
I'm going to have to do like a treatment to my head.
We'll watch that.
I will make sure it's saved a book market
because green screen stuff I'd like to watch
in a better setting where we're all ready for it.
But thank you so much, Mentosium.
We will see it soon.
Thank you, Freudian Weapon for the four dollars.
Random question, but I'm making a video game themed workout playlist.
Any actiony game OSTs you could recommend.
I love the VR stuff.
Can't wait to see the upcoming craziness.
Have a good night.
Uh, a video game theme, but any actiony game OSTs?
I mean, the easy one is probably Hotline.
Somebody already said it.
Hotline Miami is really, you know, will really pump you up.
Both OSTs.
I would just get them both.
Any other OSTs?
That's what I would say those first.
Doom.
Doom is more, man, maybe.
Just go get the whole Smash Brothers.
Go get the entire Smash Brothers OST.
But yeah, probably I would say Hotline Miami.
Flammable Cowl, thanks for the five dollars.
I recently started playing Chrono Trigger after you mentioned it and enjoyed it.
I didn't have the privilege of growing up in the boomer generation and was wondering
what's an old underrated game that you recommend.
Much love, The Neverhood.
I'll say that every single time.
Mario RPG, Chrono Trigger, The Neverhood.
Um, some of the other old ones.
That's probably the top three.
It's really hard to get a hold of The Neverhood, though.
Earthworm Jims.
Earthworm Jims, I don't know if I...
I'm not so sure Earthworm Jims still holds up.
It's been a long time since I played it, but I remember trying to play it again
within the last five or so years.
And it was, it was like, I wasn't really enjoying it.
The soundtrack for Earthworm Jim is amazing.
But The Neverhood is, I just love that game.
Add Desert Bus VR to the games to play tomorrow.
Well, I want to go through the most requested ones first.
Because stuff like Blade and Source, ReBeat Saber, Budget Cuts,
uh, like Super Hot VR.
There's a couple of like the...
There's at least like five that people really, really wanted to see
and that I was really wanting to play.
So we'll do some other weird random ones after we go through like the top ones.
Gorn, yeah, Gorn's another one.
Yeah, there's so many to play that I don't want to really overwhelm myself
because here's what's going to happen, right?
So when we're doing these VR streams,
I'd like to only do like a few of them each night,
maybe like two or three of them each night
because I want to get the whole experience from these games.
I don't want to just open like Budget Cuts and play it for 20 minutes
and be like, all right, what's the next one?
I got like 15 of these.
It's not like the PlayStation 2 streams or the Dreamcast stuff,
or I want to give each one at least like a couple hours
or like one, at least one to two hours.
So I can get the whole experience out of them.
And I'm not exactly sure how long something like Budget Cuts is.
But it feels like I'm getting at least enough of a package there
where I've had enough fun where I'm ready to do something else.
But we'll see.
I will have another list of about three or four,
maybe three or so tomorrow.
But thank you, Flammable Cow.
Thank you, Buster Boy, for the three bucks.
How can I gift you Steam games?
There's a game called Jet Island that is an amazing VR game
that I'd like you to play.
You don't have to do any gifting or anything like that.
If you have a recommendation for a game,
I have a Discord.
If you want to go to the Discord,
there's a recommended channel.
You can go there and just put anything
that you think you'd like to see on stream.
It's not a discussion channel.
It's just a place to put recommendations.
And I look at it all the time.
I look at the recommended channel at least once a week
and I kind of scroll up and see what's been said.
And if I want to do something and I can, you know,
pinpoint things that I'd like to do.
So yeah, recommend a channel in the Discord
if you have anything you'd like me to check out.
But thank you, Buster Boy, for the three bucks.
Hey, something or other and there's no music, is there?
No, get back here.
Something or other, thanks for the one dollar.
Agent Smith voice.
You can't escape the Matrix, Mr. Elbertson.
I'll get out.
Hey, for real though, thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents.
Did you eat your Rice Krispies this morning?
Did I eat my Rice Krispies?
It's the only cereal that talks to you
and that makes for a great company in the morning.
How do you know we don't just fucking run?
I don't know what that is.
I don't know if I want to play that.
But thank you for the two dollars and 50 cents.
Because, you know, living one life sucks enough.
Going through the hardships of one life is bad enough,
but to do it again,
I read this pamphlet at my doctor's office one time.
There it is.
You really do need context.
There's no context at the audio.
It's just, it makes no sense.
It'll make perfect sense if you watch it.
Thank you for real though.
Thank you, Tingy, for the one dollar in my last bit,
so I might as well use them before it goes to two fifty.
Just want to say that I love this community and you,
Jerma.
You guys make each stream a great experience.
Thank you so much, Tingy.
Yeah, the two fifty minimum is just,
it's just gonna happen here probably tomorrow.
I will probably continue to read under two fifty
for at least maybe like one or two more streams
after the change.
Just because there's no way with the amount of people
that are here that everybody will know.
You know what I'm saying?
It's changing tomorrow,
but I'm gonna continue to read under two fifty
for at least another two or three streams.
Because, I mean, it's hard to keep everybody
aware of what's going on.
But thank you for the one dollar.
It's a pleasure to have as many great people
here as there are.
So thank you.
Put it in the stream title.
Maybe, I don't know if I want to like
blow it up the stream title though.
It already has like the shirts thing there.
And I don't want to be like one of those,
exclamation point shirts,
exclamation point stream changes,
exclamation point prime,
exclamation point.
Once you start adding exclamation points,
they just keep going.
Everyone knows about the shirts though.
It's not necessarily true,
but thank you Tingy.
Thank you Radja Sil for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma, I've been standing outside your window
trying to get your attention for about two hours.
But you're not noticing me.
I've been revving up my engine
and honking my horn and everything.
Well, you did get my attention.
I didn't know it was you.
But thank you for the one dollar.
Thank you Clueless Sniper for the one dollar.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
And finally here we had Adala from Multitrip.
I don't know if it's on the list,
but you should definitely play hot dogs,
horseshoes, and hand grenades.
It's basically like that first game you played,
but with guns and tons of game modes.
Absolutely.
I am 100% on board
with any and all of these really,
really interesting VR games.
Because I am, it's, you know, it's great.
It's like, okay.
So if you, I'm like two and a half,
three years late to this shit.
There's such a huge compiling of awesome VR games.
This has to be what it feels like.
If you're, if you're like,
let's say like 11, 12, 13 years old right now,
you grow up, you know, you're 13,
you turn 14, 50, get your steam account.
When you, you've got like,
think of all the shit that like a 15, 16 year old
that gets their hand on steam for the first time.
This backlog of a decade of incredible experiences
that they have.
Wow. That's how I feel right now.
I feel like I'm 12.
I just made my steam account.
And Rajasil, if you're going to drive by,
at least like make it, must know it's you.
But I feel like I'm 12.
And I just made my first ever steam account.
And like The Witcher 3.
Holy shit.
I've never, what's that one?
What, there's three of these?
I can play one, two, and three.
I don't even know what this is.
What's this game?
The Team Fortress?
What the fuck is that thing?
I've never even been inside this game once.
That's how I feel right now with VR.
By the way, I've never played through
any of The Witcher games.
I'm just pretending to think they're cool.
So people will think I'm, you know,
they can pretend to think I'm cool.
That's the only reason why I said that.
I'm just pretending to know what they are.
You are not cool.
It has a horse.
And at the very end here, we got double D,
doubled 11 for the $2 here.
Hey, are you also going to do VR chat with Kiwo?
Yes.
But that's going to have to be at a different time.
Because I was told, I was under the impression,
I think that Kiwo is not available.
I think that Kiwo is doing something.
She's gone or not around or something.
I was going to get the VR chat tutorial
from Kiwo as a stream.
That is not going to be part of this,
you know, two or three streams in a row of VR.
That's going to be, I just have it.
And when we can, because maybe she's, she's EU, right?
So that's going to be, that's going to be a little
fucky trying to get that to work.
Because I am like almost eight to 10 hours behind her.
So we'll figure it out.
But I look forward to the VR tutorial.
Streams like 12 hours a day.
God, I wish I had the energy.
Like I put like laser beams into my eyes for four hours
and I have to like go lie down.
And they all say I have a 200 word essay due
and I'm here watching Jerma.
What am I doing?
You added 50 words.
Hey Buster Boy, thanks for the $1 at the very end.
I got my Oculus Rift a month ago
and I know exactly what you're saying.
Yeah, it's great.
I have like a year and a half worth
of experiences that I haven't done.
So it feels great.
And let's run the credits.
That's the end of the bits.
I will see you fine group of people tomorrow.
Tomorrow is the day for more VR.
He's pretending that that joke wasn't made last stream.
Really short post stream today.
Yeah, I got to figure it's because of VR.
Because I didn't have the stream labs wasn't really on.
I can't really see anything anyways.
But no, it's all good.
It's good shit.
Are you going to have OVR drop working next time?
Do you need any help to get it attached to your hand?
I might.
I didn't really do a proper tutorial.
So I did get the chat to be on the screen.
But I want to get it like in that position.
But here's the weird part though, right?
So getting the chat on your hand.
Wouldn't that conflict with doing actions in the game?
So let's say I was in budget cuts, right?
How do I make it so I because I have the gun on my hand.
And I lift up my hand.
There's the gun.
How is the chat just always going to be on the hand?
Or do I have to do like a certain I have to rotate my hand to see it.
Okay.
Yeah, I plan on watching a couple of tutorials.
But if I'm still having trouble, then I'll be in the discord.
You bet your ass tomorrow at like 2 30.
I'll be in the discord like, look, I tried it and I don't understand how it worked.
But I'm going to give it a try.
Hey, pigeon.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Just got my interviews with mods and newbie done.
And I'm ready to start banging out that essay.
Sort of.
I need to compile that information into sections.
Make sure you use the quote where I said, eat your vegetables.
Eat plenty of high quality proteins like salmon and tuna fish.
And if you're going to work out, make sure you give yourself enough rest.
You know, if you work out, you lift and you do bicep curls.
Don't do bicep curls for like at least like three, four days.
Let your body recover.
Get that high quality protein.
And that's how you do good working out.
For, wait, that was, okay, that was, you could still use that quote anyways.
Just use a section of that and use it as a quote.
What are the plans on the encore green screen night?
We just were talking about it.
We were talking about how it's probably going to happen in a couple of weeks.
Said that really fast.
Too fast.
It could slow down.
Just eat french fries only and only french fries and you'll be fine.
That is a very bad advice.
Hey, that's me.
Hey, Double D, thanks for the one dollar.
It's a YouTube link.
Let's see what it is.
One bit of, one bit of German wisdom.
That's what we're going to.
One bit of wisdom.
It's a lot.
It's a lot of value.
That's pretty good wisdom.
You know, don't.
Be careful.
You're not going to get out.
All right, guys.
I will see you tomorrow with more VR.
I'm going to clean up.
I'm going to clean my shit up.
There's shit all over the place.
I've got to clean it up.
And the VR helmet needs a little bit of TLC here.
I'm going to take a shower.
See you tomorrow.
Have a great rest of your night.
Take care.
And ta ta.