Hello. How are you? How are you doing? How are things? You good? What's up? I changed my Twitch
server. Let's see if that fixes the problem. Streaming on a different server. If you're not
here last night, every like five minutes I would drop like a few hundred frames for no reason. It
seemed to happen at the same exact interval. Apparently I have negative latency to your stream.
I'm seeing it before you stream it. That's weird. Uh, some people were saying that it might have
been a Twitch problem. Maybe the server I was connecting to. So I changed servers. Let's see
if it fixes it. If not, then I, unfortunately, don't know what to do about it because my internet
seems to be perfect. Today, I'm gonna, I'm gonna be very calm today. I'm going to relax. I'm going
to, I'm going to be in Zen mode. I'm not going to get angry today. I'm going to very desperately
try to stay focused and my voice will not go over a certain amount of DB level. Okay. It's going to
be collected. I'm going to just relax and enjoy the world of Elden Ring because that's all I do
now. I'm literally an Elden Ring streamer. I don't do anything else. Uh, but yeah, I'm looking
forward to it. It'd be a good time as always. Hey, Jerma the Bod for the what? The Bod for
that last boss fight got deleted. Did it? No, it didn't. Don't forget about Smite Saturdays.
Did you smoke before this? No. I would never play Elden Ring inebriated. Yeah, that's not going to
happen. You understand how impossible that would be? You're asking me to do an impossible task.
You can't, like that's like handing somebody that's like just, just zonked out of their mind
of Rubik's Cube. Then you have one minute to solve this. Huh? How's this it? It's scabbed over. It
looks pretty bad. Whatever. I'm literally doing that right now. It's not that bad. I would be
completely de-stressed, but that would be an unwatchable stream because I would walk into
boss encounters and die in five seconds and I wouldn't even care. I'd be like, Oh man,
that's what he does. Oh, okay. And that would happen for two or three straight hours. Like
I wouldn't even attack the boss. So many people like claim that they would stay here and watch
that kind of shit. But after an hour or two of doing that, I wouldn't attack the boss.
You just, you would go do something else. You'd find something else to do. You just would.
That would be the best stream. It would not. It would be an actual improvement. Oh, get out of
here. Okay. Uh, you guys ready? It's a couple of things. I, I have marked some things on the map
that I want to do. A few of them in particular. I want to continue this quest line for Ranny.
Maybe please just do one designated song stream with me strong. All right. I will, I'm, it might
be fun to do a, a me strong stream in Elden ring and I would just be role playing. You guys are
not going to want to watch it. It's going to be awful. No one's going to do it. No one's going
to want to watch that stream. I'm telling you, there's going to be threads on Reddit about this
about like, I mean, like that was like, not that funny. It was like kind of fucking like
irresponsible and annoying of him. Um, like that was the worst stream 2022 without a doubt. Like
it was, that was just boring and like, not funny. You guys are not going to like this stream. I'm
just, I want to be, I want to be clipped completely sober of sound mind and sound body. They will be
people that they're going to be a lot of people that are going to think that's the worst frame
of the year. Okay. I just want to make sure I'm clear on that. So let's just, I'm going to,
I'm going to make it so you can't nominate it. It's grayed out. Okay. You guys ready? I'm ready.
Let's get into it. Can you guys hear it? You can't. No, you can't. Make sure I've got my fan
going already. And even been five minutes. I'm getting that fan going layer blowing on me.
That cannot be the way that is though. So use me. I've got like red circles under my eyes. Why?
What does that mean? Actually, nothing sits in lighting the way the lighting is in the room.
Yeah, it's just weird lighting. All right. I gotta move this out of the way. So last thing we did,
by the way, this is the most face cams per capita you've ever had.
This is the most face cams you've ever had like in a row. So what? It's something I don't normally
do. Okay. I want to show you some stuff. First of all, let me show you some things. I have marked
on the map specifically where we are going to go. We're going to go here. I was told by somebody
in chat that this is a place that I would be very interested in. So I marked it. I also wanted to
make sure that I checked, got this map fragment. I also wanted to check out this place because it
looked kind of cool, like a church or something, right? I also wanted to go here. This looked like
an interesting boulder of some sort. And I don't know what this spiky stuff is, but this looks like
an interesting boulder to me. Zip will go away in like a week. Don't worry. And then I want to
continue the quest line. So at the end of that Redan fight, the stars all fell. And I was like,
oh, falling stars, falling stars. And I had to go find them. So I'm going to go look over here
because from the lore perspective, it sounded like it may have been somewhere
around this vicinity, if I were to take a guess. So we're going to check this out here.
Permanent Zip. South of the Mistwood. That's what I was thinking too. I was thinking like somewhere
in this vicinity here. Because this looks like an area it could fall. Nice cringe lore. That's like
one of the coolest parts of all the Dark Souls games is like the lore. Has anybody ever looked
at you like that before in your life? I used to get that all the time. I used to get that all of
the time. Like it'd be like, something, I'm saying something, saying something. That's equal parts
stop and equal parts. What are you doing? What are you saying? Like, yeah, me too.
That happened to me too. Yeah. Microwave rant. I need to start to put a tally on how many times
that happens to me. It's very distinctive. It's not a book. It's not. Nope. It's not. It's,
it's very distinct. It's, it's equally parts confused and upset and kind of like what?
All right. Let's go. We're going to check section one, which is this part right here. I'm going to
go in order. I heard this is something I'd be interested in. That's the face that I make almost
all the time when watching you. You're wicked funny. Okay. So the, how do I get up there though?
I was told I'd be very interested in this space here. Okay. I don't think I can get up here this
way. All right. There's like some, there's some cringe rocks in the way. How am I going to, from
this way? How do I get on this road? This is all, this is the bridge. Okay. So how,
I'm going to have to go from here, aren't I? I don't think I can get up there from here.
Yeah. I'll go from here or I think I have to go backwards from here. I don't know. Or maybe
forwards from here. Let's try forwards from here. Doesn't know how to read a map. You look like
some, I don't, I know. I know. I look like everybody you've ever seen in your life.
So I need to go this way. Not that way over here. Look like my grandma. That would actually be kind
of funny if I really did look like your grandmother. This is just an item here. Fire arrows. Cool.
Okay. Let's keep going. I got to follow the, just the path. Yeah. I didn't get a bunch of these
things. Hey, can you please kiss the camera? You know how many times I've done that? There's
somebody in here. You know how many times I've kissed the camera and regretted it immediately
after doing it. Who's this guy? War Master Shaq.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Battle arts.
Okay. This guy sells battle arts? Ah, okay. Very cool. Well, I don't think I really need any of
these or want any of these in this playthrough because I'm a magic magician person. So pretty
cool though. What level am I? 60. Oh, knowledge of the arts.
All right. See you later. Have fun. Good luck with you. It's the world's wacky out there.
Just be careful. That's cool though. I don't need any of that, but that's cool to know that
that's what that is. We're going to continue. I want to go that way. I had a dream last night
that you did an in-person event. You were there. You did an in-person event. You did an IRL like
tier list, like live show. What? It's like kind of fun. What are you talking about?
Ooh, this is a new space. All right. What's, what's here? There's probably something here
that I didn't get. Jort sword. Oh, come on. I don't want to fight anybody. I just want to
like take all the stuff in your camp. I don't want to fight you for it. I don't want to fight
you for any of this stuff. I just want it. I met you while lucid dreaming. We need the guy with
the green hat on. What the fuck, dude? What? We both were flying next to each other and I looked
over and you gave me the thumbs up and like, and I had the big airplane goggles on, like the big,
like the red Baron goggles on. That was so much fun. It sucks though, when I fucking,
like I stopped flapping my wings and I like froze in midplace and did a big cartoon gulp and fell.
You laughed at that, which is kind of fucking, that's kind of annoying,
but you know, it was still cool to see you though. I had a dream that you were over mine.
You're losing so many viewers. Um, I don't, I don't hear a thing. I don't think I'm,
I don't think we're losing viewers. I think we're getting to the stage where a lot of people don't
want to see because a lot of people aren't necessarily grinding out this game. So the
further we go in Elden Ring, the further that people might not be and they might not want to see.
So that's the phenomenon you're experiencing here and that's cope.
That's streamer cope, but it's true. It's true. See, one person says that. You know how I know
that. Do you know why I know that's true? Because the first three or four days of Elden Ring,
I was watching tons of streamers. Oh my God, how'd they do with that guy? I have avoided every
single person's broadcast the last like four days. I've not looked at anybody, no one. So I mean that
ego kind of, kind of the way it is. All right, so I got to cross this bridge, but not yet.
And plus, I don't, not every stream has to have
20,000 people on it. I get it, man. I get it. These guys have so much health. He's gonna break
down because he's lost it. But I mean, I've only been live for fucking like 15 minutes. I don't,
I don't pay attention to that kind of stuff that much. Should I kill this thing? It has so much
health. Wait, how come this one doesn't have that much health? These vary in how much health they have.
Okay, so wait a minute. That one that was on the rooftop, I couldn't even hurt.
Is it just because they scaled to the area they're in? Yes. Frames dropping again? No,
they're not. Don't even say that. What? It can't be. Be serious. No. Hold on a minute. Let me,
let me do it. Let me do something real quick. Give me one second. I don't get it. My speed
tests are perfect. It couldn't get any better than this. It couldn't. What's going on? Yeah,
I was running a speed test. That's why I killed it. I don't think server matters. This is happening
to east coast streamers too. What? I did switch servers. I did. Yeah, I just ran a speed test and
it's perfect. Well, that's frustrating. Sorry guys. I wish there was something I could do about it.
I don't think it's a problem on my end. I don't. Yeah. Well, I'm sorry that we kind of have to
painfully deal with this because I changed servers. It doesn't seem to have fixed anything.
Well, we will press on. I got to go down there. Cross this bridge. It's not fine. It's not bad.
Yeah, that really does. It still sucks though because this is one of those games and one of
those streams where we're like kind of experiencing this and the harder it is to experience for some
of you guys, the more irritated it makes me. This is so new. It looks fine. It's probably going to
keep happening. Unfortunately, I don't think there's very much I could do about it. Let's just
kill this guy. Cause I'm probably my leveled up for this area. Probably it's all your fault.
I think stone. Yeah, we're in. Okay. So now I'm here. I was told that I would, I'd be very
interested in this area over here. And there's also something in the middle here too. All right. I
haven't seen any of this, so let's, let's take a, let's take a minute. Hey, I have a question. Is
the, is the tree in the middle? Is that why? Hold on. Is the tree just in the middle of every zone?
It is, right? I'll, I'll, I'll show you this gigantic tree. Am I still in combat?
Oh, like is, is, is this the tree here? Just huge in the middle. That would make sense.
All right, let's do it. This is the area I was told to come explore.
I said, Jerma, go check out this area. Somebody said you'd be very interested to see what's here.
Not actually this space, but you know, a little bit further. What a boat. Why don't you just get
out and walk? What's the point of being in a boat? You're that, that's harder to push. Who Tibia,
who Mar- who is this? Tibia Mariner? Where are you? Is this, is this the Mar- is this them right here?
Where are you? Where'd you go? Are you hiding? Oh, there you are.
You can't be that dangerous, right? Like I'm- is this person just actually in a boat?
This person like sucks. I, I think they got to like the boss sign up sheet.
And from software is just like, oh, all right, I guess we're going to add you. That's fine.
Where'd you go? All right, let's go kill this guy. Yeah. Okay. Uh, so you, you want to be a boss
in Elden Ring? Yes. What do you do, man? Ah, I have a boat. All right. Boat encounter. Sick. Cool.
Boat encounter, man. All right. So you're going to be like flying down like a speedboat. You're
going to have like a Kraken come up. Um, yeah. No way, bro. Seriously. Oh, wow. Yeah, absolutely.
So how much damage do you think you could do? Two. Two thousand? No fucking way, bro. Cool.
Get them on there quick. Get them on the list. This poor guy. This is just a regular enemy. He
wasn't supposed to be in the game. I feel so bad. I actually feel bad for that guy.
Death root. Skeletal militiaman ashes. Okay. Hey, don't even say anything else, man.
Welcome to Dark Souls. Welcome to Elden Ring, man. That actually is Pinwheel. That was, that was,
that was easier than Pinwheel. Even if I was, because I'm probably, what level am I? Level 60?
Yeah, I'm level 60. So if I was like level 45 or 50, I still think that would be impossible to lose.
That's not possible to lose. That guy literally was like the last minute sign-up.
Okay. Well, that was fun. Anything else here? That was cool. This guy in a fucking boat. Oh,
just die. I was level 16 when I did that. I got bone boys. I think is it only two or is it more
than two bone boys? Okay. I think there's a place to go down here. I think there's a dungeon here.
I would be surprised if there wasn't. By the way, I have to get intelligence to 52 if I plan on
using that staff. There's got to be a way to go down. All right. There's got to be.
Check over here one more time. This, that down here. I don't know. I don't see anything. Oh,
my back. Okay. I don't see any way to go down. Maybe it's here somewhere. I'll check one more
time this way. And that's it. All right. Somebody said next to the turtle. Are you sure? Are you,
are you, are you sure? Are you for real? I said what turtle? Turtle? Are you for real? Next to
the turtle. I don't remember where the turtle was. Where's the turtle? Is it a turtle? Ah,
fuck it. Whatever. I'll come back later. I don't know. I don't know what the turtle is.
I don't know what the turtle is. What about over there? Not over here. What about this one?
Thanks. I can't go down here. Why not? How do I get down there? It's a stone sword. Oh, it is.
Let's go. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. I got plenty of these.
Let's go. Let's go for it. I don't just, this dungeon is gonna get me kicked off the internet.
I don't have to fight these, right? Okay. Cause I like the turtle thing. Like everybody loves
the turtles in Elden Ring and like, I'm not just going to kill a room full of turtles.
Green turtle talisman. I got the turtle talisman. What's that? Oh, that's good. Raises stamina
recovery speed. Turtles are known as a nutritious ingredient symbolic of inexhaustible power.
So I just have permanent stamina recovery. So what's, is that better than slowly? How much HP does
this load? It's low HP and maybe get rid of this. That's the best talisman in the game. Well, that's
was worth, that was worth coming down here. Very cool. It's really slow, but it'll save you flasks.
Well, thank you. I appreciate that. Turtle friend. What a weird animal. What a weird animal. It's
like, it's like this weird, like almost like an elephant, but they have elephant feet and like
lizard heads and like big, like rock bodies. What a fucking weird animal. Like what an interest.
And they live to be like 150 years old. So strange. They have elephant feet. Yeah. Look at
there. Look at, look at this guy's elephant feet. He's got elephant feet. Cool. They're so slow,
but they're so wise. Did we just make that up by the way? Is this reason why like the turtle in
all TV shows and movies is old and has like a brow? Is it because they're old and we just like made
them, we just pretend they are? Oh, okay. Old equals wise. That's right. They live a long time.
Yeah. That's why we've made them like intelligent beings. We made them like super intelligent alien
beings. They live a long time, but that's cool though. That's cool to you that they can live
that long. All right. So now I want to go this way. That was not what I was told to go see.
I gotta keep going. Elephants are wise. Elephants are very intelligent, right? Elephants are very
wise, but I can't remember a piece of media, TV show, cartoon, movie, video game where an elephant
was, yes, it's me, the elephant, the old and wise elephant with like gray hairs here. How many,
how many gray haired tortoises have you seen? I think I gotta go this way. It's turtles and
owls. No, the ninja turtles don't count. They got covered in ooze. That doesn't count.
They could, any animal could have been in that ooze and they would have become,
you know, that. It could have been like the ninja seahorses if they, if they'd gone in that goo. So
that doesn't count. Okay. Where is it? This is, there's apparently a cave here somewhere. I was
told explicitly to come here. How come they chose turtles for that show? They just kind of did,
didn't they? That's up further, but up there, those turtles are cool. Turtles are cool.
They should have just used people, but that would just be teenage mutant ninjas, teenage mutant
ninjas, heroes, teenagers. How would you even do that? Okay. I think this is right. What do I
have against turtles? I just told you that I thought turtles were cool animal. Can you swing
at them please? Oh my goodness. Really? Are you that bad? I just said that I thought turtles were
cool. All right. So what's here? What is it? There's something right here. What is it? Ah,
do you not think snakes are cool? I think snakes are cool that they just scare me.
Oh, all right. Okay. Cool. Let's go. Snakes kind of scare the shit out of me. Not because,
and I honestly, I don't, I'm not afraid of snakes. I'm afraid of snakes unpredictability.
Snakes are unpredictable. I have this fear of, okay, snake is just like, oh, you want to hold
the snake? Yeah, sure. And they're just kind of, it's wrapping around my arm and looking at me and
going, it's like, oh, hey, hey, hey, little guy, like licking and like, kind of looks cute. And
then I move like a way that they don't like any, and I'm like, and I start to fucking pass out and
shit. Like, I don't know if they freak me out. I just feel like they're unpredictable. Like you
can't determine like what the move is that they're not going to like. So like, if you have a snake
in front of you and you turn your eyes a certain way, I don't like that. I don't like what you just
did. And like they hear it fucking strike. I don't know. They don't, they're unpredictable.
What about children are unpredictable too? Yes, a child is unpredictable. But the difference is
watching like a two year old like bounce around walking and like bump into a wall is not the same
as a snake biting you in the neck. It's different. A toddler is not going to come up to you and look
at you and be like, what is it a little Johnny? What do you want? And just like fucking leech,
like leap at you and like fucking strike you right here. How am I supposed to get down there?
Horses are unpredictable too. I'm just saying, and I'm saying a lot, there's no poisonous horses.
Look, if a snake, if there was snakes that just bit you and that was it, it's like, fuck, I got a
snake bite. A shitload of snakes can literally kill you. They can, but there's not a poisonous
horse. Although if a horse like fucking kicks you in the face, it's going to cave in your face.
Okay, that argument's not that sound. But you understand what I mean though? Like a snake can
hide. A snake can hide somewhere in like a bush. I know that at the danger level of a horse,
if you get, you know, kicked, bucked in the face, it's going to blow up your whole face and you're
going to die instantly. But like I can see the horse, I can run from the horse, right? I can see
the horse from a mile away. A snake just like in a bush is like, where is he? I don't know. He's
somewhere near me. And then they get off and they're like this and they go like that. And
they like fucking fray out their heads. And then it's like, okay, if I move, I'm dead.
It's unpredictable. Guys, like tigers are like that too. Sometimes like a tiger or a lion will
just be like, oh, like, it's just like, whoa, whoa, what happened? What happened? What's going on?
What's going on? Why'd they freak out? Like sometimes they just freak out. Sometimes animals
like just freak out. Snakes. Tigers are like, no, I don't like unpredictable animals. I like
predictable animals. Like a, like a fucking little like sausage dog because they're just going to
lie on the couch and they're not going to like, there's no point where Otto is going to like
roll over. I'm going to be rubbing his stomach and he's going to go like, oh yeah. And like,
come and fucking kill me. Like it's not going to happen. Oh, the title of the stream. Do you
live in a rainforest? No, I don't live in a rainforest. I'm just saying I'm comfortable.
I'm not comfortable around certain animals as much as I think they're cool. I think snakes are
really cool animals. I just don't want to hold one. And I know that, oh, but Mr. Snookums,
my snake is so cool. I, that's fine. I don't care. Hold them. I'll watch. I'll take a fucking picture
like big tarantula spiders. No, I don't want to hold you tarantula. I don't get it. That's
I want to be within like three or four counties away from that thing. Your neck is all red. I'm
telling you. That's what I'm saying. I get bit by a snake. Have you ever seen a wild tarantula?
Look, we're not talking about in the wild. We're talking about like people that have pets.
There's a ton of people that have tarantula pets. A ton of people have snakes for pets.
I'm glad you like it. I hope you enjoy it. I know they're probably so loving and so wonderful.
I don't want it near me. I don't want to be near it. I just want to look. I'll look at it
from like a distance. Okay. I need to level up. And those little ball pythons, they're so cute
and they're so nice and they're so fun and they'll just kind of sit and hang out with you.
That one moment, one moment in my brain where like I did something unpredictable to the snake
and he latches on. Don't let go. You can put it on a leash. You don't put a leash on a snake.
What are you talking about? Oh, I can do it now. All right. Let me uh, okay. This that way. Okay.
Object permanence time. Object permanence time. Down, right, left. Got it. Okay. You go right.
1100 damage. Holy crap. Okay. This leads into this waterfall area. Do that once.
Okay. This is a tiny little area to fight this. What? I don't have any juice left.
Bad timing. I gotta get around him. Here we go. It's not doing enough damage to remotely even
considered using. Oh man. He's susceptible to that for sure. Behind you. What? Still alive?
You were very susceptible to that. Land octopus ovary. Cross naginata causes blood loss. Dex C.
This thing looks crazy. Oh, it's a spear. That's cool. It's a spider behind you.
Oh, got him. Damn it. My room is too clean. I was hoping I could put like a piece of like
brown or like black dust or something in my hand and be like, oh yeah, and show it.
Well, I thought that was going to be like a piece, like a little piece of something like I could put
in my hand. Why do you look AI generated? I don't know because I'm ugly. Okay. Why don't you just
say what you want to say? Ooh. Okay. So that's, there's nothing here. You won't acknowledge his
dude. I was literally pretending to bite my neck with a snake.
Can you imagine if I just showed up on stream one day and they were just like,
I just don't say anything. I need 20,000. I'm, I'm putting it into health. Don't worry.
Just be covered in boils for your next stream. No, I, that would be, that would be concerning.
Could be like, what the hell's happening? Is he okay? If I just have like boils everywhere,
like big bubbles, like I got, I went to a prosthetic makeup person or something and had
him all over me. You guys would be like, what's, what happened? I would actually scare the shit
out of people. And if I didn't make a joke about it or something, I feel like people would not be
happy about that. It'd be like, dude, come on. Like, what the fuck? Just draw a bunch more zits.
You just say you're allergic to something. Yeah. Sorry guys. I changed laundry detergents.
That's actually kind of funny. Yeah. Sorry guys. I, I, I'm using a new brand of detergent and
I think it's my blanket. I don't know. Had a big reaction to it because that is everything down
there. I have enough to level up. I think let's just do it. Where was that? I want that spear.
I'll show you in just a sec. Uh, that spear is behind the big optic octopus in the Gale tunnel,
which is in this weird section down over the off the road here between, uh,
Kalid and limb grave come down this way. There's a cave down here. There's some
enemies down here as well. You're looking for that, uh, pretty good weapon. It looks kind of cool.
I'll have to check it out. I'll try it on. I need one more kill should do it. And then I'm
going to put it into health. How big is your spear? Um, well, this is a, this is a short sword. So
it's like, maybe, well, I was using a dagger before, so three, four inches.
You talk about like the blade, like from the blade to the, uh, handle. That's a lot. That's
what I was using. It was a dagger. Oh, what? Oh my God. What the heck happened? I said something
weird and gross. All right, let's keep going. No reason to fight any of you.
I would get banned from my own chat. We'll just be clear. I would get banned from my own chat.
Like I would actually get banned from my own chat. Hey, race mimic. What is that? Oh,
it's the thing where you break it and it kills. It gets rid of all your souls and puts you to a
bonfire. Five of them. That was down here. That's it. Oh, hold on. This is, this is
smithing stone. There's something big behind here. Okay. Is there a bonfire right here?
Cause that thing is, whatever that is, it's big. This guy died at pinwheel. Yes, of course. I'm
glad I didn't just open that door. Did you play destiny too? If there was sex scenes? No,
who cares? It's down here. This is the other entrance. Uh, I have way too many flasks
been acting up lately. Like this chest thing. Let's do, uh, I'll do seven and two.
All right. Who's in here? Go headphones. Magma worm. Didn't I already fight this guy?
All right. Oh no. I thought the magma worm maker. So this guy is made by the big magma worm guy.
Okay. Well I have experience fighting you, but glint stones. What am I doing? I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not like at Disney world. Like what am I doing? Oh, now does he stand up like his friend?
Stop doing that move. Stop doing the move. This tiny little area. Stop doing that move. Stop
doing that move. Okay. Like dude, you guys gonna run a circle? It's a tiny circle.
I got it. I got it. Not all these magma worms. They're magma worm maker. He makes the magma
worms. He's like, he's like the chocolate factory guy. He died to the magma worm at level 60.
Did your magma worm do three or four magma runs in a row? I didn't think so. So who?
Okay. Object permanence. Where are we going? Wrong way. Can I summon Oleg in there? But Oleg
kind of sucks against these guys. I actually would rather have the boys. Oh, the boys are dead.
Oh, he spins all the way around. Let that fire dissipate. Dude, I got a river of flame here.
Oh, you stand up. Do you stand up like your friend does? He does stand up. I don't think he stands
up. That's the difference. It's annoying. It has a lot of health. What the fuck? Oh, what the fuck?
What the fuck? What the fuck? What the fuck? What the fuck? What the fuck? Hey, I dodged it.
I didn't. Oh, another dragon heart and I got nothing called moon veil. Moon veil.
Int and deck scaling katana. Really? Wow. It has a magic slash. Shit, this thing's fucking crazy.
Chief blade holding it at the hip in a composed stance. Follow up with either a normal or a strong
attack to draw the blade at great speed. Both attacks fire a wave of light. Oh, my whole body
just like got like cold. What does it take to level up? It's fast. It's fast as fuck too.
That's a huge one. I wonder how much damage that does. How much man does it take? That goes far
and look at that's a huge wave. That doesn't take very much mana. I wonder how much it does.
And it has bleed. Are you kidding me? It's a magic bleed weapon. This is the best int weapon in the
game. What the fuck? It hits like a truck. All right, dude. Okay, for now, let's I got to put up
but the carrion knight sword has been passed down for generations. The carrion knight blade is like
so it's a regal and look at it's both best in the game. Yeah, I know that's subjective. Well,
I need to go investigate that because if that's the case, if that's the case, then I might have
to actually use it. I need to see how much damage that magic part of it does though.
Well, that's really cool. Passed down for generations. Well, I mean, I yeah, this wasn't
passed down to me. I took it off of some guy. Oh, passed down for generations. I like I kind of
just took this off a guy's body. Oh, do I really? Am I that attached? Okay, let's do a little I need
to do an investigative work here. I it's not going to do that much damage that I don't have enough to
I need one point in strength. But how much damage does that do? 173. How big is the arc?
That's a big arc. He's serious, dude. I can't even I'm not like that. I'm legally not even
allowed to have this like on right now. And I'm still like, all right, no, no more testing.
I don't know. I don't know. You're too handing it so you get the benefits. Okay, okay.
Cool weld. It looks cool. It is cool. It's like a like a see through. It's like bubbles.
It's like styrofoam. I have a styrofoam sword. This is kind of weird. It's just styrofoam.
Am I sure this is actually hurting people? Do not use it. All right, let me I want to see what it
what it takes to upgrade. Because I can have a couple weapons, right? But let me all right,
let me clear this from I did that there. Bro, watch out. There's a snake. Good kidding. See
through brain Andy. Let me clear that. And then all right, do I go back to the Smith?
Is there anything else over here that I marked? I don't think so. No. I just had a panic attack
for one second. I actually thought I actually thought that I was going here. I was like, oh,
I have to go fight that guy on the radan guy. I beat him. Thank God. All right. What was next
on the list of like my cleanup list? Here, I wanted to see what this was. So we're gonna go
there. Yeah, I did. I fight I fight it over Dan. And he he wouldn't take me about three or four
hours to beat him. planning all the way. hating the game the whole way. So this way, I get up.
Oh, no, nevermind. I don't Is there even a way to get up there? It doesn't look like it. I don't
think I can get there from here. If you have to go from here. Whatever. Okay. Alright, nevermind.
Where's three? Three was this I was like, what's this thing? This is kind of weird thing. What's
that? Let's go find out. You please play Lego GTA. Stupid game. Finish Ronnie's quest. Yeah,
after I clean up these waypoints, I'm going to go to the Smith. I'm going to see what I have
available and see if I want to potentially upgrade that katana. I also need 12 strength.
I don't know. I'm not sure yet. It's definitely available. Alright, so what is here? Play Lego
elven room. Let's explore this island. frames are still dropping. Yeah, they are and they're
going to continue to. It's some something going on with the twitch servers right now.
I've confirmed it is not my internet. This seek three wise beasts. Tetsu's rise. You must solve
the puzzle to enter. Seek three wise beasts. Oh, we're just never doing this one.
Kill three turtles. Oh my god, the whole island is here. God, get off me. How many people are
just gonna spawn here? I mean, I'll take the souls. There's not stop. Let's farm here for a minute.
Why not? So I'm just gonna farm here. What? Oh, I thought I had the sword out. Oh my god,
what? They're not giving you any souls. Are they not 65? That's a lot. That's not bad.
That's not bad. Then actually, it's not that. Yeah, you're right. Let's get out of here.
All right. Well, I can't do whatever this is, but I can check the back. I don't think I can do this
yet. Oh, okay. Well, that's cool. Magic turtle. Find three wise beasts. That's a turtle right
there. What do I do? Is that it? It's definitely fine. Three wise beasts. It's actually turtle.
It actually is, isn't it? You gotta be kidding me. After all the shit that we just talked, is it?
Oh, that was kind of mean. That's what it is. Oh my god, it's actually that.
Let's kill the three wise beasts. It's the turtles. And then that's gonna open. All right,
where's the other turtles? That was one. They're just hiding in random trees or something.
Come on. Where are you? I know there's more. Two? Where's three? Everybody see three?
I don't know. Other side? It's gotta be here. Like right here somewhere. Where's this third
turtle? On the beach maybe? Over in the rocks. Where the hell are you? I don't know. Behind you.
There's one more turtle. I need to find it. Oh shit! Do I have to get them again? I just reset it.
Wait, okay. Where the fuck were they? Where were they? Where were they? I don't remember.
Object permanency. Where is this last turtle? Look over the east cliff. Thank you. Thank you.
I don't- I'm not playing where's Waldo for like another fucking five minutes. East cliff? This is
the east cliff right here. I swear to god damn god man. Just teleport quick before I fall off.
I have to start the puzzle again? I'm just gonna sprint as fast as I can.
Oh, it's because I have to activate it. Right. Okay, because all those guys didn't spawn.
Seek three wise beasts. Okay, where are they?
I'm just waiting for one of them to go.
Oh, I'm awake. They always sleep and they always wake up and have a white beard. Where are they?
Oh, there's the dog mouth too. It's like- all right, let me at least get the other ones.
Where's this last one? This last one's gonna be like a suction cup down a wall. I know it.
It's gonna be so stupid. Are you sure that they are- I reset it because I don't see the one in
the tree anymore. He's in a bush next to the stairs. You lying motherfucker. There's no turtle
in this bush dude. East- it's off the side of a cliff. Southwest cliff. Southwest cliff. Southwest
cliff. Southwest cliff. Oh my goodness gracious. I have a confession to make. I thought that was a
sickle on the compass and I was wondering what the hell that was the whole game. It's S.
Southwest cliff. I thought that was like a sickle and it was like oh this is some kind of a sickle
enemy or a sickle thing. They're like- I don't know what it was. That doesn't look like an S.
Okay, southwest cliff. This is southwest. Here's the cliff.
Right? This southwestern cliff. I hear magical sounds near the edge. I'm just gonna look up from
here. Stop throwing. I'm looking for a turtle that is randomly in a spot here and I can't find this
little bastard, okay? Southwest cliff. Why am I still in combat? I can't even look at my fucking
map. Wrong side. This is the southwestern- look at the compass! It's just- where the fuck is this
thing? It's not on a cliff. Look at the map. I know- I know- people- I feel like people are
fucking baiting me. I need to- I'm gonna circle the whole goddamn island. I'm not- dude, southwest
cliff! Yeah, last time I did that I fell off the edge. This- I am at the southwest part of the map
right now. I don't see a turtle. Like, you mean out here? He just looked at it? Flying above you.
No, it is not. It's not a blimp. It's a turtle. Go on the cliff. I am at sea level right- I'm not
supposed to be yelling. I'm currently at sea level right now. South cliff. Look down. There's no cliff
on the southwestern part. South cliff. Look down. I'm gonna listen to that person.
There's no southern cliff. It all leads down to sea level.
Where are you? Where are you? Dude, it was right there. Right side of the tower. Run along the edge.
The edge of the tower or the edge of the map? Like, the cliff. Oh my god, it is stupid motherfucker.
I thought- I thought he was gonna be like- like, suctioned on the edge. Okay, I get it. What's in
here? This is very intriguing. Very intriguing. Seek three wise beasts. I can't believe it was
wise beasts. We just had a whole rant about that. Okay, so what the hell's here? Do you think- oh,
question mark, question mark. Do you think turtles have suction powers? LOL, what an idiot.
One of them was in a fucking tree. I don't know very many tortoises that can climb trees
and get to the top of the fucking tree. Is that for your logic? Oh, wait. Oh, hold on. Can I get
over there? Oh, look at this. Oh, look what's over here. Really? Come on. Is there something I can
do about this? Where's the shot? Wait, illusory wall. Don't tell him what to do. Let him lose on
his own. Okay, fine. That's interesting. Gonna be a teleporter. Oh, another spell- another memory
stone. That's it? That's kind of cool. That's kind of cool. It's a little puzzle to get a memory
stone. This is definitely a place where online messages make a big difference, yeah. Lugades
is probably the hardest boss in the game. Oh, I hear- yeah, yeah. General Lugades. That guy's nuts.
Crazy. That's a crazy fight. Okay, so that's cool. As I did want to check that out, I wanted to
see what that was. I also wanted to see what this was before we continue on our on our main
quest here. Very curious what that boulder thing is. Very curious about it. Are we in the end game
now? No, I don't think we'll be in the end game for quite a while. All right, what is this big boulder?
Royal Grave Evergale. Go to Evergale. Yes. Okay. Alabaster Lord? What did this guy come from?
Oh, shit. That's all right. All right. All right. All right. All right, Mr. Lord.
Not bad. I got magic of my own. See how it works against you. That was- that staggered him too.
Hold on. Get a better one. That not even hurt me. That did. All right, now we're fucking around.
No more testing. No more theories. Let's go to phase two. Okay, so that doesn't do damage,
but just knocks you down. Oh, okay. He kind of reversed a long way. Oh, boy. This bad.
All right. That wasn't that bad. Alabaster Lord. Meteorite. Cool. That's just- that's just a boss.
It's just like a phantom boss thing. Let me see what that looks like. I can use this now. 30 in.
All small meteorites down from the sky. Someone's avoid that in his reign of small meteorites hold
to continue the effect. I definitely want to try it. I've- wait, you haven't done any- I've not done-
that's- I didn't even know they existed. How many more of these are there? Is that the first Evergale
he's seen? Yeah. There's a lot of these? There are dozens of these. Okay, let me ask a question. I
have a question for everybody watching. Did I, like- because I spent a lot of time exploring
in the first stream or two, did I just go the route to avoid every single possible interesting
thing? Did that- how did I miss everything? I did so much exploring. I did, like, I did a bunch of
dungeons and, like, I looked down here, the burnt ruins. I didn't find any of this stuff. It was a
required item that I was supposed to find. I just didn't even know it existed until, like, literally
fucking 12 hours ago. You can fight these? Okay. Well, that's cool. You explored armpits when the
full body was exposed. That's, like, weird. That was a weird thing. I don't even know what I said.
That was a weird thing to say. That was a very weird thing to say. I don't even know what you're
saying. That was weird. That was a very odd way to put that and, like, I don't know. It's freaking me
out. You explored the armpit when the whole body was exposed. What's that supposed to mean?
What's that supposed to mean? That's freaking me out. I don't know what that means.
Did you expect a serious answer? Yes. I know this is a very serious community.
Okay. Pretty cool. I think I've tied up all the loose ends. There's one more loose end that I
want to tie up and I just want to get the map fragment for here because it's, like, come on.
Really? Try the meteor? Yeah. Yeah. You want to try the meteor? Okay. I'll try it. Sure. Okay.
Let's see what it does. It shoots me in random directions?
This is fucking terrible. Hold on. Does it? If I lock on, will it? Let's test it over here.
I wonder if I lock on. All right. Let's see what happens here. That might be the worst move in the
game. I didn't hit any single person. It's probably good against big enemies. I guess maybe if you cast
right in front of them maybe. That's a lot. I thought it was a different spell. I thought it
was one that, like, shot little ones. It says small meteors. Those are huge. Okay. Well,
it's not very good, but maybe it'll be good in random scenarios. I need... I'm going to get to
25 vigor. Do I have enough... So what? What? Oh, wait. I got a new great rune. What does Rodan's
great rune do? The void of any benediction. Seek the divine tower of Kaelid, which stands upon the...
I think I have to talk to the finger lady. Yeah. Let's go talk to the finger lady. Upgrade strength.
Wait. Do what I came here for. I could, yeah, I could go to the dragon thing.
But those are all faith moves. And Rodan's soul weapons. Yeah. Let me get the map fragment.
Should do the katana. I'm going to make a very, very hard decision. I'm going to make a decision.
Not going to be easy. Lunaria East. Finally, I can see what the hell's going on here. I wonder
how much further up this goes. You know what I mean, Vern? All right. Time to head back to the
blacksmith and make some decisions. This is not going to be easy. I don't have enough to level up
one time, but I could get it pretty easily. I also need to... Let me do this while I'm here as well.
Greetings. Are you here for spirits? There's something you should know.
I need to warn you about something. A little while ago, someone started lurking in the wing
on the opposite side of the round table. And I can hear, from all the way over there,
a thing of spirits in fear of a curse. I can even hear the repulsive twisted malice in itself.
A plethora of spirits in an unceasing cacophony. I can't even imagine
how much suffering inflicted to who knows how many souls. Not even the crafting caused anything
like this to happen. You should keep your distance. I know you're strong, but please.
Wait, what? There's like a boss in here? This little one.
But you want to give me a little friend?
I'll be glad if you'll come to me, I think.
Favorite jellyfish. All right, let's get the boys up. I need Ghost Glovewort II to even do Oleg.
Boys love free. I'll do the wolves as well. Level the boys up, yeah. I'm curious what
she's talking about. I'm gonna go take a look. All right, so...
So, somber smithing stone 6 is what I need to get this to plus 6. I also need to start
upgrading. I gotta get this upgraded. My scaling is such shit. What does it take to get Katana
upgraded? Also, somber smithing stone. That's C scaling, C and C. All right, all right, all right,
hold on. This is 150, 150 plus 29, 38. The scaling is so much higher. And with the strength,
it would be, it'll be fine. What does more? 137 plus 62 plus the bleed. Yeah, I'm gonna put a
point in strength. It's, yeah. It's time to put the, uh, carrion knight sword to rest, because that's
D and D scaling. This is C and C scaling. It's like, well, is this a no-brainer? That's a
no-brainer. I'm gonna miss this little guy, but this thing just seems way too good. All right,
I just need a point in strength. And I'm also going to do this too, because where's that staff
that I want to eventually use? It's here. Okay, somber smithing stone. I can do it again. Get this
to plus four, which I'm going to do. I want to equip, it's almost an S scaling, bro. My current
staff does not use somber smithing stones, so I'm just going to use the regular ones on here.
So I need, I need six. Uh, bro. Okay, now I've got to, what do I gotta do? What was I gonna do?
What the hell am I doing? There's something very specific I wanted to do.
What was it? Oh, the, uh, the boss soul and the finger lady. Go find out what the deal is.
All right, what's the radan boss soul? Cause I'll just crush it. Okay. This is just a huge strength
weapon and a bow though. That's kind of cool. I am great bow. Star color cry. Bring the,
wait, it's two swords. You pull people, you pull them in. The great bro is pretty pog.
Radan's rain. Archery skill performed from a low stance. Oh, it shoots. It does the arrow move.
Sucks. Okay. Uh, I'm just going to crush it for souls. That's really cool though.
Oh, don't what? Let me don't. Why is everybody going? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't, don't,
don't. Why not? Wait, what are his namesake? I'm not by the finger reader. Yeah. Or used to gain
a great bounty of ruins. What are you talking about? What are you guys talking about? That's a lot.
Okay. That's, that actually just helps me a lot. Big time. All right. So we can get strength.
Yeah. If you're not going to use the boss weapon, then just remove it. Let's point
one point in strength. That's, and I can do one point strength and we'll do, uh,
I'll get 25 vitality. Good. All right. We've got a new weapon and I'm ready to check it out.
Somebody do some math with me here though. I need a calculator.
137 plus 62. That's there. It's 67, 80, 90. That's one 99 and one 15. That's 29,
one 25, 35, 36, 7, 8, 9, 41, 2, 3, 4, 144 and one 99 versus one 81, one 90.
But it has bleed and it's also as the magic built into it's close.
This also is, is it not leveled up? Oh, it just, it just says it there. That's cool. Okay.
Three 72, three 44. Okay. But it does have the bleed and it's also plus four when the
carrying a sword is plus five. So fuck it. Let's go. I'll use it now. Very important. I need to,
uh, talk to you about something. I can get his helmet. That's kind of cool. I can also get his
lion armor. Holy shit. That's a lot of defense. Look at the robustness increases intelligence
by how much, by how much is this thing increases intelligence, but it makes me, it makes me slower.
My stamina is gone. It's the same. Okay. But hold on. So I get my stamina back.
Fucking idiot. This is going to just, I'm, I'm going to tell you, this is distracting.
This is very distracting. That's going to, it gets, it's like, it's in the way. It's actually in
the way. You look like a coat hanger. I look like a moron and it's takes up too much of the screen.
Real estate. I don't like it. Fucking idiot. Well, I have to like put on other clothes then, right?
I just look like I'm about to go to sleep. I'm wearing pajamas. This is like, okay. Do you
know like back in like the, like the 1910s, this is like the pajamas that people would wear. They'd
wear like the pajama hat and pajamas. Okay. Well, whatever. It's better than it is actually
statistically better than what I had on the carrying night stuff back on. I'll keep the
dunce cap on. Now I got my new weapon. I've got my new stuff. It's time to continue the video game
and that means go find the shooting star that landed down here somewhere. I'm going to continue
Ranny's quest. You look like a Frito. Okay. I definitely don't want that. I'll put this on.
Yeah. All right. Let's go like here. We're looking for a star fallen star. Anybody sees it? Please
let me know right there. Look in the sky and it would be on the ground. Something here, man. Hold
on. Oh, I thought that was a bush. I thought that was a bush. He's stuck in the thing. He's
actually stuck in the wall. Perfect. Holy shit. This thing's fucking incredible. This weapon is
unbelievable. It is a place to go down here. Very cool. Let's do it. Katana. Good. Katana. Good.
Yes. Katana. Very good. Well, let me put the purpose. I've been saying magic Katana. Very good.
Axe talisman enhances charge attacks. That doesn't count for like this, right? It's only this.
That's really cool. It's just R2 attacks. Okay. That's still cool though. I feel like I would
want to remember that for me strong because holding R2 with like a big gigantic club because
that's the weapon I'm going to use the big huge like turkey leg. All right. Well, that was cool.
Very cool. All right. Looking for a star shooting star East East. I feel like it would be glowing
and really, really visible on like the whole map, right? I don't think it's something that I have
to go searching for desperately or maybe I do. Maybe it's tiny. Is that it? It looks like down
here. Did it make a big crater? Can I jump down there? Go down. Jump. Is this going to kill me?
Okay. I thought I was going to put with like a magical realm or something.
I thought it was going to be a magical realm. I didn't know. How do I get down?
If there's a, there's literally a path down there. Oh, I don't know. This guy's got literal brain
rot. I don't look, I don't know. It looks very magical down there. Plus it was a little fog.
It's not, it's not so foggy right now. Do you see how much fog was covering this whole thing?
I can actually see now. What? It wasn't, it was like a thousand ruins or something.
Okay. Uh, the fall damage in this game, I got to tell you, I don't make no much sense to me.
You either die or you take like five damage. This is where I jumped from. That's not that far.
That's not that far. That was a Reddit comment. This is crazy though. It's cool. How about,
oh, I got to go over there. Oh, fuck. What the fuck?
You guys, this is going on magical down here. What? I thought it was magical.
Yeah. I thought it was like magical or something. Like there's nowhere else to go.
Where else do you go? He's always frowning. I don't, I'm not sure what I'm supposed to be
doing here. It's, I definitely have to go this way, but I don't understand where. Don't do it again.
I'm getting laughed at. I'm getting actually laughed at. I'm getting laughed at. Dude,
just play worms. Okay. What's happening? What keeps happening here? This game's too hard.
This game's too hard. All right. What keep, what, what the fuck actually keeps happening to me?
I don't, what's going on here? I keep getting here and then my brain goes nowhere. Go lose that way
left. See how fucking foggy it is here. Dude. It's so foggy. I couldn't see this.
It's too foggy. I couldn't see it. Are you malding? Yeah, dude. Oh, oh, oh yeah.
Are you balding? Yeah. Not that rapidly though. I'll probably have here for a while.
Probably into my like forties. It's gotta be a, a touch stone thing here, right?
Bonfire. If it's not, then like, I'm sorry, but the developers like seriously made a fucking big
mistake. If there's not a bonfire down here, then like, I mean, the devs made a fucking massive
mistake. And like, if I was on the team, I'd probably know how to do, I'd probably fix it.
You know what I mean? If I was like one of the devs, I would like know what to do. Like this,
this part here, like I'm not a fucking big fan of that. Like man, if I was on the team, I'd fuck,
I'd fix that quick. The small animation cancel at the end there. I would have fixed that if I was
on the team. What is he talking about? I'm doing the thing where like when you suck at Dark Souls,
you talk about how like the game's not good and you would explain why like, and how you're
going to fix it. And like, you would know so much better. Oh, this is we're now. Okay. I get it.
I get it. Be careful. All right. Dual headphones going in. You explain the joke minus two.
Sometimes you have to because people think I'm actually sitting here doing that.
I'm sorry. I'm not going to fall. No, I am going to look for secrets.
Oh, you go. Gross you.
What was that? People genuinely think souls games are perfect. No, they're not.
Absolutely not. Radan is in the game. It's not perfect. This is weird.
Holy shit. I thought I just walked off the edge. Whoa. It's just like the thing from clay fighter,
the blob was his name. Oh my goodness. Be careful. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Oh, hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt. If it gets that reference.
You're, uh, you're a real one. That's literally from clay fighter. We were just talking about it.
I can't believe some people just don't get it. What's that? Silver tear husk.
Stop doing that or I'm going to fucking tell on you.
Those guys are fucking terribly easy. Just get them. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Come here. Come here. I still get it. Right. I win. Right. Ascent butterfly.
Next game. I fall through this. Okay. For a second, I thought I was avoiding that accidentally.
One of them, maybe you can go right through. I wouldn't be surprised.
When is Elden Ring going to come out? Um, I don't know, dude. Check your fucking local listings.
Leave me the fucking line. Cool. You just got to type in, go to walmart.com and type in Elden Ring
PC CD ROM. Okay. I don't know. I don't know when it's coming out. Is that what I need?
No, it's somber smithing stone five. Pretty cool. We use the CD. I don't know very many people that
still have a CD drive on their computer. Uh, is this safe? I don't think this is safe. Is it? I'm
kind of scared to do this. I don't think this is safe. This kind of frames. Yeah. I don't,
I'm sorry guys. There's nothing I can do about it. If I could fix it, I would.
Something with a lot of people on Twitch's connections streaming to Twitch right now,
it's not good. That's seriously like unfucking good. Damn, that's good. It's better on mobile.
Um, I, it's, it's my connection to Twitch, whatever is wrong. But I would originally
be kind of concerned about this. But according to what a lot of you guys have told me, this is not
just a me problem. Cause when I do a speed test, it's perfect. Okay. I can't level up
for anything. So what I, something I do want to do, I want to get rid of this enhances left hand
shield damage. How much though? By what? Either that or maybe starlight. I feel like I'll need
it at some point. What about Glenstone arc? I have Glenstone arc as this weapon, so I don't need it
anymore because I have it baked into this weapon. It's pretty damn good. Something tells me I'm
about to fight something here. I'm getting very concerned about it. I'm getting very concerned.
Please don't curse. Yeah. All right. I'll do my best. If I think about cursing, I'll just,
I'll mute. Glove ward. It is ghost glove ward. That's exactly what I needed to upgrade. Oh, like,
I don't know if it's exact this one though. This is a boss area. It has to be. So let's prepare.
The audio is completely out of sync. I think it's because the stream keeps like hiccuping
and I think it's happening on the browser. Hey, oh, stop. Oh, stop it. Oh, stop. I don't know what
happens when that fills up, but I don't want to, I don't want to find out process frost. Okay.
So it just makes me slow. Not a big, not a big deal. Ghost glove ward pickers bell bearing.
I can bring that to the store. That's kind of cool. All right. I can read it in the store
that five times fast. Ghost pickle bell bearing. Ghost sword pickle bell.
I don't know what it was. Let's check this side. I want to miss anything.
shit. All right. I was close to my boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat.
Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. That was a record. I think
this channel at least that was probably at least 10 plus times in a row what other channels do that
i'm just saying in general i can't claim to have the record because somebody probably did it a
hundred times in a row that's mad damage that's actually that's actually just mad that's mad
damage i like this area's music it's very blood-borne-y that leg
great one two that's five great shield boys interesting tank boys all right so i can go
in here i could go down there let's see what's in here can't replace the boys i can at least get them
so plus three marvel tier i'm gonna do an item uh like recap essentially i picked up a lot of
stuff in the last like hour okay i think that's everything i'm gonna go down there is a desync
i i don't think there is i think i don't see it on my uh preview i honestly think it's the internet
shit that was happening with twitch's servers oh shit okay there's a boss here one of those statues
hmm i think i level up first yeah definitely i have enough runes i think to put
another point into intelligence which is what i'm gonna do
oh fuck out of here
big whip do i get the whip you kissed erba i already have what that was a different whip though
that was a like a chain it almost looked magical a magical whip would be kind of fun
hmm yeah i definitely can level up for uh going in there without a doubt so that's what we're gonna
do another larval tier oh i need that's why i don't have the arc i have it already i think
that's all i can do but i'm gonna level up unless because there's a statue back there so that's what
they want you to respawn after you die a multitude of times here i do have to pee too so we're gonna
take a break before doing whatever the heck this is yeah all right i'm going back to the bonfire
i gotta pee whoa what did i just go what no that's not what i wanted to do
what happened what it's the wrong one what's the right one this one here okay yeah this is the
right one all right uh let me see if i can level up yeah i have so many of these it's gonna be 5k
okay 23 000 24 000 i believe it's 24 or 23 23 okay i gotta kill a couple things
hello everybody aggro everyone a few more level up p why what's wrong with having is the zip
now i've been very vocal about my zip i've been very vocal about it i'm not very happy about it
gotta be honest i'm very not happy about it all right level up now one more for good luck
disgusting i have to i think i just have to keep stacking intelligence
because if i i need 52 with the mask on what do i have right now with the uh the helmet on
i think it's like 35 34 well okay i'm gonna pee i'll be right back uh i'm gonna maybe refill my
drink i will see you guys in two three minutes oh uh yeah because we're gonna fight a bus
so we're about to we're about to be here for the long haul see you guys in a moment
hey be quiet i forgot to mention uh the streamer awards the voting is active been active for like
a week or so uh this channel has been nominated for a couple things if you go to the streamer
awards you can go vote if you want to you get a link yeah this channel got nominated all right
all right all right uh yeah whoever you think deserves to win for all those awards it was hard
for me to do it a little bit just because i don't really know that much about valorant or
what fps stuff but it's uh it's available very available yeah thanks josh uh yeah i'm nominated
for a couple categories uh the dollhouse is nominated and i am personally nominated
there's some really really awesome nominees go uh go voice your opinion i'll see you uh
i'm not turning the stream off and i'll see you later see you like goodbye i was about to turn
like about ending stream and i'll see you tomorrow see on the next one okay let's bash our head
against a wall against like a huge boss sounds fun my streaming tomorrow um let's see how this
goes maybe we'll see how this goes uh for the next three four hours yeah thanks everybody for
linking it voting i think voting ends tonight or tomorrow so you'll you know you don't have very
much time let's go that's gonna that's a no uh i don't that's i wouldn't rule that out just yet
okay time to fight the boss let's do it let's go here double headphones gonna need it stretch
the back move the back lean forward pulse okay so who is this who am i fighting maybe i should
take off the well let's let's just see the bosses let's just find out what it is because i'm either
gonna do all katana or i'll switch it up a little is the statue right here right yep i'm gonna be
sure i look at it so i get it okay let's go oh my god i thought you were here i was not even looking
oh well i remember i gotta jump over that i don't know aggro these guys i don't care it's i mean
yeah i may have lost a flask but whatever i i just want to see what the boss does we gotta get a
picture of what's going on here this blob just died oh it turned into me mimicked here oh this
one person i know more than anybody it's me i wouldn't have done that that's how i know you're
fake what's something that i would hate oh i know slow fucking moves yep uh right now he's fucking
screaming in his chair god damn it come on yeah all your moves suck that's how i know i'm gonna
beat you you your character sucks dude your character's awful
hold on wait wait wait wait wait oh nice moves jeremy good moves very cool
fuck you're out of potions you're an idiot what's it when's he gonna let go of it i don't know the
timing on this i don't fucking understand time oh good one good okay you're learning
okay see how long it just took him to do that all right no more messing around time to die
larval tier silver tier mask what is that like a clay mask greatly increases arcane to the
detriment of physical attack power by how much 17 versus oh my god that's a lot it's a lot
okay well that was not that bad maybe if he was a stronger character very cool yeah i mean i we
might have to come up with like a command for like the frames or something like like exclamation
point frames and just have like they have like a corporate response like i don't understand what's
going on my internet is fine i think we've narrowed it down to possibly it's something going on on
twitch is in bear with us all right well that leads to this which this looks like the real
encounter coming up here this is a huge bridge there's no way that this is not the real fight
i have 10 000 souls i'm kind of concerned about this how come no one else is losing
frames if it's a twitch problem i don't i don't understand i thought people i thought it was
happening to other people i can upgrade the katana those are fine they've gotten way worse
other streams are fine i did switch servers brutal right now what the fuck is going on i
actually am dropping a huge an insane amount of frames though like it's actually really bad
this server might actually be worse it doesn't make any sense because i i have i i literally
have a thousand megabit upload right now like i just i just did a speed test it was like 940
megabits up i don't get it should i change back to the other server it is definitely happening to
other people it is literally happening to other people don't let anyone don't listen to everybody
worse than yesterday though it's not happening it's not happening to every streamer but it's
happening to a lot of people um that's this is like really not good though i kind of might go
to the other server yeah let me let me try that i i changed maybe it's happening to like where like
maybe some route is fucked up so people may be in like the i don't know in like the western part
of the country or something but let yeah this is bad like i'm i have six percent drop frames
let me go back to the server i was on before see if it makes it even a little bit better
because i have 6.6 percent of all frames have been dropped which that's really not that's awful
let me refresh the stream i'll be right back see if it gets any better if i go to the place
i was before i'll be right back don't go anywhere don't move a muscle be right back okay whoa
holy shit i can't even connect to this server what the fuck yeah like i i'm dropping
60 percent of all my frames trying to connect to this one what the fuck is going on right now
this is insane what i'm gonna have to connect to a i'm gonna have to go somewhere else for like
my server what the fuck this is by the way this is the server that i use i've been using for like
two straight years holy shit this is unbelievably bad i don't know what's going on but this is
really really weird i'm doing a speed test right now and i do 900 down 900 up
fuck yeah this is fucked up yeah i just did a speed test 900 900 um well we're gonna try a
different server yes there's no way i can connect to this one i will see you guys again in a moment
yeah i have officially confirmed this has nothing to do with my internet zero i just ran three or
four speed tests in a row it's perfect officially confirmed has nothing to do with my internet i'll
be right back i'm gonna try another one uh it's not my vpn i don't have my vpn's not on
be right back we're gonna try another server okay how are we doing are we good
now something's still wrong it's better but it's still really bad i'm gonna stick out let's stick
on this one for a little bit for a minute or two because this is the third server i've tried i'm
gonna stay here for a minute let's just let's just chill out for a moment i i i have a live
monitor over here and i can see that it's it's still about 10 maybe i should turn the vpn on
because that'll route traffic in a different way maybe because something to do with the connection
to twitch maybe it's a good idea to just to turn the vpn on and have it just kind of go somewhere
else and have the track of traffic come in a circle it seems better we'll give it a moment
oh hello what can i do for you all right i'm gonna i'm not gonna go brb actually i'm technically
gonna go brb because i think you need something uh i'm gonna sit here and see because i think it's
all right it's definitely better than it was before at least it seems that way what are you
doing where are you going what are you doing ato all right yeah i think he's probably just
he just i think he wants a treat or something i would just give him a treat
oh you want a treat yeah he always wants a treat he wants a biscuit um i i'm just gonna go for it
well the treat stream that's right me and holly we're we're actually talking about it we were
like how are we gonna do like the treat tier list how are we gonna do a treat tier list i tell
yeah it's better than it was before and we're gonna have to deal with it because i can't just
sit here and just do nothing for like another 40 minutes so sorry about that treat stream yeah
we actually did talk about it but sorry everybody i know this is kind of annoying but it's annoying
for me too trust me but it seems to be settling down dude i don't know what's going on with the
west coast servers maybe the josh you were saying the east coast servers are doing it too but
i connected to the server that i've been connecting to for years and i couldn't even
put anything through but it's okay it's all good i'm just glad it's not my problem because
you guys know i have like traumatic experiences with my internet being terrible but thankfully
i can confirm that it's not my internet but we continue it's a long bridge oh oh okay
we see auto um he just ran away all he gave him a treat and he's he now he doesn't care about me
he's like hanging out with her he's incredibly food motivated wait go to the end of the bridge
maybe a little bit later a little bit later i'll show i i will show auto i actually he did lose one
pound but that's good i wonder if i can get down there like right there he was way too chunky
weight like bad he's supposed to be like between like 22 and like 26 pounds yeah
he may have been uh closer to 30 so i'm glad that he's uh getting back down to like 27
we want i'm trying to get him to 26 because he's a dachshund mix so he's not he's actually
supposed to be a little he's supposed to be bigger so his ideal weight is like 24 to 26
so he was like 28 he's down now to like 27 trying to get him down to 20 all right you get it let's
go fuck you well these guys got a lot of health huh all shrimps get the mushrooms oh that you
don't like that jawbone axe pretty cool these guys really don't like that move oh if you're
getting um stream syncing problems because of the weird server issues uh refreshing apparently
works load of blood your eminence i beg you grant me a seat at the table of the dynasty
long live the mogwin dynasty long live that come on with dynasty i kill these things no
there's been a split second delay for months i think i went over this before that like
the way that my webcam is picking up my voice like my voice comes out sometimes my voice doesn't
match my mouth movements a lot of times that's normal i actually talk really weird all right so
where am i going from here probably explore this top part i get on the horse too we're singing
again this is gonna am i gonna get attacked by like the goats is it a goat call all right for
interrupting it was such a weird death face forward that was actually kind of like terrifying
all right another one of these okay i gotta go light the fires again really i gotta do this on
top too that move is so good against these guys hey man you're killing me with this bullshit
love it love it not let this guy kill you of the one person that's here
oh you're using the op katana why you were my favorite streamer sorry man
sometimes you gotta be the bad guy oh we're fighting another hello horn okay i'm assuming
this is probably an upgraded version you i can't believe you're doing this you were my favorite
streamer well come on it's an int katana it's int and dex huge scaling of course i'm gonna do it
all right i need to light six of these that's gonna be pain in the ass so i might not do that
right now but maybe i will depends on how far i need to go is that one there there's one here
i'm the incest ancestral woods grace and then jump from all right well that's a lot hold on
i have to be careful i could get so easily killed too be very easy for me to get killed
there's a lot of people that i could get killed so hard look at all these animals
there's a couple of these these like old gods or something oh shining horned headband whoa
strengthens ancestral infant's head we're taking that off immediately so this thing is on the
ground it's kind of dead keep doing anything well i don't like that that was gross all right
i got three where else can i go from here this is the grounds where i have to fight that eventually
i need three more of these right three more i'm just gonna keep going this way sure i'll run into
another one get that grave love walk that's a big dog that looks like a rare dog it's just the same
dog i thought this guy right oh man damn oops whoa i'll get you fucking friends out of here
get your fucking friends away from me not fair oh you want to play that fucking game fine we'll
play i don't have any men that's so goddamn dumb like i'm i'm in the middle of fighting you and
i'm like we're just going well get out of here come on really oh fuck you what i
was unfair that was that was stupid i literally refilled the flask and i'm trying to like click
click click i i had them too i was like focused but let's let's have like five wolves just be
there and attack you that's what i gotta say about that dumb shit it's like fucking wolf patrol oh
like eat my asshole like fuck out of here you're a dumb ass patrol oh what are you looking for
somebody oh hi guys just fucking so many animals everywhere like i don't want to i don't want to
see any more fucking wolves do i actually have to run around and clear out like the 30 wolves
that are surrounding this stupid ass area okay never mind no no no no no no just go
fuck this place i already killed this guy and got the item like what do i care what are you guys
doing over here what was that nothing wait i could have refilled that i think it doesn't do
enough damage oh that's it that's it there's no i don't get anything for that there's nothing there
what 2.4k and not a single item i can't come on you're not supposed to fight him i know it's
optional but i mean come on he was easy though yeah i know he's not like a boss but like 2.4k souls
oh you're better than that i mean we have 5k i wouldn't have been that upset
how do we go ahead and kill your entire family i leave one okay don't be an idiot beast blood
oh are you coming to get revenge for your dear old dad it's the only way to fly and don't make it
so sweet this time i'll make it i'll make i'll show you how to make it old-fashioned the old-fashioned
way like dear old dad used to make be sure to make it old-fashioned the old-fashioned way
like dear old dad it's probably only three people in this whole chat that
have any idea what that is no you don't understand i'm i'm trying to we're finally
gonna close the case smiler grogan and his tuna factory robbery no one's gonna get that
nobody i would be surprised if one person knew what that was no that's not a columbo
although you're close you're pretty you're kind of close but not really
oh shit i have 26k man don't fall no not mash not gilligan's island it's a mad mad mad mad world
mash no not mash ash of war enchanted shot i'll show you how to make it old-fashioned the old-fashioned
way like dear old dad used to make when i hear like oh let me show you how to make it old-fashioned
the old-fashioned like dear old dad used to make that's like that's like that drink that is
undrinkable it's probably like 40 alcohol it's probably that it's what half the drink is alcohol
don't make it so sweet this time let me show you let me show you how dear old dad used to make it
oh no no not 40 alcohol by volume i mean like the drink is 50 alcohol and 50 something else
which is like oh that's too much all right i need i need two more dude you're a lightweight
okay please yep there it is i can upgrade the katana not yet oh dude shot what do you do
fucking oh a drunk ring dude every time i like beat a boss take a shot i'm still missing
did i already get this one i got that one on the other side maybe i don't know didn't look like i
could go over here yeah i got that one maybe all the way on the other side okay left see in an hour
pepe laugh uh what have i done can you recommend whatever it was um oh i don't need that
if they laugh this is like too this is too simple but what this room is this is too simple this
guy's gonna turn into like an eagle or something this person's gonna turn to an eagle ancestral
infant's head what is that didn't it say something about that i have an item that is wait what is
that uses fp to spray spirit vapor the vapor becomes a temporary geyser which deals continuous
damage to everything it touches and then the helmet that i have right strengthens ancestral
infant's head is it just one use or how does this work i'm just gonna try it that's actually kind
of cool it's just reusable that's really actually pretty cool i wonder how much more significant it
is if you have the helmet on all right well i'm gonna keep it on the bar because that's kind of
cool i might use it how do i get out of here now do i have to just teleport i'm not sure i can
like do anything about this i think i just teleport unless i'm missing something else here
yeah i got i gotta teleport i gotta teleport out of here jump what do you mean jump jump
jump from here foot i mean like no guys i can't that's not gonna happen
it's not possible how's the how the frames is it a piece of shit still are you okay i haven't
really been paying attention to it how are we going off let me see how many have dropped
it's better than the it's better than it was it's still a piece of shit though but it's better than
it was we went from six point eight percent to three point five percent so i don't know what
the solution is but well hopefully they fix it soon well i'll just stay on this server i need
to upgrade the katana we're gonna do that oh what was that shit they were saying about the um
somebody was here and like don't go near them they're scary or something whatever it was
somebody here there's somebody in the round table now and there's terror there's terrifying
and one this is now this is much better 150 plus 73 that's pretty big deal okay so she's like i
hear the whales i hear the whales screaming they're yelling whatever they're wailing
please to see you again would you like me to i don't have a good day to you great oleg oh yep
ghost glove work why not thought i picked up a bunch of it didn't it just pick up a shit
load of this stuff all right well she's like i can hear them so if you can hear them they're
probably laying down this hallway oh maybe down where are you hearing this from where are you
hearing this are you gonna do an almond milk stream no almond milk is not it's not hot for
me right now it's oat milk actually by the way i want to buy the uh stone sword key thing uh down
there okay somebody's down here freaking out for some all right okay all right hold on offer bell
bearing offered ghost form pickers bell bearings and now ah here we go ghost glove work 2 is what
i need awesome i think that's all i needed all right what's this person's problem you ever felt
with your whole being if itself feared and despised by all the reviled blessing
yeah are you not you are but a lamb as strange as a defilement ignorant of your own ignorance
you no longer interest me i've been long without peace don't spoil my quietude
i asked you not to disturb me we're gonna do about it thankful of the whole serenity
it is all that keeps your death and defilement at bay well what are you what are you going to do
about it i asked you a question you're dealing with the magician now i can make the room brighter
what do i do okay maybe you can just hold a lighter up to him yeah what do you think about
this man okay so we're good i'm gonna use that ghost grave glove work on oleg yeah you just
show death root well listen to reason hey voice for weeding death root and the strength of beasts
if you're inclined to haunt more of those who live in death and their death root then i'll introduce
you to garank the beast clergyman i have a matter of my own to attend to all right and the beast
himself wishes for someone to take my place what say you yeah that sounds cool very well show me
are you gonna actually mark my map location for you you do of a hidden gateway he marks it
the beast clergyman the rank the red mark was made on the map people actually put marks on the map
really all right that's pretty cool what is it still knowing about that indicates where the
gateway is hidden it will lead you to garank thanks let's just let's just go do that i guess
it's kind of in the front of the brain right now wait i need to upgrade uh people yes
upgrade people upgrade people this way at least i can do uh i could probably do all like a few
times yeah i just need souls 34 that's a lot 3400 great many runes i think i would like that
damn i can get oleg again 4300 i know i've been picking up all this stuff all the time and i
haven't had an opportunity to use it i can do it again 5270 i have one ghost glove word plus five
well i'll remember that getting powerful now yeah all right let's uh let me go check this out this
is kind of cool but let me remember what i was doing before so lap burn this into memory this
knock ron city there was what was i doing here i don't remember i was um what was i doing i was
progressing here oh lighting the beacons lighting the beacons was lighting fire i'm gonna okay let
me put this down i actually have to write this down i'm gonna write in all caps light fires in
knock ron got it got it in the meantime i want to do this this is interesting you are also doing
ran ranny's quest yep that was part of what i was doing in knock ron though that was um
that's part of it let's see what this is very interesting they said there's a gate
hidden over here it really is wow it really is kind of just buried in the corner here
i definitely don't think i would have found this look it up regal's dragon barrow hey hey
notes notes notes excuse me i got notes here i got notes uh do you remember this
dragon barrel far to the east has the other half of the coin that that medallion that i have the
second half is here so that's interesting dragon barrel so holy shit what is that i was scared
though that actually scared me that was terrifying to me that was terrifying why are you writing
notes like a nerd because i'm trying to good luck keeping track of anything going on
east yield sanctum okay so this is the guy he's like i'm gonna send you to my friend
hand over death root let me let me first uh figure out what i'm handing them
so i don't even know what it is death root east clergyman seeks and devours these
where did i get this i don't know where i got that from where is that from like your notes
ghost in the boat oh okay i see hold on let me one second i want to i want to for air circulation
air circulation naked no i have shorts on uh so what happens if i do this
give him one death root sure does he talk to me now
lawmark seal east i
uh said to tremble when close to death root
i said to tremble when near death root the murky violet iris writhes if it's alive
i wonder what that that's an indicator on the screen fort farrowth in the dragon barrel
that was kind of interesting what was the other thing give me two things flaw
was it sometimes i like kind of wish this game had a like combat log of history that happened
happened what was it i just got it gave me two things i and the claw but what is
it's a weapon where is it it's a talisman eighth talisman where is it didn't give me two things
it's an offhand oh bestial incantations okay i was i'm looking around i thought it was an item
um that's kind of cool so it's a dude does that thing that cast spells very cool all right that's
pretty nice all right should i uh just get embarrassed and die from this thing that's
really cool all right let's uh this area i'm probably not supposed to be here so let's go
ahead and like just spray this guy wait this is a boss what this is a boss that took me a while to
figure that out i was mesmerized okay he's that's one hit i don't i don't think i'm uh
it's a weird place to fight him too you're not hostile until you hit him well now i now i want
to go out there and fight him i was he versus this stuff let's see very bad what if he was like oh
and i blinded him i i'm gonna try it one more time it's just fun whoa that goes far so i'm an
oleg actually i'll summon oleg get the hell out of here man can you not follow me inside
that actually could be kind of funny if i can just cheese him no no i'll come back and actually
fight him i want to actually fight all right yeah i'm level like 62 or something i shouldn't be here
okay well that was kind of cool now i know what this is for we're all the way over here
uh so we are going to go back to knock around because i need to light the fires in knock run
still missing i believe who who files how's the chewy noise
joey joey i always have to lean in and get off camera to do a voice because i don't want to be
because i make like weird scary weird faces this is seriously this is not the closest
this one closer but i'm already doing it why is the stream stuttering exclamation point frames
all right let's go let's go let's go i definitely am an idiot because there's absolutely another
bonfire somewhere right here it's all right though i need two more fires we fight whatever
that is and then maybe i'll do i continue that the ranny quest all right i did i went to the
right i need to go to the left what about yes yes oh my god really yes now here's an interesting
thing what's this for whoa that person alive holy shit i think that person's alive oh my god
this is huge okay night's sacred ground oh um maybe i'll find a bonfire og you found
renee's quest og you found renee's quest silver tier who's that ruin are you can't they can't get
up here so it doesn't matter i'm just i'm doing item search you know that there's but yeah of
course there is celestial dew i got a couple of those now tell a joke um i'm not very good
with jokes i'm not very good with i'm not very good with jokes can i go down here okay jump to
there with the horse is not available i'm not very good with jokes i have to be able to i have to
prepare them and tell them silver tier all right so this is like a okay i'm ready let's go is that
all you do is that all you do okay hopefully there's no item on that person
i would be remarkably pissed off it's a big ruin another way to go over here what are these
butterflies oh frames drops only happen when you attack i think uh i think that might be
a really interesting coincidence i wasn't make it it's your pc it's not my pc my pc's fine
my game is playing flawlessly my internet is perfect there's nothing wrong with my face
i have no pimples to go up where we're going oh shiny in there it's too quiet in this place
it just is that usually means something horrible is about to happen
black wet blade yep i knew it i heard it oh it's you what's that how many do i have
what do you say i have i have seven stone sword keys i'm gonna use it this looks like an npc
why can i attack this person what's going on who is this oh it's a chest
okay what is it wow this is gold mimic tier ashes that's a gold beam legendary ashen remains used
to summon the spirit of a mimic tier summoning consumes hp rather than fp the spirit takes the
form of the summoner to fight alongside them but its mimicry does not extend in imitating the
summoner's will what do i summon a copy of myself to run around that's kind of interesting i'm
curious this one sucks oh legs better i'll try it oh no how much does it cost to use
that's kind of good it's literally the best summoned by a thousand miles
because how many keys that take to get in here not that many there's only one okay we're good
very cool okay more items i i'm pretty i'm item collect andy by the way just
i guess everybody needs to know that if i if it's available i'm gonna try to get it
how do i get over there the gold the ball is alive why is the ball alive the ball has a health bar
what is this an enemy why is the ball alive oh shit doesn't look like it does that much damage
don't fucking go that close holy shit it does a lot a lot a lot like a huge a lot
oh man fuck you i gotta have a hit a wall get away from me you're stuck
oh jesus okay that's a okay that was a sentient ball what did it drop
larval tear okay i got a lot of those and i got i that's a respect thing right
it's so weird it's weird that was just odd okay nothing let's go there's so many cool
enemies and stuff and then there's just a ball that's very from software though right
god it's so from software we're slowly making our way down to the lady huge lady there sitting
there an old lady this takes health it said i'm very curious how that works how okay that's a
lot of health not some health that's so stupid he's a fucking moron all right this might be
the best someone in the game if it wasn't this character because that's a move i don't think is
worth doing he's gonna do the spinning staff move oh he sprayed the goo he's just a mind of his own
he's trying to drink a potion now i understand why this is so fun to watch you like watch the
streamer like lose that's funny oh shit can i not okay i can i feel like this is an encounter that
i need to pay attention to we'll see now the celestial dew i think i have to fight these things
i think he's gonna get up isn't it hello two versus one's not fair what do you say we equal on
he's back he's fine all right get up you and me let's move it's two v two now back here help me
that bleed is sick too by the way that's awesome that that does that what a great weapon
get him he's kind of a fucking idiot he's kind of stupid like that was dumb that was a really
dumb thing to do the spin is so good the spin is not good the spin is very bad oh
where is he where is he what happened to him come here come here come here come here come here
give me his head that was scary bleed was pretty good all right so now i have an audience with
whoever this is what's the deal what's going on here who is this what weapon is this this is the
moon veil all right i'm gonna make a prediction this character whispers tarnished you must
go forward it's gonna be a whisper it's gonna be a very light whisper okay well here we go
do anything there's a teleporter there is a teleporter you're doing anything all right i
just i'm looking you know you gotta make sure you walk around in case there's something there
okay talk there's a chest here another golden thing finger slayer blade great ghost glove wart
key hidden treasure of the eternal city of nokrom this blood-drenched fetish is proof
of the high treason committed by the eternal city and symbolizes its downfall
and i'll be wielded by those without a fate but it's said to be able to harm the greater will
and its vassals let's take this to ronnie i got a super glove warp okay this doesn't do anything
that's i mean it's cool looking where does this take you i don't so now we're gonna go to wait i'm
not going there yet i want to light the other fires welcome for the ad revenue thanks with the
advert i want to light the other fires because i'm there's a couple more that i have to light
and then i can fight that other boss i want to fight it but where are the last two flames
i don't know how am i missing them i'm just missing them apparently two more here somewhere
that one right there just look dumbass what are you doing here i don't know lags every time he
swings lags when he swings
yeah it's it's random intervals okay is it up here i think i found one of them maybe all right
yep yep yep yep there's something well there's something weird right there i don't know what
though what's this like smoldering rocks oh ah okay it's one more that i'm missing i think
i don't have any idea where it could be oh no that's it is it oh i got them all all right cool
all right got them all i'm gonna level up first i want to get i need to get to uh all right first
of all just kill the people that are attacking me because some of my friend maybe i will he's
still fighting me this weapon is so good i didn't abandon oleg what are you talking about i'm sure
he'll set he'll be really useful in a lot of time a lot of places level up time this area looks
cool this area is really cool 25 000 i think is what i need maybe 22 20 what do i need
25 all right i'm gonna kill a few more people hey come on it's so good it's so good
that enough i think i need 25 i'll just kill this group here that's such a great move i wonder if
that's only good against these guys but whatever i'll take it he's just kind of a pain in the ass
all right that should do it it was 25 and some change hopefully it's not more than that
works on shield with enemies too wow that sounds fucking incredible uh health or more
into i'm gonna try to get health to 30 i feel like i'm really lacking in that right now all right
you guys ready ready let's go for it see if we can fight this thing this is another one of those
deer bosses something okay let's go i wonder how different this one will be
let's go eagle ancestor spirit is it the same fight seems to be pretty similar
two that's different what so this one does three what that does four
four that's a one two three four
these pigs are in the way don't be greedy i love that sound whoa what's this
excuse me what happened here you healed to full health oh well that's gotta stop that from
happening i have to stay i have to stutter that i think what the holy shit okay that was okay so
that it's not a big aoe move it's a heel what the fuck it's like bunny hopping is that it holy
fuck i thought you're gonna do the bunny hop yeah oh fuck i think it's run maybe you can dodge
through it no no no no no no no no no no i gotta go faster i gotta kill him faster than this
i just happen to be drinking all right yeah i gotta kill i gotta kill you faster than this
you gotta burn i gotta put the burn fight it's a burn what the fuck are you doing stop
this shit's a burn fight what or shit and i mean that literally fuck i could have done more hits
on this idiot no no no god all right all right okay okay so the dude heals and i gotta kill him
before he does the deal twice i gotta get when he's healing get in there whack him a bunch of
times i thought it was a giant aoe explosion that's why i didn't do it the first time and
he got full health i got him like i'm no sword skill um i feel like i could have just beaten
him without it i'll try it though don't even make sure you use that sheath magic i'll try it
he shit like that like i didn't know that now i know that i'm ready yes dead what about killing
the animals uh i could try it maybe it's the amount of heal he gets that's a great question
actually i should probably try it god damn it got greedy being stupid yep that's definitely
that's what it is he eats the animals he eats the animals all right i gotta i gotta run around him
oh come on i could have had an opportunity all right yeah i he i gotta get rid of the animals
he eats the animals that's what's going on here oh that's a stagger let's get him right in the
head see you later oops try dodge it that hurts me too all right bro fuck you
fuck what he added that dude what the fuck stop yes yes yes yes yes that's a remembrance
really okay that's actually kind of cool i wonder what that boss weapon is
all right really cool really really cool pretty cool pretty cool that's another level too very
nice i want to see what that does whatever to the burger king head uh it was kind of nerfing me
this thing dude this thing is the same thing as the burger king head the only difference is it
does not it's way less defense but this brings my stamina down 10 this doesn't it gives me the same
intellect increase but it's not as funny you can do this again what's that all about
okay so let's do let's see what the remembrance is i have to imagine this is probably sorcery
right because i mean think about it that was pretty much all sorcery imagining a pretty major
spell winged great horn axe ancestral spirits horn restores fp upon defeating enemies
this is a helmet or is this a talisman this is kind of huge deal how much fp does it bring back
because man we're gonna be needing that talisman it's only about three fp per kill is that worth it
i guess maybe hold on how much does it cost to how much fp does this thing use hard to tell
is that worth using well how much is like a just regular source removed to tell you
fp costs seven okay so this is 12 i get three back per kill which would mean if there's like
three or four enemies i don't know i don't know worth it more just to probably level up into fp
what else are you using your talisman slots for this one i'm not taking off for the rest of the
game this one i could replace because i'm using the magic on the weapon not necessarily sorceries
that much anymore and this is i could probably replace this one i'll get it the heal is pointless
i'll get it let's try it i want it let's try it we'll put it on okay bingo restores fp upon
defeating enemies i replaced the heel very cool well that was awesome oh oh uh ronnie do i have
any uh crunchies i have to be careful i do have the finger blade so i gotta bring it back to ronnie
see what else i have to do i want to test that talisman as well see if it's worth it okay hello
it was the not blithe it seemeth even in my slumber i sensed it i picked it up it is in
my possession is it not the hidden treasure of nokron my thanks finally all the pieces are in
place soon must i begin my journey on the dark path only i may tread but before i leave i shall
entrust you arian inverted statue nice sterling efforts what does that do a strange gift perhaps
but a rare source such as thee would welcome it i'm sure i am certain now fate steered us
to our reunion i must thank torrent too for his part you may leave now it was but brief
but thou gavest me fine service what is it i too and depart on a journey
upon the dark path probably fight this lady so what's that he revealing the hidden form of
carrion study hall reveals the hidden form of the carrion study hall which connects to the divine
tower to unveil the secret fix it to the pedestal of the celestial globe carrion hall i wonder where
that is in like carrion manner right i would imagine probably near the the is a carrion hall
this is the academy this is the carrion hall i would imagine i mean this is isn't this carrion
manner royal grave uh area behind carrion manner and his rise to the two towers to the right
towers over here that's a birch you haven't found it yet so i gotta keep going this way
middle right of luniero here right here right under right there okay
oh yeah this is sick all right we're gonna go we're going all the road and just up there
i don't i got no beef with you guys i have no beef with you guys stop
i gotta go up i'm in the wrong spot i have no beef with you leave me alone there's no beef
thank you i think i think i have to do a different um far is that across into that
big tower area i gotta get up there who is even okay please oh oh what's this oh this is it right
here is it this is literally it this is literally it i thought like i had to go up here i thought
i'd go i'd go up on like that thing and walk across the bridge wow cool i've made it all right
let's keep going put the thing on the pedestal i'll put it on there yet oops what's that all about
i can't oh i can take the statue off all right i'm gonna take it off because i want to explore
without it i i want to go up the stairs without it just gonna do it all over it that could have
been so much better if that character was going like put his arms out and shit like that would
have been awesome let me look before i do that because there could be something here that i need
to do before i do that very possible i need to spend my souls definitely jesus oh my god am i
gonna explore this whole fucking area and then turn the whole area upside down stop walking you
need to use your souls i i will i can't i need to love i don't have enough to level up yet wait
isn't that my friend don't i know this person hey you piece of shit what's up what's up what's
up what's up what's up what's up huh get off the stairs this is so much stupid place to fight you
get off the fucking stairs get off the fucking stairs oh my god get off the stairs it's the
worst place to fight in all of dark souls history get off the fucking stairs i'm not moving till
you get off the stairs i'm not moving till you get off the stairs i'm not moving keep doing that
shit waste all your mana i'm not doing this till you get up get off the stairs what the fuck i
didn't have any blockage oh you're rightfully fucking annoying aren't you oh you're rightfully
annoying aren't you we're gonna have to do a sorcery fight you want to play that game we can
play that game what were you i don't know where you're shooting from oh i see where you are you
piece of shit i see where you are you real piece of fucking work aren't you
you're a real piece of work aren't you oh you've got friends oh look at your friends
this is fair oh i can't summon anybody what the fuck this seems unfair
are you oh run away fine just run away rise are we all the way down
harry and staff where where did she go oh wait unfinished business out here i have unfinished
business where they go up you actually just go up don't jump please i'm not gonna jump
all right i've got i've got them pretty close more of those uh swings that'll be it more swings
and i got it in fact i'm not getting one hit killed by a meteor this is not happening really
no you're gonna drop a chandelier on me or something right i'm not just gonna run forward
yeah it's all a bunch of traps and shit i'm not gonna get killed from yeah okay there you are
you're a real pain in the ass what a pain in the ass get over here oh you were faster than me
you sneaky little shit where are you now not this time you're not gonna get away
magic downpour oh that fp item is actually helping a lot yeah it is downpour
magic down for some of the magic mass that sprays projectiles be cool all right well
now i can level up but let me see what else is okay hold on something up here
oh yeah i see the ladder i see the ladder from come on from what's with this like what's with
this weird glitch from this is dangerous hold on hold on hold on nobody do anything weird
what why can they walk like this oh we're good yeah all right oh shit i got some mana back
that's how that works there better be something good up here all right what's the least the path
of the least resistance here i don't know i'm gonna get spawned on they're gonna climb up
something i gotta be i gotta get myself situated that straightaway right there
boost fp restoration from flask it's really not that big of a deal that's not worth climbing
two ladders for that's not worth climbing two ladders for okay uh that's it nothing else here
i'm just gonna jump down to here i'm gonna go back down i'm gonna go up a little bit more though
be careful wait why uh i do want to go here though because there was another place to go
what is this wait no no no no no this is the way up oh i think i missed something
i think i missed an item maybe not no never mind
okay i think that's it at least well that's cool to get i'll try it out a little bit flip
the thing upside down go back up here and i guess do whatever i need to do for this uh
ron rainy quest ronnie i haven't been here for a few hours what's going on uh with that hat
i lost a bet with uh chat and they said that i had to wear this hat for the next three to six
hours of gameplay um it does it's so stupid when you put this on you take 25 more damage from all
sources uh it's a lot of like speed runners and like like really like hardcore gamers are going
to be using it because your movement speed is like 10 faster so but it's like really bad to
have on right now it's actually a pretty stupid thing to wear for like a first playthrough
and actually it might even be 30 more damage with a 10 movement speed buff
why do they just lie all the time i don't know because it's kind of funny
well i'm just making conversation but oh what's going on with you
oh
i'm gonna get this to 30 and then we're gonna do some more intelligence
let's check it out magic down four i'll try it see what it does
oh actually pretty good area denial i charge it i can charge it that's pretty good denial
right like i can kind of catch people up guard does like no damage yeah but it's probably good
to some area denial okay now let's go for it i already saw this let me check the frames i'm
just curious it's a pretty consistent three percent frame drop for some reason on twitch what's going
on with my connection to your servers what's going on here no no i don't want to do this
area there are hands here i don't want to do it no no no i don't want to do their hands here
i don't want to do it this is my least favorite enemy in the game are you actually back i killed
you already what oh here comes the cheese whiz here comes the cheese whiz what's wrong you guys
wanted me to play worms here it is i don't have any more mana left mask of confidence
am i safe right here there's a knife pointing at me no okay look i gotta get in there and kill
what the fuck what are you looking at this feels like a modded pvp area
i feel like i'm not supposed to be playing here
let's go dodge what the fuck is happening stop getting caught on whatever bullshit you're
getting caught on get out of here with your fingers fucking hand away from me
okay that was cool wait what's that what's that what's that i want to see what that was
what was that i hope this bonfire down here because i want to go back and kill that person
what was up there hold on what's that what is this where am i what was up there what was up there
any items that probably went hidden um very confused uh i need a bonfire i don't think i
want to open this that's kind of scary that's definitely a boss in there all right go back up
and i'm gonna jump off hey hey go back up go back up i can't go back up basket confidence
increases arcane oh not good enough for me oh what the hell's going on here what is this
oh god damn it it's a fucking boss door
or is it what well at least i have that it's gonna be a dragon or something it's gonna land on the
bridge 8k sells his lop but it's not too much to lose what is this like stomach oh Jesus um
i think i can do it i think i can do it i actually think i can do it
and here's why magic down for holy shit that goes real far your moveset it's fucking weird
yikes uh oh you're on a fucking goddamn ledge i can't even do it all right that's the play here
stop do the roll again i'll stagger it
here we go roll do the roll do the roll again i asked for it and i didn't know what you were
doing and now shit's all fucked up i was in a weird spot the roll do the roll do the fucking
roll do the roll now oh is it i'm bad is it is bad do the roll please i think i can do it i this is
hard but i think i can do it i think i can do it i can do it i think i can do it in fact i'm gonna
show you something else here i feel like this is gonna be really really good let's try a few
things here check this out ready watch this are you doing it i don't know because like it's
it's kind of fun maybe though maybe maybe she'll drop something i'm gonna spray this shit check
this out cause a problem it's not a problem how much damage does this do just regular
looks like a rocket c i wonder if i can hit him like right in the stomach i staggered before i
don't i don't know how i'd be right up in there i think got it hey hey fuck you huh hey hey all
right strategize strategy strategy strategy strategy do i have any items that i can use
right now i have i got items right gradually recover fp check this out this is it oh my god
you still have wait ready i'm gonna use the blue shard bingo ain't fucking moving i'm gonna equip
the talisman i'm gonna loretta bow from across the whole map right they're not healing are they
use a rune arc no not worth it i have okay wait oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit
oh the fucking poison the poison fucked with me i i poison build up poison build up i didn't
think i was gonna get poisoned i didn't think i was going to be poisoned i thought it said oh
add poison build up not you will be poisoned sir sir you're gonna get poisoned sir you're going
to be poisoned that's what it needs to say sir you're gonna get poisoned don't tell me poison
build up i thought it was gonna fill the bar by like 70 oh fuck you come on oh oh i had it
if i didn't have if that didn't freak me the fuck out this guy they're dead they're dead in that
fucking two seconds that's shit out of here dude fuck that stupid lock on the lock on makes you
let go like i'm dying to die i want to dodge through this motherfucker not like grab their
back and ride on the ride like a fucking car i can't lock on for that i'm not fat rolling stop
i'm not fat rolling all right this is my last try this is my last try i'm gonna get a full charge
loretta i can't believe i didn't beat that motherfucker like you all know it stupid oh
we had to eat this but it instant poisons you not poison build up build up oh shut up with that
nonsense fuck you
yep you're not gonna fool me with that one are you again don't lock on game sucks i i just gotta
get i just gotta go get my souls that's it i just gotta get my souls and then i'm i'm gonna just
leave i'm gonna leave i'm gonna get my souls and leave i'm gonna get my souls and i'm gonna leave
it's gotta get them they're right here i gotta get grab them they're like close enough to maybe
just like maybe look at them for a second
can you hit one of those fucking moves can you hit that once what was this like weird
strafe jump i kept doing can't fucking see can't fucking see can't even fucking see can't even
fucking see i'm just fucking tilted i seriously just like i would have okay in these games when
you get to a point where you like were a centimeter away from victory it's like every
organ has come out of your body because you like did it you did it but now you have to now you
got to do it again run past i'm not gonna i refuse it's like every organ has been taken out
like rubbing alcohol dumped on it and put back in my body like i beat them i can have i can ride
my horse what i didn't know that when can i when have i ever been able to ride a horse like this
on a bridge where are my souls where the fuck are they where are my souls why are they in this
corner oh my god check this out it's awful it doesn't do shit that's terrible i'd rather do
downpour in fact like i would rather probably just do this just like spray fucking nickelodeon
gac everywhere oh you better believe that strategy are you kidding me we're playing mario kart it's
oil just kind of sucks fine i i don't want to i hate ripping the fucking band-aid off and giving
up you would you are dead you are dead you were dead they were you you were dead it's just the
poison build up that fucking language that was like that language was so incorrect for me that
fucking language what's that remember you're gonna get an epic item come on i'll be back
that's poison build up say it causes wearer too consumable to be poisoned
poison build up i know stop saying it because it's making me fucking angry and i'm angry about it
and i keep seeing it is i'm i'm so yeah it's poison build up first mark of death stargazer
heirloom that's plus five intelligence okay i have a question is this considered a sorcery
or is that just magic intelligence based scaling does that consider it a sorcery
it's a weapon skill so it's not a sorcery it just stacks with intelligence okay so i i'm gonna lose
the potency but i mean that's just gonna make this weapon do so much more damage and gets me closer
to the other stuff but now i scale even more oh my god plus 82 holy shit all right so that's all
it's up here there was something else up here too what was that was like a key item or something
what was it what else was down there's something else here first mark carved into lunar princess
ronnie's discarded what that's her what happened what the hell happened also known as the half
wheel wound of the centipede this curse mark was carved at the moment of death of the first demi
god and should have taken the shape of a circle however two demi gods perished at the same time
breaking the curse mark into two half wheels ranny was the first of the demi gods whose
flesh perished while the prince of death perished in soul alone does that mean so what where do i
bring this i don't know where i'm supposed to bring that back to back to ranny i gotta get the
other half is here uh hold on i want to i want to kill that person is somebody that sorcerer
person i want them to die this person pissed me off royally and i'm not i i've got two pissed
off things happening here and 450 damage oh now i can actually just cheese it this would be easy
i have the flasks hey hey nice dodge
i'm not going down there quietly see how much hell on earth that was
oh come on now where did you go what's that i didn't see that all right so we're all right
all right all right all right i'm gonna go i went that way last time i'm gonna go this way
there's shit over there there's some shit over here well cool man but where are you down there
you lost your fucking mind you lost your goddamn mind who are you shooting at i'm out of ammo
okay i gotta make this jump i can't make what all right oh my god down where do i go over here
i lucidity lucidity all right i got lucidity i don't know what that is i'll look at it later
lucidity punks seriously what assholes so what is down here i didn't do wait this is just this
a lucidity 10 times fast lucidity lucidity lucidity lucidity lucidity lucidity lucidity
lucidity lucidity lucidity anything else you want me to do did i miss okay so i was supposed
to go this way but there was another place i could go remember i went down the elevator and
it was like another area i want to check that first all right so i i did all this but i want
this is another area to go to halfway through the elevator i mean nopers are you saying nopers
yep um yep yuppers actually okay so ready i gotta be can i jump off i can't get off
wait yes i can i can go right through here all right here we go you ready
hey no i gotta go over that all right where is it i'm just gonna show the thing please kill the
fat guy i can't sleep until you kill the back i can't it's too hard i can't lucidity aluviate
alleviates build up of asleep and madness oh good thing it alleviates the build up
okay when i hear the word build up i think of like that's what i think of i don't know that
when i think of the word build up building up to it this doesn't happen instantly you're not here
are the other tower that's number four is it gonna kill me there's a whole roof system here
hold on is this gonna kill me where are my souls even gonna be where are they even gonna be
that's gonna be such a weird place where are they are they gonna be just up on the roof
i can't see from here god damn it i'm not gonna lose 16 000 souls trust me that was a that was a
complex fall joke time is it my phone's dead what time is it 9 46 what did i get the inverted
statue thing i had no idea i don't i actually don't remember i got it from after i beat radan
i went to the meteor place at least the meteor i'm so fucking impatient like i just want to get
out of the tower so bad and i don't want to wait for a fucking elevator i don't want to wait
with the elevator i just want to leave i want to just jump out of the fucking window
i could teleport but i it's right here i could literally just jump off and run
he's gonna smash his computer i'm not gonna imagine if you just heard like
my like desktop was right here and i was like smash smash smash smash no way it's too important
okay i can't jump from off of here just teleport down to this just get out of here
no i would never smash my computer do you understand how how dumb that is
there's like there's tons and tons of money and electronics in there it would be a disaster
that would be a oh we have here another dragon maybe one day there's money in the computer
i mean yeah the parts are worth fucking tens of thousands of dollars i have eight gtx
rtx 3090 tis in there just because i want to make sure that i can run the game at 120 fps
okay so it's this tower right here so what's in here this is open this was closed before so it's
open was this the one that was open or was this the one that was closed you still drop frames
that's not my problem that's not that's not my problem that's not my problem that's not my issue
my internet's fine exclamation point price please snow witch hat oh i got the witch outfit
no bonuses strengthens cold sorcery oh man i don't use that stuff i have to keep
dickhead hat on let me see what it let me see the other stuff i want to see what it looks like
really high magic defense though damn it harry and knight stuff is just all around
it's really good and also the other one too this one uh which one's better are we the cuckoo sir
coat uh it's gonna be killed i have 16 000 souls this is a stupid idea full fit please
pencil river main or underground bullshit not that i'm saying that's not well not bullshit it's
really cool but miniature ranny miniature ranny all resembling ranny the witch unresponsive doll
seems pleasantly cool okay sorry someone else let me just take a look and see the name else is here
doesn't look like it go to the grave you need to talk to the doll i actually i talk to it
incoming drown joke no not with 16 000 souls the comedy meter goes off
at 16k okay sit down here let me get one of those thanksgiving things on your head um
that like what was it fake laughter i didn't want to laugh really hard on camera so i just stopped
talk to the what dogged fellow aren't we or is it merely thy habit to talk to dolls
unexpected any soul to recognize me in this guise but now the cat is out the back cannot
allow thee thy freedoms perform for me a service as recompense eliminate the baleful shadows which
prowl these lands these lands the witch is already studied by the i will not disobedience
in this matter do not disappoint mr potter form for me eliminate eliminate the baleful shadows
baleful shadows the witch is already studied by i will not put disobedience in
does that mean the hell are you talking about like i mean actually these lands here because
it this is where i found the doll who's that is it a dragon
it's like a giant dragonfly what is that oh is that its head that's it is that its head curved
down like that or is that its ass what is that oh what the fuck okay i have too many souls
that thing is really really weird hold on can i eat this with the magic shield i don't want to
do this yet i need to level up first i'm gonna lose all my souls i need 20 yeah okay so i can
come back here though i'm just gonna go we're going to the farm zone and i'm gonna use one
of those things all right check this out i'm gonna use one of those pickled things and just run
around and collect um shit one of these things i haven't used them the entire video game
where are they boost rune acquisition for a time yeah this is my farm zone i wonder how long a time
is seems pretty good not great but i gotta find a new spot it's okay only 25 000 it lasts pretty
long time it's like a minute or two oh fuck you i'm dead that's so lazy wait wait what the
fuck am i whatever uh they're right there it's fine that was a nice farm yeah but you know what
i'm saying it don't matter i got really lazy i know that's my own problem i gotta get some
eye drops some just lubricated eye drops not medicated i'm almost there it's fine i'm stuck
in the middle of this bullshit oh yeah oh hi guys what happened what wrong potion i didn't want to
have to use my actual moves but now you pissed me off i'm like one of the i'm a villain in an anime
i have to use my actual moves now oh i see you have some skill finally that's gonna do it
see you later goodbye let's go to a bonfire we've been talking about anime a lot recently
have you been watching it not really not really what not particularly no need like
it's pretty much it okay goodbye okay stop for a second if you could
vitality here we go let's fight this weird dragonfly dragon bug monster alien thing
i am going to put the flasks differently though i need to get the 10 flasks that's next on the
agenda all right let's go we don't kill these guys yeah yeah yeah yeah but listen to me man
like i'm one of these guys is gonna come up behind me and ruin everything all right let's go
can i get can i line of sight let's see i can line of sight with these bricks good to know
they have splash damage god human bone shard
yeah see what i'm saying get away from me that guy somebody weird animal animals or whatever they
are what the fuck do i do oh shit plus seven oh shit that's a that's a big one i love that
stun i love just stunning so that's a huge deal but no no no no no wait wait wait wait how do
you get up to the mantis thing um in uh in ronnie's tower and ranny's tower the one that you can't go
in yet it eventually opens up after you do ranny's quest line and you can go into the
northern tower there's a teleporter that turns you down here that's bad so you do it
can you do a stone called stunner on camera uh maybe if i maybe eventually if i do a wrestling
thing that that's gonna explode ghost glove wart seven i have a lot of the high-end ones
number 13 can i get a look at me please oh what's that all right so here's the question
there's a cave down here i explored this oh there's weird bugs down here those ants or something
oh god they're spiders oh great what the what i what my eyes got the chills oh they're weird
enemies
ah this is so odd it's so weird these are flying ants shield grease these are wasps
there's a huge one over there plus 10 golden rune times eight wait what did that say
wait a minute what did you what the fuck are you talking about times eight times eight what
holy shit that's insane what's that gonna be is that gonna be like 80 000 runes that's actually
ridiculous okay well let's not lose any lots of health don't you all right you gotta get behind
him he's got like the shield head holy shit okay well whatever well i'm gonna be far away
that was just like a wham wham wham okay all right well i'll just i'll kill him with the magic
that's far away shit this thing doesn't respawn right oh palace room weird architecture
hold on i'm not i'm not gonna go all the way over here but i want to pick up the item
none of the enemies here respawn they just die even the ants okay let's keep going i'm very
intrigued by yeah everyone's respawning very intrigued by this area what hit me for that
much that was almost my whole health bar almost 15 16k down the drain what was that okay i gotta
take this place a lot more seriously not fucking around use the magic i'm a magic
person use the goddamn magic souls are behind him too that's bad holy shit he's moving
oh yeah yeah go go all right what were you hiding i took starlight off shit
the one time where i need the goddamn thing oh there's another one
so unbelievably good it's so unbelievably strong question is getting down there is gonna be a huge
chest wing of astel wrong way andy wrong way andy uh i'm kind of i'm kind of busy right now what is
that sword fashion from a delicate wing strong attack unleashes a wave of enchanted light
unique skill nebula and look at it okay it's like a scimitar that's my my my heart a little bit
whoa look at that it's like as cool as the katana that's as cool as the katana i gotta take a look
at that that could be better heart attack doesn't cost mana either i wonder if it scales with uh
intelligence all right let me what's what do i do i can do a weld i gotta kill this thing right now
because i can i can teleport back and we can go the other way i gotta kill this thing somehow
all right let's go three two one fuck it
jumping r2 is so good especially with some weapons just they just decimate everybody what's
what's back here has to be a reason why this is here surprised dead end how is this gonna hurt
falling yeah even if i'm going i can go the other way i'm looking for a i'm looking for a bonfire
because then i can just travel between the two and the ant bonfire shit i got souls maybe i can
buy something nice okay interesting very very interesting is someone there custom who has it
look birch of vows or i mean i have the this is the my original outfit crafting repertoire
i don't know i guess i'll get it the money are you marking merchants on the map still kind of
not really but i might as well as you mentioned it all right well that was cool something else
uh let's i'm just gonna keep checking out still this granny quest line is so long this is
ridiculous how long this is i got all those ruins too all right i gotta find a place to go
oh jesus hold on so good oh i'm so powerful nothing can stop me
looks to be to me like a boss door of some kind they're giving me a bunch of items i feel like
that's a boss door what is all the way down here so i'm kind of getting all right all right i gotta
be careful i'm starting to get lost i'm i'm lost and i'm in a i'm in a place where i don't know
if i want to be um uh these ones are red you're so susceptible to magic it's not even funny
immunizing horn charm master grace did i hold on let me clear this
master grace i don't know i'll get it i just want to clear this i just want to clear this up
i'm gonna check up here i knew there would be a little weirdos oh you're in every from software
game you do the petrified bullshit you do the petrified bullshit that fills up all the way you've
turned to stone i'm just i just want to take a look i'm just taking a look that's it get out of that
soap number smithing stone okay well we ain't going that way i'm going to go find a bonfire
which you guys saying back here in the river there was i actually i'm gonna go back and upgrade
the katana again because i can i might take a look at the differences between the two there it is okay
all right good night oh what am i saying bobo so here's here's the plan check this out look at
this i got a times eight let's make i'm gonna break them all 40 000 souls it's a big number
all right 55k this will be enough to level up and to upgrade a couple times
30 vigor i'm done with vigor for a little while now we're going back to either dex or intelligence
maybe even some endurance i could level up twice not going back yet never mind i want to see what
was through here this is to go outside over here somehow for some reason right out here so many
people stop oh my goodness just funnel into the door can you please beat the game soon i does i'm
not gonna beat the game probably for like i'll probably another month now where the fuck am i
jesus all right don't be a fucking idiot all right let's take a look i think a good night song for
boba boba the kitty have a good rest see you in the morning boba such a good kitty see you in the
morning watch out for the waterfall that's up in there nothing in here come on oh but why do i get
up there okay what is this so many ways to go that was really weird like that was a horrible
voice crack that was eric cartman you like the game absolutely yeah i think it's great i think
it's fantastic i think it's the best thing that from software's probably ever made i love one of
these oh this is where i couldn't get to last time why do you hate it i don't hate it i gotta
stop before people think that's real what's going on now now what this place is massive
okay we're getting apples and bananas remix are you talking about like the i want to eat eat eat
apples and bananas that's what you mean i like to eat eight eight eight percent bananas
i like to eat well there you go that's the only that's all you're gonna get i'm not doing that
anymore what's down here i never end where am i on the map okay well what the heck jesus oh
shit man no smithing stone what is up here wait did i just come from here no oh oh oh oh
that's the queen if i touch the queen they're all gonna fall all right all right here we go
i need uh i need magic here we're going with i need something with a lot of spread i think it's
magic down for just spam it if we put up this fill the fill the room with it don't fucking just
spam everybody oh holy shit what did i get for that a golden rune that's it just one times 10
110 golden room oh this is plateau's allegory of whatever you said was 10 is it actually no it's
just one okay so this brings me back to here and get the item that i couldn't get before two items
i couldn't get before i think stone
god damn it i gotta go back to the do i actually have to kill everybody here
you can de agro yeah i can de agro by killing everybody in the room is that for de agro
stop there's too many oh i'm just running fuck it who cares it's not that far it is far though
fuck i can't believe i didn't get that it's right here just run an ad while you're doing this i'm
not gonna run an ad yeah if this is a rune arc i'm gonna be pissed all right this better be
a sorcery that's the best sorcery in the game run an ad fine all right okay fine i'm gonna run
i'm gonna run two minutes of ads no people are gonna leave all right by the time you get back
i will i will be by the time the ads over i will be okay uh here we go at the home depot
why did i do that i just i just made a bunch of people leave it'd be so funny if i fucking died
and i was dead by the time they got back that would be kind of funny i wish you didn't have to
i wish you didn't have to i wish you could sit there and let it stay on the you died screen
it's how goddamn funny would that be if i was on the you died screen like talking a bunch of
shit to chat and everything all right it's down here through here i got it i got it i got it i got
it i got it i killed everything they're not gonna spawn yeah i killed queen i didn't run five ads i
ran one minute what's going on did i go the wrong way i went the wrong way how what where where's
the right fucking way where's the right way go back to the right okay i got this way watch out
for the queen jeremy how can i avoid ads at the top of the hour um i haven't i know how
just stay and watch i don't run them ads at the top of the women ads at the top of the hour
okay don't fuck it up celestial do what a waste what a waste what a waste
okay so now where do i i'm kind of now what now what now what i don't know back to the other grace
back the other way you agree i would love to look at my map but there's 500 fucking people
aggroed your grace bye bye i'm just trying to de-aggro these guys i think i was successful
okay so here's the bonfire this is the other bonfire now let me see if there's another way i
can go that's not this way it's not okay so i'm going to lead to believe i'm led to believe that
i'm going to go back to the other bonfire the one that was over here ansel river downstream no
which one i believe it was downstream imagine if i had a voice like this it'd be so
the hours would melt away so much quicker than the way that i talk now
my chaps am i going chaps am i going the right way i don't remember trying to find out where that
is oh i think if i were to go further down for which way it was ansel river main i think it was
you tell me where to go i'm not going to stop doing that you tell me where to go i'm not going
to stop go to the main and turn right if that person's lying i'm going back to british accent
cringe i was wrong i'm led to believe that you're getting the completely incorrect the ant place is
down river so i go to here go down to the right path i'm telling you that i'm punishing that
person 5000 people are leaving you're losing viewers it's so funny losing viewers because
i'm doing like a english accent that's so funny doing an english accent and people like i'm fucking
out of here i'm leaving man okay so i haven't been down this way maybe i have i don't know
all these tunnels look exactly the same like gone i dude i don't know i'm just gonna go in
a direction is run i actually don't fucking know okay this is right i have not been this way
melted mushroom come back okay if you have me in like a just come back what i did an english
accent and 500 people left more than that almost a thousand people left just come back come back
what what's the problem do you have a problem come back come back wait i've already been out
no i this is new this is very new another one of these people sitting in a chair
but dragon kin soldier of nox stella well his whole body's like
all right when he does it in the middle he goes he does it twice your body is so weird man i can't
hit it he's like missing parts of his body holy shit that hurts a lot
fuck holy smokes the fuck out of here so strong this weapon is so good it's unreal how good that
is that shit does 400 damage every time i did it now i mean the problem with this which i have
to be careful is it takes i kind of takes a second use the ash of war to buff its magic scaling
here's the crazy part right this is the most ridiculous part about this weapon
i have not been building this character all intelligence really i mean i put like i put
like 10 what 11 points in dexterity if i had just 50 points in intelligence this might be just stupid
you're over leveled i don't i'm only level 70 i'm not that high when i because people
okay his thing people said i was under leveled for radan and i was like 55 for radan this boss
is an earlier game boss well that makes sense too this area is but that this area has to be
after radan though because this is part of the witch's quest or am i just out of my mind and
i just found this isn't the quest this is not part of the quest oh okay so there's just there's
just a boss down here very cool well what was the spell i got some kind of weird like frost spell
or something didn't i what was it didn't i get a new spell frozen lightning spear oh it's an
incantation okay well that was cool that was very cool this is an area that you can get too early
this game is insane this guy's just down here game's insane great ghost glove ward
there's probably only like four of these in the game okay well that's awesome uh
should i just leave so much more down here uh yeah i gotta keep doing the what's what am i
even look what am i doing down here for rena's quest but what am i actually doing here i don't
know to go kill the shade thing she talked about is it down here let's go the other way
oh all right um so i need 29 i'll be fine so if i were to go go back over here where was that
area with all the red bugs and shit and my throat's been kind of annoyed cancel river main to main
and then head into that okay yeah my throat's been although i'm just talking a lot
i'll probably get some water in a minute here okay so like over here this is where i came from
so from here it was another way wasn't there yeah there was okay there was another way to go
that's right that's a whole huge area that i just was there for like an hour and a half
i don't know why am i fighting these people how long am i going to play tonight
um was like another hour or two couple hours maybe a little more i think oh if i still have
gas all right so i went through those doors that was where i went through there was that big
ugly guy i did not go this way so we'll check this out you're gonna go kill the fat guy before
the end of the stream possibly i don't know all right what else is down here waterfall
am i gonna die holy shit it goes down it goes down it doesn't go down man no it goes down
okay so not there it too no it don't like my favorite part of that video is the
when he leans back like that he goes like it goes okay so back through here
this is just kind of taking me back to the area that i was before i'm right at the ants
i need a better gamer chair holy shit this thing sucks this thing actually sucks
like a this is like concrete elbow pads they'll go this way i didn't go this way you're right
don't think i did i got a lot of upgrades to do too what do you want what do you want ugly
i need a much better gamer chair an actual really comfortable one that has a good support and
everything moxtella eternal city wait have i been here like i've been here have i been here
oh i don't think so i guess not i haven't okay damn there's more shit down here
i gotta pee so bad i gotta pee this time see you guys in like two minutes oh i don't know
if i'm like junking up my voice but my throat is killing me i don't know why it's only one side of
my throat too am i screaming too much maybe i got some water though i'll be all right we'll go for
like another hour or two we'll see what happens at the end of this because once i get to wherever
i need to go here i'll try to complete some more of this quest line i don't know how much longer
it's gonna go it'll be a long time for all i know okay i did get some more water though i want to
make sure it's cold i got an ice cube in here you're too tight no i'm good i'm good i'll be good for
like another half hour at least and then we'll be live again tomorrow we'll do it again tomorrow
then after tomorrow i'm gonna have to start to figure out what i want to do with this game
we'll see i i really don't know i'm still having a bunch of fun and i'm still finding new things
and finding more reasons to play oh that person riding a bug can i use my horse down here time
tomorrow probably on the same town for about four o'clock pacific four p.m pacific uh i could almost
level up again and i think i'm gonna just keep putting in intelligence try to get to that 52
i can't use the horse here i go up into the building or right this way there is so much
content there really is i don't it's like it's kind of overwhelming in a way it's just it's
i so much to do there's so much going on oh that hurts oh that hurts a lot
it's very overwhelming yeah it's every and every area is so different and fresh it is every area
just feels so and that's why it's almost hard to remember what's going on because everything
is so different there's so much going on that it's almost like wait this is a whole new zone
you almost you don't even give a shit what happened like two zones ago even though
that's important stuff going on there it's like that ant place that i just was there might be
something else there but it's like whoa look at a new pretty area i may i may as well have never
gone there to the ant place it just constantly a drip feeding new crazy places it's ridiculous
in a good way obviously not in a bad way right like in a very much a good way
germ of the ruins germ of the ruins i got him what's my take on asiago bagels um they're good
nothing wrong with them they taste good i'm gonna go over here i think i have enough to level up
i will do that this soft cap at 40 yep how do i compare this to bloodborne i kind of can't
it's uh it's actually becoming very difficult to do that for a few reasons the first most important
reason is bloodborne is a ps4 exclusive game that came out that's locked at 30 fps that was made in
2013 or 2014 or something right i mean that i consider that to be one of the best games i've
ever played in my whole life if not the best single player game i've ever played we all know
that we're all aware of that problem is this game comes out and i would say completely blows it
completely out of the water a thousand percent technically speaking it runs way better right
there's so much more to do there's so much more going on but it's like it's just it's kind of
unfair to say that because this game came out like look at eight years seven or eight years after
bloodborne did if bloodborne were to have if this was elden bloodborne right maybe i don't know
we'd be having a different question we're having a different conversation runs better yeah blood
borne was locked at 30 fps and all the time it would drop i remember that dropped down to like
25 frames a second a lot of time so it this game runs a thousand times better 2015 yeah well you
know what i mean it's been seven years since that game came out it's a shield how's this poison
build up if you attack with it oh is it alive damn what's the damage mitigation on this is
this thing's alive 100 physical guard boost yeah cool why does everything have to be alive in this
game it's kind of creepy isn't it yeah i i have already played through more areas in this game
than bloodborne times two already what is going on up here i feel like i've played through bloodborne
twice already and i'm not even like what halfway through the game why these guys electrified
it's killed each other okay well whatever i'll take it okay not even half yeah there's no way
they were not working on this game for the last like 10 years it's impossible i know that they
already had all these assets after making dark souls 3 and bloodborne and sekiro they had a
shitload of assets no fucking way this game took them three to four years to make it this game
has probably took them like seven or eight years to make it there's just too much to do there's too
much in the game there's too many things to see the game is too big you're gonna do the electric
explosion thing holy shit oh they have shields on their faces okay well let's change that then
okay can i get behind them whoa this game is worth 60 this game is worth probably
this game is worth probably 150 like this game the actual value of the video game is probably
worth like 125 dollars maybe even more this is like three video games like you're getting
all three lord of the rings movies in one game and you don't have to wait like three four years
between them like you know what they could have done and this is i'm gonna okay time to get from
software some some praise here they could have had like elden ring become like an episodic thing
right if it's like oh yeah elden ring part one we're seeing that a lot lately like oh it's like
the first part and the more will come later they could have done it in three parts they could have
done it in two parts it could have been like elden ring part one and elden ring part two
because there's that much content to do it episodic i know i say it weird
oh more stuff in the shop the whatever the dlc they do to this game is actual full-on
would be like the fourth or fifth dlc in dark souls 3 you're getting a game that has the amount
of content that would take probably five dlcs for dark souls 3 i don't even know what they're
gonna do for dlc it's already here it's already in the game i'm playing it right now final fantasy
7 remake that's a good point that's exactly kind of what i was talking about it's just
it's they they could have done that they could have actually just released it like in two or
three parts not saying the final fantasy 7 is a bad game to remake whatever it's just
i think they could have done that
final fantasy 7 remake is a bad game well i didn't say you did
i do it should i do it what do you think should i do it i'm doing it i thought those were statues
these are people they're not npcs either nox monk greaves all right so what is it what's in the
chest purple night maiden and swordstress puppets cool very cool fireplace this is literally the
area i just was looking at oh my goodness i can jump down be careful i didn't think i was gonna
be able to make that i i honest to god it's it's it's kind of bizarre to think that like what how
did they make sakiro if this was still going on i know they have two teams right who made sakiro
and who made this member it was like dark souls 2 wasn't uh oh i thought it was frozen i thought
i didn't know could come get me what the dark souls 2 team must have made sakiro that was so
much easier yeah because they had like an a team a b team and the b team would work on stuff while
the a team was working on something else all right i really hate to say a team and b team
but you know what i mean not like oh a like gray and better but like just two two teams
sakiro was still directed by miyazaki though yeah how does he have enough time to do any of this
like i'm just a streamer you know what i mean like i'll like get up in the morning
i don't know time is two o'clock i don't know what what am i doing today i got streaming
this guy's got like holy shit man the amount of work ethic and the amount of time and like
genius level iq to like have that much time and dedication and passion to do stuff like this it's
ridiculous in the morning you're still on boston time uh 2 p.m early bird yeah the early bird
special i don't know i'm at least happy that we get to experience just think about this this might
be a little sad for some of you but don't be sad it's literally probably one of the worst games
ever played i'm sad now only two hits gorsh gorsh gorsh okay so what i was gonna say
is this is gonna make people probably a little sad this these from software games have all come out
in this kind of like what like 10 like what 15 year span when did demon souls come out on ps3
2009 so it's been 12 13 years we are we are experiencing those of you that have played
these games a lot those of you that have played all of them which i have right or a lot of you
guys have to here's the generations that are coming after us because these games are so
interesting and they're so unique and they're so uniquely made and they're so weird like in
10 to 20 plus years people are going to be younger people right like in 20 years younger
people will be playing these as kind of this crazy wow well can you look at all look at how
ridiculous this was look at how much fun this was imagine like this this was coming out and
you get to play it right when it released that kind of shit right so many kids are going to be
playing this in 20 years and having those kind of conversations like the way that we have conversations
almost about like um even stuff like ocarina of time right or even before that but it's not even
the same though it's a boomer thought all right i hope i don't die that's worth it because we get
to play these as they come out and that's cool but being able to like play all the from software
games that at least since kind of the demon souls era of them making games it's going to be really
interesting because they're going to play them and what does it hate them or something like
they're going to die they're going to fall off a cliff or something and be like grandpa i don't
understand that's right you little fuck now you go back and get those souls like it's going to be
correct what if they what if this is like they think it's dumb get good grandson your grandson
died to pinwheel you'll see you can sit there and laugh all right i'm afraid to open this door but
let's do it i feel like i'm missing a potential bonfire uh-huh just electrocute yourselves to
death hurry up how many people are in this room how many how many are here i see that globe i see it
i see it you're not going to fool me on this one here we go jesus man what the fuck
can't move oh yes it can 20 000 souls right now i just got 10 000 souls from this room
oh my goodness is this a farm room it seems like a farm room my god pick your poison
i gotta figure out what to do with those that's the respect currency right you need a certain
amount or something i can upgrade the katana i think twice give me another bonfire or something
or a shortcut i thought it was somebody hiding waiting to ambush me i didn't know it was one of
those nice just let him have his dung it's my dung it's mine i don't know where the bonfire
do i have to actually run up here if this is a fight looks dangerous oh oh oh let's go bud
do something else do a different move did you seriously lose all right all right all right
okay damn he's just over there doing party tricks yeah he was just messing around oh you're looking
this way never mind can you parry with this katana i don't can you i don't think so hey funny man have
you beaten uh radan yet yes i have this is another legendary moon of nox stella is that the item look
i'm looking for versus memory slots not a big deal it's not a big deal that's all the way up
here though another way i didn't go that's the only thing that's up here not a big deal
not a big deal at all ah this way right i hear some something growling oh yeah i've guys i've
been streaming and doing youtube for over 10 years but you know that half my material is just
calling back to other things that i've done over the last 11 years we've reached that stage where
i can do a widget it's just re-reference these things that's like the whole thing now
i'm gonna get attacked by something there's a whole nother area down there
this endless content hog where am i now oh that's good oh dude where where am i now they made too
many games there's like four games in here and there's like 10 different systems my nose just
started bleeding after that okay well um i would really like a bonfire that would be amazing
actually is that what's that i'm gonna go in there you're close okay all right don't fight
the ants they're scary they actually are very much so i saw how much damage they do but did
they say how much damage that i do quite a bit i love this thing i think it's so ridiculous
this ring must be so old the elden ring and yeah probably a few thousand years old
what the bloodborne spiders those are awful as well what do you think is the scariest insect
i don't know scary like i am like irrationally afraid of this or scary like this thing is
terrifying and can like hurt people because i guess probably a centipede or something
or like a uh like a yellow jacket like hornet because hornets are just mean they're just
actually mean angry little shitheads really hey this wasn't your fight those guys suck
i wouldn't make it a day in this universe you none of us would make it a day in any of these
universes we've had this conversation before oh i wish i was in this universe but like all this
magic and shit you want to be in a universe where hold on oh fucking god i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead
and that was hard hitting how do i get back here this is all the way up
holy shit um oh my fucking god this is so far away i have to run the entire thing
wait is it under here yeah it is just under here all right well i don't want to die i don't want
to lose that many souls i gotta play really passive here you look so menacing i don't like it
i gotta play slow and passive i gotta play flat i gotta play passive this is something here i need
it there's something right there i need it but what about the souls i'll be fine don't worry
what did you get the fucking frying pans from i see a frying pan guy now we're good i i want
what is in there's something in here there's nothing even in here did i already get all this
there's nothing here i already got it oh you gotta focus all right yeah yeah yeah yeah let's go
so these like snails oh what are these snails snakes they're so strange those are weird those
are weird you're you need to die you're too weird it was gonna strike everything they attack that
poison build up didn't even get me the souls i know i know i know i know i know i'm just
getting distracted i know shit i'm getting ganged up on nothing here is an invisible wall
i don't think so maybe that thing scales so ridiculously with intelligence it's not even
funny it's just such a disgusting move it's a it's a disgusting move all right so where
yeah i gotta go up here then it's down yeah let's follow the river there's a chest in here
what was that sound sorcery sorcery it's a regular item that's actually i think i didn't even have
one of those minus 33k andy i'm gonna be fine look you didn't think i planned this this guy
is freaking out down here and i can shoot him from up here because i'm kind of scared actually
it's all the river i'm not gonna attack any of these things you are a dickhead it's a golden
room right there all right i made it where are they oh stupid oh oh no i almost fell what the
fuck dude stop get out of here please i'm a little scared i'm a little scared an item down there
okay i want to get that that was a cool kill it kind of was wasn't it okay i got everything i
need to get that was cool let's keep going uh i wanted to go over here because there's another
place to go up i wonder if there's up there i get a um bonfire i hope so see what this does
what's the moonvale level plus four or actually plus five i think uh plus five thank god
thank i definitely have enough to do i have some of those plus tens oh yeah how many should i do
need 30 000 30 something thousand right all right 35 inch which actually is
40 something inch right 43 intelligence i'm getting there the doll all right
all right
through her body away she's anti two fingers i'm gonna stretch
oh whoa whoa no no i'm on your team
i think i have three i do have three all right eight and two sounds good to me um so
now what i could go back down and keep going down the river i could go through here
what level is what i am level 73 these guys again get away from me let that build up
oh yeah yes jerma slay thanks baleful shadow wait is that that's blade it's bad oh my god
okay oh my god you have 100 trillion hp that wind up oh you dude fuck you twice
fuck you three times and bro okay all right he's got yeah he's got a cool move set oh that's a lot
of souls to lose i don't have to fight him do i i could upgrade yeah i could upgrade the katana
that make this a lot easier let me grab my souls i think i can just run away and i just run and go
put another point in the town i feel like i had the got the hang of the video let me try it one
more time that was that was sloppy i always do so well in the first try and then i just get in my
head uh all right let's go i don't need to be a hero i'm gonna go uh upgrade the tunnel
okay get the souls and run i'll get them i'll get them i'm gonna run bye bye i'll come right back
jerma you have very noticeable bags under your eyes that's the lighting actually not as bad as
you think they are lighting all right i think i can do it twice yeah i can do it twice so that
would bring this that would be a lot better i can do it twice yeah hell yeah absolutely hell yeah
that's that's that's now i'm gonna be hurting them i wasn't doing that much damage to him before and
now you bet your ass i'm gonna be hurting him we're at b b scaling now he's fucking dead
and so i don't have to keep freaking out with the souls let me buy oh yes i am going to give the
bell to that lady so i got another one it was the greatest food spot on the strip uh that would be
hash house ago go at the link they have a blue cheese ham uh blue cheese cheeseburger there and
it's just it's unbelievable how good it is uh i'm gonna buy buy an arc as well i don't have any
souls i'm not gonna use it because i think that upgrading the sword a couple times is gonna make
this fight much easier i'm also going to no yes all right that was this one here
blue cheese cheeseburger sounds good oh it is all right so now i got i'm ready to play i've
upgraded the weapon twice the little chip damage i was doing to him is now going to be
real damage and i'm going to really kill him all right let's go i am now prepared this time
let's go buddy a lot of unnecessary damage here
whoa what happened is that poison or something he's still hard to kill
there's a dot he has very varied swings but there's a lot of telegraphing on them i'll get it
he has a bleed tick oh that piece of shit all right let's go let's go
okay let me drink this too while i'm out here that will help he's got fire bleed on his sword
what a punk i'm all fucked up now again isn't that insane the first try i dodged almost every
single fucking one of these like perfectly and now it's like i i can't even fucking i'm like
trapped in a fucking bag i can't get out it's so weird why that happens you know that's so
strange i got him down to like 40 health first try and then it's just like he's now he's just
killing me instantly it's so weird i think it's just like i just don't care right when you when
you first see a boss for the first time be like i don't give a shit if i lose or not like i who
cares i'm like trying too hard i don't care kill me kill me right now you prick
like can you i'm trying to backstab him i can't get it i'm trying i feel like i'm right behind
him can i i feel like i was right behind him wait for the jump attack yeah he does like the here i
come swing and then the jump i try to get behind him well i wonder can i stagger him maybe i should
just do jump attacks i'm not gonna go for it i'll try to kill him and all right buddy that's a big
deal oh come on i thought i got around it shit he jumps fuck i thought it was a swing
fuck these stupid fucking cinder blocks in the way is the heal again that's the strat man
that's the strat he's gonna get the backstab this is easy now that's the strat yeah that's this is
no that makes this fight no problem yeah oh yeah okay yeah all right okay so that this is farewell
my dear i'll blide discarded palace key this is this is like escape room levels of how much more
shit do i have to do there's more to do let me see what the fuck else do i have to do here
what else is in here is this just this area i did not think this was gonna be this crazy i thought
this was literally gonna be just like go take this item here take that item there take that item there
and then maybe fight a boss this has been like five straight hours of just doing one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve opens the treasure chest pass down to carrion
princesses it is said to be found in the grand library of rael lucaria with her mother ronala
going to the grand library that was cool he's gonna hit a hit a real cool move i almost kind
of wish that he didn't do that move that frequently because um i really like that fight he was really
cool oh this is all the way down here now lake of rot this looks like a boss this looks like a big
boss don't think i want to do this right now uh lake of rot let's go to the academy right library
brand library take care of yourself man no i'm all right i'm good i will say if we get to another
i'm probably this is that chest this is this chest what it's this one behind the boss
dark moon ring it's another key it's that chest i okay very cool very cool very cool
ring of lunar princess randy's cold oath whoever thou mayst be take not the ring from this place
the solitude beyond the night is better mine alone okay i'll be honest with you guys i open
to fucking guide up i see i can see everything obviously i didn't start cheating until it got
to a point where it was like okay now i don't know what the fuck i'm doing only since like the last
brb was i actually using it and i wasn't even using it i would look over and see what you guys
had to say fake reactions well where do i go next hold on collect the miniature randy doll and
talk to the grace until it speaks bro what happened what do i have to do i have i swear
to god i promise i have not really been using this shit at all it's fair i i know it's fair
because that was how we've been working on this together i only have it over here in case i need
it just in case we couldn't figure it out yeah look how many times have i opened it up and said
oh yo that's where i need to go right i don't i'm just this is just in case i'm not even using it
i'm not even using it i promise since the last brb i'm so i swear to god i had it open
and i was like no i'm not gonna use it and then i just looked at it for a second close it right
now i don't i'm only going line by line i'm not reading what happens next you felt guilty that's
why i can't lie to you guys can't lie to you again we don't wrangle us in no because look
i'd go like this i'd go oh shit i just got that item that's where i need to go and then people
go oh yeah you do have to go there yep yep and i go where what one is that you just reminded the
teacher of homework all right so now what i'm not going to look over here because i don't want to
i'm not going to look at it i told you i'm not going to use it so what do i go i'm not going to
look at it see you guys are even doesn't really matter you guys are writing all the answers
anyways within 10 seconds of me picking the item up okay go back to lake of rot i'm not looking at
this guide fuck that guide i don't want it anymore in fact i'm gonna i'm gonna click it out i'm gonna
click the x i got it why is he manipulating us i'm not i've actually genuinely not looked at it i've
been i'm just telling you i have it just in case we need it back to rot lake oh go back to the
lake rot see i didn't even look over here you know him that was legit i was like well how the
fuck am i supposed to know what i'm doing i only opened it just in case because it was like holy
shit this is turning into like kind of a convoluted crazy thing okay here we go spirit tuning this i
don't i think this thing sucks i'm definitely going to do oleg or should i should i do mimic
or and get mimic up all the way do the mimic the mimic is broken dude please just do it it's souls
i'm gonna sell some shit it seems kind of crappy some of this shit is really cool but i'm never
going to use it start getting rid of stuff this stuff is so cool but i'm not going to use it on
this character ever three of these yeah give it to the arrows these i can get a lot for these
don't sell all the weapons no i'm not just the ones i know i'm not going to use
like i'm i physically will never be able to put this on it's cool but i'll never be able to use it
two thousand getting rid of doubles too relax relax relax we're in storage i i want to i want
the souls all right let's go let's do it let's go let's go rot lake rot lake rot lake arm for
five minutes no but i'm not going to use them what am i going to use those when am i going to use
those please take the spin off of your staff it's too late so you're saying go down here
this is really cool looking i love the way this looks this is like ghostbusters too
uh that's not gonna work rot lake i'd like just this has got to be something cool up here right
no uh can i use my horse no i need like anti-rot gear is it is it immunity or robustness which
one is it probably immunity right immunity yeah it's the best thing i have
okay the foot soldier tabard is the best thing i have for that
all the horns are scarab okay soldier gauntlets soldier greaves okay now just run across the lake
to like where how do i get this off i need soap so i can't use the horse here um guys kill me
i get it kill me i get it run and tank it run towards the statues okay i have those like
ballaces things alleviate scarlet rot build up and cures rot i can make so many of these can i
i can only make two i make soap should i just make a hundred of these okay um i'll try the soap
first here we go so i gotta get that item i didn't fucking do anything that doesn't do that didn't do
anything that didn't do anything i just made 20 soaps for no reason that's a plus eight
smithing stone i can get the town of the eight um whatever just run around who cares read that
one in your guide i don't have i have i have not been using a guide ever the only time i used it
was when i opened it because it looked like this was going to get confusing this quest i've played
50 hours of this game without a guide we've been you and i have been talking and trying to figure
out what the fuck man where do i go i haven't even used it nobody said dude it's really cute
even you've been pretending what like you don't know where to go but we can see the reflection
of the guide on your forehead i swear to god i'm i want to experience the game
let me ask you this do you really think i'm using a guide if i didn't know what a sacred tier did
until literally yesterday do you think i'm using a guide if i didn't have the physique flask until
40 hours into the game do you think of what i'm just i don't what do you think what are
you talking about i'm dead all right i got the items over here i didn't know that sacred tears
were in churches until like seven game like 12 game hours ago you're getting a tactical advantage
all right so just tank it and run i got the items over there we're gonna go get the items over here
an item run what don't you think doesn't the rock grease just sound like a big fat guy is like
cooking food for you what's that rock grease it's healthy it's fine rock grease to me sounds like
they didn't like change the fryer later oil and i have something about it like i don't care
like that's kind of like that's weirdly appetizing to me i don't know why is that strange i don't know
like something about like oh oh like grease i don't know i don't know something about it maybe
i think that sounds good somehow in a cartoon pretend way you know what i mean i was just
just seeing if there was any items over there everyone relax you sound delirious just get to
the ball i'm i'm just telling you it's a cartoon world i'm talking about i'm not going to go put
like rot grease on my hot dog i'm not going to put rot grease on like my cheeseburger later i'm
just saying like uh grease like rot grease just sounds like something like a big fat cartoon
character would put on his hot dog and in that world in that context i'd be like it's that's
not bad wait what the fuck just happened what did i just step on i just drained the lake of rot
it's still rotted what happened i summoned platforms are they still are they going to be
there now permanently read your guide i shouldn't have even said anything because like i just
i opened it just in case like i needed it and i've never used that shit you know i've been
playing without it and stuff but like and everybody knows that we're just like hanging out
now everybody thinks i'm a guide andy and i'm not you told us not to tell online chat you
betrayed yourself but i actually haven't been using it everybody in offline chat knows i opened
the guide but i haven't been using it i haven't used it you know it i haven't i'm not using a
guide i'm not i'm not i'm not doing that fuck probably gonna wash that off stop jumping oh
my god he's delirious i i'm trying to get up here there's nothing i thought it was a button
warming stone warming stone any more buttons there's gotta be like another button over here
somewhere right there is that a strat jesus jesus
use the soap use the soap use the soap too late now this is gonna stand up this thing's gonna
stand up yeah it is gonna stand up it's a rotted dragon dragon can rot how are you supposed to
fight this guy down here how are you supposed to fight that guy all right i'm almost at the end
soap cleans off the effect literal brain rot no it's not brain rot that if this doesn't clean
this this guy i want that person timed out for one second i'm up for one second you don't have the
effect yet it doesn't work on the effect either i tried it all right i need to do i need to go
that way because that's what i was told i needed to do and yeah we're gonna end the stream don't
do that yet idiot go on that way on that way and i'm going to those two statues use the pellets i
don't want to use them uh we're streaming elden ring tomorrow four o'clock stream is going to end
very very very soon oh fuck you now it don't matter just go no it doesn't really actually
matter either way no i think there's a platform to jump on and touch right here though i'm going to
do it already got that one is there another one over here somewhere like so whatever just go to
the statue there's a button here there is hey hey whoa whoa whoa whoa i don't want to go up here
hey oh shit it's it's supermarket sweep i gotta find as many items i can right now before i die
hmm guide say r1 r1 l2 r1 r1 r1 start
oh that alabas what is that where is it alabaster lord sword the great sword
this thing is fucking ugly
seems kind of really good though this is an ugly ass sword though it looks like shit that's really
cool i think stone nine major decision needs to be made here soon anything on the other side
of that probably not all right play mario golf next uh thursday i i'm not gonna play mario golf
like that's just not gonna happen like i don't know if i played mario golf with a bunch of other
streamers or something that might be fun but i'm not just gonna play it okay that i i think i'm
gonna die if i fall here can i even get down and how do i get down from here at least on the right
and that um how do i get down your ladder just play it alone in total silence of course you can't
summon the horse here there is a ladder this goes this way what's over here no no no no i need it i
need it i need whatever it is what was it smithing stone this way made it all right so you want me
to go in here what was i in here for still doing ronnie's quest all right this is this is just
gonna go on forever isn't it i'm not checking the guide i'm not using a guide there's an item
back here i'm so lazy i'm literally just gonna do this you're looking for a coffin down there
we're gonna do it tomorrow because it is way too late i want to go in there though real quick
just really quickly who cares if i get the rod i don't care i want to go in here all right yeah
chest right here that's so cool that key leads all the way back to that library
all right that's it i'm gonna stop it right here i'm gonna sit at the fire i'll see you guys
tomorrow i'm gonna go eat some food i'm gonna rest my voice for a little bit because it's
kind of getting a little junky i will see you guys tomorrow let me put on the credits
we're at 4 pm the pt so how i haven't really done i didn't do any of the main kind of quest
line today did i just kind of running around doing this stuff i really like this area this
is a really cool spot how much more realistically percentage wise like where am i percentage wise in
the game realistically 30 to 40 40 maybe 50 that's ridiculous you're legit like 50
that's crazy so this really is like 100 plus this is a 100 plus hour game on a first playthrough
without seeing everything that's ridiculous the game took me about 80 hours to fully explore it
i believe i'm like 48 49 hours in that's still in the 30 to 40 plus hours are you liking the
game yeah i mean i think it's it's ridiculous it's really easy to get overwhelmed but i think what
i have to start doing is i didn't do this yesterday and this is where we're gonna i did it today is
i picked four or five things that i wanted to go do specific areas i wanted to go look at
and just did those and if something led to another thing if that thing led to another thing i did
that too uh yesterday i kind of just was wandering around i got like lost and i didn't really have
any direction or anything but i uh i definitely like the idea of picking a few places to go
but yeah thanks for watching guys see you tomorrow four o'clock pacific same thing elden ring after
tomorrow's stream we're gonna have to evaluate what i want to do with this game i'm gonna have
to evaluate what the plan is because i don't want to just stream elden ring only so the stuff i'd
like to do we'll find out after tomorrow are you gonna drop it after the stream tomorrow
i don't know i don't think so i may um maybe we sprinkle in some mario golf go back to it
problem with coming back to it and this is the problem with all souls games
my fear of not playing this game for more than two or three days
coming back to this game a week or two later you just you're gonna get your ass kicked and it's
gonna be hard to get back into the swing of things to remember where anything was
to have the timings down it's it's rough to come back to a from software game
if you don't play it for like a few weeks so if i were to stop playing it every day or every stream
they would it would have to be a case of all right we're gonna do mario golf and then like
like the next day we're gonna play elden ring two days in a row right they're gonna be a lot of
streams i think for me to continue to want to play this but we'll see i mean i might just keep
going as of tomorrow as well we'll see i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll pick up right here
take care of yourselves see you guys soon have a good one really important before i go
did the frame drop stop and if they did when they kept going the whole way even up until like right
now did they actually get better or has it still been happening maybe like an hour ago
it weren't as bad as they were a few minutes ago yeah so this is definitely not an internet
problem for me yet like one o'clock in the morning no way yeah now i confirmed it a few times anyways
hopefully that whatever routing issue or server issue that's happening with twitch
i really hope that gets resolved because that would suck all right good night see you tomorrow