What's going on guys, it is Jerma. I'm going to start this video out. This is a gameplay commentary on Badwater as an engineer, but before that I want to give a quick update on the giveaway that I am currently doing on this channel.
I want to thank everybody for subscribing, even if you just want the hat, even if your only intention is to get the hat. I don't care, I'm glad that you guys came to check the channel out.
I hope more of you come and I hope you tell your friends and your family and your family's family about the channel. No, but thanks a lot guys.
The update that I want to give to this giveaway is a guy by the name of Smokin' Jojo Davis decided to give me a Plants vs. Zombies bucket hat.
And he wants me to give that away also with the Honcho's headgear. So I'm going to be doing two giveaways on Saturday. One of them is going to be the Honcho's headgear and the other one is going to be the Plants vs. Zombies bucket hat, courtesy of Smokin' Jojo.
So if you see him in game, give him a thanks, give him a shout out because he's a cool guy. So keep subscribing if you haven't subscribed already because there's going to be more giveaways like I said.
I'm going to start giving away potentially even Steam games every month so you want to stick around for that.
So here is the gameplay commentary right now. Like I said, this is on Badwater. Defense on Badwater.
Playing a engineer with the regular sentry gun, the Jag, and the Frontier Justice. I love the Frontier Justice. I don't think I'll ever go back to the regular shotgun, ever.
But I'm a little late here. I started a little too late. 30 seconds left. I lost about half the time just kind of with my thumb up my ass in there setting up the recording.
But I'm a little nervous right now. I think, you know, why am I even being an engineer? I should probably just switch classes.
But I say I'll put it over here on the left. It'll be okay. No, okay. There's an engineer's nest already built there.
So I think I'll come up here into this little ledge up here on the left. No, there's a mini sentry there. The round starts.
So I just put it over here on this ledge. And I think I'm just going to switch classes after this anyways.
A few people come out. It kills them. And you'll see what happens here. I get shot in the face. I go, time to switch classes.
This is a bunch of bullshit. Whatever. I'm just going to go play like a heavy or something.
But my sentry gets a few more kills and I look over and I say, hold on a second.
The engineer that was there was repairing it and he upgraded it to level 2. So I say I'll give it another shot. Why not?
I'll just go back out here. Who knows what's going to happen.
And I'm not going to be able to commentate on this next part because the sentry kills way too many people for me to even tell you what's going on.
So I get it to level 3 and I don't have any metal left. I'm like, oh god, I've got to turn around and go get metal.
So it kills this heavy that comes out. I turn around to get some metal.
Hopefully I'm thinking, please, please, please, please, please, please, please do not get rid of this sentry gun. Don't kill it.
More people come out and die. And like I said, I can't even commentate.
This thing gets, I think, like about 15 kills and nine assists or something like that. Something ridiculous.
So what turned out to be a very bad situation became a very good situation in a matter of seconds.
Killing more people with this thing. See, I'm more concerned right now with my own life.
I think that I'm in no man's land here. I'm really scared about spies because, you know, obviously I'm just facing one direction this entire time.
That other sentry now has a wrangled sentry on the right. So they can't even get out of their spawn now.
And this sentry gets a lot of kills. It's very, very, very, very dominating.
And the server was a little laggy, but I figured I had to upload this anyways.
A spy comes over, saps on my stuff. I go, no, it's going to be over.
But that other engineer comes and saves the day with me again.
So props to that guy because he's a team player. Upgrade the dispenser.
And I'm still scared. I still think this is not going to work, but it's been working for a while.
I get more kills. And like I told you, it's killing so many things right now that I can't even tell you what's going on.
Like, who just died? Who was that? What was his name? Who was his family?
But a soldier comes out, starts to take it out. It doesn't go down, it's still up.
I go, oh, here comes the rockets here. At this point I'm thinking they have to be talking to each other and making a strategy.
This heavy is shooting it from a point where I cannot target him, or where the sentry cannot target him.
So I decide I'm going to try a little scare tactic, so I pull the Wrangler out.
And I aim in there and he just goes...and runs away, which is exactly what my plan was.
So that worked out pretty well. I get back, stabbed by a spy, and the party is over.
But what was supposed to be a complete, like just nothing, I don't care, I'm going to put this down and I'll change to a soldier or a heavy next life.
It actually turned out to be quite a good gameplay, so I'm very, very glad about that.
And right, I probably should have switched to the Gunslinger at this point, because you'll see I kind of just drop level ones as if they are from the Gunslinger.
So, see, I'm going to drop this and get it to level one. Oh well, just do it again. You killed it, who cares?
At this point it is only a minute left and they haven't even gotten halfway to the first point.
So this is merely just for distraction, so my teammates can give the final blow, so to speak.
I sneak up behind these two, I let the spy, I'm not going to blow his spot up, I kill the medic.
He only had probably five health anyways, but I didn't want to blow that spy's spot up.
Kill the scout with a couple of revenge crits, and this is over. It's pretty much the end here.
I drop one sentry here just in case like a spy comes back and doesn't realize what he's doing or a scout tries to run past the point or something.
But with ten seconds left, I'm pretty sure you guys know the outcome. I don't think I have to tell you what happens.
Alright, I'll tell you what happens. They come back and they win. No, I'm just kidding.
Thank you so much again, guys. You don't know what it means to have 95 or 100 of you subscribe to the channel.
Even if you want the hat, like I said before, even if you just want the hat, thank you so much.
I hope you guys look forward to more stuff as much as I look forward to you guys being around.
Thank you so much and I look forward to Saturday. Take care.