Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with another episode of
ENLIGHTEN. The series, of course, where I go back in time, look at a title that was
overlooked by a lot of people. Well, maybe not so much overlooked by people, but a
title that fell through the cracks and nobody really talks about anymore. So this
time I'm going to talk about Heart of Darkness. No, not the book. This has
nothing to do with the book. It's got the same name though. It's gone
funny. So the guy responsible for this game, his name is Eric Shahee, and he's
sort of the grandfather of cinematic storytelling in video games. Eric Shahee
is the guy that made Another World, and if you type Another World into Google,
you're gonna find a million different articles on this guy. And if it wasn't
for guys like Eric Shahee, we would probably be stuck still in the press A to
jump, press B to shoot, kill the boss at the end of the game type gameplay. But
let's start talking about Heart of Darkness. Gonna do this in review style
just like in the last video. So what do you say? We go back in time, space, the
infinite journey. These are the stories... No, that's not how this works. This is
Heart of Darkness, a game so full of imagination that it couldn't even handle
itself. Releasing in 1998 under the now defunct Interplay, Heart of Darkness is
the definition of development and publishing struggles. The game saw many
many different delays. Mostly it was to create the game's many cutscenes and
pre-rendered backgrounds. Not to mention the bidding war that went between a
bunch of different companies on who was actually going to distribute this game.
For all these shortcomings though, the game did do quite well. Over a million
copies sold. Now that's quite a success for any game company's standards. So what
happened to this game? How come you don't really hear about it? How come nobody
cares about it? It's because of Ocarina of Time. Ocarina of Time, Banjo-Kazooie, and
Resident Evil 2 all released in this same year and Banjo-Kazooie actually
released one day before Heart of Darkness. So what's a big uphill battle?
Especially Ocarina of Time. Ocarina of Time is considered one of the best games
ever created. So when your game is going up against those types of games, you're
in a little bit of trouble. Heart of Darkness is about a young boy named
Andy, a young middle schooler with an authority problem. After getting in
trouble at school in what seems to be a regular occurrence, Andy meets up with
his faithful companion, Whiskey. After a strange eclipse sucks away his dog
companion, Andy rushes home to start his journey of rescue. The story is pretty
cut and dry, but it can be cute in the right places. The cutscenes in the game
are very, very interesting. They always start and always end in gameplay. It can
be something as simple as talking to your dog or dropping you in front of a
50-foot monster that's about to eat off your face. And this is something that
Heart of Darkness does very, very well. They give you a sense of urgency. You
have to pay attention to the cutscenes because if you don't, if you get up and
go get a soda somewhere, you're gonna sit back down and be dead over and over
again. And these cutscenes are really, really streamlined. Sometimes you don't
even know they're happening. It's a fantastic mechanic that really should be
the norm for the industry. More people need to take a page out of the Half-Life
book and have cutscenes and have cinematics be part of the experience
rather than just be something you load and watch. So gameplay-wise, Heart of
Darkness plays just like the other Eric Shahee games. In most situations, you are
going to be jumping on platforms, climbing on walls, or solving strange
puzzles. Difficulty-wise, this game is on an incredibly difficult scale. The
controls are very difficult to get used to, and at points the game is just
unfair. Your only real means of defense is a wonky laser beam gun and a magical
green goo attack. So what I'm trying to say is, you are going to die in this game
over and over and over and over again. So prime your wall to be ready for a
controller to go through it. And it can be also said that Heart of Darkness has
some very, very graphic death animations. You get ripped apart, you get squished,
you get crushed. There are a lot of terrible ways to die in this game. The
game is also very, very short, spanning two discs. It only takes about two and a
half hours to beat the entire game. Most of the room is taken up by, of course,
the cutscenes, 30 minutes of them on both discs. But if you can take the stress of
the gameplay and you don't mind watching a cutscene every now and then, this game
has to be played. Eric Shahee has created a fantastic game, and I am so glad that
he got back into the industry. He created that new game from Dust. That is an Eric
Shahee game, so it's great to see him getting back into it after so long. But
that's going to wrap up this episode of Enlighten, guys. Thank you so much for
watching. I really do appreciate it. And go check out this game, if you have a
chance. So thank you, everybody. I will see you all next time. Take care, everybody.