I just want to read. No chat. Hold on. No chat.
Jerma doesn't hate streaming. He just delays every single stream and talks about retirement every week.
That's not fair. No. Hold on a second. The last, the last like five streams, I have reverse delayed.
I have started a day or two early. The last, besides this one.
Excuse me. There have been at least three or four straight reverse delays as of the last two weeks.
Hey, just because you didn't see it doesn't mean it didn't happen, right? Just because you weren't
here doesn't mean I didn't do it. So anyways, after today, I'll see you in like 12 days.
Why do you have to be, why is it? No. You knew about that October break for a while. That's
not a delay. Well, I just pretended it's fine. It's my birthday. What are you doing? I'm crying
right now. Dude, he hates streaming. I love streaming. It's like one of my favorite things ever.
Anyways, welcome to the promised, promised breath of the wild Sunday stream. I told you I was going
to do it and here I am. Well, let's warm up with a little bit of platoon. What do you think?
I'm kidding. Relax. I'm kidding. Today's the last day of Overwatch one. Um, oh, but all right. Um,
when was the last time I even played Overwatch one? It's been a long time.
He doesn't even care. I mean, I don't, I don't really play Overwatch. Should I play Overwatch
too? I mean, I'm sure I'll play it. I don't know if I'll stream it. Should I stream it? Take for a
day? No, you won't. That's a lot of no's. That's a lot of no's. Adding PVE. I mean, is it as good as
the Splatoon PVE? That's my question. No, thanks. We're good. You know what? I really hope Diablo
four is good. You know what I mean? Like I, I hope like I've been there. I look, I'm a Diablo Andy.
I really like Diablo is like, okay. Cause I hated Diablo immortal. It was like, I fucking despised
it. I hated every second of it. It's, it might, it might be all right, right? It looks Diablo four
looks okay from the things I've seen about it. I hope so. I hope so for your sake. No,
it's all right. I will remember my fondness in Diablo two and Reaper Diablo three Reaper was,
was good. They made a lot of good changes. It's okay. Diablo three Reaper launch like the first
three or four months of that game. I thought were great, but then I didn't really like the subsequent
patches. I think they did a pretty good job trying to get it back to, uh, back to life.
Didn't all right, correct me if I'm wrong. So I want to be corrected if I'm wrong,
cause I, if I'm incorrect, I want people to say that's not correct.
The, did the game director for Reaper of souls end up leaving Blizzard because that's, is that
incorrect? That's not correct. That's correct. That's not correct. Great. Thanks for the help.
I love how somebody wrote probably. Let me, I'm just going to look it up because you guys
aren't helpful. Let me see. Reaper of souls director. Hold on. Hold on. All right. Yeah,
he's gone. He left Blizzard, uh, in July of 2016. Well, I mean, isn't that one of the reasons why
that was the game was better? I don't know. It was my fault. What did I do? Well, okay. My point is
in my opinion, the, the, the guy that made Diablo through Diablo through the guy that made Diablo
three, a better game. And obviously there's tons of other people that worked on it, right?
But I would have liked to see that person come back to D four. I don't know. I don't know the
story. I have no idea, but I hope it's good. Look, I was overwatch one fun. I thought it was kind of
fun for the first like six months. I just didn't care as much as I did about like something like
TF2. It just didn't have the staying power that TF2 had. And obviously, very obviously, I mean,
you go back to my old YouTube channel that it was like a, wow, here we go. Lizards making like a,
a potential kind of FPS arcade TF2 like game. It was a big deal at the time, but it just,
it didn't keep me. It just didn't. I did have fun with it though. I, I'm not going to lie. The
first six months of that were really fun. It was pretty fog before all the balancing. I thought
it was fun. We'll see. Anyways, somebody said, stop stalling. Um, ban that person for life.
Hide that guy. Hide him. Wait, I'm sick. I don't want to. What? All right. Well, you get to stay.
Please eat sushi. Why? That's a weird request. Do I like sushi? Yeah. I think it's good.
Why do you want me to eat it? Why do you want me to eat sushi? Why do a sushi tier list?
Okay. I'll do it right now. I don't even need it on the screen. Uh, spicy tuna roll S tier
salmon roll B, A, everything else F spicy tuna roll S tier, pretty much everything else F.
I'm not a huge sushi fan. Okay. I'm one of those people that will eat sushi and pretend like,
I think you made a good idea ordering that. What do you want to try it? Oh, it's, um,
it's like a yellow fin or whatever, or yellow tail or something, whatever it is.
She's like, Oh yeah. And then you eat it and you're like, Oh, all right. Hmm. Okay. Oh,
you never want somebody to do. Oh, wow. This is gross. No, I'm not going to say that
because it's not, it's just kind of not my thing. I love spicy tuna. I like, uh, what's maybe people
might think I'm insane for saying this. This is going to make people probably gag when I say this.
Uh, no, it's good though. It's, is it weird for me to say this?
I, okay. I like a Philadelphia roll. If you don't know what a Philadelphia roll is,
it's salmon, cream cheese, and avocado. I feel like people would think I was gross for saying that,
but a lot of you are saying based and wow, good, good, good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's basic. Hold on.
Isn't the very nature of like true sushi basic? It's raw fish on rice. Oh, that's the very
definition of a base of basic. Basic doesn't mean bad. It's just very, Hey, you got a little bit of
raw fish laid on top of some rice. That's it. I'm actually, I'd rather eat that. I'm not into the,
um, like Omega volcano roll where the thing comes out and it's like stacked four feet tall.
Like, well, you know what I mean? I don't, it's like, Oh yeah, well, this is it. We'll see it's
eel. And then there's a, there's like a Szechuan sauce on top of that. And then on top of that is
tuna. And then on top, it's like a kebab. I don't, I don't like those. You can't eat them in one bite.
Those are sushi kebabs. Those are, I don't, I don't really like, I like eating it in one bite
as a Rick and Morty reference. I don't, okay. If that's from this season, I haven't seen it.
So it's, it's just, we both thought the same thing was funny. Anyways, let's play.
Could you please consider streaming another shitty, I don't want to say the company.
I could just say the name of the company, right? Like I'm not, Hey, can you please play the,
this game from this shitty company? Like I, I'm like, I don't want to say that out loud.
No, no, stop, stop it. Anyways, welcome to the stream. Hope you're having a good Sunday.
Yes, this is going to be, I will not be live. I will, I will not be live until I return from
my October break. I will not be live. Okay. Okay. I will not be live. Okay. I'll be back.
Do a baseball stream rerun. Now I'm going to spend some time with friends, spend some time
with some family. I feel like it's pretty overdue, but it's time to play breath of the wild. I've
stalled for about, it's been two hours and 45 minutes on the orbit in soon screen. So that
person was right. I'm sorry about that. And kind of just chilling for like two hours and two hour,
42 minutes to 41. Yeah. I thought we were your family. You guys are my family guy,
not my family. Make sure you get it right. Where, where your POG champs. What's that mean?
How long is the break going to be? Um, it's probably going to be maybe like eight days.
Okay. It will be eight to 10 days after the, um, okay. I'll be back in about eight to 10 days
after the last time you see me on, on camera. Okay. Cool. All right. You understand.
You're basically dead. I mean, no, like, I mean, like not the last time, whatever.
Everybody just be quiet. Breath of the wild. We're going to continue our play through.
Uh, I believe it's just this one right here. I just beat the divine, uh, beast, the elephant one.
You're wearing the shaggy shirt again. I am clean though. Don't worry. It's just so easy to wear.
Like I don't, okay. Just solid colors are just so easy. I don't have to be like, what is this? Oh,
it's just green. Green. Easy. Like gray. Blue. Easy. Done. Can you eat a comedy sandwich? What
is the comedy sandwich? Oh, right. Okay. I just got, what did I just get? I got this thing.
All right. Everyone said, don't use this. The comedy sandwiches is like, I don't know,
cream cheese, onions, Tabasco sauce, and like a turkey leg or something, right? It's like,
oh ha, it's like a funny sandwich you made. That sounds pretty good. A knuckle sandwich,
maybe. Are you going to punch me in the face? Hey, I got a funny sandwich for you. It's right here.
All right. So where do I want to go? I just, I beat this divine beast. I could go, hold on. Let me
take a look. What we got? Destroy Ganon. Where's the other, this, this four, right? What area should
I go to? I mean, the easy, the easy thing is just to kind of go up and over, right? If I went over
here, then why not just kind of wrap around here? I have this marked for some reason,
so I'm going to go see why. We'll go to this pin. I think it's a shrine and cool.
Make a car tier list now. I don't know anything about cars. I mean, like what, like car types
or car like makers, like Chevy, Ford, Chrysler. What do you mean? Like, oh, truck hatchback. What
do you mean? All right. How do I get out of here? I think I have to go this way. Yeah. Okay. I'm
going to go, I've got to go this way. What are these? All right. Wait, why do I have somebody
stamps on the map? Car companies. I don't know anything about car companies. I don't know
anything about them. Wait, I have to turn this in, don't I? Here's the picture. This is the one I got.
What do you think? Yeah, that's pretty damn good. My apologies. That sound was not very dignified,
was it? Pardon me. I'm all better now. That Lionel. How terrifying. Well, look at this and I
doubt anyone would get any reckless ideas about visiting Plymouth mountain. Well,
here's a follow-up to that. He's dead. Send as many people up there as you want. I killed him. Oh,
shit. Okay. This is part of the Zora set for now. Cool. East Reservoir Lake was created in a
collaboration between Hylians and the Zora. After East Reservoir Lake was finished, we made Zora
Greaves as a token of our friendship. Thanks. Cool. You can swim fast. Cool. You think they'll ever
make like, you know how it's like, oh, we have to have game difficulties. Do you think they'll
have a game in patient modes where we just kind of use like fallout to zero intelligence dialogue,
like get through the story and stuff, or just like take these. They're good. Make you swim fast.
Oh, cool. Thanks. Appreciate it. Like swim fast. You get equip if want. Oh, I get it. I understand
it. I know what you what you're asking and telling me. I hope not. Do put on caveman communication
mode. I don't know. Sometimes you're just looking for, did a bubble just come out of my mouth?
Sometimes you're just looking for you do this by it's kind of I know I'm going to make a wild
reference, but it kind of reminds me of you just run around the town and wow, pick up every single
exclamation point, skip everything and just hit M and look where you need to walk to like to the
quest. That's it. You don't read anything. Guys, I don't even I didn't even know what half of the
quests were until I got to the point of the map where it was like a circle and said kill that
thing. I was like, oh, that's what I'm supposed to do here. All right. So I'm I don't think I
can climb this mountain. Well, it's not raining anymore. I get up here. I'm going to try it like
I can stand up there. Doesn't everyone do that with every MMO? I mean, probably it's the most
efficient way to level up. I shouldn't have done that. What an idiot. OK, I definitely can get up
there. I'm just so I know I can get up there. Start here. God damn it. Hold on. OK, I'm going
to skip like 30 minutes of walking by doing this. You can go up the waterfall. Oh, wait. Oh, yeah.
It is right there. It's been like a week. I haven't played in a week. It's been a while. I
haven't played. Let me see if I can even do this. No, no, no, no, no, no. We're just going to go up
the waterfall. Watch your skip. No, if you skip, you made a mistake because look, now you skipped
like 10 minutes and you're like, where am I? What the fuck? I thought he was climbing a wall.
Don't tell people to do that. OK, where's that waterfall right here? Vod Watchers skip four
minutes. If you if you're going to skip less than five minutes in this stream, come on. Are
what are you skipping? Really? Though those of you that are saying Vod Watchers skip two minutes
are caveman communication difficulty. Andy's like me. I don't want to hear it ever again.
What I just said, I got question marked and now people are saying skip two minutes,
skip five minutes, skip 10 minutes. Isn't that what I just was talking about? I wanted to.
Where's my mode where I just get to get to the parts where I want to see? I'm not going to die,
right? I have stamina food, don't I? Oh, fuck. Hold on. Hold on. Eat the stamina food.
Because I'm going to die if I don't skip to the next sorcery stream. There we are.
You know, I just thought of a funny thing. What if? All right. Now it's over.
All the Vod Watchers skip all the Vod Watchers skip. What if I opened up sorcery
and just played it for two minutes? So people that skipped got just absolutely just screwed over,
right? Like, wait, what? He's playing sorcery. What happened? Whatever. I'm out of here.
And then that's that's what happens when you skip. And in that two minute stretch of this stream,
I talk about how Breath of the Wild is like, not for me. Now, I'm not a fan. I'm not a big fan.
I'm just gonna play sorcery. You know what I mean? So that'll do, you know, that'll teach you to skip
five minutes and then you just don't watch the rest. Mm hmm. Camera was weird. All right. One,
two, three, four, five. Moblin guts. Can we just play the game? LOL. Yeah. All right. No,
I did say that I was today was guaranteed to not be a crack stream. I did say that.
You are right. That's very accurate. I did say that. Where are my pins? All right. Well,
I'm going to take this off. Wait, no, I'm not. Why is this pinned? Who did that? OK, so we got one
here. There is where else you stole that? You stole his organs. OK, any others? Yeah, over there.
OK, and one over here. Nice shrines. My favorite part. What is that thing? Oh, shit. Look at that
one. All right. I got to delete the other pins. I don't know what this was, but maybe someone
will remember. So which one should I go to first? I'm going to say start on the left side, right?
I don't know. I'm going over there. Go to the tower first. That one. That's the tower right
there, right? Is there another one? Oh, all right. Bro, I didn't see it. Look, I was looking like
this. My field of view was this. I'm going like this down. I see I don't. It's not there on my.
My eyes don't see it. It's no, it's not. It's not blind. Look, do you see a tower? I don't.
There's no tower on my screen. I'm going left. I'm looking for a shrine going right. I mean,
like it was like this. Now that I go like that, I can see it. It wasn't in frame. No, it wasn't.
You went up. No, I didn't. But I wasn't looking. All right. I'm going to go get the tower.
Can I make it from here? What is that? I'm falling off the cliff because I thought I was
zooming in. It's up on the D pad. OK, Guardian Skywatcher. What the hell is that? All right.
I'm going for it. Let's go. I just don't go in that light. I'm sick. I'm just going up there.
Oh, don't go over there. It's going to go.
But that's sort of way for that sort of way for that sort of way for that sort of way.
I'm going to start my fucking lightning. All right. OK, put how do I put the weapons out?
How do I unequip these? All right. Thought I got hit. Geez. Oh, you know what? Hold on.
Let me put my climbing gear back on. What the fuck? All right. Whatever.
Well, very obviously, I'm going in the wrong direction. I can still I think I can at least
get on the lip up there or something. Right. Come on, get up and stand. Come on and just stand up.
Come on, everybody. Just get up. Come on. Put your hands up. Everybody. Just stand up.
Come on. Put your hands up. Everybody. Just stand up. I forgot about that. That's like my
favorite song. Everybody put your hands up. Everybody. Just stand up. Everybody. Put your
hands up. Everybody. Just stand up. That's like so fucking funny. It really is. I it's genuinely
funny. Everybody put your hands up. Well, I need to hear it now. Right. Like I have to listen to
it now. There's no world where I don't put that on. Was it called the American Bible Challenge?
That's what it is. This is it. Right. OK. American Bible Challenge theme song. I want to be able
to hear it because I have my headphones plugged in a different spot. It's that this is I love
this so much. You have you have no idea. One more time. Then I think that's him singing it.
Right. Right. I think that's Jeff Fox really singing that. Is it? And then that makes it
so much better. No, not one more time. We're done. No shot. I am not kidding. I genuinely
like that. I love that song. It's so funny. It's it's perfect. I just love every second of it.
All right. I got to plug this back in. Hold on. Put your hands up. Everybody put your hands up
and stand up, too. And your hands up yet. Stand up and you better put your hands up.
Everybody stand up. This is not a crack stream. I can get up and stand up,
but I actually can, though. I actually can. I can. Damn it. I felt I'm doing this the wrong.
Oh, can I get up here this way? This probably one path. I can't do it. I don't think I can do it.
All right. Please tell me if I'm. Can I actually can I actually get up there and can I actually
stand up and put my hands up and climb up that? Can I do that? Or am I just wasting time here?
Yes. OK. Oh, just the weather is in the corner. Oh, all right. So it's going to be rainy for like
another few hours. Can I pass time? All right. It's almost gone. This guy's going to clear up
a little bit. All right. We got clear skies. Let's go. What? You piece of shit. Really? All right.
This guy's going to clear up actually in a minute. You have climbing clothes. They're on. What about
season's tier list? You got it. Well, where? What region? Where I am right now in Las Vegas
or what region? Because it depends in Boston, New England. All right. My favorite New England
season is not summer. It's like hot. It's kind of gross, sweaty, humid mosquitoes, bugs, ticks.
No, thank you. Spring. That's all right. It's cool. I'm a fall guy. I'm a fall guy from New England
and has nothing to do with the trees all change colors. No, I like that fall air. The fall air
is even over here in Vegas. It hits different, doesn't it? There is a different smell. Did I
wait too long and miss the fact that there was no rain? Whatever. Fall air, that like 60 degree fall
air has a certain sense to it. It's like that fall, slightly chilled, but like room temperature
on a kind of earthy sense. Do you know what I'm talking about? Fall has a certain smell.
It's not a smell. It's like a sense. It's like a crispy. Yes. It's a crispy sense in your like
face. Fall is the best. Winter is cool too. I like winter. Winter out in Vegas is actually really
cool because it's so cold, but there's no snow. It's just free. It's really cold, but no snow,
no precipitation. It's really interesting. So you can go. The air is so still and chilly,
but there's never any snow. This is an NPC conversation. Like you mean like a GTA NPC
or what do you mean by that? What? I can't talk about the weather. Why would it be like an NPC
conversation like in a game? This is a Morrowind NPC talking. A Morrowind NPC does not know. A
Morrowind NPC is like this. Hello afternoon. Hello. They don't do that. Watch it. They don't say
anything. The Morrowind NPC is not going to give a weather tier list. What are you talking about?
What the fuck? It's not raining. It's cloudy. It's supposed to be cloudy.
Oh my goodness. I don't have a weapon. All right. See ya. No.
It stopped. I found the place to go. Oh my God. I annihilated that guy. Oh shit. What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do about that? What do I do? So I hide? How do you hide?
Man will always be smarter than machines. I'm going to try to stand right up here.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I got it. I made it. You're doing a lot of Switch stuff, huh? Yeah, I am. I'll get away from the
Switch eventually here. But to be fair, let's be fair, there was a long period where I did not
turn this thing on for like eight months or something, right? So come on. It's only fair.
Are you going to finish the game on stream? I don't know. I can tell you all that I know.
And what I know is I'm very much enjoying playing it on stream and hanging out until that stops
being the case or until I want to be able to finish it off stream. I don't know. I'm still here.
What did that even do? I thought that was going to clear all the all the goo.
Oh my god. Get out of that. Get out of it. You better. All right. You're not going to tell me
what I should and should not do. Okay. You understand me? There's probably a few of them
that I have to get rid of, right? See any more eyes? Oh, I thought that was a chest. We got sword,
rusty sword, rusty shield. I'll take it. I can cook, but I don't. I don't. Ah, I'm not going to
take it actually. Never mind. I have tons of food. I don't need to cook. Oh, it's emote only mode.
That means it's a puzzle. It's a puzzle of foot. Okay. Can you shoot these? I'm going to blow these
up though. Wasn't that nothing? Nothing. All right. I'm just going to turn it on. I got four shrine.
This is going to be a shrine stream. Okay. So why does he keep over fucking reacting? It's like
annoying. Time the person out. Oh, you can't even write. Never mind. I can't gaslight you guys.
It's emote only. Never. I didn't even look. This thing's been low. Never mind. It's going to break
broken. All right. Let's use the club. Ooh. Can I sneak in there? Wow. That thing's actually
really powerful. 24. That's better than the Lionel sword. Okay. So let me go over here.
I can sneak in here. I found it. Did you hear the sound? I'm exploring. Don't tell me to hurry up.
I never would have found this chest if I did. Nice. Nice. 100 rupees. Now why is it on emote
only by the way? This seems pretty self-explanatory, doesn't it? I mean, now it does. I can't hit that
like piece of sinew, whatever it is. There's definitely another eyeball somewhere hiding.
All right. Maybe not. There's definitely an eyeball attached to this sinew. See you later.
Where is this? There's an eye somewhere. It has to be. It's definitely. It's going to be definitely
attached to the sinew. Um, can I break that? Where's this eye? Well, I'll go over here. All right.
Now what? I need some more weapons. I'm out of like shitty weapons to use. Wait a minute. Can I
burn it? I can burn it. I think I can burn it. Can I burn the sinew or can I? Where is this thing?
The inside of my, my brain is itching. The inside of my ear all the way in is itching.
There's an eyeball just sitting hidden somewhere and I got to find this stupid eye in here.
Shit. No, no, no, no, no. Oh my God. I almost died. I'm all right. I really hope there's no
goo up here. I can't climb that. Why? Oh shit. Hold on. I tried to jump, but he jumped up and
not back. How do you jump backwards? I wanted to, I wanted to jump backwards.
I don't want to jump. How do you jump out? I didn't want to jump up. How do you jump out?
Where is this thing? Oh, there's a chest over there. It has to be something with the fire.
It has to be with the fire. Don't not like this me. Bomb arrow. All right. It's got to be like a
explode something. I don't know. I, there's no eye. I'm looking for another eye or fish.
Should I release them? No, not yet. I don't understand what's happening. I don't get it.
Can I do, can I do this right now? Do I have to come back here later? Grab. I'm going to try.
Okay. Can I, can I even hurt this stuff or do I have to hit? I was under the impression you
couldn't hurt this shit. Like you have to destroy the eyeball. That's the only way. But can I,
can I bomb the sinew? I'll try it. I mean, I'm lost. I'm going to bomb that sinew right there.
Wait. Soccer ball kick. Catch. Kapow. Referee. Touchdown. What's that? Shoot the cannons at it.
Shoot the cannons at the, all right. Shoot the cannons. Shoot. Turn the cannons around
and fire the cannons at that. Shoot the bomb through the touchdown. Shoot ball. Ball goes
touchdown. Fly torch. Ball goes touchdown. Santa Claus. There's no Santa Claus here.
Catch. Catch football. Throw football. Touchdown. I don't know. What? What are you talking about?
Cold. Chill. Throw. Touchdown. Where, is there a place where I can put a bomb?
That's something over here, right? Oh my God. What the? What? Hold on. Oh shit. My cover. Oh no.
Um, dude, you fucking idiot. Let him out. Let him out. Let him out. Let him out. I don't care. Let
him out. Let him out. Let him out. Let him out. Let him out. Tell me. Just give me the,
give me the solution right now. Just tell me, just tell me the answer. I'm going to get kicked
out of class. I'm going to get detention. I'm going to stand up right now in the middle of the
test. I want the, give me the answer. Climb to just climb. What? I thought it was a puzzle.
Just climb. Just climb is the answer. No, it can't be. Just climb. It's not a puzzle or like,
oh, I'm going to get like a puzzle shit. Just climb it. There's a magnetized platform. There
it is. But what was the football thing with the hands up? Climbing is the puzzle. I pressed B.
Why did it not register? Hold on. Let me just heal. Okay. So just climb up, but there's a
magnetized thing, dude. Okay. I'm getting sick and gosh, darn tired of that happening. It just
doesn't register the jump. It's not, it's not the controller. It's the game's input engine. Okay.
Okay. So what the heck? There's a magnetized platform. I tried climbing up that side. Use
the stasis. Oh, oh my God. Link stop just gluing to every single surface. All right. Down by the
eye that you killed, there's a magnetized thing. What the fuck was that? I, what is happening?
Why is that not? I'm pissing off. I'm getting pissed off actually. How come I can't activate
it? This is where the eye was killed. You just passed it. Huh? It's outside. What? This is the,
this was the solution. I'm not going to die to the sludge. This, this little metallic door buried in
the goo is the solution of the puzzle. Get out of here. This guy takes a lot of hits. Yeah. So
what now? What did you mean by it's the uprights? That's a good shield. All right. So now I can put
this over here, bro. You talking about do this and then it'll fall like that. Oh, come on, dude.
What the fuck? What? I'm sitting here looking for eyeballs to kill because I thought it was going
to get rid of whatever. That's, how is that a touchdown? That's not a touchdown. Well, that was
fun. Let me throw this away because this thing is 40. So people are saying you can actually just
climb it up it. Can you though? I feel like every, I tried to climb that. It wouldn't let me do it.
Do I, do you like damage just hurt? Just, just go. You can't though. You can. It's on the,
it's the pillar. Okay. What's wrong with my character? You can jump off the half arch.
That took so long. I have, oh, I'm cold. Okay. Is there a, does this make me warmer? I don't think
so. That literally took an hour. No, it didn't. It took like 25 minutes. I had like a 30 minute
opening of the stream and then I was walking around for a little bit and it's been 20 minutes.
Do not add an hour just because it makes it funnier. It was 20 minutes. Eat something.
You're going to die. I'll be all right. All right. Look. Hey, we made it. We made it. How is that
kicking a football? Somebody give me a full sentence. Hey, I want a complete sentence on how
throwing a football through the uprights is what I had to do there. The hands he makes was gas
lighting. Throw down the path bridge to go up. At the arch you have to touch down the plank.
The hands point up. You can climb up. It's the shape of the magnet. Oh my God. What?
It is the shape of a magnet. And you were saying I needed to pick. Okay. Well, I would never have
gotten that. That's so funny. All right. Cold resistance. This one here. All right. Look,
I got it. All right. Now let me do what I want to do with the thing that I like doing the most.
And that's go to the shrines. Should I go to this one first? Which one should I do first?
I'm just going to go to this one first. Whatever. This one. All right. Yes. Let's play. Let's go.
Yes. That's right. Okay. Bye for like another 30 minutes. I'm going to do this in 15 minutes.
Goodbye. See you in 15 minutes when it's done. See you in 15 minutes tops when it's done. What
time is it right now? It is 4 11 right now. PM Pacific at 4 21 at 4 20 at 4 26. You'll be let
out. All right. Here we go. Got it. Times it for 12. It's been one minute. I'm almost done.
Do not bet against me. Just saying. Don't bet against me. And a surprise. A few people here,
I think. Hmm. Okay. Very cool. What's next? All right. Cool. All right. Just checking out some
stuff. Very nice. All right. What's this? Okay. Let's go. I'm going to scream so bad to get the
energy out. You know what I mean? Just like reset it. Oh, look at that. Let's bet against them.
Let's bet against them. Times it. Oh, wait. How much time do I have? Oh, look at that. Who
bet against me? Which one? Which one of you bet against me? Who did? It's 4 15 right now. I'm
11 minutes early. Just saying. I'm 11 minutes early. Literally the easiest shrine. Well, why
did you bet against me then? That's your fault. How do I get the? I have two, by the way. I'm
covering the screen, you know. I lost a million points. Ooh. I did say don't bet against me.
I made it very clear. You didn't get the chest. Well, I completed the shrine. I'll go back in.
Well, could I pick something up? The rules for completion are getting the orb. Yeah,
come on. Nice. All right. So how do I get this? That was interesting.
All right. So now I mean, I think I have to walk on this. Can I hit it with a bow?
Oops, a daisy. Okay. What? Where is it? I do I jump on that? I don't get it. How do I stop it?
Good luck. I'm imagining I have to stop that. I'm going to run out of arrows. Oh, come on. All
right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. You got to get the lip. It is stuck on the lip.
Yeah. I stuck on the lip Andy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. God. Just do it.
Just do it and stop. There's going to be an apple in this chest. It's not going to be worth doing.
Oh my God. Don't jump. Why am I jumping? Just crouch. I'm going to have no arrows. It's so
stupid. If there are. All right. If there are five arrows in this chest, I'm going to uninstall the
game. Damn it. Hold on. Oh, thank God. Don't screw this up. All right. I'm glad it's not five
arrows because I didn't want to uninstall the game. How do I get out of here? Pick up your arrows.
Oh my God. I forgot you could do that. All right. I'm going to pee. Never back. Pee time. That's
where I deserve peeing. By the way, it's 421. Even if I did that, it still wouldn't be 426.
I still whoever bet against me still lose. One sec. Why did I die? Oh, it's cold. Right.
I froze. Okay. That was cool. That was a fun one. Let's do another one. Where's the other one?
There's a couple other here. There's that one. Is that I'm going to go to that one down there.
Get a big hole. My favorite part about this game is that there's atmosphere.
So when you go higher in the atmosphere, it gets colder. Yeah, I think. Holy. Oh,
this one right there. All right. I'm going to go to this one and that one. Should we
place bets again? This way, that way, this way, that way. What if a middle hair part?
I don't know. My hair naturally just parts that way. I think. Yeah. I mean, I can do this,
but show Otto. I showed Otto like a week ago. He's fine. He's just chilling. He's chilling,
chilling out in his bed, chewing on a bone. He's having fun. I don't want to disturb him.
All right. Let's do 15 minutes. Let's go. It's 426 right now. That's 36 at 441. I will have this
completed 441. Let's go. Done. Easy. This would be the easiest one all night. That was on purpose.
If you didn't know, I did that on purpose to make a funny thing. So everyone would go, oh my God,
he got hit by the rock rolling. Actually true. I actually did that on purpose. And if you,
people are like, oh, he's like pretending that he did it on purpose and like pretending that
it wasn't on purpose. Right? No, I did that on purpose. I want to make that really clear
and transparent with everybody here. I'm not kidding. Okay. All right. So let's obviously,
we have to freeze that. Okay. Good. All right. I shut this one off. I broke this one. Okay.
That one's magical. Why is that one magical? Oh, they're all, they're all okay. Nevermind.
Game's fucking easy. Shit. Yeah. I know. I know. I know. Skip. I just can't die. Just don't die.
I'll be fine. I can pick those ones up. Weird. Oh, what weird. I can pick those up.
Strange. What is that for? Weird. Interesting. Kind of weird. Okay. Weird. That's good. I'll take it.
Thank God. All right. There's only one of these, right? All right. I got a plan. Imagine voting
against me. Imagine voting against me. Right. So many of you guys just probably just lost twice
in a row. That's three spirit orbs. I got the chest too. It's 11 minutes early. I should drop
it to 10 minutes. The game is quiet. I'll take care of that. That's one of the easiest in the
game. So vote accordingly then. All right. Where's the other one? I want to do all these
shrines. I love them. A lot of people say that their favorite part of this game is when Link
goes, but mine is the shrines. I would say. You're wrong. All right. Let's do, I'm going to,
I'm just going to keep teleporting back here and just fly to them. So much easier than walking.
Where was that other one? Oh, right here. This is a bad idea. Wasn't there another one down here?
If I land over here, I think I should be fine. So watch out for this butt head. Yeah. Sorry. Yeah.
I, my language is pretty, it's pretty bad. I'm sorry. Where are you? Is this water too cold
or something? Am I going to get hurt in here? I made it. Wait, what's this? Ooh, radishes.
I should have taken a picture of it. I'm an idiot. These things are one of the most high quality
foods in the game. And what? In real life. Looking for one of those little seed guys, whatever.
Walk off the cliff. Oh, all right. Where is it? It's right there. Drop it. Then take a picture.
Oh, so it, it still works that way. Oh, it does still work. You're right. You're right. I like
this area. Uh-oh. Bandits. Uh-oh. Bandits. Let's go. All right. 10 minutes. When I press the button,
I'm, I'm giving, I'm making it easier for you if you want to bet against me. 10 minutes.
The time is at 435. Wait till I get in. This doesn't count yet. I have to get actually into
the shrine. You have to get the chest too? No, it's just for the shrine. If you're reading this,
I hope you're having a good day. Hey, you too. Thank you. All right. I got 10 minutes to complete
the shrine. Let's go. Minor test of strength. Oh, you guys are whoever batted against me.
You've got, I don't know. You've got some time here. Uh, um, seriously? I think this is free
money for anybody that's going to bet for me. This is free money. You're literally watching
it right now. You can still bet it's free money. This is free money. I'm just telling you right
now, you're going to get channel points for free. It's free money. It's, I mean, it's free money.
I forgot that. I forgot the move set, but it's free money. It's actually free money. Watch.
It's free money. It's literally, it's free money. You just, I'm not understanding that.
It wasn't even, the timer wasn't even over yet. Oh hell yeah. Ancient battleaxe. Dude,
the timer wasn't even over and you still could have got it. You cheated. You eat it. What? This
isn't Dark Souls PVP. Cheated. He eat it. Cheated. He eat it. Oh, please. Giant ancient core.
Extremely rare find. Ooh. Ancient armor. Ooh. Don't sit. Please save those. Don't make anything.
Okay. I got four. I'm going to do stamina, but I'm not doing it until I have at least a double
turn in. That's how it works. What was it? It was 90% voted that you were going to do it. It's so
funny. I think the, the like 4% of you that voted that I was not going to do that. I think we're
banking on, uh, like my house getting struck by lightning and the power going out, right? Like
it's like, it could happen. It could, and you'd get a huge return, but it's not probable. It's
like, man, it's possible that like his internet just goes out now, right? It's possible, but not
completely, not probable. It's possible. All right. Where was that last one?
You were too overconfident. That's why I doubt it. Oh, 75 million versus 3.5 million. Damn. Wait,
does that mean that the people that bet 3.5 million, it goes to the people that bet their
points? That's how that works, right? So would you guys get like 50 points each? That was what,
that probably wasn't, I mean, that's a safe return, but it's not a big return.
We've basically gotten nothing. The three and a half million got split to everyone. That's so
funny. I got 10 K. I got two K. I got a, I got 150 points. I got six K. I bet six K and I got
6.9 K back. Okay. Safe return. That was a safe investment you made. Where the hell am I? Wait,
what? Oh, I went to the wrong place. The people that were betting no had a 22.5 time return.
If they won a lot, bring back, you need channel point rewards. I know the thing is I need to find
a way to make something for channel points. That's not going to just like destroy every stream.
Those of you that remember when channel points first came out and it was like, oh, what do I do
with these? I had a thing where you could redeem a certain amount of, was it a hundred thousand or
75,000 to make me wink on camera. And it's like, oh, that's funny. It's like a hundred thousand
points. That's a lot of points. And people were redeeming them every 15 to 25 seconds at one
point. It's just like, I can't do that. I'm not going to wink every fucking 30 seconds. It's weird.
And then eventually I just stopped doing it. And then I did one where I just
caught up and did it like 5,000 times or something. Right. All right. So where was it? There was one
more. What was it? I swear there was one more. Am I crazy? There was definitely one more. What was it?
Check the pins. Well, the problem with the pins is I never removed them. There's a pin right there.
What's that pin for? What did I pin? What did I pin? I think it was this one down here.
Did I do them all? It's in a canyon down here. I just don't, I don't, down, down, down.
Where? Look down. Where is it? Between these two. Where? Where is it? Down there. All right. Down
here. It's like down here, right? Yeah. Yeah. Mini map. No, I, yeah, I know. I was just making sure
I had it in the right place. Hey, sunglasses Andy. Look at the mini map. I know I'm going,
look where I'm going. I'm going in the right direction. Why are my sunglasses Andy? What does
that mean? Smarten up fuck face. I like that comment. That's funny. Smarten up. All right.
10 minutes. It is 4 44. The second that I go in here, the timer begins. I would start to bet now
because we don't want to give anybody. No, you know what? Forget that. It starts. I'm not going
in here yet. We're waiting until people bet because I don't want people to get an advantage.
It's the timer starts not 4 50, not 4 55. It starts when I go in here because I don't want
people to get an advantage because they're going to see, Oh, it's a, it's a minor combat test. I'm
going to bet this way, right? So it's not 4 55. It's like 4 56 or something, right? Yeah. So you
don't get, no, you, you have to bet now without knowing what it is. Oh, wait, we were fun. One
wink a year. I just burnt my eye when I did that. I hope you all know. There you go. Yeah. Well,
I beat this in 10 minutes. The thing is, a lot of you guys have played this game. Why am I acting
like the game came out a week ago? This game's been off for like four and a half years. So a
lot of you guys know what is in here. So those of you that don't know what's in here, I mean,
you can just Google it and find out and decide whatever. That's all right. Well, I beat this
shrine in 10 minutes starting now. What's the ratio? Power of fire. Oh shit. It's not a minor
combat shrine. Oh, okay. Power of fire. That's easy. I don't have any arrows. Oh,
don't need arrows. I don't know why I thought that just said, let's go. Like, let's go. All right.
Now I got to knock that down. I don't have any arrows. Shit. I'm good. Why is that here? Why is
that? There's a little lip there. Why? All right. So now I got, okay. All right. Okay. Can't knock
this down. I got the treasure chest. Knight's bow. All right. Get rid of this fucking thing. 83
to 17. Yes. Goodness. All right. So I can't let you guys down. How am I going to break the ones
higher though? Isn't that impossible? If I don't have arrows, how can I shoot it? All right. I'm
going to time a bit here. I'm on a timer here. Hold on. You break this one. Excuse me. Wait,
what? Oh, oh, we're good. I got five minutes. Oh, I win. I got the chest too. That's everything.
So that's all the shrines. Good. Very cool. Very cool. Very cool. Easiest points of my life.
Yeah. I had some time to spare. I had at least four or five minutes to spare. How come you're
only good when we bet? When I stop pretending. All right. So now, interesting. I got the shrines.
I could over here, I guess, right? I guess I'm just going to try to find a road and just go up
this way. See what I find. No, you know what? Let's go back to the tower. Is that, let me
get a good kind of bird's eye view of this whole place. Don't listen to the haters.
OK, so this is where I want to go, is over here. I'm going to put a pin right here because I want
to see how far away it is. I can't even see it anyways. All right. So it's past the volcano.
So the volcano is the next major thing that I have to do. So why don't I go over here
that way and then up? Wait, around the volcano? I'm going to go to that tower over there.
Wait, what's that? There's something right here. And then I'm going to go here and I'm going to go
this way and then bang a right over there, I guess. OK, is this a oh, this is a stable. Cool.
I'm a traveler. You must be a man who sets his mind on something and then gets it done.
I'm the best. OK, I was really into sword fighting, but I'm a bit of a rut with it.
Doesn't help that the sword I'm using right now is way too blunt. That's why I thought
if I can get that legendary sword, maybe a new path will open for me. What do you think?
Finally figured out that it's near Death Mountain. However, it doesn't seem to be
in this direction. Maybe it's on the opposite side, closer to the Woodland Stable. Maybe I'll just
mosey over to the Woodland Stable. What are you doing over there? What?
Oh, wait. No, Highland Stable. Where's the Woodlands? Oh, I haven't found it. OK.
OK, let's get Frank II over here. I've got to buy some stuff. Thank you. Let's get some.
I actually think I have some food to make, don't I? All right. Very hydrating liquid. Heat
resistance. I mean, I'm going to the Fire Mountain right now. Let's let's do that.
Heat resistance. Yep. Heat resistance. I mean, it means it's a volcano.
See what I get from this. All right. Six and a half minutes of low level heat resistance. Good.
Individual radish. Wait, movement speed. All right. I'm going to do movement speed and radish.
It's going to be pretty sick, right? But then I work. That didn't work. Boost your movement
speed when the seeds are cooked into a dish. What happened? Oh, god damn it. All right.
Whatever. I forgot. I thought this was just yummy. Well, that was a waste, but whatever.
OK. All right. What about any lixir? I don't think I have anything, right? I don't think
I have anything. Wood in your food. Here we go. All right. Three and a half minutes of movement
speed. Do it again. A dash of salt. Good. Now. Do I have any, like, hot heat clothings? I don't
think so. I'm going to wear the heavy armor. I feel like it's better for now. All right. Hi.
Hello, Frank, too. There is a general story around here. You have a store, right? No, I don't.
Beetle. Beetle. Oh, is this Beetle? Thanks. A guardian in the eye. To find him, go way
north past Zora's domain all the way to Kala Ancient Tech Lab. All right. Somebody remember
that. Write that down. What do you got? OK. Yep. Arrows times ten. Give that to me. How many of
these do you have? What a waste of money. I'm not buying that. Oh, speed boost. Fire elixir. Let's
go. OK. Let's just. You know what? Just buy it. Buy the whole store. Take the whole thing. That's
a lot of money. Whoa. Hold on a minute. That's a lot. That's too much money. Is that too much money
or should I just buy it? Let's do it. Whatever. Speed boost. Yeah. I mean, I have a lot of materials
to make elixirs. Let's do it. And because I'm a piece of shit, you know, how much is that? No,
way too much. All right. Let's go make some heat elixirs. Wait, look what I got. I need some
backseat Andes to help me. Should I just sell all these? OK. If I keep selling all of my ore,
I'm not going to have any ore to do anything in the rest of the game. Keep the luminous ones.
Keep three of each. You barely need them. Keep like three of each. They're easy to get. OK. Well,
or do I use to upgrade armor? Oh, that's right. I'll sell two of each. OK. I'm not going to sell
the luminous ones. What about these? Two hundred and sixty bucks. Really? Is this bad if I sell?
It doesn't. I don't think I use them in anything. Sell the gems. These are just money, right?
That's a lot. All right. Now I actually have some cash. Oh, no. All right. Now I'm going to make a
bunch of elixirs. Goodbye. It's a pretty good Mario impression. OK. So if I do two lizards,
if I go boom, boom, double heat lizard. And then what's what's a rare ingredient? Just do one,
not two. Just one. What's the highest quality monster part that I have? Does that matter?
The guts? Does it actually matter? Oh, do what about the lionel horn? This would be like a this
would be like an hour of heat resistance. No, no, no. Don't do that. Keep the keep this for later.
OK. What about like the horn? Like these? These look like they're high quality. Keep Lionel. OK.
All right. All right. Let's go. Let's see what this does. High level fireproof effect,
which prevents your body from catching fire. Be sure to pack this when venturing to explore
the Death Mountain, which is where you're going. OK. Yes. All right. Ten minutes. Let's do another
one. Oh, that wasn't a good one. Why was that one worse? All right. Well, whatever.
Why was that one worse? All right. Lizard. Temporary hearts. Oh, no guts. OK. Oh,
oh, it's just a full heel. That's pretty sick. Oops. That's OK. Fuck. I ruined everything.
Can I reload the game? Where's my last save? Sixteen fifty three. When was that?
It's good. It's OK. No, no, no, it's fine. All right. All right. Don't sell the Lionel hoof.
Why does that sound like I'm saying that word wrong? Mid level haste. Nice. You can't really
softlock yourself. You'll find pretty much more of everything. All right. Five arrows. I already did.
All right. I'm ready to do Mount Doom. Where is it? I got tons of food. I'm ready. Look at all this.
Look at it. I've got more food. I'm a goddamn catering service. I've got plenty of food. Let's
go. All right, Frank. Let's go. So where do I want to go? I got to go this way. So I'm thinking maybe
just wrap around. I don't know. Let's find out. I go down and then right. Let's see where I go.
Oh, my God. I just fucking ran that over. I don't know you could do that.
Oh, pretty. Stay right here. Oh, it's a bomb. Good. Why did it? It's a bomb. Why did it explode?
OK, we're good. Flurry rush. Oh, my God. He killed me in one hit. Hey, that's not going to be on
cooldown, right? Did I just get absolutely decimated there? What happened? I died twice.
OK, we're good. Let's do this the right way this time, please.
How do you miss that? It's so easy. I'm going to scream. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. He overhand
swung me in the head. Whatever that is. Let me. Whatever that is. A huge sword just dropped. His
big sword dropped. Oh, yeah. All right. Who's left? Nice. Very good. No more melee weapons.
Excuse me. Oh, those guts are worth a lot, right? There was a huge sword that dropped over here.
What is that? Knights Claymore. Oh, yep. OK, what should I get rid of? I feel like this thing's
cool, but should I just get rid of it? It's cool. It's good. Just take a picture of it. Oh, hold on.
You're right. Good idea. OK, ice rod. All right. Oh, damn, this thing's cool looking. Oh, all right.
I think I'm good. I don't have any more room. Keep the rod. Stop it. What should I get rid of?
Get rid of the twelve spear away. But look at it. It's shining. This thing's got to go.
Didn't I? This was in a chest. One of the guardian swords. I like it. I like that. What are you doing?
All right. I'm getting people. People are doing the. OK, whatever. Drop the spear. It's blue.
It's my favorite color. I'm not dropping it. I replaced the five bomb arrows I shot into nothing.
OK, here we go. We're going to keep going up the road, right? Yep. A is not there. I need some more
seeds. Yeah, I need some more seeds to upgrade that inventory. I forgot to blink. All right. So
I'm going to keep going this way. Hopefully this eventually leads to the mountain. I'm going away
from the mountain. Let go of the stick. Trust me. Huh? Are you serious? The horse will steer itself.
I did. Why would I have ever thought that was a thing? Are you serious? Wait, what's over here?
Yep. Stay right there. Stop. Red Choo Choo Jelly. Cool. I do that strategy, man. It doesn't work.
It's my first stream here. I had fun playing this. It's the first game I ever bought. Is that what
you said? I hope so. Yeah, that's great. It's really, really fun. OK, what's in the chest?
It's a hundred bucks. I'll take it. I mean, I'm not going to say no to a hundred dollars, right?
Cool. What else is down here? Some weird down here. Some weird shit down here. I'm getting the
ding ding. I'm getting dings here. Do the new viewer song. I can't do the new viewer song anymore.
Oh, it didn't hit. It hit somebody in there. Oh my God. That's so frustrating. I'm in trouble now.
I can't do the new viewer song anymore. My God. Get out of here. You got a big sword. Where's he
going? Stop. Stop swinging. I cannot even hurt these guys. What the fuck? No, I don't want to
eat any of this food. You know what I mean? I don't want to eat any of the food. It all seems
too important. I don't want to eat this. I'll eat this. OK. All right. Well, that could have gone
way better. That was a good shot. Are you guys trying to punch me in the face? Very good. All
right. Cool. Now let's do it. My God. My goodness. The big sword dropped. Yeah, I'll go get it.
Where did that guy die? All right. Cobble crusher. I think kind of sucks. This thing's almost broken
though. So whatever. Fuck it. I'll use it. What's in the chest? Oh, it can be used as a pickaxe.
Really? Oh, hell yeah. All right. Remind me not to use this for anything besides this. Very cool.
So where should I give it to me? Why are you so short? Because when God made me, he was like,
nah, this guy would be way too powerful. He'd be far too powerful if he was like six one.
Got to think of five, seven. Otherwise, it'd be like, you know, how can you stop this person?
Be unbeatable, unstoppable, you know, whatever. All right. What was in here? I wasn't paying
attention. That's OK. People said not to get rid of the phrenic bow. Oh, this thing's kind of
dumpy, right? Now I've got to find this shrine, wherever it is. Five fire arrows. All right.
I'll take it. That's 10 fire arrows. All right. Nice. It's the only ball that zooms in when you
use it. I think it's in here. I did it. Oh, nice. I've got four of them now. You can do that better.
I probably could, but I don't really feel like it. Where's Frank? Oh, he's up there.
It's definitely in here. It has to be right. Yeah, it's right there. All right. How are we?
Are we just not doing a vote here? Probably not. I don't think we're going to do it every time,
do we? You want to bet? You guys do? Why not? All right. Ten minutes. Ten minutes including
chest. Fine. Ten minutes including chest. From the moment that I skip and I'm able to move.
Five, five, seven. All right. Seven minutes including chest. I'm going to put my headphones
in and just shut the fuck up and do it as best as I can. Seven minutes including the chest.
What do you think? Is that a good time? Make it six? No, it's seven. Seven minutes. Oh,
I can do it. Hold on. I can run it. No, why am I running a poll? I don't know. How do I do it?
How do you do a prediction slash prediction? I actually don't. I like don't know how to do it.
I did it once. Flash prediction. Oh, okay. You're doing it. All right.
I've actually only done it one time. Oh, there we go. Okay. Somebody said they're going all in.
Oh, yeah. I'd be betting if I were you. Lock it in. Locked in. Locked in. That was fast. Yeah.
You got to be fast. Locked in. Let's go. I was too slow. Here we go. All right. It starts.
Not right. Hold on. Not yet. Not yet. Time begins. No, it's I got it. I got it.
I got this. Wait, there's like five chests in here. Oh, burn it. Burn it. Burn it. Burn it.
Burn it. Burn it. Quick. Quick. Quick. Burn it. Burn it. Burn it. Burn it. Burn it. How do I get
in there? I need a key to get in there. Where's the key? Where's the key? Where's the key? Where's
the key? I need a key to get in here. Where's the key? It's going to be one of the boxes.
That's it. I got it right. All of them. That's it. I win. Sorry, guys. Sorry. I had two minutes
to spare. I didn't miss a chest. I don't think. I got them all. Chest in the wall. Chest over there.
I got them all. Chat cheated. They showed you it was a magnet. No, that's not accurate.
Thought about that. It's not rigged. All right. Cool. So let me get back out on the road. What's
that? The mineral? Spam the magnet emote. There is no magnet emote. You. This is the referee.
Ooh. All right. Diamond. I got a diamond. I've got diamonds. Hmm. Okay. Back out to the road,
I think. Right. Back to kind of out here. Reality. Hmm. Frank too. Can't hear you. Why
not? Oh, you're far away. It's going to get back on the road. It's very good. I got to get back up.
Wait a minute. I forget this. Copas and salt. I keep hearing the reverse music. That means
it's going to be a moon, right? All right. Where are you, Frank? Go. Who are you? What's that word?
It's on the tip of my tongue, but I just can't think of it. Starts with L ends in K. What is
it though? Lurk, lick, leak or link? Uh, me? Oh, right. Yes. The Hylian champion. Or so I've heard
somewhere. That's you, right? Your link. You just pretend to not know who I was. That's kind of
weird. Wait. Nice. Stop fucking disappearing. Annoying. Frank, watch out. Frank, get out of
the way. I was going to say that was weird. All right. Now we want to go this way. Yep. Okay.
Keep going down the road. I see anything interesting. I'll stop.
That's interesting enough for me to stop. Nah. Hang a right. Yeah. I'm just going to go down
this road here. Bones. Cause then now I'm going to go yoink that way. Why is it playing this music?
This is definitely one of the- this is a bad guy right here, right? I just set a check.
Looking to buy bananas? You can. Just take a look at these fine bananas. Sure. I'll buy.
I did check. I- okay. I was right. I was literally right. I was right. I knew it. Oh,
whatever. Oh, you piece of shit. Ooh, that's pretty- wow. All right.
I mean, whatever. I'll just use this for now. He sounds like Eric Cartman.
But they're like, nah, nah, nah, these are my cheesy foods. It kind of does. Well,
I don't know what you think about that guy. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Cause if I go up this way,
I'm sure. Yeah. Surely I'll end up in the right spot, right? He's proud of himself. Yeah.
I got to get some of the lingo sometimes. What's this? Oh, I bet he's slacking off.
I mean, what's that? You're dying for some shield surfing action.
Chill out, my man. You don't need to worry about the details.
My best bud is standing over there beneath that tree. He can show you the ropes.
You're going to go up there? Yeah, why not? Finally, shield surfing gang. The shield breakers.
Yeah, this is a chat member. We're shield gang. Shield gang here. Live the experience. Okay.
The night shield is perfect for shredding. I already have one. Isn't that what I have right
now? This is perfect for shredding. Do I have to buy one? Or am I just going to just leave?
Should I just buy it? Just shred. I have to buy one? Well, I have no room. Stop talking.
You keep standing in the same spot. What? I talked to him. I just, I'm, he's saying buy a shield.
Oh, lie down the west of here. All right, let's go. Let's shred it up. How do I do it? ZL jump A.
That's B. Right. Jump. Cool. That it? Thanks for the tip.
There's nothing better than the generic rock song. I love the generic rock song.
That didn't, it's a, and usually it's, when it's on, it's on the piano or regular piano,
not a keyboard. They're like, done, done, done, done, done, done, done, done, done, done, done.
Aren't you 40? No, not yet, but soon. I don't know what you want me to say.
All right, let's go. So we get the tower. Wait, that's a weird rock.
Oh my God. Don't scare me like that. I know I did the red dead joke already,
but I want to just look at him and go. Oh, you're ugly. Hey, I'm just kidding with you.
You know, you look like a dumb son of a gun. I'm just playing around with you.
Why are you being so serious? I do it every time. Wait, what's that?
A stick. You don't like the water, do you? All right. You're good. Very nice job. You're,
look out. I thought he was going to get hit right in the head. He's going to drown. No, he's not.
He's fine. He's not being attacked by a wild animal, right? No, he's, Frank's fine. There's
a weirdo over there though. I'm kind of concerned about that. All right. He's, he's fine. Ooh,
this is stable. Cool. All right. Place your bets. Seven minutes to get the chest as well. I mean,
I can't win every time, right? Wait, what is that? What's the point of this? What does it do? What
should I do with it? Why can I pick this up? It's weird. What purpose? What is the charge?
I don't know. Does it matter? Do I have to do anything with this? I don't get it.
I don't get it. I'll come back later. It's all right. Come back later. All right. Are we betting
or what? Seven minutes and chest. That's locked in. All right. That's pretty 50, 50, really.
Seven minutes with the chest. That's a locked in. Let's go. There's nothing in there. I had to
replace it. All right. So that time begins. Not yet. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Chest,
sledgehammer. Okay. What do we got? What do we got? What do we got? What do we got? What do we got?
What's that do? All right. It goes. What did that do? Okay. It didn't, I don't know. It didn't do
anything. What did that do? What's that sound? I hear like ding. What's that mean? Okay. Let's
throw this and see what happens. Okay. Now what? Okay. It makes, it makes a new one. I got it. Okay.
So what do we do now? We need to, we need, we, but we're all in this. All of us. We, I say we.
What are we going to do? Okay. We are going to, um, what do you mean? No, no, it's we. Oh, I say we.
I'm going to, I don't know. Ice. I'm going to do ice. Um, that you actually do football. You
actually do have to do the football. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Shit. Okay. Um, yeah. Is that it? Is that not it? This is another one. Or is it another one?
I don't know. Um, wait. Okay. All right. All right. I get it. I know what to do. I know what to do.
Watch this. I get it. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. Ready? Oh, I know too. All right.
That would have killed me. I would have just died. I thought you had to ride on it. I thought you
had to ride on top of it. Okay. We're good. Oops. I just, ow, my fingernail. Okay. I win.
Imagine if I rode on top of that and just got splatted against the wall. That actually
would have been really funny. You didn't get the chest? What do you mean? What? What? What do you
mean not yet? What? What is the chest in here? I didn't get it. Wait. So I gotta get back in.
Where is it? Don't tell me. Okay. Hold on. I'll get it. All right. Four minutes. Three minutes.
All right. Speedrun strategy. Loading screens don't count, right? They like speed runs pause
the timer pauses until you get control of the character back, right? There's a chest in here
that I didn't get. What? Where did that go? Are you fucking kidding me? Oh, good. Fast. That was
fast. That was super. That was fast as fuck. All right. Where's the chest? Where is it? Where's the
chest? Where's the chest? Where's the chest? I don't see anything. I don't see a chest anywhere.
I don't know. I don't know where it is. This shit's hidden in a fucking wall somewhere.
Oh, I don't understand. Is that one there? Then wait a minute. What if I do this? Hold on. I got
an idea. It's probably inside. It's inside of this. Is it? I don't know. Is it inside? It's inside of
this thing. I have to smash it against the wall. It's inside. That's all right. I lose. Where is it?
Where is this chest that's apparently here somewhere? Magnet. Magnet. Yeah, but magnet. What?
Magnet? I don't see anything here. Hold on. Wait. Can I have... Can I hit... Wait a minute. This is
gonna move now. Okay. Then you move it down and that unlocks the next thing. Wait. What? What is
it? Where is this? Well, I got it. All right. Let him out. No. Look at the direction I'm facing. Why
would it do that? Dude. No. You idiot. You idiot. Oh my God. It's gonna be faster than that. This
thing's gonna break. Oh my God. It's so close. It's the one right below the maximum. This thing's
gonna break and then I'll be left with nothing. Oh, what the fuck? How many times? One, two,
three, four, five, six. Five times? Shoot it with an arrow? Stupid asshole. Oh my God.
Oh my God. Just look forward. All right. Here we go. Ready? What the fuck? I'm gonna break all my
weapons, man. All my weapons are gonna break. I'm gonna break every weapon. Hold Y? Yeah. When I
hold Y, I do this barbarian spin and I can't get the right angle. Dude. Hold Y? What are you talking
about, man? Stand still? You can't stand still. Look. Oh, you can stand still. You can stand still.
All right. Time that person up for an hour. I don't want to be looked... I don't want to time
the person up for five minutes. I don't, I don't, I don't get it. How many, how many hits should I
do with the spin? Seven? Seven. Do all of them. I'm out of weapons. I don't want to, I don't want to
break my weapons. Everything's... I broke another one. Oh yeah. It's gotta be good. I thought I was
gonna get like a light sword, like a lightsaber, like a light sword. What the fuck? That was,
what is that word? Not even worth it. It is good. Those are rare. Okay. Well, that was fun. It's
actually a good item. Giant ancient corp hog. If it actually is worth it, then that's cool.
Just warp to the shrine. Teleport. Wait. Oh, I can just leave. Where's he going? What does he look
like this? Why do people ask that every day? People ask that question every single day.
Hey, why does he look like this, man? I don't know. Why do you look like you?
Why do you look like that? Okay. So let's get back on the road. I'll figure that puzzle out later.
I have my elephant recovery. Do that now. Do the puzzle now. I don't even know what to do.
How can I do a puzzle now? Oh, okay. I'm good. I can't, how am I supposed to do it now? Figure
it out. I don't know what it wants me to do. Do what now? All right. Fine. I'll do it now.
Nice tuber reaction. Figure it. I'm gonna drown because somebody was calling me a name in chat
and I looked at it. All right. I have stamina, right? I just don't want to drown. I don't think
I have any stamina food. I think it's over. It's over. I'm gonna drown here. All right. So
what do you want me to do now? So this is a puzzle. Figure it out. It's a puzzle. I mean,
I think I understand what it wants me to do. Let's see if it's as simple as I think it is.
Like a better camera angle, please. You don't just connect it. I figured it was like one,
two, three, four, right? You connect it, connect them all. That has to be what you do. What the
hell is with this before? Can I push it? Okay. That's not what you do. So I guess it's a little
more complicated. Are there any instructions on it? Yes. I know it's a magnet. I understand it's a
magnet. Yes. I currently am using a magnet. I put it through it. I didn't work. I put it through.
I did a field goal and it didn't work. What even is that? I don't even know what that is.
Do I have to swim through it? Wait, there's another one over here.
Was it a typewriter? What is that? What email is this? Copy this. Copy this. Copy this. I don't
know what I copy. Like I have to copy it. Copy this. Copy this. I don't know how do I copy it?
There's no such thing as copy. Should we free them? Yeah, let them out. Let them out. I don't
know. I can't do it. I don't understand it. I don't get it. Copy this. It's a really good hint.
Copy. Copy. Copy this. Do I have to match the other one? But the other one already is. Looks
like that. Where did it go? Yeah, the one already. Oh, wait a minute. That doesn't.
Oh, wait. Hold on. Oh, okay. Oh, okay. Uh huh. I dropped that fucking cube on the ground 30
times over here and it didn't land in that spot. I desperately tried to put it down like five times.
You're stupid. Yeah. Oh, you got to copy the one under there. How would you know that? You didn't
know that. You went to, you went to, uh, you, you went to the extra life dot breath of the wild dot
whatever. And you had to look it up. This is the single most infuriating thing I've ever watched in
my entire life. How is Jerma a functioning human? Cause I didn't see, I didn't see the puzzle
underground. Okay. If, if a live streamer not doing a puzzle correct is the most worst thing
you've ever seen in your life. Whoa. Whoa. That's the worst thing ever you've ever seen.
Holy shit. It started raining. I, it's raining. I can't see shit. It's the second worst thing I've
ever seen. You didn't know where to put the, you didn't know how to take the cube from that place
and put it where the cube goes. How do you put your pants on every day? It's impossible. You know
what? Look, they're on, they're on and they're tied correctly. I know how to tie my shoes too.
To be fair, they didn't have 21,000 chat chimpanzees throwing coffee machines at them.
All right. So let me upgrade my gear. All right. Shields, definitely shields. I don't know how to
tie my pants. It's not hard. Hmm. Again, I think again, two shields. Weapon is three or four. Hey
Jerma, if you're getting stressed by these comments, it's a cigarette joke. Nevermind. All
right. What do we got? We keep going. A weapon is three or four. Okay. I'm going to save it
because I want to do weapon again. Or should it bow? We love you Jerma. We have to guide you to
victory. I'm going to figure it out. Give me a minute. All the route. Hope you enjoy the game.
Take it slow. Okay. For every, for every one person that says enjoy the game and take it slow. Don't
rush. Just take it at your pace. So it's like a one to one to how did he not finish this puzzle
in 10 seconds? Push him, push him to his limits. I don't mind you struggling with a toddler puzzle
as long as you can prove you can dodge a battle act. I just fucked that guy up. How was that? Huh?
How's that for a gamer? Put that in your, in your textbook and go and go learn. All right. Where am
I going? Wrong way. It's weird that all the CEOs of major cigarette companies hang out in Twitch
chats all day. That's so stupid. Does the road split? Should I go this way? Bad marketing.
Just imagine like a cigarette company CEO just sitting there just
like a tank top and his underwear just lying in bed. Just like, Hey, you should, um,
have you ever smoked a cigarette? Cigarette comedians. I'm just, I don't know. I'm tower,
tower, tower. All right. I'm ready. This is going to be sick. And when you couldn't read a clock.
Yeah. Cause I was wicked high. Okay. I'm sorry. What we get, you get where you want me to defend
every bonehead move in a game I've done. I happen to be a little bit on the side. I was a little bit
high at the time. I wasn't even trying to target that guy. Don't die. Holy shit. This weapon is
amazing. I don't want to break it. I will dodge your fucking acts in real life. I will. I swear
to God, I will contact some like martial artist group. And if you get, go to go into like a
martial artist studio and fucking dodge a bunch of weapons on screen. I swear to God,
I will do a, like, I, this is what would happen if I was ever like attacked by an act stream.
Wow. Oh no, that's not that don't do not spoil what the joke would be though.
Come on. Don't do that. Don't spoil the joke. Don't spoil. Do not spoil the joke.
Come on. Biting my lip. Don't spoil the joke. Please. Just wait. Just wait. Just wait.
I okay. I'm going to do this soon. I'm going to do this really soon.
This is not going to take that much time to do. So I'm going to do it very soon.
Was there a chest? Okay. I'm like, this stream is going to be, this stream is going to be funny.
No spoilers. I'm going to do it. I'm going to try to do this like this month.
It's not going to take a whole lot of time to get ready, bro. The tower. All right. Yeah.
Why did I think that it ended right there? All I saw was this and I thought it was the clip
red sky. I'll be fine. And the title of that scream is going to literally be the dodge.
The battle act scream. Okay. I don't, it doesn't need a fancy title. I don't even,
I don't need to, I need to sponsor that stream. It doesn't, I don't have to do that.
I mean, maybe it'd be kind of funny. I don't know. I'm into this now. I swear to God, I'm going to
make it. I'm going to scheme. It's going to be such a fucking scheme. I can't wait. All right.
That's literally, I'm not going to say anything else. All right. I got to just wait because the
blood moon is going to happen, right? And they're going to respond anyways. They're going to respond
anyways. Just whatever. I'll, I'll tell the mods. I was typing. I was typing to the whatever. Okay.
I just, what, what just happened? Is it, I'm very confused. Why is it raining meteors? Is this water
boiling? Who is doing this? Okay. Where, this guy's annoying. This guy's really annoying.
This guy's fucking annoying. Okay. Hold on. Can you be in a spot where I can actually fucking hit you
with a weapon? Oh my God. Give me that thing. Fuck away from me. Ooh. I'll take the fire rod.
Annoying dick. Okay. So is this thing boiling? I think this is burning hot. That's why, right?
Oh, it's quicksand. Okay. You just die if you're going. All right. So now I get it. So I can't go
that way. How do I not have a weapon equipped? See you later. Goodbye. See you later. Hmm.
Would ice actually work here? Is this technically water? Okay. I thought it was sludge or something.
One regular arrow. I don't think I can make this jump. Don't you fucking dare. Oh my God. I panicked
so much from that guy shooting at me. I'm going to just electrify the fucking whole thing. Just
get out of here. Little shit head. No, don't, don't. If you fire at me, I will be very upset.
Don't even think about it. Okay. Now I can do this in peace. Chest over there. Remember the
cigarette CEOs are winning. Don't let them win. Every time you see somebody write about a cigarette
in the chat, I want you to write extra lettuce or something. No. What's like a healthy thing? I don't
know. Exercise regularly. Yeah. All right. So I need to go over that. Is there anything else over
here? What is, what's that for? That'd be a reason, right? What's this here? This is a weird thing.
Just be sitting right here. Ooh. I'll take that. Sleeping. This thing's broken anyways. So just
drop it. Wasn't it a Knight's bow in there? Okay. I'm going to head back there. Ooh. Can I even break
this though? Oh wait, I have bombs. Hell yeah. Power time. Woodland power. Okay. Can I just climb
it? I think so. All right. Find out something up there too. I can't wait for this stream. It's all
I can think about right now. Am I going to make it? I don't think so. Dude. What? That's impossible.
I fell in the pixel perfect place to die. This has got to be a different hold on. I have to just
climb this. I don't think I can even make it. I don't have stamina. Wait, drink a climb potion.
You wouldn't have been able to do that if you tried to do that. You genuinely would not have
been able to do what I just did if you tried to like a hundred times over and over again. It's
honest to God. I don't think you'd be able to do that. You can't throw shit, right? You can.
What? I thought the rock boomerang didn't hit me. I thought the rock boomerang didn't hit me.
It's you. Oh my God. No. Oh my God. I just got the full heal thing. I'm okay. I'm fucking done.
Jerma's not here anymore. My name is extra lettuce. He's smoking a cigarette under the shirt.
Did I get? Did I do it? I hear the music. Nice. Nice. New area unlocked. I don't know. I don't
know about. I can see stinks in there. I had to come out. Okay. So we're that's cool. I'm kidding.
I smell fine. All right. So this is a great Hyrule forest. Weird. Let me actually take a quick look.
You want to know what I actually smell like? Let's see. Uh, cigarettes. Oh yeah. I'm sorry.
Lettuce. Don't smoke cigarettes. Seriously. Don't smoke cigarettes. Don't. Don't do it. Eat. Get
healthy and exercise and eat radishes and shit and like drink water and you know, whatever,
but don't, don't smoke cigarettes. It's really not good, but you know, you're going to do what
you're going to do. I can't stop you, but don't if you can, but you try to quit, you know, or reduce.
What the fuck is that? What is this? What the fuck is this? This is an AI image.
They just, okay, I need to show this. They extended that image with AI. That's insane.
Why is this a thing? What does this mean? What does this mean? What does this mean? What?
That's what I'm holding down here. Is it a Nintendo Wii back there? It's a fortune teller.
It looks like you're about to do an alt. Oh my God. Are those my legs? Are these my legs on the
right? Am I sitting with like jeans on? No, no, no, no. I'm in like a beanbag chair. Oh my God.
Post-apocalyptic human lettuce mutant. You're bigger than the chair. I didn't even look. What?
What the shit? I don't understand. I think I'm sitting in a beanbag chair.
Why is there a Wii? I mean, there is, there is a Wii. There is a Wii. So that's actually there.
Okay. Let me take a look. There's some shrines probably out here. I don't see any shrines
actually. Hello? Are we good? I hope so. I don't see anything. I don't think there's any shrines
that way. Go back here. Hard to tell. Okay. Cool. I can go up that way. Can I get up there that way?
Okay. Climb up one. Climb the skull. Climb the skull. Climb the skull. I missed it.
I just want to see what's over here. I can always teleport. Oh wow. That's cool. Go to the woods. I
will. I just want to see what's over here. Stop rushing me in my playthrough. Derma, you're not
doing puzzles fast enough. Derma, climb the skull. This is my playthrough. I'm going to go where I
want to go. You got your playthrough. I get my, it's my playthrough and I want macaroni and cheese
for dinner and an egg. Just one cooked. No, I want McDonald's. My playthrough. I get to decide what
food I have to. Baby. Spoiled. Ow. What happened? Oh, it's heat. Put it out. Okay. So this is made
out of wood. So get rid of it. Ooh. Go fight already. Am I just going to get burned if I walk
over here though? Does this hurt? Okay. The air hurts. So hold on. I specifically made food for
this exact purpose. Although my brain's itching. Okay. So this is 10 minutes of fire proof. Is
this a good idea? Yeah. You can swim in the lava. Yeah. All right. What else is on fire? Something's
burning. Oh, it's me. Oh, yikes. It's me. Right? Come on. I've seen this episode a million times.
How do I, does it matter? I'm just going to try to get over there or whatever.
Ooh. Crunchies. Put the bow away. I switched the bow. What? Ice rod. Now I'm decked out. Okay.
I'm here. Cool. Should I grab anything? I think I have to just get up here, right? You're in the
volcano for fuck's sake. I know. Dude, I'm trying to figure out how to get in here. I'm on a time
limit. I can't really stick around. Yeah. What's that? Water. I hear water. Oh Lord. Okay. I don't
have much time. Um, I wonder if there's a place where I'm safe from the fire or something. Whoa.
What is this? Yep. Hold on. I don't have time to explore that. How do I go? Um, where should I go?
I don't know. I'm just going to keep going this way. Where's your flame guard?
Unk. Oh, really? Where? Where is it? Oh, it's a chameleon. How am I going to actually be able
to get up there in 10 minutes? That's a good question. Oh, hey, what's up? What's going on
city? All right. Cool. Well, looky here. Welcome master link. How did you know? What do you mean?
More importantly, I hope you made it past all those magma bombs without injury. To be honest,
we haven't had many visitors here since those magma bombs started falling from the sky.
I'd be bored to tears if I didn't pass the time pretending to greet the long lost Hylian champion.
Heh. Oh, in case you didn't know, uh, link is the little Hylian who fought alongside the
Goron champion Daruk. You want to hear more? Talk to the boss. He lives further in town.
Am I safe in here? No, it's like a million degrees. I didn't mean, did I hit you with that?
Am I actually, uh, well, I die in six minutes. Maybe I can buy like a flame suit from town here.
I bet you I can. I'd be shocked if you couldn't. Who sells this armor? That blasted Rudania.
With Rudania running wild recently, Death Mountain's eruptions have gotten real bad.
Do you see Rudania stomping around up there on the mountain? They say that a hundred years ago,
it actually used to protect our people from harm. But that was then and this is now. Now all it does
is mess up our mining operations. We're all suffering because it's stopping us from doing
business. Can't tell you how many times we've used the cannon to chase off that fiend. But it
always comes back. Oh. Ouch. Ow. Just some back pain. Wait, who are you? I see. So then you came
all this way to pay your respects to me. I like you already, brother. Well, my name's Bluto.
I'm the great Goron boss who's fearsome enough to silence a crying child or to make a silent child
cry either way. Yes, it's none other than I, Bluto. I was planning on a drive off Rudania,
like I always do. But then this blasted pain in my back flared up out of nowhere. Blasted
Yunovo. When will he return? Yunovo is a young Goron who helps me drive off
Rudania. He went to grab some painkillers from my back room out of the abandoned North Mine.
Really hasn't come back yet. Slacker. I bet. Hey, I'm gonna see Yunovo. Let him know I'm looking for
Goku. Ah, oh ouch. Okay. I need to buy armor. He said the thing. Oh, yay. He said it.
That's the one thing I have not retired, right? I keep doing the Mr. Satan. I just won't stop it.
Okay, there is, okay, right here. I got a lot of money. Should be good, right? Okay.
Oh, right. Here we go. All right. Flame Breaker Armor. It's made fire-resistant rocks to protect
the wear. How much is it? 600? I need it. Cool. Now, what about the other stuff? Flame Guard sits
700. If I just have one piece, is that okay? Would you need the whole set? I need the whole set. No
way. I have a lot of gems. I should probably go upgrade it too though, right? I need at least two.
Two out of three will protect you. Okay. What's the cheapest one? I probably should get the pants
and upgrade it. The one piece is real. Okay. This is 2000. What? Why is that so expensive?
Excuse me? I need to go to the forest area and upgrade this. This is a three armor. Are you
kidding me? That's terrible. Yeah, I'm getting out of here. I do need to get to a shrine first,
which I think is probably one here. I'm not staying. I need to find the shrine so I can
teleport back here. You need the helmet. Where's the shrine? Above? I need a place to teleport to
because I can't teleport to over here yet. The shrine. You don't need the helmet. You only need
one piece. The one piece is real, I suppose. What's this? God damn it. Don't just get rid of it.
Look at that up there. I'm trying to find the shrine. I'm going up here. It's definitely up.
Has to be. You stupid Mega Man enemy. I hate those things. Where is it? Can I move this?
Let's go. That was fun. There it is. Yes. Shrine time. What do we think? Seven minutes with the
chest. Hello? What was that? Oh, it's you. Seven minutes with the chest. I think that sounds pretty
good. So to me, I didn't touch anything. I was resting my leg. I got the armor. It's on right
now. Look. He's looking right at me. I didn't like that. That was weird. All right. Get it in.
Let's go. You know the deal. Right when I get control of the character. One second. Go. Get
those bets in. I'm going to concentrate. I'm not going to talk. Here we go. Get them in. What is
it? Here we... I need fire. I need fire. Make our own. Okay. All right. Chest. Stone. Holy shit. Is
that 42 damage? Goodness. This thing is insane. Okay. I got that. Now we need to burn something.
All right. I don't know why I did that, but I did it. Guardian sword. Chest. Okay. That's two chests
down. Take a look over here. I know what to do about this. I think. Uh huh. Nevermind. Go this
way. Key. I need a key. This place is huge. How am I ever going to do this in seven minutes?
This place is enormous, guys. How was I supposed to ever do this? Why did I just do that?
Whatever. This place is enormous. It's enormous. There's no way I was going to get this done.
Not a chance in hell. Don't. Congratulations to everybody. This is the longest dungeon I've done
so far. Don't roll off. What is stopping? Stay here. Don't fucking move. I didn't know you could
even do that. Okay. Now. All right. I got the right idea. Whatever. Fuck it. I got the right
idea. You might as well pay out the people that bet against it because there's no way I'm going
to do this. Wait. I don't even need to do that anymore. Hold on. Oops. Okay. Cool. Key. Wait a
minute. How much time? What do I have? Time? What's my time? What's my time? What's my time?
What's my time? Not even close. Congratulations. You won. What does this do? Okay. I can't grab
that. No. What? Why did it want me to come down? What was it for? What was that even for? Okay.
Do I need to do anything else over there? I mean I need to get the barrel. I'm just going to burn
it but I can't like yank it. I mean technically I could. Does this work? Can I just break it?
I could hit it with a sword or something. Arrows? I could just shoot it with a fire arrow. I don't
have any arrows. I mean I'm just going to. Will the bomb work? Does the bomb cause fire? I don't
think I've ever tested this. Okay that worked. Oh my god. It was literally right here. So many
people are probably just going like just shoot it. Shoot it with a fucking arrow. Just screaming
and they lost all their points. I'm sitting here like oh puzzle. Okay so like oh oh yeah put that
over there. Oh yeah then move that and no that's I just shoot with an arrow. Dude you suck. Hey
close it. Close this. Close this. I don't want to hear it. I don't want to. I don't even want to
hear it. Pay him up. Pay him up. Pay him up. You over thought that so much. Yep I don't know. I
think it's like oh it's a puzzle. I gotta be careful. What if I get it wrong and chat goes oh
I'm just I don't know. I'm thinking about people thinking I'm stupid and then I just don't shoot
it with an arrow. Did I get the chest? I got all the chests right? So I have a teleport now. Wait
let me let me check over here. You just killed those birds. I didn't. You are a monster.
All right I promise I wouldn't scream today. Hello. So many people out and about. You should
know it gets much harder past here. There are also lots of monsters. It's dangerous. This is
the abandoned north mine. Oh and this is the little ditty we all used to sing as we worked.
Ammo goes boom till ore fills the room. Gather said ore for rupees galore. Dig all day to get
the good pay. That's a pretty good song. Oh there's more. You get the idea. You gotta put your
stand up. You gotta put your hands up. What stranger like you asking about Unobo? The boss
wants to know. What? Okay. I went to the vault to fetch some painkillers but now that you mentioned
it I suppose he never came back. It's dangerous. Don't go looking for him. Okay. Vine beast va
Rudania. All right. Cool cool cool cool cool cool cool. All right I need to get the heck out of
here because I want to upgrade the the gear. That was where? Down here right? No no no no no.
Over here? Right here right? Pagariko yep. Did you already add germa turtle? That was quick. Oh from
when I started singing to when the singing stopped I lost 400 sub. I'm just kidding I made
that up. I made it up. I'm kidding. So what does it take to upgrade this gear? I wonder. What am I
going to be for Halloween? Um a turtle. Shit. All right I need fireproof lizards. What do I get
those? Did I ever take a picture of those? Aren't they kind of just running around outside? You said
you're going to be a pineapple. They're all okay so I gotta go back there. Buy more from beetle?
Okay. I've seen them run around as they catch them. How much longer are you going to stream for?
Um I don't know. Maybe like an hour or two. I definitely will at the very least get inside of
the divine beast area right? Okay looking for lizards. If I see a lizard I want to take a
picture of it. Get the camera ready. Lizards. I'm just looking. I'm just scanning the ground.
I'm just trying to see if I can see any. See any? That didn't count. There we go. Nice. Okay. What
the fuck? All right. How many do I need? I need 12. That's a lot. Oh I don't want to watch that.
Uh okay down here. I don't okay. I can't go there. You're gonna scare the fish. Get out of here. I
don't see one. Oh wait right here? No. How many do I need? Two or three or four? Just two? I need
nine more. I don't have the materials to even make it. You only need two with your current
upgrade kit. All right so I'm good then. Let's do two. Okay that makes sense. Do you have the
strategy guide open on another monitor? Uh dude shut up. Um shut up. Shut the fuck up. All right
so let's go do this. Omega lull. It's such a classic song. All right this will go to five.
It's not that much. Better than nothing. Better than nothing. Could I do this again?
Mm-hmm. Oh wait. I am so dumb. I okay. Do you know why? Because it was in the same slot. So I was
like wait I can't. No because it was literally the same spot and it moved. If you got all the
chests in a shrine there should be a chest icon near or on the shrine's map. Oh all right. That's
good to know. Do I have anything? Can I do anything else? I guess I could do this. Am I going to
utilize this again? Try to just do it while I'm here. Yeah probably. Not worth it. Oh because I
already. I mean not really. Just kind of a swimming. All right cool. Let's. I have plenty of healing.
I got tons of food and shit. So I think I'll be all right. So let me head to uh the divine beast.
See how it goes. Post the tweet draft. You know what? I think I still copy and pasted it. Let me
see. Yeah no it's yeah literally still copy. It's still on my clipboard. We were talking about the
adult happy meal that I was like wait how is that. There's an adult happy meal coming out or
something. And I was like what does that even mean? It's just a regular meal. That's what an
adult happy meal is. And we were talking about like what the hell would even be in it. And I
was going to write a tweet that said uh the adult happy meal colon one single can of Bud Light,
two cigarettes, a 10-piece nugget, and three business cards. One for a landscaping company,
one for a CPA, and one for a real estate agent. I'm gonna put it in the draft. I thought I put it
in the draft. You know I'll launder it for a while. Honestly though what is what what is in
the adult happy meal? I'm imagining a bunch of businessmen in suits going to McDonald's and
getting happy meals rather than going out for drinks. What's in it? It's so funny how this is
rated E for everyone but Mario Odyssey technically isn't because it has a tank. What? Is that real?
Dude it's just a solid gold bar. That's I don't even know that's like a funny joke I guess. But
like what are you that's like so outrageous I don't even I can't even laugh at that. Like
what is that what are you talking about? Why would there be a solid gold bar in a fucking happy meal?
Oh is there a better way to go here? Oh wait oh no no no I turn this off this is just for the
lizards right yeah okay is there a oh I can't do ice over here right I got that I didn't even
know he died okay can I do the ice cubes here oh my god was that my good one oh my goodness
no it was the shitty one thank god what the fuck just happened okay I was I can't it's hurt if I
walk in this that hurts a lot oh cool who cares though what's that what does that do for me
can I move it I didn't know that was a lever look at that that does not look like a lever
what the hell that's like a just a big chunk of metal sticking out of the ground
okay am I gonna gonzo out of this I was about to shoot myself in the face with a cannon
what do I do uh I actually kind of don't get it my fucking looney toons character all right well
do I feel like what is it even doing should I go catch it or something or it has to be a reason
for what that or that let me load it first hold on okay so what else can I even do over here
it's hitting right here what does that matter what was it I mean that was kind of cool but
didn't really do anything oh there's another cannon nice nice dude hi up you guys can't even
reach the soldiers but I'll just get rid of it the cannon over there let's go yep see that
you watching nice close again oh man it's sometimes it hurts to be so good
really I said you're not funny you've been subbed for like three months you're a liar no don't
fall hey well my mother said I was funny so sorry I really have to destroy the whole thing kind of
excessive oh shit cool your thoughts on aging and dying um uh damn I mean you got it's crazy
shrine over here this I like this uh zone this is cool just in case there's something over there
that'll do it right yes oh what's in there is the music a bit what oh my god you freaked me out I
thought there was a song playing this whole time two chests in here you know now that I got a good
look at it yeah that's definitely that's gotta be a holly are you doing I'm kidding I'm making them
make it to stop all right we the one who broke through that crag to rescue me Goro thanks brother
what brought you all the way out here to begin with so where how do we get to the divine beast
from here everyone calls me you know Bo makes sense Goro I came to get some painkillers for
boss but a magma bomb caused a rock slide sealing the entrance by the way how did you break those
rocks the entrance you use the boss's cannons I think it's so difficult to use I thought only
boss could handle it it's not the time to chat I got to deliver these painkillers there's a reward
for you this is a little side quest or is this part of the main uh story that was fun there's
a shrine out here too nice I need that money whatever why don't I pick up some through the
wall or something lots of ice arrows you get the shaggy look again it's because I have a
green shirt on all right very cool where is the shrine this thing was beeping
I have to ride on a mine cart can I get there from here oh maybe I can hold on
oh this scared the shit out of me all right um what's the point of these rocks then um I'm
just gonna go back I'll turn around and come down this way though let me mark on the map where that
is I think that's important well now I'm just dead I literally can't leave I have to teleport
out make an up wait bomb launch yourself time that person up five minutes make a fire what the
why do they make what happened why don't make three all right let's go okay all right how do
I do it how do I use it how do I do this how do I do it does I need more more wood it actually
worked I thought you guys were just making jokes wow all right I made it are you serious it actually
worked so now can I spider-man under here I thought I could spider-man under here
okay we're good no no god okay I'm fine stop screaming and relax you're gonna spawn right
there oh my god oh my god oh my god all right oh the cart doesn't work it's probably at the very
end all right if I can make it the entire track by walking this whole thing what do I get I try it
okay let me just see how the how fun this is we're good let me go wicked fast I didn't make it go
faster use bombs um I don't want to blow that up I don't get it no stasis just bomb wait you put a
bomb in here what the fuck does that actually work if I want to go this way I mean it kind of
worked oh I was protected I thought where am I gonna end up all right we're good why was that
it didn't happen the first three times all right I get it that's fun we doing a timer no no shrine
bit this time ah well we're doing it I gotta pause it so you guys can't see yeah I don't want
you to see what it is you know what I mean because then I don't want to give you guys a
oh wait this is what it is I don't want you to see oh my god dude what holy shit this is going to be
impossible oh my god this is impossible I just want to let everybody know is he serious or is
it a minor test of strength I don't know okay we are going to begin uh by the way this looks
like it's gonna be fucking impossible and I meant that three two one start fire okay water flame
over there fire over here uh torch oh shit um what can I get rid of just take the fire rod
and swing it stuff I'll go back for the chest don't worry how much time do I have I'll go back
for it let's go um wait wait wait wait wait what happened I can't light this I can't light that
with the blue one what is that for real I think wait I can I walk that sucks no what am I supposed
to do this I have to walk I cannot go over here how am I physically able how am I physically going
to be able to get it to get over there what is blue I just blew up I blew up something I tried
I tried it um is there a ball or something I wish I had a flame to shoot or something I don't know
I don't know I actually just don't know it's gonna take me more than like five minutes to
figure it out I need arrows what the fuck I need arrows you do with arrows right I just don't have
any it's like a weird other way to do this that I just don't I don't understand shit how do I get
that I can't reach from here what do I have for time oh I'll get the chest at least I don't know
why Mario doesn't decide to grab it has half the time holy shit that's an amazing bow sorry guys
all I can do is just shoot it from here or something I don't know what if I shoot it from here
well I completely missed but whatever um I don't know I'll figure it out eventually
the ice it's hot hot I don't know I don't know I lose you guys win sorry tried I had arrows this
would be no problem at all but I don't so I gotta let them out football throw football
burn the wood and fly all right burn a shit load of wood and fly up that actually is funny
it was saying throw the torch oh but yeah I don't think I can make it from here
I can't make it from there okay I honestly did not think I could make it that far I was like this
there was no chance in my brain that that was gonna make it I didn't even want to attempt it
because it was like it's not possible like there's no way you can go that far that was just a that
was a complete thought oh throw the torch that was the first thing I thought of and it's like oh
okay no no way no chance in hell it's not possible it just physically isn't possible
but apparently it is you go okay throw the torch you guys are so funny all right well let's try it
again oh shit gamer fatigue no that's not it oh these are all lit no not gamer fatigue
oops it's still up there oh my god I think I've died no it's not gamer fatigue it's not
gamer fatigue is it gamer fatigue it could be just all right I'm gonna build a fire why are
they not burning uh is it enough I've no what else can can I burn anything else it's one more
oh my god they don't work in shrines okay well whatever I I need to I need to restart wind
doesn't work in shrines that's unfortunate that's sad crying pepe it's like no it can't be
it almost just took I was just okay I almost just kept running and I was like oh I made it
and then the camera pans around and half of my other half behind me is gone it's like you just
see through everything it's like I'm cutting half this way okay let's try it again this is burning
me just die I have to do it again you have another torch I don't have any arrows go buy
arrows I'm already in here you're trending on Twitter why what I do you can teleport I know
but I have to at least prove that I'm capable of doing this one arrow Andy just buy arrows where
are they who sells them who sells them don't tell him he doesn't want to know he doesn't need to
know your forehead's big it's not it's not it just really isn't what do you know no my forehead's
not big my hairline is receding get it right okay uh who sells arrows here general store
I imagine the general store yeah I have a normal sized forehead it's just my hair is going backwards
you have arrows here you got arrows you do I want them all what are these you got these arrows I'm
all of them any more arrows in this house I want these I want them all FSO you this person has a
quest I'll do it later Graham drops uh-oh what's your favorite piano note uh the one that sounds
like this you know the one the very end either the very end of the right side or the very end
of the left side because you just press it hard ones on the left and it's a scary noise and then
you go to the right and you do the last two notes into just one two one two one two one two and it
could be something magical or somebody sneaking along like this you know or just do the shrine
all right if I stand up am I dead I can't stand up I can't stand up I couldn't even hear what that
sounded like because I'm plugged in I'm listening to the switch audio not the desktop audio drop
the frames I know it's because I don't know for some reason every time I try to stream at eight
o'clock to nine p.m. I have issues I don't care it's fine all right we're good I am gonna eat
though very cool so let's do this imagine that's the thing to do bye and imagine if I had arrows I
would have just beat it 60 that thing is so so good uh okay two chests up here oh all right
that's cool big flame sword these are really really good items for just kind of walking up here
okay I don't have the torch anymore rate this game out of 10 I know you people keep asking me
to do that but wait oh this water spraying oh shit okay um hold on um wait hold on a second okay
all right uh well I have an idea then at the same time oh wait okay okay um okay okay
I'm gonna be streaming for windows 94 computer what does that mean we're good oh wait a minute
there's a lot of chests in this one I was never gonna do this in seven minutes
horse dweller sword I think it's time to get rid of this 22 damage it's good I'm running out of
shitty weapons to care about do not care about oh burn all right cool guardian spirit oh my
goodness I can't pick any of these up um shit I don't know what to do I guess I could get rid
of this what's better you're lagging I know it doesn't matter I I guess I'll get rid of the
get rid of the fire rod yeah it's cool but
what guardian spear ancient battleaxe 30 versus okay now this is probably it's 30 damage
everything else is good maybe get rid of the cobble crusher and pick up the
sword guardian sword is 20 versus yeah no heavy weapons suck keep whatever you like I like the
fast weapons the might you but what about mining oh you're right yeah I forgot about the mining
that's true that's true what on earth hmm this is interesting how am I gonna do this
oh shit I'm in trouble here I don't think I can make it use the sword the wooden sword I just
got it though this thing's cool this thing I'm burning this thing this thing's awesome
got it frames are dropping frames are dropping you honestly I wonder why between eight and nine
pm sometimes specific and then it's fine it's fine all day fine after I wonder what's going on
well I mean uh all the eu fans will tell me this is the great idea to just stream an hour or two
earlier that's the thing higher traffic shouldn't matter I have I have fiber I have a gigabit line
that I don't share a connection with anybody else so it shouldn't matter I don't have I don't
share like a node with a neighborhood or anything I do not share a node sorry it's me chewing on
your internet wire oh well stop a giga line yeah I'd say I have a giga chad line all right let
me move this is that correct up there that's fun I'm gonna go um turn in that main quest
yeah but it's super strange I really don't really have an answer because um technically speaking
in a technical sense it's not like oh it's peak hours you should that's it happens it shouldn't
be I like I said gigabit to I have a gigabit to the street so I don't there's no sharing of
the internet with the node or whatever um and it's perfect it's bad for like 40 minutes between like
8 20 and like 9 it's weird something with the way the traffic is hopping from like 8 pm to 9 pm
it just hates it I don't know well I don't want to get upset about it I know that I always go on
these are kind of tangents where it's like I don't know I don't know I let me I let me talk
let's talk about it again let me go over like 40 straight minutes of why the internet's not
um it's gonna play it's all right it's what it is it is what it is it'll get better okay here's
the reward that's a pretty good reward see that statue um I can't uh we can we move out of the
way oh all right back when I was in high school we literally had squirrels munch on our lines
that's so that sucks but that's like so funny for some reason
let those other champions know they better eat their gravel and want to keep up with the roof
speaking of which can you believe this you just look at all those delectable rocks sprinkled on
those mountains mighty tasty I may not know a whole lot about this calamity cannon thing
but mark my words I'll protect this land of ours to the death right little guys
they could have killed me hey by the way congrats on becoming the princess's appointed knight
that's a really big deal protecting the king's daughter no pressure seriously though the
princess is a strong personality so strong she can't quite see the range for the peaks
remember that and you'll be fine so what was I saying that was a little strange as far as I
know death mountain has been quiet for decades but if the mountain is shivering enough to send
down a bunch of boulders that size then never mind forget I said anything
it's gotten into you highly ensure our strange anyway you know but he's actually descendant of
the great Daruk okay that's why that slacker can even use Daruk's protection he's to protect
himself when we fire at rudania that's the only way we can chase that blasted beast away
we have no choice because normal cannonballs are no good against him all right that's enough
out of me time to go drive off rudania oh gosh are you okay yeah just peachy dumb traveler of
course I'm not okay oh wow I'm afraid I won't be going anywhere today I hate to put you on the
spot but can you please go tell it you know both that I'm gonna have to cancel for today
you should be at Eldon bridge Eldon bridge all right let's go to Eldon bridge Eldon bridge all
right Eldon ring cool let's do it simulation is breaking what I frames internet frames internet
you know what I mean uh should I buy some stuff before I go over here like I should purchase some
stuff or am I just ready look at all this are you kidding me look at all this shit I have
you need more arrows should I get more arrows I have 42 ice arrows I think I'm all right
I'm just gonna go for it it's the quickest way over there you can never have enough regular
arrows well I'll just buy some more then there's the uh store where is the general store all right
what do you got uh you've got you don't have regular arrows in here cane sugar um sure I'll
take two spices no regular arrows do you have arrows at least free no all right let's go what's
the best way to get up there wrap around oh wait a second here I've got guys heart or stamina
stamina I'll do stamina and heart stamina twice how much longer you're gonna scream for uh probably
be calling it very soon over the next like 10 to 15 minutes maybe I'll do two stamina now again
I just go full on stamina I'm doing it it's probably a mistake but whatever he's gonna be
gone for 12 days what's this you look like Minecraft Steve he has a blue shirt what are
you talking about how do I get up there don't hit me don't yeah where is it that where's the shrine
you can't hide a shrine hide a shrine I think it's time to end stream I think that's it and
yes I can confirm I will be playing breath of the wild again I will be streaming it again
oh okay hold on this makes me happy when they come up right doesn't make you happy I don't know it
just does scary all right if I can find the shrine I will end the stream after this shrine
unless it's not talking about the dinosaur thing over there right when is your next stream I don't
know when my next stream is going to be at some point in the next week and a half you don't know
I'm sorry to say I will be I'm gonna be taking a break I have a lot of friends and family members
that I want to see kind of overdue haven't seen some family in a pretty long time so
and then I'm gonna go do some stuff with some friends too and
go watch out bats bats bats I'm so sorry that's so scary they just just ran at me
geez you missed is there a uh is there a card over here where's the shrine ah there it is nice
all right we'll do this last run yeah sorry about the internet it just it just randomly does this
at night sometimes you probably give a range oh yeah and I'm not gonna be gone for like the
whole month of October or anything um you will see my face again uh let's say the like the middle
of October like the 14th let's go with the 14th because when this stream will turn on again
probably maybe sooner though maybe sooner it really depends on a few things I'll let you know keep an
eye on the sus it's early this coming week uh well no early next week I mean I'll let you know
I ain't going anywhere don't worry but I'll see you I'll see you soon just keep an eye on the sus
all right how do I do this oh we didn't bet that's all right we don't need to bet it just happened
Jeremy you're in deep trouble now oh wow I got it already holy shit I'll do hell for this next one
I'm gonna do any two more two more there's a chest in there oh there's a chest in there
hey keep an eye on my twitter too just because go to the forest you won't be here for two weeks
just do it this one here all right is there a cart here where's there a cart come on there's
gonna be a cart just sitting right here right really wait another diamond oh yeah oh shit okay
the forest is a huge area I'm just gonna look at it and I'm gonna fly into it and then we'll
be done what a fucking lightning sword holy shit all right um oh my god don't even tell me what
should I get rid of wooden I can these are everywhere okay uh I got it I got it I thought it
was a lightning sword a game like the switch just crash why is this oh I don't get it still about
my items and shit right I don't get it what was that for is this what you wanted me to do
that's what you wanted that was it all right well that was that's funny um cool we got uh they
teleported us that's fun no that's not what I mean there's a road here let me eat something too let's
go with this yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes yeah all right all right so what what's happening
why does everybody wants me to run in here am I gonna get the kojima just gonna delete my save
or something interesting all the fire that's it man oh god damn it my computer sucks what the
fuck I don't want that no I do this when the internet's not as bad what's closing in on me
fire fire fire yeah yeah yeah with the arm up be quiet wait like that all right so burn it I have
to burn this place down what the um what what the fuck fire fire of handing it to somebody
handing fire to someone handing fire to someone handing fire to someone to a spin
handing a fire with a spin tornado fire handing a fire with a spin spin with a tornado fly with
turning into spin quiet quiet and spin well you can spin with the be silent while you spin
I don't understand music spin Doritos snapshot Doritos snapshot Doritos snapshot
copy dorito goal doritos snapshot doritos frames doritos frames cheese frames cheesy frames your
frames are cheesy your frames stink oh that's what it is all right orc minecraft fire me me
build dirt house and burn it um your frames uh minecraft burn cheesy dorito quiet sweet sugar
spices is it the sound of making down here quiet quiet okay i'm quiet goal goal all right i'm being
quiet i'm not making that much sound copy fire hand it snapshot quiet and fire tornado give
fire to the tornado bro there ain't no tornado on the screen hand the fire to the tornado but be
but do it quietly yes give the fire to the tornado but do it quietly what tornado shh shh
okay that one was shh shh i don't i don't know what that means give fire to the tornado dog dogs dog
dog music yes tornado goal tornado spin why are you writing doritos minecraft creeper explode
tornado minecraft exploding tornado creeper i just that was just like a made up name that
a little kid would use at recess i'm the minecraft tornado explosion um tornado music spin dog music
tornado spin dog music i don't i don't get it i don't know what you i don't get it i just don't
know just proper sprint just fucking sprint fire goal fire goal fire is the goal fire is the goal
fire yes why i don't get it football row the football catch goal fire goal nice frames
i can hear somebody saying that how do i go from here i get out of here doritos doritos yes yes
doritos doritos wait oh i was already in here wait no i wasn't what is this forest dweller spear
all right i was already here
i don't see another torch i don't i don't see another fire is that where i came from fire
illuminati fire illuminati yes yes fire illuminati fire i eyes i don't get it i don't know what to do
illuminati goal quiet illuminati i'm gonna fucking puke um i think i don't think i can
i don't know what to do is it something it's something okay i have to take a certain path
if i don't go the exact right path they'll come out and they go yeah and they go back to the
entrance i don't think it's this way this way this can't be right now why am i still alive here
why am i why haven't i been poured out what's that help wait wait wait no come here come here
come here no no no come here come here follow the fox yes oh wait this is where i was what the
hell are you doing out here is it just as simple as avoid the i'm dead okay i can see the green
streams is it avoid those i've dropped 14 000 frames holy shit man
so why is that happening here oh fuck i keep it in the same dead end here ex mask by those
fun-loving co-roaks shakes when one is hiding nearby what ex mask what the fuck is that can
i see them now where's my torch uh-oh this is bad no no no no no no no i i just like i don't even
know what i'm doing i'm kind of just walking shrine can i go in the right way yet i gotta turn into
fucking jereba turtle what the fuck is that hand give me the torch fire fire fire fire fire fire
fire fire fire fire fire doesn't work fire doesn't work fire doesn't work i'm just being
honest with you fire doesn't do anything i'm running a straight line so it's about fire and
it's about sneaking this place is huge fire what what does a tornado do tornado spins a tornado
destroys okay i'm gonna say some words here spin spin spin no okay destroy destruction destruction
wind wind powerful wind wind yeah i don't know where i went
wind it's wind wind wind wind so it's powerful wind you have to go up but where do you go when
it's up don't even do that that's such bullshit okay wind no nay nay nay nay
okay gust i don't know climate change i don't know climate change um storm storm a storm
a raging storm music storm a musical storm ow the fucking music's coming after me the music's
coming after me i get it now the it's the music the music's getting louder it's music's coming
after me that's the music coming after me when it goes like i got it okay i get it let's go
that means i gotta turn around or something i don't know get up there i want to look i
give up i think i give up i i think i give up okay these guys okay these trees are going like
thank you i don't know what that means that doesn't mean something look see some of them are like
happy okay i have to walk behind the ones that are sad and walk in front of the ones that are
happy he's still stuck here i don't i just don't get it am i supposed to fly like do this and
fly am i supposed to go up here and fly i just like break it just jump across okay there is in
okay a mod has just pinged me and the solution is in a spoiler they're like hey dude i mean like
you know is it just so i just outrun the little cloud that keeps hold on i'm gonna sprint that
didn't work okay what was what would be happening here are the trees pointing in a direction you
know what i mean like hey the tree this tree is like drunk right this is like a shit face tree
and he's like pointing over here so don't trust that one right with the happy trees are like yay
it's a point that way you have to point at the fire just look at the fire point at the fire
excuse me what the fuck are you talking about point at the fire i'm gonna burn okay i'm gonna
point at the fire point at the fire what do you want i don't get it there it is okay i've been
every single mod told me the answer under a spoiler and i i don't i don't know if i want to
click it i don't know if i'm gonna click it point at the fire but what do you mean by that point
at the fire how do you point at point at the fire point at the fire you know what i mean look at
this fire while i'm walking right like as long as i have a fire in my field of view or something
what the fuck was that get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way
i think i made did i make it i gotta turn around i gotta turn my back to here turn my back i don't
understand what's going on don't look at it don't look at it don't look at it i i got so far how
did i get that far i have to keep a fire in my field of view let me be very honest when i play
a game on my own on the couch my ass sits there and if i can't figure something out in two tries
i open up my ipad and i just go how do you do the forest maze thing in zelda breath of wild
i don't even i i don't even give a one second of time how did i get that far last time though
i'll give it like maybe three tries before i'm like oh no what is it how did i i don't understand
what i did this this time do you know what i mean like how did i get over that far last time what
did i do differently i have to point at it i'm gonna lose my mind point at the fire guys but
there is no i can't go like i don't know what that means point at the fire all right is it wrong way
fire dot dot dot fire dot dot dot dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
quiet you're gonna fuck it all up for me did i do it baroque forest i made it
places two frames a second there it is the toy that's in walmart link you are a fate of hyrule
with you you follow the fire's trail what the fire's trail what are you talking about
who is that what she quite does off again well it's the fire particles
better late than never to 100 years i've nearly given the embers coming off the torch
no you fucked up you should have done a dark souls emote you fucked up it should have been
like dark souls fire dark souls like dark souls right i would have ember i would have been like
oh shit okay that is the weapon the sword that seals the darkness so all right hold on this is
like a cool moment hold on a second must warn you take extreme caution oh the jug was elden ring
is a test to anyone attempt to possess it as you are dude you need a break i'm fine man
if you sought to free the sword any sort of win state tornado tenor dog tornado tornado dog
dorito fire fire wind circle circle spin tornado i gotta read this tornado tornado dog dorito fire
fire wind circle circle spin tornado jesus christ man that whole time i i actually just
brute forced it really dude there was one point when i'm walking backwards and i almost made it
dude i almost made it walking backwards i got to the stone if i had just turned the right
direction i would have done it just okay uh do i have enough power to pull the sword out
i'm not strong enough kidding me
heal up and try it i i have very highly doubt that you probably need like a full thing
13 hearts do spirit hearts count no yeah complete the trials that was fun oh my god um no
holy shit all right i said i was gonna turn the stream off at like 555 it's 650 i did it for an
hour no i didn't i did i not do that for an hour that was not a full hour was it that was a holy
shit an inner tornado dorito what was the dorito thing why doritos i'm you got okay here's the
problem and this is the problem that i had with emote only mode and people like dude how come
you didn't figure that out like what the fuck you couldn't figure out you had to mirror the thing
because i look over a chat and i make up a scenario that is not even close like oh dorito
dorito tornado all right so that means like this guy there's a piece of cheese on the ground
that i pick up and i throw into a tornado i'm just making it way harder i'm throwing myself off but
what was the the dorito was supposed to be dorito dust dorito dust are embers yeah i never would have
gotten that i never would have got that there's no way in my brain seeing a dorito chip in the
chat is oh that's embers or dust no no to me that's a dorito that's cheese or like like junk food or
fatty food dorito cheese if there was a okay there was a cheeto emote like a flaming hot cheeto emote
i would understand like like cheeto fingers right oh i thought we were just spamming the dorito for
no reason oh that's so stupid i'm glad i did it without even knowing i thought it was an arrow
all right all right i'm that's it i'm getting out of here that's what i was posting in spoilers
that's hold on let me see what the mods were writing okay so yeah i wind fire sparkles goal
i got i would not okay i would not have gotten that i gust fire sparkle goal it was the goal
thing was fucking me up too but like fire goal goal goal it's like what do you mean goal do the
shrine all right i'll do the shrine i'll do the shrine and that's it oh you made a bed oh yeah
let's i i look at my hearts back to emote only mode well now there's no doubt the stream title
is accurate that's right yeah all right look where's the shrine i'm i'll deal with all this
later i'm gonna do one more bet yeah so see see look at this uh the drop frames have stopped as
of like 30 minutes ago right i don't i don't understand what's this like satan hour between
like 8 15 and 9 15 i don't understand it's why is it like a satanic hour where like the internet
just doesn't work but i'm not disconnected or anything i'm not usually i would have lots of
other problems i just don't have any back when i would have actual frame problems back when i you
know uh at the old place it was i would be dropping frames and the chat would stop it'd be like oh
and that is messed up right so i have no idea it's bizarre i don't want you to guess this
i don't want you to see it still like bet and what was the shush that was throwing me off big time
the quiet shush what i what does that mean what was that supposed to mean the how is that embers
off of the flame it's quiet right starting three two one start to the stars for guidance the
constellations of the key it gave me a headache did i get it one two three four five all right
it's one two three four five on either side okay um that's okay there's the little dipper so little
dipper is at the bottom over there a little dipper over here i don't i don't know what it's
trying to tell me um okay so okay i have an idea one two three four five six okay the i don't
understand what the placement is for there's no number there's no coordinator one two three four
five six seven dots that one's over on the left oh does that matter i don't i don't know if this
matters or not like this one is over here and it's over there and then there's one two three four
five wait wait wait wait hold on a second this one is okay it's over here what does that mean
that's the correct one so what do i do with that what do i do about that this is the right one
right here that's the correct one what does that mean i don't know what that means i know how to do
it one two three four four all right how much time do i have three minutes one two three there are
three of these one one got it is there a chest i don't think there's a chest in here is there a
chest oh shit okay hold on there one two two all right i gotta get some memory of one minute four
two of those weird ones one of those one long one four tiny ones one long one four tiny ones
one long one four tiny ones one long one four tiny ones and then one long one four tiny one one long
one four tiny one one long one four tiny one one long one four tiny one one long one four tiny one
one long one four tiny one one long one four tiny one and then here we go one long one four tiny one
one long one four tiny one one long one four tiny one two of these one long one four tiny one of
these one long one four tiny one and then we have uh one long one four tiny one one long one four
tiny one one long one one long one and then two of these hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry up how
much time what do i have ten one one minute one minute i forgot how to play how much time do i
have how much time time time how much time is time 30 seconds i just ran back to the entrance
time did i get it i got it we need to confirm we need to have this has got to be like reviewed
This has got to be reviewed. I actually don't know what okay you touched the wall at the exact time my timer went off
Wait, really? Wait, hold on. We got I I got I need I need to go
I gotta go to the VOD hold off. I gotta go to the VOD
I actually have to look at the VOD cuz I actually we're not sure this is gonna be like a photo finish
Hold on. Let me go to the VOD
Hold off on paying out that actually might have I can't play off ran the wrong way
Hey, hold on opening the video hopefully this it might not have caught up yet. It might not have caught up yet
Let's see video. Come on. Open up. Let me see
Alright, well, I'll put it on screen. Hold on and this is by this is the end of the stream by the way
But we need to see alright, we're gonna it's here
We're gonna review it on stream because I think it's gonna be really tight. I got it here
Oh shit, whoops hang tight for one second. I'm putting it on screen
I want to plug in my headphones for this to get this shit on HD so we can see
Okay, hold on a second. Alright, I'm gonna save this we're gonna wait. Don't pay. Hold on. Don't pay it out
Okay, here we go. Give me one sec. Okay, let's review this right now. This is important
So it seems we need to start this at
656 right? Let me see. Okay. So hold on. Let me see six
What was the exact time that started it was 655 and what was the shush that was throwing me off big time, too
The lunch
Quiet shush. What? What does that mean? What was that supposed to mean the
58 how was that embers off of the flame? It's shut up and do it. Wait starting three two one start
Okay, so it's
656-19
603 I just ran back to the entrance. Oh
That's what ruined everything
656-19 that would have been it
Time that was it. Yeah nine seconds, right?
656-19 I've turned the wrong way. I just ran back to the entrance. Oh
No, I'm sorry guys
That's it I lose
Time oh, that's too bad. All right, that's it. Ah
I did not make it. Everyone's gonna be so pissed. Why did you turn the wrong way? Oh
That's so bad. I'm sorry. That's a good time for me to leave. I'll see you guys later
Oh, I think I broke the credits. Oh, there we go. I am so sorry to all the believers
I will never trust you again. It's because I I looked over at the chat and I went I turned the wrong way
I started the Doritos spam and it did not mean cheese dust particles
It's actually a reference to the
2021 sci-fi adventure film Dune which you should watch on stream. I will literally get banned. All right
I will see you guys later. Keep an eye on the sus. I won't be too long
There's actually gonna be a lot of really cool things to talk about when I come back
Breath of the Wild obviously is still having still having a great time. So I'm gonna play it more
Yeah, keep an eye on my Twitter too. I don't know maybe the weapon chest thing
Yeah, cuz I've my inventory was full. It was a bunch of bullshit now. It's great. I love it
I think it's great. I just followed you on Twitter. Well, you'll be pleased to know that you're gonna get
three or four actual tweets a year
and then like a
Hundred plus I'm live tweets and then maybe like ten or twenty or something sponsor tweets is literally all I do
It is the best Twitter to follow. I tweet like once every four months
You're still gonna do October spooky games. Yep, when I come back, we'll we'll do all kinds of stuff
Yeah, keep an eye on the sus. I will be very not just gonna like disappear. So I'll tell you guys
I'll be in the offline chat. I'll jump in the discord and
I'll keep you up to date, but you can expect at least a week plus
But keep an eye on my Twitter, obviously
I'm back
Have a great week or so. I'm gonna try to keep it to less than ten days or so
I really don't want to be that long, but there are a lot of things that I'm doing
I'll see you soon. Have a great rest of your night. Thanks for watching. Have a great weekend, obviously
Tell your mother
I'll see you guys in like a week plus
You know, keep an eye on the sus. Good night. Goodbye. See you later. I have a quick question
Was my camera out of sync the entire time?
No
Uh, I hope not. Don't think so. All right, just making sure I didn't change a setting
All right. Good night guys. See you soon