Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, Saturday's edition.
And, oh, I just got a headshot. Today I'm gonna be, as you see, playing as the spy in this
beautiful Saturday afternoon. And we're gonna, like, lose right now. I never play spy, live
at least, and you are getting backstabbed. No, you're not. Um, we are gonna, pfft. Well,
I can't even think. Let's get out here. This is on a bad water, as you can probably see.
On the, uh, on the screen here. Let me kill this heavy. This heavy medic bear are dead.
They are toast. One, oh, give me that headshot. I got it. What's going on? I'm stuck. Oh my god,
I'm, like, legit stuck in that thing. I'm just, like, standing. That was stupid. I got, like,
legit sandwiched into, like, the wedge of that dome thing. Ah, that's a good V8 fusion. Oh my
god, this is a long respawn here. So, spy, you know, I wanna take something off, but I don't
wanna take something off. We're just gonna stick with it, you know, whatever. We can hold him for
over seven minutes. Probably not. Oh, you know, I wanna go as a, oh, let me just, like, turn this
corner. Hi, everybody. Like, I'm just dead. I'm still bergafone. I need to, like, change my,
god, at least he killed him. Frontier justice. Come on, back up right into me. Back up right into
me. Oh, the anger in that knife. Why am I standing right in the open here? Oh, let's change to a pyro
right here. See if I can't do something. Oh, I just, like, that guy knew.
I should have just jumped down. What am I doing? Instead, I just stared right at the guy's face. I
was just like, hi, like, I spy, like, who are you? Should have jumped down and stabbed the heavy,
but no. I wanted to get overzealous. I wanted to get behind everybody. That was a stupid idea,
but it's okay, because they still have not gotten close to capping this. They were close. Not
anymore, though. Oh, let's go sniper. I'm gonna take out the SMG. Oh, by the way, if you don't
know what I'm doing, I'm hitting B when I change my weapons. When you do that, you switch to your,
I just feel bad about that. You switch to the weapon that's in that slot for that class. Oh,
my god, that was sick. That wasn't even my, I didn't even do that either. Oh, my god, I gotta
play. That was just like the sloppiest, like, oh, spy. That was one of the sloppiest, like,
that was a reverse stair stab. He, like, jumped over me, and I'm back. Oh, my god. That guy just
killed himself. Oh, my god. This is turning out to be, like, quite the spy round. Like, so much
goofy crap happened. Oh, what are you gonna shoot? I wanted to shoot him in the face so bad. Why
didn't the first one register? God dang it. Oh, what the hell was in that? Oh, all right. Well,
you just got, like, a live reaction of me swallowing, like, a mosquito that was in my drink.
Hell. Is Otto still in here? Oh, shh. Okay, let's do this now. Let's do this.
Gotta get in the try hard mode. That's when my eyes peer down like that. It means I'm, like,
trying really hard. And it means this guy is, what a nice shot that was. Holy crap. What is
this guy doing? I can't, like, decloak next to him because, like, that guy, wow, I just, like,
screwed myself up. Maybe he won't even know. Oh, he won't know. Oh, get him. Any snipers? There is
a sniper. Oh, come on. Give me that headshot. Oh, give me that headshot. Give it to me. I want it
so bad. I want it so, mmmm. No. Oh, God. Oh, well. You can't get them all. Wish I could,
though. Oh, I'm, like, this thing's had given me, like, burp gas, too. Like, jeez Louise. I'm gonna,
like, puke on the screen. You are definitely an actual engineer. I'm sorry for ever doubting you.
I gotta stop changing to the same damn thing over and over again. Let's go.
So, uh, alright, let's do this.
Get on that cot, guys, we gotta like save the day, and I just bumped into somebody.
I might as well just, okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Alright, this guy, I'm gonna get it this time.
Alright, I got it that time.
If I screwed that one up, I would have peed my pants.
I killed this, what?
What just even happened right there?
Okay, I'm like flabbergasted right now.
Oh, Heavy, you don't even know what's going on here.
Now I gotta run all the way, you know what, I hate when that happens.
You see, I had a beeline for that Heavy, but there was like a sentry going up.
See, I was gonna do what this guy just did, you know, maybe he just succeeded.
Let's see, come on.
Oh, it's okay.
Surprisingly, we have held this for this long, and oh, come on, we can't lose this.
What did that guy say?
I have my voice turned down so low, I can't hear anything.
Oh, the power jack.
Get that.
Get up.
That's fine.
Let's go Heavy.
This guy doesn't know the Heavy.
Doctor!
That's what I wanted.
Oh, why didn't I bring it out?
How much, hold on, how much health did I just have right there?
Did I have 180 health?
I didn't even like pay attention.
That item is really awesome and totally fine to use.
We're gonna win.
Nice smash.
Nice smash, dude.
Okay.
All right, don't screw this up.
Let's go, let's go, baby.
Oh, don't screw this up now, baby.
He is gonna spray everywhere.
No, don't turn around, don't turn around.
Oh!
We're gonna win.
We'll win.
See, when I play Spy, this is how I get.
I get like, I get like all shaky and jittery and crazy, especially live.
We're gonna do it.
Last point defense.
Oh, oh, I don't know.
Still a demo man, still a demo man on the point.
No, that's it.
That's it.
Good game, guys.
Nice job, team.
Top.
Okay, I'll take it.
That's gonna be it.
Thanks a lot, guys, for watching.
And let me get one person.
Let me just like smoke one person, come on.
You took it from me.
But yeah, take care, buddy.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
Otto, are you sleeping still?