Is it mercenary or mercenary? Is it M-E-R-C-E-N or C-A-N? Is it mercenary or mercenaries? Mercenary,
right? Yeah, yeah, with an E. I had it right. No, no, no, no, hold on. It's M-E-C-M-E-R-C-A-N?
Whatever, I don't care. It's merc- mercenaries? Mercenary. No, it- my phone's not telling me it's
wrong. I'm just waiting. Mercenaries. All right. Hello. Hi. Welcome, everybody. Welcome back.
Hope you had a good weekend. Welcome back to the stream. Today, I guess you just heard it,
we're going to be playing Mercenaries 2. There's a funny story about this one. This is on PC.
Didn't want it to be on PC. I wanted it to be on PlayStation 3, but unfortunately,
I couldn't get this game to get- I couldn't get my PlayStation 3 to get captured. I was trying to
capture my PlayStation 3 and it wouldn't work anymore. I don't know what happened. We played
the Olympics game, like, 12 days ago, right? Like, last week? A week and a half ago? What happened?
I don't know- I don't know what happened. I was trying to figure this out for, like,
a fucking hour. I was supposed to start an hour ago. I was ready- I was here ready to go.
I don't know why I wouldn't get captured. It was- no, not- it- not the- I mean, I streamed from
this exact setup 12 days ago. I didn't change anything. Was there a Windows update or, like,
an OBS update within the last 10 days? It- something got fucked up. I've no- yes,
there was. Okay. Of course. There was a PS3 update. There was a Windows update, like,
five days ago. Okay, I think- I think we may have found the culprit then. What are they even doing
anymore? Can we just talk about this very briefly? What the fuck are they updating? What are they
even doing? Like, the operating system is- just works. Just fix- what else could you be adding?
Okay, I understand, like, security holes, right? Fix the security holes and, like, fix the bugs.
But, like, I don't give a shit about any of the new features you add. You know what I've been
sitting on the Windows, like, update? There's, like, a features. Windows features. Please install me.
It's been, like, a year and a half. I'm like, no, fucking get out of here. I don't want you.
I don't know what it adds. What does it add? Like, yeah. Let me see what it adds. I'm curious.
I want to read it. And I'll tell you if any of these things are things that I would ever use.
Okay, let's see. What does it got? Okay, learn more. Okay, this one. This is for, uh, okay.
Great news. What's new? Here we go. Troubleshooting. Wait, there's only a troubleshooting list.
Hey guys, here's the new Windows update. Here's what it adds. It breaks everything,
and here's a list of how you fix it when we break it. Windows 10 versions. Okay,
Windows 10 versions 1909 and 1903 share a common core operating system and an identical set of
system files. As a result, the new features in Windows 10 were included in the recent monthly
quarterly update for Windows 10, but they're currently in a dormant state. These new features
will remain dormant until they are turned on using an enablement package, which is a small,
quick to install master switch that simply activates Windows 10. What? Why do they have
like a dormant ancient creature that's being built into the Windows 10 update? I'm not going to
enable that. I don't want this Cthulhu fucking update on my computer. No, just fix the security
bugs. Anyways, an Eldritch update. An Eldritch update. That's so perfect. I'm not enabling that.
No, I don't want that. I don't want a dormant fucking Microsoft computer monster on here.
And then they just like they turn it on one day and like break your computer.
Why does there have to be a master switch? It feels like it shouldn't be there. It feels
like they shouldn't like turn on a master switch. All right, we're going to play Mercenaries 2.
Let's go. I already hear like explosions. Okay, here we go. Can you see it? Does
German not know how Windows works? I know how Windows works. I just, I don't,
I don't want all that shit. And I know everyone just says, dude, just use, just use Linux. It's
okay. Everything I ever hear about Linux or like any of the Linux operating systems, it's just,
hey, it's, it's just like way better. From my understanding, you've got Windows is like the
Best Buy computer that you buy off the shelf and it has like fucking Norton 360 on it already.
Right. But Linux is like you built it yourself and there's no bullshit on it. Is that how I
understand this? But the unfortunate thing is everything is made for the Best Buy computer.
So a lot of times you have to have the Best Buy computer. I know I don't want to play online,
play online. Wait, I have to pick my character. Um, I can't see the other characters. Okay.
Matthias Nilsson, Chris Jacobs or Jennifer Mew. How do I see the, I want to see them.
Oh, okay. Hmm. Jennifer duh. What do you mean duh? I like the cigar. I do like the cigar. I'm a,
I'm a, I'm a big cigar fan. I've, I've never smoked one. Jennifer, Jennifer, Jennifer, Jennifer,
Whoa. All right. Jesus. But Chris has a cigar. All right. It's done. Wait, runs faster. Hold on.
Okay. Which one of these guys has punches harder? Regenerates health faster. Hmm. Carries more ammo.
All right. Runs faster is, I feel like, all right, that's probably pretty good.
Jen to only to her friends is the most expensive mercenary on earth. If it seems like she focuses
on money and nothing else, it's because she focuses on money and nothing else. Okay.
Kind of a big fan so far. She finds it amusing that there are people dumb enough to think
that anything else is important. Is there, is this, is this like a video game? Is it like a cut scene
or is it just throw like grenades at stuff? It's probably low, but whatever. I'll be quiet.
This. You should have done the same. Oh, I got paid. I always get paid. I need your
guns. No one sees the boss. I feel like this is a machinima made in the sims. Jennifer,
this is Ramon Solano. Mr. Solano is the richest man in Venezuela. I can tell we're going to get
along perfectly. What's the contract? Last week, general Carlos Caramona and his soldiers attempted
a coup. It's made by EA. Oh shit. It is some great plan for general Caramona and his army
plans for Venezuela. So it's me against a bunch of VZ soldiers. That's it. Will you accept the
contract? As long as your checks don't bounce. I feel like I'm going to really like this game.
Is that the case? I've never played this either of them. Welcome to Venezuela,
Solano's paperwork. So we're good to go. Packed into a CIA satellite.
I can see you and most of the area around you. I'm working off a laptop connected to a cell phone
here. So don't expect miracles. Leave the miracles to me. 2008 cell phones in the right direction.
This is like iPhone four. You're literally coping. What? Oh shit. Okay. Here we go.
Accelerate. What button is that? How do I land on a bunch of
pointy rocks? Okay. Steer and then break. What are those? What are those? Objective added.
Land on the beach. Okay. But what, what buttons are those? Okay. It's obviously A and then what
is B? Break? No, B is horn. Land on the beach. How do you exit? Wait, do you drive cars? Wait a
second. Wait for a weapon delivery. Melee bash is use melee bash to open crates.
Punch. Oops. What's made? I already like it. I love it already. I don't mind getting a little
dirty. Okay. What's in here? There's nothing in there. Equip grenade launcher. How do I pick it
up? Did I get it? I did. I don't think I picked it up. Oh boy. This is not, I don't think this is a
controller game. I don't think this is a controller game. Let me see. Why are there no ammo stores
around here? Why do I zoom in? Right. Hold on. Right. Stop. Okay. Wait. Right mouse button doesn't
zoom in? What the hell zooms in then? Shoot reload. Why? You've given me like Minecraft pictures.
What's the button that I have to press? Zoom. Switch weapons. Yeah. How? How do I do that?
Q? Hold on. Okay. Mouse one. Primary switch tab. Reload is R. Secondary attack mouse two.
Secondary switches V. Melee attack F. Use E. Jump space. Crouch C. Binoculars B. PDA F1. Lookup I.
A. Support. Walk. Switch. What's zoom in? Sprint is left shift. Okay. But what is the
zoom in? Mouse two. I'm pressing mouse two. Wait. It's crouch. Sensitivity has got to go
way down too. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I like playing with the controller. Hold on.
Joystick sensitivity. Here we are. I want to play the controller. I don't want to keyboard and mouse.
I hate that. All right. Let's try that. All right. That's way too slow. But you get the idea.
Yeah. This is much better. That was not good. That was very bad. Oh, it shot. All right. Oh,
okay. That's how you equip it. That's a little too low though. Way too low. Way,
way, way, way, way. I think that's going to be good. This game was wild as a kid. You played
this as a kid? Open PDA is the pause button. It's the select button. This is a great kid's game.
I don't think I agree. Okay. Destroy the gate. Thank God there's a fucking fallout New Vegas map.
What do I do? How do I blow it up? Do I have to switch weapons? All right. Let's go. Dude,
you know what? Okay. My up and down sensitivity is crazy. Open support menu. Use support item.
Wait, satellite guided satellite mom. One for free. How do I use it? Use support item. Oh shit.
Okay. Over the target. Confirm. Confirm target. Do it. Go. Did I do it? Okay. There it is. Confirm
target is. Okay. Got it. Oh, it's a mini game. Oh shit. All right. Run, run, run. Get out of here.
I mean, let's be honest. You would do the same shit. It doesn't matter how like hard you think
you are. If this an explosion that far behind you, you're not going to be like, yeah. No,
you're going to be like, Jesus. I'm glad that that happened. Oh fuck. Look out. All right. How do
you sprint? How do you crouch? Okay. Don't want to die in the tutorial. Uh, I have an idea.
So soft. Got them. Did I get them? Your AK is freaking out. Get to the way point.
Holy shit. That was pretty good. Come on. Dude, do you get cars in this game?
Tell me you get a car. Do you get a car? Yes. Okay. I'm, I'm, I'm incredibly excited. Wait,
vehicle delivery, vehicle delivery. Where is it? Dropped out of the sky.
See if it was going to crush me. Drive the iguana. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Drive. Where am I driving? That is a full letter grade. That is a full letter grade. That's what
happens. Okay. We go back down here. Went from F to a D. Um, no, it went from a C to a B.
All right. Now it's, wait, now it's a B minus. Now it's a, now it's a B plus. Okay. I just had to
see what happened. You can actually do it. Okay. You can, you can ghost ride cars. Did I get them?
Oh, I didn't get them. I thought I got them both. Where's the car? Where did it go? Did it keep
going? Okay. This blend. I thought this was part of the rocks. There's a handbrake. How do I do it?
Okay. That's it. Excellent. I love spending other people's money.
Okay. She turned into a hermit crab. Why am I still alive? Okay. Open up the menu.
Satellite guided bomb. Where is it? All right. Take it out. Got it. Tank. Give me that ammo. Oh,
wow. Level destruction. Yeah. That's cool. All right. Let's go. Let's get in the tank.
How many different vehicles are there? Is there a motorcycle? This is a motorcycle.
This game's automatically an A minus. Steal it or nuke it. What do I mean? Yeah. Get in it.
How would I destroy this? Um, okay. But move, steer, shoot. Oh God. This game is fucked. This
game is mega fucked on PC. Is it? I can't, it's hard to turn. It's mega fucked on PC. What do you,
is that going to be a problem? Switch weapons. How do I switch weapons? I'm trying to do it.
Switch weapons. Oh, there we go. This just sounds like popcorn in the microwave.
I gotta make it realistic. Hold on. Do I take it out yet? Do I take it out yet? No, not yet. Okay.
No, that's fine. That's fine. Let's get it out. Get it out now. Get it out now before it explodes.
Anybody else have that irrational fear? You don't have that irrational fear.
You know, you're supposed to count two seconds between pops. If it's longer than two seconds,
then like, I, I feel like there's a risk of explosion. Get to the way point. Wait,
hold on. Can I just like, why would you stand up there? Okay. If you're this guy, don't you
dive off now. Why would you continue to stand up on this? These are houses. Wait, but there's
people shooting at me. Okay. That was, it was pretty fucked up. All right. Let's go the right
direction. Bridges out. Oh, sweating. Bridges out. Get inside the complex. How about we just blow it
up? Just take it out from over here. Why is it healing? Don't worry. They'll come out. Don't
worry. We'll smoke them out. Can you destroy everything? Wait, why is it being rebuilt?
This is just like when you're destroying a building in Warcraft and the guy puts like
10 peons on it and you're just like, get these fucking things out of here.
Oh, what's this? Wait. Oh, wait, where is this? Did I do it? What happened? Mission complete.
Wait, was this supposed to be a hideout? Oh, where's the rest of your team? I'm the complete
package. So you're a merc. He knows a good deal when he sees it. Let's get the hell out of here.
Jennifer, welcome back. Job well done. Just like old times. Me doing all the work, you nowhere to be
seen. Is somebody really mad that they don't have the premier project file anymore? To be
able to re-render these in HD, like full 1080. First I get paid. I'm sorry. The job is not for
you. The job is you. Tomorrow, General Carmona's troops will roll into the capital and I will be
Venezuela's new leader. You should have just paid me the money. I love money. This means there will
be many bounties on my head. I can't have your friends hunting me. It's bad for business. So is
this. Now I have to kill you. Sorry, Jennifer. You piece of- Why is it, why is it bleeped?
That wasn't even a bleep. That was like a phone touch tone. Why did she do that? Oh my God.
That was what the after the beep. If you like leave a message for somebody. Jen, please sit
down if you can. She got shot in the ass. Trust you to be looking at my ass. We're leaving Venezuela
tonight. That was ridiculous. I can't even process what just happened. That was fucking crazy. It's
not safe because I'm here and I am pissed off. Yeah, no one shoots her in the ass and gets away
with it. He didn't pay her the worst thing it could have done. I'm being told now that Ramona
was giving a press conference. This is a crack game. Yeah.
Everybody pays Blanco. I don't know. Whatever. What am I saying? Everybody pays. I blinked and she
kicked a guy in the balls from behind. I didn't even see the cut scene. I felt like I just had a
dream. What? Okay. So I'm trying to piece this together. Okay. I don't know why, but I thought
that was that guy. Director Cameron Brown. I was like, all right, this guy, this is a
solid snake. Metal gear snake. Whatever. Wait, you can steal cars? No, you can't. No, you can't. No,
you can't. You can't do that. No, there's no way. This is you can't, right? Can you get hit by cars?
Kind of. There's a motorcycle. Okay. There's a motorcycle in the game. Okay. It's an A minus.
Give me this thing. Oh yeah. Holy shit. Okay. I have to have fun. All right. Give me that
motorcycle bike. This is, this is too much stimulation. There's another one right here.
We'll take this one. Wait, is that bike? There's two bikes here. Wait, can you punch? Why is a
bike still driving by itself? What? I'm getting battlefielded? Wait, they have a out of bounds
like battlefield. All right. How do I? This is a first person mode too. This is amazing. All right.
I'm going to do first person driving. How am I getting shot at by? Wait, what's that? Money?
How is he still alive? I feel like I'm an animal. Like I'm a wild fucking animal.
Just put like fucking screaming like bear noises right there. Wait, I didn't get the money.
Police academy. What do you mean police academy? Wait, I think I know what you're talking about.
Okay. No, no. What's, what is it? Um, naked gun, the naked gun movies. Wait, there's a bad guy.
What's this? Oh, $25,000. All right. That's not a bad guy. Did I get everything? All right. Wait, how
what is this? Oh, requires a helicopter pilot to steal. Are you kidding me? Wait, what?
I have to do a mission. I'm going to lose my mind.
All right. We're gonna bang a left. Don't kill people. I've, what are you? I'm being shot at.
I do want a motorcycle though. That's way cooler. Will this guy fly over the handlebars?
No. Why would you turn into me? I'm not killing anybody. I want a bike though. I want a bike.
Give me the bike. Why is this thing on ice? No, get. There we are. Come on. Let's go. All right. I
want the other camera angle. Oh shit. Wait, turn left. All right. Turn left. I almost got it. I
almost got it. I just had to drive as fast as I could. Wait, how do I open this gate? Open the
gate. What did I just get a little jump for? That was cool. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Get a real car. Oh shit. There's a temporal disturbance. I'm pulling you out. I'm
pulling you out, Jen. No, don't do it yet. I'm not ready. No, you've been in there for too long.
What do I do? I can't get in. I don't have access to an airstrike. I don't. It's not. I don't have
an airstrike. I need a car. Use a grenade. Use a van. I don't have any grenades. I don't have any.
All right. I'm going to take that car. There's a car right here. Use your head. I've tried that.
It didn't work. All right. Car. Give me. All right. Open up. You actually had to drive through it.
You got to be kidding me. Okay. But it was like a little scavenger hunt. Is this supposed to be a
maze? I found it. Wait, I have to kill that guy. Did I get him? That guy had an elaborate setup.
Is he dead? I got him. All right. Imagine being that guy. Yes, I'm going to hide in the
elaborate maze that she will never find me. Boss, she's driving through the hedges.
Somebody, when they write about this in the history books, make sure you said
it took her at least two minutes to find me. Why did I just hacky sack that into the air?
Take ammo. Take ammo. We're out of here. Wait, what was that? I want a grenade. I'm going to
sneeze and I'm going to try to be very, very, very. I'm back. Hi guys. Welcome to the stream.
Today we're going to play Mercenaries 2. I have nine grenades. I do have nine grenades.
I didn't even realize that. Is this like Dora the Explorer? Oh, come on. All right. Watch this.
Here I. Oh, come on. Really? I thought the whole thing was going to come down.
Do you see? Do you see where Jen went? Nevermind. I tried. All right. There he is.
Wait, that's an explosive thing. Isn't it? Is it? Oh my God. That guy. That guy was like,
Holy shit. It didn't get me. Machine pistol. Oh, he just took him right in the lip. All right. I
got him. I need a car. What's this? Oh, $55,000, man. What else is back here? All right. Like,
give me that car behind that cover. Yes. Nice throw, dude. Okay. That was pretty good though.
Can I just drive through the wall? This is the most efficient way to mow the lawn.
Just throw a grenade. All right. Where is he? Right here. Another maze guy. No. Oh, party's over.
Party's over. Yep. Party's over, guys. Why am I sinking into the ground?
Where is he? Holy shit. You are horrible. You sucked. Oh, fire. Why is there fire? Let's go.
Don't shoot that. Don't shoot that. I need that. I need that. Do not. Thank you. Don't blow that up.
Get out of my way. Get out of my way. I need that. Are you serious? I need this. Not going to work.
Not going to work. Whatever. Who did he throw that at? They didn't throw it at me.
Wait, that's money. I need that. Just shoot. What? Give me that money. That's a lot of cash.
$85,000. Behind the tree. Behind that wall. Behind that car. Behind that thing. Behind that
structure. Was this two people or is that one person? What? Why are they dead? Okay. Go to the
front entrance. They can't swim. It's always so funny in games where you can't swim. Where water
instantly kills you. It doesn't cause any blood. It's like a poison. It's an instant poison.
It's like getting electrocuted. Water is electricity. Oh my goodness. You dick. I
needed that. I want your thing. Give me that. Like an acid pool. Yeah. Okay. Wait. RPG. Nice.
So much fun. Check this out. I can't blow the... I got to go to the front of the... Can I go on
the side of the building? Wait. That's going to take way too long. Never mind. Is there another
car I can take? There we go. Yeah. I've got my tried and true. My trusty. Important. This game
has a manual save. If you die, you go to the beginning. What? Oh my God. Thank you for saying
that. Why did you tell him that? I'm so glad you did. Don't shoot. Don't shoot. Don't shoot. Don't
shoot. No. The same fate. The same fate as the last one. All right. I made it. Now what?
Inside the villa. All right. I got one shot. Wait. Can I destroy everything?
All right. I'm going to destroy the statue of Michelangelo. What's going on? We good?
Any resistance inside? There's kind of a tank in here. Okay. Get close to the tank turret.
Hijack the tank. Oh no. Okay. Whoa. Hijack. That was weird. I just kind of fell through the ground.
Behind that tank. Go to the courtyard. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I want a motorcycle in here so bad.
Behind that thing. Behind that building. That does it for the estate ground. I'm seeing some
activity inside the villa. All right. Hijack the tank. All right. I got $115,000.
Do you buy new weapons and shit in this game? This is, I'm going to like this. This is going
to be a lot of fun. Okay. I'm ready. Got it. Is there any resistance inside? There's kind of a
tank in here. Come back over here. Come here. What is the sound? The music stopped.
Okay. I just wanted to see what happened. I'll get it instantly. Ready? Count to one. One. I don't
want to hijack this. I don't think that's what would happen. Destroy the
entourage. Is the plane part of it? Die. Die. She's the last guy. Right there. All right. So
do I leave? All right. So we go up the stairs. Destroy the statue. We don't have time. No,
no, no, no. The statue stays. That was Harry Potter music. Kind of. Yeah.
Huge oil company. They own all the derricks in the area. By someone named Ruben. Yeah,
Lorraine Ruben. Do you know where Blanco is? Look at that. She deals with Blanco. And if we find
Blanco, we find Solano. All right. We got to find Blanco. Is that a casino?
Uh-oh. Ready to get to work? We can talk about how we make contact with Universal Petroleum.
Also, it might be a good idea to practice some of your basic combat skills now that
we have a base of operations. I can help you with both of these. Oh.
Implaced weapons challenge one. Let's do it. I know you hate target practice, but I know you
love losing money. I mean gambling. Oh. Not without a friendly wager to your normal routine.
Okay. That's a magic word. All right. Here's a simple wager between you and me. I've set up
an emplaced weapons challenge on the PMC grounds. You use the weapons to blow up targets before the
time runs out and you win. Destroying the cars during the challenge will pause the timer.
Wager a thousand. Let's go. Where's the last one? Where's the last statue? Where is it?
All right. Shoot the cars. Move to the recoilless rifles and shoot cars.
What? Oh, I gotta do it in the air? Shit. Come on. Come on. Come on. God damn it.
Damn it. What's the travel time on this thing? Shit. Shit. Oh. Now what? He sucks. He does not
suck. Move to the grenade launchers. I've got two minutes and 48 seconds. All right. Move to...
What? Where is it? What do I have to destroy? There's nothing else to blow up.
What? It's a hundred thousand dollars that is made. It's the easiest hundred thousand I've ever made
in my life. Like that's the easiest hundred K ever. I had a full three minutes. I have to...
That's like... Come on. Grenade launcher challenge level one.
Grenade launcher course for you to be. Use the launcher to blow up the targets. You can
only fire from behind the sandbag. Let's go. He's addicted. All right. Let's go.
Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload.
What? Last one, right? All right. Two minutes. I got plenty of time.
Oh shit. I have one shot left. What? What do I have to do? Destroy statues? What statues?
Where are they? I don't understand. It's behind them? It's splash damage. Okay. Splash damage.
Oh shit. There's another one. I did it. That's a hundred fucking thousand more dollars.
Save the game. Quick. Pistol level one. All right. Hold on. Let me save it.
So I get like a million dollars? Another one. Stop gambling Gary. All right. I'll do pistol
challenge and that's it. Pistol course. Shoot down all the Solano portraits with your pistol. Remember
you can only fire from behind the sandbag. Let's go. Just retire. I haven't even done one mission
yet. All right. How do I beat this? What does it have to swim underneath this?
Okay. How do I get up there? Wait. What's going on? Wait. Am I bugged out of the map?
This is not fair. This is a huge disadvantage. Do I have to swim to the shore? I'm only going
to have one. All right. Right here. I've got to be quick. I'm swimming further down. I can't shoot
from here. Medivac. Wait. I lost a hundred and ten thousand. Now that's bullshit. That's
absolute horse shit. I'm not going to stand for that one. I'm not standing for that one.
Why am I going so fast? Where's my money? How much money do I have? There we go. All right. Wait.
This is like a thing. Wait. Can I buy clothes? No outfits found. How do I buy them? All right.
Is the game running at sixty FPS and the game is not running times two speed? Am I going crazy
or what happened here? No, I don't care. Let's go. I'm doing the mission now. I got three hundred
and fifteen thousand universal petroleum. I've done some research on that American oil company
that Blanco is involved with. They're called universal petroleum. Before Solano took over,
they had exclusive rights to drill for oil and only gave the Venezuelan hyper fast game even
faster. Oh, by the way, just to make sure everyone knows August 23rd is the last day
you can submit for the DLC movie night. And then that stream is going to be on the 29th.
Solving some problems for UP senior executive here, Dr. Lorraine Rubin,
should show them how much more useful we can be. So far, there are about four hundred videos.
So it's going to be wild. It's four hundred of them. We still have to go through the origin,
the first wave of vetting them, but I have to imagine it's not going to be too far from like
350, 360 or something. I don't know. Or omega well, omega well. Yeah. All right.
Steel guns. Return the shipment to the up HQ. Five hundred dollars a gun. That's nothing. I
could make a hundred thousand dollars in five seconds. Well, this is not looking good.
Am I just going through the sewers? Am I going to open up underneath this guy's toilet?
With your PDA, you need to be looking at your PDA to set the GPS.
Well, I'm having a little bit more trouble, lady.
No, I'm trying to get back up to the surface. Stop talking to me for a second. OK. Beacon,
place. Good. Now you can follow the GPS. Thank you. There's got to be a way I can get up here,
right? It has to. All right. I'm going to go this way. Get away from the house.
I feel like I can probably swim up that. Am I making any progress? I think so.
Swim to the bottom of the world. I don't think there's a dive. You have to find a pool and swim
up. I don't want to do that. Oh, no. Do I have to go find it? Oh, that's not good. Oh, don't give me
those things to do because I'm going to do them. I actually have to find a pool in the town and
swim up the pool. Is there a body of water over here? There's a pool in the backyard. There's
one at the villa. It's too late. OK, there's no more water right here, so it's going to force
me up onto the land, isn't it? That's false. No, Omega-Lel, no. There's no more water to swim in.
Wouldn't it just push me up through the earth? No, it'll push you down. Oh, my God. Where's the
fucking pool? Where is it? Lock your frames? I mean, if the frames are locked at 60, should I
lock it to 30? Lock it to 30? Oh, but that's ugly. Let me see if I can go up here. Is this the pool
right here? This looks like water going straight up. I just want to climb up this. OK, I'm almost
there. All right, now go up. No? Just pull me out. Don't forget to stock up on fuel and support.
Retry? Yes. All right, come on. Don't drop me in the water again. There we go. All right, we're up.
We're up. We're up. We're up. We're up. We're up. We're good. We're up. Look, I made $300,000.
It's OK if I lose 10. Steal a truck. Yep. Open that PDA. Set a route. You guys say route or you
guys say route? What do you guys say? I say route. Thank you. So, what are these two
whistle things? Go back in the water. You missed a secret. I don't care. All right, I need a
helicopter pilot to get this stuff. Fine. You call a router a router? No, but if you have a route,
you have a route. Like, it's either one works. They're both phonetically correct in English.
NA wording. No, they both work. They're both right. They're both correct. Stop! Are there police in
this game? I don't think there is. There's no star system, right? Follow that person. No,
I want to do the mission. Whatever. I want the bike, but I can't get the bike. You know what I
mean? You're a maniac. I'm so glad there are bikes. I can't wait to go off a sick jump.
They spawned in. That's not my fault. Like a glove. I just bumped him. He's all right.
Give me that. I want a motorcycle. There's so much fun. I love driving around in like GTA
type games with motorcycles. I'm going to get it. Oh, are you still on it?
I love it. You can just go up on one wheel. Ow. Right up here. And then I do have to steal the truck.
Right. Okay. Give me the truck. Not the right truck. Can you get in the canoe? Cargo value.
All right. All right. I need to go up here. Harry Potter. Stop. Don't bang up the truck. MCU music.
Why did he do that? He was trying to flip me.
I'm not going to have anything left. 1.5 thousand. Are you shitting me?
Okay. Need at least $500 of cargo. Let's go. I got it. I got it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
This is fun. This is fun. He's going to keep the shit in the back. Oh, this is a cool car.
That hurt me. This is a fucking Cadillac. All right. Not going to mess it up. So I'm
going to try to get as many as I can. Like I can pull it off with like movie wire.
That was a matrix scene. What happened? I know. I look, I did it already. I'm already a full step
ahead of you. Dammit. I was trying to hit the guy in the head. I will get like a headshot with
a bike. I promise you at least once. All right. Cargo. All right. Let's be easy. I'm going to try
to get as much as I can here. Why would they just be loose in the back? You can't wrap these up
like Saran wrap or something. Where's the bungees to hold these things down? Put a tarp on it. Yeah.
That's what I mean. Like tie a tarp down behind here. All this loose shit. You never should
carry anything like this. But you always drive by that guy in the highway that's got like a
fucking mattress with one bungee on there. And he's going like 40 miles, like 30 miles per hour
in the highway. It's like, dude, you can't take a back road. Like what the fuck are you doing?
How much is in there? There's still $500. Push it. Can't move.
God damn it.
All right. Well, it's this guy. This is a deliberate sabotage guy drives across the whole thing.
And he tries to, he just murders you, just drives into you from the side.
How does it feel to get sabotaged? I feel like that happens quite frequently.
I want to go the other direction. Okay. Here we go. Oh, go, go, go. Okay. Do not let the guy
in the Mack truck smash into the side of the car. I gotta be the guy in the highway going 30
out of the way. All right. When does it happen? And he comes right from the left side.
Truck joke incoming. No truck joke, not incoming. This is where truck joke truck. I can't even say
here it comes right here. He drives over here. What was that? Did I go over a bump? There it is.
All right. He's waiting. He's waiting. He's waiting. This is like an online player.
Fuck you, buddy. Not going to happen. Yup. See you later. Watch out for grenades. Now I've got to
hold on. I got to take an alternate route. I don't want to go straight up the front.
All right. We're going to go this way. We're going to turn good. Okay. Now we're going to bang left.
We're going to, we're avoiding that huge barricade. Is that water? Okay. All right. Hey,
okay. We're good. I did it. I got $9,000. One of the guns spawned outside the truck.
That's unfortunate. Sneak through here. It's okay. It's all right. How do I have 31 health?
Okay. Here it is. $9,000. Exit the vehicle. Thank you. Return guns to contract me bonus. $9,000,
$9,000. I think it's shooting at me. Didn't I just do a mission for them?
Is the head Ruben in there? Didn't I just do this with these guys?
Why are they doing this? I'm a dipshit. I was, they were just lighting me up.
Wait, I shot at the truck. Yeah. And the cut scene, that doesn't count.
I found your missing guns. Now I'd like to talk to Dr. Ruben.
The name's Mui. Your boss wants to speak to me. All right. You're the mercilano shot in the ass.
Hey, you know what she's got? Tim times gave $50. Thank you, Tim times. That's a huge amount of money.
Say thanks for all the laughs. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. Dude. I'm listening.
We need you to retrieve. That's fucking crazy. Classified tech. Can't say much.
Loving every laugh. Laughing about it. Okay. Action up. The up mercs want a favor before opening the
gate. Retrieve their one of a kind vehicle. The Devastator. 25,000. Let's do it. Am I going to
have aggro on these guys for the rest of the game? Shit. Okay. Well, it's just the guys outside,
right? It's just the guys outside. We're fine. They're not firing. Yeah. They just, they just,
they're just angry. All right. Who do I have to talk to? So I don't have to be here.
Where is it? That's it. It's X to reverse. That's me.
I'm so excited. What? I need to reload. You have got to be kidding me.
This isn't funny. This is the Devastator. Okay. You're my hero. So I have to take this fucking thing?
Where? This is 25 grand. That means you have to ride the little pink bike.
Get out of here. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Laugh it up. Nice bike. Huh? None of you
dickheads could do what I just did. Everybody just shut their fucking mouth immediately after
seeing that. So this is just like, haha, you have to go get this dumb, embarrassing bike.
You're doing, I have it. It's okay. Let's move please.
$25,000. One of them is, you know, can I just kill one of them? Don't shoot them. Don't shoot
them. Don't shoot anybody. Oh wait, I can go in here. Do not attack anybody in here is what you're
saying. Don't do that. Wait. Enemies sighted. I'm sorry. I mean, you got the enemies here.
She's in the car. What are you doing? Why did he just do that? Why did he just do that?
Why did he just do that? You psycho. Oh, he's too smart. He got out. Yeah, he did get out. Outplayed.
I can't help it. I love these games. This is so much fun. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I have
to go. Ow. What's the X? What's that mean? X, X, X, like a bar filling. What does that mean?
Skies as a voice suspicion to keep your disguise up. Open up. All right. I'm going to save, save,
save. Oh, shit. You're being completely unreasonable. There's over 2000 people here.
How can we possibly get this? All right. There's almost 7000 people here. You got it a little wrong.
You got the most expensive haircut here. You must be in charge. You're the
mercenary my security people call me about. My name's Marie. Well, I'm glad you're here.
This presents a fantastic opportunity. Why are these not right? Universal petroleum. Sure.
I'm Dr. Ruben. What a little costume. Anything you need, I can provide. I'm here with only one
instruction. Keep the oil flowing. I'm empowered to use any of the all methods. You met with someone
I'm looking for. A former mercenary. They call Blanco. I'm familiar with him. When Solano has
bad news for us, he sends Blanco. This is really bad stage production. I just memorized my fucking
lines and I'm just going to say them. Hopefully you get yours right too. Let's hear it. Arrested
strategy of corporate disincentivization. His men kidnapped my marketing VP, Victor Contreras,
and are threatening to kill him. I don't think Solano's men are particularly bright. They call
me regularly from Victor's cell phone. I'm going to loan you my helicopter. Damn it.
It even has Sims music.
I can't follow any of that. I have no idea what just happened.
Um, okay. These ethugs have kidnapped a universal petroleum executive.
Use the provided helicopter to support, to deliver listening posts and then we can track the
kidnappers. Oh yeah. Then rescue the hostage $500,000. Is he pretending about the FPS? No,
I liked it. I don't want it to be 30. I, it's fine.
The first thing you'll have to do is set up three, set up listening posts.
I've identified the best places for the listening posts.
Okay. Deliver listening posts. We're going this way first.
Holy shit. Something just exploded. Save game. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Increase the FPS. Universal petroleum helipilot in the air and ready for your signal.
This is going to get hairy Devlin. You ready to dodge air fire?
Holy shit. The helicopters just flew into each other. What the hell is going on up there?
Did you see that? Wait a minute.
An alarm has activated. Give me a break. Blaster bomb.
Ow, my head. Okay. I'm going in. What I have to do, listening posts, listening post delivery.
Right here. Get in the X wing.
One of the most satisfying noises in all cinema history is the quack, quack.
Fucking landed on my feet too. Jesus. Where is it? I know I was going on the roof,
but then they blasted me off. What happened to it? It's gone. What? I'm so confused. Why is it gone?
Good. Good, good, good. All right. I'm almost there. What? He's looking over there like,
oh no. Oh shit. Oh, that's not good. It's not good. Oh, it's okay.
Listening port. Hello. Let's do it. No shit. Did I do the wrong spot?
Switch secondary weapon C4. What is this? All right. Did I turn it on? Do I need that?
Do I need that? Somebody tell me. Do I need that thing? Yes, I do. Is it fall damage?
Is it fall damage? Yes or no? Fall damage? I need that. It's on the other side of the
fence. Fuck. I got him. Buster bomb. What do I do with it? How do I use it? What? What did I just do?
Wait, what? Where's the C4 that I threw? It's somewhere over here. I think it exploded.
It doesn't matter. I don't even need it. Oh my God. Just go, go, go, go, go. Get in, get in,
get in, get in. Good drive. Okay, Ren. Stevie, I'm going to kill you. Switch secondary weapons
to equip C4. That's going to be on the screen forever, I think. How do I get that off the screen?
How do I get out of here? Equip it? I don't know how to equip it. Switch secondary weapons to equip
C4. But I already, I equipped the C4 and I threw it over the cliff. What's going on with this
helicopter? Grapple. How do I grapple? I need a grappling hook. What? Right back up. What the
hell are you talking about? Whoa, what's this? Collect spare parts. That's $200,000 but no reason.
All right, here we go. Right on the beach. It's listening post two. Increase the FPS. I can't.
There's no increasing FPS. Get a guy on the turret. Will he get on? Okay, there's one right there.
Just take it. I gave you that one. Take that one. All right, make sure your aim is good.
You're just shooting up into... All right, well, I didn't even know. I think you aggroed those guys.
Money. No, I don't want it. I can't even take it. Come on in. Get it. Get him. Shoot, shoot, shoot,
shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot. Shoot him. Shoot him down, please.
Shoot him down. Get him. Enemy tank? Oh, you got him. You got him. Good, good, good.
Shoot that tank. Steal it. Steal it. Get him. Did he have a ball gag in his mouth? What was that?
What was in his mouth? What the hell was that? Wait, I think I... The whole building just came
down. Oh, shit. Okay, I'm ready. Use... Listening. Listening. Grenade. Active.
This game is literally times two speed. Is it? Is it really though? Like, is it actually?
I can't... I cannot change this. This is not changeable. All right, one more.
I'm blowing this place up. Look, it's a red thing. How could there be two of you in here?
How many people are in there with a rocket launcher? Why does every window have a guy
with a rocket launcher in it? Turn on V-sync. Change their voices. No, it's the same, right?
Yeah, it's the same. I have a deadline. Move. Like, I'm just complaining about the humidity.
Now it looks like it has a Snapchat filter on it. It's... Now it's worse. Hold on. Wait, is it worse?
I can't change the refresh rate. It won't let me. Put it on four three. Why would I make it four
three? Don't stand in the road, dude. Don't shoot at me. Going to advanced. I don't think I can
change this, guys. Advanced. Water effects. Particle level. Motion. Yeah, none of this
means anything. Please add me back on Snapchat. No. All right, here we go.
V-sync is off again. Yeah, because everyone hated it. All right, this one should be easy.
Oh, give me that tank. Three out of three. I got it. Okay. Yeah, I'm destroying this building.
This is the guys with the rocket launchers hang out in here. What's in there?
Okay. Building destroyed. Wait, what's all this blinking for?
Rocket launcher storage.
What? Kill the executive? No, no, go. Hijack kidnapper's vehicle and save the...
Shoot the... I'm not going to shoot the old lady. Stop.
Oh, that's a good guy. Wait. What's a 200 fucking thousand dollars?
All right, give me a faster car. I need a bike. Just give me the sedan. Bootleg Star Wars. It is
kind of like Star Wars. All right, I only have 11 minutes before this is all done.
I love the... Who's in that vehicle? Oh, it's one of ours. Why would they care? They have to check
every single car to see if it's one of their friends. Good link. All right, hold on. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. Well, here's the problem. I can't click on the link yet because alt-tabbing
freezes the game. So we have to wait till I get to... Wait, I have to steal this or what?
It'll only be hijacked from the rear. So what, am I supposed to drive up behind and jump out of the
car or just wedge him? Check the link. I can't right now. I cannot click a link right now. If
I alt-tab, the game will crash. You're going to have to wait until I'm done with this mission.
Don't drive into me. This is an armored car. Get out of the way. You're driving on the wrong side.
Yeah, I do that in every driving game because it's quicker. You actually get to where you're
going way faster. And why is the GPS set incorrectly, by the way? Who put that in?
Oh, I just kind of wanted to get you close. Get me close. What do you think I could do?
You don't have confidence I can't get you where you're fucking going?
All right, quick, get him. Wait, wait, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, easy, easy.
Can I actually... What? Can I fly this? Oh, just a... This is huge. Where are we going?
Who's landing zone? Um, that's dumb. That's dumb. I want to... Why can't I fly it?
Okay, come in. I got to spend this money. I have like a million dollars.
How does this guy get in?
Holding a match in his mouth. He's like smoking a match.
Like this dude is... What are you? What are you? Like 15, you go to the gas station, you
buy... You just take like the matches and you pretend to smoke the matches. What are you
trying to be cool? I don't get it. Is that the only thing you can get from the store?
What happened? Wait, did this...
We just saw this again.
Wake up! Wake up!
Okay, here he is. We got him. Good.
Is this changing? Skip! Jesus. New shop item. Top supply drop.
CQB kit. All right, save game. All right, click on the link now. Let's take a look.
What is it? What do you want me to see? Why is everybody spamming? Wait, what is this?
Wait, is this somebody like... Are you like watching a presentation in like college?
What? Wait, hold on. Why are you doing this? Go back to school. Show it. It's a Twitter video.
I can't... Hold on. All right. No, I had... No, no, no, no. This is cute, but like... No,
I don't... That's... I don't want to... No, no, no, no. You go look at it. My game is about to
actually freeze. I asked the professor a question. Well, I didn't. You're doing an illegal move in
college. I think it's broken. Are we in? All right, I'm good. I can't stay tabbed out for too long.
He's gonna get disqualified from class. You should be doing your homework and not watching
this shitty stream. True. Don't even say that out loud. All right. What about... What about
winching? What about a star system? Well, it's a good ques... Wait, get the toolbox above the
specified height and you'll win the wager. Am I gonna be too short for this? I let the trans...
Um, okay. What the hell was that? You can fly it? Play and retract the winch. You can fly
helicopters. Okay, how do we fly this? How do I deploy it? Up, down? Okay, it's left.
What am I trying to do? Am I picking up the tree? I got it. Okay, now where am I taking this? What
do I... What am I taking this? Out of bounds! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What do you want me to do?
What? Target five. Do I just let it go? Did I do it? Hold it at five. Okay, hold it at five. Okay,
now what? Stack it. Stack it? Stack crates. I dropped it. Okay, it's off, right? Drop it. All
right, go. Why is this one heavier? Okay, what? All right, I got it. I did it. Is that nine meters?
What's the goal? Too much? The target is five. Yeah, but I can't go over the target? Okay, two,
five. Okay, nine, seven, six. Is that it? It's six. Oh, come on, really? I did it. What are you guys
talking about? I did, I won. 1.4 million. Level two, transit. No, no, information about Eva.
Okay.
Can we get rid of this guy? All right, pistol challenge. Introduction to the Plav sniping
challenge. All right, one more. I've set up a sniper course. Destroy the portraits of Solano
and destroy Solano's cars. You have to stay on the roof. Okay.
How do I zoom in? How do I aim? How do I go into sniper mode? Okay, I got bonus objective updated.
Destroy the bonus statue. What? Wait, am I in like a... I'm like stuck in here. That didn't get
destroyed. I think it's still possible. Ice cream truck. I can't even shoot these ones. This is so
fucked up. What the hell? I didn't even save the game before this either. I'm loaded inside of the
wall. I get it. Okay. Maybe I could have jumped up here and... That's so stupid.
Whatever. It's 100k. I have 1.3 million. All right, I'm just doing introduction to the Plav.
I've got some information on the local corruption. The People's Liberation Army of Venezuela,
or PLAV, is a group of leftist radicals. Very radical. They've been hiding out in the
jungle for decades. They hate Solano enough to risk direct... What's that laughing face?
They're also keen on disrupting Universal Petroleum's business for being
willing pawns of the capitalist military... See that? What was that? Whose emote is that?
Bella Acosta. She's unusually well-funded, thanks to close ties with the People's Republic of China.
She's willing to spend some of their money on world-class mercenaries...
It was a laughing face. Yes, that one. What is that? Who is that? All right, I'm ready.
Where do I buy things? We could probably go public. Get investors, silk stocks. What do you think?
Um, I want to buy something. I have a lot of money.
3D streamer refuses to advertise other streamers' emotes.
Okay, what is going on here? Destroy targets? This is Eva's Garage and then
Southeastern Amazon Outpost. All right, we're gonna go to Eva's Garage. This is very far away.
Yeah, where are the clothes? I want to put on something cool. I want to wear a different
vest or something. Call a helicopter? Transit. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. All right, yeah, I get it.
You have to get... It's gas. Do I need to get gas? Easy. Nice. Okay, there we go. All right,
I want to go to Eva's Garage. Why can't you go there? Wait, it has to be another helipad
that I've already unlocked. Yeah, he gets the picture. Kill him and take it. I don't think I
can. Oh, that's where the fuel tanks and money too, right? What do you say? All right, here we go.
Wait, is this bad guys or good guys? Good guys. Nice. All right, these guys are friendly.
Come get this. Resource pickup. Right here.
Solano makes us an offer. Oh, sorry, lady. Universal Petroleum can kiss my ass. I don't care
about the oil, just the paycheck. When do we get it? It's very quiet.
Good to see one of us made it big. Hold your fire. It's Jennifer Mui. Resource pickup.
Okay, get it. What? What happened? You're my hero. What happened? Why do they hate me?
Oh, okay. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I need to redo it. I stole the oil. Holy shit,
this guy doesn't even care. Wow. I got to track this guy down. Holy shit, he's just going nuts.
He's just, he's not stopping. What am I doing? What am I doing? You're right.
This is such a long ride. Wait, does the UP organization hate me now? I didn't even do
that. I just, I don't, whatever. Why would you do that? What's with these planes flying around?
There's red planes that keep showing up on the mini-map. Why can't go up that?
How's that? Oh, okay. I was going to say that makes no sense. Trying to shave some time off.
Wait, do people know who I am? I guess they kind of do, huh?
I'm kind of going too fast to be identified, aren't I? Oh, I made it. I actually went through it.
Okay, so far so good. I got 25 bucks. What'd I get $25 for? It's a guy in the driver's side.
Okay, let's go. Yeah, this is a shitty gun. I want a new gun. I don't want just like an AK.
I want something else. Wait, I can take that, right? Can I? Or am I too far away? Can he
actually get this? Steel tank buster. Yeah. Hello? Wait, somebody's shooting. Get on it.
Wait, you mean like stand on that? Oh shit, can I do that? I'll try that next time. I'm just going
to crouch on it and see what happens. Let me go to the mission first. Am I going to play Ratatouille
for the Xbox 360? No, I don't think so. I'm sorry. Why? Play Jump King? I'm not going to play Jump
King. I promised. When did I promise that I was going to play Ratatouille? Did I? I don't know
why I would ever say that. Money. Is this doing anything? I don't know. Was that a grenade or
is that him coming to get this? Okay. This is the best game. Wait, that's the best game ever made.
Wait. I forgot. There's another one right here. Don't worry. Ewan stops up. Ewan, come back.
He's busy. I know. Come on. Hurry up. Get rid of it so I can do this.
Save the game. Yeah, that's a good call. You promised you'd play it in 2012. What? Do it.
Did I get the money? The guy drove over it. Come on. Give me a break. Remember when you said you
were going to read Diary of a Wimpy Kid to us? You had a dream about that. That's not what happened.
Here we go. Mission time. Read it? I'm not going to read Diary of a Wimpy Kid.
You, Ava Navarro? I know who you are. What is?
You're the mercenary. The one Solano shot in the ass.
Solano's goon shot me. I figured you'd come here.
What do you mean you figured I'd come here? You're alone. You need help.
You go through vehicles quick. Need them repaired. I'm the best-
So this is the- You hate Carmona.
You hate Solano. You probably need a helicopter pilot.
I've got a helicopter pilot. What do you have against Carmona?
If you're planning on using airstrikes. I am.
Which I figure you are. All right, so you've got a thing against Carmona.
No, just because I'm anti-Carmona doesn't mean I'm pro-mercenary.
All right, you're available. Otherwise, you'd have kicked me out already.
How did you know? What is that going around to?
All right, let's see. There's one last job I must finish before I can close up and help you get-
I'm Solano. Yeah, I'm building a unique vehicle
for a special client. I need help getting the parts and then when it's done-
It's funny each time. It's funny every time.
And the oil company have a bouncer on me. You don't have a lot of friends, do you?
And I heard something about a jet pilot hiding out with a pirate.
And when this is done, you'll join me? Probably.
Okay, test drive the Acharo de Muerte for Eva.
You remind me of me.
Oh, the PC version is fucked. Yeah, that's why I got the PlayStation 3 version and I couldn't
capture it. I don't know why for no reason.
Okay, test drive.
Hop in and take her out for a test run for me.
Why aren't you driving it?
Oh, this is a comedy car. I can't wait.
Is this a tuber car?
Are you telling me it's a jump?
Is this a jump?
It better be.
You know what kind of car? Okay, I had one of these.
I had a car like this where I could flip it over and it would still drive.
I'd be driving around and they would just flip the fuck over
and I would I could still drive it upside down and right side up.
It was awesome.
I would drive it this shit over fucking like Clebson.
I would drive it all over the place.
I'd gone off on the grass and stuff.
It was awesome.
It was so much fun.
No, not a regular car.
A like an RC car.
Yeah.
What was that thing called?
It was called like the Reverso or something.
Right at the strip line.
It was fast, too.
I can't believe this is an actual jump.
Rebound.
That's the one.
Yep.
That thing was awesome.
Works.
All right.
Rough terrain.
Let's see.
Crackdown?
Too bad that crackdown three was terrible.
All right.
We're good.
Crackdown three was destined to be awful.
I don't even remember crackdown two.
I remember crackdown one.
I never played it.
Two was the same mission 12 times.
That's unfortunate.
Crackdown two was just crackdown one with zombies.
Well, they went with that trope, huh?
Oh, I have to hit this.
I'm not just going to drive it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What is it specifically about this game that is fun?
The whole thing.
I think it's really fun.
Oh, I have 25 seconds.
I'm almost there.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
No.
It's proof of you saying I was going to play Ratatouille.
All right.
You know, in my, in my defense, who cares?
I do.
Yeah, but like in my defense, it's Ratatouille the game.
Oh, who, who does it really matter if I played or not?
I mean, I'm going to on September fucking like 28th or something.
I don't know.
He's doing the same joke again.
You figured me out.
You figured out everything I do with a jump.
This is a long mission.
This is I guess your hydraulics work.
Can I go back to driving a motorcycle?
I quit after this mission.
That's not going to be me.
I want to fly the helicopter.
No, no, no, no, no, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Please, no, why?
I don't want to do this again.
Oh, my fucking God quit after this mission.
No, it's not going to happen to me.
No, it's not.
Okay.
I'm just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Next?
No, but next.
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, just hold on.
No, I'm staying here.
I'm not this game is fucking fun. Just this fish is stupid. Okay, don't worry
We're gonna get up the stupid mission and we're gonna go back to fucking full of grenades and people
Cars gonna drive by and I'm gonna get it's gonna hit me and I'm gonna go. Oh, I actually do want to see what else is in
The game. I'm having a lot of fun in this one. All right, I don't don't fuck. I have plenty of time
It's still challenge if I can do it. I would love to do it. I want to spend money to everything spent a dollar
It's definitely like a jetpack or something. I don't fuck Matt. The funniest part about the ratatouille game stream
Yeah, well, let's see. I bet you I bet you're like 3,000 or you don't even show up
It's like one of the lowest viewed streams in history
Play ratatouille do it, but he's actually playing ratatouille. Yeah
Oh, I got something else going on today. What's going on?
How do I get up there what the fuck wait
And then but I have to go back all the way around. I'm not gonna do this. It's gonna fail
Have nine seconds to go around the entire course. Oh my god
Why did I?
Know I'm gonna beat it. I don't care. No, no, no, no, no, I'm playing this. No, it's not gonna happen. I have
Okay
There is no next game it is only this game
Yeah, I'm not gonna quit. I am not gonna quit. I want you to remember who said that
All you that think I'm gonna quit it's not gonna happen. I'm gonna play this through until it I beat this
I'm not the whole game, but enough till I fly the helicopter into like the
car
You know, that's gonna be funny. It's good that way. I don't want to do this again. I don't want to do this again
I want to play the game
Don't fuck it up. Just do it. Normally you have plenty of time
Honey, helicopter bit people happy. Yeah
I might be able to get in like a plane
Like a boat too. I was in a boat in the beginning of the game. It's still more to see
Alright, stop this. Here we go playing minecraft after this. We're playing minecraft in like two weeks. Oh
Let them flip you
Yeah, FTK
I'll give you some updates on FTK. It is pretty much ready to go. We have to do some testing on it
Here are some of the things that are going to change. I'll tell you right now. You're ready
No aging system. No stamina. The goal of the game is not just to walk around with a stick and try to kill me
No more three months sub
Requirement because I wasn't streaming for two months. So that would be stupid to have that
You have to have been subbed when I wasn't streaming. No, you just have to be an active sub
It doesn't matter I don't think it matters if you're community sub or a regular sub doesn't matter
The food there's no food system. It's going to be a full-on adventure
We're gonna do with all of us together
Should be a lot of fun. The rules in the game system is completely changed
What's FTK? It is favor the king
Favor of the king you have to be a two-year sub, but I don't think there'd be very many people that be participating
Alright, this is it. This is the end
Don't flip over it at the very end, please
Why are you taking me through this? Oh
That was my entire- he just blew my face-up
Wow long is this
Wait, I thought- I thought you were supposed to run people over
She has not communicated on radio for a while. I don't think she's still talking to me
Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! Finish it! This is
vision to have an end
I don't think this mission has an end come on dude I don't want to do this
again all right if I fail this I'm not doing it again I'm going to the other
mission I'm gonna piss my pants too I have to piss really badly you were
literally at the end that's why would it drive me through a bunch a big bunch of
tanks he pants pee pants beef not yet ah you god damn it game why no not you
guys this this guy can I repair the car favor you yes that's right favor you you
got it you know the deal I'm gonna play yes uh is it weird that I think that
because I've had the 3do for like 14 months I'm afraid that its internal
battery will not turn on like the console just won't turn on because the
it's been in a closet for too long that possible did I burn out the internal
battery that isn't the thing okay how old is it 25 years old or something my
GameCube died like that that's what I mean yeah you gotta be careful so quick
you never know taking so much damage right now how do you not take this
damage I have to drive through this shit hello things almost dead this thing is
almost gonna explode again 82% but what that meter that meter was going down was
that that wasn't a health gauge or anything what was that that it's 82
guy uh-huh left at the bridge don't go down the bridge thank you I'll go off
don't go off don't go off don't go off please don't go off okay I'm fine I'm
good I'm fucking confident and cool I'm letting any rocks
you're rejects one you're rejects two all right this is where it got hairy last
time this gex even any fun that was the man the gex is the Mario of the 3do
that was their mascot back then animals and and like little fat guys were but
mascots stop talking for a second Jeremy please for the love of God don't speak
just go get off of you can I am I all right I'm all right okay okay okay okay
what did you shoot that at am I about to beat them the missile what was that that
was weird kill the gunner to hijack the tank I don't care about the tank I just
want to complete this all right get the scooby-doo mystery vans out of the way
please that oversaturated market that's it I went thanks God mark the car inside
the garage all right I'm not gonna fuck I can't fuck around right now
beautiful down boy Ava is a mechanic uh-huh can you do jets and tanks I can
fix anything with an engine welcome aboard do I have to work with him crap
whoo yep yep grappling hook grappling hook how do I get it do shop do I finally
get to buy stuff I have 1.5 million dollars I'm just working on I don't
care your storyline does not mean anything to me I just want to buy things
okay custom-built monster truck 40,000 oh I buy 38 of them what happens if I buy
38 what happens anybody know well will they all spawn outside I do it Jesus
all right where are they you just have they just boxes okay you just get them
dropped okay well then fuck that I'll buy one and they get the grappling hook
that is the number one thing that I'm doing right now where do I get the
grappling hook get it right he'd I have it already oh great Lord Walden just
came in with 20 community subs 20 committed back to the 20 subs dude great
Lord Walden appreciate it hey boss I'm just working on this you know I'm not
some that's some free shit for you and some free money for me I want to actually
try to do this don't put me into the water god damn it I'm just doing that
I'm just doing the next mission I'm just gonna do the next mission we're gonna
gonna be sick use cheat codes it's more fun well not yet so you tell me I have
the grappling hook now I just own it all right PMC what are the missions are
there stockpile go to the stockpile talk to Eva hey boss let's talk the
grappling hook I gave you will come in handy if you want to hijack a helicopter
oh yeah point and shoot yes yanked up to the bird
however getting the pilot out of his seat once you're up there that's oh I
cannot wait all right information about Misha remember the jet pilot I told you
about I've never met him but he's supposed to be pretty good he's hanging
out with the pirates apparently okay let's go get him what do you think he's
up here how I'm gonna get over there I'm gonna have to take a helicopter there to
this thing all right let's go take a helicopter wait there was five tier two
subs there was paper box thanks for the five tier two subs that's ten dollars
each for those when people can do community subs for tier two or two or
three it's insane that's so much money what's happening oh you can fall through
the map and it happened again it's twenty thousand dollars down the toilet
oh please come on this should I go up this side oh my god why no shit this
thirty thousand dollars down the drain how do I what am I supposed to do about
this I'm set to quit you won't lock the FPS didn't we know I don't want to play
online I'm taking a piss I can't even leave this I'll be back I'm peeing bye
okay I'm back hello I'm gonna try to actually leave the room again for the
shot okay cool three two wait that's like clockwork I had another dream but I
sincerely don't remember what it was I'm at the FPS all right I'm gonna show you
this one more time because people look this can't move I cannot move this hear
me do you hear that I can't move it do it on the main menu yeah we're on v-sync
I can't I can't do it I can't look oh I didn't do it before I turned this on
everybody fucking hated it everybody told me this looks like a snapchat
filter you must what if I was faking it that would be so stupid all right I have
the information about me sure okay good what do you think I put this in a jeep
zero to 200 in one second here we go I'm working download the patch patch all
right there we go we're good look it works here's the thing I don't know if
it worked I'll tell you one reason why I think we just got lucky cuz remember
why I came out here before without the limiter and it was fine if the patch or
here we go let's go transit and then we're gonna grapple hook them you can't
grapple hook all right we're going up here what happened up here why where's
my where's my helicopter pad what where's the helicopter pad they hate me
now oh god damn it are you serious wait just give me I'm taking ready when you
are just give me give me give me give me it get out of the get out get out get
out it's mine now we got a raid raid from raid from John Silver what's up John
welcome everybody those that don't know John Silver is gonna be doing a lot of
the artwork where they choose your own adventure game what how what happened
hold on settle down those either don't know a choose your own adventure custom
sorcery like board game is being made right now John Silver is gonna be doing
some of the art Ashley is too and stars gonna be making the whole game itself
they've all been commissioned out it's gonna be a lot of fun
story that's right yeah my star underscore that's the guy something I've
been wanting to do it something I've wanted to do for a long time at least the
last like probably a couple of years but it was never really an opportunity to do
it but now there is but I think welcome everybody from John's channel John
Silver does art on stream and he's incredibly talented he's insanely
talented check it out sometime I'm gonna try this now disturbingly talented
uh is this thing on fire how did you even know I was gonna be over here I
take the boat who is shooting wait what there's a JK shoot him I can't turn it
around holy shit all right let's get it all right I'm gonna try to stay on this
Lego racer 2 waiting room what if I just changed scenes right now and it was a
Lego racer 2 oh that didn't work that person would just start choking on
whatever they were eating I push this back in the water okay well very
clearly I need to go across the water so I get this back in the water I don't
think so yeah I can took a hit go let's go let's go scream it right scream it
let's go did I do my best let's go wait this guy's in a tiny little but I want
this just give me it I'm just around am I drowning this guy oh no okay give me
the boat get it I'm trying okay it's he's fine he's fine he's fine okay how
can I steal this I'm just doing magic tricks for this guy now okay just get
him oh no go on go on let's do the thing go on get out of here goodbye why
is it not detonating why is it not detonating you have to be you can't be
driving a car he's alive he is not alive wait is that the same guy no it's not
that was $5,000 okay I'm just doing the mission let's go go mission mission
mission mission mission why did you do that I don't know sink the oil platform
no not yet let's fucking go I can't the jet ski wait if it's actually a jet ski
I want to I actually want that no like fucking around and be an idiot it's a
jet ski it's not but whatever I want it I actually really want to drive this
oh no he's gonna get crushed he's not looking pay attention in front of you he
made it holy shit I can't believe you made it I want that wait should I get
the huge one no I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm gonna go I gotta move I have to
play oh my fuck I'm just just I don't care I have to get out of here I have
to stop us at once no no way I can go in the back no what just happened why
dolphin dive get on the fucking thing why is half of it underground wake up
I'm what I'm trying to get on this boat I promise this is not an act what oh
okay I want it it's happening okay I don't know what's going on I don't get
it the boat can't be moving um fucking great wait a rescue thank you I'm here
uh I can't I can't I got it yeah why is this guy still next to me I know what to
do next I'm just current I'm just dicking around you never dicked around
before Eva come on you never just jumped into random boats before okay here we go
good okay I mean you got it I gotta see if I can hit the head by this
everybody has that's a sniper that's a sniper rifle I'm in trouble where is he
oh shit but these are these guys my friends right wait no they hate me they
hate me on the boss don't call a boss what do you mean call on the boss put the
phone down I'm calling mom we're almost at the next mission I promise you money
I don't even care about the money I can't spend it anywhere anyways mom said
it's my turn in the armored car it's another goddamn ocean how far away am I
oh shit dude what the hell was that mayday mayday mayday person in need person
in need what what is this where did it with the boat it's not still alive I
just I'm yes I'm trying to get it got stronger I'm just trying to get to the
stupid next part of the game was dissolved I have fast travel if I the
fast travel location that I could go to that they hate me now I don't know what
even happened I stole their like oil and they had like an oil can and I took it
from them and they all freaked out and then I was just defending myself and I
did like ten people attacked me and I threw a grenade up there and then too
much ADHD to make it to the next mission what the hell even am I I'm almost there
all right look is shooting at me with no don't knock it all down you idiot what
just hit me for that much damage damn it just look how many wait just go what do
you mean just go there's like 50 people on this boat there we go there we go
there we go please do you like yeah there's a there's currently a guy in
the machine gun spot I jacked the helicopter I mean my mouth they sacrificed
it shit okay now can I make those guys at the up facility like me again I'm
gonna try to do that damn it up to Fiona and bribe them who's Fiona by a
helicopter I don't I can bribe faction universal truth that's too that was a
lot that was six that was three hundred fucking thousand dollars okay I'm for a
transport let's go I want to transport to here that's give me it come on
transit you also have a helicopter available to have delivered it's called
the Raven do I hey the lucky ladies ready when you are go to your stockpile
let's check that in a little bit okay there we go on universally hated here
now I have to set the get to here shouldn't be that difficult to get to
here you stockpile used up how do I get to that stockpile vehicles light
military airstrikes artillery strike supplies CQB kit I have oh I have this
now what do I get the CQB kit oh yeah give me I'll take a shotgun
race that was a waste why it's an I guess a shotgun I really just kind of
we just did like the Saturday morning paperboy thing huh I open it how do I
open the crate
oh it's like seven boats in here what are the weapons are here the still
shotgun and transit see okay car oh yeah that's right they don't hate me I can
take one of these wait should I take one of the cool cars yeah let me see what
was here okay vehicles light military vehicle let's do it the Raven didn't
somebody say this is here comes all right can I return it it's the same car
as all the other ones but this one is mine though so that's there that's the
difference okay I fire from here now move a ZVZ base all right here we go you
honk other people get in the driver's seat that's awesome what is that kill
or capture HVT gotta verify this guy keep them alive I'm using a pistol against
a fucking heavy machine gun what the fuck wait we're 8mg what is this all
right where's this dude it's like up there maybe just have to go around all
right I just have to subdue him don't kill him it's right up here trying to
drive through his house but that didn't really work now did it just get out get
out get out get out get out get out where is he right there okay
subdued oh this is bad I gotta carry this guy you're not gonna shoot him
kill you know I'm going to kill you wait I need that car okay wait no holy
shitty best come here what do you have that kind of aim fuck off this is
unbelievable Jesus oh my god wait wait wait wait wait wait context menu wait
wait wait wait wait this load him I got him I got him I got him I got this guy
is ruining everything this guy is playing his own video game all right I've
had enough I've had enough of you okay all right come with that where's that
guy extract him extract I don't want to start screaming I'm gonna be mellow
all right one out of ten what am I doing why am I doing this can I climb what
happens if I I can't even aim the camera anywhere I can't even I can't look down
all I can do is stop grappling and I don't think I want to do that steal
this helicopter I can't drop now I'm over water I don't want to drop in water
wait where we going wait there's another one of those all right I can look I'm
gonna get another one of these why is he going over here there a reason why this
dude is dropping over here all right I'm gonna drop right up assume the escort
submission position very you piece of shit so I'm doing data here okay I'm get
this one too it's wrong but wrong button wrong button I tried to verify him take a
picture of his dead body apparently can I pick him up can you take this instead
uh I'm waiting for waiting for him to move they're not gonna be mad at me
right nope wrong way I mean I have to cross the water that's just a fact is
there any way I can cross the water without being in a boat that is pretty
good that is what somebody would be saying plane all right I have to have
to swim let's just go drive into the lake I know just trying to see if there's
anything else over here hold on what is this who omega well who that's exactly
what I do when I try to pretend like I'm doing something in battlefield
battlefield is it's impossible that game is I don't know how people play it and do
well all I do is just kind of shoot regular bullets at buildings and in
random tanks and stuff and I just go well I'm just kind of participating
there's like probably four people playing against three people in
battlefield and then like 55 people are just shooting at random buildings or
just or they're like one of the five people in the tank that just die from
bidding just shot by anti tank stuff all right I got it I actually made it I
actually made it here on I'm gonna go for the captain they have to open the
door wait there is open the door wait can this guy not stand up in the boat
no no stop that's all I'm gonna let stand up I'm gonna be smacking this guy
around it was well hell yeah I did it destroy this target all right so what I
just throw what what happened to the mission I was supposed to do you're
fighting somebody not anymore they're fighting me I've marked one of the
buildings of such a good throw unbelievable get me up on just get me
up all right just run we had ten community subs from VARX and ten from
really funky really fun guy that's a good hit by a car and there it is
thanks this up okay here we go I've destroyed this building you got it I do
from the inside god damn it I have airstrikes airstrike
ooh artillery strike I'll take it okay drop me an artillery strike here
ready like it all right now get me the fuck off this dock it's 100k nice all
right don't let him do it again don't let him do it again fun what is this the
division come on dude pretty good all right now I can see it and then 140 gas
I don't have enough gas all right I gotta go that way I'm going that way now
I'm in a big lunch mood right now what do you guys think for lunch what's a
lunch that you guys like tell me a lot a good lunch no not taquitos that's not a
good lunch thing right now I know not steak I'm not pizza not McDonald's the
ham and Swiss that's not a bad lunch chickpea fries that sounds amazing I
don't know look into that a sub good to old pork sandwich that sounds pretty good
too the cheese omelet hey hold on a minute about an omelet with mushrooms in
mushroom omelet hmm this is the pirate HQ western-style omelet that sounds good
too is the place I need to go inside of this dome so far away still how did I if
I die it's gonna be so sad buffalo wings mmm not into a hot sauce right now why
am I swimming because there's not a boat within a hundred meters eat pure lard
those are jet skis I unlocked the jet ski they are I'm gonna get one oh yeah
this one right here on the left is ours drive the little dimba move yep oh yeah
this is awesome oh it's already gone she really helped me I chipped over how is
he getting on it okay why is he doing this hi can we give him a push all right
I'm gonna give these guys a push we gotta get these guys into the water we're
good okay once they get in the water they're gonna be really happy I promise
god damn it needs to be some don't bump into anybody get out of the way move
what are you doing get it what are you doing I can't just drag it into the
fucking ocean I need okay I need a smaller car wait no I don't I can do
with my body god damn it all right I need something small they have a bike
or something it's so close I just have to get it in there let me try it back
into it that's the way that's the strategy it's definitely the way to do
it bingo we got it someone look behind me they're gonna take off and it's gonna
be so awesome it'll be worth it where they're gonna just ride into the sunset
oh oh they're not dead they're fine mission success all right now go wait
hold on they're on the truck wait what's what he did all right go do it move you
guys are in the we are in the ocean go be free go be like just go to the ride
of the Sun do something what I killed that guy what's going on I don't care
get rid of it it's gonna the streams gonna do real like four hours what
oh shit start the mission start the mission shut I gotta start the mission
now it's quicker go go go go start the mission thought they were gonna drive
away come on you gotta give me like that what I gotta try right what do you want
I'm looking for a jet pilot Misha Misha's the jet pilot I am the jet pilot
you're the who's Misha I am the jet pilot is me Misha is me jet pilot I fly
jets you can fly jet yes I fly jets I fly any jet you got fly all over the
world any conditions don't matter got my and I fly a jet I really hope so
let's say you call me once you sober up I don't sober up you don't sober up not
if I can help it you see my jet you would not fly it sober wait as this guy
trying telling me that he's driving drunk in an airplane very bad
I drop bomb in the right place but is wrong place he tries to blame me guys
with big hats come but I show them show them wrong coordinates big heads get mad
at lieutenant he gets mad at me now I'm stuck here the lieutenant wants to kill
you oh yeah wants to kill me back but these Jamaicans are so crazy no one
messes with them I'm safe here you'd be safe with me that oh yeah would be a
great sub sound if I still had one
which where is this guy lieutenant is in bunker you know where the bunker is I
know where the bunker is right so you need a bunker buster I have no bunker
boss where I come in you you already came in I'm saying I'll get you a bunker
buster and I picked one of those up already and point the little laser
so I hit the target and we're in business I think I already got one you mean the
designator yeah it's too hard to hit target without it all right I help you
bomb this busy lieutenant back to the Stone Age and you'll be free to come
work for me yeah simple no that's yeah it's all Misha's problem by taking out
the lieutenant who is mad at him you'll need a bunker buster watch a letter
strikes an anaconda to anaconda's to piranha boats let's go I want to scream
it's so bad but I can't I don't have didn't say I needed to get a bunch of
other shit too all right well let's go the other shit is optional okay that
sounds like fun I'll do that bunker buster bunker buster fun feels amazing
man yeah all right what's gonna do is it gonna go straight ahead I wish you could
shoot so just drive but hey I mean you can't fault them there is a drivable
vehicles vehicle sounds a whack yeah they kind of are they'll whack all right
got to extract three of them do I have gas for this though my life 70 gas is
that enough I have to steal a gas thing it's gas right here but is there a gas
thing there's no gas thing to take I'm not sure I'm gonna be able to do this
mosquito that does kind of sound like a mosquito when they get really close to
and you have an extreme panic attack because for some reason you just think
that the mosquito is going to go into your ear and crawl into your brain it
starts sucking blood out of your brain and shit yeah no I want one of those so
bad wait this wasn't even close that's the next island it's this one here okay
laying eggs in your brain all right has there ever been a recorded case of a bug
laying eggs in somebody's brain has that ever happened or is that an irrational
fear that like Eli Roth made up has that actually happened look it up um I don't
think I want to look that up this does not sound something I want to see all
right let's get rid of these guys that's a big gun you know I want you to get on
it oh you don't want to get on it fine I'll get on it okay what is this 105
millimeter artillery rifle tank over here oh my god no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no give me give me give me I'm good we're good okay
now we just have to get up here and destroy all this shit not that but you
get the idea lateral damage that was easy anything else you need me to do wait
this gas over there too it was a very large explosion you can play destroy all
humans unfortunately no because I played the original destroy all humans right
before they announced that they were remaking the game but I'm one of those
guys all right this is it don't get into a fight around the bunker busters the
bunker busters are going to explode well don't bring the tank demon souls remake
you think that's going to get the tank don't shoot that buster don't shoot the
buster don't I gotta kill these guys right now
are you doing up here don't get it do not blow them up got it okay got stash one
I'm going I'm gonna go up okay it's too much to process the guy that just fell
trip to his death after being so ecstatic to go get the tank oh that's
where this is coming from okay oh my god who is hurting the alarm all right we
got that one more up here and that's it he's gonna get it is there anybody even
down here shit I need all right it's busy it's busy busy busy busy let's go
hurry up if that shit out of here I'll get it one day all right that's three or
three people the music's not that bad all right I have the bunker busters now
I can destroy the bunker airstrikes bunker buster how much does it cost
my bunker buster is 300 gas I don't have that I gotta get gas it's one right here
quick get in get in okay do I fly this wait I have a bomb I missed that's sad
I need what I gotta get gas man I can't have like a fun time look I need this is
the I have the bunker bus this guy I hear a lots of luck on you know I gotta
get up I need these whoa that guy's gonna die before he shoots my guy die
die die die die die die die that's all right I don't care get that just get the
gas oh go go go just go what's in the way nothing's in the way go nothing's
in the way why is it too heavy did you bring the wrong car you fucking idiot
he's good he's good he's good he's okay he's okay he's gonna make it he's gonna
make it come on make it he just bumped into like what are you doing fly this
thing here how did they hit each other in the air it's still fucking following
him did he get it nice he did all right why is he coming back here what are you
doing why excuse me okay I thought he was driving directly into me that was
bunker if but I have full gas all right now he's good art hillary's right our
till every strike times one what does it mean no no no no it's bunker buster
there it is how do I use it oh no oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god why why why why why why why what do I do I have to fight the
at the end the laser at this oh it's bad this is very bad I put this away okay I
can put it away right I can't put it away yeah why do you have to do this
shit right now okay what was going was what was the angle okay this is it ready
ready we're good we're up we're okay we're okay we're okay we're gonna we're
not gonna take any damage from the fall okay we're fine that was loud but that
was fucking ridiculous okay I just have the laser aim the laser aim the laser
bunker buster here we go this is a tank right here okay we're going the other
way but wait I need to heal yeah help okay here we go it's right there bunkers
right here okay eat shit give me the where's the fucking bunker buster dude
right there I gotta get out of here all right stop firing up here I'm in it I'm
inside of them stop firing stop firing I'm good yeah I told you guys I'm gonna
get it
okay I just remembered from the very beginning of the game when I drove the
bike like a thousand miles per hour into the gate he's making me laugh right
now always drunk I need drink he can barely stand but need to stand to fly
jet we can buy anything we can buy a steel that's important and I need a jet
pilot to deliver ordinance all right I trust you where did you find these guys
they're cute you worry too much class they're cheap okay so what does he do
for me now wasted what he just died on the couch he had like a heart attack
oh hey boss just hang a night you know waiting for your call always at the
ready you find more bunker busters he can drop them for you oh that's awesome
hi where is he am I going the right way oh wake him up is he like what I mean
the bedroom there are a lot of bombs in this it feels like they are you're
pretending what where is he not this guy he said he was up here so okay well
what the fuck are you doing over here you can get a literal nuke how do I get
this okay when do I get new clothes cheat codes cheat codes cheat codes
hold on Jennifer has a catapult really need to complete challenges so what is
the next job what do we what's the goal here somebody have a new mission here
challenge destruction race it's just a bunch of challenges do the Moab cheat
it's the up logo yeah all right let's go here you'll it's gonna be New Vegas how
do you put the cheats in is it some weird thing at the menu or something in
the an I&I file or something I don't know come pick me up cheats don't work
on PC okay let's do this that'd be really why not all right let's go into
the up he missed he missed really this guy's a sniper rifle I'm just gonna get
it that dude has a huge rifle look at this thing why is there a sniper up here
how do these I how do they even get up here though all right let's go level the
up building that's pretty clever how far away is this part of the building
does he know he can destroy skyscrapers yet no just found that out right now by
you I don't care though what if I don't care no no this is not what I want go
and do the next mission blow the building up nice try holy shit he shot
into the camera how can you be better with a rocket launcher than I am with a
sniper rifle I don't get it jump scare this is a friendly tank right here though
there's a 3d movie okay if you take if you make that a little bit red and then
you make another one copy it right next to each other make it a little bit blue
and then you like in Photoshop or something you move it close together so
it's that stereoscopic 3d right somebody will do it this could be the most
roundabout way to go in the front door that I've ever seen in my fucking entire
life let me in I'm ready for my next job
press LB RB RB LB LB LB LB LB of cheat mode respect a hold on for real new
contact well you can afford me let's not waste time we need to help universe
patrol and take over an outpost in Altagracia once the outpost is secure the
up will set up their own operations 300,000 a tank a raven and upgrade I'm
in count your blessings act active X but you PDA during gameplay if you like the
motorcycles in this you need to get the Panzer cycle what is it LB RB RB LB RB
LB RB LB LB LB somebody's got it right I'm not gonna use it very much I don't
think that word LB what is it LB LB RB RB LB RB LB LB LB LB LB LB is bullshit
nevermind strike team wait I get a bunch of soldiers in this one okay that's
cool strike team we're gonna go in we're gonna it's gonna be so much fun that's
right they hit the music this is like the trumpets means we're going let's go oh
no no no that means when we get there I'm gonna take a tank though how far away
is this not that far but I can't I have to just swim over there don't I are you
holding a sniper rifle as a pistol all in the strike team not until we go it
says wait till we get close it's not I said I'm gonna just drop in the water
wait I thought I thought I said I couldn't do that they actually drop
that's gonna see what does let's go Wow I have my own team this is awesome this
just became so much more fun okay can you guys swim please say yes or no it's
like I'm so excited with a little kid so excited oh my god my friends are over
for my birthday and there's a slippage slide it's a fun pool I can't even yeah
they follow me right and then they go you start ballin you guys coming why
they're not coming anymore that was not the worst noise of 2020 please okay well
I don't know who cares about the strike team they don't move I have like five of
them that was a medium worse noise you have a gauge that tells you what how bad
or good a noise is yes you do okay well there is criteria I'm almost there easy
bake oven scream was the worst we mean easy bake oven scream how many can I
have three six nine am I gonna like ten people wait wait guys wait wait wait
don't go in yet stay how do I say stop stop he's just gonna die he's gonna go
in and die all right let's go strike team we want more I need more crew don't
fire hold your fire I'm doing the command and conquer bullshit where I'm
sitting on the coast where he does not know where the fuck I am in an
unexplored area of the map too many soldiers let's go move up move up move
up let's go all right wait wait can we fill a pickup truck can they get in the
back of the pickup truck all right everybody in okay hold on wait first of
all that guy there's like ten people in the passenger side I gotta drive him in
this is the goal I'm gonna drive him in don't slow down because if I slow down I
can't even tell you what's happened I'd like I yeeted that guy across the whole
game and then ten people got in okay wait wait wait wait wait wait
collateral damage somebody die in the front seat there we go okay where's the
front door we're gonna dump everybody in the front door okay let's get in boys
here we go all right take it my lemmings you wanted to drive okay we're good get
back in it get back in get back in everybody in get in get in get in get
in they're all dead like hell they're all dead oh shit my safe in here clown
car subs ten community subs from subpar rump here catjacket ten subs thanks
guys all right we're gonna take the other one you need a supply drop I have
one go to the shop how my ears life is pain he's no they're still here look
for it on your radar who's really shooting at David yep let me hear this
sound I mean that wasn't even that bad this would be yelling into a shitty
microphone okay do I get to do I'm so happy I can just do this whenever I want
all right let's get everybody in a pickup truck again it's that pallbearer
yeah I'm like that it's only a matter of time before Solano makes us an offer
the enemy is here okay we're all gonna fit in we're gonna get into this thing
the enemy is here I mean too many soldiers in the area freaking feces
one of these shoes plus more than you can imagine I think these guys have been
glitched since the very beginning of the game I'm pretty certain of that I
wait I can do I can take a helicopter right it's not it's not a grenade it's
not a grenade it's not a grenade it's not a grenade it's not a grenade all
right where to boss right here you're aiming a sniper rifle at an innocent
person no I wasn't I was just using him as binoculars to see what was going on
around me we're good I've made a car and I want a strike team it's just added
another like an hour of content to the game for me strike team in the sedan
what you I can't I have to pay attention I can't even read that
was a direct hit that was loud too all right here we go you guys ready let's
get the strike team here I want what 12 you cut that shit out right now wait
let's get him in the truck again feel like I'm gonna make a mess here
easy easy easy easy fellas no no no no no no stay stay stay well okay you're
smart stop don't go up there no you gotta get in the why did you go over
here it's only one guy in here get in get in get in get in all right dude
you and me whatever here we go get in the other gunner seat get in the gunner
seat in the gunner seat all right I'm all right I'm okay I'm all right are you
all right where are you where is he I want the sniper rifle what that's what
shirt he's playing on easy there's no such thing as easy there is only game
I think I just have to stand next to it don't I yeah I just have to go like this
oh shit strike team all right I'm right there with the checkpoint you healed for
two while flying through the air what I just do I didn't no no no no no no no
I didn't want to do I was trying to get it again all right so the goal is you
okay here's what you have to do you got to get your guys don't just drop them
and then go in you have to drop them in the front how do you feel about Kim
admitting to being a paid actress well the German 985 wonder how long that
username is going to last well I mean how am I supposed to feel like don't
act like it on Twitter where you didn't get to be your name so you just put the
in front of it so now you're the real one nope I gotta fly I gotta fly let's
fly whatever is Kim a paid actress no if you don't stop saying that I'm gonna
flip out you don't stop you guys don't stop saying that I'm gonna flip out
sure I'll drop you off it's what you pay me to think keep saying it don't say
that you're gonna make me flip out why are you shooting a rocket launcher in
your own base it almost looks like he accidentally turned that on all right
enough it's time so you don't pay her no you gotta make me flip out hey are they
making me flip out I say this like I get the guy I know you guys just want me to
come in here and just flip out you know it's not gonna happen man I wonder how
many strike teams we can get on here oh I can't wait to fly into the strike
team I can't wait to go like this with a strike team best friend he's a psycho
flipping out okay let's go over here I'm ready so right here up on the top of
this island strike team go they're all still here and only have one can he
shoot don't get it yeah you got okay okay I'm gonna wait eventually this guy
is gonna make his weight all the way around and I need people destroy the wall
destroy the wall okay why is this guy have an indicator what is that friendly
what holy shit dude all right you can relax I need another bike the alive
where did he go around the edge where is this guy I need more strike team fuck
this shit all right go go go go go go go go go on go on go on get out all right
attack what are you doing all right the two of you we're gonna wait for four
wait just wait for everyone to get here don't go out there you fucking idiot why
don't I have a button that I can press that just says like no stay back these
people are so dumb don't just run in throw grenade take out the towers why
is that guy still allowed to be right there use an airstrike I don't know I
don't have enough to do it I missed I missed I missed I missed do we have
any more all right we're good we're good this guy alive on the ground what are they
shooting at what hostile gun spotted hostile gun that's fucking funny all
right get in I want everybody get him one look at this wait he's driving it I
think he's dead nope he's trying to figure out a way out we're good we get
CPU pilot right now let's go man come on you can do it he just killed everybody
you ran over all of our teammates all right let's go you got it I don't know I
feel like I feel like they're like why are you in this window that makes no
sense going what car fucking just man the missiles house give me it give me
give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me
give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me come on I need
one more one more shot one more shot okay what was in me what was even in
there was there anything even in there hey God heal I'm trying to not die you're
hitting me in the back oh shit somebody get in search for you on Amazon why no
don't don't don't don't I what am I here hold on give me one sec one second okay
I'm good don't don't don't well it's okay well somebody took my whatever
what am I gonna do well go then in the car we need one more guy in here get in
here get in one more one more don't forgo go go go go go go good good good
good good good band my band that's my career name well you guys have to
understand even if there was stuff on the internet that had my like face on it
it's like okay get rid of that get that down okay see you tomorrow when I just
make a new account and just do it again at some point it's just like what am I
supposed to do make them official yeah all I can tell you is work hello where
those going didn't you just fire it in a straight line why is one of these guys
shooting at me you won't do it you're not gonna fucking do it
he actually did it holy shit I call this bluff so bad I gotta blow this up Jesus
I have no ammo how do I open this well what if you help me all right I'm just
fucking I'm going in the dump and see you need fuel to use airstrikes okay well
I'll go get some fuel make it quick time is money hey into the green zone or
Kavima's outpost shop whoo look at this okay fuel storage fuel storage ground
attack wipeout person on light vehicles multiple explosives air support attacks
enemy armor light tank a raven supply drop or an inflatable raven I already
have one of these you'll storage upgrade you're gonna both DMC fuel storage DC
fuel storage upgrade and that's way better okay how about an inflatable I
want it equipped on here it's a ground attack there's a lot of money wipeout
personnel light vehicles and multiple explosives and I guess I'll buy it tank
attack a mantis light tank I'm gonna get I gotta get some fuel let's get this one
too get the Raven okay supply drop I'll take five of them I okay cool I'll do it
as revenue do not say German I 85 in the mirror three times now don't don't do it
don't do it you up ground attack all right I want let's get some fuel so let
me ask you a question is this technically stealing if it's mine why am I how am I
stealing this I own it up owns it well why didn't I steal it before giving it
to them that was the brain big brain that I didn't do this is the last one okay
we're gonna I gotta fly over here fast travel please please do an Adam Sandler
impression okay let's do this so what you're gonna get that's it I'm not doing
anymore that's just you though it is not just me you can break most things
using c4 grenades are bad I have what 2c for my 5c for all right I will try to
destroy a big building that's directing Oh too many personnel right all right
let's get you I'm gonna pick up every bunch of people
you know mine please when you engineers want to get in there we go hey get a
passenger passenger side get in the car get in the car get in the car get in the
car inside the car in the holy shit this guy went crazy oh he flipped out yeah
the dude fucking flipped out guys at this fuel all right let's get about
let's deal a bunch of this field how do I not have a single bullet watch out you
use all the ammo and can't shoot I can't shoot this guy's still in the car no he
got out oh god that's bad watch out got it we're good all right let's go are
they're actually cheese for this by the way was that just a bullshit
Jesus oh I gotta have guys I gotta land dudes here I don't have any strike team
all right all right all right all right where that Sam happy birthday it's not
my birthday it's not my birthday okay then this really is just battlefield I'm
just sitting in the back just watching battlefield was the best game to eat
food because you could just sit there while a guy played the whole game I just
poke out the window every now and then just sit in a guy's tank or sitting a
guy's jet or something you just sit there it was awesome all right we got a
strike team okay I'm gonna I'm gonna steal some quick quick quick quick
quick quick before it gets destroyed I don't feel this great Jesus is there a
person here there is somebody right here all right give me give me give me before
they take it take the other one too I don't feel too community night that
might should be kind of fun all right let's get strike team how many more
to do I feel like I'm doing this like the last two years me that ammo battle
front to battle front to what the fuck hello where am I am I trying to shoot
this guy like he's a no don't let him right in in in in in in in in in in in
in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in in one more get in go go
Go go go go go go good good good anti-tank rogue air strike the storage
Okay, I have a question oh
Okay
Yeah, I was wondering why let's do a mission transit
We're trying this left bumper right bumper right bumper left bumper left bumper right bumper. It's hard to do that
Okay, there's more cheese is you're bad at the game. That's
Is that like an elite that that's like a cracked copy of the game
Don't want to download a cracked exe of the game any updates on the baseball stream. It has been postponed indefinitely
Until it is safer to do so it was going to be
like 40 people 50 people in the same spot
players crew
Other things it's not possible in this current environment
A lot of stuff has already been paid for so I have it ready
Whenever it becomes safe to do so
What about the webcam stream
Um I did I
Be honest I haven't put very much time into that yet because it's such a daunting task at the moment that it's in the back
of my mind every day
He bought 20 webcams for nothing
Oh, but I'm just gonna sit in my closet. I'm gonna use them eventually protect the executive. This is a million dollars
Okay, one million dollars
This is an escort mission well, I'm gonna teleport over
Give me um, I'm gonna play seaman 2 isn't seaman 2 in Japanese. I don't think I'll be able to do it
It is yeah, when are you gonna learn Japanese
Probably won't be able to learn a new language. I'm not gonna learn a new language
for one live stream
Find the executive
Kill attackers
You took a pottery class yet taking a pottery class is not the same as learning an entire language
How are they?
This guy's still alive
He's alive
Oh, he's up there everybody good
Showed up
Do you understand people would love you
I'm not gonna learn Japanese
So I have to get him out of here
Yeah, there's the drop-off bring executive to first sight
Okay, freaking
There a jet ski their boat. Oh, wait a minute
I have access to a boat
It's time to get in the dinghy. I've waited so long drop the dinghy here
Where did you?
Okay, let's see it. Are you ready for the radio life? Dude is gonna be awesome
You know, I thought about it at last second I'm like, you know what what if he dies
I didn't shoot him
Start gaslighting the fuck out of me into thinking that I I just shot him. All right, I'm gonna I want some time on the road
It didn't even it didn't even hurt all right
All right. I gotta I gotta fucking relax
Think I'm laughing at everything
Retreat funny man make a funny noise funny man make a funny noise. All right fine
There you go, okay fine
Funny her man make a funny noise
What they don't happen to my bike?
Don't do that only make noises. No
All right fine
There you're pressing the fucking like Nickelodeon funny machine
He's not dead
No, I get on this get on this
He's on
I
Been oh that's but don't can't it's because the mouse is on the screen. He might be broken though
So tempting just go wicked fast, but I can't this guy I can't kill this guy
Get in there
Bring executive to the first site
On the deck. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit shit shit shit shit
Comedian germa. I just see all the shit that was all flew all the way to the right with those bodies
That was kind of it was ridiculous. Look like straw. They didn't look like people
This is simple. Why can I not kill this guy? Oh
Quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick. I can't shoot in the middle of there. I can't shoot here
They have to take care of that fuck. Oh he got in
Somebody behind me
Get out of here, man. I have a bad feeling that this guy's gonna get in the way and I'm going to shoot this guy in
the head
That was friendly fire, yeah, it was unfortunately, I can't hear anything
Wait, they're more common
Get up here
Am I right bring executive bring executive
Come on, come on executive
You know like you know, I go like good good. Good. Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness
Yeah, get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. It's the checkpoint. Don't worry
I've been shot
I've been shot. Oh
Okay, no bike this time get on wait, can he drive will he drive the car? Oh
Really? That's really unfortunate. He won't get on the gun. We're good. They're approaching the way
I just we're gonna have to do return to objective. Aren't I on the way to the objective?
Thought I was on the way to the objective
Site two
Why am I doing that? They're all getting out of the back. Don't let them get out of the back. Oh
You're right
Everyone's alright
When am I going to play naughty bear?
I'm not going to play naughty bear
Nice whoop toss that good job
That was a lot of lag
from the east and west. Oh
Shit. Oh shit. Oh
The frame rate is so bad double tap
What else do I need to do? Oh
fuck
No, that was one of the guns
Yeah
Put on 30 FPS for that. Oh, I want to ride around with the executive
I want to get them to I have to win but how far is it? There's a I had a checkpoint, right?
I gotta put it on 30 FPS
Come on. It's gonna be right at that checkpoint
You need a better PC clearly if you can't play a poop game from 20 years ago. This is not a poop game
This is 2008 TF2 came out a year before this bingo. Let's get in an armored car, please
Nothing even loaded in this is perfect. What kind of Pentium do I have a?
Pentium
dual core Pentium 2
When that's all you needed and what are you gonna need in like 20 years? We're gonna be getting laughed at
years and years from now
Like six core eight core twelve core, that's crazy two CPUs and one motherboard that's insane
That shit will be in your brain
in like 50 years
Here we go. I just wait till they get out. There's really no sense in destroying the vehicles at all
It's just too much particle effects as it just ruins everything shoot the people good I would love to attack this guy
Let's get in the tank
East and west are I hold on now yet, but okay gotta move move move move move move move move move
All right West blanket blanket. Excuse me. You on the 50 cal what?
What oh shit that guy has a we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Is there an enemy over here?
I need it. I need a gun. I need a gun. I need a gun. I need a gun. I need a gun
Helicopters dropping off. I have a weapon for you. Wait for it on the roof. Why is this?
Health pack you can do better than that
Anti air kit. All right. What is it?
Anti-air missile that's to destroy. Okay, we're gonna lock on
Get out of here
Done anymore. I'm me in this shit. You missed that one. I want to do like a
Helicopter fight, but can I pick him up in this but that wasn't the building he was in right?
Can I pick this is so awkward to drive around him. I get it
I have to tell him to follow me. I follow follow follow follow follow, but is he piloting?
That's not an up building right
Okay, thank God it went over it dear lord that was so close
I
47 boys, yeah
It's like a bounty here
Where's this dude?
Where's this guy? Oh well destroy the building
Wish I had that missile. That'd be great. Just wait. Okay, see for wait
Wait, wait, wait see for on the building and then we get in and then I can detonate it, right?
Does that make sense finish the job first? Oh, right, right, right. You're right. Do the mission. Yeah, that's true
Dave helipads are for nerds
Helipads are for incredibly rich people. I mean you can be a nerd and be rich
But you got to be rich to have a helipad. That's just the way it is 2.4 mil
I'm taking my help. Look at I can I'm gonna go down there
Dave, okay. Yeah, so uh the next game we're gonna play
It's probably Desperados 3. I played Desperados 2 and I loved it
I made a video on it end of the stream voice. Not quite. No, not yet
But Desperados should be really fun. If if it's anything like Desperados 2 that was a lot of fun as well
UPHQ is in the northern part of the city. How high can I go?
Finish LA Noire
Three years ago
But just finish it
Okay, I want you guys just we'll take bets
Do you think from the highest point in a helicopter is falling onto the ground is gonna kill me?
If it does stream is over if it doesn't and I'll do the mission
We want Naughty Bear
You don't want Naughty Bear
What's that? Am I being swarmed right now by other aircraft?
This is really far away shit
All the way at the top of the mountain
People who want Naughty Bear are the same people who want Ratatouille
They've wanted for the memes for like three minutes and then they leave when he actually plays the game
Yep
Sounds about right to me. All right, here we go
Does this kill me? Yes or no, we'll find out. Here we go. And then they come back
Four hours later and they go. Holy shit. He's still playing this game
Yeah, that was the plan. Here we go
We're good. We got to do the mission now
You need help with something ooh, okay river outpost wait, here's a shop scout
Ooh
transport
Sure, I'll just take one
Why not? Sure
Rifle grenades and ammunition. All right, we need to
Sure do it who gives a crap. Hey who gives a crap anyway, this is just
Good it's like a buddy
This
Where this is
Here it is. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. We're here. We're here. We're here here here here here
You're me you should play mercenaries to ban that guy for two minutes down here. I got our wheels back. Oh, you're gone
Whatever get on somebody get on I want a friend my bike. There you go. Nice. He's dead
He died bullshit
Use the guerrilla commanders. Wait, this is the same mission from the before is different people
There any difference at all?
John himself, that's ours
Oh shit, we need one more guy
One more you got it. All right, it's there
Is there anything else to do?
Is there an ownership should we end it? I mean, I had a lot of fun. This was fun
Like about five or six hours
Cheat now. Is it actual cheats? Are you guys actually making that up?
Hold the L&R and then do start up a left a I don't like that's I went by too fast
X-ray cheats old L&R and do start up a
Left. Haha. Yeah, that's funny
almost close no
Oh LB up a a again quit game that yeah, that would have been great. Um
guys
Why did you do that?
That's a friendly. How do you even time that missile to land on me like that? That was fucking crazy
All right, let's I want to blow up. Let's let's get a building. I need to try that
Cheats cheats cheats. I don't think this is real. Let's let me say games radar
Okay, he's up up
Nuclear Bunker Buster. Hold on a second. All right PDA map screen
Up up down down left right left right up up down down left right left right on the at the PDA screen during gameplay
PDA map screen votes are available after the October 31st 2008 online update is applied
Do I have that? Okay, I?
Enabled cheats first
PC doesn't have updates. Oh
I mean, this is on games radar
one
Enable cheats first. Yeah, that's what I just tried the copter delivered one pilot hoofing it back to the villa
Yeah, yeah, when I press go online, it's that I couldn't connect to the servers. They don't exist anymore
You have to highlight the PMC first
That's not that's a that you made that up
Right bumper right bumper left over right over left over left over left over right bumper right bumper right bumper left bumper
Alright, what's a cool skyscraper?
Okay, wait, why is I'm gonna kill somebody or capture in here?
What wasn't I just working with these guys?
How am I still alive?
You're a mercenary. It's not no it doesn't work all cheats
LBRB RB LB RB LB LB RB RB RB RB LB and then hit the back button again. That's back
All right, LB RB RB LB RB LB RB RB RB RB RB RB back. I'm not a trainer. No, that's it
I'm out of here. There's a tutorial here. Okay, if this is a screamer or if there's a gnome or a rick roll
The stream is turning off. I'll allow this
Don't they sing there it comes do the bark man
Why did you give this to me is now I have to listen to the whole fucking thing real tutorial
Oh, if you body if you can do the part, I forgot the songs awesome
He was lying in the street how
Do you always sound like this 30 years ago
Remember the voice actors that does Bart is like 75 years old. He was like 30
She was doing Bart for the first time I
Said she all right. This is the end of the scream. I'm done. I'm done. This is fun, though
Here's the real tutorial real real real, please last time Larry last time Larry last time. I try to help you. Okay, oh
And it's a good one too. I'll give you one second
Yeah, that's the last time I click on a link from you Larry
Real tutorial, okay. This one is this is watch this now. I swear to god of a muselk video place
like I
Good grammar and spelling are important. But if you want to write essays that inspire
messages that forge brighter connections and
emails that
Get the job. All right
Here's the other me to tell you something about like grammarly, right?
We are just teaching people that they can just mash their keyboards, you know, you have to know how to spell anything
You don't even have to know when to do periods commas exclamation points never, you know, who cares
Eventually, we're gonna start you can start writing emotes and Grammarly is gonna write your essay for you
It's gonna be like German old German rats
Mugga ash Omega lol and it's gonna write is a fucking story for you. I don't fit the
What is that? I've played this game before it's terrible. It's just not it's so bad
What do you want? I that's not it. What do you walk around you like to attack? I it's not good
Although I didn't play the remakes
Hey guys, I deleted the browser source and I can't stop it
Isn't that interesting?
It's off. It's not here anymore. I cannot control it
Like I deleted it from the source. I
Don't know why it's still playing. It's not even here anymore
What do I do?
It's not on the screen. It's not even in my Grammarly does more than you Grammarly
It's the GTA radio
I know some of you guys think this is a joke or something. Oh, what a funny like bit he's doing
I've removed it from it's not up here. There's no capture source. It's not here
This is gonna knock this is gonna happen it until I hit the X on OBS
Because the better we all communicate the better we connect yeah, you have to prove it
Grammarly
Helping close the window
The window there is no window and download today. I don't have a window
Wait, I think I found it. Hold on. I got it. I got it. What are you linking me?
Yeah, I you know how times I've seen this image of me shibby and it's Alex and somebody writes something fucked up on my shirt
You either make me like five inches shorter put like a big pee stain on my pants. That was really nice
Look at like the oily pee pee stain. I remember that one. That was funny
Alright, I'm done. I'm I'll see you later. I'll see you later. That's it
I had a lot of fun, but I think it's time into the stream boys. Yeah
No stream tomorrow, by the way, I have doctor's stuff to do. I will not be around tomorrow
But I will be around Wednesday and Thursday
Wednesday and Thursday is probably gonna be Desperado's 3
That's gonna do custom robo as well
So Wednesday will be Desperado's 3 and then if the game sucks and game sucks will do something else
Eternal darkness I also have but that'll probably be October. Am I gonna finish mercenaries?
Probably not
Although this is this could be one of those now probably not. I think I've seen everything I wanted to see
What time PST on Wednesday probably around same time today?
fucking jump
Probably same time today around like 10 o'clock and 30 started 11 today because of the ps3 problems, but several like 1030
Am Pacific he's gonna run over by the boat. Wait, he's alive. I
Can't shoot through this glass
Well, I can't end the stream I can't stop I'm trying to stop
All right, I gotta go. I'm gone. I'm officially gone. See you later. This character is invincible
I can't stop playing. All right, I guess I'm gonna hit the button. Am I sad? No, what?
My sad
Why would I be sad? All right. I'll see you guys Wednesday. Take your buddy. Let's go
I got I got a pull it I got a pull the plug pull and plug but done
Hey, look at that plug has been pulled. That was fun
I just I couldn't stop but there was mercenaries to but exactly when I wanted out of this game and it is exactly what
I thought it was going to be I'll see you Wednesday
Thank you to all the community subs by the way speaking. I want to make sure I make this really clear. There is
No multi month sub that you need for FTK
The server is apparently going to be able to handle over the course of I believe it's six or seven different servers
Connected together somewhere around a thousand people
Now the people that can actually play in like the main game is somewhere around like two or three hundred maybe four hundred
Well, we made it differently this time when I say we I mean they
Where there's gonna be a lot of different like hub worlds connected for a queue system
So it's not just like the server gets fucking diarrhea don in
Ten seconds and there's 400 people and then the whole thing crashes
Top sub gifters to another this top sub gifter hasn't worked since I implemented this in stream labs OBS. It's just there
It's just those guys. It's a slug every time. It's the rich money guy in the middle and it's like the the metamorphosizing
Alien squid on the right. It's always these people every time what day you can do custom robo either Thursday or
Monday depends on how long desperado's is if I have fun in it, but let's run the credits
Hopefully this works because I'm testing a theory here. The theory is do I have to be on?
The stream labs page for it to work. Let's test it ready
Yep, the stream labs page has to be open and on my screen the whole time
That's new that I didn't need to do that before
Those are these I stopped streaming for two months and all these windows update makes a bunch of shitty updates gonna be one person
Stop using stream labs, you know, I wish I could but I've been so used to it for so long that
I don't want to relearn another system. Hey one guy nice job
Thanks for the subs everybody. I'm sorry you did I my theory is correct
Actually one guy his channel is dying sad face
During's been rough lately. No, we're good. Everything's fine. That could be one person and it would be alright. Don't worry
Have you seen totally accurate battlegrounds? Uh, I have I wanted to play it a long time ago, but if I was like
It's early access, right? Why is he so sad? No, no, no, no, no, no. No, stop. Stop it
You cut this out right now
But you're all gonna be in big trouble a lot of players recently. Maybe I'd play it. Alright guys, I'll see you Wednesday
Have a great rest of your night
Let's do a raid
If we're not ready in a long time
I want to try I want to try to cycle people like people that we haven't rated in a very well
We haven't rated or we haven't read in a very long time
Who's online at the moment? Let's take a look seeing a bunch of names
You know, let's let's write Kraken. It's been a long time since we've rated Kraken
In a while since I've talked to Kraken to it's been a few months
See how he's doing was he playing outward? Oh Kraken. I said hello
Enjoy yourselves if you feel like sticking around on a Kraken stream then go for it. If not, and we'll see you Wednesday
Are you gonna ever use channel points again? Yes
Eventually, there will be something else to do. I promise. All right. I see you guys later. See you Wednesday
Have a great rest of your
Next day or two. See you Wednesday for Desperado's 3 now get out of here scram. I think I spelled his name wrong
I didn't all right. Take care guys. See you soon