Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Borderlands 2.
This game just came out last night in North America at least. We actually had a conversation with Boo about how he couldn't join our game because it's not out in Europe yet.
But if you're watching this a few days from now, it is probably out in Europe and this is totally irrelevant.
But there's three of us on the screen here, me, Stealth, and Italics. Boo will be joining us shortly, like I said in the next coming couple days.
But I want to make this video, just want to introduce this for a second or two because I do not think I'm going to be doing a full let's play of this game.
What you can't expect to see content-wise for Borderlands 2 is along the lines of this video.
This video is going to be broken up into a bunch of just highlights. Maybe two or three minutes here, two or three minutes there, just some funny things that happened or crazy boss fights or something like that.
I'm just going to be constantly recording this game. So anything that I come across will be uploaded to this channel.
So I'm not sure how many videos it's going to end up being in the end, but expect at least a few of them.
So that's going to wrap it up. Just wanted to introduce this guys and enjoy the live commentary and take care everybody.
Oh, you're not going to have any health and no weapons. That's great.
It looks like there's the Hyperion ship in the distance.
Where is it? Over there.
Imagine if it just exploded. If it just exploded. That would be amazing.
I love the reload animation for this sniper. Right? Oh, geez. Yeah. It's like a revolver sniper.
I still don't have a weapon.
I found the collectible. I found money.
Oh, wait. Yeah. That's something we do like look around for money and stuff. That's one thing.
Is this what did the claptrap just die?
Oh, no, that's a different one. Look at it. It's like there's like a dead claptrap corpse right here. I thought he'd like just passed out.
All the claptrap are dead.
I do much better with low sensitivity in these games.
Use mouse one to fire. Use mouse two.
Can I say that I love the ice like part of this game? It's great.
It looks really cool already. It looks great.
Yeah, you can hold E to pick up like everything around you.
Oh, thanks for the tip. What did she just say? I'm assuming it's not important.
Retrieve claptrap's eye is what we've got to do.
Oh, up top.
This guy's terrible.
This pistol is the worst gun in the game.
I didn't hit one person, by the way. Good job, guys.
Yeah, I didn't hit one bullet on anyone.
Good job, guys.
Hold on.
What is this personal item?
There's monsters, by the way.
Monsters. Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey, everybody.
Oh, critical hit, baby. Critical hit, baby.
Oh, this pistol. Why do you guys get real weapons?
That's the big one.
Is there bullet travel time in this game?
Oh, critical.
I don't remember there being like travel time with bullets in the other one.
Maybe I'm just crazy.
Claptrap, come on, get out of there.
Get down there. Get down there.
Oh, handsome Jack.
This claptrap has no idea what's going on.
Run.
Handsome Jack.
I don't think handsome Jack's that handsome.
Oh, health stuff.
I would say something, but I'm not going to.
How do you use the health injector again?
The person who thinks they're so handsome.
All I said was, handsome Jack.
Oh, God.
What's with the pendant on his neck?
I can't read that. Holy cow.
Knuckle. What did that even say?
I think that was Knuckle Dragon.
Let's get the Knuckle Dragon.
Bye.
Shoot him in the face.
Why is he chasing me?
Go after italics.
Only go after italics.
He's looking at me funny.
He's walking towards you while looking at me.
This gun is so inaccurate.
There's so much recoil on this thing.
It's un-aimable.
Sniper, nice crit right there.
They're coming out of the walls.
Does everyone else have a sniper?
No, I have a pistol.
Punch in the face.
Give me all this stuff.
Why are they all chasing me?
This sniper rifle is way better.
He's back down on the ground.
He's throwing snowballs at him.
Say goodnight, baby.
Give me everything.
Hold on every button.
I just got a pistol.
I didn't pick up one single thing.
I picked up one thing of money.
What happened to my sniper rifle?
The sniper rifle just disappeared.
It's still here.
Does anyone have anything that they want to give?
Can I just throw this on the ground?
How do I throw this sniper rifle on the ground?
I want you to have it.
You're the sneaky guy, right?
That's what you're supposed to have, isn't it?
It's all this stuff.
Make sure you open up every single compartment.
That's how we get money.
We're on Chapter 2, apparently.
I don't really know what that means.
I think we have to touch this button.
Travel canceled. Italics is in a menu.
Come on.
Get out of the menu.
You're so short.
I told you to get out of the menu.
There's a lot of stuff down there.
Be careful.
Oh, hey.
We don't take fall damage.
Do you hear that?
There's something shiny down here.
I must find it.
This thing does some mad damage.
It's shiny.
Get a shot, baby.
Unlocks the skin for the catch-a-ride system.
Italics, are you playing?
Why is it like a Warcraft character in the top right right now?
I told you.
I found something shiny.
Who invited the Diablo 3 character?
I saw a shiny thing and I went to go pick it up.
We're going to defend him.
We're going to defend Claptrap.
From World of Warcraft character?
That was like a Tier 1 Warlock set.
They're on the other side.
How do we get over there?
Jump over on the left.
Bogey on your left.
Got him.
I take my berserker tips from Burger Boy.
Run straight at him.
Get shot in the face.
They're here.
There's a dog somewhere on the map.
The train station?
Punch.
How did I miss with that?
I shot him right in his face.
He went BRB?
Did we do it?
There's one more guy over there.
We did it. We're good.
I did it.
We all did it, man.
Everyone except for you.
Which is only me.