Hey, good afternoon. Ah, it's it's evening. Never mind. Yeah, I'm here. It's really late. Yeah, it is
It ain't no time like the present to play Elden Ring
Elden Ring. Yeah, I uh, we streamed yesterday
When I say we I mean me
At the end of that stream. I said that Tuesday is what you probably could expect
but
Uh, I want I'm I want to go now. So we're doing it now
So we're very very early
Because i'm supposed to stream tomorrow, but i'm like, you know what? No streaming tonight
So it was very very early to tomorrow's stream
But this is a very late stream
starting at like 7 15
pacific
so I i'll tell you
I am
Makes sense if you're like, you know what dude? I don't know if I mean
I'm okay. I could probably be here for like an hour or two
That's all right. I don't okay. I don't think this is gonna be like a 10 hour stream
I'm just playing i'm just gonna jump in we're gonna play we're gonna hang out
Get some more progress done in the volcano manner
And look after four or five hours, let's figure it out. Whatever
You guys are all addicted. That's why you're here
Hey, well, you know
That's whatever if the game's fun and there's a bunch of people think it's fun
400,000 concurrent people still playing the game by the way
We're all here. So let's just hang out
Is this the guy that says Aaron?
well
It used to be kind of moved on from those kind of that kind of material
Moved on to an elden ring streamer
uh, so you're probably gonna get some elden ring kind of references and
I would appreciate it if those of you that are here now can say things instead of like aaron
You know like praise the sun and not maiden lists and you know that kind of thing
I changed my brand a little here
I would appreciate it. Nobody said like, you know, nobody said aaron anymore. We're trying to move on to other things
We're gonna move on to elden ring stuff
Aaron ring
All right. We're in the volcano manor. I do I really need an intro
We just I stopped streaming like less than 24 hours ago. So let's just keep going
What about doi doi doi? No, that's not that's not what we're doing anymore
please
I don't even know what that mean. I don't know how
I don't know how to do it
Just sit here for 20 more minutes talking about your old noises
You know how weird that is to think about? Oh man like
Those old jokes. Oh those jokes from you know years past those noises
They're not they're not even jokes, right? Like a lot of my old material
sound effects
the sound effects
Oh that classic germa 985 joke
Oh germa 985 was is a comedian. Yeah classic comedian
What's some of his material?
Oh, man, he's got this amazing routine
Where he sits there and are you ready? It's it's insane. He sit so he's sitting there and he goes
Yeah
Yeah, that's it. Does he do anything else?
Well, I mean his old stuff was like it's I mean, it's all right, but he did a dollhouse
Uh, he just did the dollhouse. He's got baseball coming up. But um, yeah, he used to make like noises
All right, man
So you're saying you're saying I should start watching the material from like 2017 and onward
Nah, maybe a little bit later
Maybe like 2018 2019 is when he stopped doing noises for content, but he still does it
Anyways, I like those noises and i'm gonna stick to them
Where we were we were here. Those noises were from like a month ago
You watch from spi nest onwards, right? Yeah
You do yoga. I can't do yoga. I can't my body physically can't move that way
You should respect the character. This character has been incredible
Respect the character
Respect the character. This character is amazing
All right. So last thing we did
All right. So last thing we did we we uh killed the boss that was in this room
I think there's a way I can go over here. Maybe
What is this? This is really late. Yeah, this is late night stream
I'm doing a late night at least maybe I don't know after like three or four hours
I just want to play and i'm not gonna play without you
Unless I do limb grave and i'm not doing limb grave another day
um
You know, I thought about oh man, like maybe i'll just go tomorrow and i'll do limb grave again today on my own on another guy
No
I stepped on this before the stream started so I think no it's here
Sorry played without you for 10 seconds before the stream started. Sorry. Sorry about that
We need a me strong stream
Maybe all right. Let's go. I this game. I love it. Let's go
a lot of candles
You know a thing next to the piano
the piano like object
Was that a good villain here? I just calmed it back
nothing over here
Resident sleeper. It's been the streamers been off for fucking five minutes
You know what? That's so funny. Like
You guys don't have any idea how much power you really hold
Like oh i'm just i'm just a i'm just a random viewer in a sea of people you have you hold a lot of power over
The people that are streaming
I'm telling you right now when a streamer looks over and sees resident sleeper
They have an internal panic attack
But they're like what's happening this person? Why is this person think my stream sucks? My stream's boring. Why what happened?
I need to do something. I gotta do something now. I gotta wake that person up. I gotta make like a joke
I gotta do something you hold a lot of power, but i'm gonna choose to ignore you. All right
This is what what is this like wacky?
Twisting hallway thing. Am I just walking in circles? There's nothing here
How can there be no items here?
None at all zero across this there's got to be a secret wall, right?
You gotta go back to your old your old material man
Ooh
All right, I can go that way. Yeah, dude. Your old material was way better
Wasn't there another way I could go? Hold on
Can I seriously isn't nothing here?
That feels impossible. But whatever
These are really romantic candles
No, it probably stinks up here
Uh, yeah, boss. I filled the room with the red candles like you wanted
gerry
You fucking idiot
Did you have to get the red cinnamon apple candle from yankee candle and put it in every room
We have to we're gonna have to fucking open the windows and not come back here for like a week
Which by the way, that's one of the most powerful. That's one of the most powerful of all the candles and I hate them
I I swear to god I can tell
I can tell when a neighbor lights one of those candles
It drives me crazy
Is that like cinnamon? It's like the fall cinnamon cider apple one. It's just like no
Yeah, I like it for like a second, but
I don't want to fill my whole neighborhood with that
wait
Take it to jump in the lava
What's my death count out right now?
What is it? I I don't what is it even at?
My under 500 deaths. I didn't even say it went too fast
How many deaths are there?
I don't have 700 deaths. No, I don't
Does anybody
Know how many times I died in securo or dark soul 3? All right, well i'm going down here
In here, I think I I don't think I died more than like 150 times in dark souls 3. It was like 200
Have I been in here?
Well shit, I guess not
Okay. Well
Go on here. How many was securo?
What the what the fuck? I was over there. Shit. All right, never mind
All right. I'm going back up. I'm going I walked in a circle
I locked in I literally walked in a circle
I can't well, here's the thing. This game is also like five times as long as all the souls games
So I that makes sense
Okay. All right. Let's go. Let's go up that way. There's nothing over there. I guess I can drop
I don't know why you would want to drop down there
That's a that's a big run
So I did look up
Yeah. Yeah, he's using a guide. No, this is beautiful though
I love that
You guys have just put on youtube videos of like that weird gooey lava just like falling down and somebody like hitting it with a stick
I want to do that
Like I wonder like where you do that like I want those videos of the people like oh and here's you take a look
And it's like really slow moving gooey like almost like cookie batter
and they like knock it with a stick and it's like goopy and it like breaks up and
I would do that for like three or four hours and that would be a vacation like that
That's what I wanted to do on vacation
I wouldn't care about anything else
You'd fall in i'm not gonna I wouldn't fall in the lava. It moves at like 0.2 miles per hour
I'm not gonna fall in the lava
Why would that happen?
Yes, you would no, I would not fall in the lava. Why do you guys think okay?
Why do you guys think that I like need to ride a bicycle with training wheels on it still?
You know, but like no, I see how so I was riding my bike yesterday
Oh, yeah, he has to have training wheels on he's he's he's brainless
No, I could ride a bike normally. I i'm not gonna fall into lava
I'm not what am I just gonna sit there and stare at it and just like lean forward until I face first like put
My face in the cake
That's what are you talking about?
Yeah, i'm gonna ride on my training wheels tricycle just into the lava and fall forward
This is so cool
I would go on vacation here
That would be the ultimate fall joke. I would wouldn't that would be awful
Do they make like
They gotta make like candy that's like this, right?
Is it like a and I don't want the lava candy that's like cinnamon red cinnamon apple bullshit
Okay, let me be very clear about that. They make like lava candy and it's red cinnamon bullshit
Why does everything no, I don't all right. This looks I don't like this
This looks like a boss place
Cinnamon's good
I you know, I have not jumped onto the cinnamon train. I'm sorry
I really kind of don't like it. It just overpowers everything that it touches
Oh, you want a latte? Yeah, sure. I'll take it. No, no, no, please
Can I just only taste cinnamon put like sprinkle one little ounce of oh my god
If you get anything with cinnamon on it, it's just a cinnamon thing. It doesn't taste like the thing you have
All right. Stop fucking complaining. Stop talking to me
I don't want to fight this fucking thing because like it is a million health
Will it burn?
I gotta put on fire resist
What the fuck cinnamon bros no cinnamon is
It's oh, it's too much
I appreciate cinnamons, you know that what what it's doing. I don't what i'm why am I acting like cinnamon is
like alive
I appreciate what cinnamon's going for but i'm not really into it that much like what are you talking about?
I get out of my way. I'm going to the building
Okay, you go through walls fix your fucking broken game
It's been a problem for a decade fix it people can shoot hit through walls fix your broken game
Okay, so this was where is this?
What was that?
It was it was you what the fuck I was terrified
Because the capcom rant no
All right. So this is
It's a bonfire up here, right?
Isn't there because that's a shortcut to isn't there a bonfire like right here?
He's god but you're not like cinnamon rolls. I just I it's too much for me. It's just like it's too much
Anytime I have cinnamon, I always have the same like
Reaction to it. All right, so this is where that was
so
Okay
We go from here. I just want to get this burn in my brain. All right, so from this bonfire we go up
shortcut achieved
You have children taste child taste
Wait, go back down. He has one taste bud
some of you like some of you cinnamon andes seriously are like
Really? Like you don't care that much about cinnamon, right?
Okay
That's where it is i've been hearing this for the last like three in-game hours
What is it? Oh somber spinning stone. I can probably make that just run across right?
I have you what?
flabbergasted you're using cinnamon as a bit
don't
I don't like cinnamon. So that is this is like a like a comedy routine
Okay, wait a minute
If I had a microphone in my hand and there was a slight echo
I guess you I guess that play that whole okay
Play that whole thing back the entire thing that I said about like cinnamons and like red apple and stuff
Add a little bit of an echo and like a little bit of a mic effect and an audience laughing every like
10 to 15 seconds
If it probably would be like a comedy routine
Oh god
Still don't understand why the cinnamon challenge was
Even
Yeah, I forgot about that people would just like take a bunch of cinnamon and go like
Yeah, like spit it out. I forgot about that
That was a thing for a long time
I don't want this guy's gonna kill me
I'm sorry that I mentioned the candles
I was observing it too
please next joke
You go to a stand-up routine the whole like
10 minute open mic night is the guy just talking about like red cinnamon
Cinnamon red cinnamon. Yeah, it's gross. Remember the cinnamon videos people used to eat cinnamon. Yes, it sucks by the way
All right, that's my time. I'll see you guys later
I'm gonna look out for the lava. Holy fucking shit this lava here
I didn't even see it
What the fuck dude?
Thank you
No, seriously like thanks man. Like I
What the fuck it's it is everywhere it's like everywhere
All right. Well, that was cool. I got a uh
somber
You know
Just wait, can I keep going?
You're inside of a volcano right now
All right. If i'm from software i'm putting
How come you don't take fire damage? Where did this guy even come from?
Cinnamon is great 78 percent
Am I really that people really that in the uh,
You guys like cinnamon that much?
All right, let me go this way I could walk around the other way, which I think I might
Yes. Yes cinnamon slaps
Okay, I want you to do me a favor
uh
Name me something that cinnamon
Is good on
That's not a pie
Or uh, like a some kind of like dessert
Like what else where where else can you use cinnamon besides like a fucking like the crust of a pie?
Cinnamon toast crunch does not count. That's like cinnamon sugar bullshit. That's not real cinnamon
Yeah, yeah, that's that is like not even close to being real cinnamon
It's like sugar
Somebody in a flavor lab came up with that. That's not cinnamon
apple sauce
Apple sauce drunk you drunk
on eggnog
All right. Look, I gotta pay attention to the fucking game
This is where I want to be
Yes, okay
I spent like two hours yesterday just talking and like walking in circles. I gotta like progress through
elderberry ring
Probably should sit at the bonfire though. I love cinnamon apple sauce
I mean, I guess it's like, okay
So I would put it pretty low on like the
kind of spices list
All right, that one has it right
Why would I jump to it? What a spices tier list
I don't think one exists
All right. Let me check down here first
what about
Apple jacks or apple jacks is it's all this like cinnamon
It's cinnamon sugar fake cinnamon shit. It's not actual cinnamon
You know what they do?
They put like one they put like one little dash of cinnamon and then like five tablespoons of sugar and they mix it up
I think i've been over here already
Let me go back up. Yeah, I was
You're moving goal posts that's what that's what I do here
Opium cinnamon sugar isn't actually cinnamon
Is whipped cream milk?
Does that argument make any sense? Somebody will I don't know maybe
No, it's not it's not milk. It's it has milk in it. It's made from milk, but it's not just milk
Cinnamon just cinnamon is gross
I win
It's one place that I would agree with you
and that is
taco bell cinnamon twisties
That is the one spot. I will agree with you
but again
Not really cinnamon is it it's like one percent cinnamon
I've been down here, right?
Where does that?
Oh, okay. Okay. So this is that this ladder goes. Wait a minute
I've not been here yet. Have I?
No, I haven't. All right. Hold on. Where's the elevator go?
Add I did there's no ad for taco bell that taco bell is like the best fast food place
best
It goes it does go over mcdonald's for me
It is better than mcdonald's
Because it has the single best menu item
Any restaurant in the world and i'm not talking fast, but I mean restaurant like you go to fight the best single
Restaurant item on earth. I would eat a cheesy godita crunch over filet mignon and be like, yeah, that was better
Just a single best menu item in the world
Kind of spitting facts
Well, thank you. I appreciate it. Is this an illusionary wall?
Dude kind of spitting facts right now
Where's he going? I just got an elevator. I'm trying to see where it is
Wait, I already went in that elevator. I'm very distracted
Okay, I am
All right. I'm extraordinarily distracted
Zero progress. It's been 30 fucking minutes. I know but I just like whatever
I told you i'm an elden ring streamer now and that means this is like I got to drag the content out
Fuck all right. I'm doing progress now. No more talking about anything that doesn't all right. Hold on
I want I want to save all these crunchies, but i'll use them
1000 there we go. I stubble I need to shave tonight probably
All right. I have 20 endurance
I am at everywhere. I want to be
Another question is do I keep leveling up vigor?
Or do I put some more points in mind get mine to like 25?
I'm gonna say mine mine and then maybe go back to an int
I'll get mine to 25. I feel like I do really need mana. All right, here we go time for progress
You should pretend you're let's playing, you know how many times i've made that joke
I've done the like i'm making a let's play
After the age of twitch, right? I don't you guys remember but people would do let's plays
They probably still do
Where it would the video would be 10 to 15 minutes long and then there'd be like another video
Good luck making one of those kinds of youtube playlists with this game
You're gonna have like 800 videos
This is gonna be something crazy get to the uh, the vigor soft cap. It's 50
Yeah, after after mine 25 i'll get there
All right. So here we go. Let's go. Here we go. This is the way i'm going
Game progress i'm ready
Going this way. We're gonna progress not going down any weird ladders
Oh, but I was gonna I looked up, uh, I didn't look up any explorers or anything
but I wanted to see the level kind of range for uh mount delmer
And it's the thing that I just looked up level range mount gelmer
And it says 80 to 100
so
I think i'm all right. I'm right at the kind of top end of uh of being like leveled for this area. So
What is this place called? It's not gelmer
Gilmer what's this place called?
What is this place called?
mount gilmore
Helman mount gilmore. It's gelmer. That's what I said. I said gelmer
What are you talking about? That's exactly what I just said gelmer
What is it? Is it like is it like gel near?
How many times do you swing this around the circle, dude?
All right, fine. Fuck it
crystal barrage
That move is seriously so bad. I don't know why I have it in my loadout
Gelmer
It's not gelmer
Oh come to gelmer
mount mount gelman
commoners, hey
I heard somebody
Yes, I got it
mount gelmer fun
That is a filthy liar. Okay
It is it's it's it's gelmer
It's not like gelman. What are you talking about?
No, i'm the dev. It's gelmer
You know what we're gonna cast stay with me at the same time here
casting fucking
Come on
I like it. There it is. Thank you
I could I couldn't fucking cast it unless somebody said it
That's my chat we got a fucking back and forth me my chat
You know what I mean?
Doing this for a little while i've been playing fucking games on twitch for a little while and like my we got a fun fucking
Back and forth together
Oh, these guys are so poisoned
I gotta put on some different gear. I think i'm taking a lot of damage
Man serpent. Oh, you can have a snake friend. That's actually cool
You have one of these oh my goodness, that's cool
What happened to taking a break today?
um
I don't know. I just kind of feel like playing feel like just hanging out
I really want to play
and I the last week so over the last week it has like kind of
kind of medical problems
I haven't really been playing that much. I didn't want to play off stream content that I haven't seen yet
so
Now that i'm like, i'm like I can stream i'm like good to go for a little bit. I think
As I want to play like I want to play elden ring and I don't want to play off stream unless i've already seen it
All right. Well, this is one of those things back here
I feel like i've not been paying attention to the amount of these keys that I still have
I've just been using them
Okay, I got a lot of 11 heads up. You're almost at the cutoff for the assassination missions. Thank you backseater
I actually appreciate it. How far down does this go?
Somebody's casting a spell at me
Oh fuck don't move. Don't move go this way
Oh, why did he have range and I didn't how do you get over there? How do you get up there?
Inaccurate what is it ledge? Is there a ledge?
All right. Yeah
I don't you can't jump on that
Double that right there. I don't think you can no you can't jump on that. Maybe there's an elevator that goes up
I love this. Is this safe to fall down? Oh fuck. I probably messed that up
I don't know. Who's the who's your your favorite life?
All right, so this is down here it's the wrong game is it though
another one of these
Right. How many how many of these do I have?
When I have over one of these already, where is it? Uh-huh. I have two of these
I gotta feed these to the dung eater before I go up. I'm gonna go over here. I never want to hear you say
waifu again
Why do I have to play by a certain set of rules though?
Right, like you a bunch of you guys say that shit a lot
But I can't make a reference to it, right?
Like why do you get to play by a different set of rules that I do?
I feel like that painting's gonna be as alive royal knights resolve
Because you're a grown adult
Yeah, but I you I you guys make references to this shit like what I
And to be very fair, my my response was a very joke response. Okay
Because you're 36
Oh
Hey
Wait, is this that door that's locked? This is the manor. What is patch is doing here?
Okay
He's such a dick
Are you surprised that I belong to the volcano manor?
I always hated the gibberish about lost grace and the laughable two fingers
I thought I could lend a hand in unmasking the charade not to mention
Tanith has always made me curious
I think her master must really be something
She's pretty damn smug about it
Even after announcing her blasphemous ambitions. She still stands proud
I've never seen a woman quite like her. I just you have a regular
Plus two short spear
I don't think you get to tell me how what what i'm doing here. Okay
You see me you see what I got?
It's grace mimic gold. Ooh, can I make that not that I really care but
I'll own it
All right, bye
All right. So somebody said I was getting painfully close to
um
Not being able I gotta do the assassin assassin. I can't that word is hard to say say it a few times assassin
um, somebody said i'm getting close to
Needing to do the assassin missions or i'm gonna be kind of fucked right?
say assassin 10 times
Assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin assassin
wasn't there a wasn't there a wait wasn't there a wasn't there a did i i don't remember that thing
i'm really lost yeah i don't remember that thing was that that big mechanical thing wasn't there
it's a new area but didn't i come from like one of those key gargoyles you fell down here bro i don't
fucking actually remember like i remember putting the key into the stone thing going in and falling down
there were two ways to go you jumped down the cages yeah but wasn't there another way i could have gone
oh my god it's okay i'm gonna go that way there's so many places to go
bro i'm just saying it out loud i'm exclaiming it all right well then let me
i guess i'm going this way but somebody said dude you're painfully close to not being able to complete
something so should i do that first that looks to be very very much a room that i'm gonna be
careful of all right all right all right all right all right all right so i need to talk to
somebody to get another assassination mission you got brain rot nice bitrate what's wrong with
my bitrate this should be another letter on the table okay let's do this on drugs all right i'm
not on all right here we go another letter let's see what is this one for it's in a weird place
right yeah it's in like this weird okay old knight is no i already killed him it's like i
already did that riley the idol he can be found at atlas plateau okay down here bridge of iniquity
he's idle right now is he actually just sitting around so that so over here are you down in the uh
like in this butt crack down here all right he's down in the butt crack how do i get down to the
butt crack from here i think i can make it i think i can land on that oh boy i have to commit i have
to commit i'm falling i have to commit should i commit i'm trying to jump no i can't commit the
other way we're good i guess i could go from i think i have to go from all the way down here
right like this way i'm assuming does it have to start like from the lift no fall joke today
oh there's already been one this just brings you right up right you're taking the literally
longest wrong way look i don't have i don't have the goddamn fucking game informer uh special
edition elden ring guide on how to get there i don't have the special edition game informer
that's eight extra magazine pages that shows all the places to go this is safe how do i get
get down here all right i don't know i don't have like a game informer oh where do i go let's see
you here i think all right so what's a better one what's a i don't give a shit about losing those
souls is there a way i can get from here to there you said i took the longest way possible where's
the closest bonfire then okay where's the closest bonfire then if you're so smart oh i found it
okay hey what was actually shocking that was shocking that was shocking why did i die from
that i've i'm shocked i look at my look at the expression on my face look that's you have to be
pretending dude i'm sorry i do that five out of five times and i land that every time so what was
wrong with that that you're telling me that's too far but this that there's no way that that
there's no way i refuse to believe it actually not possible that that killed me there must have been
a bug in the fucking code somewhere three that's it i actually didn't even come down here before
there's no fall damage in the cyclones all right let's let's let's kill this motherfucker
this person this is the idol invade riley the idols world yes thought all the old men were asleep
now i don't know why that took me like five extra seconds to figure out how to get that menu like my
my inventory menu correct what do you got your highest shit right now i am not you didn't drop
anything i thought i oh crepus vile black key bolt what's a crepus vile that's not a eliminates
all sound made by the wearer during movement all right this gotta be like a fire a bonfire i can get
right this this area here that i have marked it has to be a bonfire down here
oh that's a little berry a bonfire fast this place is cool this place is fucking stupid
what do i um their front entrance hello ah shaded castle i don't want to do this part yet i don't
want to do this this is like a whole ordeal it's gonna take like an hour or two it's a whole ordeal
let me go back to the manor and see if i how many assassin i can't say that fucking word
assassin mission is because i'm adding the sh that i want to say on mission like a shashan mission
this place might be easy for you at this level maybe i'll maybe i'll do it on another character
though maybe i'll do it on another character uh it's the guest hall so oh
and i saw guest room and i thought that was the right bonfire it's not oh oh
there's one more okay did good right i see you performed another task for us
here is your usual reward am now perhaps the time has come to tell you
of the true ruler of this manor lord oh i'm here to kill him the erd tree blessed the tarnished
with grace but it was all too meager in the face of the enormity of their task the tarnished were
forced to scavenge squabbling for crumbs like the shard bearers vying for power in the wake of the
shattering our lord indignant has refused to scurry about fighting over what miserly scraps
they allow us if the earth tree and indeed the very gods would debase us so then we are willing
to raise the banner of resistance even if it means heresy we at the volcano manor under lord have
sworn no rest until i kill him if you follow this heroic path one day the lord will see
are you gonna be able just to backstab him visits with our champions are always a spectacle it
cannot come a day too soon what's up dude yeah that arm is pretty fucking cool that's pretty
sick armor i can i mean like that magic defense on it though pretty fucking low right that's what i
heard my tailor does kind of stuff like that too but magic is pretty low on it right i would yeah
probably not that i'm gonna you know not that i'm worrying about it just like i've been worrying for
you i'm looking i'm trying to look out for you man that's defense low on that yeah pretty low
all right fucking all right kid all right fucking see you later hey mama said hi i don't know not
in like a weird not like you know what i mean that was like supposed to be respectful that's not
supposed to be mean that was supposed to be respectful but this one's red
sorry something's wrong with me today i swear to god all right
all right final request the letter is vivid red you know hoslow no wait night of blood
it could be found in the mountaintops of the giants find the red mark on your map isn't that
you know this person it's you is it i'm terribly sorry but would you mind giving me some time to
myself i haven't achieved anything at all this far even though i've dirtied my hands time and time
again i'm still yet to achieve anything perhaps i am a fool after all no it's worse than that
as things stand i've given up on the path of revenge and solid the name of my house
this is a plot twist one easy mark i must have been how did it take me so long to realize honestly
there's just no end to my foolishness is that what's up dude yeah now you're not foolish kid
you're fucking fine how high is that our defense on that for magic just just by fucking bobby was
talking to me the other day about how his uh armor was fucking pretty low on magic defense
yeah he's a fucking loser i don't talk to him anymore but he told me he's uh that the kind of
gear that you have is it is low all right fucking all right fucking yeah all right shut the fuck up
all right i'm so sorry everybody hates that everybody hates it but i love it and i'm never
gonna stop doing it everybody hates it all right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah all right i don't i can't
do but i that's really far away can i do this before i thought did you guys lie to me i thought
you guys said that i was supposed to do this before i fought this guy talk to the hammer guy
look at you a recusant through and through i knew you had it in you take this
letter to bernal a special invitation to hunt some of the first tarnished who sat at the
round table hold if you should accept i'll next see you on the field of battle
really so i i'm not gonna i'm kidding okay so what about um what is this written request from
volcano manor addressed to bernal disclosing the names of two tarnished to be hunted bargram the
raging wolf an errant sorcerer willhelm both men can be found in the royal capital of lendel find
the red mark on your map this is not an official request over here i do this this is not an official
request if you follow this it cannot come back to patches patches was where was patches was he over
here he was sitting outside yeah he was like leaning down i think this is for you how many
errands do i have to do i don't trust okay he's gonna make me go somewhere and he's gonna like
jump on me like a fucking goomba yeah he's gonna jump on me like a goomba and just crush my like
body it's fine and shit i don't i don't trust anything this guy says so where does he want me
to go dressed to patches wait i'm doing all their shit for them they got these letters and they're
making me do this okay well let's just get this one out of the way
frag off um where is he which one i think is that one right
okay so where the hell are you right here apparently invade great horned
frag off i feel like this guy's huge is this a giant oh that was pretty sick i'll give it to you
oh you piece of shit you can't even dodge like that how are you dodging like that with a hammer
that big holy fuck what just happened sorry chonished that was from patches though so there's
something weird about that germa i you germa he had cats at home i can't believe he did that he had
cats at home that's this is way too heavy but it's cool looking oh i got this no no no no no no
not the finger maiden fillet what is it uh this one here why would i get this this late in the game
old goat helm provides high poise it does doesn't it that's pretty cool i got a there was a new
weapon too wasn't there this thing xc poison build up that's you know what that's like one
of the first poison weapons i think i've seen in the game it's like three it's hana very cool
that's actually a really cool weapon all mug he's crying i don't think bog exists in the game i feel
like we made that up last night okay so now let's go over here and get these this too i'm
imagining it's probably here so where is it are they in this round table hold i think they're
probably just right here all right let's go i think i have to fight two people at the same time
yeah these people are co-oping wait oh it's it's both of us i'm annoying i'm annoying i'm annoying
all right i'll get this one doing good over here man he's getting his ass kicked
hey it's like chugging potions did you die nice job high five you're getting carried so hard
i think i was doing all right you did not even contribute raging wolf gauntlets and grieves
someone by vagram the raging wolf one of the first tarnished to visit the round table hold
oh i've been wearing this let's see if we get anything better here that's not going to put me
over to um heavy load raging wolf armor this is just still better it's just still better
this scaled armor is insane but i don't even get this oh from istvan okay okay um so let's go back
to the manner because i'm imagining that i just that's i completed it so let's go talk to them
gale dumber is really good it is you secrete noxious fumes i think everybody does at some point
if you follow the hip cannot let's talk to the people over here i did what you wanted now give
me that cool weapon it's just as my another says complete fool i'm a champion i know you're you
i've you've been here for the beginning of the game look i don't want you to perhaps i am a fool
no it's worse than that let's think what an easy mark i was i don't like that i all the
npcs that i like are starting to like kind of go away ah you'd soon return what is it 5050
it's yours galman's fury that is trepiducent until we reach the miserable is that a sorcery
it is it's faith and sorcery not happening cool though so faith and sorcery i always thought you
had to pick one but i guess when you get later in the game you can kind of combine them that's
kind of cool you still a lot all right so let's talk to patches who's that what is this brave
tarnished what is your business here i'm afraid this is not a guest room what's that peculiar
look upon your face is this the girl goodness am i still a serpent oh how dreadful how dreadful
my distress i ought to be thanking you for treating me as usual despite this appearance
brave tarnished this is my true form my real name is zorias please forgive the deception
do understand this duplicity is my own doing lady tannith speaks no falsehoods
and the volcano manna is just as it seems wait okay lady tannith is my mother oh i am told i was
born by the grace the lady tannis is a serpent that cherishes this form i inhabit what i am
okay all right people are cruel if they saw my true form they wouldn't speak to me perhaps so
i assume a guise when seeking new recruits but you are not like the rest don't worry
my serpentine form zorias the secrets known only to lady tannis and i now i share the secrets with
you as well please keep them safe from anyone else i would uh advise you we close the door
you want to keep a secret that you're a serpent
um like that's not a great way to hide all it takes is for you know like like
i don't even know his name dalios just needs to come out and get like a coffee
from like the fucking lobby and he's gonna see you all right so should i talk to the mom
i gotta talk to patches but if you follow this it cannot oh shit do you see her
the girl with her true face if she confided in you the name zorias then perhaps it is not my place
to speak but as her adoptive mother ask of you please be kind to her look after young zorias
all right true visage belies the purity of her heart honestly i hardly deserve the sweet child
she's a snake whatever she's snake lady whatever anything else to say please be kind
there's like this like all kinds of this like turtles that talk it's like the little apes
that talk and stuff don't worry you're good you're good don't worry about it i mean that you can like
turn into a like a dragon can't you in these games don't worry you're good what do you get
to worry about we're good perhaps i am a fool after all it's worse than that there's giant
talking pots stand yeah i've given up on the one easy mark look we we all we all now think
this we're like wow this character is so what a cool character this character is dead in less
than fucking 40 minutes you know what i mean like from software is gonna just just ruin it for us
look after her look after her she's gonna be lying on the ground if i have the opportunity i swear
as a knight of the volcano manner that i will protect her at all costs you're running between
rooms i'm taking in the lore relax let's go talk to patches or i yelled at you but you deserved it
are you certain fuck indeed i'll give tanith the news and have some rest by all means all
right so something weird's going on here cheers for that okay so sure now i'm gonna i'm gonna
rest i'm gonna he's not gonna be here you're a dick i'm what a dick they made fun of me for
walking in a circle anybody else i can talk to or is that it dial it back he's gonna get feral
if you follow the hip cannot come okay so where's patches i got some rest what's the reward
sharper than you seem aren't you i was just holding on to it for you you know here you go
the reward for hunting your ruined fragment all yours really stingy little beggar try to find it
in your heart next time hey wait that thing is probably crazy it's dex faith magma whip
but is it a whip it's a whip that's so awesome i need to like to swing it really it's a sticky
hand from those like 25 cent machines that's definitely way cooler if i had the specs to use
it i mean that's awesome that's probably the coolest faith weapon i've seen in the game so
far all right well that was fun thanks patches so is that it where's there more if you follow the
hip camera somebody said i what do i lose access to doing these because i don't think i'm comfortable
going to that other zone oh shit he's gone you're still alive he's gone oh hello it's you forgive
my mind never ceases to turn of late no i can trust you i saw something
in the pitch black of night it entered the room next to this one and never came out
if i'm not mistaken it took the form of a serpent just like me does the volcano
manor hides in secret that lady tannis has kept who's the snake i realize that i shouldn't impose
but if you discover anything who's the snake would you please share other of the oh i already saw it
was a secret after all lady tannis has deceived me was i not the grace of a king oh you're good
you're good you're good serpents i oh yeah i picked that up it's a gamer chair
what is that's the thing i got from the sense distinctly funny isn't it i am certain born
inside of this i was born inside this it's a part of my birth mother you have my gratitude
thanks to you i am no afraid i want to know how i was born and met lady tannis one day i hope to
call her mother once again this time from the bottom of my heart you know that's really
inaccurate but the teller stork comes and brings us in a little cradle i'm i feel like i should
tell her i want to know how i was born and met lady tannis one day i hope to call her mother
okay so should we go talk to it there's some there's some family drama brewing here
let's go find out if you follow that it cannot come she said that to you i should have known
something was wrong the signs were clear enough
zarias has placed her trust in you the reason i must tell you that some things are better left
unknown besides no one should be blamed for why there's somebody why the monsters involved
we are resisting the ways of the urge tree itself what matters one's lineage in such a crisis
your drywall was trying to kill me earlier so like i wanted you to explain that
shit has placed her trust in you but some things are better left unknown besides no one should
okay you don't go fucking near her by the way okay where'd you go oh i thought there was her
lying on the ground all right it's time to it's time to watch the credits and open up the next
episode right now the timer on netflix just went five four three two one zero here we go
here's the next episode what happens wait i don't know that yet hold on i don't know that far
no go back you skipped the intro too far you skipped the intro too far ah she's gone
where'd she go if you followed him okay where i haven't seen zarias anywhere why and she has
no scouting duties now has she gone off in search of answers why won't she just listen
yeah may i ask you not as the man as proprietress but as his mother if she discovers the answer to
her question and it causes distress or have a drink this potion to purge that which would
cause her pain i don't want to give her a fucking potion tonic of forgetfulness yes my wish is a
grave disrespect to her no different than the earth tree's imposition but i have no choice
it must be done my wish is a great i've noticed okay so hold on a minute you're telling me that
i'm supposed to give her this drink that is going to make her like do what forgetfulness
let me see what that says where is it tonic in a small brass bowl vanish vanishes distress
and bitter memories a gift bestowed by ryckhard sworn to blasphemy to lady tenneth who unfortunately
had no use for it my lord there could be no greater distress than to forget you small
flask received from perceptor selvis containing a cloudy tonic of bluish black find nepheli and
ensure she drinks it all right make sure i don't like fucking mix these up i also have like a bunch
of perfume like potion bottles i i need like a little bit of a management system here just chug
both there's only one of these what okay so i need to find where she went which is not very much info
i'm imagining it's probably somewhere here all right it's got to be somewhere in the manner
right if you follow the hip cannot there's no info on where she would be is there like a clue left
in the room or something you want directions do you want to find it yourself um i'm gonna imagine
it's probably in the walls either that or it's further in the zone that i haven't been yet
i'm gonna okay tell me if i'm on the right spot am i on the right path going in like she's in the
in here somewhere in the secret wall no very cold okay somewhere in the dungeon overall okay
all right uh we'll beep as you get closer he's in the lava area you guys can start beeping
all right now my question to you all is this it was the concern that i know do you got to do this
first because you might lose access to it after doing the boss here am i safe to do the boss now
is that okay am i safe to continue to progress i'm gonna go i have to finish the assassin missions
but dude i've i hadn't even been up here before that's like far away you can do the boss you can
come back to the boss later just do the boss it's fine especially for no kidding the boss after the
snake girl you don't need the assassination missions okay so i'll let me try to find her
i'm very intrigued so people were talking about how she's in the lava area i'll try to find it
you must defeat the assassins master bruce yeah you must defeat the assassins master bruce
i can't even do it man okay lava area you must defeat the assassins i feel like i'm just doing
like i don't all right where is she in the town down by the lava people were saying lava lava area
do i die from this no did i just find her is she like right here she like right there she's
right here right that was her all right i have not explored over there so i'm gonna i'm gonna
guess that it's that way this is like a lava area i haven't been to there's a bunch of
shit over here too all right wait a minute oh you see when someone is stabbed in the back
don't make a sound like oh it's for air coming out gasping for air
what's this thing's alive what were you doing i'm probably i'm gonna pick an item up and it's gonna
it's gonna activate i'm did i just i didn't kill anybody wait i thought that it's not you it's not
is it you is it you man is it you in there why can i attack why can i i don't want to kill your
like child i can i not talk it's self-defense and you know it was why is this is this alex
this is alexander it's moldering shield i get on the horse here no i just think i've lost a
few points with you guys but if i can attack that means i'm gonna end up walking across
they like trigger point for them all to attack me it's gonna be an item that i touch or a thing
that i do and they're all gonna stand up that's how it works in every single bomb software game
okay don't give me shit it was gold oh that's why is there anything else here
this everything's strong sticks all right i won't kill these three what's that this is like
suspiciously you know this is a suspicious thing oh god damn it i can go that way um let's go that
uh yeah okay we'll go over here first the loathsome dung eater her eyes he tarnished
can't get up there well he did he yet live who yet live i've ruined it loathsome dung eater
idiot the all-knowing well that was kind of cool i wonder if there's something else i can do there
but that's gonna have to be on the me strong playthrough i hope i can make this jump i don't
think i can can i make i don't think i can make this no no way not a chance in hell they might be
a way to get up there from okay i'm gonna go for it though fuck it i didn't even press the fuck
jump up god damn it except yeah it's a way oh i've been here i don't know hey over here all right
all right what is that oh yeah they're all kind of congregating around that this place sucks
i think it's all right um i think i'm just gonna i want to know what why are they over here i'm
curious is there an item that i already picked up over here
all right uh can i get some beeps please am i close what's the hot and cold meter look like
freezing cold beep beep ice cold ice cold ice cold is it really ice cold i've never found her again
all right it's really apparently i'm ice cold right now shit all right so let me go up this way
this is ice cold all right it's climbing this ladder and walking over here how what's the
temperature like this way all right if i were to walk through this door and straight through here
what's the temperature like warm warmer warm it's cold but it's warmer okay all right so all right
okay all right so if i is this cold that's cold is this cold is this one cold this one's hot this
is gonna take an hour for you to find her no it's not i'm gonna give up in 10 minutes i'm just gonna
ask you guys to tell me where it is i'm gonna act i'm gonna ask for the exact location i'll be like
just tell me where she is cold cold cold cold what the am i getting warmer i am
him this way really over here oh i found her is it actually is it whoa is it down here
all right just tell me where the book she is i don't care it's probably over here what do
you mean back down i'm not gonna go back down you just told me to go up i want it down bro drop
down take the elevator dude i'm on top of the snake statue right now can there be no item here
all right so you're like a cactus take the elevator again was wait this i can jump off
the right of the elevator this is the wrong elevator other elevator other elevator
this too where's the other elevator there ain't no second elevator right here it's the one outside
wait hey i walked out here and everybody screamed and said i was going the wrong way
the next room wait what are you talking about face the grace and gold left oh dude uh yeah this is
okay all right all right all right all right all right all right all right all right all right
relax relax relax relax i thought you were lying to me i thought you were lying to me i was like
they're lying about somewhere to go because i you told me do you i thought you were lying to me
hey it's i you cried wolf god damn it okay it's right there i'm fucking kidding guys give me a
break
what
oh shit no i'm not doing it
oh i'm not gonna do it you and me i made you a promise i said that i would defend you and i would
i would try helping take care of you that goes against my code of not killing anyone that i have
come into contact with that i say that i'm going to protect i have a code it's the germa 985 code
and it's i it's it's it's my it's my germa 985 character code if i'm in a game and i say i'm
going to protect somebody i will protect them holy fuck i almost actually hit her all right
now come back here reload and come back yeah save and quit oh i'm back after the boss
potion saves but at what cost wait she's gonna jump into the lava don't come back after the boss
potion makes her forget i'm supposed to potion is rude you gleefully would kill the pot guy
and his kids i never swore an oath to protect pots if i did i wouldn't have done that i i would not
have done that i was standing in the room and i said i am going to protect and help you at whatever
it takes all right i'm going for it do i have enough runes to level up one more time i think i
do let's use this hero's room the assassinations i i really don't want to go all the way over there
yet that's like across the whole world that's like the next zone you have to or it's gonna go away
yeah me strong take care of it they're not vital yeah me strong i know just for items yeah it's
all right all right i want to i don't have enough let me just kill a few things they don't go away
yeah it should be fine uh let me just get i gotta kill a few things i need some souls
because i want to level up one more time i had it was it 60 000 60 something 67 000 that's way more
than i thought it was going to be sorry and i remember the bonfire that it was to go because
there was like a big open door probably gonna be the boss remember you promised that you were
gonna throw auto on stream sorry me strong will take care of it yeah all of my duties all the
things i say are just gonna go on to me strong i have to start killing these things why are you
procrastinating an elden ring i feel like that's a huge part of the game is to kind of wander around
and come back and do stuff way later all right i need i need to kill a few things where can i go
to just kill a bunch of random shit i'm gonna go to where that boss is um where i was right from the
church from the church right what's the bonfire to get to where i was looking i was like oh look
at that big open door i think it's here the more you rush the more the less elden ring content
we're gonna get oh that's literally where i was just fucking standing jeremy i was just standing
there i was standing there i need the fucking goddamn vitamins today all right this is this
is this is correct yes it is all right so now i want to go over here and i want to go not that
way i want to go the other way there's a place that i wanted to go and i don't remember where the
where the fuck it is it's up up there i don't know dude i have no idea
did you find the illusory toilet is that where you you sit down to take a shit and when you shit
you actually like squeeze out your shit the toilet goes away and you shit on the floor
what would that mean it's all right i i need to really fucking figure out where i'm going here
this area is just my brain is having so much trouble with this zone because it's like the
yes somebody did say that yes they did i read that i read it somebody said it all right give
me a hand here because like i've honestly like we've been talking about like illusory toilets i
don't i what's what about where am i going i remember i looked at it and i was like i need
to go that way and i just kind of i forgot where i was going where was it it was like up there i
think was the temple because i had to be like up higher i didn't know how so much verticality in
this game my brain it's like the map doesn't show like verticality so it's just like is that one
higher are we up are we down and then it's from here out yeah and then it's to the left of here
right no it's up and then off the balcony so much fucking verticality this is like this is like
two thousand feet up and down like from from each of these four bonfires it's like it's like four
thousand feet up and down below and up above sea level because then there's this way which leads
to up here and then did i want to go i want to go up from here right because then the manor is
behind me i think this is correct but this place is fucking 10 000 feet below and above sea level
like it's huge it's a goddamn mountain okay it's a mountain and then oh fucking god damn it i have
no idea where i'm going take to go at the shortcut elevator what's he trying to do i actually
don't i don't know like i i'm trying to go to like with that area where i could i've looked over and
i'm just gonna go watch the vod and go see where the fuck i was i just i can't put it into long
term memory there's so many there's so many like levels to this mountain you were going the right
way can i really not go to the map because these fucking slugs are in front of me if all the slugs
have all right let me let me let me play out a scenario this is fucking confusing all right so
let me play a scenario out go to the elevator that is next to the not the elevator where the
boss was that second elevator and then go from there right i think that's right you had too
many flintstone gummies okay yeah so it's like out here and then in this elevator and then out that
way and go all the way up i'm painting it in my head right now okay then we go this way nice try
and then out here i think yeah okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then over here and then okay
all right but this is where i want it this is yeah yeah yeah yeah yep and up yeah it's so hard to
find this stuff i said they came in that they came back like an hour and a half later and i
was still in this room i just i did a bunch of like side quests shit okay i did a bunch of side
missions i i did like the whole serpent girl quest line i did the assassination mission i've been
doing things i've been keeping myself busy yeah because then i went down here and i remember
specifically being like how the fuck do i get back here me strong gonna handle that one i me
strong's gonna handle that one yep it was so long ago that i didn't put this into long-term
memory it's so funny that i keep saying me strong is gonna handle this but i don't think me strong
is gonna be able to like get out of limb grave me strong is gonna walk off a cliff and limb grave
like 50 times and i'm gonna have to turn the stream off i get your step will the will the me
strong jokes last as long as the 50 hours it's gonna take for this character um i am not gonna
play through the entire game as that character so don't worry that will be maybe one afternoon
stream where i'd be lucky to be able to even beat the tree sentinel all right so this is
i get where is this gonna take me find out i have no idea whatever i'm not ready this is it i'm not
ready for this i have 48 000 souls i need to hold on i'm not ready for this this is the audience
pathway all right hold on i need to i need to get a few kills don't call me a coward i actually i
need to just kill some stuff more stalling no i have 40 i have 50 000 souls i don't want to lose
them i have to just get to 60 something thousand it's not gonna take that long i promise
i just need like 15 000 each one of this is okay i have to kill like 10 things
look i'm just gonna aggro the whole fucking dungeon i'm gonna do what i used to do on my
like warlock and wow and that's aggro the entire dungeon when i was 20 30 levels higher than it
whatever and then do seed of corruption and kill 55 a million things in one second see 52 we're
fine oh wait i can go down here this way i get that item oh shit i don't want to be down here
all right just i'll do that again for me you seem like the type of dude
i don't know what the follow-up to that is but i i can assure you
don't know me don't know me come on all right that's what i'm talking about hey there
why shut up why am i like killing dead air it's awful hey there like what the fuck man that was
worth 3 000 almost there i promise almost there someone was guaranteed to lose these
i don't want to lose them i actually want another one of those all right we'll kill that guy again
i guess hard get them all all right 61 000 almost there ripped his loss all right everybody round
him up there we go 62 only a few thousand more and we're done i already explored down here
what you don't see you never seen a streamer grind for souls on stream before for like i'm sorry
for 10 minutes where is it it's one of those there it is the fuck away from me all right we
did and we got it it's over i completed it 67 need to kill one more thing oh that's enough 67 for
67 all right let's go i'm ready audience pathway like the boss um and what happened to the boys
i've been summoning them i some of the boys at the last boss i fought like last night i'm
getting mine to 25 and then we're gonna dump pretty much everything else into vigor and
intelligence all right let's go it's time what is this serpent hunter is this a all right is
this a gimmick fight where is it serpent hunter weapon that serves as both great sword and spear
thought to have been used to hunt an immortal great serpent in the distant past it manifests
a long blade of light when facing such a creature okay when their master's heroic aspirations
degenerate into mere greed his men search for weapon with which they might halt their lord
great serpent hunt perform a powerful forward lunge and follow up with an upward thrust via
additional input when fighting a great serpent a long blade of light will appear revealing the
armament's true power so should i take off should i try to get to medium load or i don't
let me let me what does this do all right okay so let's i gotta get to medium load
okay there it is all right um gimmick fight i'm ready for the gimmick fight there's a beam
oh shit does the r2 do it too all right i need both headphones for this god-devouring serpent
it missed fucking bad idea oh you need to go upgrade it up i'm not gonna upgrade this
fucking thing what do you mean go upgrade it you died to the gimmick boss shut up i'm not
gonna go quick but like if i just no i i was doing pretty good damage i'm fine boys there are too
many chandeliers in here let's go boys i was so confused what was happening where the fuck am i
what's going on what does that mean hey ah he got me he got me he got me he got me he got me
i'm okay phase two fuck it's an extra half second that's fine i'm all right i'm fine i'm fine
stop it oh my god it's poisoning all over me this poison all over me fuck what happened
how did i end up over here do l2 twice this poison all over me turn into a boston guy
how did i end up all the way over there l2 combo wait i do it i can do l2 l2 all right let's go the
boys are not gonna do anything here i got it i got it i got it i got it i gotta be patient
oh shit ah out of the fire i can't i get this fight's not hard i'm just so impatient
what the fuck you like little tiny little pieces of fucking fire is what's hurting me
oh my god no god what the fuck is happening yeah all right get me the fuck away from him
like this all this fire bullshit everywhere what i didn't have animation uh control there
why did that not hurt me oh the shield right that was cool that was cool fight
that was really cool it was a gimmick fight but it was a fun gimmick fight although that's probably
phase one and phase two he's gonna come out of the head and he's gonna be like tarnish tarnish
tarnish tarnish and then it's like uh here comes the real fight and it's gonna be horrible
oh very well why does this cut to that it's gonna be fucking hell do i still have to use the gimmick
oh my fucking god dude that was a lot bro you hit the ground first the fire follows you
what the hell's happening what oh can we stop with that move can we stop oh my god
again oh fuck that fuck that fuck that get the fuck away from him give me you go go go go go
go get away from the fire fire shit oh my god the fucking camera is gonna make me shit my pants
i swear to god i don't have any mana oh i'm fucked i i can't even can't even attack him anymore
dude i i don't i you have to run from this you gotta you gotta run run run run run run
i won't even go near him just literally run in a circle this is over oh wait a minute wait a
minute wait a minute okay all right all right i get it i get okay all right wait a minute
all right all right wait a minute okay all right wait a minute
those motherfuckers come out for a very long time all right i gotta pee so bad i'll be right back
all right let's uh let's kill this guy i like a plan he's not that bad it's just trying to
trying to run away from the skull move seems very very hard i there's probably a way to
to get away from it i wonder what's the best way to get away from that just run i wonder if i just
do a full sprint you need to try to stun lock his entire second phase well let's just hope i can
get to the second phase again oh you're gonna jump over that shit i don't know i'm too greedy
not locked on that's bad news oh i don't want that on me for this shit zombie fuck i'm poisoned
fuck fuck go get him boys what is that he's already doing this fucking move he's already doing it
he hits the ground shit all right now run whose item whose fucking costume is this
hey fuck off oh shit oh sorry should i jump are you supposed to get away from that a jump
i don't i don't understand that move when he comes you can't dodge it you have to jump over it well
can you just you can you just can i just out run it if i just run this motherfucker i swear to god
i feel like i've dodged it pretty well the last few times it just still hits you with it
dodged later it's fucking slow ass motherfucker i swear to god
greedy that's very very that was very greedy um let me try to outrun it if i just sprint i wonder
if it works come on do something really what get away from the fucking poison please
i'm gonna try to outrun that move i'm just gonna run if he still hits me then it's your fault
because you told me to do it oh come on do it again again again again again oh
where the fuck am i oh shit he changes fucking combo up chug chug chug chug chug chug damn
that was crazy so honestly the he's not dead all right the strategy there honestly was just to
just to eat the flame skulls and just try to dodge them don't run am all right cool also
you just got to go aggressive uh the chatter was right i've just taken too much time to try to just
wait for him to do something just get in there and just have mana potions and l2 l2 and just
unlock the fuck out of them just keep hitting them over and over again that was cool fight
it was very cool 130 000 that's a lot yeah all right so uh let me rest here i said i want a 25
mind right i wonder what you get for this for this remembrance reload the boss area
he's level 106 reload this area go back to volcano matter and income all right well
hold on let me let's do this first i want to see what's in here this boss weapon is amazing i
wonder what it is is it intelligence blasphemous blade faith dex and strength another great faith
weapon some hp is restored upon defeating an enemy raise the sacred sword of loft is set
to blaze with blasphemous flames is steel hp that sounds insane and this is wow this is 40
int 18 releases searing spirits that repeatedly explode oh it's the skulls try to get this that's
i don't have any the faith though no i'm not it's not gonna be close 18 faith i'd have to put on
a rune which would get me to 11 and then some faith talisman which would be 16
and then a faith helmet which is would give me to 18 could respect too but is it really worth it
the spell is for the birds don't worry i wonder not for one spell not worth it the sword is cool
but i just it's not this character that looks like it'd be cool too but i think i'm just gonna
smash it if you do anything just get the sword instead be strong would like this yeah probably
yeah i'm gonna break it i'm gonna smash it it's it's too much faith to have to go respect for one
spell i don't think so although i do i've been neglecting sorcery really badly so like the last
few um last few streams i i think i'm gonna have to go get a couple of good spells these are comets
really good swift glenstone's all right for like range but i don't know actually i should
probably upgrade the uh staff as well go kill the dragon in the ranny area yeah that's a good idea
i'll go do that that's the best spell in the whole game okay i'll go get it but first
literally almost everything from the volcano east needs faith all right let me see if i let me
upgrade my uh staff i think i might be able to upgrade the boys as well well i took you for that
matter it's all about your own smithingstone eight these are very high okay how about you can
i upgrade anybody i can upgrade the boys boys plus nine what a waste of fucking materials
let's go who else do i want to try oleg is plus four but we got a lot of other we got other ones
too maybe the snake that sounds kind of fun i have the mimic but we we don't like the mimic
anymore got nerfed i think we're gonna go snake friend i think i'm i'm choosing the boys and the
snake either that or these little weird bucks right here i want to try i'm gonna do snake
i already i have the mimic plus seven i yeah this thing is probably amazing too perfumers probably
amazing still the best even with the nerves mimic is still the best all right well i want to do the
snake i'm going for it it's grave glove wart which okay yeah yep all right okay snake time
we have to change this uh how do i open up okay the pouch is right here the dogs are gone we're
gonna replace it with the snake i got the boys at plus nine and you better believe the boys are
gonna be plus 10 in the end here oh like i i'm gonna get the snake up after very cool in the
meantime i have to go let me do this first let's clean up the manor a little bit and then i'm gonna
go get i'm gonna go kill the dragon in front of randy's castle let me do this he's bell bearing
he would oh right these oh these grave no these are ghost glove warts not grave glove warts all
right okay let's go let's move to i'm gonna go to the manor okay so from here i'm gonna go talk to
the the zarias have you done the capital i have done the capital although i don't i don't know if
i've done the entire capital but i've did i did the major bosses in the capital and i did a lot
of the sewer and did the uh dung eater stuff get the giant rat rat ashes it's too on brand for me
i'm i'm gonna go with the snake yeah i thought that i thought the dung eater kicked his ass all
right so this i needed to go where where where was she was down where was she
i'm a map now will you get the fuck away from me you little weirdo uh she's like over here right
can i drop down where the hell is she she's like down here right yeah you're not gonna okay
oh hello he's being so kind i thought that was like a scary moment why is it red don't give it
i suppose i knew in my heart i think you always reloaded again and i just i can just do this right
i just quit the game and come back that works right i was supposed to protect her
oh
araya's letter eddy car's whoa brought me a letter what does it say farewell letter written
okay she's alive i wish to set out on a journey so that one day i can carry on mother's work
be the proud daughter of tanneth of volcano manor farewell you've always been so kind so
uncompromising my champion because she's alive it is left a few trinkets could have fucking killed
her could have killed her increases damage taken it has said that this woman named dedica indulged
in every form of adultery and wicked pleasure imaginable giving birth to a myriad of grotesque
children okay another one of those from software what's the point of this items
this just makes the game hard okay i'm not gonna keep it on it's for masochists i wonder if uh
if she shows up again later well now this is gonna be very interesting what do they have to
say about this she's probably gonna be pissed yeah hi me i uh i fucked up you it's true then
you've defeated our lord dude no i must thank you our lord was yet weak you have taught us that
defeat is not the end our lord is immortal and will one day rise again stronger you mean like
tomorrow when i load the next day on the bonfire stay the path and it's gonna be like an ultra
version or something right i will leave volcano manor you're gonna leave i suggest you do the same
i will miss these encounters the champion who walks the tainted path shines all the more i always
was an admirer what you're gonna rope us all into this and then leave this is farewell perhaps we
will meet again i killed people i killed people for you or like this whole like little fucking
club we're in i killed my own like friends and tarnished and shit and now we just visit
where are you going this is perhaps we were this is perhaps kidding me and you fucking i can't
believe this my thanks well that was that guy that was here all right so hey can you guys
can you guys believe what's going on here can you believe it everybody it's it's just me and you
you are you and i the only two suckers left here you killed the strong on patch yeah patches is
there which is our code even he was prepared to meet a wretched end when he first took blasphemy
into his very flesh but any road the volcano manor is no more and yet fulfill an old promise
i'm gonna get in that weapon soon the time has come to rise against the earth tree oh greater will
hear my voice i am the recusant bernard inheritor of my brother's will and you will fall to my blade
you want to kill the greater will consider this fair warning the greater will that seems that
doesn't that seems kind of like an entity you can't like go nearer you're like angry at
essentially magic air right like the greater will is not like a person
it's a thing it's like a it's like a concept the force hear my voice i am the recusant we
refuse to become you okay well that's cool so now let's go talk to patches and then i'm gonna go
to the boss room because everyone said to go there those patches say you're still here
you scheming little bastard you make this nonsense seem well less nonsensical perhaps a tarnished
will be elder lord after all but for now this manner is finished the demigod beast is slain
and tana has lost her head a fine mess but how else could it end when daddy ambitions head over
heels courting lady blasphemy once again bye my friend bye yeah if it kicked me down a
fucking ditch again two or three hundred feet up then leave me i'm gonna smash your fucking
head with a mallet like galaga used to do like i used to smash watermelons what a weird thing
you guys remember the comedian galaga guy would literally just he would go on stage and he would
just put up watermelons and everybody in the front four or five rows would be in like plastic
and his routine was he would just go up there with a mallet and smash them that was his main
part of his routine was just smashing fucking watermelons now that i think back what a fucking
crazy routine and everyone would be like oh my god it got on us it was like being on like a ride
like splash mountain or something right like what the fuck now that's entertainment you dreamed
that no i didn't i did not that is not what i did you will never be as funny as galaga wait what's
this room this is scary room what is this room have i been in here oh i've been in here all right
it's time to go to the boss room and see what's in here back is back oh he's growing back
i kill it again who's that who's eating him oh you allow me some time our lord's carcass is vast
and not easily consumed dear ricard was this please find purchase within me
i wish to be your serpent your family no one day oh it's also wrong the gods together
this is also wrong this i would this is where i just drop a grenade and we'll just go this way
and run and just fucking leave i don't i don't know about this dear ricard please find purchase
within me i wish to be yours one day what oh hey what'd i tell you one day you and i were
meat blows and today is that day hey how panic dodging put your fucking guard down oh oh shit
i thought it was gonna be a smaller cone than that bye bye aspects of the crucible breath
and you drop something too mask oh man that where is it ask one by teneth lady of the
volcano manner in the image of a queen increases dexterity oh long ago when ricard first set eyes
on tennis she was working as a dancer in a foreign land soon he made her his consort he was the only
human to remain by his side when he became the serpent of blasphemy it's only one dex too
what about the robes on sorts robes sucks ass why did he kill her she's literally eating this guy
and i i they they were bad i'm sorry if i'm gonna kill an npc i'm gonna kill the npc that's
literally eating the boss to try to become as strong as the boss and become the boss
i'm gonna kill that npc so now if i go back to the manner wait let me reload here they're gone
so what if i go back to the actual the manner is there anything there they weren't on the protect
list no nothing here no item all right well i'm imagining that breath is like frog breath right
not a sorcery so it's definitely yeah it's an incantation yeah there it is
throat pouch to spew fire all right next on the agenda volcano manner is pretty much complete
there's probably a few things i didn't do but you know me strong will take care of it eventually
i want to i want to go and kill let's go to the yeah here there's a dragon here that drops a spell
i want it go to the plateau plateau south of plateau down down here back to ranny's rise
that's what i was saying yeah down here you want you want to talk with this this jail
but did i do this i buy runes top of the map not the jail the church each rule
no there is a oh oh oh oh oh oh oh there is a dragon here you're right there was a dragon here
wasn't there where you at okay literally right here a lot of fucking help shit oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh can't get off the horse i forgot i've rebounded the damn thing to triangle and up on d
pad oh okay what are you doing why would i use magic against the fucking magic dragon oh fuck
coming down that was 10 feet that was like 10 feet that was not far how far would give me a clip
give me a fucking clip that was like i am fucking flabbergasted that was like 10 feet that was so
small i hate that face i made that like get fucking out of here that was so small give me a fucking
break that was tiny that was not far nice cringe face whatever that was stupid
you'll be good this time that was doing fine
finally oh my god that crack what you man watch out for that shit get off finally
oh my god hide in the building hide in the building hide in the building
oh fuck i'm good what did i just hit him in the air what the fuck just happened
what i just launched him like a thousand feet in the air he was like get up boy what are you doing
jesus christ a doula's moon blade you guys didn't do shit you guys didn't do anything
you just you just sat there like this i'm very disappointed in you you are plus nine i fed you
four or five of you dickheads so much grave glove wart you're gonna be bloated later you're gonna
be bloated i can't believe you didn't they didn't do anything all right so what was that sweeping
slash old projectile ponders a cold magic great sword then delivers a sweeping blow that launches
a blade-like projectile of frost and be cast repeatedly 120 000 souls too jesus i didn't
even get those either oh my god holy shit i'm gonna level up like two three times all right
there was there was another dragon here wasn't there here i remember there was a dragon that
hung out here wasn't there or am i crazy but that was the same one oh okay he just moves around
all right well let me try that spell there's your 25 mind that's that's pretty good i still have a
lot of souls i don't know how much is it to level up oh okay okay i can do it again so now what do
i focus on do i just dump points in intelligence or should i get up to a 50 vigor probably vigor
i would imagine it's a 60 and you both i'll go back and forth between the two let's get into 60
okay so we have okay this spell is dog shit get rid of it i have this a doula's moon blade which
is going to be insane uh i use i use style light all the time swift is good comments good i don't
have anything better though okay did they buff some of this shit to not be awful which one of
these is actually worth using now crystal barrage is terrible but some of these actually worth
using they're not just terrible the arc is better now the comet i don't have that but like night
comet or something great bow is good now great glint stone shot was buffed that's just better
that's cost less too maybe i'll try that instead of the um in a comet there's an ice spell that's
like comet did they make okay question is meteor any good because this was terrible terrible really
truly terrible truly awful it's still useless how about night comet and i'll put it on there
all right let's see how cool this move is yeah okay can i charge it
holy shit that's an arc how far does it go and with member this is important
this staff is reduces casting time of sorceries so i that actually is really quickly happening here
awesome you can multi hit you get a better meteor later on like the guy at the bottom of the tower
okay say so one of the best aoe trash killing spells it feels like it it's a huge arc
i wonder how it does uh damage wise oh shit who's that who the fuck is this person can we talk
it's one of the assassins why would i be fighting him why would i fight blade i don't think i should
fight blade i like this guy he's lost he lost his mind what oh oh shit he is crazy holy shit
how much damage did i just try you see what i just did why would i just floating in the air
oh my god i got him what no i why does it have to be getting killed royal greatsword in all of his
armor i really liked that guy so he went mad okay so he went mad this is int greatsword decorated
in royal carrion style favorite weapon of lied the half wolf in defiance of the fate he was born to
lied for to serve no master but runny as proof the sword was imbued with a cold magic at the
moment the oath was sworn confuse the greatsword with frost and perform a forward somersault
i can't do it but that's cool that's a beautiful weapon
oh that's that's a beautiful weapon very cool so what about the armor i would feel kind of
icky putting on the armor don't you think so it feels like it doesn't feel right well worn
black armor of the man wolf blade pelters as a cape protecting from cold why was the blade of
ronnie but the cold bothered him anyway frozen reference does actually they actually put that
in that seems really out of place the cold bothered him anyway but um the scaled armor is better
just is gauntlets are good though the gauntlets on anything do i have anything better these are
still medium load scaled gauntlet this is better it just is oh but uh i can stay i could put blades
graves on still medium load yeah i think i feel like the scaled armor is some of the best armor
in the game very interesting very cool very cool okay george r.r. martin is a huge frozen fan really
that's funny all right that takes care of that should i go what about did i do all this there's
still this i don't understand this i don't know where this person is i don't know where
this person even is but i'll go see if he's in there go up and go to ronnie's go up to ronnie's
room i mean like up here go talk to the ronnie doll ronnie fell up here yeah i did i did ronnie's
quest i did complete ronnie's quest the whole thing not here did i not have this go to the
other tower oh i can get the grace why is my cam so small i don't want to take it up that much
space is some of this stuff to see on the screen okay so i can talk to the doll i take it thou has
noticed i shouldn't be surprised i thought i might expand a little further upon the order i envision
mine will be an order not of gold the stars and moon of the chill night i would keep them
far from the earth beneath our feet as it is now life and souls and order are bound tightly together
but i would have them at a great remove and have the certainties of sight emotion faith and touch
all become impossibilities which is why i would abandon this soil what with mine order
wouldst thou come to me even now a one and only lord you want to get rid of all of our
five senses touch sight smell taste gravity touch sight smell touch sight smell taste
what water hearing so she wants to remove all of our senses no i don't want to do that
wait you mean you tell you tell me i never be able to taste the steak again i don't know if we can
do that ronnie i don't think i can do that i got another great run he's making a utopia we don't
know that i walked through like a lake of rotten stuff grabbed a ring and put it on her finger and
i did all of a sudden i'm just supposed to trust everything that she says yes he wants to free the
souls what about what i want to do so i get to make a few stipulations here fuck again look if
i'm gonna do all the work um then i get to make a few like i get to make a few amendments to this
okay yeah you can remove all of our senses except for once on friday friday or sat on thursday we
get to taste food on thursday and then that that's fine i want once a week and i also require
it on thursday as well to get to be able to feel that feeling of really digging in deep and getting
a wicked huge booger out of your nose that's been bothering you for like an hour i want to
be able to have that feeling it feels great sometimes happens in the shower all right what
else do you want to do gold but the stars and the moon of the jits i don't want to be cold
chilly nights no and i would abandon this soil with my words thou come to me even now i don't
know about that it seems kind of like depressing it's like cold and dark not like i don't know i
don't know i don't like that chilly all right well that was that's kind of cool let's go that way
we know you're doing the dung eater ending i mean i don't even i don't know what ending i'm gonna do
all i'm saying is as of this moment right now i don't like being cold i keep my place pretty
warm we've had this conversation i don't want to be like freezing out and like some fucking
chilly night thing no i think 72 to 73 degrees i like i like it i like my place to be like 72
73 i like it hot okay let's go over here and see what's in that tower that's the correct
temperature you wouldn't believe how many people think i am an insane person for wanting to have
be like 73 degrees am i the crazy one somewhere between 73 and 74 i think is a perfect indoor
temperature is that that weird i don't think it is and i don't know how people oh yeah i like it i
like it like 63 64 i would die in that i would i would die in that temp 64 65 that's way too cold
62 60 no 68 okay i could understand 68 like 66 to 68 69 anything under 66 65 is that's
way 64 no way too cold i already did this so i'll just go in it so we can anything under 71
i'd say 70 is fine 70 is getting there but i think 68 is the lowest i would be like comfortable
maybe like a little higher less than 68 is also psychotic i would i you look oh yeah i did i did
sorry all right cool it's time uh it's time to go towards this what i assume is one of the final
areas of the game i'm gonna go for it let's do it i'm very excited oh i didn't go to that
me strong will take care of that all right so how do i get there i make this jump not that
i really want yeah and i it looks like i can be planning on beating the game tonight i would
highly highly doubt that i'm going to assume that this whole this this whole area up here
at the very least would take probably a whole stream but we'll see i i want to go take a look
it's at least probably three or four more streams yeah whatever i look i'm
there's always that theory right where oh uh i'm playing the same thing over and over again and
it's the same game and people are getting tired of the same game over and over and people want
to see something else and i i think this has been really great i've been having a great time
um so i don't have a reason not to just keep playing this until i am satisfied with it right
uh somebody said go to the one near the tree there's a lot of people here i i'm really actually
very very surprised at the amount of people that are here i was thinking right the first stream had
a lot like there was like 15 to 20 000 people on that first stream or two and it's like holy
shit that's an insane amount of people to watch me play elden ring there's still a lot of people
here um so not that i've paid that much attention to that but that number is i mean i was i did not
think this many people were gonna watch me of all people play this game because i yeah it's maybe
after the first like few streams or whatever okay but i'm still going and people are still here so
i'm gonna keep doing all right uh i need to head that way do i get over there go back to that
previous bonfire it's fun oh this it looks like a little place i can go can i go like down here
one of the northeast of the city is this one here or this one here yeah i can't get there from here
probably from here right yeah because i could go yeah this one randy's supposed to be saying
the literal opposite of what she says all right so now i gotta get down here
this one go back to the main street you want that central road that had the urn tree avatar in it
ah i have to go okay so i have to go down from here i gotta go like this way and then down and
around right i believe this is correct okay i know where i'm going use that blood key item
i don't want to summon mog in an elevator you want to see mog in an elevator then just wait
for when randomizer mods come out wait for like the bosses can be enemies mod okay so now we gotta
go this way here uh-huh already a thing i would i mean they all existed for dark souls 3 and dark
souls 1 there we go this is what we're doing now this is exactly okay so everybody freaked out when
i walked down here because they were like dude wrong way so now this is the right way
i think i already did a little bit of this so let's go let's just go what level am i
i am level 109 which i believe puts me in level zone with this upcoming end game content area
i would take a guess well i guess i did that the fucking complete wrong direction
all right stop being lazy and fight them you are lazy you could have had that easily
i'm just like the fucking laziest sorcerer in the world just like with my bubble wand just
hopping around like an idiot yeah i got this too you're right i'm gonna go to bog stream instead
i have a few unpowered ruins i do i really do oh what a pain i should i really should have just
godrix is still one of the best when i got the other one and i looked at it it seemed like
it was just better than the other one in every way godrix increases all your stats by five
and renales increases your health fp and stamina but that's already happening with
godrix plus five on like endurance and shit right it almost feels like not unnecessary
yeah i i know i have to i haven't been using any rune arcs it's bad they would i do i gotta
start using them for bosses remind me literally the best move in the fucking whole game
there's one of these guys here that goes far as fuck what i was just in awe of how crazy that
move is is there another one good move wait a minute wait a minute i i need to look at
something strengthens cold sorcery that counts right so is two intelligence more than what this
would give to that spell or is this better i don't i don't know what how much percentage whatever that
means not at your level okay oh okay so i was doing like 350 before i wonder how much it does
now that's gonna be better is there anything else that does that okay great i don't think i care
about hp vastly raises maximum fp i already have that on is anything else boost fp no i already
have a lot of this on do i have anything else potency of sorceries that would count right
okay do i have anything else i think i want to keep the staff on though and listen one of these
boost cold sorcery which would be a huge deal it's a glint blade sorcery enhances crystalline
sorcery not cold let's find out let's take a look at the offices renalis staff does full moon spell
i don't think i have that no i don't it's a remembrance but i can go to one of those bells
and get it can i i didn't use any of the bell demon things i mean i might have to go do that
because that i'm into that that's cool you need 60 into staff i have 55 right now
though it's not like i won't get there or i could take a rune because i'm very curious because this
move is insane that move might actually replace how i feel about the baby rattle
because so far the this has been carrying for essentially the last 30 game hours it's an awesome
move but if that move is that good which it is i think i'm gonna have to use it lame drake talisman
one the glint stone uh from cell yeah yeah yeah maybe usat staff is the highest damage staff in
the game yeah but me i don't have to do the best you know it's not about what the best item is it's
what how much fun you have with whatever you're doing i need to one all right sneak
i can get it don't kill me here this guy's on a horse knight's great sword oh can i get it i can't
get on a horse here why he's allowed on a horse that's not fair one's just better but it's fun
to i like the i like the staff it's cool i don't matter i do have enough mana to cast this right now
okay cool shit
tuber reaction remember you have stylized shots for fp regen oh i do you're right is it retreat
no i thought i was like on fire anybody could have made that mistake it's the same fucking thing
okay it's literally the same exact entrance nobody noticed um yeah some people did it's why you said
it just for people to understand that like i'm not making shit up like i'm not hello well it's not
gonna get bigger are you can i get something else that's not five and six smithing stones
i feel like this probably bonfire soon i'm not gonna do a starlight shard
right turn right what are you talking about turn right yeah it's the urn tree if you want
no at the intersection dude but um i wanted i'm not gonna not do the elevator first
how would i not do this can we please dial mug with snowy oh forbidden lands
shit all right hold on i'll go i'll go back up this is pretty i am curious what's down that way
you got a mug raided you earlier what back down that was supposed to jump oh my god no what i
thought i was i thought there was i thought there was collision against wall i thought i thought
that i was just whatever i thought there was collision with the wall it was it's not against
the wall that doesn't make any sense i was trying to run against the wall so i could just go right
into the so i wouldn't have to jump and get it wrong it's right here it's literally like the first
in one second i fucking can't even do this right ever seems bored i'm not no not at all i'm not i'm
just fucking relax i'm bored of this because i don't want to fuck it up over and over again
official attire nobody's probably in here this is the mayor's office blade of calling blade of
calling eighth sword another faith sword oh it's a dagger power of its former owner the kindling
maiden is still apparent blade of gold leap into the air charging the armament with golden flames
that are then shot at the enemy as a single blade-like projectile okay i got what i got
something else too the official robe where is it officials attire ruby blue robe worn by
magistral officials to carry out the grim tasks surveillance executions gruesome rituals the
darkest duties drive the wheels of mankind the official robe found it and now i gotta go back
up because i want to go the other direction the official germa 985 rope can you do the
mog dance it's hard i can't i'll try it's hard it's it's actually really tricky to do it i've
seen people do it right because it's like a meme because like you fight the fight and his like his
eyes are closed and he opens them and his eyes are closed and when he opens his eyes you have to
hit the eye and the way that it does it he let me try it his eyes are like he closes his eyes like
this it's like let me see if i get it right like one two one two one two shake it's it's a funny
dance it's a cute dance um i've seen it like a little bit on like youtube and stuff was it
at now 4.5 billion views on youtube or something it's like took the world by storm it's insane
i'm gonna go the other way yeah i passed like a bunch of records or something recently
four and a half billion five billion views a billion of those are probably me right thanks
fucking god fucking starlight kid i'm gonna just gonna it's gonna be it's gonna be a monster
fell twin no i don't want to do starlight again kid holy fuck that hurt you a lot
this guy's still running from all the way back there what's wrong with it oh my god this move
is fucking insane he's still running where where is he still running holy shit oh my god that move
is fucking crazy what's the crazy with these guys killer rollo there's a lot of damage yeah
a bit of both they're just regular mobs yeah they kind of are aren't they they were yeah they were
they were two mog like um enemies i have another i have a lot of souls i only need 60 70 something
thousand thirty four thousand shit well whatever what's in here i even open this divine tower of
east atlas it was the mogdonoth twin oh this is where i turn on one of the runes okay that makes
sense it looks like that looks like i can go there doesn't it never mind remember you should sub to
atriach on youtube we're very close to 300k everyone should sub to atriach not just me
hey you should all go do it right now stop what you're doing right now and go sub to atriach
on youtube do it right now it'll take you two seconds i'll come right back in fact leave me
open in the tab oh do it right now there you go just go do it nothing crazy is going to happen
in like the two seconds you're in the tab right now right good i'm just walking around
what the fuck what the fuck oh my god that was fucking insane so whose run is this
tab is i don't i never did this what does his run do greatly raises max hp but by how much though
raises i feel like they kind of feel like they kind of botched this in a way because raises all
attributes raises health raises max health raises health raises health raises health like i feel like
i wish these were a little different they all kind of do the same thing but maybe some do it a little
bit better than the others i would like i would have loved it if it was like this one is all
attributes this one is you do more damage but take more damage this one is your fp uh the
cost spell costs are cut in half or something right these all kind of feel way too similar
they're just talismans for that these feel very similar like that raises max hp fp and stamina
raises max hp it's like why would you use this one i feel like they keep getting slowly worse
unless that's an insane amount you get to choose what an ember does
yeah i mean it's it's it's cool but i think that's the i think that part of the game for me is
feels the like the least kind of interesting it's not that much of a complaint though considering
your health bar will cover the entire screen well that's cool um we can keep going is there
anything else here that i need to see or is that it you sometimes these towers have weird shit in
them mog is here mog is not here yeah you have to use the rune arc i just have i'm just not using
them what does he hate this game because it was hyped up and i all the hype fucking failed man
like look i mean look at how big this map is it's annoying it's annoying it's like too much
it's like too much stuff to see they should have just had it like be this area here and
like this is dlc and shit like this is just like fucking stupid all this up here is just like i
don't know it's like a waste of time they could have like condensed this and made it like limb
grave and caitlin and that would have been much better like hyped up fucking hype is so dumb
all right let me rest here yeah you're you're you're going this is why like game design is so
fucking stupid you expect me as a player to go like walk from here if like and eventually go
like spend all the time to go all the way up here i just don't i don't understand where like where
the time they think they think we have the time for this it's way too far i'm just spending these
ruins oh this is cool why don't they let you just buy ruins with money i know it's like what if i
don't fucking want to get ruins i should be able to spend 9.99 and get like you know 30 40 000 souls
that was awful this should be loot boxes you just open up to get armor the move is okay is this
seriously elden bucks let me actually go down here is there a map fragment yet no not quite
you have a horse i know but i don't want to just like this is a cool area i don't want to
just run around and forget i don't want to just fucking forget where i'm not seeing anything and
miss everything i would have missed that if i got on the horse this is this game just reminds me
when video games would just fucking video games video games are just allowed to be video games
that was it i love how i've turned for you guys like the boston accent guy into things that like
i'm allowed to kind of come out of my like i can just say whatever i want as that voice that
character and it's universally despised anything i say so it's like i don't know it's kind of like
kind of relieving and almost like liberating in a way that i can just fucking go like this and say
whatever i fucking want and like we all know it's not real and we can all it doesn't matter i can
say anything i don't know why it has to be like the boston guy with the cigarette outside of a cvs
like i don't know why it has to be that guy like i don't know why that person in my brain has a
tank top a cigarette short sandals sitting outside of a cvs with a gatorade in the other hand
and like you're walking into the cvs and he's just like i fucking i don't know why that you
can't just buy fucking rooms with money like all right yeah all right man like i don't know why
that's who i see that's what happens i don't know why that's that's how i feel what would happen
and you just go you go into the cvs and then you leave and that guy just kind of shows up
everywhere in random places you know like that that guy you could be at line at the deli and
he'll just turn around and he still has cigarette in his hand by the way and like they haven't
thrown him out yet he's like damn i wish they were fucking two drive-throughs three drive-through
windows instead of one at like every restaurant all right dude like okay it's just like a bot
the boston npc guy you just you could just say pretty much whatever you want as boston
like gta character and that's it and here this way okay why is the tank top gas station cigarette
boston guy invested in elden ring i don't know he just he's invested in everything and he would
always be like like it would always be after the after he sucks it in right like hey what's up man
see the price of bitcoin like he would talk when it was in his lungs and then you would see it
trailing out slow like it that there's a person that just lives in my head completely rent-free
it just does it all right easy easy easy
don't you think they should fucking decentralize cbs this is my god what the
fuck are you talking about yeah i don't know man it's fucking i think they fucking should
i'm not gonna lose those souls don't worry i gotta be careful that's it i gotta jump though
let's jump i don't even need to fight these things just move but i will you okay fuck you
what is even hitting me that hard it's making that happen uh that's a thousand damage it it
it hits more than once damn that's crazy okay and this is this is the end game theater so that it's
not like i'm over level this is like a 100 to 110 plus zone isn't it just a crazy fucking move
who cares little weenies leave me alone somebody asked why i wasn't using mana before
because i have the flask of wondrous physique uh i have a tear in there which means i consume
no fp when i cast spells for about 15 seconds it's not gonna close the teeth aren't gonna close
right what do i feel like the teeth are getting the mouth is gonna close on me that's a crunchy
i'll take it i believe this is a fly yeah i think i have five now i'll have 13 14 no don't let that
get away oh it's just so that was not a bonfire i thought it was wasn't there i feel like i saw
one what was it i think it was just a glow from the uh was it just a glow from the mouth
am i crazy or is there one over here it was a glow from the seed yeah yeah yeah ow
oh it's 69k how does he look like that because my parents combined forces and they made this face
okay if you have a problem with it then i don't know what to tell you sorry sorry that like god
mushed his thumbs in like here here here and like here okay i i didn't do that you should fix it
board he didn't even hit anybody jesus man you i think he's gotta run from that shit huh
all right we're going traditional did one of the boys just stagger him was that me jesus that just
did almost 100 percent of my health bar jesus yes god that move is good gargoyles black blades
and black axe honestly man that that does a thousand damage if you do if you do the double
tap close that's an unbelievable move the boys actually helped a lot there too and my axe and
my bum and my bum and my bum wait keep looking around a lot of you guys said that the boys were
going to be a mistake uh leveling up plus 10 they've been pretty good they actually have been
really good yeah yeah they're really good they're actually they're annoying to deal with there's a
lot of them too five people it's kind of just sponges in a way i was getting hit by for a lot
of damage though that was a lot one swing from that uh almost killed me in one hit so is this
the stage of the from software games where we all do a ton of damage and we're all just going to
kill each other in like three hits two hits down here looks like i can go down there yeah oh my
god i have 130 000 souls you're right that'd be a bad idea just check the other side real quick
oh i thought it was a dungeon promising oh well wait is that even worth doing i could have just
walked in the front door yeah i could have just walked it and i and i missed this cool like misty
area oh butterflies was very well looks like silent hill it kind of does doesn't it
shit all right uh i said i was gonna alternate between right i'm gonna get to 60 intelligence
so i can go get the remembrance and get the staff and maybe play around with it what's your favorite
pokemon um
that's the only one i could think of that was it's just trophies smash brothers
to such a task how come i have i can't just be my thing
watch your tone here you're about to get r1ed one the one warning i'm gonna give you
okay so is there a grand lift of rolled oh shit there's one right here market
voice medallion what medallion is that the grand lift of dectus medallion
i was from uh morgan okay
how far am i into the game uh i'd say pretty far this is the last zone i believe of the game
although i don't know if that's 100 accurate i do know that it is probably the last area that i can
walk to i'm getting pepe left oh i guess oh what was that oh i guess that's what was happening
i guess that's wrong damn yeah very cool very cool i like this area because it makes me feel
like john snow on tops of the giants other what's with what's with these trees are these like phantom
trees stop stalling dude i do i really have to tell you that like once in a decade a game like
this will come around i'm gonna look around for a sec mog has the same voice actor as frog detective
frog detective didn't have a voice oh wait yeah wait i see you scared the shit out of me what
happened can i go down there who's somebody dying i can go i can do that let me get the map fragment
first it's like right here somewhere isn't it the giants west ruins right here new mog
no i'm i don't know what that means oh hey i remember you it's for his flesh he gave it to me
what to sacrifice something precious it died so that your ascendancy requires her sacrifice
whether she wishes it or not also chosen tarnished spare and sings your own flesh in her stead
if you are prepared to show resolve and attain lordship through righteous hardship
then the heads of i shall be who the fuck are you and what happened to the guy that came in and
helped me it's a different person what how did how did you do that three fingers
two fingers where's the thumb where are the thumb cultists
deep beneath the capital
who's the faction that just wants to like sit on the beach and drink it like a margarita
what is that one what's the faction where it's just like let's just relax
and like enjoy the sunshine and like drink some mead i don't burn the tree consult with the two
fingers consult with the thumb consult with the index finger consult oh tarnished consult consult
with the big toe of of absolution i okay that was i guess i um okay i appreciate the help i guess
i'm gonna go in these rooms consult with the middle finger tarnished
consult with middle finger the rude oh it's just like what the fuck happened what was that
what happened what are you doing oh no cold versus cold good thing i still got the baby
rattle which is magic damage didn't get you you're losing to a goomba you all right there's
definitely there's definitely you look like a mushroom it's a special hat look for a place
to go in there's a lot of these like spectral animals right down in the the um seo for there
was all these spectral ghost deer and stuff well i'm what's what's the deal with that
let's what's the deal what's going on there really nothing in here saying it wrong she
i'd see all from whatever that's just a regular enemy holy shit those guys are crazy
some more ice storm oh don't make me just do cold sorcery all right these guys i should not be
fighting this many of these guys i gotta find the entrance to this dungeon because it definitely
exists right here is it a dungeon or no it has to be 73 degrees yes
yes smithing stone i'm sorry smithing stones miners bell bearing three oh that's actually a
big deal that's getting old uh you should ask my mother um how many times i like repeated old
cartoon like lines over and over again like hundreds of thousands of fucking times i can't
leave get me out of here let me out jeez okay can i get out of here now please what was in that
chest oh the smithing stone bell bearing guy are you roger from american dad you mean like the way
i look here or the way i look at there like that character or this person here that's it for that
place i'm gonna go over there holy shit okay i'm good i should use the mog key item please go to
bed for the love of mog i've been living in this room for like four and a half hours i'm fine all
right i want to go let me go back this way because i want to go up here let me check that spell too
it's 28 oh my it is late let me just let me get to like a let me get to like five or six hours
need to get that's so high up how am i gonna get up there check the notes you know what we
haven't done that in a long time uh i wonder what the notes say now door next to spawn is blocked
shut okay prawn guy says piss off to me he's at the prawn shack find nepheli for the potion quest
gold needle from the deep swamp of scarlet swamp what i feel these are very outdated he's very old
at the very bottom of lendell frenzied flame lord oh that's what that guy was just talking about
that's the he's like go consult with the three fingers
oh find mog that those notes are from an abandoned insane asylum mog key is fun i promise you're
missing out i'm gonna i don't want to use it and have something happen that's bad
whole body hurts why are you even attacking me
me holy shit that's much they buffed the hell out of that yeah you knocked me all the way down here
annoying i think i can get up there though dungeon over here like over here somewhere but
mog waiting room i'm not gonna use the mog item i'm not gonna but i will tell you that i am gonna
turn the stream off shortly probably in the next 30 minutes maybe are you drinking more matcha
yeah i am this is green tea though it's not green tea has not very much caffeine although
this stuff might have some more this is great it's green tea man don't worry fucking sages drink
drank this shit like 5000 years ago every single day every moment of every day so i'm fine like
20 000 30 000 years ago grands just sages were drinking this stuff my god i'm gonna fucking walk
push me away from you nothing even up here this is this
that looks dangerous i'm supposed to cross that i'm not doing that yet out of all the people that
type auto you didn't read any of them i talked about auto but that i promised that he was going
to be on stream and he's not here yeah i did that too he'll show up don't i promise i'm hungry
i wonder what i should eat can i actually get up there anywhere from here
how do i get up here maybe i can turn around from over here hey what's with the lag
i thought they fixed that we miss him don't i'll show i don't he's doing good he's doing okay
that's the zenith sash and i still i just i can't say that fucking word riders of punishment
i gotta see those spells i have to get another uh flask as well it's a sorcery no it's not
but why is it in the sorcery's list wounds caster to unleash trail of bloodthorns why is
this in the sorcery list if it's no intelligence you have to cast it with a staff that's weird
trail of bloodthorns running over the ground to impale enemies from below
an aberrant sorcery discovered by exiled criminals theirs are the sorcery's most reviled by the
academy okay wait i got another one too where is it this ice sorcery strike the ground with
a staff to create a freezing tornado charging enhances potency cloaked in icy tempests the
knights of zamor have challenged the fire giant since ancient times any good we'll try it it's
good i'll uh i'll try it i feel like i don't want to be on the horse race what what night comment
let's try it oh my god that fucking hurt a lot all right let's go you after dodging
that many fucking times oh my god dude jesus that whip is probably available they've had a i there's
seven or eight whips in the game they added way more whips all right i gotta be careful because
this is a potential disaster here i don't think i want to do this on torrent but you know it's
probably what i need to do all right be careful this is really really beautiful though don't go
that fast there's no reason to no reason to do that how would you have been a chair out here
you're just gonna bring like a chair out here at least you don't i don't think you want to be
sitting oh he's got a bow and arrow all right i'm safe right here for now at least for now
let's try dodge through it i just try to dash through it what's over here a golden ruin
oh all right i'm fine what are you doing i don't want to get hit by the bow and arrow man
he's i was trying to be like we're gonna radix so he wouldn't hit me with it
i thought he was further back oh my god damn it dude i'm killing this motherfucker right now
you're not gonna shoot the literal ground are you oh please you don't have that much gas coming off
now i can like at least take a look around and see if there's anything i don't want to miss
i'm standing on something what was it 13 oh okay so was there anything else on the bridge
that i missed in my freak out did i miss anything here i don't think so okay so we're coming up to
this poslow person and then this is that is that her tree let's go take a look all right i'm
i think it might be time to call it soon here like really really soon like next bonfire soon
i think i have to call it it's getting late i just felt like playing and i felt like streaming it
this area is really cool though i like this place a lot that's good because i think i actually need
one of those go that way too oh let me get that how far down is that i ain't i ain't going down
there so let's head towards two and five who is up to fight poslow five is that kind of
urtree looking thing you show auto i'll show it on like a next stream or so i don't know
you jumped that maybe i have too many souls to try to find out to that last stream yeah but i
will i promise you'll see him soon i promise all right there's the bonfire all right we're
at a we're at almost 12 30 pacific we're almost at 3 a.m eastern so let's all right all right that's
it that's it i'm done that's it i don't want to go too too much longer uh tomorrow's tuesday
i wonder what should i stream tomorrow i don't think so i don't think so tomorrow i want to
say maybe thursday we'll do like thursday friday tomorrow's wednesday technically yeah
so we'll do wait hold on tomorrow's tomorrow's tuesday which tonight today is tuesday so we'll
do we'll go thursday thursday probably thursday friday i might break it up a little bit we
probably won't do elden ring the whole time but we will for most of it i might go back and do some
doth stuff i haven't done that in a long time thursday four o'clock pacific friday four o'clock
pacific same time same time we uh usually start for this was just kind of impromptu i was supposed
to stream tomorrow which is technically today but i just had the craving i had to play i think we
made some pretty good progress i mean i got pretty far i think this is still a lot to do over here
and probably even back here too i also maybe want to go back to the sewer because he was like oh
converse with the three fingers three fingers two fingers it's a hand right like that makes sense
doesn't it why would there be two fingers and three fingers was it the same hand whose hand
is that why is there two hands is more than two hands like somebody have two hands like some
giant god or something uh we'll go back to it i'll see you guys on thursday i all right let me ask
you a question can we do a poll real quick in chat uh would you rather break it up on thursday
or break it up on friday you want elden ring on thursday or elden ring on friday which what would
you prefer wait uh we have three options elden ring thursday elden ring friday wait do the poll
again i'm sorry i'm an idiot elden ring thursday elden ring friday or don't break it up just go
baby what that means is i'm not going to play a different game i'm just going to do this sorry
mods if you by the way if you if you pick let's go baby your implant you're saying that you don't
want anything else besides elden ring at least for the rest of this week oh okay that's a lot
that's 85 percent of you don't want this to stop yeah i was once in a generation event i whatever
i'm getting close i'm getting close i can't promise that i'm gonna what here's what i do want to do
once the game is completed once i have no nothing else really i really want to do there's a lot of
secrets and a lot of other stuff i haven't explored that i'm not going to do but i want to do i want
to do like a pvp night where we have a password on it and we just kind of like i did with dark
souls 3 remember like just there was summoning signs literally everywhere and i was just picking
up random people i think that'd be fun we did that before so i imagine one of these streams when i'm
done with the game will be pvp slash summoning kind of stuff i think it was fun you also need
to do a me strong run we'll figure that out too i mean i am an elden ring content creator at this
point right i haven't played this game for a month this game came out a month ago you guys think
about that i have played elden ring and mario golf in the last month oh i did play pit cross
and brain age that's right all right i'll see you guys on um see you guys on thursday for more
elden ring thanks for watching thanks for the subs as always i know i don't really read them
i don't read any of the sub messages or bit messages or anything but we appreciate it one
stream a week that's not true besides the last six or seven days i've i've been streaming like
four times a week with elden ring before the streamer awards i was live like four or five
times in a row and stream two i'm gonna go thursday friday yeah this is like four i'm
going like four or five times a week with elden ring is when i'm here what guys it's a once in a
generation event yeah uh take care of yourselves i'll see you guys on thursday get some sleep
thanks for staying up hopefully didn't stay up too late some of you may have this on right now
uh on an ipad that's right next to you in bed with you flat on its back just playing
and i i'm just still on hopefully have a good rest hopefully you wake up well rested and um may
may health and wealth bless you and may you get the things that you most uh desire in your you
know personal life then may um may you continue to move forward i'm doing the cheers to you thing
right now i want to thank you you go the extra mile now see you guys later thanks for watching
take care see you thursday