Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a live TF2 gameplay commentary, but before the live commentary kicks in, as you see by the title of this video, 25,000 subscribers. Thank you all so, so much. You guys all rock and freaking roll, dude.
So what does that mean? That means now I have to pick three people from my Twitter to get 33% of my entire backpack. I have just done that. So please, please go check your Twitter mentions right now, because I just mentioned three people.
And if that's you, if you're one of those people, please direct message me on Twitter, not on Facebook, not on YouTube. Only send me a direct message on Twitter. And in that message, please include your Steam ID. I need that. That's like the most important thing in this whole thing.
But yeah, congratulations to the winners, guys. And my other announcement for 25,000 subs is guys, I'm finally going to get a TF2 server and it's going to actually work. There's going to be people behind it that know what they're doing. So look forward to that. Hopefully we can have some good times on there because I know I had the last server I had was a real, a real mess. And hopefully this time around that will not happen.
But yeah, thank you so much, everybody. You guys are all amazing. I love every single one of you guys. Thank you for subscribing. Thank you for supporting the channel. And yeah, those of you that won, enjoy my goddamn backpack.
So here comes a live commentary, guys. I had some fun with Italics, Boo Man 61, and of course, MLC Stealth. So I hope you enjoy the video, guys. And as data trickles in on this new TF2 server I'm getting, I will absolutely let you guys know the second I get new info. So yeah, I'll see you guys all next time and take care, everybody.
No, you meant to say boo. Oh, that's what man 61. I hear he's much cooler. Oh, what'd you hear that? I'm on blue. Yeah. Are you really? Oh, no, I don't know what everyone's special steam name is on here. I'm German. Yeah, that's gonna confuse so many people.
Like, wait, why is this guy? What's this? So wait, okay, which one am I? That's like the real mine's already highlighted. Nevermind.
Who's demo night war interrupted by a scout?
So boo, who are you on blue? Oh, I'm flat 2012. Feel like I'm making a Dr. Seuss poem right there.
Boo, who are you on blue? Oh, I'm Flump. See that to me that sounds like like a like a Disney movie. Like see Flump and his friends.
The new Disney Pixar. Flump 2012. Coming soon to HD DVD. Oh God. I'm just kidding. Oh, that was you.
Pixar presents Flump and Cole. Can I just tell you, it just said Jerma and Bungo killed somebody, but it was lit up right on my screen.
So I really just thought that's confusing the hell out of me. Oh, look, there I am.
Oh, jeez, that's so funny. God.
Let's just switch all of our names around. Oh, there we go. Or maybe demo night, not the best.
I'm doing horrible too. Oh, don't let him get the help. Hey, Jerma, don't let him get the help.
Wait, what team is there? Like what team is there? Jerma, are you on my team? Me and you are on the same team.
And then me and me and Boo. We're both, we're both demo, demo men. Oh God, I have no idea.
You guys have like four sentries and we need to blow them the fuck up. Hey, I think we're all demo men.
We're just different forms of demo men.
What is this guy doing? Oh God. Oh, get destroyed.
I'm so scared of that Huntsman sniper. I really am. Whoa. There goes the teleporter. Hi Bungo.
Oh, hey Jerma. Oh, jeez. I just charged right into it. And there goes the sentry gun.
Don't worry, there's only like another two. Yeah. Oh my God. We really do have so many sentry guns. It's a joke.
It's a joke. Even worse news is that I've managed to switch team to red.
Really? Come on. Everyone versus Alex.
Hey, I found another crate. Oh, oh God. Oh, I need to open mine live on television.
Okay, here we go. Oh, that scout is dead.
Come on. Yes, I do have 20 crates now for anyone interested. Hell yeah. I'm going to open mine though.
I'm going to open mine though. Hey, will you stop talking in the chat as me?
All right, fine. I'm jumping on the bandwagon.
What is this heavy doing? Oh my gosh, hold on. I'm lagging super duper good right now.
I'm about to critscreeing both of you snipers over here. Oh my God, you got the ubered.
Oh wait, this is a regular one. I thought I had critscreeing out. Oh my God, I have the Huntsman right now.
You pretty much just ubered like a stack of hay.
There was a heavy back there, but he was just standing around not doing anything.
So I was like, forget them. I'm going to uber this sniper out here. Watch out for the scout.
No, you scout bastard.
There's like a floating tank. What is this? Oh, come on, push the cart, Jerma.
Oh, Peepa's helping push the cart. Oh, look who's on our team, Shibby2012.
Shibby, if you're watching, I'm so sorry about this.
Shibby2012. I can't even say it. My brain doesn't work.
Oh, I just hit the cart. Maybe we can make a roll out of this, huh?
Oh yeah. Maybe. Watch out for spies.
Watch out for spies. We got two heavies out here and two medics.
Jerma and Shibby just got a kill plus assist.
Watch out. Watch out on the right. Watch out on the right.
I can't even hit this guy. Oh, he's dead.
Sentry. Oh no, I missed. No.
Oh, I didn't kill that sentry. Come on, heavies, take them down.
Oh my God, look how many people we have on this sentry.
There's a lot.
Oh my God, I'm killing everyone. Good Lord.
And we managed to take them down steamrolling the competition.
That was unbelievable, dude.
Did you guys do something amazing?
Good job, Shibs.
Oh, you're going to get smashed. Oh, he's got the, never mind.
Spencer. No. Oh, Jerma stole the kill.
Jerma. I stole everything.
I'm trying to give you guys like healing prep rolls, but I can't keep track of who's who.
How did I miss him?
Wait, heal Jerma right now.
There we go. Oh, crit rocket. Come on.
Come on. Oh no, like six heads.
Oh, and spied in the back.
Oh, he's trying to spy me too.
Spied, spied.
I got switched.
Oh no.
Shibs on the other team.
Auto balance servers for the loss.
In the title of this video, it should be like, oh, like TF2 with MLC stealth, italics, boo man, and Shibby 2012.
Oh, can I just tell you right now, dude, I keep thinking you're a spy.
I keep checking you and oh my God.
Like every time I see you, I'm guaranteeing myself that you are a spy.
Oh wait, that's not me. Oh wait.
Oh no.
So funny.
I think we're going to win.
Are we going to win? Oh no.
Is this going to happen?
Jumping around like a prof.
Flying out of nowhere.
All right.
Shibby.
Yeah, I'm on blue.
Are you going to get it?
Coming down the stairs.
Shibby.
No.
Push it.
Oh no.
I don't want to be here when it blows up.
I fell down the pipe.
Oh yeah.
That should not even count as a kill for you, boo.
You didn't kill me.
You brought me on me and I committed suicide.
At least I made it onto the top of the scoreboard twice.
As two different accounts.