I don't know. I don't know if I like that. No, there's something wrong here. There's
something wrong. It's the elephant. It's not, I know elephant. It's got to be something
else. Giraffe. Now that's what I'm talking about. That is the perfect animal. Yeah. Hey,
what are you doing over here? Click on him and look at his name. What is that? Look at
its name. Do you remember in real life? XD. What is that? Is that a hippopotamus gorilla?
Yeah. No. Get out of here. This is a giraffe. Skunk turf. Get the fuck out of here. I don't
think you could have hurt him. Can I not kill this? Get out of here. He's too awesome. Come
help me long guy. I need help from long guy. What do you mean long guy? Is that a dachshund?
Ready boss. You're the boss. No building is up. Somebody's cheating. Building's done. Oh,
really? Thanks for the heads up. No. Stop. Just stay here. Just stay here.
Can I do anything? Can I do any funny moves? Where are my funny moves?
One of these times you're going to spawn there and it's going to kill you.
That's not fair. No, it's really not. And what the hell are you two doing?
You're supposed to be guarding the perimeter. Kill him. No, kill him. Kill the disappearing
shark shithead. He's dead. No, you got him. I did not kill him. He is very much alive.
See, I told you he was alive. Okay, nice. How am I supposed to win? I can't. Stop. Let them
have a fight. You're not supposed to just let them die. That was all the fight I had.
The Quillers are under attack. Come on. What is that thing? What? You don't like,
you don't appreciate the meta. What meta? The overlord scouting meta. I don't think I understand
this joke. That's a whale bee. What is the overlord? No, he's like a zerg. You send your overlord out
to scout first. I didn't play Starcraft. I don't play Starcraft. I have not played Starcraft enough
to know what that is. I think everyone who has ever played a video game at the very least knows
what a fucking zerg rush is. Yeah. Well, that's not. Here comes my zerglings. I wasn't even ready.
Come on. Okay. All right. Okay. All right. Your overarching theme. I get it. You're doing a
Starcraft thing with your turtle bugs. That's really great. It is really great. Get the fuck
out of here. Get this thing and get your overlord and fucking stuff it up your ass.
He says he's coming with himself. We have plenty of units. We have the strangest animal
the whole time. Those people. I love how my, they're not even attacking. Attack them. Kill them.
Kill the people. This is so shit. The Quillers are under attack. The Quillers are under attack.
We're not going to win. We're not going to win. Steal their coal. Steal the coal. Get out of here.
Get the coal. Come on, snake. Spit it out. Spit it out, snake. No. Start mining. Start mining.
Everyone mine it. I would have figured these guys would be dead way longer ago.
They are getting eaten by giant crocodile bears. He's getting out with the coal. Where are all the
sound effects? We're taking this into the base. We are taking this shit into the base after you
kill them, Darren. Go for it, Darren. The fights in this are so anticlimactic. Kill them all, Darren.
That's right. Who is Darren? Very good, Darren. Very good job, Darren. You thought you could
mess with the Darons. You thought for one second you could fuck with the Darons. I didn't think I
could. Come on, Darren. You've got this, Darren. He thinks he can beat us with his beaver praying
Manchester. Does he know who you are? You're fucking Darren. No. Darren. For centuries. I don't know
how to start this. How do you start this? I don't know. What are we fighting for? I would like to
speak with your leader. Yes. The other leader. The other one. We have plenty of leaders.
When one goes down, the other will take his place. I need at least one. There's another one right
here. There's another leader. Would you like to see a new one? This is also a leader.
Yeah, see, one of your guys we caught the other day, he was on our sand and we agreed that was ours.
We had a treaty 2,000 years ago, your people and our people, that this bridge shall never be
crossed unless for diplomatic reasons. We're crossing it right now. We caught one of your...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. We did not cross the bridge. What are you going to do about it?
What are you going to do about it? That is an act of war. That is an act. You back up or that is an act of
war. What did you say? Nuclear transform. I don't know.