Hello. Good afternoon. And for some of you, good evening. Good morrow, maybe for a handful of you
as well. Yeah, uh, stream was scheduled for tomorrow, but like all things, sometimes you can
move stuff around and decided I was gonna stream today. Would you look at that? Nice EU time.
Uh, four, let's see, five, six, three, like fifty, three, thirty, three, zero, four, five, six, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven. It's like 1130 EU, right? Nice game name that I didn't name it. All right,
daylight savings time too. I hate that. There's nothing worse than sitting on your computer,
just getting shit done. And it's you're up a little too late and you know that. And it's
1230 AM, one AM. And you're like, I still, it's all right. I still get to one AM. You go up to
go to the bathroom. You come back and all of a sudden it's three AM. What, how, what happened?
No, this is not fair. This is not fair at all. I gotta, I have to, no, I have work to do. And
then you have to force yourself to go to sleep. And that sucks always because you're sitting there
lying like toy soldier style in the bed, closing your eyes, squeezing them, going like,
fuck daylight savings time. Oh, I'm, I'm well aware, especially for school too.
When I was in college, hated it. It was the worst thing ever. You'd be sitting there looking at
your phone or something or hanging out on your computer and it would just teleport an hour
forward. And it just screws you up for like a week. But regardless, happy daylight savings.
Today we're going to play Seaman. Does the microphone work? I don't know because,
well, it knows it exists. I loaded the game up and it said, please put, uh, this is Leonard
Nimoy, by the way, is the voice of Seaman and the narrator as well. So it did recognize that
it was in there. I don't know if it works because I really didn't want to jump into it unless we
were all here. And that's five computer subs from Hot Take Alert. Thanks for the five subs,
Hot Take. So this is what we're doing today. I don't know how long this is going to be.
We'll find out. I'm ready to close the lid and get going. I bought a counterfeit Seaman mic.
I don't think that's possible. Is that possible? You can't buy a fake one. Can you?
I don't think you can. Let's close the lid. Let me get this over here.
Hey, you've seen that familiar face before, haven't you? That is the Dreamcast. All right.
Seaman, here we go. So just to give everybody a little intro here as to what the fuck is even
going on. This, this is the Dreamcast controller as you see, right? Only difference is this time
there's a little thing on it. This thing right here. I have to speak into this to talk to the
Seaman. And I owned this game when I was younger, but I was too young to understand what the fuck
was going on and how I was supposed to play it in the first place. So I got bored because
I think I said like, hello, three or four times and realized it wasn't like a fun,
like welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset. Hold on. You'll witness before you a
phenomenon like no other. A man of the sea. Seaman, this legendary creature will be dependent on you
for his life's blood. You'll begin right here in Gasset's laboratory. What awaits you within?
You have no idea what Seaman is or how it evolves. This is something you must find out for yourself
as there's little documentation to help you on your way. My name is Leonard Nimoy and I will be
your guide. Well, this is your first day with the Seaman kit. Your first step will involve preparing
the tank for Seaman's arrival. Adjust the tank settings to be an adequate temperature with
sufficient oxygen. While adjusting, keep in mind that blue is the color of the sea and thus an
appropriate color for the care of Seaman. Then take the egg from the storage matrix and place it in the
tank. Okay. The water's temperature is key to the hatching of the egg. So we have to hatch an egg
first. Once hatched, the nautilus will play a very important role in Seaman's development.
Each time you visit this laboratory, I'll be here to offer advice and guidance. If you tire of my
voice... By the way, it's kind of hard to pay attention because of the fucking deli slicer over
here next to me. Very well. I completely forgot about the deli slicer. As you see, press start.
What's he saying? Oh, look at this calm game where you make a creature. That's like all I
hear over here and I buried this. This is not even on my desk. The Dreamcast is over here,
down on the ground. Does it give a turn of garbage disposal on with a fork in it? That's what it
sounds like when you play with the Dreamcast. Don't be careful, by the way. That's dangerous.
Don't even use your garbage disposal. It's fucking scary. Think of how many horror movies you've
seen where the guy reaches in and... Don't ever have a garbage disposal. Just clean your plate
in the trash. All right. So this is Seaman. We have our hand here. I think we have to get the
temperature and the temperature has to be raised. Turn the lights on. Okay, here we go. So left
trigger. Here's the egg. Food pellets. We have to feed it. Use voice. There's nothing here to use my
voice yet. Hello? No, there's no animal. This is the thing that they tell you not to do at every pet
store. All right, let's put the egg. I need lights. The nautilus, right? Use the nautilus.
There's a camera. This is the one problem with not having any manual to know. Wait a minute,
I do have the manual. Got it. Welcome to Dr. Gassa's live laboratory. Thank you for purchasing
the Seaman kit. Please note this software is designed only for use with the Dreamcast
console. Do not put this in a PlayStation. Why would you do that? This package contains
a Seaman habitat and one Seaman egg. Thank God I have this. Seriously. To begin with, let's learn
a bit about Seaman, shall we? Historical references to Seaman first appeared in the spoken folklore of
ancient Egypt, passed down from generation to generation. Until recently, it was assumed that
the Seaman creature did not actually exist, similar to many other mythical creatures of ancient
Egypt. However, in 1997, the discovery of a live Seaman in the Egyptian city of old Alexandria
disproved this assumption, and Seaman can't be known as the world over. While the originally
discovered Seaman specimen died shortly after being captured, its remains were quickly rushed
to the foremost biologist research institute in France, where a number of eggs were discovered
inside its body. We at Vivarium were then able to assist in the endeavor by covering the research
and development costs in return for the sole distribution of rights that have enabled us to
this product to you. There he is.
No, that's not what it says.
Welcome. Okay. A memory card is required.
Should I read this whole thing? I mean, look, this was like a fucking hundred bucks.
I'm reading the whole thing. It was 80 fucking bucks for this microphone, and the disc was like
28. I'm reading it. I'm milking this stream for all it's got.
Dr. Jean-Paul Gasset. Dr. Gasset was a member of a special team of French biologists
dispatched to Egypt by the French government in the 1930s when he discovered references to a
creature dubbed the Omnipotent Messenger of the Gods. Among ruins of the third dynasty,
he became determined to pursue this line of research and unravel the mystery.
In March of 1932 in the city of Alexandria, Dr. Gasset happened to meet up with a local resident
who had caught a seaman while fishing. Dr. Gasset obtained a sample of some of the eggs,
which he carried back with him to France. When Dr. Gasset returned, he immediately attempted to
raise the seaman eggs in his Parisian laboratory, but unfortunately in the midst of his experiment,
the seaman died. Dead. The seaman died. Shortly thereafter, Dr. Gasset published a detailed thesis
of his work. He didn't do very well. He brought, you put him in a backpack and they died.
You're gonna write about it now? Oh, I'm not like, oh let me, hold on a minute there. There we go.
Uh, let's see. However, after leading academics of the day,
dismissed the young scholar's work as a publicity stunt and without the proper evidence,
e.g. a living specimen. To support his theories, his work was shunned and no one believed him.
Dr. Gasset's hypothesis suggested that seaman was perhaps responsible for transferring knowledge
that proliferated during the third dynasty across oceans to other lands. This theory
eventually became the basis for it. Anthro bioarchaeology, a highly valued field of study
today. Soon after the publication of his thesis, Dr. Gasset was dismissed from his post. He then
disappeared for quite some time. Recently a dire, I don't know, I don't need to read the rest. He
like genetically put his fucking brain in the fish and that's who you talk to. I figured it out.
He like, he is the fish. Guaranteed. Continued research to unravel the details of seaman's
evolution. For further details kindly refer to the following website. I don't think this website
still works. It's www.meetseaman.com. I would highly recommend you don't do that website considering
the potential pornographic consequences because it definitely doesn't exist anymore.
All right, here we go. Before starting a game, this is the first things first reality check.
Seaman is a one player game. So once you begin raising seaman, you're expected to assume complete
responsibility for the care and upbringing of a living breathing creature. So before you begin
with the initial setup procedure, you are strongly recommended to double check with yourself that you
are mentally prepared to assume this important responsibility. It's not like buying it. It's not
like owning a dog or cat. This is the conversation. Okay, this is the mom. This booklet is the mom and
I'm the kid and I just said I wanted a kitty and it's given me the whole, okay, well remember
you've got to take care of this cat. Are you, are you ready for that? You have to clean its
litter box and it's like, yeah, yeah, I will. God. The first step you must take in preparation
is set up with the required equipment. At this time, should you experience any tension related
symptoms such as heart palpitations, perspiration, etc. Resulting from the sheer weight of the
responsibility for rearing a seaman. You may wish to loosen up a bit by stretching or taking a bit
of exercise. Once you are sufficiently relaxed, you are ready to begin. Do not turn the power of
the dream cast on yet. Says it right there. Do you see? Do not turn the power of the dream cast on.
Whatever, we already did it. It's too late. Okay, got the memory card in, got the micro. As seaman
matures, there will come a time when it will begin to converse with you. A microphone has been
included in this package for the express purposes of speaking to your seaman. Whenever you wish to
play with your seaman, always be sure to insert the microphone into expansion socket two.
No, the VMU must be inserted into expansion socket one. The seaman software will not run
if these two devices are not correctly inserted in the right slots. All right, so how do I play?
Got it. Creating a seaman habitat. Put that down for now. Oh, don't break. Just buy the domain
already. Just buy, wait, buy the seaman domain? Buy the seaman domain and just have it be a
fucking picture of this. How much is that? No, I'm not doing that shit. All right, maybe I'll do it.
All right, creating a seaman habitat. Memory card file, got it. Yep, okay, let's figure this out.
Here we go. Do you see what that says? That says mental preparation. Mental preparation.
The most fundamental requirement for successfully raising seaman is daily care and maintenance.
At the very least, you are kindly requested to attend to various custodial tasks such as providing
oxygen, water, food, cleaning, etc. on a daily basis, just as with a daily exercise program.
It is important that you participate each and every day without fail. This concept is a
prerequisite for being a guardian to seaman. Seaman is a game in which you will experience
the growth of a living being. You will witness the drama of life over an extended period of time.
Therefore, you do not expect an experience similar to any other games in which clearly defined
events happen each time you play. This is like 1998. They figured this out.
Neopets figured this out in like 2006, don't worry. This is not the type of game in which
one can spend several hours in one sitting and expect to experience vast amounts of action or
change. As with life itself, change only occurs over time and even then slowly. Change is only
evident through the accumulation of experience over time, aka do not stream this game. You wasted
a hundred dollars, idiot. Enjoy communicating with seaman while you attend to these daily
maintenance tasks. Tap on the glass of the aquarium to get its attention. Use the microphone to greet
and converse as well as other methods you will discover in order to express your affection to
it. This is paramount to ensuring the successful growth and development of your seaman. As seaman
matures and reaches a certain level of development, recognition will increase and it will begin
conversing with you. I have to stream this every day. A daily stream. Seaman's development will
accelerate when in good humor. The only way to ensure seaman is kept in good humor is to take
adequate care of it daily without fail while constantly providing loving affection. Although
raising seaman does require a bit of perseverance, it is a bit like writing in a diary. Just set the
date forward one day. Just cheat. Should I just make my internal clock like 2040? No, I have to
go every day. I'm gonna have to turn off the console and go and change the clock every day.
We're gonna we're gonna be like four weeks. Oh this is gonna be a pain in the ass.
Although raising seaman does require a bit of perseverance, it is a bit like writing in a
diary. Something you need to persist in doing on a daily basis. By doing so, you will find yourself
experiencing a grand drama the likes of which have yet been rendered possible by even the most
realistic of computer or console games. For those of you with time to spare, one highly recommended
and interesting method for enjoying your time with seaman is to darken the lights into your room and
simply vegetate while watching your seaman go about daily life. Similar to a typical aquarium,
what about working or school? This is encouraging you to literally not go to work,
not go to school, and sit there and vegetate it says all day. Seaman will provide completely
different and ever-changing scenery for your television set and for as long as seaman lives
the show will go on. Let's begin. That's so that's weird. Were you expected just to have it on,
turned on all day? Here we go. Transfer the egg into the tank. All right, I'm ready.
Here we go. Subsequent, we've got here are the operations. Here we go. Ready? This is if I if I
didn't have this book, I would be fucked. Thank God the people that I bought this from. It wasn't
just like a jewel case. This game sounds like shitty SCP. Relax. All right, operation day one.
I'm ready. Hello. Once again, you are urged to review the setup or procedure. Yeah, I know how
to do that. Okay, press the open button on your Dreamcast to open the disk door. No, this is how
to put the disk in. Please. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. Press the start button on the Dreamcast
controller to display the raising habitat. In the beginning, this will be an aquarium. The very first
thing you must do is place the seaman egg into the tank. L trigger to toggle the display over
the storage matrix. The milky white object located in the top of the storage is the seaman egg.
Use the analog thumb pad to select the egg. Okay, so I got I've got two here. All right. Yeah,
I know. I know. I know. I know what it said. I heard it too, but I just swallowed it. Okay.
I like no, no, no. I just didn't react to it. And that's like, oh, wow. I said that on purpose,
right? That's like has to be what it was. Nobody would say that unless they said it on purpose.
Like, absolutely not. God damn it. What a fucking idiot. Anyways, first transfer the egg into the
tank. Who gives a shit? I'll be fine. So while use the analog thumb pad to select the egg,
and while pressing and holding X, press and hold the trigger to grab the egg. Okay, I got it. If
you are successful, you should see the egg displayed on the clipboard in the lower right
corner of the screen. In this state, press L again to toggle the display over the aquarium.
Ooh, shit. So you have to hold it the whole time. So we go like this, right trigger, left,
and now we're over here. Next, let go of X and R to release the egg into the tank. This the clipboard
will disappear and the egg will be visible in the tank. This process is used when moving items from
display to display. Whenever you grasp an item, it will appear on the clipboard. If you release
the item, let go of X and or R before switching to the display in which to release the item,
the item will return to the original location. So let go. Where is it? Did I just drop it on the
ground? How do I zoom out? How do I like zoom the camera out? Where's the egg? When continuing
from, please insert the memory card into... How do I turn the lights on? This is not dead already.
How do I turn on the lights? Would you like to save and end the session? No, not yet. Okay,
then it says subsequent operation. All right. When continuing from previously saved file,
only one seamen habitat is able to be created on a VMU. Therefore file selection, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whenever the start screen is displayed, there will be a short narration that reports on the
current status of your seamen's development and provides a brief explanation of what has occurred
previously, as there are often important hints and tips on how to proceed offered during this
narration. It is recommended that you listen to it carefully every single day. If the mushrooms
do not evolve within a few days of their hatching, they will die. How do I turn the lights on?
Position the hand over the nautilus at the bottom of the tank and press R to patiently tap it.
The mushroomers will float towards the nautilus and be eaten. Do not be alarmed by this behavior
and continue on as normal. Once the nautilus has consumed at least four
mushroomers, it will begin to undergo a transformation, so observe it carefully.
How do I turn on the lights? How do you turn on the lights? Before turning on the Dreamcast,
flip the light switch. Controls, yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
Toggle, once displayed, toggle between each function. Use the D-pad to operate the various
devices that control the habitat. Okay, so we got heater, air, light. Oh, okay, where's the egg?
Press down to hide the habitat panel. So what do I need to do for heat? How do I clean the tank?
How do I give the, how do I give mushrooms to the thing? Tap it, right? Turn on the heat.
Leonard didn't tell me that. Hold on. Would you like to save and end the session? It didn't tell
me what heat I needed to put it to. How to interact with a flick seaman. Caring for your seaman.
I just had to keep reading, okay? Relax. Use the D-pad to operate the devices on the habitat
operation panel. Because the analog design for this device is old-fashioned,
you are only able to perform operations such as raising the temperature or increasing the
oxygen level of the habitat. For the duration, you press the relevant button. Once you've released
the button, the temperature will begin to decrease and the oxygen to dissipate with the
passage of time. Maybe I haven't prepared myself mentally for it. I am absolutely prepared mentally
for it. Okay. Granted, the system used to operate requires far more work than would a fully automated
digital habitat system, but let us not forget the benefits that this analog style system provides.
Perhaps such work will be useful in teaching you a concept that is often forgotten in this
fully automated society we live in. Mainly that the first step towards conveying true affection
for another is through constant attention and care. Not through Twitter, not through Facebook,
not through Instagram. Delete them. You don't need them. You don't even have to use them.
Get rid of your Facebook. Leonard Nimoy told you fucking 20 years ago this was going to happen.
Don't use it anymore. Go outside. Go outside and at least once a week. Leonard Nimoy warned us about
this. It is necessary to maintain appropriate levels of temperature, oxygen, etc. in order to
provide semen with a suitable living environment. Therefore, it is necessary for you to adjust these
levels as required to display the habitat operation panel on the screen. The functions that are
available for use at the current stage of your semen development will appear on the panel.
Press this way or that way to toggle between the available functions and then press
that way or this way to activate the selected function to hide the habitat updation panel.
Press okay. Display the habitat operation panel and toggle until the word light appears.
Press. I thought that was a house. I was like where's the home button? You see that? I was
like home. It's up. It is recommended that normally you keep the light on at the brightest setting
in order to observe semen properly. All right. Fucking heater. Display the habitat operation
panel and toggle until the word heater appears. Press and hold up to turn the heater on and to
raise the temperature. The heater will only activate and operate while the switch is pressed.
It will take a few moments to get going and then may continue for a moment after the switch is
released. Practice your timing and above all take care not to overheat the habitat. Just after the
habitat is first created, temperature is zero. Unlike modern American heaters, the heating
units are measured in Celsius, the same scale used by Dr. Cassell. This is going to be bad.
I can't change that. It's in Celsius. I don't know what that means. I just saw the image in
the preview. That was fucked up. Okay. To ensure the eggs hatch properly... Are you listening to me?
Are you listening? To ensure... I don't care. Whatever. I'll never get it right. To ensure the
eggs hatch properly, the temperature of the habitat should be maintained between 15 and 20 degrees
everywhere else in the world besides America. After the eggs have hatched, observe semen carefully
to determine the appropriate temperature setting and then maintain it accordingly.
So 15 between 15 and 20 degrees. Okay. Oxygen supply. Imagine not doing this. I can't fucking...
I'm so glad I did this. Remember like...
Display the habitat operation panel until the word air appears. Press and hold up to supply a stream
of oxygen into the tank. The oxygen supply will only continue to increase for the duration you
hold it. Just after the habitat is first created, the level of oxygen is zero. When the oxygen level
is lower than 50, when it's lower than 50, semen isn't in danger of suffocation. The appropriate
level depends on the number of living objects in the habitat. However, it is safe to assume
that this level must stay above 80 whenever possible. All right. Let me like just fucking
do this first. So we've got... Here's the menu. Heater. 15 degrees, right? Okay. That's 0.05,
right? Oh, I see. It slowly does it. Okay. This guy's a bit 15 to 20. Camera's not big enough.
Oh, fuck. All right. I gotta turn on the generator. I gotta let it go, though. I gotta let it go,
because it takes a minute to stop, right? Put it to 100 to do a soft-boiled egg.
You are fucked up. That's not nice. Did you think about what you just said before you said it?
Wow. Is it gonna suffocate? How long does it take to suffocate? Probably would have already
happened. Okay. Slow down. Slow down. Well, how do I like my... I like my eggs over medium.
Yeah, I know. Someone's gonna be like, really? Over easy? No. Over medium. I like a soft but
tangible yolk in the middle. Over easy is disgusting to me. It just is. I'm sorry. It is.
It's barely even cooked in the middle. All right. 15 to 20. Here we go. All right. So I'm
gonna keep it in like around like 17 to 18, you know? Like right here should be good.
Okay. Now we need to do air. What did it say for air? 80? I'm not fucking it up, am I?
Do you don't drink raw eggs for strength? No. I don't drink raw eggs for strength.
Clean the water. I don't know how to do that yet. I need to read how to do that.
Let me at least let him breathe. Are you guys sour, please, into this? Holy shit. We can actually
see the tank now. It said keep it above 80. Who knew that reading would help, right? I know.
Can you have too much air? What happens if you have over air? Oh, that's as high as it can go.
All right. Cleaning. How do I clean? Let's get this to higher. What happens if there's too much?
No. Oxygen. If there's too much oxygen, it's bad for you, right? Isn't that how that works?
Would you like to save and end the session? We breathe CO2, right? So if like the O2 wasn't
there or if it was too much, it would be like helium. It would turn into H2O, which would be
helium. Now we exhale CO2. Sorry. My mistake, scientists in chat. Okay. Cleaning. You will
discover that with each passing day, the water in Seaman's Aquarium will become cloudier,
indicating a worsening in sanitation condition of the habitat. Cleaning the water is simple,
and all that you must do is increase the oxygen supply. That's it. As you do this,
you will notice the water become clearer. Keep the water clean. So you just have to put air in it.
Just make it oxygenate the water to clean it. H2O is water. It's hydrogen and then oxygen.
That's not water. Hydrogen is its own thing. Oxygen, when you combine them together,
you get hydrogen and oxygen. Water is water. It just exists. You're talking about like a chemical
made in a fucking lab. All right. Please don't leave if you think I'm like actually that stupid.
Some of you guys might just be like, all right, this guy's fucking out of his mind. I'm out of
here. All right. So I need to know how, what was the thing about the Nautilus again? The Nautilus
down there. All right. Feeding your Seaman. Press L to switch to the storage matrix. You'll notice
11 food pellets that are used to feed Seaman once it reaches the Gilman stage of development.
We're not there yet. How to say goodbye to Seaman. Living in harmony with Seaman.
Ah, exchanging food with another razor. Advice. Final notes and pointers.
Okay, hold on. How do I make the egg hatch? Do I have to feed the egg? Do I have to like inject a
syringe into the egg? What was the thing about the Nautilus like eating mushrooms? So this is,
okay, we're in day one. So day two. So, okay, let's just take a look. So that's grab. So this
is to move forward. Okay. This is the zoom. Yeah. But you know what I mean? Like what can I,
that's just the egg right there. All right. It's multiplying. It's turning into four cells.
Is this going to eat it? He's going to eat this. Okay. So now it has to be tomorrow.
When am I going to eat it? No, I can't talk yet. I don't have the ability to speak. It's called
mitosis, stupid. Doesn't it take actual days for the game to progress? Yeah. So how do I save it?
Okay. How do I get, how do I change this clock in the Dreamcast? It only takes a few minutes.
I'm going to have to go, I'm going to have to turn the console off like 30 times this stream.
I have to go change the date and time until tomorrow. All right. We'll just get away to
the egg to hatch. Save and quit. Would you like to save and end the session? Okay. You just have to
wait. But hold on. Do I have to wait? I think I have to wait till tomorrow is when the egg hatches.
So I can't just leave. What do you mean no cheating? I'm going to cheat the whole day.
It only takes a few minutes. It hatches. Okay. All right. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Let me
get to the part of the instructional booklet. If the mushrooms do not evolve within a few days
of their hatching, they will die. Whoa. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What, what,
what do I do about the balloons? What, how do I do this? We got it. We got life. How do I,
when do they turn into, uh, sea monkeys? What do you mean it died? It didn't die. It's all right.
Now do I have them get eaten? It's not dead. These are like the eggs. One of these. Some of
these are going to survive. Make sure hot water heater. These are the mushrooms. Okay.
Tap the nautilus. There's too much air in here. I don't need too much air. It said keep it above 80.
Uh oh. Hello. Oh shit. Look at this. Get him. Should I be doing this? He's going to get one.
He's going to get one. Is this how do you make a sea man? Now saving. Now saving. Now saving.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. He's pissed. What did I do? Whoa. He got one. He actually just got one.
This is making me uncomfortable. Just open a guide. I think we're good. They aren't dying.
Don't worry. No, I know. They're going to get like spit out. What's going on up here? How's the air?
How's the heat? It's okay. Air is okay. Takes a few minutes. We can just chill. It's all good.
How many does he need to eat? If the mushrooms do not evolve within a few days they're hatching,
they will die. Position the hand over the nautilus. The mushrooms will float towards the nautilus to
be eaten. Do not be alarmed by this behavior and continue as normal. Once the nautilus has
consumed four mushroomers, it will begin to undergo our transformation. He's got to eat two more.
Eat two more of these. Come on, grab one. Come on. What's his problem? Eat it. He already ate three.
I think he needs to eat four. Does he have a brain? We need more air. We got plenty of air.
The heat and the air are fine. Come on, grab one. Grab one. Come on. You need one more. Come on.
He needs to get one more. Come on. Down here. Come on. No. No. Just go get eaten. Did he eat four?
I thought he only ate three. Don't annoy him. Just let him be. That was weird. All right. So
there are only four left in the tank. So that means maybe he did already eat four. All right.
So then he's going to shit out a seed. So should I go on the clock now and make it like two days
later? He only eats them when the air is lower. I'm not going to believe that bullshit. There's
too much air. I can't even lower it. So even if that one guy was telling the truth. Are you sure
you want to continue with this? It's a very disturbing experience. This was a hundred bucks.
So yes, this was eighty dollars. Eighty. What's going on? I think is he doing something here?
Just use an emulator. An emulator cannot do the microphone. This is the only way.
Whoa! What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Why is he like dying? Uh save him. I don't know.
How do I? Is that I can't save him? And I want the real experience. I don't want the emulator
experience. I want the real microphone. The real controller. I want to be authentic. So when my
children come into the world they can use they can do it too. Check the oxygen. Here we're good.
This is actually pretty disturbing. I don't think I want to tap. He's going through some shit right
now. This is okay. Do I have to do anything? It looks like he's cooking in a fryer. Like he's in
a pan. Yeah that's fucked up. Yeah yellow is bad. Red is dangerous. Yeah as long as it's blue it's
good. It was between 15 and 20 for here and above 80 for this. So we're good.
Turn off the lights. Is that the problem? I feel like there's something I should be doing here.
Turn the oxygen off. I can't. You can only turn it up. Why would anyone buy this game? Because
it was one of the first video games to allow. Would you like to save and end the session?
Uh communicating. Communicating once seaman has learned a reasonable vocabulary. Try to
initiate a conversation in the beginning. It is generally acceptable to address seaman with
hey or seaman. To do so a mature seaman will often respond to phrases such as say something
or talk to me. If you observe seaman's manner closely you'll have no problems distinguishing
when seaman is ready to begin conversing. All conversations with seaman must be made
via the microphone. Be sure to press a for the full duration of your utterance when speaking to
seaman. Once each utterance is complete be sure to release a. Note that the general progress of
your conversation with seaman is indicated by the icons that appear on the LCD screen of the VMU.
Hello. How are you? What is your purpose? What is your purpose?
Where's the mothership? How do you like your tank? Are you comfortable?
Hey how are you? They don't they don't how do I teach them? This one wants to talk. This is the
one that's closest. Look it keeps coming over here. No no I want this one. Back off. Good afternoon.
Hi hi play door play dough chicken strips crayons crayon
hoi mac and cheese. What are what are the lives of kids like? School.
Fortnite. I'm gonna teach him the alphabet. A. B. C. D.
He's gonna see the avengers progressing here. We'll see end game theater. E. Seaman.
Waha. U. Seaman. U. Seaman. U. Molo. U. Seaman. Squeena. Squee. Seaman. Seaman. Play door. Seaman.
How do I feed how do I feed them? Would you like to save and end the session?
Feeding. Once you'll notice 11 food pellets that are to be used to feed seem once it reaches the
Gillman stage of development. Are they they're not are they at Gillman? Not yet right? No no no yes
yes they are at Gillman. No yes. It's speaking Simlish. Yes they are. Yes yes. Oh you guys saying
no you don't know what the hell are you talking about? Okay to feed once it reaches give it to
feed. Seaman use the analog thumb pad to select food pellet and then press and hold grab it.
Press L to toggle to the aquarium tank then release X and R to drop the food into the water.
Okay the food pellets initially available in the storage matrix will enable you to feed Seaman for
a short time provided you do not overfeed it. However after that you will need to create an
alternate method of providing Seaman with food. What? There is no need to panic for Seaman may
be able to help you to determine a new method for providing food when the time is right.
So be sure to observe carefully and listen well to what Seaman has to tell you.
What is it gonna like eat its own shit? I don't understand that. Take the utmost care to prevent
using up all the food in the storage. You are advised to only feed Seaman when it is hungry.
Prick up your ears listen carefully to what Seaman says and be sure to carry out its
instructions in a timely fashion. So hungry? Hungry? Are you hungry? Hungry? Yeah yeah said yeah.
Hungry? Cool okay. Who gets to eat it? Oh they do they all they all share the cookie. He just
stole it. He just took it. Hello? I told you not to feed them. Well I wouldn't mean that not to feed
them. They're not speaking English. How do I know what hungry means? All they're going they're doing
like reverse speech like death line. Like that I'm hungry. How am I supposed to know what that means?
Now I was right to feed them. Are you ready to evolve Pikachu?
Is it chilly in the tank? Yeah I think it's chilly in the tank. Hold on let me see.
All right yeah it's a little chilly. 17 about we'll make it 18.
All right let's get the stuff stuff stuff stuff stuff stuff not too hot too hot. All right we're
good. What's going on over here? These are like the mushrooms. Are these things just gonna die?
Didn't why are there only three before that are alive? Yes. Yes.
Yes. How do you teach a kid language? I don't know how this works. I don't have any children.
How does a kid learn? I have no idea. I have no idea what to do. See if any died. I don't think so.
No I think maybe maybe two died. What's what's a sim uh greeting? Like like uh
how do I do this? How do I speak? How what's with it? It's like it's like bravolo mule
bye right? Sul sul. Clap clap clap. Ratanar fly.
Waha. Lumpa. Lumpa. Wrap. Laffy. Laffy. Laffy. Fortnight. Forca. Pabra. Pabra. Pabra.
Yeah. Hooray. Hooray. Fibula. Fibula. Isn't that an organ? Fibula is like here right? Where's the
fibula? Check the other ones. Hold on. Hello. Hello. See it's reversed. Are you comfortable?
Comfy? I have one. Are there translations in the handbook? I don't think so. It just tells
you when they understand what you're saying. Advice. Here we go. Please realize that concepts
such as goals or scores do not apply to this game. You are free to enjoy semen in whatever manner you
find appropriate. However if you endeavor to successfully raise and assist in semen's evolution
there are a few points you must take into consideration. Go to sleep. Sleep.
Okay. First off is a strong relationship between knowledge acquisition and semen's growth process.
Just following around. I've got plenty of air right? Just watch this one for a while.
As semen's caretaker you are encouraged to take the initiative and talk to semen daily to stimulate
its desire to learn and in turn aid its maturation. Note that without conversation
semen's growth process will stop. Therefore it's important to speak to semen throughout its growth
and development even well before it's matured to the stage of being able to converse with you.
Secondly it's imperative at some point that you transform the habitat aquarium into a terrarium
for semen as this is crucial to aiding in its evolution. But not to worry semen will assist
you in achieving this goal when the time is right. Be sure to listen carefully and attentively to
all that semen tells you. Eventually when an appropriate level of maturity has been reached
you must help semen become free of the confines of the habitat. How do I transform the habitat
aquarium into a land-filled terrarium? What environment lies outside the habitat? How do
I enable semen to gain freedom from its confines? These are all questions you must be longing to
have answered. However we have opted not to provide these answers in this manual. We feel
it would be far more rewarding experience if you do experiment using the exact same laboratory
conditions as Jean-Paul Gusset in the 30s. We have the utmost confidence that you will be successful
in your semen rearing efforts. So I just keep stimulating their brains and then I'm going to
turn the clock forward. Hello? Hello? Hello? Okay. Who got attention? Hey, how are you?
Have you heard any good jokes lately? Oink-a. Oink-a? Oink-a. Oink-a.
Momma. Read the B-movie script to them. I'm not, I'm not gonna fucking do that. Yeah, what?
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna read these children the late six and a half year old meme. At least
give us something that's more relevant to today. Okay. Sure. I'm gonna fast forward time now.
Yeah. I will fast forward time now and then I'm gonna come back and see how you're doing.
Gnome it. How am I gonna do that? I don't have speakers. Sing him a song.
O Canada, our home and sacred land.
True patriot side and all thy sons command. With spoken word we see thy shine. The true
north young and wise. We're, that's all I know. Any words for that? I'm not, I don't, I'm not
Canadian. Why would I know the Canadian theme song? You know, I'm supposed to know every country's
theme song? I live in the United States of America. I've been to Canada twice. I'm supposed to know
the words to their fucking song? Are you serious? Twice is enough. Wow. Can you believe what they
just said? Cool. Cool. All right. Um, should I fast forward now? One day. I'm gonna save it. I'm
gonna end and I'm gonna fast forward the clock a day and we'll see how they're doing. Okay. Be good.
See you soon. Goodbye. Goodbye. I'm not gonna fast forward 40 years. They'll be dead. I'm gonna
go one day. Come back one day until they get to be adults and I can talk. The tank is not gonna be on
fire. Let's put the heat up to like 19 and then I have to, oh, not too hot, not too hot, not too
hot. Stop before 20 please. Put the oxygen, get it to like 100. Okay. Dim the light a little bit.
All right. Now they're good. I should be able to. Would you like to save and end the session?
Save and end the session. Go into the clock. Make it tomorrow. I'm not cooking the fishes, guys.
Just, you just wait till I get to fucking have a conversation with all these
butt heads. The cliff, there's a cliffhanger in the game. The sequel is only in Japanese.
It's not gonna work. Why not? All right. Here we go. Saving. We're locked in now. I'm gonna
change the date to tomorrow. Oh, by the way, I wanted to show you this because I, you may now
turn the power off. Okay. But before we go any further, you guys need to see this. So I also
made sure they got Space Channel 5, the original Space Channel 5. And I don't, that's like a plan
to play this. I don't want to open this because look, this is like original shrink wrapped
packaging. Isn't this like an artifact? I don't want to open this. You know what I mean? I don't
think I want to break the seal. This might be worth like 50 grand in like a thousand years.
You know, my great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great grandchildren
might be able to sell this for like fucking a million dollars. Here's the crazy thing. Okay.
Imagine like this clip is going to be saved for probably a while. I don't know if it's going to
take a thousand years, but let's just say that like Twitch, somebody saves this clip on a hard
drive and it gets thrown in the dump somewhere. Like a hundred years from now, somebody comes
across it and they see this clip of me fucking ripping this and they have a heart attack because
it's worth like $10 million now. We're talking like a thousand years in the future. This is going
to be one of those like viral videos that people are like, Oh my God, I'm cringing watching him
open space channel five. It's going to be worth a million. All right. Let me, uh, let me just do
this safe to turn the power off, right? Let's fast forward to tomorrow. Okay. Here we go. We're good.
So now we go to settings to three 10, 2019 date and time. Okay. So now, uh, three, uh, three 11,
right? That's tomorrow, right? Okay. Let's go. Let's see how they're doing tomorrow.
That's not month. That's day. Holy shit. Someone just gave a hundred bucks. Why is that not on
screen? Uh, flying muffin man just gave a hundred bucks. Thank you for the a hundred fucking
goddamn dollars. And they say, Hey man, you're the best. I don't have the attention span to watch
streams too often, but it will always be a treat to see a new video up. Much love. Hello. Thank you.
So welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gosset. That means a lot. Thank you, man. Greetings and
welcome back. You're doing a good job. First, a recap of your previous visit of recap episode
two, the Nautilus has become prey to the parasitic mushroomers and thus the Gilman were born.
Gil stands for the gills of a fish. So a Gilman is a being who breathes underwater.
Gilman has learned human words. Try speaking to him if you haven't already.
I did that. I did that. At the moment, the habitat contains four Gilman.
Four Gilman. They are suffering from the cold. Please use the heater to raise the temperature
to a more comfortable level. They are suffering. So let us get over to the tank. All right. Well,
flying muffin man, thank you for the insanely generous amount of money. Thank you. 10,000 bits.
A heater goes down over time. All right, let's go. How are they doing? Hey, kids, dad's home.
They know words now. You shouldn't have gone ahead 24 hours. How am I supposed to fucking not?
You're not. No, we're going to do. We're all right. Let's see. Oh,
oh,
okay. I swear to fucking God, this keeps getting stuck on the bottom of my glass,
but I need it because of the coaster. Slow down. Don't burn them. It just keeps. It's like a
suction cup when I lift it up and then it falls. Good thing. Good thing. I got this beautiful new
keyboard. Oh, you guys, I want to make sure you guys see this new keyboard, by the way, pause the
game. You guys need, would you like to save and end the session? Uh, you know, people have had some
recommended keyboards. Hey, you should check out like the Logitech, like G 1000 or something,
right? I'm like, yeah, that one looks kind of good. Razor's got some like fucking awesome
keyboards. I mean, that's all right. Stick with my own fucking bread and butter right here.
This is an Amazon basics keyboard came in the mail today. I believe this keyboard was seven
and a half dollars. I could be wrong. Basic streamer. You don't need all the bells and whistles.
It's just a block. Guys, I'm going to tell you the biggest scam in all of human history.
This is just a plastic brick with letter buttons on it. Some people sell you this shit for like
fucking 300, 400 bucks. This, it's a, it's letter buttons. Don't let anybody fool you.
Like $400 keyboard and Amazon basics $8 keyboard are the same keyboard. One just clicks has like,
you know, Oh, I got the O-rings on mine. We both have the same function. You know, don't,
don't fall for the bullshit. Same thing with the gamer chairs. Look at this thing. This is fine.
You don't need those, like the big thing that comes up and guess what? Hey, I got one of those
gamer chairs. All right. Yeah, it's nice. By the way, the rest of my stream forever
has a billboard advertisement of the company that is fucking that I bought this chair from,
that I got this chair from. You're a constant advertisement forever. If I got one of those
chairs, I would just fucking duct tape gun across the whole thing. And they come up so high. I feel
like I'm sitting in one of those like the egg from the men in black test. Everyone, Will Smith
is doing like the test and he's in like the fucking egg. I don't want to sit in one of those
fucking things. No, you can go, you can go to Staples and get this chair for like fucking 80
bucks, 75 bucks, 40 bucks. You don't need a personalized billboard for a company that you
fucking probably talk to twice in emails. You know, I got such a good relationship with this
chair company, you know, I exchanged two emails and they sent one to me. Fucking come on. That
chair is $150. I have one. How many emails did you exchange? All right, what do I have to do?
Oh yeah, the heater. They know English words now. That bit sucked. That wasn't a bit. That was me
speaking in reality. You can tell it's a bit because I'll do the bit voice. You know, this,
this is the bit voice. Let me tell you something really funny. That's a bit voice. I was just
speaking as Jeremy Albertson there as a concerned streamer. All right, let's go see what they've
learned in a day. So a good light heater. Let's make it a little hot. You're doing a bit while
your kids die. Are they hungry? Well, let's check, check on that. They look a little fatter. Hello?
I thought you knew English words. You heard it. That was such a shitty burp too. That was just a
fifth grader burp. That was like I chugged a juice box and tried to do a big burp at the lunch table.
How are you today? How are you? Seamen. Seamen.
What? English. More time. You just said more time? English. English. What's the point?
Already like a nihilistic fish. Crap. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to say to this.
The point is food. Hungry? Hungry? No. How do I? Can I like grab it? I'm sorry.
English. English. What for? To learn. Spanish. Japanese.
Japanese. Molo. English. More time. Hurry up. Yeah. All right. Should I feed them? Hungry?
Check on one of your brothers and sisters. Where are they? Let's try you.
Where'd you just go? Hello? He heard it but he just didn't respond. Hello?
Pabra? English. English. I'm learning. Very good. Very good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. No.
Cool. Learning. Learning. Learning. More. More. More. Good. Good. Good. Very good. Very good. Good.
Sick dude. English. Teach him fuck. What am I? Like the 13 year old older brother
that has, you know. No. Hungry? Food? No. All right. What's he doing? Food?
Should I feed them? It's been a day, right? I think I have to feed them. How many? Are they
like a camel? Do they eat once a day? Once a week? How much does a sea man eat? Just one pellet a day.
That sounds good. I got 11 of these. So I got 11, 10 more days worth of food. All right. Let's
put it down. Go eat. Come on. Come on. Come on. Don't let them have the whole thing.
There's four of you. Come on. Get over here. You're gonna be, you're dead. I love how their feeding
is just me dropping one cookie crisp into the tank. Ate it. Ate it. Ate it. Food? Good. It was good,
huh? People. Eat. Eat. Wake up. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Good. Good. Yes. Yes. Yes. No. No. Hoy. No.
No. No. There we go. We got yes, good, no. We need to, I need to teach them food.
Food. Arranger. Food. That's how you do it to a kid. You go, food. And then they get it. Food.
I'm not going to scream in a microphone. Good. Okay, fine.
Are you guys all set? Okay, guys. Have a good day. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye. Bye.
Bye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Bye. Okay. Let's see who we got. They've been fed. We've
conversed a little. Let's make sure we got a good heaters at eight. Let's put the, put it up to like
just, I'm going to get this close to 20 as I can. Tell them you love them. They don't understand
that yet. Teach them their names. They don't know what they, how am I going to do that?
They know how to say yes, no, and cool. I got to get this a little higher. 19, I'll get it to 19.5
and then stop. Teach them the value of Bitcoin. Do research. Do research on market trends before
investing. Do not FOMO into new things. Only invest what you can afford to lose. Don't do
what Jerma did. I'm implying that I lost a shitload of money. Motherfuck, I gained money.
I think I just scared him. I scared him out of the tank. I have to get this higher.
Seaman. Seaman. Seaman. You. Seaman. Seaman. Seaman. You. Seaman. Seaman. Seaman. You. Greg.
Bamboo. Seaman. Seaman. Greg. Seaman. Greg. Yeah, we. Well, they know Seaman.
All right, heater's good. Let's get the air of 200. Okay. Would you like to save and end the session?
Shouldn't be teaching children how to say Greg. What's wrong with Greg?
Okay, here we go. All right, it's the next day. So maybe I shouldn't be, maybe it should be tomorrow,
but not completely 24 hours. How's that? That looks good. Looks fine. All right, let's go.
It's, we're now two days from now. Teach them hatred for other sentient beings.
Why the hell would I do that? I'll go with like hungry first. Let you know, like, that's how
my niece, whenever it would be hungry, it'd be like, do you, you, this, this? And she'd go,
and you go, oh, okay, yeah, she's hungry. Just grow hands. Here we go. Welcome to the laboratory.
Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good job. At the moment, the habitat contains
four Gilmen. They are suffering from the cold. Please use the heater to raise the temperature
to a more comfortable level. So let us head over to the tank. Okay. Feed, converse, English,
all things that need to be considered. Is that a metal straw? It sure is. It's a metal straw.
I like it because the straw, if you have a cold beverage, the straw gets cold and it makes it,
when liquid goes up to the tube, it's, uh, it's colder and it felt like that. I like the way it
sounds. I like the way it feels in the mouth. I prefer a metal or copper straw. All right. How
are we doing? Hi. Hi. Hi. Fuck you. I'll just talk to your brother. Hi. English. English.
Talk more of that.
Oh, they're cold. They're cold. They're cold. Right. Right. Right. Right. I'm just going in there
going English. Speak English. It's cold. English. Yeah.
Dirty tank too. All right. All right. Relax. Don't like go more than 17 for now.
Yeah. Which one's the more talkative?
Talk a little bit, feed them. How do I do interactions?
Talk to all of them equally. I can't do that. That's too hard. Good morning. Yeah. Good morning.
Hi. Hi. How are you? Are you having a good day?
What's the point? So I can understand you.
So I can understand you. For me to understand you. Let's talk.
What's your favorite food? My favorite food is pizza. Hi. Pizza.
Pizza. My favorite food is pizza. What's your favorite food? Mine's pizza. Hi. Hey. Hello.
English. This is that was German. How would you how would you learn German? I haven't said any
German words. No. Yeah. It's Russian. Not German. Nine is German. Russian. Why is he speaking
Russian? Russian. Russian. English. Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. Good morning.
Halleray. Pee blood. What are you talking about? It's been nice talking to you. Are you hungry?
Night night. Night night. Good morning. Play, play, play. You want to play? All right. How do
you? Would you like to save and end the session? How do I do that? He wants to play. Advice.
Exchanging food with another razor. Living in harmony. Okay. If a seaman is in a bad mood,
it will elect to discontinue conversation with you. Whether the cause of this mood swing is
inadvertent or intentional on your part is of no relevance. The following situations have been
noted to cause a deterioration of seaman mood. If you are violent towards or speak rudely to
seaman. If you're constantly using strange or foreign terms that seaman does not understand.
If you willfully and consistently repeat the same types of words over and over like pizza.
If you fail to feed seaman over an extended period. If you fail to maintain a suitable living
environment. If you willfully and continuously flick or grab and pick them up. Pay attention to
seaman's health. Seaman is a living creature. In order for seaman to remain healthy, it is an
absolute must for you to provide food, oxygen, and a clean living environment. Pay careful attention
to the state of the water and oxygen levels. Keep in mind that if you are away and unable to attend
to seaman for a couple of days, seaman could possibly die. So if I'm away for more than a day
too, they can die. So how do I interact? This feeding, this carrying, how to interact? Okay,
tapping the glass with R, flick. While locked on in a close-up, position the hand icon over seaman
and press and hold R for a few seconds till the icon changes as illustrated, then release it to
flick. However, note that if you do this too often, seaman may begin to dislike you.
There's also tickle. Use the zoom function to zero on the seaman and position the hand over it,
then press X repeatedly. This will put seaman in a good mood. Okay, note, do not attempt to tap,
flick, or tickle other household pets, wild animals outside of the seaman kit. Seaman is a
very special creature that will respond to such stimuli. However, other animals not in the seaman
kit have been known to become far more aggressive when administered such contact and it is not
advised. Yeah, don't do that to like any birds. All right, so here we go. So, I'm sorry. Okay,
what about the other one? All right, that's how you just tap that. That's like, okay.
So, I have to make them all happy. Hello. English. English. So, we're just gonna like pet them all.
Only focus on one seaman. Well, everyone, people are just pissed off because I was only focusing
on one of the children. Who's the smartest? Hello. Hello. I think we found the smart one.
Food. How are you? How are you? Come here. Don't do this to a wild pig, you find.
If you see a bear, don't run up to him and be like, hey bear, how are you? You're gonna get
fucking face ripped off. Why would you do that in the first place? Come here. Fun. Does it really
have to give a warning? Are people gonna sue this company if somebody tried to like pet a bear
because they played a game about sea monkeys? Having fun? Are you having fun? Fun, fun, fun,
fun. Let's play. Play. Having fun? Okay. Yeah. In 1776, Columbus signed the Declaration of
Independence and then the British invaded and we repelled them and then we gained our independence.
And then a couple of big wars were fought between lots of countries and then the computer came out
and AOL was the first internet provider and then there was Netscape was a browser that eventually
turned into Mozilla and after that there was faster internet and when the faster internet came out
everybody lost their minds and that's kind of where we are now.
You should be a history teacher. I'm condensing it all. I'm condensing it for the fish.
That's a lot. Trying to explain to a child like the concept of states that no it's not going to
happen. There are 50 states in the United States. Hello. He's not paying attention anymore. Come here.
Having fun? Having fun? Hello. Hello. How are you? Did I feed him today?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Okay. No, I haven't.
Come get it. Eat, eat, eat, eat. Good. Very good. We have to get a refill. English or no food. That's
kind of fucked up. That one didn't even eat. English. English. What for? To learn.
English. Learn English. Learn English. You first. Implying that I don't know English.
What a dick. Are you in chat right now? Yeah, I won't. Get fucked, idiot. Easy.
Easy. What's your favorite thing to do? Flibula. They always love, they love flibula. Fun. Dog.
Who are you? Seaman. Oh, we're getting progress here. What's your name? Hey. I've said hey so
many times. That's why. Hey. What is your name? Baby. No, baby. Baby. Baby. You are baby. You are
baby. Baby. This is the moment we're keeping alive. See you tomorrow. See you tomorrow. What?
See you tomorrow. Seaman. Seaman. Yes. Goodbye. Hi. Bye. Hi. Goodbye.
Bye. See ya. Seaman. Seaman. They have no concept of time. Bye. All right. Let's go.
Good night. Night. Good night. Good night. Night night. There we go. All right. Let's make sure
everything's good. Now we're going to skip another day. Do you see what fucking is happening here?
This is what I'm gonna have to deal with. Every time. Skip a week. No, they'll be dead. I'm not
doing that. They'll actually be dead. Let's get the 19.5. Nail the coaster to the desk.
That would ruin the desk. Get an actual coaster. This is an actual coaster.
What do you get an actual coaster? I bought these. They're coasters. Put salt on the glass.
All right. Have a good air. It's the lights dimmed. Okay. Would you like to save and
end the session? Tomorrow. Here we go. Now I have to piss. All right. You got pee break?
Been two hours? Just about? Has it been two hours? Holy shit. What the fuck have we been doing?
Jesus. I'm having a good time. Time flies. This shit, apparently. All right. Let me just
piss it right back. Let me grab a refill. Okay. So I'm going to skip ahead. Is this bad for the
Dreamcast? I'm not going to fuck up the Dreamcast, right? I think it's old as hell anyways.
It's like turning it off, turning it on, turning it off, turning it to break it.
I feel like it's going to cause a problem. All right. Settings 313. Like 8 a.m.
That sounds pretty good. I'm going to fuck that up. Make sure everyone screams in my fucking mouth
if I make that the wrong day. Because this has been a long time coming.
And this is going to take, this is already taking about two hours. If I make that like
two days ahead or like a month ahead, freak the fuck out and just spam. Because I, that might
happen. I might change it to like 2020 accidentally. So keep me honest. All right. Here we go.
313. Closed it up. How do you do that by accident? You've seen some of the dumb
shit I've done on this stream. You're asking how I would do that by accident. Think of half the
stuff you've seen on this fucking camera on your television set here that you will like. How the
fuck did he do that? It's very possible. All right. Let's go. Leonard Nimoy. How are we doing?
Updates. Change the date to 3019 and sell the game for $10 million.
Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset. How are we? Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. At the moment, the habitat contains four human. They are suffering
from the cold. Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable. Good,
not great. I'm doing a good job. Let us head over to the tank. How much more? Okay. I only have like
eight more days of food. What happens after eight days? Save them all.
Okay, let's get. Let's see what they say about the goody. Oh, goody. Oh, goody. Yay. Yay. Okay.
About time. Yay. Goody. Goody. About time. It's been like 12 hours. I'm late. No, I'm fine. All
right. Let's see how they're doing. Whoa. You look different. Hello. Hi. I can't breathe.
How are you? How are you? Get off. What are you doing? Stop it. Stop that. Stop it. What's he
doing? He's killing. He's cannibalizing his brother. Stop it. Hey, hey, what am I supposed to do about
this? He's assimilating. He's like doing the Borg shit to his brother. No. No. Hey. Hello.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. Heaven. Heaven. You English. Heaven. Everything's gonna be all
right. Heaven. I don't know how to do. How do I? What was that for? Why? Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey, that
hurts. Hey. Why? Hello. Hello. What are you doing? What are you doing? Seaman. Why did you eat your
brother? Eat brother. English. English. You don't want to talk to me? My side hurts. Bad touch. Bad
touch. Would you like to save and end the session? Okay. Anybody hungry? How was your day? That was
tasty. Tasty. Tasty. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. What is your name? What is your name?
Execute the murderer. I can't do that. What is your name? Is it the Boston accent doing it again?
What is your name? What is your name? He doesn't want to listen to me. He's not paying attention
to me. He doesn't want to listen to me. Hello. Hello. He, it's showing the indicator that he's
hearing me. He just doesn't want to pay attention. Listen. You hurt my feelers.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Go eat brother. Eat brother. Hello. Why does nobody want
to talk to me anymore? Cold. Cold? Can we get him out of here? This is fucking bad. No wonder they're
don't want to talk and shit. Like literally this is a dead seaman floating down to the bottom. How
do I get rid of him? How do I pick this up? This is bad. This is like fucking morbid and terrible.
Get this out of here. Would you like to save and end the session? Starting over. Exchanging food.
Living in harmony. Advice. Final pointers. The sanctity of life. How do I remove a dead fish
from the tank? Grab and lift. Press X to transform the hand to grab while holding X. Press and hold
R to lift and grab seaman out of the tank. I can't do it. No. He's just gonna have to stay there dead.
I'm sorry. All right. We're good on air. Everything's fine. Just whatever. I tried.
How are you guys doing? Hello. Play. Play. Greetings and salutations. Greetings and salutations.
Salutations. Greetings and salutations. Hello. Greetings and salutations. How was your day today?
Guess. Guess. Very good. Good. Is that a dork? I can't feel my nose. This is terrible.
I can't feel.
Flick him. He's dead.
Is he alive? He's still talking. Are you still alive? Are you still alive?
Oh my god. Hi. Raise the temperature. Hello there. No, it's blue. I'm good.
Is it between 15 and 20? How much? How hot does it need to be?
20. Isn't blue correct? It needs to be 40. No. No. Didn't it say that blue was correct?
Yeah. No. This is correct. You're not gonna try to. You're not gonna debate me into
fucking burning my fish alive. 20 is optimal. Yeah. Come on. Excuse me. They're good.
Speak English. I don't like mornings. You don't like mornings? You don't like mornings?
Do you like mornings? Fucking Garfield cat. Yeah, really. Hi Garfield. Garfield. Good.
You like Garfield? Do you like Garfield? Seaman, seaman, seaman. Your name is Garfield.
Your name is Garfield. What's your name? Guess. Garfield. Garfield is your name. Your name is
Garfield. What up? What up? What up? Hey baby. That's not appropriate. It's fine. No it isn't.
Good morning. You've seen every one of my interactions. Every single one. Don't tell me.
How is your day? What's your name? Seaman. Your name is Garfield. Hey Garfield.
Thanks Pookie. Hey Garfield. Hey Garfield. Good. I don't know why. All right they've eaten,
right? Well he's eaten like three times. Chadfish versus the virgin streamer. Hi.
Are you okay? I'm so mad. Why are you mad? You make me mad. Why? Why?
Why? Why are you mad? Why are you mad? It's just a game. I'm upset. Why? Why are you mad?
Settle down. You make me mad. That's enough. Relax. I'm upset. I'm very sorry. I'm sorry
about that. No. Tired. You want to go to sleep? Do you want to go to sleep? Would you like to
go to sleep? Look at that face. Okay. Turn on the lights. I'm scared of the dark. I'm scared of the
dark. Where's your brother? Goodbye. I'm upset. Why is everybody upset with me? Well you keep
leaving him for 12 hours. Should I come back in like three hours this time? Or what? You called
him Garfield 40 times. Is that why he's pissed off? Food. Food. They've eaten. This is day three.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. They've eaten. Did they eat? Maybe they didn't eat.
No, they've eaten. No, they did. They ate. They ate. I know. Don't keep repeating words. Okay.
I'll put up like a thesaurus and start saying different stuff.
All right. How are we doing? Let's say goodbye. Let's get this to about like 1996.
That looks good. Oxygen's up. Let's dim the lights a little. And let's go. See you tomorrow. Would
you like to save and end the session? Hopefully you're both still alive. Let's see what happens.
Ah. Do English lessons. There we go. 313. Let's make it 314. And make it so it's been less than
that. 24 hours. 314. That's correct. 314. Let's go ahead and close it. Dreamcast is going to die
before Seaman does. Read them green eggs in hand. Jeremy, do you have any gray hairs?
I don't know. Probably not. I don't think so. I've had Kim examine my head a few times. Look good.
Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean-Paul Gasset. Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. It's 4 a.m. I look like I'm shitfaced after a night of partying.
The Gilmen have begun to suck each other's blood using the tubes on their heads. Did you notice?
The number of Gilmen has decreased due to natural selection. It seems cruel, but survival of the
fittest is an integral part of their lives. At the moment, the habitat contains two Gilmen.
They are suffering from the cold. They always are. Please use the heater to raise the temperature
to a more comfortable level. Allow me to give you the highlights for today. Highlights? I'm not sure,
but it seems that Seaman wants a name. Pay close attention to what he says.
So let us head over to the tank. This is important. All right. Garfield and Garfield and,
I don't know, Greg, right, right, right, right, right. Here we go. No longer a baby. It's getting
cold. Turn the heat up. I will. Don't worry. So one of these two is going to eat each other.
Oh, goody. It's about time. That's much better. Is that George Takai? It might be. Slow down. Don't
go too hot. All right. That's good. So how are we doing? Let's take a look. Hello. Yeah. Hello.
Whatever. What's wrong? I must say you've taken very good care of me up to this point.
Thank you. No, leave me alone. I heard you wanted a name. What is your name? What is your name?
What's your favorite color? It's not children anymore. Hey. Let's take it down a notch, huh?
Hey. Hey. Hi. I love you. What? It's rather difficult making out what's on the other side of
this glass. So let me inquire. Are you a male or a female? Male. You're a male of the species,
eh? Okay. Yes. Well, I was hoping to meet a lady, but I guess I'm not in a position to be too
choosy, am I? Not really. I probably should feed. Are you hungry? No. Leave me alone.
Do you want to play? What do you want? So I was led to believe I would be cared for by a fairly
young, responsible human being. Right. So far this has proven to be true, but I am wondering
about your age now. Tell me, are you in your 20s? No. Oh. Hmm. That hurts. Well, then perhaps you
are a teenager. Is this correct? No. All right. I'm tired of guessing. How old are you then? 33.
You're 33 years old? Yes. Yes. A 30 something. The body doesn't feel as good the next day after a
night of revelry. You can't stay up as late. It's tough growing old, huh? Yeah. You got that spot on.
What is it? So what month is your birthday in?
Are you going to dox me? Where do you live? What month is your birthday? What's your mother's maiden
name? September. So what's your answer? Let's try that last question I had for you before again,
shall we? So what month is your birthday in? September. You were born in September? Yes.
You know, autumn babies are often melancholy adults. Not that I mean to imply anything. I'm
just saying- He's talking to a 33 year old fucking- No, I've stuck my fin in my mouth. Melancholy guy.
He's just kind of roasting me. All I have is he's just destroying me with this like
fucking fax and all this awful shit and I'm just like, what's your favorite color? What's your
favorite food? I've got to- Hey, what's your birthday? July 29, 1999. That's odd considering
you're only three days old. That's very weird. What are your aspirations? What are your goals?
What do you like? Hey, why all the noise? What do you like? What do you like? Yes. So
what day is your birthday on? All right, let's try that one more time. What day were you born?
Let's think about what you said, shall we? I'm just gonna get my like name, my birthday, the fourth.
Let's take it down a notch, huh? Anyways, how has your day been? No, go away. Fine, I'm gonna do the
streamer joke. Are you ready? You all here? There's almost 6,000 people here. I will do the fucking
streamer joke, the YouTuber joke. Here we go. Fuck you. You can go away. It's really not a difficult
question. I said, so what day is your birthday on? Fourth. What's all that racket? I said the fourth.
I thought I'm like not paying any attention to the brother. He's gonna- he's gonna fucking
borg this motherfucker anyways. Who cares? This is our seaman. What is your name? Seaman. Seaman
Jones. It's really not a difficult question. I said, so what day is your birthday on?
Four. The fourth? Yes. Well, I'm sorry, but don't expect any presents from me, okay?
I'm just a poor seaman trying to make ends meet. Liar. Are you hungry? No, thanks.
Can I still like pet him? Or is this like- is he gonna be- is it like-
Don't make me laugh.
I'm gonna pee if you don't stop. I don't know what to say. I thought he wanted a name.
Pick him up. I'm not gonna- no, I don't want him to hate me. Good afternoon. No, it's not. What time is
it? Hello? What time is it? Now, where on earth do you think I could wear a wristwatch?
Decrease the oxygen in the water, but don't do enough to kill him. Just starve his brain of IQ.
That's fucking diabolical. What is wrong with you? Drop the oxygen in the tank to starve his
brain of oxygen so his IQ drops. I will name you. I will name you. So what are you looking at me for?
I want to name- I've been thinking about this, and if my calculations are correct,
you must be a virgin, right? I meant Virgo. Sorry, I know Virgos are very sensitive.
I hope I didn't hurt your feelings. No, I'm not, so sorry. Honestly, it's none of my business what
you do in your free time. Hey, no, what's up? No, I'm not a virgin, actually. What about you?
What about you? I am Seaman. Applause, please. Because to me, you're kind of just been in a
tank this whole time, decimated by Chad Jones. No, actually, he gave me a false statement,
and I threw it right back in this tank, and he doesn't even want to respond.
What's up? All right, let's see the other ones as much as a dick. Where is the other one? Up here.
Hey. Hi there. Hello. Hello. Hello. This one doesn't want to talk. Are you there? Are you there? Okay,
this one's dumb. He just swam his head into a pole. I think this one's just food. Yeah,
this one's just food. Let's get the heat up a little. Try it one more time. Good morning. Good
morning. Ow, knock it off. Are you awake? Excuse me. What's the problem? Finally, Jesus. What is
your name? Seaman. Seaman Jones. You both can't be Seaman. That's not your name. I am Seaman. Hear
me roar. You are not. That was interesting. We'll speak again soon. Is that me telling me that he
doesn't want to talk to me anymore? What do you want to be when you grow up? What's up? What do
you want to be when you grow up? No, leave me alone.
Okay, we're good. Anybody hungry before I go? No, not yet. Okay, so let's go.
He said he's not hungry. Feed? I guess I have to, right? I'm gonna be gone for a while.
I'm still full. Are you trying to fatten me for slaughter?
Pick it back up. Sorry, sorry. Just leave, leave, leave, leave. Get out. Would you like to save and-
Tomorrow. Next day. I'm completely invested in this now. I need to know everything about it.
All right, let's try again. Okay, so this is technically, this is going on five days game time,
right? I think. Should be, right? 315. No, no, no, no, no. Back it up.
When do we start? I don't remember, like the 10th? We started, I've lost track of time. I don't even
know what day it is now in real life. The 10th, right? This is playing with my brain. All right,
here we go. See if any of the new developments. This whole game is an elaborate phishing scam.
In a few days, the seaman will access your bank account info. What happens if you set time
backwards? That's a really good question. I have no idea. Would the game just break?
Or would they revert back to eggs? Good evening.
Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset. Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good
job. At the moment, the habitat contains two gill men. They appear to be very hungry.
Let me divulge the highlights for today. Would you like to give seaman a name? Call one of the
gill men and try saying, I will give you a name. I will give you a name. So let us head over to
the tank. So I have to feed immediately. Greg and Garfield, yeah. Chad, no, that's too easy.
I'm hungry. All right, just eat. Give me something to eat. I'm starved. Hey, thanks.
Where's the other one? Turn it on again. The other one didn't get to eat.
Do I have to drop another one in there? The other one?
How about turning up the heat? Peaceful. It's heated up. So he ate this one over here on the right.
Now we're good. Slow it down. That should stop at about 19 something. Hey. Hi. Shouldn't you be out
partying or something? I mean, this is technically a party. I will give you a name.
Okay, I'm going to let you give me a name. When you've decided what you want to call me, say,
I'm ready. I'm ready. All right, then. Here's how to do it. You're going to say my new name
three times. Each time I say now, say the name once. Got it? Now. Greg. One more time. Greg.
One more time. Greg. Okay, I'll remember that. Next time you want to call me, call me using that
name. And don't forget the name you gave me. Because if you do, I'm not going to tell you
what it is. Well, I think that pretty much covers it later. Hey, Greg. Greg. Okay, just be sure to
save some for later. What? All right, now I gotta give you a name. I will give you a name. I will
give you a name. I will give you a name. Hey. Hey. Food. Here. No, why? He's gonna become food
and he's gonna be eaten by his brother. Why is this one the smork? Go get it. Oh, good. Food.
Right here. Now will you talk? There you go. Okay. Hi. I will give you a name. I will give you a name.
My compliments to the chef. I'm gonna pee if you don't stop. Listen. Listen. Not right now.
You are the dumb one. You're the dumb one. And you are just food for your brother. I just want to
make sure you're aware of that. I have to make it very clear. You are in this tank to provide
sustenance to the smart one. Doesn't seem to care. Hey, you hungry? Greg. Greg. Hey, Greg.
What do you want? Greg, come over here. Does he pee? Do they actually pee?
I'm gonna pee if you don't stop. Don't make me laugh. Be nice to your brother. Can't see
anything. I share a name with the seaman so it's throwing me off. Hey, Greg. Greg. That would be
really weird. Clean the tank? The only way you clean the tank is you just put air in it. Hey, Greg.
Greg. Great. Now everyone will want one. What one? What are you talking about? Greg. What the fuck is that?
Adieu. What the hell is this? What is that? Is it an egg? What is this? Whose egg is this? Put this
tongue in that mouth. Dream on. That's poop? Uh, there's no way that's poop. That did not...
A big brick cement shit like that did not come out of one of these things.
There's an egg. That's a big ball of shit, okay? Let's play. Hey, Greg. Hey, settle down there.
Let's play. Do you want to play? I could use a hug. Okay, that's all I needed to hear.
Quit it. Quit it. It hurts. English. I'm not ignoring you. I'm thinking. What are you thinking
about? Hello. What are you thinking about? It's a secret. Okay. Tell me. What's up? America. America.
Look who's talking. Do you like America? You can go away. Remember when you were like
12 years old in a chat room for the first time? You went into like the international chat room?
And you literally just wrote, do you like America? And they're like, yeah, I guess. Yeah.
And they're like, do you like Japan? And you're like, yeah. You guys didn't do that? You guys...
Wait, that's because I was... Okay, my means of chat room. You guys don't understand this.
You have like a Twitch chat room right now. You've got all kinds of forums. You've got like Reddit.
Back in my day, we had Diablo II battle net and like wrestling fucking chat rooms. That's all there
was. I didn't have a Twitch chat. I had a Diablo II chat in a random battle net server. It was
incredible to talk to somebody on the other side of the world back then. It was. And kids these days
don't even realize. When you talk to somebody from Japan 20 years ago, it was like boom. Your
brain just could not comprehend it. Let's have a conversation. Let's talk. No, I'm all talked out
for today. Okay, I'll see you tomorrow. Goodbye. Bye bye. Don't eat your brother while I'm gone.
No, leave me alone. Good. We are reaching critical boomer. Goodbye. Goodbye,
food. That's really mean and fucked up. All right, I'll see you tomorrow. Let's go. Would you like to
save and it was crazy. If you were back in the day, if you were on the internet and somebody
picked up the telephone, it would the whole thing would break. It's got their Instagram and their
Twitter. You start to go to a pay. I'm sorry. I forgot to turn it off. Sorry for the blue. I'm
sorry. Yeah, back. I couldn't make a phone call from a device in my pocket. I had to go to a
pay phone and put in a quarter. I have Twitter. Yeah, but I tweet like once every three weeks.
All right, let's go. That looks all right. Let's go to like four for two in the morning.
Wrong date. We talked about it. That's fine. 316. That's the Stone Cold number.
I wish I could have experienced the dawn of the internet like you. It was pretty weird.
I remember playing Command and Conquer. Red alert. Neighbors. It was wild. It was a weird time. Yeah,
you just build power plants into the other person's base and then send 20 tonyas over
there. That was the strategy every time. Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good job.
First, a recap of your previous visit. You have given a name to one of the Gilmen.
His coloration has changed, so you should be able to locate him easily. Please take good care of him.
So that's the one that we have to take care of. Oh, yes. They have started to produce droppings.
The tubes on their heads serve many purposes. At the moment, the habitat contains two Gilmen.
That's weird. They have a forehead butthole. They are suffering from the cold.
Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level. They like poop out of the
top of their head. So let us head over to the tank. Somebody just said shit for brains.
It's cold in here. Please increase the temperature.
I thought I was definitely going to suffocate for a minute there.
Hey sup, boomer. Hey sup. Yay. It's the movie phone voice. Oh my god, I forgot about the movie
phone voice. If you know the name of the movie you'd like to see, press 1. If you know the name
of the movie you'd like to see, press 2. Holy shit, that's so old. Is that guy still alive?
Hey you. You used to have to do that. You had to call a fucking service on the phone to find out
what time the movie was playing. You know how easy you've got it now? We had to listen to a weird
robot guy give us every movie that was playing in the theater. Unbelievable how easy it is for you.
I used to have to walk to a pay phone and call movie phone. It was two and a half miles.
Okay, don't answer me. What did he say? Greetings and salutations my good friend.
How are you? Hello. Well hello. I'm thinking about some food, eh? You got it.
Food coming in hot. Hey, thanks. You're welcome. What's your name? Hello. Oh yummy,
baity goodness. Well you are the bait so that's true. Did you eat it? Okay, you have to eat too.
Technically I am a millennial. I know I'm a millennial. I know that. I want the recipe for
whatever that was. It's called molded together oats and like soy sauce probably. I don't know.
What is, how do you make fish food? It's like soy sauce and rolled oats and they crush it up
and blend it up and put it in a like salt shaker. Good morning. Hey, why all the noise? I'm sorry.
So what did you do today? What's up? What did you do today? What do you want?
Do you have any questions? Do you have any questions? Hey, hey, I've got something to say.
Hello. I just remembered something. Some of my memories are coming back. What is going on?
We're gonna get cut scene? There was this French man named Jean Paul Gasset who was trying to
raise me and he made this cage to hold insects and there were a lot of really tasty looking
insects in it. Is it still there? Can you take a look? Okay, so after a while some moth larva
will start growing in there. When that happens, use the L trigger to switch screens and grab a
larva and drop it in here. Can you do that for me? Yeah. Yes. So these not ready yet? That's wrong?
That's an egg. Oh, fuck. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? How do I fix this? How do I fix
that? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Can I get more of those? Do I have to reset? I
can't reset. There's no resetting in this game. I can't pick it back up. I still have one.
Unplug the console. It's fine. Okay. You can get more. You just need to water the other seed and
it makes more. Okay. Cool. Moisten the cage. Spray. How much do I have to spray? More spray?
It's red. Okay. It's good. Can I go? Can I overspray? Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I'm overspraying. Okay. No, that's it. It's already dead. It's not, there's no, it's not even,
it's already dead. All right. What does anyone want to know? Let's talk. Hey. Let's take it down a notch,
huh? Any questions? Yes. Do you have any questions? Let's have a conversation.
I will give you a name. What's up? I will give you a name. I will give you a name.
I will give you a name. That's not Greg. I'm thinking about some food, eh?
Greg, no, Greg is over here. What's up? Okay. Let's talk about, no, maybe tomorrow. What the
fuck? Today. Hey, thanks. What are you doing? What is he doing? Let's talk today. Tomorrow.
We'll talk again tomorrow. Let's talk today. Oh my god. If the larva things die, you have to start
over again. So make sure that this is always up to, up to being sprayed. So these are eggs and I have
to pick up the larva and feed. So I gotta be very careful about that. 100 spray, 100 spray.
I can't, I don't want to mess that up. Okay. Let's go back. Just turn the heat up a little.
We'll talk tomorrow. We'll talk tomorrow. Always make sure there's at least one egg
or larva in at all times and do not mess with the seeds. Okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
too hot, too hot, too hot, too hot, too hot. Cool it down. That's enough. That's fine. It'll be all
right. Goodbye. All right. Next day. I didn't kill one of them. What are you talking about?
No. Okay. You just get the shit out of me. Goodbye. Bye bye. Oh no, he's immune.
I'm gonna pee if you don't stop. Sayonara.
Hello. Goodbye. Good night. But I'm not tired. I was gonna scream go to bed as
loud as I could, but that was a bad idea. All right. Here we go. We got air light.
Let's dim it a little. See you tomorrow. Would you like to save and
peek, Mike? The other one's not an adult. When you name him, it makes him an adult. At least
that's what the guide says. Yeah. Every time I try to name that fish, it just doesn't,
doesn't want to do it. All right. Make sure I don't get you a blow. Get the blue.
There we are. Let's go. One more day. Another day. More evolution. Uh, that is Leonard Nimoy.
That's correct. That is Spock. What the fuck just happened? That is the Spider-Man down
the top of my mic. 317. 2019. Like, let's go like 11 30 or so. 317. Man, this would have been a
pain in the ass. You would have to play this for a week to get this far. That's way too long.
That's more than 24 hours. Wait, what? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
317. That's 11 39. What are you talking about? All right. Because it's okay. All right. All right.
That is way too long. How about it? Like 130. That's almost two days. That's good.
You can do up to two days. Yeah, but I don't want to do that. So it was just 316 at like one or two
AM. Now it's 317 at like one AM. One 30. They're not going to be dead. That's fine. Cause it was
like three AM before I just itched my nose and my nose and my nostril got stuck for a full second.
I don't know if it, did anybody see that happen? I went like this and the nostril was closed and
then opened by itself a second later. It was really weird. All right. That's fine. I'm going
to go with 130 thoughts on killing the seaman. Why would I do that? All right. 317 at one 30 AM.
I want to see what I just want to see. I'm going to like zoom in and look. I'm actually curious
to how fucking weird that looked. I didn't, no, it didn't do anything. I thought that was way more
interesting than it was. All right. Let's go close it up. I was going to do with like my feet. I was
going for an hour. Did he starve the seaman yet? No, they do. I got two. They're doing very well.
They're both doing just fine. Bye. Fuck. Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory of
Jean Paul Garcet. Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good job. Oh, my mouth. Let's see.
You have obtained the insect cage. This will be helpful in raising more food for seaman.
Keep your eye on it. Something will happen within shortly. Okay. Oh, the spray.
The insect cage is equipped with a spray to keep the moisture level up. Please don't forget to use
it. At the moment, the habitat contains two gill men. They appear to be very hungry.
Allow me to divulge today's highlights. Gil man has been growing and would love some variety in
his meals. Try giving him some larva from the other tank. I'm sure he'll be pleased.
So let us head over to the tank. Start lifting the weights of loser. Quiet. Remember 33. If you
were to guess my age right now, what would you think? Jeremy? Wow. I mean, I would have guessed
like 25. 24. Really? Double threes. I'm doing just fine. You understand? I'm doing just fine.
Double threes. Don't fucking look at that. That's so embarrassing. What a fucking idiot.
Give me something to eat. No, I'm a human. I sweat. That's what people do.
Relax. We're all humans. I'm older than Jesus. I don't, I can't, of what context are you talking
about? It's hilarious you kids talking shit about Jeremy. You wouldn't say this to him at land.
I don't go to lands. I'm good enough to participate in the land. So you probably
wouldn't see me there. Hey, listen. Oh, goodie. Larva time. Other than your weird forehead window,
you look great for your age. What's a forehead window? Your forehead window? Oh, good. I'm
feeling a little warmer. I'm starving to death. I don't know what that means.
Okay, finless wonder. Joke's over. Feed. Okay, let's get some food in here.
Why is there no egg here? How do I get an egg? Guys? Egg? How? Are you going to starve me to death?
Feed me right now. Well, come eat. Hey, thanks for the food. Go eat it.
Yeah, this really is the monster rancher monster. Okay, so you fed. Is it still alive? Oh, good.
Food. The seed sprouted into a little plant. You can eat this too? All right, thank god. I want
the recipe for whatever that was. All right, let me go back here and see this. It has a seed now.
There's a little plant there, so I need to spray. So will these things? I've never gotten here.
So if I spray, these things will all stay alive and that plant will grow.
Always leave one of them in here. Okay. Yeah, the plant will feed larva. Okay. So always leave one
bug. Always. Always. Okay. So they've been fed today. So that's good. You guys are good to go.
So let's chat. Where'd you go? Are we good? Make it a little hotter. Talk to the bugs. Hey, you.
I'm back. Let's chat. Bonjour. Happy St. Patrick's Day. Beware of green beer.
I forgot we were teleporting forward in time. Happy St. Patrick's Day. Like the spice. Let's chat.
Tell me, what do you do for a living? Streamer. You're an athlete?
No. Well, then what do you do for a living? Actor. Let's take it down a notch, huh?
He knows. He knows that was horseshit. Let's chat. Let me start over. I said,
tell me, what do you do for a living? Clown. Okay, I'm going to try this once more.
Once more. What do you do for a living? Clown. You're a plumber?
Yes. Perhaps you can tell us all what shoes go with a tool belt.
Close enough. I'm a clown plumber. What do you want? Let's chat. Well, I could go on and on and
so I'd better stop right now. It's been a pleasure. Saving. What did it save? The fact that he said he...
How old are you? How old are you? Well, aren't we rude? I will rip you from this tank,
put you in a pan with a coat of butter on it, sear both sides, and serve you to a rich family
at a rich restaurant if you don't start talking to me. He don't fucking care. Anything else?
What's up? Greg. Greg. Goodbye. Greg, what's up, dude? Word. Greg, can you sing? Sing me a song.
Did I tell you guys that I walked... Would you like to save and end the session?
I didn't tell you this yet. I walked to auto yesterday and I saw him. I saw the car. I saw
exactly who it was. Described the car. It had... All you need to know is, yes, it had a racing
stripe on the top. That's all you need to know because of course it does. Would you like to
save and end the session? Yes. I fucking... I couldn't get the license plate so I like...
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I didn't catch it though. He was going like 50. I could only run
like 30 or 40 so... All right. Anything else you got? Let's have a conversation. Let's have a
conversation. What? What do you think of humans? What do you want? What do you think of humans?
Let's talk. Let's talk. No, I'm done for today. This is the original Clash of Clans.
I gotta come back and play tomorrow. Can I like drop some fucking gems in here?
Good night. Hey, why all the noise? Greg, let's talk. Greg. Bu-bye. Greg. Greg. Remember to chew.
Change your console's clock. What the fuck was that? Yeah, we've been changing. I've been going a
week. Did he just shit? All right, let's make sure everything's good to go. Talk to the brother. I
keep trying to. The brother doesn't want anything to do with me. Every time I try to initiate a
conversation, he just doesn't say anything. Hi. Hello. Yo. Yo. Yo. Yes. Listen. Are you listening
to me? Are you listening to me? I will give you a name. I will name you. I'm just trying to get his
attention. Hello. No, this one doesn't talk. What? Quit it. Hello. It hurts. What's up? What's going
on? He doesn't want to even. What do you want? He won't even respond to anything I'm saying.
Let's talk. No, I'm done for today. Oh my god, of course you are. Pick him up. Stop it. Let me go.
What are you doing? Let me go. Talk to me. Come on. Let me go. Masher. Masher. He's dying. Okay,
put him back in. You good? Hey, settle down there. Now he's gonna listen to me. Hi. Right, I know.
Finally. Are you hungry? Here it comes. Well, here we go. What comes? Oh, he just pooped out of his
head. Okay. All right. Good night. Goodbye. Let's just make sure everything's fine. Heat it up to
about 19.5. Make sure the spray is at 100 and come back. Boil them. No, I'm not doing that.
I'm not gonna. I'm not going to kill these fish. The stream has been going on for three hours.
I'm. If you want me to end the whole thing. Would you like to. How are we doing over here? A big plant?
You have to understand something. This would be. I would waste the entire three hours if I just. Oh,
let me turn it up as much as it goes and we'll get to see them turn on their side and go up.
No. Would you like to save and end the session? He's supposed to ask multiple questions. Yeah,
he's I think he just doesn't like me. Easy. Here we go. Fast forward a day. You can play
Seaman 2 after this. I can't. Unless I have a Japanese console. Because that is a Japanese
only game. It never came out in the West. So it's now going to be the 18th of March.
Yeah, there is a two for some reason. It is 317 at 154. Let's go ahead and make it.
318 at 54. So at 1254. We had five community subjects coming right now. Five community
subs from Harmony Accord. Thank you. Five spot. Congratulations to those who got the five
community subs. And again, thanks for the fucking subs. 318 2019. We've been playing this game for
eight days at this point. After school, we come home off the bus and we sprint home
for eight straight days. After school at one in the morning. Yeah. You stayed at
the extracurricular activity. I don't know. You might be in like the drama club. Maybe you're
doing shop. You're in the math club. All you said to him when he was a baby was English and pizza.
No wonder he hates you. Anonymous Gifter just gave five community subs. Good evening. Thank you,
whoever it was. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset. Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. First, a recap of your previous visit. I seem so dedicated. The eggs in
the insect cage have hatched into larvae. It is important to raise them carefully.
If you put too many larvae into the tank, you may find yourself running out of food for seaman later.
But if you manage the larva well, you should have no problem keeping seaman well fed.
At the moment, the habitat contains two human. They appear to be very hungry. So let us head
over to the tank. Here we go. Do not remove the memory card during gameplay. Fucking kid. Don't
remove it. I had four before. Yeah. When they were babies and then they started eating each other.
It's cold in here. Sweet oxygen. Feed me right now. Five more community subs.
Potter fan. Oh, it's 15 in a row here. Thank you so much, Potter fan. Thanks a lot, guys.
Those are going.
Heat it up. Turn the light on. Hey, food here now. Hey, player, drop some chips in here.
Let's take a look. Give me something to eat. Just relax. I'm starving. Let's stop at 18.2. There we
go. Now we should be good at 18.9. That should get you 19.5, 19.6, 19.7, 19.7, 19.8. 19. All right,
here we go. Here's a plant. So we've got how many larvae in here? Maybe I shouldn't even use one.
Maybe I should just drop the pellets in. Another five community subs from Magellan. Another five.
Thank you. More 20 community subs now. More like 30 because Bebraham just came in with 10.
Thank you to all of you. And now here comes another five from Scrumpledungus. Thank you for five.
Thank you, Bebraham, for 10. The subs just rolled in hard here. Thank you. Thank you for like the
40 community subs right now. More than that. Jesus, thank you. That's a lot of subs. Missed me. I
didn't get one. Remember when I was, I was going to give like a thousand community subs, wasn't I?
If I fucked up that, oh my God. Amscoots. Would you like to save and end the session? Amscoots
gave 20 essentially. Oh my God. What started this? 20 from Amscoots, which is a huge amount. And then
La Cranda gave 10. I gave like 500. No, I didn't give 500. It was almost going to be like 500 or
something. I was doubling nothing over and over again. Thank you everybody. 20 from Amscoots,
10 from La Cranda. Holy shit. Thank you. Much love to you all. Let's feed the fish. So as long as I
leave one of these in here, right, then I'll be fine. I want to make sure that that's very well.
Like, no, I need more in there. More. Oh, no, no, you're talking about the subs. Spergiltron.
Spergiltron, thank you for the five community subs. Must have food. Another five. Now. Oh,
yummy, bitty goodness. How do any of the people in this chat know how to play this game?
That's a really good question. A wiki. People have the wiki open maybe. I wouldn't be surprised.
Another five community subs. Exifer. Hello. Thank you, Exifer, for the five community subs.
Is anyone out there? I'm right here. I'm right here. Hello. Hi there. Let's talk. Hey, Greg.
You have a bloody nose. Greg, let's talk. No. What's up? I was wondering, are you married?
No. You're unmarried? Yes. Really? Hey, that's okay. Don't listen to people who say you need to
get married. It's an antiquated notion, really. What a smart fish. You want to be to lower the
oxygen to make his brain IQ have a problem? No. Moo means moo, by the way. Moo, thanks for the
five community subs. All right, so you don't have to get married for what? You're not gonna get
married? Let's talk about politics. What are all your political positions? You know it.
Politics. Politics. This better be good. I will name you. Yes. I will name you. Do you want a name?
Okay, I'm going to let you give me a name. Finally. When you've decided what you want to call me,
I'm ready. I'm ready. All right, then. Here's how to do it. You're going to say my new name
three times. Each time I say now, say the name once. Got it? Got it. Now. Garfield. One more time.
Garfield. One more time. Garfield. Okay, I'll remember that. Next time you want to call me,
using that name. And don't forget the name you gave me. Because if you do, I'm not going to
tell you what it is. And there it is. Would you like to save and end the session? I gotta go like
wash my mouth. This is like a used microphone. I just put it in my mouth like deep. I don't
fuck around with that shit, guys. Somebody could have shoved that up their ass. You know what I
mean? Can I reliably say that somebody didn't shove this up their ass? I don't know. I'd like
to say no. It's absolutely not. But can you be sure? I don't know people are fucking crazy. I
don't know. I have to go see a doctor now? No, I just like rinsed my mouth with like toothpaste
and water. I took like I squeezed some toothpaste on my finger and like mushed it into my mouth
and like smeared it all around my teeth and like chewed it up and then like swished around and then
spit it out. On second thought, why didn't I just use a toothbrush? All right, sea man, let's go.
So this is Garfield. Hey Garfield. I'm not ignoring you. I'm thinking. I put another mic in my mouth.
That wasn't a used microphone. Tell me something. Do you like girls? Yes. Then do you have a girlfriend?
Yes. You do have a girlfriend? Yes. I'm not surprised you stood. Okay. Okay. Anything else?
What? See, he likes me. He thinks I'm cool.
This is the dumb one. No, it's not. This is the golden one. The golden one's the smart one.
This is Greg. Oh, fuck. Wait, now they're both golden. Greg. Hey, Greg. I'm thinking. What's
going on, Greg? What's new? He called. Yeah, he did call me a virgin like 30 minutes ago. He did.
Yes. Let's talk. Since you have a girlfriend, let me ask you. Are you two living together? Yes.
Really? You live with your girlfriend? Yes. Hey, good for you. Just remember, she's not your mom.
It's not her job to clean up your messes when you're a slob.
You don't think I know that? I know. What? So what month is your sweetie's birthday in?
April. April? Yes. An April fool, huh? Feel free to use that joke if you'd like.
The fuck did you say? Throw a fucking drink at him. That would be a very gross overreaction,
by the way. Oh, April, huh? But she's an April fool. Then she, shut the fuck up. You'd be like,
whoa, dude, you gotta calm down. So. Word. Word. So what day is your honey's birthday on?
Nine. The ninth? Yes. That's so sweet that you remember. I actually don't. I don't know.
Of course I know what my fucking girlfriend's birthday is, guys.
I'm doing it for the fish. I'm fucking with the fish. So, anything else? Word. Word. Word. Shut up.
You shut up. No problem. I'm just kidding, talk to me more. This is the whole video game,
I need to talk to you. Let's talk. Hey. Hey yourself. Let's talk. Let's talk. Well,
you're not just going to shit the bed, are we good? How are we doing? I think we're good.
Let's talk. I'm mad at you. I think I can. I think I can. Don't be mad. Don't be mad.
Don't make me laugh. You can't be mad. A pee if you don't stop.
Quit it. Quit it. It hurts. Are we cool? Garfield, are we cool?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Get some rest then. Let's talk. So I figured a couple things out,
matchmaker that I am. Your self-being a Virgo and your partner an Ares, no doubt the beginning of
your relationship was rather tough as you took time to learn where each person was coming from.
Ares tend to rush into things, whereas your Virgo personality will spend more time planning.
Don't be discouraged though, as there are many things you can learn from one another.
For example, you can teach your Ares patience and your sweetheart can help you cut loose a bit.
Live a little on the spontaneous edge. Just be aware that your Ares friend may be rather sensitive
of your criticisms at times and the two of you should be fine. So there, that'll be five dollars.
That was just vague enough to be real and just real enough for me to care.
Here's your five dollars. You hungry? No thanks. Let's talk. So listen,
do you have any kids? Yes, seven. No. So you don't have any kids right now, is that correct?
No. No. Wait. No. Wait. Wait. He didn't leave. He fucking daffy ducked me. He did like the Looney Tunes thing. No.
Yes. He daffy ducked me. He fucking like duck season, rabbit season, duck season, rabbit season.
I got rabbits. I don't even know what the fuck he said. Kids in the future? No.
I don't like how much information they're getting. Thank god there's no internet because this was a
game now. Everything you ever say to will get uploaded to a fucking data server and then they
would start selling it. Thank god this shit don't work now. I guess like this is Siri is the closest
thing. You don't think they're fucking putting that data somewhere in a fridge and keeping it nice and
cold? I disable Siri, man. I don't want that shit. You think I want Siri? Like Siri's always just
listening. How many times have you had like a loud ass diarrhea and you want like Siri to hear that
and get sent to fucking Apple? Are you kidding me? You stream on the internet? Yeah. But I don't,
I'm not streaming in my bathroom. I'm not like lying in my bed at two o'clock in the morning
like this on my iPad streaming under like the covers. What? Let's chat. Garfield.
Hey Garfield. What's up? Let's talk. I don't want to talk. I'm getting ignored. So tell me,
how is your father's health? See they want this data. He's fine. He's okay then? Yeah. I thought
you said he was okay. Is he or not? Yes. He's okay then? Yes. Good. I'm glad to hear he's doing well.
Is that like a idle mafia threat? You're gonna ask for like protection money in a few minutes?
Or how the bugs? I still, what is this now? This is like a cocoon. Can I talk to this? Hello?
What is this thing turning into? I got one more of these. Yeah, they have a face. Is that gonna
turn into a, that's like kind of freaking me out. All right, whatever. Let's heat it up a little bit
more. Can I tap it? I don't think I want to. Hey Greg. Greg? Okay, just be sure to save some
for later. Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's talk. Hey.
Call your dad right now and make sure he's okay. Oh, how's your father? Father's fine.
Oh, that's good to hear that your father is doing well. And there's like a long violin
horror sound. That like? I pick up the phone. I drop the phone like three times. I drop it again.
Dad? Dad? Dad? No answer. Let's talk. Let's talk. Is your father still working?
No. He's taking it easy, is he? Yes. Well, he's retired. He deserves a rest after all those years
of supporting your family. Actually, call him. You know, unless he was a deadbeat who never gave you
a dime. In which case he should be forced to work 80 hours a week hard labor. That's pretty dark.
Hmm. I'll try you again later. Let's talk. So, what month is your dad's birthday? Jesus, what the
fuck is with the birthdays? December. Hello. What month was your dad born in? December. He was born
in December? Yes. Yes. Interesting. The fathers of most people I know were born in December.
That's weird. Would you like to know the day? What? He knows your dad. So, what day is your dad's
birthday? 25th. The 25th? No. All right. Let's try that again, mush mouth. On what day was your dad born?
Mush mouth? 16th. The 16th? Yes. I'll remember that. Your father's birthday is important, you know.
But if you ask me, the most important thing is that your dad knows how much he means to you.
Unless you think he's a huge pain in the neck. I'd probably keep that to myself if I were you.
What are you gonna do to my dad? What are you gonna do to my dad? What are you gonna
do to my dad? Let me go. I'm just kidding. Maybe you should take a nap.
Quit it. Quit it. It hurts. Let's talk. Who wants to talk? Any news? Any news? Not much.
The fish have... What are you talking about? Anyone have any news? Garfield. I'm great. Thanks.
Let's talk. Let's talk. Is your mother in good health? Yes. She's doing well? Yes. That's certainly
good to hear. Thank you. Let's talk. When's your mother's birthday? So, tell me. Does your mother
work? No. She doesn't work. Is that right? No. Well, I bet she works hard enough without an actual
job. Being a mom is hard work, you know. And giving birth? Ugh. Let me tell you. I'd rather be eaten
by a shark than go through that. Not that I have any choice in the matter. The age group for this
game is for probably teens and early 20s. Not for old fucks like me. Let's talk. He wants the birthdays.
He wants their health reports. He wants the medical records. What month was your mother born?
August. She was born in August? Yes. My knowledge of you and your family grows ever more complete.
Let's talk. What day is your mother's birthday on? 20. I'm not familiar with that date. I said 20.
Do you have your own special calendar? Let's try it again. 20. The 20th? Yes. Of course.
It's all becoming clear. I think mothers are great. I hope you know how lucky you are to
have a mom. I'm gonna go downstairs for a break. You wouldn't want to end up like me. Forced to
depend on complete strangers for food and attention. He's gonna find where I am. He's gonna know my
mother's information, my father's information. He's gonna be holding a fucking knife. Put down
the knife. Put down the knife. Let's talk. You done? Is your significant other in the
room right now? No. Is there anyone else in the room besides you? Technically, yes.
There's like 6,000 people. Yes. Oh. Never mind. Let's talk. Tomorrow. We'll talk again tomorrow.
Okay. They've eaten. Let's make sure they're comfortable. What if there wasn't somebody
else in the room? What would he have said? It's kind of creepy. Actual murderer. I'm in danger.
We'll never know. 19.5. Looks good. Put the air up. Put the light. Let's go make sure we're sprayed.
Up at 100. So we have one. Here's the thing though. We have one. I got two pellets.
I have one bug and then one cocoon. The question is, should I just feed the pellets and let these
turn into seeds? You know what I'm saying? I'm just gonna use the pellets tomorrow.
I destroyed that egg. It was not. That was a bonehead move. It really was.
All right. Let's go. Would you like to... Tomorrow. Fast forward the clock. Now he asks if you're
like cheating on your girlfriend. I'm telling you. That's why. Shit. I forgot to fucking
mute the screen. Sorry. We did get a lot of talking though. 19th at just like a day later.
Close it up. Lots of personal info. Telling me doesn't exist. I'll try that.
The Dreamcast was really cool. Yeah. It was a very interesting system. Who should we call
if you were missing tomorrow? I don't know, buddy. They tried shit. Yeah, they did try shit.
Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset. Let's get some info. Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. First, a recap of your previous visit. Do I have any tattoos? No. None.
At the moment, the habitat contains two gill men. They are suffering from the cold.
Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level. Would you ever get a
drunk tattoo? Allow me to give you the highlights for today. Would you ever get a tattoo? No. Not
anymore. If Professor Gasset's data is accurate, we can expect a change in the gill man's body
very shortly. A change. So let us head over to the tank. We're gonna get an evolution here, I think.
Is Seaman gonna be Landman? I told you about the tattoo that I was gonna get when I was like 21.
I was gonna get the venom symbol right here. The venom. Good thing it didn't go through with that
one. I thought, I think it would be pretty cool. Remember, I was also like, I was also fit. So that
would have looked cool, right? Remember, I had like a fucking stacked up body. Somebody's dead. No.
It's about time. Another day. You want everyone to know that you're going to the bathroom. Yay.
Well, they do. They know now. Took you long enough. Hey, how about turning up the air in here?
Let me make sure I didn't go too far. Come on. It's like the wheel on Wheel of Fortune. Stop.
Thought I was definitely going to suffocate for a minute there. Having the venom symbol on your arm
would be the equivalent of wearing a monster energy hat. Hey you. Is anyone out there?
Wear a tap out shirt. Hey. Good evening. Does it evolve? Good evening.
Let's talk. Do you see any differences? I have another question for you and it's a serious one,
so no fooling around. Do you like yourself? I'll be honest. Yeah. You do like yourself?
Yes. Yes. I'll bet you like yourself. In fact, I'd guess you like yourself at least twice a day.
But seriously, there's nothing wrong with liking yourself. I like you too. Something's going on
here. Does this imply that, that's no, he's really just totally incorrect. Let's talk. Let's talk.
So what's the one thing you like most about yourself? Fucking loaded question.
What do you say? Let me ask this again and this time I'd appreciate an answer.
Okay. So what's the one thing you like most about yourself?
My intuition. Let's try that again. What do you like most about yourself and enunciate
this time? Sense of humor. Sense of humor. You like your looks? Yeah. Well, I like your looks too,
except for when you give me that one dirty one. What physical feature in particular do you like
the best? My teeth. Hey, why all the noise? My chin. My chin. Chin. Are you trying to break my
thing that allows me to hear? Come on, stay with me here. I said, so what's the one thing you like
most about yourself? Chin. Your chin? Yes. I have to say I've never noticed anyone with a particularly
exquisite chin before. Well, I mean, that is until now, of course. Where, what are we doing? Yes.
It'll cost you a buck. Let's talk. I know you said you like yourself and that's great,
but I mean, you're not perfect. Nobody is except maybe me. What's my biggest flaw? There's got to
be something you don't like about yourself. So if you had to pick the one thing that you dislike
most about yourself, what would it be? Hey, when somebody asks you a question, you answer it.
So are you up to answering my question now? What I wanted to know was, I know you said you like
yourself and that's great, but I mean, you're not perfect. Nobody is except maybe me. There's got to
be something you don't like about yourself. So if you had to pick the one thing that you dislike
most about yourself, what would it be? Your height? Well, as long as your body's long enough
to reach the floor, you should be fine. Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's talk. So it's interesting
that when I asked you what you liked best about yourself, you picked a physical feature. I mean,
you could have said personality or intelligence or a variety of other emotional or intellectual
attributes. Fake words. So in general, do you think that you are attractive? Oh my god, this is
like fucking with me here. I don't know. Sometimes maybe. Yes. You do. Sometimes I look in the mirror
and I look like shit and I hate it. Sometimes I look in the mirror and I go, I think I look all
right. Yes. That's good. Usually if you believe that you are attractive, other people will think
so too. What do you guys think? Because at the very least, they will be attracted to your
self-confidence. Okay, what do you guys think? People are gonna screenshot that and I look like
fucking crazed. Let's talk. So you think you're at least somewhat attractive. Well, do you think
other people find you attractive? Do you guys think I'm attractive? What? What? I can't hear you.
You know, let us revisit my last inquiry to you. That is, if you can cooperate this time.
So you think you're at least somewhat attractive. Well, do you think other people find you attractive?
Yes. So you do think people find you attractive? Yes. It's great that you think so highly of yourself.
Just be careful that your head doesn't get too big. Otherwise you'll never be able to buy a hat
again. I have a small head. Anything else? Let's talk. There's nothing I want to talk about right now.
What do you think of yourself? No, leave me alone. What is your best trait?
What? So not too long ago, I asked you if you liked yourself. Now I have a slightly different
question for you. Do you think other people like you? Yes. You do think people like you?
Yes. Well, that's good. You like yourself and you think other people like you.
That sounds pretty healthy. How are you going to turn this around on me?
You don't exist. You don't exist. How's that for a brain buster? Put this tongue in that mouth.
Dream on. You are a video game. Right, I know. You're not real. What do you want?
You aren't real. You are not real. Right, I know. You are operating on the Sega Dreamcast.
Everything is fine. Let's talk. We've been talking a lot about how you see yourself and how
other people see you. Now let me ask you this. Have you ever seen yourself on TV or on video?
Yes. So I guess you know then that the rumor about the camera adding 10 pounds isn't true.
It adds at least 20 and a couple of unsightly fins. It can be weird seeing yourself on video.
Were you surprised by the way you looked? No. Well then I guess you are just very comfortable
with seeing your naked body in all those positions. Oh wait, maybe you haven't seen that video yet.
You got tapes of me naked? Is that what he's trying to say?
You're going to jail. What do you want? You are going to jail. You're going to jail.
What do you want? You are going to jail. Let's talk. So you said you liked yourself. What is
with this whole self thing? You think other people like you. You think you're attractive
and you think other people find you attractive. All right well when you put it like that I sound
like a fucking narcissist. I'd say it seems like you have a lot of self-confidence and a positive
self-image. Would you agree? Sometimes, yeah. That's great but don't get too big of a head.
Otherwise. It'll make your body look funny. Hold on I gotta like take care of the other animals.
What the fuck is that thing? What do we do with the moth? Can I talk to the moth? Hello? Hello?
I hate this thing. I hate this thing. Hello? I can't even fucking. No I don't want to look
at this. This thing's fucking freaking me out. Another moth coming up. Smash it. Kill it. I'm
not going to kill it. Feed it. Do you have to feed this thing pellets? No, no. This thing.
No you don't have to feed that thing. Just make sure the spray is there and I'm going to feed
the pellets to these two. Oh yummy baity goodness. Can we eat claymation, streamer? I think that's all
that they're going to get for today. Tasty. Although you need food too. You also need to eat.
I'm out of food though. This is kind of the last bit of food I have for the two of them.
Can just one of them die? Hey thanks. How are you today? What? Tasty. Are you human?
What's the meaning of life? Eh? What's the point? As if you care. Give me the secret. Since I don't
have anything else to add, I'll be going now. Goodbye. Are you going to get legs or something
here soon? This might be ugly. You may want to look away. No let's zoom the fuck in. Evolve? No
let's just poo. Look at those little legs. See the little legs on the side? Someone talk to me.
What's up? Do you think you're attractive? What? Do you think I'm attractive?
Do you think I'm good looking? Hello? Am I attractive? Let's talk. No not today. Maybe tomorrow.
Skip ahead a few hours? Will you evolve? You're not so bad looking yourself. Thank you. Finally
I got the answer I was looking for. What are your fears? Are you afraid of anything? Amazing.
Well yes I guess so. Are you afraid? What do you fear most? Is this better? Goodbye. Have a good
night. Good night. Uh I think I'm gonna skip an hour or two. What time is it right now in the game?
Would you like to save and end the session? To skip till tomorrow?
To skip a day? Only go an hour or two. Yeah I'll go a day. Like not a full day.
I love cheating in old video games. So 319 at 47. We're gonna do 319 at like three four hours later?
Like maybe three hours? Two hours? I'm gonna say two hours. Not a whole day. Three hours.
Is your father working? I already gave you that answer. 12. 12. 12. You know a lot of 12s.
Let's just go there. We'll go there. Like 8, 10. Let's see what we got. Oh yeah. Blood type. I don't
even know what my blood type is. That was some weird like video game physics engine bullshit.
I just picked it up. I didn't do it. There's nothing in there. I don't know why I keep trying
to sip out of it. Here we go. This is your second visit today. It is good to have you back so soon.
Let's see. Last time did you notice the Gill man has begun to sprout legs? I did see the little
one. Preparing for the next step in his evolution. Land. However this tank holds only water at the
moment. Changes must be made to facilitate their new appendages. Also with the addition of legs,
this creature can no longer be referred to as Gill man. Rather he'll be referred to as podfish
from this point forward. Podfish. Did you see the moth emerge from the cocoon? I did. It is quite
amazing. If you missed it, watch your next pupa carefully. Vodfish. At the moment the habitat
contains two podfish. They are suffering from the cold. Please use the heater to raise the
temperature to a more comfortable level. So let us head over to the tank. Let's see how these
podfish are doing. Don't break that. You're gonna need it. So I'll be honest, I've never seen or
heard anything about this game other than the fish. I owned this game when I was a teenager
and I think I told you I got maybe 10 minutes in and said hello and then turned it off because I
didn't get it. I don't even know what possibly could happen. They actually have legs now.
That's scary. Oh goody. Yay. That's weird. That is very odd. Yeah that's weird. Let's take a look
over here. Uh oh. Where's the food? I don't have any food. There's an egg here. I see one egg. I
don't see any. Are they gonna die? Because right now this, I have maybe, it says two days and they
die right? The moth is food. I don't think I should do that yet. I'm gonna wait till tomorrow.
It's still the same day technically so they're good. You know I could really eat. Fuck. Hey.
Leave me alone. Let's talk. I like your new legs. What are you doing? Cool legs. Nice new legs.
I like the legs. Let's talk. Let's talk. Yes. You loading up on an answer? Let's talk. He's pissed.
What's the matter? I'm a little hungry. We're gonna have to fast forward today. They're not gonna be
dead right? Let's talk. Let's talk. There's nothing I want to talk about right now.
Now let's have a conversation. Don't repeat. It makes them mad. Well look here.
The reason why I'm repeating it is because see the little thing in the middle? When you hold a down
and you say something, that will change to tell you if they even heard it or not.
So when I talk, let's say I go let's talk and it doesn't change. I'm only waiting for it to change
and then someone over here wants to eat. All right I'm gonna have to go one day.
Is it chow time yet? Let's wait a few hours. Add land. How am I supposed to add land?
Oh I was looking at chat. We're fine. It's a little hoppy. That'll be fine.
I have no way to add land. All right this one's about to come out. All right I got two moths now
which means there's an egg here. I don't want to kill one of the moths because that's how that's
how they produce eggs. I'm gonna have to fast forward like three or four hours. I think I need
some food. Shit. I will feed you later. We're gonna fast forward. Let's go. Would you like to save and
end the session? We're gonna go like six more hours. Ask them for food. No land happens
automatically. I can't add it. Get some food. It'll cost you a buck. Produce food. No no we
gotta fast forward. Would you like to save? We're gonna go like six hours, seven hours ahead
because then it'll be one day. I hope they're not dead. Oh fuck. What do you think like 10 hours?
I'm saying probably six to ten. Why is a blue screen such a big deal? Because it's very bright
and if people have a full screen it's like incredibly jarring because I have a full screen
here and it hurts. I'll go four hours ahead see what happens. This is your third day coming back.
You are addicted. Please feed us. Why did Leonard Nimoy do this game? Who published it?
Um I think this was this was like a launch game for Sega Dreamcast wasn't it? This is no this is
a Sega game. This is produced and developed by Sega. It's like a first party title I think. I
should change it by like 10 minutes and come back like 15 times. Good. Good. Still alive.
Can I just get rid of one of the sea men? Screen show. Oh fuck. He said that I need to feed them
immediately. I'm sorry. I want to get rid of one of them. Like that's just too much to feed two.
He said that their legs are developed and they're hungry and to feed them immediately.
Damn it. I'm gonna have to right? Is it a larva? No it's just two of those eggs.
How long does it take for an egg to hatch? How long does it take for a little larva egg to hatch?
An hour? Should I just go back and do it an hour? Feed the moth? I there you don't feed the moths.
You can feed the moth now? Feed them what? Feed the moth? Well I don't have any food.
Oh feed you mean talk about feed them one of these moths because here's an egg that'll hatch
and then I got two of these. Is this a bad idea? I don't know if this is a good idea.
This is what's it despite there's a spider in here. What the fuck is this spider? What do I do
about the spider? What's a spider? What is the spider? I can I can eat this one. Kill it. I can't
kill it. I don't need to kill the moth now. Spider is food. Oh can I? Is it poisonous? It's a poisonous
spider. I have a larva though right now. We're good. I don't need to kill. Should I throw this away?
Flick the spider. Flick spider. I'm trying. I can't flick the spider. Spider eats the bugs. Flicker.
I... Would you like to save and end the session? I'll do it. No one's ever written anything about
this. Ctrl-F spider. Also note that all living things in the insect cage can be picked up and
either fed to the semen in your tank or stored in the storage matrix. I often find it useful
to keep a larva or two in the storage matrix in case you're having trouble getting moths to lay
eggs in the cage. Often because they are being killed by a spider. Speaking of which, occasionally
a kimoth egg will hatch into a spider. Although this seems highly unlikely, it does happen. So
we got a rare spawn here. If you feed a spider to you semen it will become sick. When this happens
you must spend a couple of days saying kind things to the sick semen. Like get well soon or I love
you. Cheesy I know, but it's better than having your semen die. Okay. Another annoying thing about
spiders is that if they are left in the cage long enough they will spin a web that your kimoths can
get caught in. If a kimoth is caught in the web it cannot escape unless you grab it and then drop
it back in the cage. The spider will kill it if it's in the web long enough. Since you cannot store
spiders in the storage matrix, the only way to get rid of them is to drop them in with your semen
after you've fed your semen. By the way we have to get the rare fucking spawn.
Since semen always ignore any food dropped in its cage after it has eaten they will not eat the
spider. The spider is also harmless to your semen and you should not worry about it being with them
as long as they have already eaten. Okay. So feed them the larva, feed Greg the real food,
and then feed Garfield the spider. That was a really fucked up strange laugh and I even saw
on the preview how fucking weird I looked. Okay here we go. Pick it up. Dude pick up the fucking
larva. Okay here we go. Which one of them is Garfield? I don't know. Whoever gets it first
lives. Oh good. You get to live. I don't even know who you are. Fucking he got it. God damn it. All
right now they've both eaten. Where's the spider? God this thing's terrifying. They've both eaten.
So now I can drop this in here and they won't eat it. That's what the game facts from like 1998
said. Don't eat that. Why are you doing this? Don't eat that. You just ate. Okay was this going to
drown? Don't eat it. Don't eat it. All right everything's good. I still have the two moths.
Perfect. Now they've both eaten and we're good to go. We're still surviving. Good. Now I have a
question. Does the spider stay in the tank forever until somebody eats it or will it just drown?
I don't see it. Hello. Get arms. Hi. Hey Greg. Greg. Greg. Hello. Come on let me talk to him.
Greg. The fuck are you doing? Hello. Garfield. I'm not even getting an indicator that they're
hearing me. Greg. Hello. Hello. Hello. No they're not even paying attention. Snap out of it. Let's
go. We have conversations to have. Let the mating begin. What do you mean let the mating begin?
You're not gonna like do two brothers and there's not they're not doing this right? Hey this isn't
the spice channel. Turn around. Why is this happening? Why would you have? How long are you guys
gonna do it for? I okay. Who's your daddy? Why is he dead? He fucked to death. What? He had sex to a
point where he died. He had a heart attack during sex. Okay. That's unbelievable. One of them had a
heart attack and died. So is. Hello. Hello. Just unresponsive. Let's talk. Let's talk. Talk to me.
So tell me do you own a computer? That's the first question. Yes. First question. So you
own a computer right? Yes. You have a computer and yet you'd rather sit here and talk to me.
Well that's touching. No really it is. Do you have a password? What is the password?
Let's talk. About what? You having sex with one of your siblings and then them dying immediately
after. Let's talk. What are you doing? Why? It's doing like the back though. Why did you do that?
What's wrong with you? What is wrong with you? He's very unresponsive lately. You. Garfield.
Garfield. He doesn't even want to indicate that he's hearing me. Beep beep beep beep beep beep.
Beep. Are you pregnant? Are you pregnant Garfield? Out of context. That sounds very odd.
Greg. This is Greg. Greg are you pregnant? That doesn't want anything to do with me.
I think we have to just leave for the day. It wants nothing to do with me.
See you tomorrow. Can I move the rock? What do you mean move the rock? Wow now that's dark. What's
this gonna do? Is this gonna like? You want to move the rock eh? Well if you want my help you're
going to have to answer my riddle first. If a human types 60 words a minute for eight hours a day
six days a week what does it have after seven months nope sorry the correct answer was
carpal tunnel syndrome well guess i can't help you then can i
so do you own a mac or a pc i own pc is better for gaming pc yeah you and the rest of the world
yeah so what kind of pc do you have a gateway i love those boxes they make me think of farms and
those computers were such dog shit gateway computers they were like two hundred and
twelve dollars they did exactly what you wanted they wanted you wanted to like read emails
and type on a word processor it was like a it was like probably 200 bucks or like top of the line
gateway they came out of the box it barely worked it was obligated that whoever was working at the
gateway like studio fucking had to boot over every single desktop before they shipped out
all right we've got this computer here hold on this i gotta have to have to do this for this to
land no i don't never mind yeah i do no i don't fucking whatever they would just drop it from
like a story up and then put it in the box let's talk let's talk so do you own a laptop or a
desktop ready for this i'm gonna flex on this motherfucker right now both both huh can't be
away from your computer for more than five minutes can you i got both let's talk word why don't we
have a conversation hello let's talk so what do you use your computer for video games tv movies
recipe recipes so you use it to send email now i thought you just said you use it for email
what do you use it for you want the laugh out loud lol answer porn i'm going to go do a
couple of laps doctor's orders let's talk okay one more time i said so what do you use your
computer for funny answer everyone's saying taxes so you use it to
browse the net huh yes we'll be talking a little more about the internet later on
i said taxes i didn't say anything else you're stupid you're an idiot i don't even like you
all right let me increase the time you get off to taxes point thank god we don't have to deal with
any others it's just garfield that's left spray it up now we have two we got a larva gonna be
hatching probably tomorrow sick yeah dude cool cool sick yeah sick yeah sick dude would you like
to save and end the session i want to i'm getting so excited about this 33 by the way sorry to back
seat you but do the rock again i'll go tomorrow don't you guys feel like if i go if i go far
enough and hard enough but uh that's like me ripping a tooth out do people really actually
do that shit i'm serious i know there's like a dumb stupid trope about like attaching a string
to your tooth and slamming the door with the doorknob being attached nobody actually why
would you just pull it out you know people that did do that why would you do that you have a
fucking hand go like this and pull it out why would you tie it to a door and slam the fucking
door that's such an elaborate cartoon villain way to do that let's turn it off another day
you went to the dentist and the dentist did that yeah go on come sit in the chair let me get out
of that are you comfortable yeah they're gonna get this out fucking fuck all these tools i'm
gonna tie your tooth to the string and i'm gonna slam my office door thanks that'll be six hundred
and eighty seven dollars 319 320 what cartoon dentist cartoon can you guys believe we've been
playing this for 10 days straight what cartoon dentist did you go to goofy did my braces
that'd be so cool imagine being a dentist and being in the full disney world goofy costume
and working on somebody sitting in a chair that'd be so hard just in the mascot costume you get
that that mesh vision like you're in a mask hello hurt somebody welcome to the laboratory of jean
paul gasset greetings and welcome back you're doing a good job very well did you see the pod
fish mate it seems that the tubes atop their heads have even more uses than we thought hold on i just
realized something however the male potfish died immediately afterwards it is unfortunate they but
he spent every last bit of energy ensuring the continuation of his species i'm sure he has no
regrets they go to the bathroom they poo through that too and use it for at the moment the habitat
contains one pod fish he appears to be very hungry so do we let me divulge the highlights
for today you don't poo have you noticed that you can move the stones which ornament the tank
hold on the largest rock however is too heavy for you to move alone the pod fish may help you
but only if he's in a good mood so let us head over to the tank i'm not even gonna say people
are saying it in chat already that's what i'm saying you do though you don't i'm not gonna
google that term i'd like to keep my lunch down not up many uses many uses remove the memory card
what what do you know let's heat it up calm down you creepy person you creepy person i didn't do
anything how big did they get thanks i believe i'm beginning to thaw that's good give me some air
how are the bugs doing all right how are the bugs
no hatching yet wait do we get a hatch yep hopefully there are no spiders left in here right
i don't think so nice okay two larva he can eat why don't you have some food must food now oh good
food in the matrix i mean i'll store i can store this piece right never eat again how long am i
gonna stream tonight i mean pretty much until uh we're like done with this hello is anyone out
there time store a larva in the matrix hello uh i couldn't think of a better person to whittle
away the afternoon with how do you have sex hey seaman don't play that what is on your head
you're too young to understand he's dead he's dying i thought i thought he was dead let's talk
let's talk let's talk he's doing tricks
he's coming over here what is it what are you doing you want to learn a trick cool trick
would you like to learn some tricks he hates me he doesn't even want to listen to me
he's gonna move the rock
help me with the rock nothing thanks can you please help me move the rock please move the rock
please move the rock hey thanks you're sweet too so would you say the computer makes your life
easier or more complicated you must know more about the computer easier hmm i see
obsessed with the computer let's talk uh more about the computer you were saying before that you
own a computer so i'm assuming you're not unfamiliar with computers what they do and so forth
would you be willing to say that the computer is the number one invention of the 20th century
no no no electricity really well then what do you think is the greatest invention of the 20th
century electricity i think i'd have to disagree with you 20th century sure computers aren't
perfect and some would say fast food restaurant humans all soft and weak
but people are evolving into much different creatures nowadays there's no need to escape
the jaws of any natural enemies your brains are in the process of a much higher metamorphosis
let's talk let's talk hey let's chat there's nothing i want to talk about right now move the rock
help me move the rock please well you know i try can you move the rock i'm okay
all right he's going over there do it all right it's quiz time
oh how many lives does a cat get one you asked someone didn't you okay let's give this a shot
then well animals you get you die you get one life you can move it i answered a stupid riddle
do i have to move it to help him where are we moving this to i don't know where we're supposed
to move this to just just move it what did that do it moved a little bit i think something's
going to happen if we move this rock all the way all the way move rock come on what do you say we
rest up for a second rest i'm not used to this sort of manual labor no you can't do it all in one
day everyone that's saying like god like 200 iq lol you can only do it like an inch a day
cover the air hole no take that off what a bad idea let's talk no let's go you're gonna do it
again here he goes come on move rock with me wait a little longer my limbs feel like they're going
to pop off if i don't recuperate first tell them you're gonna delete your save i'm going to delete
my save game hello i'm going to delete my save i'm going to delete you i'm going to delete my save
what do you want i will delete you he doesn't give a fuck cover the air hole and add air
i don't want to fucking torture him you ready to do this again again come on i need a little
rest fine come back in two hours i love you well this is a little sudden isn't it do you love me
okay i'm going to let you give me a name when you've decided what you want to call me say
i'm ready i'm ready all right then here's how to do it you're going to say my new name
three times each time i say now say the name once got it greg now greg one more time greg
one more time greg okay i'll remember that next time you want to call me call me using that
you are greg i know and don't forget the name you gave i know what it is you forgot if you do
i'm not going to tell you what it is wiggle this with me come on and there it is see you later
greg later fuzzy why is he telling me later greg help me move the rock
well as you can see i find computers pretty fascinating computers they've changed everything
around you so much that you probably couldn't even visualize a world without them
and of course as with any huge technological advance they've brought with them a lot of
dangers to watch out for but i still think the good that computers have brought to the world
outweighs the evils it's just important for you humans to communicate with each other
and not become overly dependent on your machines i'm not and that's all i have to say on the subject
let's talk again sometime soon let's talk now let's talk tomorrow we'll talk again tomorrow
fuck you might is he out of uh is he out of gas here can i not move this he's out of gas come back
tomorrow put larva in storage does it go bad these don't go bad right do they go bad doesn't go bad
okay cover the air hole no i'm not gonna cover the air hole we've gotten so far in the game i'm
not going to kill him your hair looks nice hey thanks all right so we got two moths i think
we're good we only have one person to feed this is uh sprayed up cover it and then add air add
air after you cover it i'm i'm not doing that yet not until i have a save and end the session
it's gonna blow the rock up and a piece of shrapnel is gonna
right through his head and everyone's gonna laugh their asses off because that's the end of the game
and look at like i'm very i'm so emphasize with my hands i need to get like something to eat i'm
gonna i'm gonna like eat a pizza should i eat like a whole pizza on stream i've never eaten on
stream before maybe like maybe i'll just eat a pizza on stream should i do that you've eaten
a raw onion before on stream i have not eaten a really you're thinking of somebody else where
the fuck did you get that from i've eaten a raw onion i've never been into a raw onion on stream
i'm desperately trying to think about what you're talking about i ate radishes on stream that's
normal i peel you cut them you chop them and you eat them what that radish is not an onion
i've eaten a turkey sandwich well no i took a bite out of a garbage can left outside in
the trash turkey sandwich right and i threw it away because it sucked because i couldn't eat it
uh i've eaten taquitos hello on stream welcome to the laboratory of young radish and hot dog
that's it there is a definite pattern to your visits it appears you are a punctual person
every day at the same time first a recap of your previous visit do you recall that when you tried
to move the rock the pod fish helped you while now that you nor seaman can move the rock alone
working together you were able to move it if only slightly
at the moment the habitat contains one pod fish he is suffering from the cold
please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level so let us head over to
the tank i will like mute i will get off the camera when i eat the pizza okay no no show
eating pizza what can i get a pizza all right i might have to take a i'm gonna take like a brv
here in a minute and go get actually get a pizza ordered because i'm not stopped i'm not the
stream is not over and we're still going i don't want to stop the stream as i have to eat
the last couple days off so i'm gonna eat too later no chat pizza what kind of pizza
i don't i'm not like the phantom nose i mean i like pizza hut but pizza hey listen up i don't
know if there is a pizza hut around here is there even a pizza hut in las vegas
does it even i don't even know is there did i eat it i don't think so it has to be i mean
vegas has everything is anyone out there it's probably like 15 get the decomposing corpse
pizza which is sausage pepperoni and mushrooms it's okay if you ignore me i don't mind what are you
talking about hi there hi there so it's the first day of spring is it just me or do you feel a
little tingle south of the border too i don't i do not you know i could really eat okay i will feed
you just hold on we got some uh spray issue here got another uh hatch that happened here down here
looking for spiders i think there's a spider down there yep get the fuck out of here i need to
don't touch him don't touch don't touch no no no get the fuck out of here okay i need to feed and
then drop you come here you come here no you where did i just get another egg from all right
i'm gonna make this quick hurry up eat that oh you used to eat first before i dropped spider in here
okay now go get spider drawn spider come here dick get over here good this game makes me feel
disgusted for some reason hey how are you leave me alone you just ate come here quit it quit it
it hurts let's talk so tell me do you use the internet guy is so weirdly obsessed with the
computer yes so you surf the net yes good you have to keep up with technology or you'll never
make it in this day and do we have anything else to talk about besides computers and the internet
have you ever browsed the internet do you use the internet what's up move rock it's quiz time
again if you answer correctly i'll give you a hand with the rock okay ready if you put a blue
lamp next to a yellow lamp in a room with white walls what color would the walls be white
that's right you've tried this before i'll take it okay let's why would it be green
don't three of you guys said green come on what the hell's up with that all right let's go
all the way to the left ready it's got to move sometime move that's it the third times the charm
i do it three times i hope it's like guy with a big fucking oven mitts let's talk talk to me so
this world wide web what do you use it for porn you use it for pornography yes sure
yes you've been at least you are on just fine do you have any more questions about the internet
i don't even care i'll do the funny meme answer just keeps asking the same question let's talk
about something else do you ever use email yes so you email people yes
do you prefer to keep in touch with people through email or the telephone telephone
yes there's nothing as comforting as the sound of a human voice
i must say even i've gotten used to it over time the game came out in 99 give it a break
i'm just kidding let's talk let's talk now here's something that you might be interested in as an
internet user okay i'm interested do you think the internet should be censored oh wow wow we're
really getting into this here that really i mean that's a loaded question
no so you don't think the internet should be censored is that right but that but what's that
yes yes well that's not surprising considering you're such a big fan of downloadable nudie
pictures but i only said i guess one can always count on the pervert vote in the free internet
debate i only said pornography because that's what he wanted to hear he was he want e do you
use it for emails hey about the computer i've heard the computer could be browsing the web
what do you use the computer for uh taxes oh taxes what do what else do you use the computer for
emails oh you even what what give me the answer i want so i can make fun of you let's talk so as
i was saying before there are a lot of really amazing things about the internet but as with
everything else it's not completely perfect think of it this way you can do almost anything on the
internet workshop chat get the news play games listen to music still true to this day pretty
much anything else you want to do that's all terrific but pretty soon people won't even need
to leave their homes in order to conduct their daily business you humans are going to get lazier
and less mobile and forget how to deal with each other face to face holy shit c man i think things
could get pretty ugly a few decades down the road do you think the internet is dangerous
holy shit wow is the internet dangerous yeah well i think it's good that you're exercising a little
caution about your internet use this is two decades later fire is a wonderful thing but i
wouldn't want to sit on yeah like literally two decades a place for everything and everything
in its place 2019 isn't that how the saying goes well i don't know about you but got it right i've
enjoyed this little chat about the internet it can be a wonderful thing for the first time ever
people can finally communicate with each other and not have race gender or culture prejudices
get in the way so in that sense it can be a great tool for removing biases and bringing people
together the telephone not after all on the internet nobody has to know i'm a c man on the
other hand like i said it can be very dangerous because it removes the need to interact directly
with the outside world especially with other people it's up to all of you humans to decide how
to use the internet intelligently knows too much so oh he knows too much you gotta go i come from
alabama with my banjo on my knee oh oh you're how would you start singing okay hey stop it stop it
stop it let's talk let's talk something let's have a conversation everything is fine somebody
wants me to ask do you know what memes are hello what's a meme okay one more time i said so as i
was saying before there are a lot of really amazing things about the internet but as with
everything else it's not completely perfect yeah think of it this way let him speak you can do
almost anything on the internet workshop chat hit the news play games listen to music and
pretty much anything else you want to do that's all terrific but pretty soon people won't even
need to leave their homes in order to conduct their daily business you humans are going to
get lazier and less mobile and forget how to deal with each other face to face i think things could
get pretty ugly a few decades down the road today do you think the internet is dangerous
yes well i think it's good that you're exercising a little caution about i will hold on i'll order
the pizza fire is a wonderful thing but i wouldn't want to sit on a sofa made out of it a place for
everything and everything in its place isn't that how the saying goes well i don't know about you
but i've enjoyed this little chat about the internet it can be a wonderful thing for the
first time ever people can finally communicate with each other and not have race gender or
culture prejudices get in the way so in that sense it can be a great tool for removing biases and
bringing people together after all on the internet nobody has to know i'm a sea man
on the other hand like i said it can be very dangerous because it removes the need to interact
directly with the outside world especially with other people it's up to all of you humans to
decide how to use the internet intelligently so that it won't harm you he said his whole speech
okay that was wonderful what well spoken well spoken yes yes it was let's talk
i have nothing to say are you real no i'm glad all right pizza time let's see let me see where i'm
going to save and end the session i'm gonna order a fucking deep dish and i'm gonna do like a huge
deep dish bite on camera it's gonna you can hear the squish of the dough it's gonna be like
i can't wait i'm so fucking hungry all right let me order a pizza over here back
deep dish deep dish all right yeah you guys gotta remind me you guys have to let me know
in eight minutes exactly from right now i'm preheating the oven and i'm gonna put this
by the way it's dr rokers so i was gonna order one i was like holy fuck what i just have dr rokers
why do i need to order a pizza uh but yeah so i this is gonna be the worst pizza ever because
i'm gonna put it in the oven for like three or four minutes i'm just gonna sit down there
and just gonna stare at it i can't like bring you guys down with me all right seven minutes let me
know hello i'm here how are you well i think that pretty much covers it later okay that's
doesn't want to do anything else we moved we moved the rock we talked about uh the internet again
what do you think about japan hey greg what do you think about japan is this better what do you
think about japan um i don't think so i tried all right so let's make sure everything's comfortable
got the light a little your house is on fire now kim is here but i need to like just be a
war i need to put it in what do you think about japan kim is burning no it's just it's safe
because of somebody else in the house so don't that's what i'm saying and don't fucking talk
about my shiny forehead how dare you okay no i think we're good to go would you like to save
move the rock one more time let's do it out kim is going to eat the pizza
seven minutes it's been seven minutes shit i'm sorry i got five minutes left well i'm just
gonna go down i don't even care if it's preheated i'm gonna go down there in like a minute and just
put it in and then let it sit in there and then five six minutes do it again seven minutes and
eat it it's gonna be fine 22nd of march looking good just bake it like a normal person it's in
it's the shit on the back is just a guideline you don't have to worry as long as it's cooked
all the way through plus those things are such bullshit anyways how many times have you left a
pizza in an oven with the right settings with everything done correctly i know what's that
it turns out all gross and burnt and shitty you i you always gotta do like two or three minutes
under what it says good morning welcome to the laboratory of jean paul gasset let's see what we
got greetings and welcome back you're doing a good job you do two or three minutes over
at the moment the habitat contains one podfish two or three minutes over dude he appears to be
very hungry so let us head over to the tank i'm so excited i need to have a good i got the good
good place for it it's gonna fit right here on a plate and i'm gonna munch on it it's gonna be
so hot i'm gonna go whoa how many days has it been how many days did i set it to
why is that so low well okay no no no no i thought that was air for a second
i thought it was air this is here i'm gonna go put the pizza in five minutes took you long enough
all right would you like to save and end the session all right pizza's in so in six minutes
i'm going back down there you're gonna drop the pizza you think this is an elaborate joke
we're gonna put the pizza on the fucking ground why would i ever do something like that i'm gonna
go in there and just be like a clown and like whoops it's gonna fall and flat down on the ground
camera's not even set up for that that'd be a waste of joke pizza on the floor you guys are out of
your minds put the pizza on your face hey food here now we have any more no spider right
i don't see any spiders i think we're good we got two larva feed me right now all right i got
i'm gonna hold on to you i got fresh ones right here did they go bad these don't go bad right
in them i think i asked that already here's your food let's move the rock
keep an eye on the clock i'm serious in like three or four minutes i'm gonna get it
you already asked that i know but i'm fucking dumb that hit the spot hello you must talk are
you listening i'm here hello what time is it uh fuck this is i'm gonna get this wrong
9 p.m. what do you want move rock as if you cared okay let's try this again shall we
what pizza place did you order from the frozen section from if a man yells for seven days straight
and his pitch raises an octave every three hours what does he have at the end of the week
a sore throat correct very good okay let's go how is that cheating it's just a basic
trick question an average germa stream all right move it let's go
this is the last day i need to move this go go go go go i just do it more wow look at what we did
what did we do i don't know what we did i don't get it let's talk we just moved to rock that
pizza would you like to save and end the session all right it's been four minutes
oh i gotta turn the stream off i was rushing to get back up here and i dropped the whole
thing on the ground i dumped the whole fucking thing on the ground going upstairs
so i'll see you on that i said goodbye guys you want to see everybody said oh it's gonna be raw
it's gonna be raw look at this fucking pizzeria pizza take a look at this you don't think you
should you don't think a dr roker's pizza is the best fucking frozen pizza you could possibly buy
are you shitting me right now like are you shitting looks fucking incredible i'll give
you a bite look at the cheese come down nope that was hot i'm never going on camera ever again
zero crunch oh yeah zero crunch huh
oh
oh i'm gonna eat i'm gonna enjoy it
crunchy why did somebody just give a hundred bucks somebody actually just gave a hundred
dollars luxuriant hat thanks for the hundred dollars they say ow you just bought this pizza
like 12 times thank you so much for the hundred bucks now there really is crunch on this though
that's what a fucking embarrassing clip look oh shit ready is it on my chin what is that
oh it's just shitty facial hair never mind ready i'm gonna give you a crunch warning
people don't like hearing crunches mouth noises and that shit i completely understand here's your
five second uh warning here here it comes i'm such a filthy fucking eater that's why i can't
eat on screen you should see me in a restaurant i'm filthy i'm absolutely disgusting i can't
fucking drop them how do people eat on stream like this i don't fucking understand i have so
much self awareness and self-conscious when i'm eating i can feel everybody's staring at my
disgusting mouth all right how many pepsi to wash it down what is that i don't want that in my food
don't touch it what the fuck now it's gonna i thought that fell did it fall off the plate
all right there's one piece and i'm gonna go back i need to get a drink i fucking hate being
on camera needing fucking tv commercial oh dr roger sucks really you've seen a ninja turtle
cheese slice like that that looks disgusting oh shut up give me a break really disgusting
unbelievable i got god be i'll be quiet it looks like boogers it's no that's um i don't know what
is it that's like um i don't know whatever it is what is it pesto that's pesto mozzarella tomatoes
it's mold yeah this tastes like really this tastes like penicillin i don't know why
i'm so high don't tease me like this i'm trying to turn it off that was a mistake okay this is
really hitting the spot though for real i can hear it going into his nose oh it goes just down the
same tube eventually don't talk with your mouth full i can't help it i'm from boston we speak
with each we eat our hamburgers and hot dogs and fucking chicken no this is good this is like a
eight out of ten all right look just i'm gonna just watch seaman for a little while i'm gonna eat
let's see in a second i got one more slice i need like an ice cold coca cola coke i like coke
coke versus pepsi i think uh coke is better it's got more earthy flavor pepsi's there
uh germa lied about minecraft vr just get 10 community subs i did not lie i'm doing that on
the next vr stream which is gonna happen next week why how can i lie your name is gonna be very very
irrelevant in like five days you have to change it to germa told the truth about how good this
crunch quality was all right i'm done i just ate a whole pizza in like six minutes not even that's
got to be some kind of record right eat a whole dr oka's pizza in like seven minutes
come on that's got to be a record that's a whole pizza i told her i was gonna do it
i could probably eat another one if i really wanted to but alas we're not going to do that
i'm gonna like burp really loud off camera and then i'm gonna get a coke so sorry the last like
20 minutes or so has been about eating food and shit oh i'm good let's come back
my grocery store recently started selling dr dr oka pizza and you're right they're by far the best
brand yeah absolutely they are dr oka's pizza is the best frozen pizza you can buy i will fight that
every day i just will but seriously thank you to luxuriant hat for the hundred bucks all jokes
aside it's a lot of money and let's go well i didn't have to come back right when i like did
buy like lick my chops that's good okay back to seaman hey i'm back how are you oh you almost
gave me a heart attack let's talk click on the rock again didn't we already do this all right
here's another one what do you have if you put a cat in a fish bowl a wet cat right you are
all right i'll give you a hand i was gonna say catfish then i looked at chat and cheated
how much further do we really have to do this this is too far let's go it's got to move sometime
cutscene why wait why wait a cutscene i think we did it next stage of the game let's go
right he's gonna die can he live outside the water he was called seaman oh it's like a new habitat
okay i'm gonna sneeze okay i got one at least i got one i'm gonna fucking stream i'm eating like
sneezing burping how do you like your new home every time i eat every time i eat i get like
stuffy nose that happened anybody else if i eat a huge meal my nose starts to run
i have like a day in the illness or something let's talk maybe he doesn't doesn't want to talk
let's talk hey sorry i'm busy you're busy he's having fun that's good are you having fun
what do you want are you having fun should i be yeah let's talk i don't want to all right we got a
new habitat he's gonna grow legs he's gonna start walking around okay when is it gonna have
babies isn't it pregnant would you rather be the funniest or smartest person in the room well the
funniest person in the room is the smartest person in the room because they can come up with the
observations and the kind of comedic value and things maybe other people couldn't see they are
probably the smartest person in the room so the funniest person would be the smartest person
because they can just go through all the knowledge and come up with the scenarios that require you
know for conversational purposes what am i going to feed greg he already ate all right i think
we're good let's make sure it's hot does it need to be colder or hotter this might need to be
warmer now is it not warm enough too warm that's too hot right hotter than this is this going to
be too hot is this too hot okay no it'll be probably between 20 and 30 now what's the cutoff
here 30 no it's too hot now okay all right i didn't know i didn't know i didn't know hey
enough with the heater already between 20 and 25 so what about there's no more oxygen though
it's only heat no more oh two interesting what's my favorite musical instrument stand-up bass
just this so that's gonna come down i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry you'll be cool in a second
all right any more larva yeah we got a larva here let's store this larva we're good spray it up
new day would you like to see what let's see what happens tomorrow
english horn is my favorite instrument it's actually not but it's the stand-up bass he might
miss it what are you talking about he might miss what he's gonna miss it the birth the thing's been
pregnant for four days the animal's been pregnant for like four or five days it'll be fine we'll go
the next day 23rd 4 30 close it up he did miss it uh i gotta get closer you've been streaming
this game for days and i missed it all this time um yeah look at your watch man you can see i got it
all right lennard update me how are we doing today good morning welcome to the laboratory
of jean paul gasser your schedule appears to be quite erratic i hope that seaman is not disturbing
your everyday routine you woke up at 4 30 to play seaman very well your team effort with the podfish
to create dry land was very impressive congratulations on a job well done at the
moment the habitat contains one podfish one long fingernail he must be grateful to have
such an attentive caregiver i'm sure he will respond to your feelings for him
letter what are you talking about today's highlights the pregnant podfish will soon
give birth he missed it make sure you do not miss this dramatic experience he missed it though
so let us head over to the tank it sounds like me can't believe you missed it why did you miss it
i just did the voice i did the voice somebody said do the voice
don't bully me and you feel like you're being bullied i didn't bully you heat it up do the funny
scream hey hey where we at light turn it on it's fine maybe a little bit more hello
is anyone out there i am but not yet check the bugs let me see oh that's the worst when you
drink soda and you burp and you hold it and it comes out your nose and it hurts
oh it's like acid shooting through your nostrils uh no spider i think we're good
all right hello how are you doing you what what what is it oh this is too early too early
let's talk are you gonna get birth or what wake up do you wake up wake up be seeing you
here we go birth no
where are your babies where are the babies babies what where are the babies you still pregnant
you still pregnant yep what's up where are the babies what the hell is going on out there
where are the babies where are the babies where are the babies who's talking where are the babies
where are the babies you're just not my type what do you need i'm mad at you right now so go away
wow i'm even better looking on land you look great you look great you're not even on land
you can't okay i have a what does that mean oh wait we're getting a cutscene
is this motherfucker gonna get disney world first ever male pregnancy from the sea man
um
should i be doing something
are you okay are you all right
oh do you need me to get you something
this is like what my father sounds like when he's doing deep tissue massage
i can't there's no i have a function here put food in there
oh are the babies coming out
do i have to put food in here
just giving birth
push push push push am i allowed to leave this game is upsetting me
yeah you can leave if you want
look i'll turn it down so it's not as horrible uh i should have gotten the pizza here i'm an
imbecile what what what what do you mean i'm sitting there what i can't do anything i have
a i have the no smoking sign what hello is everything okay in there how are you i can't
help him back into the water i can't he's stuck oh god he's gonna puke he's gonna puke four
quadruplets deceptuplets more no way no wonder it took you so long that's six tuplets
you're not gonna have seven six babies well that was fun yes i'll uh i'll call you let's talk
no how do i take care of the babies dead no not dead dead okay we're back here looks like a
cricket okay um so i guess we're gonna just fast forward now what's going on over oh all right
we're good a couple more about to hatch put the eggs in the water put eggs in water i can't was
he supposed to have the babies in the water you can't even do it no yeah i'm getting jebaited by
one guy all right and end the session let's see what happens tomorrow let's see how mom and babies
are doing tomorrow there's water inside the egg that's true you're right oh my god i almost fell
down uh tomorrow 24th at not like a whole 24 hours flex for us ah i'm good i just ate a whole pizza
i can't do that for you right now i just ate a whole pizza for you guys i ate a whole pizza
for you flex that's asking too much does coke expire good evening welcome to the laboratory
of jean paul gasse here we go greetings and welcome back you're doing a good job so this
would be two weeks no no four yeah two weeks let's see since the game technically started fish
emerged onto dry land to lay eggs however it expired immediately afterwards take good care
of the hatchlings so dead as an important life was sacrificed to create them oh shit
that was we've known that me to divulge today's highlight we've known greg since the very beginning
it is about time for the eggs to hatch pay close attention to what emerges so let us head over to
the tank all right so the eggs are about to hatch no more talks of the internet don't worry the
babies will come out and ask about emails he was mad at you when he died he died with all the
knowledge of my family that's true why would the game have you do that if they're just gonna die
in two in-game days and two in real life days two in real life weeks what's your father's birthday
we ain't gonna get to december what do you why do you want to know that i've lived for two weeks
can't wait to wish your father a happy birthday in six months are they gonna hatch i see them
moving around in there so are they gonna come out with arms and legs or are they going to go right
into the water i don't know i already see a major issue though there are six babies and i only have
realistically one to two larva a day i don't know what's gonna happen here i don't have enough food
for the six miles to be let's get the light on all right that's good slow down slow down no no no no
25 25 25 25 25 25 25 stop stop stop stop stop stop back back no back back oh that's bad
Why is it still going up? Sorry, it's not that bad. What are we doing over here? Two.
About to have three moths. I have another one here. Let's put you. Two of you guys.
Alright, get over here. Let's store these two. There's a spider. Where's the spider?
Oh fuck. I can like fuck up his web, right? Thank God I caught that. You come here.
What's with this one? This one's different. Kill the spider now. If I drop
this spider in the tank, is it gonna kill the babies? Is it gonna be bad?
Drop it in the water? I can't choose where it goes. It just falls. Where is it?
Where did it go? Anybody see it? I heard it drop into the area. Shit. It's alright.
How do I get rid of this web though? Is that the only spider in here? Yeah. How
do I like kill the web? I don't think I can. It's behind the rock? Alright, that's good.
No. No, he's gone. He ain't here. I think he went right into the water and drowned
instantly. At least I hope. Alright, let's get this party started. Come on. You guys
got me paranoid now. You ready? Come on out. Let's go. Out, out, out. Life goes on.
Oh, it's... What? Why are you alive? It was behind the rock. How do I kill it? I can't
pick him up. Don't eat the fucking eggs, please. Make it run into the water? It's
running into the wall. Flick it? I can't. See, it's gonna go flick. No. Drag the other rock
into it. That's gonna take like three years. I can't move this that far. I can't move this
rock either. This rock is stuck here. How do I get rid of you? I think he's dead. No.
Into the water. Into the water. Drown in the water. Go. No, why are you going this way?
What the fuck is he doing? God damn it. Spider's gonna die in a day, but what if they're born
in a day? They might be born right now. And then there are just three kills. I'm so afraid to turn
this off and go switch to like an hour. Use the air. I don't have the air as an option anymore.
All I have is a heater and light. I'm stressed. Yeah, you better believe I'm stressed. This is six
like plus hours of in-game time. Of course I'm stressed. I don't want this to go that wrong
after six straight hours. Save scum? I don't think you can in this game. That's like the whole point,
right? All right. I'm gonna. Hello. I don't know. Should I go fast forward like two, three hours?
Just wait a day and hope for the best. Would you like to save and end? All right. Let's see what
happens tomorrow. I have no idea what's gonna happen with the spider. Does anybody know how long
it takes for actual in-game days to see the completion of the game? I'm gonna say probably
30. If I were to take a guess. Was this 25? Did I change? I don't even know. Did I change this?
Was it 24 or 25? 26? I don't remember. It was 24? We're going with too many time
warps into the future for me to remember. It's 25. It should be 25. Three. Okay. It was 24.
It was 24. Changed it to 25. It was 24. Okay. Good. Okay. Just making sure. What's all over
the back of this? Chat actually needs to stop. Nice webcam. Thanks. It's the Logitech on the shelf
at Walmart series in every single Walmart. Greetings. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean-Paul
Gasset. Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good job. Let me divulge the highlights for today.
It is about time for the eggs to hatch. Finally. Pay close attention to what emerges. So let us
head over to the tank. You said that last time. Did they leave an audio clip in there of him
clearing his throat? They didn't. They cut that wrong. The audio director really kind of let that
one slide through, huh? All right. I think the spider is gone. Watch there be like 12 spiders
over here on the corner. How are we doing on heat? All right. Hatch already. So we can see what the
hell this is all for. He heard you talk over him, huh? That's pretty cool then. The creator of this
game wants to make a sequel. I think that now is the time to do it considering the technology
has probably gotten so much better. Just speech recognition in general has probably in 20 years
has gotten about a thousand times better. You could do so much more with a game like this.
There is a sequel. Yeah. I'm talking about like a current gen sequel. All right. Stop that.
Are you guys ready yet? You're causing us all so much anxiety. It's time to get out. It's just
saved right there for some reason. That usually indicates a cutscene or something. We're getting
real close now. Hello? Are you going? No spider, right? I don't see one. I got plenty of food
stored up though. This is great. Three moths. I need to fill the coffers of food. So did somebody
say that these were poisonous or did it just look different and that's all? Cman3 is in the
works. It's going to be VR. They tweeted about it. Well, I know what we're doing when that comes out.
You better believe it. All right. Hatch. Hatch. What else do I need to do? The environment is
perfect. Hello? Come on. Come on out. Come on out of there. Come on out of there. You can do it.
I love you. You can do it. I love you. How did I get a Dreamcast? I bought one. You can get them
pretty much anywhere. You can get them on Amazon. You can get them in local electronics stores.
Ebay if you really want to. All right. I'm getting impatient. Don't you see the spider? No, you don't.
Where? No, no spider. Come out of the egg. Get out of the eggs. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. All at the same time. That was odd. All right. Hey you. Hey. Hi there.
Welcome to the world. Welcome to life. Come over here. No, I'm fine. I had some hot chocolate
earlier. Let's talk. I don't want to. Anybody hungry? Hungry? No, thanks. Not hungry. Hi guys.
Welcome to the world. Can I help you? I was wondering how is your health these days?
It's okay. You feel all right? Do you? Yeah, I'm okay. I thought you just said you felt great.
I didn't say great. If you're just going to mess with me, I'll have to remember not to give a crap
about you. Let's try this again. How do you feel? I feel good. You feel all right? Do you? Yes.
Back to the dumb question. Well, I'm glad to hear it. You know how I worry. You just came out of the
egg and you're back to your father's tricks. You're a baby. Throw up. Let's talk. So you feel pretty
good, huh? Well, that's great, but being the Virgo that you are, I bet you probably take your
health for granted sometimes. Is that true? Yes. Uh-huh. I thought so. As long as I've been around,
you soft little creatures, you never seem to know how good you have it. You just have to walk to a
payphone and call collect. Now you guys have got all your little fucking devices. He knows.
Let's talk. Let's chat. So as I was saying before, you humans haven't always had it so easy.
Picture this. Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago. There's no heat, no cold medicine, nothing. Okay.
It's just you against the elements. Imagine if you had gotten sick then. Hey,
are you listening to me? Yes. Oh, good. You might actually learn something then.
Egypt 5,000 years ago? Well, let's talk. Anyway, where was I? Oh, yes, I was berating your species
for taking your modern amenities for granted. For example, it's spring, but I don't see you
out in the fields planting the crops. That's because I need to explain how this works.
What do you want? Are you hungry? Yes. Okay. Tell me something. Have you ever seen the Egyptian
pyramids? And not just on PBS. I mean, with your own eyes. Your father was obsessed with computers
and now you're just talking about Egypt. No, I've not. I didn't think so. God forbid you should
go somewhere farther away than the Starbucks on the corner. I just moved across the country.
How much time and work it must have taken to build those pyramids. I mean, there's no way that even a
whole group of you little humans could have lifted one of those rocks with your bare hands.
They had to invent levers and axles and who knows what else. Now that's evolution.
Uh, the Egyptian pyramids were built by like fucking hundreds of thousands of people
that did have to do that. You don't know shit. Like 45 million people died making those pyramids.
They had to invent levers. You're not the brightest fish in the tank, are you?
Can I help you? Here's another question for you. About Egypt. Do you wear glasses?
Well, actually it doesn't matter. My point is this. If you'd had bad eyes when you and your
ancestors were still running around in the wild, you'd have become some lion's midnight snack pretty
darn quick. And yet right now, one of the most powerful people in the world is that four eyed
guy in Seattle. You know who I mean. How far do you think he would have gotten in a fight with a lion?
See, you humans are totally helpless without your two gates.
Bill Gates? Gabe Newell? I mean, you just described like potentially every other tech giant company CEO.
Anything else? Got anything else to talk about? You're not so bad looking yourself. Are you keeping
up with me, Fuzzy? Can I go on? Fuzzy? Yes. Okay, good. You might want to pull up a chair because
this might take a while. What? It gets lonely in here. I have to talk to someone. Anyway, as I was
saying, at some point, about five or six thousand years ago, humans finally came up with the greatest
tool of all. You know what that was? The shovel. Oh, do you? Well, what was it then? The shovel.
Oh, do you? Well, what was it then? The wheel. The wheel? Good guess, but no. The greatest tool of all
is language. Without it, you wouldn't be talking to me right now. I'm not even going to ask if
you're grateful. Anywho, sooner or later, this guy named Pythagoras came along. Pythagoras theorem.
You know who he was, right? Yes. Well, good. I can see this conversation isn't a complete waste.
So this Pythagoras fellow came up with another important tool, and that's logic. So after you
have language and logic, you have mathematics and technology and industry and everything else, and
that's how you've gotten to where you are today. With your glasses and your cold medicine and
farming machinery and cars and TV sets and dreamcasts and rock and roll music. He said it!
Okay, so it's a little more complicated than that, but the point is, humans started out pretty
helpless and created all these things to make their lives easier, just like Whirlpool. And that's great.
Would be for you. Just be careful not to get too dependent on all your little crutches.
Well, I hope I haven't bored you to death. Okay, if I have, go take a nap or something.
Go figure out the Krabby Patty, you fucking loser. Hey, do I grab you? Let me go, you jerk.
Masher. Masher. Are you crazy? Put me down. Masher. Who's the one in control here, buddy? Let me go,
you jerk. What are you doing? Oh, you're crushing me. Let me go, you jerk. Stop it. Power is power.
You best not forget that. Any more brain busters from the fish, people?
This is expensive, don't do that. Oh, hey you, come here. I'm okay. What do you have to say?
Anything interesting? Let's talk. Is your significant other in the room right now?
No. Is there anyone else in the room besides you? No. Good. I have something I want to ask you.
Come closer. I don't want anyone to overhear us talking. Okay, here's what I want to know.
Are you fooling around on the side? No. You're not cheating? Oh, come on. Tell me the truth.
Who am I going to tell? The Rock? So come on, are you having an affair? No. Well, that's good.
I wouldn't want anyone to get hurt, you know. Why do we want these things to breed? If you're a
scientist in a lab, aren't you right now having an internal meeting about like,
we can't, this is not what we want right now. This is bad. These things are going to grow up
and they're going to, they're going to kill us. They're going to like enslave us all and we're
going to be, it's going to be horrible. Look at this shit. You want these to grow up and have like
cyborg laser arms and shit? No way. If they were big enough, we'd all be dead. At this point right
now, you've got to drop like five or six packets of Kool-Aid in here and like baking soda and like
vinegar and stuff and just stir it and then leave. You'd be saving all of mankind. Release the spider.
Let's talk. Do they not want to eat? I'm surprised no one, are you hungry? No. No, I don't think so.
Let's talk. No, I'm all talked out for today. Okay. If they're that smart as a tadpole, think
about when they're, yeah, they're as, as intelligent as a person. If these things even got to toad
status, they would have already developed a nuclear weapon. Let's go back. No spiders.
So I heard of this thing called the nuke. What is that exactly? All right, so we got three now.
Would you like to save and end? Let's check on them tomorrow. Nice bug collection, nerd. Have you seen
what these bugs are capable of doing and saying, if you came over my house, I go to your house,
what do you have? Oh, you get the new Nintendo entertainment system and you have the light gun.
That's cool. I have intelligent nuke bugs that are talking about Egyptian times and giving me
all kinds of knowledge. Enjoy your duck hunt. No, I didn't do it. Sorry. This smug is rubbing off on
him. To be fair, I have been sitting here for about seven hours. I've been absorbing the
smug dicky fishes for about seven straight hours. So of all of you, I'm surprised you guys aren't
as smug. I actually, some of you guys are. I've seen what you've been writing. 26, 10, 16. Oh,
we're almost 20 days. We're almost at three weeks. I think that's the end of the game.
What's my mother's maiden name? Uh, Greco. Carol Greco. Just fucking kill them, please. No,
I'm not just going to kill them. Story of Jean Paul Garcet. Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. Yeah, you can have my phone number. Recap of your previous visit.
The eggs have hatched and new creatures emerged. Due to their appearance, you will call them
Chadmen. At the moment, the habitat contains six Chadmen. They are suffering from the cold.
Chadmen. Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level.
So let us head over to the tank. So they grew up. I wonder what they look like now. You have one
evolutionary stage left before the end and the credits. Yeah, I'll do it tonight. We'll see the
credits tonight. As long as I don't kill them accidentally somehow. Hello. It's me, dad. Hello.
I just made it lag. I actually think I may have just crashed again.
Oh, come on. That's not how this ends. Pull out. Hey. Hey. Say, is there a full moon out? Because
I feel a little strange. Strange? How? It's a little chilly. Don't you think? Oh, I'm so sorry.
My mic's quiet. Fuck. Good. I'm feeling a little warmer. What's going on? What's going on? Oh,
somebody's he's parasiting this one. Just remember all the good times you had. Who ate who? Oh, I
think we just got our answer. So this is one of the ones that are. Let's talk. Do you own another
game system besides your Sega Dreamcast? Yes. You own more than one game system? Yes. Wow.
I hope you still find time to go outside. Who's talking? Or better yet, feed and bathe yourself.
He's going to ask me what I have. Let's talk. What's another game system you own?
Nintendo 64. Ah, yes. They have been around for a long time, haven't they?
Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's have a chat. Cheerio. Let's talk. Fine. You're a pain in the ass.
How's that? And you'll be dead if you're not nicer to me. What's wrong, Fuzzy? Is it the same thing
as last time? Yes. You poor little biped. These anxieties haunt you so. It sounds like you need
to come up with your own ways to cope. Some sort of closure to your situation. Perhaps you should
get out of the house a little. Take a stroll maybe to help you clear your mind? No. Whatever.
Goodbye. These ones suck. How do I flick? Let's talk. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Existence.
Existence. Sorry, I just can't boogie right now. I didn't say dance. Existence. Sorry,
I just can't boogie right now. Existence. Do you like your Sega Dreamcast?
Yes. Well, that's good to know because I've been authorized to award you a check for $10,000
for saying that. My ass. Do you dream? Do you have dreams? No, but thanks for asking. No, really.
Are you a part of my dream? Well, you know I try.
Do you know what it's like to boil alive? Do you know what it feels like to boil?
Let's talk. Let's have a chat. What's all that racket? Let's talk. Talk to me.
What next generation game consoles are you looking forward to? PS2? Sega's next console.
Wow, that's all I ever hear about anymore. The original and by another Dreamcast.
You never know when you're going to need another one. Didn't get one of those, did we?
Talk to me. This better be important. Talk to me. So what games do you like?
Sports, shooters, what? RPGs. Role-playing games? Yes. Everything's going black.
No, I was talking to that one. Why would you do that? That one actually had good questions.
That one wanted to know what my favorite video games were. It wanted to know how
like how school was going. Hopefully you absorbed all his information because like
I want to keep talking about game cubes. Talk to me. Talk to me. Let's talk. Hey, talk to me. Hello.
You called? No, okay. Let's talk. Once more with feeling, I said,
so what games do you like? Sports, shooters, what? RPG. Role-playing games? It is a hive one.
Yes. And I'll bet when they created you, they rolled an eight-sided die and you got a 27
for charisma. There, you can't say I never gave you a compliment. Is that a compliment?
I don't know. Is it eight-sided die? That means it could be eight. Talk to me. Talk to me. So
what would you say is your favorite game so far for the Sega Dreamcast? Power Stone. A fighting
game, huh? I myself am a lover, not a fighter. That's probably the best one. Talk to me. Talk
to me. You know, some people say that like most video game characters, I'm not real and that I
don't exist. You gonna Westworld me here? Can you believe this? It's a bit of a shock to say the
least. I mean, if I don't exist, then what am I? Am I just some imaginary creature? I mean,
do you think I exist? No. You don't think I'm real? That makes me sad. I see I'll have to prove it to
you. You probably can't imagine the feeling, the shock of being told you don't exist. It destroys
everything you hold dear. Your reality becomes shabby. All right, cook this one. But why don't I
exist? I'm living, I'm breathing, and I'm thinking with my heart and soul. I tell you I exist just as
much as you do. Go drain them. Please, I need some time alone to think about this. I'll talk to you
later. I know you are not. You are not real. No, leave me alone. You are part of the Rebel Alliance.
You remember our last conversation. You know, the one where we talked about yours truly maybe
not existing. Well, I've been thinking about that ever since. And I came to the conclusion that I
do really exist. I am real. Here, allow me to illustrate. Okay, you've heard of John F. Kennedy,
haven't you? Yes. Where the fuck is this going? All right, then do you believe that John F. Kennedy
existed? Yes. Okay, how about the Beatles then? Do you think they exist? This is getting weird,
like Jip K, fucking John Lennon. Yes. All right. You see, you've probably never met these people,
but you know they existed because they were on television and in magazines. Well, the same
goes for me. I too am on TV and in magazines, and here you are even talking to me and thinking about
me. So from that point of view, I exist. But what is existence anyway? What? Is existence
just our conscious mind collectively agreeing that we all take up the same space? What is it really?
Talk to me. Are you trying to break my thing that allows me to hear? Talk to me.
Talk to me. Talk to me. Do you mind if I flex your brain? Oh, he's gonna flex on me, huh?
Let me tell you about my theory. Okay, here goes. You can't accurately measure water's temperature
because the thermometer will affect the temperature of the water. You know how when you stick a
thermometer in your mouth, it feels cold? That means that just by trying to measure your temperature,
you're lowering the temperature inside your mouth. Do you know what that means?
If measuring something changes reality, then there is no reality independent of observation.
Nothing's real until someone measures it, observes it, sees it, hears it, or
whatever. People, places, and things exist only because you perceive them. So when you see me
and listen to me, I exist as a part of your consciousness. I become real. And because I
can see you and hear you and smell you, you exist as part of my consciousness. And as I
have a very limited attention span, once I forget about you, you will no longer exist. See ya.
I could just snap my fingers and you would cease to exist. How's that for
knowledge? One, two, three, go! Let's talk. I hope you've learned something from our little chat.
Take care. Thanos every stream. He's the best fucking Marvel character that's ever existed.
Behind Deadpool, of course. Let's get to that point where I've been live for too long.
I've been going live for too long and I'm just like a stream of consciousness here.
That's it for today, for tomorrow, okay. Spider! What happens if I drop, okay. Does anybody know
what happens if I actually drop the spider in here while they're in there? Because I don't know,
because they won't eat. I can't feed them. They'll eat it and then they'll get sick.
Oh, who cares? Who cares if one dies? I want to eat this one. Wait, another one died too.
Oh shit, the numbers are gonna be kind of dropping here. How's the heat? The walkthrough
only mentions the spider during the fish phase. I wonder. Dim the light a little. Make it 24.
Streamer derangement. What does that do? I'm disabling clips on my channel. I'm just gonna
turn them off. I don't, people still clip things that I say and they try to embarrass me to other
friends and shit. Nope, not anymore. Need more spray in here. I thought you disliked censorship.
All right, would you like to see tomorrow? Let's see how our children are doing tomorrow.
Goodbye, scream. This game is making you go fucking insane. I'm good. I really don't like
turning off my Dreamcast and turning it back on 25 times tonight. We're close. This would be 20,
that'd be 10. This is 17 days out of I think 21 and that's an anonymous five community subs
that just came in. Anonymous five community subs, thank you so much to whoever you are.
Wait, wasn't anonymous, was it? Why does it say anonymous? No, that was Ryanasaur. It said
anonymous for a second. That was weird. Thank you for the five community subs though. Appreciate it.
Congrats to those who got them. I'm seeing this through. You can't read. Thanks for the great
content. Hey, thanks a lot. Thanks for watching. I can't see. I can't see. I can't see. Now you can.
Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Garcet. There is a definite pattern to your
visits. It appears you are a punctual person. Every day at 1 33 a.m. Last time the Tad men have
developed hands. Did you see the Tad men sucking each other's blood? It was a terrible battle for
survival but it's a necessary part of their development. Nature can be cruel. At the moment
the habitat contains four Tad men. They are suffering from the cold. Turn it up. Please use
the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level. So let us head over to the tank.
When do I have to start feeding them? They don't seem hungry at all. What was your least favorite
food as a child? Do you still love it or hate it? Do you know the reason why I keep one-guying this
guy? It's because he's putting a fish on the end of the sentence and my ADHD is like, oh cool fish,
and then I read his question. That's good tactic. My favorite food was I think just chicken breast.
Whoa. Okay, they're pretty creepy looking now. Could you put the heater on for me? Yes, I will.
They actually have arms. They're turning into frogs. They're gonna get the nuclear codes. Oh goody.
Yay. Oh goody. Wow, that was cold. Sorry. Hey you. Hey. Good evening. How are you? What's up? Up
where? As in how are you? Like what's going on? What's going on? Coming your majesty.
Let's talk. I'm not your trained monkey, all right? Lately I've been thinking about the
preoccupations you humans, especially Americans, have with media. It seems as if the subjects most
of you like to talk about are not politics or philosophy, but rather movies and television.
Wow, 20 years ago. I'd like to know more about what your interests are in these areas.
So first off, since you are in fact human, I'm assuming you like to watch movies.
Tell me, do you prefer renting them or going to the cinema? Well, one of those
semen doesn't exist anymore. So going to the cinema. Yes, the in-theater movie experience
can be extremely exciting. Human. It's fun seeing images portrayed on a huge screen.
In fact, that's how I see most of my world through this aquarium glass.
It's like I'm watching a movie 24 hours a day. Although I can't say this is the most exciting
film ever. Red box rental still exists? Yeah. In fact, the plot could use a little
thickening if you know what I mean. Do you go with your girlfriend? Yes. Spending time with
a loved one is always good. We saw Into the Spider-Verse together. Just make sure all your
quality time together isn't spent sitting in the dark. You want me to go get the stuff to prove it
to you guys? You are not talking to each other. I'll just black out the theater. I'll black out
the name of the movie. I'll black out the credit card number and I'll black out the intro thing.
Oh, I can't feel my face. So it's just to be stuffed with piece of paper with a bunch of classifieds.
Oh, God damn it. He's eating them. You were not the chosen one. I'm sorry.
You know what I found in this game to really be the one that lasts the longest?
Just don't talk and eat your family. The ones that talk the most are the ones that get eaten.
There's only two left. No, there's three. Let's go check on the bug environment here.
Bugs. A couple of these. I don't know why they're not eating yet. This is kind of strange.
That must have a full inventory. Good to go. No spiders. Don't see any. All right.
Are you hungry? Do you want some food?
Hey, go tickle yourself. I'm busy. Stop it. I said stop it. Stop it. I said stop it.
Can they die? Are you hungry? Are you hungry? No, this is my happy face.
Do you want some food? Do you want some food? Oh, you humans and your slang. It's so cute.
Talk to me. Talk to me. I'm fascinated that not only are there so many movie lovers,
but there are so many completely different types of movies. Which type do you like? Horror films?
Westerns? What? Horror. You like a good scare, huh? Yeah. It boggles my mind that people will
pay money to have the crap scared out of them. An experience most people hate in real life.
Oh well, I know how it is to be scared. I'm constantly having nightmares about a large,
hideous creature that is constantly looming over my tank and oh, wait a minute. That's just you.
I mean, you should be scared about one of your silent mute family members that are going to
stick their antenna into your body and drain all of your fluid. You shouldn't be scared of me.
Talk to me. This better be important. Let's have a chat. Let's talk. So
what would you say is your all-time favorite movie? Casa Blanca. I've never seen that movie.
You've never seen that movie? Come on. Fine, I'll give you a better one. I've actually never
even seen Casa Blanca before. Talk to me. Well, we were talking about movies, but the biggest
influence on your culture has got to be television. A lot of people these days own two,
three, or more. Tell me, how many hours per week would you say you spend watching TV?
Thirty? No, no, that's way too much. Six. You only watch a little bit? Is that right?
Yes. That's pretty impressive considering just how much TV there is to watch these days.
Netflix is just, yeah, I know. That's why I'm counting that. I'd probably say like maybe an
hour a day. Maybe like two or three episodes of something a day. Maybe an episode or two
or something. Maybe every other day. Talk to me. I'm not your trained monkey, all right?
Let's talk. Let's talk. Blah, blah, blah. I'll catch you on midair next time you do that.
How are you feeling? Hello. How are you feeling? So when you do, oh, I can't feel my face.
This one underneath has not said one word. It's just been slowly just playing the battle
royale game. Just sitting somewhere sniping people. Doesn't talk, doesn't get angry,
doesn't yell at anybody. It just gets rid of everybody. This is like the silent tryhard
that's in the server. Hello. Yeah. Hello. Whatever. Let's see if we can get it to talk.
Let's talk. That's very nice of you. Talk to me. I have nothing to say.
I would like to name you. I would like to name you. Let's talk. Let's talk. Let me start over.
I said, so when you do watch TV, what type of shows are your favorites? Sitcoms, cartoons, what?
Cartoons. You're a cartoon junkie, huh? Yep. Hey, take those marbles out of your mouth and
try answering the question again. What type of TV shows do you like? Cartoons. You're a cartoon
junkie, huh? Yes. They're wonderful because they don't have the limits of live characters
and scenes. Literally anything can happen. Not anime. And that's exciting. SpongeBob.
I got really pissed off at Prime the other day because I saw that Prime had 12 or 15
seasons of SpongeBob and I was like, oh, this is awesome. But it's actually only the first
like two seasons. And I got to the end of the third season and the second season and I saw
you had to pay for it and I was just like, that's fuck off. You know what I mean?
Coming, your majesty. Well, thanks for telling me a little about your TV habits.
These little box seems to have grabbed a hold of people's minds so inextricably, but you don't
really seem to be the typical specimen. Maybe you prefer to get your experience live and not
through a glass screen. Those are the best seasons? Yeah, I know. I think that's worthy of some praise,
don't you? Just don't get a big head about it. Okay. What do you need? Help. Help me.
No, I don't need anything. I do. You need to teach me. Talk to me. Whoa. Keep it down. Talk to me.
So I'm going to go out on a limb here and assume you like music. It's another medium you humans are
fascinated with. Not really. Well, what kind of music do you listen to? Rock, hip hop, what?
Video game soundtracks. You like the funk, huh? No. Let's try that again. No, I exclusively listen
to anime intros and outros. On repeat. None. You like pop, huh? No. Let's try that again.
What type of music do you listen to? Listen, I like to go to the same anime intro that I've
seen 400 times and replay the same 30 to 40 second section 50 or 60 times in a row
until I am satisfied. So are you up to answering my question now? What I wanted to know was,
so I'm going to go out on a limb here and assume you like music. It's another medium
you humans are fascinated with. Well, what kind of music do you listen to? Rock, hip hop, what?
Classical. You prefer classical, do you? Yes. Yes, it's truly the music of the human spirit.
Such fire, such passion. Or am I talking about sailors again? Oh well. Anything else?
Cumming, your majesty. So who's going to eat who? I wonder. Talk to me. Let's talk some more.
Now I want to ask you about the most important medium of all, the printed word. Books. Tell me,
do you enjoy reading? Yes. You like to, huh? I'm lying. That's a lie. Yes. That's great.
Reading is the greatest of all forms of entertainment because it allows you to use
your imagination. You're not bound to someone else's version of what a character or scene looks like.
I can't feel my face. No, not yet. How's the heat going? I thought you read 15 books at the end of
the year so you say you read one every other month. Oops, it's too hot. No, it's too hot now.
Anybody else feeling kind of warm? I don't know, you ate the other two people that are near you so
it's kind of a fucked up question. Talk to me. Talk to me. Let's talk. What's my favorite
breakfast food? S'mores, pop tarts. Let's talk. Talk to me. Wow, I was boiling.
Make a pew, make a pew.
Let's talk. Chat with me. See ya. Let's chat. Tell me, how many books have you read in the past year?
Fifteen. Wow, that's very impressive. I am proud to have you as my caregiver.
What kind of books do you like? Old lady romance novels. Well, I've never read any of that,
but I'm glad you're reading. Well, I feel like I know a little more about how you keep yourself
entertained. Old lady romance novels. There is so much being produced out there for your perusal.
It's blue. Movies, books, TV, music. It's a blue cover with some red trim. If your full-time job
was being entertained, you probably still wouldn't be able to take it all in. It's a coffee table
with a flower and a vase. Nor would you want to, I guess, because there's a lot of garbage out there,
too. But as far as I know, human beings are the only animal smart enough to entertain itself in
a complex way. So I say, take advantage of as much of it as you can. No, there's no shirtless
people in front. It's a coffee table in the living room with a nice vase on the table.
And like a couch sort of in frame. And by the way, each page is written by another person.
You know why they can have five to six hundred books published by the same group?
Because how you read an old lady romance novel is if it's 225 pages, you get 225 people outsource
and commission them all to write one page. And they just follow the same outline. So what happens
is the first person writes the first page. That goes to the second person. They then continue it.
That goes to the third page again. Eventually you get to like 150 pages that goes to the 150
first person and then they write a page with, you know, outlines and shit. Fucking hundreds
of people write those books. R.L. Stein. R.L. Stein is not even a real guy. Fun? Why, of course
I'm having fun. How could I be trapped in a glass box and not have fun? Let's talk. Let's talk.
Well, I think that pretty much covers it. Yeah, Shakespeare isn't really that was like 30 people.
So what they did is they just they just screamed lines out there when they lived in the same
apartment complex. So you'd have Shakespeare, you know, it was it's all like the first and last
the first letter of their first name, last letter of their last name. So it was like Sean, like
Harrison, like Andrew, Kennedy. Right. It was it was like eight people.
Talk to me. And this yelled shit out there with apartment windows to each other.
You know, it struck me that I've been around you for quite some time now, participating in your
daily routines. However, I'm not quite sure exactly where we are. Resident sleeper. I'm guessing we
are somewhere in America, but the details are fuzzy. Like you fuzzy. Anywho, I was wondering
if you'd be so kind as to tell me which state we're residing in currently. Nevada. We live in the
Silver State. Yes. That's a great nickname, but I'm assuming they don't exactly handed out as you
cross the state lines. Anyway, what big city are we nearest to? Las Vegas. Las Vegas, a monument to
money and decadence. It's truly my kind of city. So do you gamble? Yes. I guess even if you live
close by, the lure of possible instant riches is always strong. But not very much. No, leave me alone.
Only enough to have fun and never more than that would seem to be ridiculous. Always moderate
yourself and don't you go in there and try to have fun with a little bit of a little bit of money.
You don't blow all your money. It's bad. Have a couple drinks. Maybe play like a few hands of
blackjack. Maybe spin the roulette once and maybe like a like somewhere like a minimum bed on a
machine and then you go home. And then before you go home, before the lift gets there, you cancel
the lift and you turn back and you go to the ATM four times. No, leave me alone. I'm just fucking
kidding. Relax. I'll be seeing you. Let's talk. Let's talk. I must tell you that your country
truly fascinates me. Here at the beginning of a new millennium, the most visible signs of change
for America is that it continues to get stronger and more influential in the world.
Yet for a country with so much influence, it's made up of so many disparate parts.
You Westerners seem to live a life that's very different from the rest of the country.
You're a Westerner too. Somehow everyone fits together. Colonial reachings have even brought
places like Alaska and Hawaii into the fold. What will your future be like? Will there be 55
states in a hundred years? Will there be no states at all? These are the things I think about
and I'm sure you have too. All right, let's heat it up. Let's have a day go by. What does this guy
think he is? Some kind of fucking improv comedian. You know what I mean? Like snooze. I almost just
hurt myself with the cord. No spiders? We are so close. It's almost time for the credits.
They're going to evolve one more time and then we're going to get to see what they do.
Are you mentally stable? Well, the thing is, if you weren't here about seven and a half hours ago,
let me get to the right page. Of course I am. I had to do mental preparation before this
stream started. So yeah, there's a spider in my Dreamcast. I might as well stop the Dreamcast
then. Thanks for reading me. You're welcome. All right, 27-28. Three more days and we can put the
book on this one forever. Until C-Man 3 comes out. Read this message. I'm a subscriber.
I got you, C. Get a Japanese Dreamcast and play the second one? No.
That would be a very expensive. That would be like 200 bucks just to play C-Man 2.
Good evening. A Japanese PlayStation 2. I don't have it. I have a region.
It seems that visiting around this time has become a habit for you.
Am I going to play Devil May Cry 5? First, a recap of your previous visit.
Probably soon. The Tad Men have developed legs. At the moment, the habitat contains two Tad Men.
They are suffering from the cold. Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more
comfortable level. Get one modded for cheaper. So let us head over to the tank.
Too late. There was a third one. The third one got eaten already. No, there was two. They were two
there when we left, I think. Stream is still going. Yeah, we're gonna see the end. If you gotta go,
you gotta go. But I wanna see how this plays out. It's cold, isn't it? You're going really late
for the East Coast. Yeah, and EU, I know. It is late. It is late. Slow that down. I just got to
work in the EU. What time is it in EU? 7 a.m.? 8 a.m.? You got work tomorrow and it's 1 a.m.,
but fuck it. Take care of yourself. Make sure you don't cause yourself any problems, you know?
Anybody see a spider? I do. He was right about to eat that egg too. Okay, let's continue.
Hello. How are you? Hey. Yeah? What's up? How are you today? Hi there. Do you have any questions?
Any questions? Any questions? Look, I'm very busy. Can't this wait?
Talk to me. Well, I found out a little about you based on where we live. Now I'm curious if you've
learned anything about your fellow humans based on where they live. Okay. Tell me,
have you ever traveled abroad? Does Canada count? Does Canada count? No. You know the expression
about walking a mile in someone's shoes? Well, walking a mile in their country is the next best
thing. What was that for? You have no idea how much you don't know about a person until you find out
about their home. Accent. Humans always seem to play it too safe. They stay in their own little
world instead of realizing that the world belongs to those that live in it. And if you don't travel
it and learn about it, you're not really living in it, you see? Besides, nothing gets your love
muffin in the mood for a more quite like an exotic trip. Sure. Sure. This better be good.
Talk to me. Let's talk. I have another point to make regarding travel and culture.
Shall I share it with you? Yes. Okay. A lot of just exposition. Whether or not you've traveled
abroad, you're part of an ever shrinking world. Sure. You know that there's even a song about it
being a small world after all, but never in history has it become so important to be familiar with
and tolerant of other peoples and their cultures. You and your descendants will be forced to deal
more and more with people from all over the world. Think of the effect that will have. Cultures will
become further mixed. You already see that in small ways like your pop music with musical styles
being combined in your food with fusion cuisine. It's a natural result of the world's economy
becoming mixed. The prevalence of the internet, cheaper, faster travel. The end result will more
likely be that there may be no more countries to speak of in the future. The world will be more
of a cohesive unit, just as it happened in the United States and is already happening in Europe.
That to me is very exciting. Exciting. Okay. Globalists.
Uh, gentlemen, the globalists, let me tell you something. There's going to be a post-post-human,
post-human apocalypse. I'm telling you, post-human. What's going to happen is the
sea man are going to come up here and they're going to totally just absolutely wipe us out
and then the globalists are going to take over with the sea man and then it goes real high.
It goes real high, Joe. Talk to me. Well, until next time. Bye. No, talk to me. I want to hear
more. I want to hear more. I'm thinking. Roll credits. Hello. Yes. Talk to me.
Talk to me. Fine. I'll go talk to your brother. Talk to me. Let's talk. Okay. Let's talk about
now, maybe tomorrow. Tadpole dropping truth bombs.
Yes. Fine. We'll talk tomorrow. Not very much time left. Tadpole politics.
No, guys. Impressions are not politics. They're audio representations
of what somebody sounds like. Okay. Just remember that. Would you like to
everything clean? Yeah. Tadpole politics, Andy. Did I just get called politics, Andy? I didn't
do anything. I'm going to fix this hair. It looks bad after eight hours.
Politics, Andy. I said like one sentence forehead window. What the fuck does that mean?
I'm looking that up right now. I don't have, there's nothing here.
I have three days ago, a teacher told the student to wash off Ash Wednesday on, on forehead.
What are you talking, what the fuck are you talking about? Why do you keep saying this?
That's all I could see on like a Google result. Forehead window. That's what I typed in. Get
bangs. You want to see how fucking bad I look with bangs? Hey, Scoob. How much have you ever
lost on a coin toss? Could you step outside for me, sir? Could you step outside for me, sir?
Peasant hair. Okay, that's good. That's really good. Peasant hair.
It really is. It really is peasant hair. Oh, my father owns farm upside here. Did they,
how did the farmer, no, how did the peasant talk? Yes, my lord. Yes, right away. Yes,
right away, my lord. You go shovel that shit in the farmhouse. Yes, right away. Right away.
Right away, my lord. God fucking damn it. I have peasant hair. I'm shaving it all off.
It's all going to be gone tomorrow. Witcher 3 peasant NPC. Now it's all fucked up. No, I,
that's better. No, it's not. Fucking peasant hair. I'm going to look in the mirror every day and
just think of, I got like a pitchfork, like a beige vest. I had to do the stupid fucking thing
where I parted in the middle and did the no country for old men impression,
which sucked on its own. That was bad. Fuck the goddamn face cam. I'm never using it again.
What would I look like actually completely bald? No, I can't do completely bald, guys.
I look like a fucking goddamn random British henchman that gets punched in the face first
in every Liam Neeson movie. I'm not doing it. Grow it out and braid it. No, I can't do that shit.
Just buzz it. This link, this link. That looks fucking terrible. That was real bad.
No, I'd rather get a toothpaste staple to my head than look, than have that look. I got too,
I got too rocky of a face for a bald head. I would rather you use horse glue and it,
just smear it on there and just let it stay. 329, two more days. Show a screen. Just wait.
The longer that I get, I lose concentration, the more like terrible fucking ugly impressions you
get. I don't want that. You don't want that. We both don't want that. I do. Is this a new shirt?
No, I've had this for a while. Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gasset.
Greetings and welcome back. You're doing a good job. Two more days and that's it. At the moment,
the habitat contains two... Yeah, it's gone. ...Cadmen. I don't want to drink more than one
Coke a day. They are suffering from the cold. I drink like a Coke maybe in a couple days. I don't
want to drink my fucking soda every day. Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more
comfortable level. So let us head over to the tank. I love how you're on a PST schedule. I
appreciate seeing more of you every night. His streams have definitely been longer.
You're looking extra bald today. I will 1v1 you in auto chess and just show you up. And I
ain't even ever played it. Have they grown? Not really. Hey. Oh goody. God, they're so ugly.
All of all three of us or just them two? You got to clarify that. After all this bullshit
that lasts like 20 minutes. Oh goody. It's about time. Thanks. I believe I'm beginning to... Oh
jeez. See what happens when you put a... What secrets of the universe are we going to get
after completing this finally? What was that? Oh, two hatchlings. I'll take them. I'll take
you, please. Hello. Oh, why did... The face is just so fucked up. They lift their heads up and
they just look so terrifying. Okay. Coming out on land now. They can come out on land.
That's new. Talk to me. Let's get some more info. Hi. Let's talk. Hello. Who listening?
It's good to see you again. You can like Dead Space 2 on me here. Hello. Hello. Let's talk.
Hey, I have something I want to talk to you about. Okay. You know, I'm really getting the
impression that you people are busy all the time. Maybe it's just here in America, which is such a
business obsessed culture. It seems like everyone is always complaining about not having any spare
time, but when they get some, they don't know what to do with it because they're so used to being
busy. Okay. It's strange that knowing how to relax appears to have become a skill you humans
have to learn. You seem to know how to relax if you're talking to me, but I want to know what
else you do in your spare time. For example, what do you do when you're with your friends?
The same thing. Play video games. When I ask you something, I expect an answer. You know,
let us revisit my last inquiry to you. That is, if you can cooperate this time.
For example, what do you do when you're with your friends? Play video games. Hold on. I've
got the worst gas. Give me a second. What? Hello? Is he all right? Are you okay? Are you okay?
Hello? Yeah. Hello. Are you okay? Let me repeat the question. I said, Hey, I have something I want to
talk to you about. You know, I'm really getting the impression that you people are busy all the
time. Maybe it's just here in America, which is such a business obsessed culture. It seems like
everyone is always complaining about not having any spare time, but when they get some, they don't
know what to do with it because they're so used to being busy. It's strange that knowing how to
relax appears to have become a skill you humans have to learn. You seem to know how to relax if
you're talking to me, but I want to know what else you do in your spare time. For example,
what do you do when you're with your friends? Play video games. Like to toss a few back with
friends, huh? Yeah. I guess I don't really understand why you humans are so interested
in destroying your precious brain cells. Just out of curiosity, why do you like to drink?
Because it's fun. I see. Then the fun starts during the prolonged vomiting into a garbage can.
You're implying that I drink or drink like 15 beers when I drink. No, you drink a few drinks.
You have some fun conversation. Maybe you do something fun and that's it.
Why would you say, okay, yeah, I like to drink. I like to go and have a few drinks with friends.
It's fun. You're puking. Where did you get the... I don't know where you got that from. Talk to me.
So I think I have an idea of what activities you and your friends do in your time together.
Do you see a lot of them, by the way? Not anymore. He's moving. I'm gonna say yes, though.
Yes. So I see him. Well, that's good. I wouldn't want my little biped to get lonely.
Talk to me. You know what I've noticed? People love to talk. Oh, sure. There are quiet ones every
once in a while, but usually if you ask a person the right questions, they can go on for hours.
I mean, why else would you have me around if you didn't like a good conversation every once in a
while? I think that's also what makes a good friend. If they're willing to listen to you spout
off about something, you just have to make sure you let them talk once in a while too so you don't
bore them to death. But I was wondering what kinds of things do you and your friends talk about?
TV? I don't know. I don't know. Anything. It could be anything. I don't know what many of my friends talk about.
It's not like one topic we always discuss.
Can you give me the answer, please?
Nobody just talked about one topic.
You've forgotten, haven't you?
Okay, then again. But I was wondering what kinds of things do you and your friends talk about?
Food. Oh, you movie buffs. That's great that you can share a common interest like that, though.
Movie buffs are a lot like literary buffs. They like to pick apart the things they love and get
as much out of them as possible. The only drawback is it might be harder to appreciate these things
once you start dissecting them. I'm sure you know all about that, though. I say you can never really
get bored if you have someone around who you can talk to. Sometimes it's more fun to just sit around
and talk than it is to actually go do something. It all depends on the person, though.
Talk to me.
Say, I know you spend time socializing with your friends a lot, but you have to have some time left over to spend with your sweetheart, right?
It's good to be in a relationship that's a friendship, also. You can kill two birds with one stone.
Besides, I don't know why you'd want to be with someone who bores the pants off you.
So what do you and your girlfriend like to do together? You know what? Seaman doesn't want to know this.
Just keep it to yourself. Well, I'm sure you and your sweetie care about each other, but if you don't mind
me saying so, I think you may have worked yourself into some kind of rut. Maybe you should think about
getting out more. Exploring your world, that sort of thing. Who knows? Maybe you don't need anything except each other.
Go jogging!
Nah, get out and do something before you drive each other crazy.
Why are you playing facade? This is the original facade.
Alright, how's the tank?
One of them's dying.
Question is who?
Why am I so slow to respond?
What do you mean slow to respond?
What are you guys doing?
Yes?
What are you two doing?
You know what the really great thing about friends is?
And movies and TV shows.
Spending time with them makes you really appreciate the time you spend by yourself.
And books.
I mean, you probably get tired of your friends sometimes, don't you?
What do you like to do when you're by yourself?
Sleep.
Wow. You sound like you're a thrill a minute.
It's good that you don't mind being by yourself.
It seems like a lot of people can't stand it because then they actually have to think.
I see you don't have that problem.
What is this guy doing right now?
This one's freaking me out.
You guys are just too close. Move out of the way.
Alright, how are we doing over here?
We look alright.
Got a couple more eggs.
Another day?
Would you like to s-
What's the goal of this game?
To raise a tadpole into a frog who eventually implants chips into all humans' brains.
And forces them to build the pyramids.
Well, sorry, the new pyramids.
That's all they care about.
Free 30.
20 days exactly, almost 3 weeks.
This is a lot of passive-aggressive mannerisms to deal with in one night.
That's the designer's face in the game.
That's actually-
That's really funny.
Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory of Jean Paul Gusset.
Any changes, Leonard?
Greetings, and welcome back.
You're doing a good job.
Let's see.
Last time, the tadmen are now closer in appearance to frogs rather than tadpoles.
Let us then call them frogmen.
Frogmen.
That's actually awesome.
To frogmen.
They are suffering from the cold.
Please use the heater to raise the temperatures to a more comfortable room.
So what, um...
What's the final evolution then?
Do they go from frogmen to lizards?
What do they go into?
Birds?
They don't turn into humans. No, they don't.
They turn into birds.
Tadpole, frog, eagle.
Turn up the heat.
Oh, goody.
I'm feeling a little peckish.
Would you feed me?
Now they want to eat.
Okay, I got plenty of food.
I actually have food for the next at least 10 days.
This will be good.
You eat this shit, right?
What if they didn't eat these anymore?
Someone over here wants to eat.
There you go.
Go get it.
They don't eat these.
I'd offer you some, but that would mean less for me.
They eat the moths.
No, they don't. He's going over there right now.
Okay.
Good.
That was a Campbell's soup reference.
I think I need some food.
Instead of one bite, they take a whole thing.
So.
Hello. Hello.
Are you listening?
I am. How are you?
Have any questions?
Bonjour.
Talk to me.
One thing I find really interesting about people is how very chameleon-like many of you can be.
For example, when a person is talking to their closest friends as opposed to their employer,
their entire persona will often change.
Of course, it really depends on the person.
You don't want to get fired.
You seem to do different things around people than when you're by yourself,
and that leads me to ask you, depending on who you're with,
do you think your personality changes a lot?
A little or not at all?
A little.
I think that's pretty common.
People adapt to the situations around them.
I'm not going to say the F-word.
Often, the way you act around your grocery store clerk won't necessitate quite as much ass kissing
when you're around people you owe money to.
The things you do with different people and when you're alone reflect your personality changes, I think.
I mean, it seems like there's a lot of things going on with you.
No wonder you act differently around different people.
It seems like you're doing lots of different things around them, too.
Well, I think I know you well enough to tell you that even I act differently depending on who I'm with,
and it makes sense.
Everyone has different expectations of everyone else,
and nobody expects me to pick my nose around them.
Yes, that is my private moment.
Don't tell anyone.
Hey, thanks for the food.
It gets really tough for us when the air gets too dry.
There should be a sprinkler that Gasset built somewhere around here.
Hey, can you use the D-pad to look for it?
Come on, use the D-pad and find the sprinkler.
I'm using the D-pad? What do you mean, the sprinkler?
Hey, I'm trying to sleep in here.
There. Is that better?
Put the light out or I'll put yours out.
Jesus fucking okay. Oh my god.
Talk to me. Let's talk.
That's my name. Don't wear it out.
What is this? I don't even know what the name is.
Greg? Hey, Greg. Greg.
I'm coming, Your Majesty.
That's a terrifying image.
Let's talk. Talk to me.
It's really not a difficult question, I said.
One thing I find really interesting about people
is how very chameleon-like many of you can be.
For example, when a person is talking to their closest friends
as opposed to their employer,
your entire persona will often change.
Of course, it really depends on the person.
I mean, you seem to do different things around people
than when you're by yourself and that leads me to ask.
Did you know you were in the same room standing five feet away from your brother that asked that question?
Depending on who you're with, do you think your personality changes a lot?
A little or not at all?
A little.
I think that's pretty common. People adapt to the situations around them.
Often, the way you act around your grocery store clerk
won't necessitate quite as much ass-kissing
as when you're around people you owe money to.
The things you do with different people and when you're alone
reflect your personality changes, I think.
I mean, it seems like there's a lot of things going on with you.
No wonder you act differently around different people.
It seems like you're doing lots of different things around them too.
Well, I think I know you well enough to tell you that
even I act differently depending on who I'm with
and it makes sense.
Everyone has different expectations of everyone else
and nobody expects me to pick my nose around them.
Yes, that is my private moment.
Don't tell anyone, please.
Anyway, I'm going to go think about things for a while.
It was nice talking with you.
Bye.
Why don't you go do something more intellectually stimulating
like eat paint chips?
You're dead, don't worry.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Hey, Greg.
What do you need?
I see you out there moving from place to place
and sometimes I am envious of your freedom.
There are so many things you can do.
I can imagine what it must be like to be so free.
It's weird how familiar it seems.
You must get a lot of exercise
running around as you do.
So with all that moving about, do you think you're in pretty good shape?
No.
You think you're in pretty bad shape, is that right?
Yeah.
I thought you really liked your body.
Maybe you've just really let yourself go recently
or maybe you just like your body despite being out of shape.
I mean, it's not like round
is necessarily a bad shape.
You know, circles are round
and they're great.
It's hard to say whether or not someone is in good shape.
It seems like your TV and magazines
tell you what it means to be fit,
but that idea of fitness can be pretty unrealistic.
On the other hand, it's pretty safe to say
that a little physical activity will make you fitter
than just sitting around on your butt
and eating potato chips.
You don't seem really satisfied with your level of fitness.
I don't even like potato chips.
Talk to me.
What's up?
It seems strange to me
that with all the wonderful things you can do with your bodies
there are still people out there who are out of shape.
People actually have to make time in their day
just to exercise.
And when they do, they do strange useless motions
over and over that serve no purpose
to their muscles.
It seems like such a shame that your world doesn't naturally allow
for more physical activity.
You think you're in pretty bad shape, huh?
Well, what are you doing to get in better shape?
Nothing.
Nothing? Really?
Yeah.
So I guess you must not really care
because you seem to be a classic case of cause and effect.
No exercise, no fitness.
Who knows?
Maybe you have a perfect body and are just completely delusional
but something tells me that if you exercised a little
you might feel better about yourself.
I guess I'll have to keep asking you questions
and see what else I can find out about you.
Hmm. Number one?
No, no. It's definitely number two.
All right. Time for the final day.
Good night.
Roast this smug asshole?
I need to see the final thing.
We're almost at one of the last...
There's apparently only two question sets left
and that's it.
I'm going to be the only person who's ever beaten
Seaman on stream.
On original console, no save stating,
no fast forwards, no, no.
Only person on Twitch to have beat it
with real original hardware on stream.
I got original shit here.
Oh, fast, right.
Would you like to save and end the session?
You know what I mean though.
Only goddamn person on this whole site.
Only fucking person on this site
that probably owns one of these.
I might be the only person on the internet
that still has one. Do you have one?
You got one of these? With original microphone?
That was probably up somebody's ass?
By the way, isn't this supposed to have a thing up here?
It's supposed to be a little puffball.
Welcome to the laboratory of Jean-Paul Gasset.
Greetings and welcome back.
You're doing a good job. Very well.
Ah, you can now use the sprinkler.
Frogman is sensitive to dryness
so you must use the sprinkler frequently.
Is this for PS4? It is not.
At the moment, the habitat contains
two frogmen.
Please use the heater to raise the temperature
to a more comfortable level.
So let us head over to the tank.
Yeah, I'm missing the puffball.
I'm so ashamed that I put this thing in my mouth
and pretend up my nose.
We're in the final set of questions.
Somebody said three and a half K viewers
at midnight PST.
But you're seeing it through like I am.
Hey, thanks for sticking around.
Can someone out there put on a sprinkler for me?
There's not enough moisture here.
I need a little mist here. It's too dry.
How about turning up the heat?
Give me something to eat.
Turn the heat up. Give me something to eat.
Mist my body.
Yes, my prince. Anything for you, my prince.
Hey, can you give me something to eat?
Could you put the heater on for me?
You know those things each take time.
More than ten seconds.
Could you put the heater on for me?
I'm really hungry. Please feed me.
I'm kind of hungry.
I sure could go for a bite to eat.
Let's get some food in here.
I command you to feed me.
It's like manna from heaven.
You're such a little dick.
Imagine being commanded to feed somebody.
I command you to feed me.
Hey, thanks for the food.
Why not?
So full.
Oh, fuck it. Who cares?
We have so much food and we're done.
I need to bring this over though.
Why can't I pick anything up?
Why don't you go rustle me up some grub?
Can the frog eat?
The frog, I think, if it eats the spider, will get sick.
Food over here? Kill the spider.
I can't. Well, now I can. If he eats, I can kill the spider.
Right there. Eat it. Eat that bug.
Hey, you.
You talking to me or talking to him?
What do you want? Hi.
Don't you ever go out on the weekend?
Hey, thanks.
That hit the spot.
They won't eat this, right?
They shouldn't.
Talk to me.
Oh, what are you doing?
Why did you eat that?
Did they have to procreate?
He already ate.
If they eat, they won't eat it and he'll die.
I love you.
I'm going to lose my lunch, if you know what I mean.
I'm illin'.
Yes, I am.
I'm really not feeling good.
I love you.
All we need is one.
Talk to me. Let's talk.
You know, I'm really fascinated
by health clubs and gyms,
these huge places full of fancy equipment
and open spaces where you can run around.
And you have to actually pay to belong to one
when in the past you could just pick any field
and run around in it to your heart's content.
Or you'd get so muscular
and fit from all the manual labor you'd have to do
you wouldn't need a special place and time
just to exercise.
But I guess the world you live in gives you no other choice.
So tell me, do you belong to a health club?
That has to be what's going on.
No.
So even though you know you could be more fit,
you don't want to take the plunge and join a gym?
It might help, although I guess I can see your hesitation.
They offer a lot of different activities
in one convenient place,
but I just can't help but think a human being
might want to do something more natural,
like play a sport or even jog outside
than be cooped up in a stinky gymnasium
with a bunch of machines.
I like to hit the balls in the cages.
I like to work out nowadays when I haven't done it in about a year.
Let's talk.
It seems like there are a lot of different things to keep in mind
when you're trying to stay in shape.
Exercising is one of them,
but eating right is also very important,
especially where you live.
There's no shortage of food here, well, for most people,
and it's very easy to eat too much of the wrong thing, it seems.
No wonder so many people have problems with their weight.
Would you say that for the most part
you eat a pretty healthy diet?
Yes.
You do eat healthy? Yes.
You must really chow down on the vegetables, then.
What's your favorite one?
Uh, probably carrots. Carrots.
Carrots, huh?
Good as a vegetable, even better as a snowman's nose.
So versatile.
It's a shame that the things that are good for you
don't usually taste as good as the bad ones.
And you know what? The junk food marketers know it.
So my advice is, beat the system.
Eat a pound of broccoli.
I was pressed for time, and I had to do it.
I was pressed for time.
Drinking a fucking coke and eating a whole pizza.
Let's talk.
Is he dead yet? Oh, he's getting so red.
Oh, God.
This is actually really sad.
I love you. I love you.
I'm illin'. Yes, I am.
Get well soon.
Ooh, I think I'm going to lose my lunch
if you know what I mean.
I love you.
I'm illin'. Yes, I am.
Feel better. Feel better.
I am not. I love you.
Oh, I really don't feel very well.
I love you.
I'm illin'. Yes, I am.
Let's talk.
I feel sick. Let's talk.
End this and go to bed? No, I can't get this far.
Eight and a half hours into a stream and not see the end of this.
Let's talk.
Greg. Cheerio.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
You know, I've never been to a place
that's as diet-obsessed as America.
It seems like nobody wants to stay healthy the hard way
to actually exercise and eat right.
Instead, people are always looking
for a quick and easy way to lose a bunch of weight
as if they're just automatically going to stay healthy
after the diet is over. Right.
It looks like you take pretty regular care of yourself anyway,
but have you ever been on a diet?
Wait, hold on, that's... No.
Not in that context. Maybe that's for the best.
It looks like you're already trying to straighten out your health
without resorting to lose-weight quick-skis.
No. Talk to me.
I was thinking earlier about how interested
your culture is in sports.
I would say even obsessed sometimes.
It can really get out of hand,
but now that we're talking about health and staying fit,
it almost doesn't seem like such a bad thing.
That is, if you're actually playing a sport
and not sitting in front of a TV and watching someone else play it,
tell me, what's your favorite sport to play?
Tom Brady. Baseball.
You play baseball?
Yes. I bet you just like wearing
those tight little pants.
I think I understand why people want to play sports.
It must be fun to see
what you can make your body do if you just try a little,
and you also get to hang out with other people
and test your skills against theirs.
I guess I still think some people
can get too interested in sports,
especially if it interferes with the mental stimulation they get.
As with most things,
balance is the key.
What are you guys saying? There's a fly in your room
flying around your face? What are you talking about?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Did somebody just join the stream?
Watch out, there's a fly.
Here it comes.
Talk to me.
Talk to me. Let's talk.
Let's talk. What do you mean, here it comes?
Here it comes. You just throw shit at me?
You just throw shit at my screen!
Get well soon.
I really don't feel very well.
I'm illin'. Yes, I am.
Let's talk.
I really don't feel very well.
Greg, let's talk.
Fine. You're a pain in the ass. How's that?
Wow. Now that's dark.
Turn the light on.
Hey, turn on the light. Ah, it's too bright.
Talk to me.
I was thinking earlier about sports
and how popular they are here.
As I was saying, it would be really great
for the collective health of the country
if everyone played sports, but
it doesn't do so much for you to just sit and watch them.
I'm fascinated with watching other people play sports.
Being a spectator.
Do you follow any professional sports?
League of Legends.
Well, you're a rare specimen.
You play sports, but you don't follow the pros.
It's definitely the healthier way to go.
Anyhow, thanks for playing.
Cloud 9 will win again.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
I've been asking you a lot about your health
and it seems that working out
and eating right are two big components of it all.
This game is louder than your voice.
Oh, it's because I am leaning back and talking into this microphone.
But it seems that your human body
is still so delicate.
All the working out and dieting in the world
make sure that something won't just go wrong anyway.
That's where your physicians come in.
Do you go to the doctor regularly?
Literally was there like fucking
very, very recently, yes.
That's to your benefit.
Besides, it's another excuse to get naked.
My, I am behaving saucily today, aren't I?
Human beings are very lucky
to have figured out how to heal themselves
when they get sick.
No other creature can do that.
It's easy to take all your medical knowledge for granted,
but think about it.
If you were living even several hundred years ago,
you'd still be putting leeches on yourself
whenever you got a cold.
Not that leeches are such a bad thing,
but they're actually what I would call good medicine.
Anyway, I'm glad to know
that if something goes wrong with you,
there's somebody that can help you out.
Your brother is over there suffering.
I don't know what to do about him.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Like I was saying earlier,
it's important to go to the doctor every once in a while,
because it's so easy to do,
since healthcare can be so expensive.
I'm fascinated by this idea of health insurance.
Well, actually, I find it a little sad.
You humans are so sure that someday
you're going to get sick that you actually
put money away, especially for that time.
There's no escaping it, I guess.
Do you have health insurance?
I see.
Well, if you do, I guess you might as well
make good use of it.
That didn't come out exactly right, but you know what I mean.
Do you get sick a lot?
No, but I do have a lot of health problems.
I don't really get a cold,
but I've got a shitload of health problems.
I think he's dead. You good?
Oh, I think I'm going to lose my lunch,
if you know what I mean.
Get well soon.
Oh, I really don't feel very well.
Don't come over here and eat him.
This is poisoned meat. Don't do it.
Don't stick that fucking elephant trunk
into this and start sucking. Don't do it.
Bad idea.
Okay, good.
Another day.
Still got plenty of food.
Our food supply is doing good. No more spider.
We should have another larva tomorrow.
Let's go.
How can I be expected to sleep when this nightmare is on?
One more day. Is it my bedtime yet?
No, I'm just going.
Oh, shit. We're going into April.
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Go back.
We're going into April 1st.
4-1-2019. That's correct, right? 31? Yeah.
I'm going until I see the credits.
He doesn't know. What?
No, I was explicitly told that we only had
a couple more sequences left.
At the moment, the habitat contains
two frogmen.
Seaman has become ill after eating a spider.
Please take good care of him.
Some kind words of encouragement may help him feel better.
So let us head over to the tank.
Alright, this says 25 hours,
but what you have to understand is
one person, only one person,
reported this.
So that's it.
One guy probably left his Dreamcast on for 10 hours.
He left 5 hours ago and this guy is still streaming this game.
Laughing my ass off.
So how long is the game if you cheat?
I have no idea.
Hey, why don't you turn on the sprinkler?
I need a little mist here. It's too dry.
How you doing?
It still looks kind of like shit.
It's cold in here, just like my Harlem days.
Thanks for the moisture.
See that gray square thing in the back corner?
That's a heater.
In the lore, seaman species are
omnipotent messengers of the gods.
The eggs come from Egypt, which is maybe why they have a thing
for the pyramids. I see.
Why don't you give me something to eat?
Do you eat if you're sick?
It's going to be too hot. I didn't stop the wheel fast enough.
Maybe I did. I did.
Okay, let's see. Food. How are we doing? Spiders?
I don't see any. There are...
I'm going to leave that one. That one looks cool.
That one's getting big and fat.
I need two. Come over here.
He can't move though. Can he not? I don't think I can
feed him. I can't drop it over here.
How is he going to get better?
I'd offer you some, but that would mean less for me.
I'm not sure I can feed this one.
That hit the spot. Good to hear.
Let's take another fresh one over there.
No thanks. I'm not hungry now.
What? Are you hungry?
Maybe I could eat a little antacid, but that's it.
I really don't know what I ate that made me this way.
You don't want it then?
Did I seriously just waste this?
Let's talk.
Greg, come here.
Hello? Are you listening?
Talk to me. Yes, let's talk.
Good evening. Hi.
Okay, I've got something to tell you.
See, I've been lying to you all this time.
I'm actually Regis Philbin and if you kiss me
I'll become human again and give you a million dollars.
April Fools.
You believed me, didn't you? That's why.
Quick. Help. There's a shark in here.
Help. Gotcha.
April Fools.
Pretty good. Talk to me.
So, we've been talking a lot about the health of your body.
That's of course quite important,
but it also helps to have a healthy mind.
So, to that end,
have you ever gone to a therapist?
No.
It seems that a lot of people think that
seeing their mental health through the efforts of a therapist
is a sign of weakness. Yet most people
don't see going to the doctor for a physical ailment
as a sign of weakness.
Strange how people think sometimes.
I hope if you ever feel you have a problem
you can't handle, you'll consider seeing a therapist.
Or you can just come talk to me.
At least I won't charge you.
Much.
By far the most mysterious part of your human body
is the brain.
Even your greatest scientists will freely admit
that they barely know anything about how it works.
And yet, when something is wrong in your head
I'll bet it hurts just as much as a wound
or a disease.
I hope you take care of your mind as well as you take care of your body.
Or better, since you don't seem to be too keen
on keeping your body tip-top.
Talk to me.
What do you want?
Let's talk. I feel like I've said that 5,000 times this dream.
Let's talk. Talk to me.
Yes?
Talk to me. Let's chat. Can we talk?
Well, thanks for letting me in on some of your
health secrets.
All of us animals have these fragile, organic
bodies that break down and cause us pain.
But human beings are especially fascinating
because they can actually prevent or cure
so many of the body's problems.
That's why I wanted to know what you do to keep yourself
healthy. I want to know how you humans
take advantage of their medical knowledge.
Some people take it all for granted
and do stupid, destructive things to their bodies
just because they're used to having the means to recover.
Well, anyway,
I think I'm going to go take a little rest.
I don't want to over-exert myself.
I'll talk to you later.
There we go. Alright.
Only another day or two. Maybe.
Let's talk. Talk to me.
Tomorrow. We'll talk again tomorrow.
Will you eat? Will you eat?
Please eat.
I think I'm going to lose my lunch, if you know what I mean.
Get well soon.
I feel sick.
Let's check all the bugs. Any spiders? I don't think so.
Yeah, fuck it. We're leaving the spiders in here.
I got so much food.
Look at this shit. I got one, two, three, four.
I have at least three more days' worth of food.
At least three or four days with food.
We have to talk about religion and then politics
and then that's it.
It's just Simpsons hit and run all over again.
Oh, God. The no-no topic.
I just hurt my arm.
What do you mean politics? Are they going to ask me how I
glean politically?
So, are you a Democrat or a Republican
or something else?
I'm just going to mute the stream. It's going to be a black screen.
Good evening. Welcome to the laboratory
of Jean Paul Gasset.
There is a definite pattern to your visits.
It appears you are a punctual person.
At the moment, the habitat contains
two frogmen.
Seaman has become ill after eating a spider.
Please take good care of him.
Some kind words of encouragement may help him feel better.
So, let us head over to the tank.
I'm going to give cartoon responses.
Do you understand? I'm going to give
bullshit dumb cartoon responses.
What do you belong to for a party?
I'm just going to say a mashed potato party.
You ain't going to get shit this stream.
Jerma is a communist.
How do you roll your eyes?
Can I not roll my eyes?
I need a little mist here. It's too dry.
Hey, why don't you turn on the sprinkler?
If I weren't in a tank, I swear there was a draft.
Just like my Harlem days,
I thought I was going to shrivel up and die.
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
I love you.
He don't care. Whatever. Fuck it.
Hello. Are you listening?
There is such a good Rick and Morty
bit about politics. I'm just going to say it verbatim
to the frogs.
Oh, goody.
Excuse me, but my stomach is empty.
I know you're hungry.
You know I could really eat.
I feel terrible.
Oh, yummy, baity goodness.
You're learning so many ways to say that you're hungry.
That was tasty.
What are you doing?
Hey, what's he doing? Is he throwing up blood?
You saw that, right? Thotty.
Don't touch him. Don't. Don't. Get away from my moth.
I fucking hate the spiders. I have enough food.
I do. How am I going to get rid of you?
I got. I don't think. What do I do about this?
I think I just. That was fucked up.
I don't know what to do. I cannot put the spider in the matrix
I can only go here or here. I'm just going to leave it.
Unfortunately, I got plenty of food, I think,
to molest to the end of the game.
Get both the frogs sick. No, I'm not going to do that.
All right, let's go. Ooh, he's not sick anymore.
Let's talk politics. Talk to me.
I feel sick. No, not you, the healthy one.
Hey, listen up. Let's talk.
Good evening. Talk to me.
Let's talk. Talk to me.
No, I'm not talking about you.
I'm about to pick you up and just throw you.
Talk to me.
Hey, there are laws against that sort of thing.
Get well soon.
I'm illin'. Yes, I am.
Really don't feel very well.
Come here. Greg, come here.
Make me. I'm telling you,
you're causing a lot of problems. Let's talk.
Let's talk. Finally.
You know, I've been around you humans for a long time now,
and it seems like every group of people,
every country, state, and kingdom...
Here we go. ...has a different way of setting up its government.
Sometimes one person has all the power,
sometimes everyone shares the power.
It seems like there are as many different types of governments
as there are people in the world.
Human politics is very interesting to me,
which is why I am very curious.
You're breaking my second rule.
As you are currently residing in a democratic society,
are you taking advantage of your power?
What I mean is,
are you registered to vote?
No, not here.
So you're not a voter, is that right?
No, I am a voter. I just moved.
Hmm, that's interesting.
I would think that you'd like the power a vote would give you,
but maybe I'm projecting.
I'm not registered to vote in Nevada.
No, I'm not.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
What's up?
Let's talk.
I'm still thinking about this government of yours.
I mean, with everybody's different ideas of how to run things,
how do you ever agree on anything?
You seem to have a few major belief groups
that most people fall into,
like the Republicans and the Democrats,
but I'll bet not everybody in your country
falls into one of those, right?
I guess it's just a matter of which group has more supporters.
If I had to guess,
I'd say you are a Democrat.
Talk to me.
Okay, one more time.
I said I'm still thinking about this government of yours.
Fuck!
I'm trying to skip it.
How do you ever agree on anything?
You seem to have a few major belief groups
that most people fall into,
like the Republicans and the Democrats,
but I'll bet not everybody in your country
falls into one of those, right?
I guess it's just a matter of which group
has more supporters.
I guess I'd say you are a Democrat.
Am I right?
Hey, everybody! Welcome to the stream!
What do you want?
Let's talk. Let's talk. Talk to me.
I'm ready to fucking mute it. You think I'm ready?
Yes. Talk to me. Let's talk.
You know, I'm rather curious about your general stance
about your political system.
I believe in it.
I mean, does it really make any difference
which candidate one person votes for?
All of your politicians are basically the same anyway.
What's the difference between rich middle-aged white man A
and rich middle-aged white man B?
About the most variety you could hope for
is a very rich middle-aged white man
or maybe a rich old white man.
Okay, let's just say there is a difference
just for the sake of argument.
Would it matter then who one person voted for?
After all, it's just one voice in a country
of millions and millions.
Yes. Everybody has a voice. Everybody has an opinion.
Everybody has an opinion. Everybody has a voice.
Boy, do I have to dump.
You can't just go from...you can't just shit in my face
after talking about...I guess it actually is a perfect place
for you to do that, actually.
Us talking politics is the absolute perfect opportunity for you to do that.
Okay. Talk to me. Let's talk.
You know, I'll bet you're not really interested
in politics anyway.
And I'll bet you're wishing I'd just shut up
and talk about sex or something you're really interested in.
Do it right now. Yes.
But you tell me.
Are you interested in politics at all?
For the purpose of this. For the purpose of this fucking screen.
No.
So you're not interested in politics. Is that right?
No. And I would like it if you'd stop talking about it, fish.
Well, what about violence in video games?
That's turning into a bigger
and bigger political issue every time some poor
disturbed kid decides to take his aggressions
out on his schoolmates instead of video game characters.
There are politicians in your government
that want to decide what kinds of games
you can and can't play.
They want to censor your games.
I don't know whether that's a good or bad
thing for other games, but for me
I'll probably try to make me put on some underwear.
And you wouldn't want to see that.
This is getting really, really fucking deep and dark and fucked up, isn't it?
Talk to me.
You know, when your country needs to decide
to something like whether to raise or lower taxes,
let women make a choice about having children,
or if gay people deserve to be treated
the same way as everyone else,
it doesn't have to be so complicated.
It used to be so much simpler.
A king or maybe an emperor or a pharaoh
would say, do it this way.
And that would be that.
No elections, no debates, no lobbyists,
no congressional subcommittees, no endless legal battles.
One giant rat.
Ah, those were the days.
This system is so complicated.
Do you think it's done this way to give everyone a say in government?
That's the point.
Yes.
Stop this frog.
Your system of government is actually set up
for exactly the opposite purpose.
That's you. Don't get enough power to screw things up.
So, let's see.
Boil this frog. Yes.
I do. Yes.
Know why your founding fathers did that?
So, if the people tried to actually do something,
let's say by electing a president they wanted,
Congress and the Supreme Court
could still stop them from messing things up.
So, what you have is a system designed
to stop people like you from having a say in the government.
I'm not even streaming anymore.
This is just Frog has a fucking podcast
that you're listening to.
I'm not even here anymore.
The controversial fucking politics frog
on iTunes.
All right, we're good.
Talk to me.
We've got one more day.
And that's it. Talk to me.
Talk to me.
That is not this more.
This more.
Talk to me.
That is not this more.
What do I do? I turn the lights on?
Don't. Talk to me.
Keep going. Keep ranting and raving
until you're like eight followers on your podcast.
God, this is getting worse.
I'm gonna mute this one, too.
I ain't gonna rule it out.
Because the Chalupa exists.
I ain't gonna rule it out. Maybe.
You're unsure about the matter, is that right?
Yes.
You know, some of the smartest humans have spent decades
thinking about this and have never come up with an answer.
Others seem to just know right when they are born.
It's possible. I don't know.
Thinking about it is more important than coming up with an answer.
I don't know if that's a concept people think.
I don't know, but talk to me.
Centrist agnostic streamer
terrified to give opinion on stream.
I just told you, the Chalupa exists.
No.
It's like me and my dog connect and have the same dreams.
At least it seems that they'll be all the wiser
by simply having thought about it.
Keep going, man. You got an audience here.
Your rave podcast has 3,700 people almost listening to it.
Let's go. Talk to me.
Let's talk.
I'm not your trained monkey, all right?
Yeah, do you mean to like rub your back for a second?
Are you happy?
Let's talk.
Alright, you've given me plenty to ponder,
but here's what I really want to know.
What my questions have been leading up to.
Ready?
I want you to think about this and give me a serious answer.
Do you think you're a good person?
Yes.
So you think you're a good person?
Is that so?
Politicians often complain that your society would be more ethical
if more humans were religious,
and yet even though you don't belong to any organized religion,
you consider yourself a good person.
Perhaps politicians are not as smart as they think.
You're probably fucking r-correct.
Let's talk.
Give it to me. Tell me more.
Give it to me is your name? I thought your name was Greg.
After everything you've told me about yourself,
I think I already know how you feel on this subject,
but I still want to ask you.
Do you think religion makes the world a better place
or a worse place?
God damn it.
Ready to try this?
I already know how you feel on this subject,
but I still want to ask you.
Do you think that you could take or leave the whole faith thing?
Well, how about this then?
That's not what I said.
Let's say there were only one religion in the world.
Would the world be a better or worse place?
If there was only one religion in the world, would the-
So you think the world would reverse off if there were only one religion?
You know, yes.
I don't know. No. Can I change my answer?
The world would be a lot less interesting
if everyone were carbon copies of one another.
Well, as I'm sure you've guessed,
I find the whole institution of religion
quite confounding.
Most humans run around like they're masters of the world
while at the same time bowing down to a higher power
that's supposed to make life better.
On top of that, most people can't even agree
on who or what the higher power is,
so they argue and fight over it
and bring about a lot of misery and heartbreak
in the name of something that is supposed to bring people joy.
I just don't get it.
And quite frankly, just thinking about it
gives me a headache, so I'm going to go away
and try and figure it all out.
That's it.
Took us nine hours, but I think we did it.
Talk to me. This frog's going to end your career.
This stupid Dreamcast frog
is going to end your career on Twitch.
That's so fucking funny.
Why have I been live for so long?
Because I've got to get this done.
I'm just having fun. I'm just chilling.
We've got politics, we've got religion.
Let's see what happens.
Show it to me, Leonard. Let's see the end.
It's almost 4am now.
This is almost like the 30th time
I've turned this off.
The Pope just called you out on Twitter.
What am I going to do?
Show me the end.
One of them got sick.
They did a bunch of podcasts.
I just gave this frog a platform
to give all of his political stances while I watched.
Here we go.
You watched helplessly.
He's ascended into another being.
Still two.
I'm really looking forward to this.
I've been here three seconds and I'm bored out of my mind.
You got here three seconds ago.
I was loading the Dreamcast up.
You've seen a menu.
Give it another 30 seconds.
After 30 seconds, if you think this sucks,
I have respect for your opinion.
Give it another 30 seconds.
He said he evolved into a full frogman.
That was fantastic.
This is much better.
If you want to believe in that spirit,
I have completely respect for your opinion.
I can't even read that one.
It's just too...
I'm feeling a little peckish.
Could you feed me?
There's no difference.
Sprinkler's good.
Light is good.
Who gives a shit about spiders?
I've got plenty of food and bugs.
Speaking of bugs, let's grab these.
Drop them in.
I'll put it in the inventory.
Eat and let's end it.
Go eat.
What's the final topic going to be?
I'm surprised I ended up with two.
My compliments to the chef.
My stomach is growling.
Hey, you.
I never knew humans were so nocturnal.
Talk to me.
I'm all talked out for today.
Let's talk.
Where is it now?
I could really eat.
It's right behind you.
I'm hungry.
Yummy, baity goodness.
I'm full now.
Talk to me.
What the fuck is he doing?
He's like...
He just drained all of his life for us.
Who's your daddy?
Did either of them die?
I don't think they just had sex.
They're still alive.
The last two generations, one of them died.
Hello?
Hello.
Religion was the last topic, so what happens now?
How do we get to the end?
Whatever the last thing that comes out is?
Maybe it's whatever comes out here.
They just had sex.
They've eaten.
They don't want to talk to me.
Talk to me.
Let's talk.
Fuck off.
You just had sex, you gotta take a whole day off?
Just like me?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Grind doesn't stop here.
I've been here for nine hours.
There are credits, that's when you can stop.
I'm going to see those credits.
Is there any way for them not to suffer from the cold?
I don't think so.
Well, that's not true.
Check on them instead of 24 hours.
Turn your Dreamcast on six to eight hours instead of 24.
I would assume that's probably what it is.
You can check on them every hour.
No, I ain't doing that.
Someone out there put on a sprinkler for me.
There's not enough moisture here.
Hey, it's a big hole here.
I'm going to get all the answers.
Every answer I've given, they're going to make a big essay about me.
I'm going to get Psychomantist at the end of the game.
It's going to say, ooh, yes, oh, I see.
I can't believe you don't work out.
And that you're
not fat.
And that you like pizza.
It's going to be something like that, I guarantee it.
I have an entire production of food here, even if the spider eats one of those.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not enough spray going on here.
I got plenty of food.
This is going to hatch in a minute here.
Yes, you definitely could.
We can both and see if we can get anything out of it.
This is actually one of the worst games I've ever seen.
It is a classic, though.
I looked up how to get to the credits. End the stream now.
Why are you saying that?
Yep, I'm stuffed.
You the guy from fucking Storage Wars?
How about we strap on the feed bag?
Talk to me.
Why are you phasing out?
I sound like Santa.
Yum, food.
Okay, they both fed.
Give me something. Let me end this.
Oh, excuse me. No more room.
Okay. Hi. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hey, Greg. Greg.
Wake up. Get up.
He's not even responding to my, like, hand twitches.
This is not good. Greg. Hello.
It's important.
Really, really important.
Can you let me out, please?
Please. If I am released, I give you my word
that I will keep all your secrets.
You see, there are some things I need to do.
What do you say?
Yes.
I know it sounds odd, but I must keep evolving.
I have to keep growing so I can find
my long-lost love again.
It's been a long, long time.
What? You see, my father was the king of Egypt
back in its third dynasty, and
my lover's father was a priest in the temple.
Oh, we were young and both swept away
by the passion. I'm sure you understand.
Oh, my dear sweet love.
She was the most beautiful creature imaginable,
but neither of our fathers would approve
our marriage because of our class differences.
When we insisted we be allowed to marry,
her father consulted the god Thoth
and asked him to help.
Thoth granted her father's request for help
and changed our physical forms.
And we've been apart ever since.
And I have to continue evolving
so that I can be reunited with her
in another few thousand years.
So you'll help me get out, right?
Tell it to Satan, where you belong!
Yes.
I already have a plan how to get out.
See that ring over the tank?
I'm going to jump for it.
What about the other one?
The other one doesn't have a backstory
about how he's the king of Egypt.
What about this one? This one's just a frog guy?
Okay, jump, right?
Oh, missed.
Try again.
Greetings, my vampiric friend.
Hello? Talk to me.
So, I'd like to ask you.
How are things going with your girlfriend?
Are you guys still an item?
Yes. What about this Egypt guy?
That's splendid. You know, it's interesting to me
how preoccupied you humans seem with love and relationships.
You write songs about it,
compose poems,
search for soulmates,
and are constantly hoping for happily ever after.
I'm curious as to how you experience love.
For example, do you think your girlfriend is
the one?
What about Egypt?
I'm starting to lose...
Do you think your girlfriend is the one?
So you're not the one?
Oh, I don't have to hide for this one.
I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know.
We've talked about it before.
This fucking frog is fucking up my strength.
He's making me fucking answer uncomfortable questions?
He's making me talk about things?
Why do you think that is?
Will you fucking eat him already?
I don't know.
You don't know what the number one cause of divorce is?
I don't know. What is it?
I'm not sure, but I think it's ignorance.
Why would I know that answer though?
Jump to the ring. Stop exposing me.
Jump to ring. Stop.
Well, Fuzzy, you've experienced hesitation
when confronted with the idea of being
permanently bound to your partner.
That makes me think. Is it you?
Is it the person you're with, or is it something
you've got to ease yourself into?
That's why I want to ask you this.
Do you believe that there's a perfect person
out there for you?
So you say you don't believe in such nonsense.
Am I right?
It doesn't. Now it does.
Take a stand.
Does true love exist?
So you say you don't believe in such nonsense.
Am I right?
You know, most Virgos have shy
and modest exteriors that hide wild
foolish and passionate hearts.
I guess you must be the exception to that rule.
Boy, do I have to dump.
Jump to the ring.
What can I do for you?
Escape. Escape.
You know, I've seen you naked. Now that's
scary.
How do I make them jump and grab it?
Something in particular? Talk to me.
This better be good. I have to hold up.
Grab the rock in the back and wiggle it.
I have to increase the temperature to a hundred.
Oh, fuck off with that.
Why don't you pick on somebody?
Oh, fuck. That just scared the shit out of me.
Help me move it then. Can I touch the ring?
That's what I was thinking. I can't grab the ring.
I can't focus on it. I can't really touch it.
I can't pull it down. Jump.
Talk to you soon.
Move the rock. Move rock. Move the rock.
You know, I'm really glad that you found someone
you can spend your romantic time with.
I think that's terribly cute.
No, really. I think it's hard for people
to connect in such a gigantic, scary world.
I mean, sure, it seems simple to an outsider like me,
considering just how many of you there are,
but if it were so simple, why would there be
so many dating services to choose from?
That's why I'm curious.
Where did you meet your girlfriend?
At a Christmas party.
I see. I think maybe this whole dating game
is more kismet than skill.
The thing is, it's all circumstance, isn't it?
I mean, if you hadn't been in the right place
at the right time, then things could have turned out
a whole lot differently, couldn't they?
If you'd been somewhere else, grown up in another country,
for example, and never come to be where you are,
your entire set of friends and where you spend
your free time would be completely different.
Your personality would no doubt be very different as well.
It's funny how certain events mold us all
and how easy it would be to be an entirely
different personality than you are.
Yeah, certain events like jumping and grabbing a ring,
which one of you dickheads needs to do right now.
Escape.
Like the spice.
Jump. Cheerio.
You know what I find interesting?
You were probably born into a family,
and for the next two decades or so had to interact
with them on a daily basis.
I mean, with any group of people, there are bound
to be love and hate issues, and a whole range
of emotions in between. And as you matured,
conflicts, I'm sure, arose as your interests
became more individualized and pronounced,
often differing from your family's.
Of course, maybe that just brought you closer,
which leads me to wonder,
how well do you get along with your family?
Well.
So everything's pretty good? Yep.
Wait, you said you get along with your family.
Now you say you don't.
Do you get along well with your family or not? Yes.
So everything's pretty good? Yes.
You're all swimming in the same ocean, then.
That must make those family get-togethers
a lot easier to get through.
Now, how about friends?
Do you get along better with your friends or your family?
Both.
Well, that makes sense, since those are the people
you've chosen, whereas you didn't get to choose your family.
The trick is to get along with everybody.
People are much happier when they can do that.
You probably are. Jump.
Later, Fuzzy. Ring.
You seem to love your family, and they must love you.
That's nice.
No, really. With all this love floating around,
do you think you were raised well?
Yeah. Well, at least you get along with them.
Maybe they did a good job and you didn't even know it.
Do you think if they weren't your parents,
you could still be friends with them?
You know, pals.
Friends with my mom? If it's not my mom?
Yes.
Maybe they are better friends than they were parents.
This one. So this one.
The other one was a ranting and raving political
podcast runner, but this one's just like,
if you weren't, she weren't your mom.
Jump. Jump.
Talk to me.
So it's over. I lose.
Jump.
See? Look.
Don't go to the next day.
Reload. Restart. Just reload the save.
And then wiggle the rock before
Advanced time or reset?
Which one? You have to attempt it three times.
Going for it? Okay, advance a day.
Advance a day. You got it.
Fuck the food. Who cares? They can starve.
Don't advance. Don't advance. Are we going to get like a fucking fight
in chat here about how to finish this ten hour game?
What's wrong? I'll get it. I'll get it myself.
Ring. Find on this page.
Ring. Jump.
He's going to jump? What the fuck is it, man?
Because the only way he can continue to evolve is by getting outside.
Seema says he thinks that pesky ring hanging from the upper left of the tank
should be the key to getting that.
He will try to jump to it from the big rock, asking that you say
jump for encouragement. On his third try,
he will reach it and the back panel of the tank will
slide down. Okay.
We advance. That's ten community subs from Peek a Banana.
Thank you, Peek a Banana, for the ten subs.
That's a lot of subs. Thank you. Let's go.
He spoiled the ending. Oh, he didn't just say he liked the...
He jumps out of the tank. That's all I read.
Two more days. What day was it? Five?
What if I... No, five. Right?
But Peek a Banana, that's a fucking lot of subs. Thank you.
Who cares about Seeman spoilers?
We're on four. We're now on five. Let's go. Fuck it.
Two more jumps. See you at ten hours.
See you at ten hours.
I need to see the end, because I'd have to be the first person
to play it and beat it on stream on regular,
regular hardware. You know what I mean?
You might get somebody that streams this game like,
Seeman, I heard of that game. Didn't that fucking top
one thousand streamer, German985, play that?
I heard about that through his fucking fan-tastic stream.
What am I going to do on a fucking emulator?
He did it on a regular hardware.
Well, do you notice Frogman trying to reach the ring
hanging from the ceiling?
Perhaps this holds the key to the next step
in Seeman's development.
At the moment, the habitat contains
two Frogmen.
They are suffering from the cold.
Please use the heater to raise the temperature
to a more comfortable level.
We are nearing the mating season
for the Frogmen.
This is something few humans have been...
Just pick them up and put them out of the cage.
So let us head over to the tank.
Let's see those credits.
Jump out. Say goodnight. Feed them.
Make sure they're watered. End. Next day.
Jump. Game over. I win.
If I get one more conversation
about if I'm going to marry my girlfriend or not,
or what political spectrum do I lean on,
I'm going to shot put one of these frogs.
Can someone out there put on a sprinkler for me?
There's not enough moisture here.
Finally, some service around here.
It's cold, isn't it?
Is your girlfriend in the room?
No, she's not in the room. Anybody else in the room?
Have you ever cheated on your girlfriend?
Ah, wet is wonderful.
Hey, can you give me something to eat?
Raise the temperature, would you?
He's getting defensive about this.
It's cold in here.
You would immediately and confidently say no.
That was Frogmen. Fuck off.
Hey, I got some food for you. Just kidding.
Our seaman could die of hunger in this place.
I'm kind of hungry.
It's like manna from heaven.
Say, you know what would be good right about now?
Some food. Eat it then.
Enough talking about it. I got BTTV.
Watch. I don't know how to do it.
That was damned yummy. I've no idea.
I got one more to feed.
I do have enough for one more day here.
More than that.
Speaking of being fed...
I have more than enough food for one more day.
Come here.
I got plenty of fucking food. Let's go.
Go jump. Eat that food. Try to jump out.
I'd offer you some, but that would mean less for me.
I need some good light so I can see.
Very good. You know how to turn the light on.
End my suffering. I'm trying to get this done fast.
Okay. Jump.
Jump.
Go for it. Get out.
You're lucky it's Friday or I'd be really angry.
Hey, hello.
You know today's the anniversary of the premiere of the
Vienna. Is he all right? I'm sure you know the year.
No, the other way on the rock. Does that count as an attempt?
Is that two?
I could go on and on.
All right. Remember what I told you before about
jumping to freedom to find my lost love?
Well, I've gotten up the nerve and I think I'm ready
to try it again.
So when I say now, say the word
Jump. Okay.
Here I go.
KXE gave 10 community subs. Thank you KXE.
This has been a lot of community subs tonight. Thank you guys.
Here it goes.
Jump. See you tomorrow.
Rhythmically tapping the glass
twice a second to keep it going causes the song to start playing.
What? What do you mean rhythmically?
What do you mean tapping the glass?
That's not right.
Goodbye. See you tomorrow. Bye.
Be seeing you.
Twice a second like that.
Two, one, two, one, two, two,
one, two, one, two,
one, like that.
Twice a second. Once per second.
This is two right here. Now I know it's after.
I'm just trying to get the rhythm down.
Heartbeat with the tapping.
That's probably why it doesn't look right because the cameras are off.
The camera's not synced up perfectly.
So it's...
Right? You should grow a soul patch.
All right, sure. I'm just going to grow this out like long down here.
It's going to be like an extra tongue.
Like a long tongue coming from my mouth.
There it is. Last day. Four, six.
Go for it. Here we go.
He's going to make it.
And I can solidify my house in video game history.
It's been ten hours. Give me a break.
Oh, you made it.
This is the last day of Seaman.
Good morning.
Welcome to the laboratory of Jean-Paul Gosset.
As you see, it's brilliant.
You're doing a good job.
At the moment, the habitat contains
two frogmen.
They are suffering from the cold.
Please use the heater to raise the temperature to a more comfortable level.
So let us head over to the tank.
I'm losing my really great $400,000 a year
scientist job for letting out the experiments.
Do I cause World War...
World War IV because of this?
World War IV, yeah.
Because they're just frogs right now.
It's going to take them probably 40 or 50 years to...
Hundreds of years, probably.
Hundreds of fucking years.
So they're going to go into the fucking forest somewhere
and start evolving as aliens.
There's going to be another World War III before 100 years is over.
Once they're walking on two legs,
we'll be ready for World War III.
This heater sucks.
How am I still alive?
Oh, how are you still alive?
I was going to say, I'm not that old.
All right, final meal.
So here you go.
Good thing I had a good stockpile of food.
Give it a eat.
Who's going to get it?
Thanks.
Okay, bring in the other one.
Both of you eat. Check on the spiders.
I can't help this one.
It's fine.
Still an Anor Londo.
Will you eat that, please?
Hey, how about adding a little humidity?
It's good for my skin.
Right behind you. Turn around, Eden.
Talk to me. Time to go.
Escape. Right at the rock. Jump.
Time for you to jump for that ring.
And then we're going to go for it.
Come on, end this.
Hello.
Jump.
I'm a sea man.
So many variables.
So much can happen between different people
that life seems like one big jackpot.
I can tell you one thing, though.
It's perhaps the only universal truth
for all relationships, and that is,
all of your relationships will one day end.
Even with your closest companions,
be it by your own understanding,
or be it by your own mortality.
At some given point,
you will never speak to each other again.
But don't let that frighten you.
Your precious time on this planet
and the relationships you forge
are what makes life worth living.
Instead, appreciate what you have
and what you think you have to be with.
That will certainly make you a happier human being.
You can rest assured.
Goodbye. Go be free.
Go for it. Rock.
Go jump on the rock.
Rock. What? Rock.
Jump. Adieu.
Just jump on the rock.
Say, you know what would be good right about now?
Food.
Oh, good. Food.
Stop.
I'm not hungry anymore.
Turn around. Turn around.
Turn around and look at rock.
What do you need?
Ring.
I know you're not talking about me.
Check, um...
Anyway, I hope this hasn't been too embarrassing for you.
We'll talk again soon.
Goodbye.
Jump off rock.
Rock?
Let's talk. Let's talk.
Talk to me.
Let's talk.
He's stuck. Talk to me.
Quiet.
You're very, very, very...
Fucking Burger King flame broiled in about 10 seconds.
Burger King flame broiled in about 10 seconds.
Let's talk.
Hey, there are laws against that sort of thing.
Jump. Escape.
I did let's talk on both of them.
Tomorrow. We'll talk again tomorrow.
No, just go for it.
We're going to have to do another day.
No, that's not... He doesn't understand.
Jump.
They think I'm saying bye.
I'm trying to finish this.
Do you guys think I'm trying to drag this shit out?
I'm trying to end it.
I'm going to be hearing this in my sleep, yeah?
Fuck, it's so late. It is so late.
It's almost 2 a.m. PST.
2 a.m. Eastern.
Oh man, I cannot believe...
I cannot believe there are still 3,700 people here.
I hope you're enjoying it. I hope you're having fun. Really.
You look half dead.
One of them is going to jump.
He doesn't give a shit.
He gave the fuck up too.
He's so done with saying all this stuff now.
Let's check on the tank.
Let's see exactly what's in there.
Give us a shit.
Let's go.
Let's see exactly what's in there.
Give us a shit. Just end it, man. Resident sleeper.
This would be very comfortable in the desert,
just like my Harlem days.
Hey, it's a good cold one.
I live in a food court, come what may.
What is wrong with you?
That's so fucking funny.
I was like a month in... No, just barely a month, right?
It's a little chilly, don't you think?
The Tamagotchi had more content?
I don't know if I believe that. It was made out of, like, sticks.
Hey, I'm getting a little hungry. How about some...
Uh-oh. Only one of you get to eat.
And you better jump.
I'd offer you some, but that would mean less for me.
Oh, fat boy.
Hey, listen up.
Hello? Talk to me.
Is it breakfast time already?
What is it with humans and this daylight savings?
Underwater, it's either day or it's night,
and you don't see us with a rising crime rate.
Take the hint.
How about a little nourishment here?
Talk to me. Thanks, I'm not interested.
Is this poisonous?
I'm fine. I'm good. I'm just tired.
What's wrong with you? What are you doing?
Alright, you both have eaten.
Eat it, and then just go for the jump.
You good? I'm gonna have it at that.
Perfect temperature, it's 24,
100 sprinkles, ambient mood lighting.
What does it take to get you to jump?
Alright, let's go.
Here we go! This is it!
And then it's tap tap, tap tap, tap tap, right?
Here we go, I'm ready.
I've been waiting my whole life for this moment.
Jump, jump, jump.
Does the other one get to leave too?
That's freedom.
We don't get anything from Galefrog?
The funny thing is that it's there all the time.
You don't always realize it when you're bogged down
with so many other things, but you're always free
as long as you're true to yourself.
That's where freedom lies, within yourself.
I wish you and your girlfriend
the best of luck.
I wish you as well as you treated me.
Okay, I must be off.
My evolution must continue.
Oh my, I think I know where I am.
It's all coming back to me.
This must be Gasey's island.
Somewhere on this island is a place I have to go
in order to continue evolving.
Go find it. You know you're alright.
Oh, that was really loud, I'm sorry.
I know we've had our differences occasionally, but
I like you. You took care of me all this time
and well, I'm grateful.
I will kill you first and live very painlessly
in World War 4.
Well, say something before I start bawling, won't you?
I hated every second of our experience together
that fucking snake and somebody put salt on your balls.
Hey, listen.
There's something I'd like to do for you as a kind of
thank you. It's not much, but I
wasn't exactly able to head over to a diamond
and buy you something, now was I?
It's just something for you to try sometimes.
Just try tapping on the glass.
You know, with the right trigger on your control pad.
Tap, tap, try it sometime.
Okay, friend, this is it.
I've really got to go now.
Take care and if you ever
want to talk to me, just
call me, okay? You've been a good friend.
I'll miss our time together.
Don't be a total stranger now.
So confirm with me that it's tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
Tap, tap, tap, tap. Is that correct?
This is important. Tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap, like this. Tap, tap,
tap, tap, tap, it's
tap, tap, tap.
Tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap,
tap,
oh, why is it so incorrect?
I can't keep up with
it, it's so wrong!
Why tapping?
Wait, this-
Did I drop a bug?
No, whoops.
I'm pooped. I'm not the sea man I used to be.
I thought it was fucking over.
You were wrong!
What?
Somebody say you tap with the stairs and you can stop.
That's weird.
You understand? Like, there's only two- there's only three different beats!
There's- like this?
It's- it keeps fucking up!
See how it's slowing down? I haven't changed at all.
Two, three, four. One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. It's not changing!
The double beat shit is a J.
Did you bait?
I saw all the content already.
So I'm just being fucking lied to!
I've seen it all!
Everyone's fucking with me!
I thought there was supposed to be a song here!
Tap three times, then not.
What are you- what are you talking about?
Like, it's twice a second.
So that's- this is two beats a second.
One, two.
That's two beats a second.
Am I never gonna get-
You understand that-
I've done it every way!
I've done it one, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four.
I've done it every one of those ways!
I'm gonna YouTube this shit.
So I can fucking scream in everybody's face.
This doesn't even exist.
That doesn't exist. Nobody's uploaded the end credits to see me in on YouTube. Not one person.
This fucking shit was- I- I- Do I have to put my live headset on to hear this?
Fuck! No, it's fine. It's empty.
Where is my fucking- I don't even know where it is.
Do I even have- Where the fuck is this?
I can't believe I'm still fucking doing this.
What do you mean, have I ever held an instrument before?
You saw me play Beat Saber like fucking six days ago!
This one didn't even have the song. This person didn't even do the song.
This person doesn't even do the song.
They're not even doing the song!
Metronome Online.
How many beats per minute do we want?
We want 120 beats per minute.
I was doing- I was doing this shit!
Are you kidding me?
Are you- Are you serious?
By the way, by the way, it's not off, it's not off, it's because-
Listen, you guys, I-
Shut this up for a second so I can explain this.
I have to delay the audio from the capture card.
So it's 650 milliseconds faster than the game is here.
Don't you understand?
This is what I was doing before, you guys can't tell me-
I'm out of here.
I was doing that fucking three straight minutes.
120 beats per minute.
You tell me this ain't it, I'll do it again.
Check it out.
It's so hard to do this when you hear the song because the song is off.
The song has so many instruments that are playing and you have to pretend to be a metronome.
I'm gonna have the song in my ear.
I'm gonna put the metronome on too to see just how fucked up this is.
And how fucking- how correct I am.
Check this shit out, you ready?
Let's hear it.
Let's get the metronome 120, I'll do it at the exact same time.
120.
You ready?
I have to make- I have to cue the cell.
Oh fuck, hold on, pause it.
Would you like to save and end the session?
So I need to delay this by the same amount of time so you can hear it too.
There you go.
It should be cued up now.
Alright, I'm ready for this.
I'm ready to fucking show you guys once and for all that I bought bullshit in here.
Ready?
Let's go.
I gotta get out of here, I'm out of here, I'm leaving.
120 beats per minute.
Did it work?
Can I get down?
You guys are fucking with me, man.
I've been gone for life for ten and a half hours.
Yo, you're not on beat.
How can you not be on beat, you fucking boomer?
And I'm clearly just going...
It was clear as day.
I got my audio set up at 650 milliseconds delayed, camera delayed, audio delayed.
Alright, I'll see you guys later.
So the plan is...
So I'm not gonna be streaming tomorrow, or today.
Actually, the sus was set for today no stream, but I moved some stuff around, made it possible.
Hope you had a good time.
I had a lot of fun.
That was oddly satisfying video game.
I mean, near the end though, not really.
But it still was fun to hang out.
You guys rock.
Thanks for sticking around.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday, technically, right?
Yeah.
We are going to...
We are going to speed fire these bits.
And by speed fire, I mean go through them fairly quickly.
That was Seaman.
Hope you enjoyed it.
See you on Tuesday.
Thank you, everybody.
Oh shit, this really was like an 11 hour stream.
Damn.
I usually don't stream for more than like seven, six to eight or so.
Alright, let's go through them real quick.
Just because we're very kind of pressed for AM time here.
Let me make sure I have this set up, which I think I do.
I think I do.
Why?
What's going on with my Twitch?
That's the weird thing.
Twitch, what is it doing?
Messed up.
And now I can see it.
Okay.
Alright.
Now I can see everybody.
We had Hawkeye have mine $5.
Thank you, Hawkeye.
I'm so excited to watch the streamer milk this stream about orally transmitted Seaman.
What a dedicated variety streamer.
Thank you.
PeacefulHaley, thanks for the $2.50.
Thanks, PeacefulHaley.
Was I ever into mystery science theater or rift tracks?
I was.
I loved mystery science theater back in the day.
I have not seen any of the new one, the reboot one.
But with Mike Nelson, I didn't see this super original MST3K, but I did see the ones with Mike Nelson.
I was a Mike Nelson fan.
And then he also said, I want to get into coffee, but every time I take a sip, I feel like I'm going to vomit.
And I put a shit ton of cream and sugar into it, yet it still tastes gross.
The thing about coffee is you have to, there's really two ways to drink it.
It's either just straight up, just take, just drink it black or add milk or I don't adding a ton of sugar and coffee.
It just makes it.
Yeah, I don't I don't like adding a ton of sugar and a ton of cream to coffee.
It makes it weird and tastes like a cake.
If you can't get into coffee, then just drink tea.
You know, black tea is probably better.
You probably like the taste of it more.
Green tea.
But have a good night.
Thank you so much, PeacefulHaley.
Casey, thanks for the $2.50.
If you're going to continue with Dreamcast, I recommend Echo the Dolphin.
I believe I'm going to play Space Channel 5 is still on the menu.
The original one.
I have it in the shrink wrap, so that's going to have to be a stream in itself.
But I never played Echo the Dolphin.
Fiddy, thanks for five bucks.
Play the Canada OST.
Thank you for the five dollars.
And then Flying Muffin Man, again, a hundred bucks.
Thank you.
They said, Hey, the best.
I don't have the attention span to watch streams often, but it's often a treat to see a new video.
We caught it late earlier, but thank you.
Really appreciate it.
Thanks for the hundred bucks.
Thanks for tons of money.
You've given a lot of money this week.
Something or other.
Thanks for the $2.50.
Hey, Germs, I had to go to work last year, so I missed your response.
Firstly, I'd like to say thank you for taking the time out of your day to respond to my message.
No problem at all.
And you have another $2.50 here.
Saying, Secondly, I'm absolutely appalled at your lack of decency and perversion of the truth.
The people have the right to know the full story of what happened in that Applebee's.
Yes, I did chew up a bunch of Skittles and spit it in your food.
But that was because you, they were your Skittles and you kept throwing them at people.
You kept petting that poor, you kept pelting that poor waiter right in the eyes.
And when I approached you to ask you to cut it out, you said, I looked like Adam Sandler and I lost my cool.
I mean, that whole thing was made up.
You were throwing them at me and my table, trying to get my attention.
Again, I don't know if you thought it was like hilarious because you kept on going like, stream sniper!
And you kept throwing and it would hit me in the back of the head and I was ignoring it completely.
You know, I didn't lose my cool, you did.
Hey, Hollio, thanks for the holly.
Thanks for the five bucks.
Hey, Germa, I'm in Vegas right now for about a month.
Just saying that if I see you, I'll be sure to give you a good firm handshake.
And not just German suplex you.
Please don't German suplex me if I do end up seeing you around.
If anybody sees me anywhere, please say hello.
Welcome to Vegas.
It's a good town, just be careful.
Hey, Pigeon, thanks for the 250.
This is actually so damn cute.
I love you for doing this.
Seaman is a classic.
It's great.
It's so goddamn cute.
In a very disturbing kind of way.
But it is still.
Hey, Freudian Weapon, thanks for the 250.
Can you give us another condensed history lesson?
I forgot to study for my test tomorrow.
War bad.
Spice trading.
Trade sugar, tobacco trading.
Economies.
Collapses.
Entrepreneurship.
Industry.
Steam.
Coal.
Natural gas.
England? England.
England.
America.
And now here we are on this stream.
What about France? France!
France.
EU.
EU. EU. EU. EU. EU. EU. EU EU EU EU. EU EU EU EU EU.
Great, thank you DIVUS for the $3.41.
Thanks DivaUS.
Guillermo, I hope you are doing well.
I just want to say that these are the last bits I can get for now.
Money is getting kinda tight right now and I haven't been able to get
any bits from ads
from the Twitch desktop or on mobile
on my still try to stay subbed,
but yeah, thanks for your great streams and
the fantastic content. Thank you Divas.
You have consistently
and constantly given this stream money
every single time.
take care of yourself please make sure that you are doing well first before you even consider
giving a cent to this stream but you've been a contributor to monetarily at least for ever
every single fucking stream so don't feel sorry about that don't um you know money is getting
tight don't worry about that don't worry about paying me take care of yourself jerma heart at
the end there thank you so much nio aureon thank you for the three dollars i can't feel my nose
jeremy's son's last words uh flying muffin man also gave 40 that i missed earlier shout out to my
friend blue who's watching well hopefully blue stuck around i don't know if blue's still here
but that was 40 more dollars from flying muffin man a lot a lot a lot thank you for your 140
dollars smelly boy thanks for the three bucks jerma i did the exact same do you like america
thing you were talking about but on but on omega i can't even see omega that's just omega lull to
me now i omega is not even a real word to me now but yeah everybody wants to know what people think
about them but thank you smelly boy thank you thank you spurgleton we got your spurgleton
10 bucks came in but we'll touch upon it again we're trapped in the belly of this horrible
machine and the machine is bleeding to death hopefully we get out there were a ton of community
subs tonight at least 50 to 60 probably even 70 you guys are incredibly generous thank you
so much guys and it was it's a bunch of different people too it wasn't just one or two people that
gave community subs it was a lot of people so really appreciate it thank you guys uh thank you
to thank you to bunt for the three bucks are you also going to yell at your children to speak
english no i'm not going to have any children don't worry mostly lost thanks to the 250 now
that you stuck the microphone in your mouth you can say you do eat s no you can't there's this
i'm sorry guys you don't secondhand eat s there's no third party ass eating you either do or you
don't hey garfield the monday killer that's you garfield thanks to the 250 i don't know how i
feel about having such a strange creature named after me especially one who seems to have strange
backstage dealings hope he's just a weirdo and not actually some criminal mastermind
i'm not here or there but i'd keep an eye on him for you i've had to deal with a few monday spies
in my day if fish garfield tries anything fishy i'll be there to keep him at bay please applaud
that joke thanks chat hey what's with the minus twos come on what do i do i don't don't boo me
me hey frozen crazy tuna thanks for the four dollars sorry twitch chat is bullying you for
a fish i wasn't getting bullied this was i'm having a great time this whole stream was a lot
of fun we're probably bullying we're having fun if anything the fish was bullying me and you guys
were laughing at it that's kind of what happened but thank you frozen crazy tuna for the four bucks
and thank you the message too i was bullying pika banana gave 10 bucks as well as subs too i believe
thank you yes you are attractive have some money i appreciate that thank you thanks for the 10 bucks
and those are very very nice words thanks a lot pika hey dork cube thanks for the 350 i'm using
spring break as an excuse to buy bits again and i want to say that this semester so far has been a
lot of bullshit a bunch of classes i don't want to take so when i watched you play that vr hover
board game the other week and slam into the wall i was reminded what a wonderful world we live in
i love you too to keep making people laugh their asses off thank you sorry you have to take classes
you don't want to take unfortunately a lot of schools have the the mandatory credits that you
have to take right and it's can be annoying what a wonderful world me crashing into a wall
uh any joy that you take from this stream i keep saying it i sound like a broken record
but that means a lot i'm glad that you can take a load off and have some fun here thank you door
cube good luck in school good luck in the rest of your classes hey felix felis thanks for the
five dollars and 20 cents thank you felix hey germa us and the discord have reached a consensus
on the new emote it should be germa corn no no i'm not gonna put that as anyone sorry it's just
it's a piece of corn it's just a cursed corn appreciate the uh effort though guys uh it's
time for slime gave three six nine almost ten dollars here thank you it's time for slime they
say thanks to you i'm not addicted to picross no thanks to you i'm i am addicted to picross
it's ruining my life also please activate the stupid stream legends loot thanks i will i will
all right they say now i will activate the stream legends loot thanks for the nearly 10 bucks here
it's time for slime appreciate it uh never trust a purple what's going on purple 20 dollars from
never trust a purple germa ate ergo fungus on his pizza and is now tripping from naturally produced
lsd oh yeah i ate a pizza on stream it's been a long time it's almost been like a full day
on stream i forgot that i ate a pizza like four and a half hours ago i ate a whole pizza on stream
five hours is 24 hours this is what do you mean five hours this is almost 11 hour stream
five hours i see 1040 am i crazy it's only been 10 minutes no no i don't no i don't count that
here's why a day to me is not while you're sleeping now sure there are 24 hours in a day
but when you get up you're usually awake for about 15 to 18 hours right so 24 hours is a whole day
but you don't you're not awake you're asleep a waking day is you know like vr josh it's about
16 hours so i've spent almost the entire waking day on stream you know not when you're in bed
i've said this before and i will reiterate it as many times as i want to i don't know how the
fuck people do this shit how do you stream because i'm gonna give you some insight here
when you think about streaming and you think about how you know sitting here in a chair
with a camera on or with something on the screen and you're talking and you're
engaging right and for breaks right i maybe i'll go to take a piss like two or three times a stream
right it's not like oh i'll be back in like 40 minutes right like i'll see you guys in an hour
how do people sit here and live broadcast and entertain people for 12 straight hours like every
single day that's i can't even imagine doing that i know and everybody doesn't do that but i know
there's a lot of people that get come pretty close they do it by being boring oh yeah but if
even if you're the most you could be sitting there like think about when you guys sit there
let's just say playing a video game right even sitting down and playing a game for six seven
eight nine ten hours straight it takes a toll anyways you know even if you were not on a stream
anyway if you were sitting there just by yourself people do these 24 hour streams they do these
like marathons sit in the chair for 20 hours i don't know how you function it's just focusing
on the game and less interactivity well i mean i'm not i'm not dogging it i'm just saying it's
that's next level to broadcast consistently more than 10 hours of stream i can only go for
about eight hours straight and i forget to eat yeah interesting stuff but let's keep going
uh we're getting pretty close i zoned out and played starbound for 19 hours once that's so long
somebody's gonna you gotta like get unplugged somebody's gonna come into your room and like
pull the cord out of the back of your computer at that point you're like you have to get like
woken up you gotta get like shaken awake at that point but bingo sunshine thanks with five bucks
germ please get a haircut you look tim buckley from the webcomic control i'll delete it's not
the first time either but loss lol seriously thank you for streaming today it doesn't matter how i
do my hair it's always gonna look like shit no it doesn't it looked good in the beginning of the
stream uh call me divide thanks for the five bucks germ i'm glad that you get to do what you
love every day congrats on the fastest pizza world record
thank you call me divide no i love this shit i'm fucking as happy as a goddamn clam what does that
even mean somebody look up the origins of that phrase i don't know what it means but thank you
call me divide thank you mj thank you mj wodge for the 250 pizza joke was worth it oh my god
so why do i look 60 in this picture i look like a 65 year old lion person
i look like the actor that plays evanes or scrooge without the makeup on
fucking old germa lied about minecraft vr thanks for the five dollars how much do i have to donate
for you to peek the mic uh i don't like a thousand dollars probably so i can just get a new one
no no stop stop i'm kidding i'm not gonna peek the mic no one's i told you not amount no amount
of money is gonna make me peek the mic if somebody gets a thousand dollars right now i'm not gonna
do it i want to make that very clear it was a joke that was a joke it's not gonna fucking happen
don't do it i can promise you that i will not do that you need to know that and plus streams
over anyways good night will you do it though no i won't i'm not gonna do it hey jewels thanks
for the 250 if auto were to talk this way would you treat him any differently no probably not
uh-oh bro lux in the chat uh-oh
hey thank you to peek a banana again for the 10 bucks you're a good person germa hart hope you
weren't too uncomfortable with all those questions the frog man asked you about religion and politics
no i'm just kidding around it was fun i had a good time it's always a blast but thank you peek a
banana for your subs and your large amount of monetary bits here it means a lot thank you
uh sena bunny thanks for the 18 dollars sena bunny this is the best thing i've ever watched
thanks for making my day every day thank you sena bunny thank you for the nearly 20 dollars
thanks for hanging out i'm glad you enjoy yourself here hell yeah thank you also thank you to
jewels again for the 25 zero 250 that's 2050 cents this 1998 video game frog man has man frog
has inspired me to come up with political and religious questions to ask germa for the next fan
meet and greet so excited i won't answer it i'll just be like i don't know now this bro luck bro
luck thanks for the 250 here it's a twitch clip let's see what it is do i think the girlfriend is
wait wait what was it oh it's the girlfriend clip for example do you think your girlfriend is
the one what about egypt it's true no that's a heavy question to ask anybody imagine if you knew
okay you meet up with some friends you hang out with some friends maybe you haven't seen in a long
time you know that your buddy's got a girlfriend and just you're you go out to dinner or something
and there's like six thousand of you okay you're like you're big dinner there's a lot of people
there and in front of those six thousand people i stand up and i point to the the couple that's
been together for a couple years and i say hey uh everybody can have your attention i go
excuse me everybody ever can have your attention please and everyone just fucking stops eating puts
this to shit down it's like we're at a wedding and they look over here and i go i just want to
have a quick question to ask our two uh cute couple here uh is she the one are you getting
married it's gonna be like uh what the and you look around this fucking thousands of eyeballs
what would you do that's a pretty reasonable response and if you say yes that's a ton of
weight too that's true because then you got six thousand witnesses that are like well can't wait
to see them married and what if it doesn't happen then those six thousand people all expect you to
get married and what if it doesn't happen and then you look like a dickhead you show up like
three years later with some new girlfriend you said you were gonna marry that other girl
oh wow i was one of the six thousand fucking people that were at the uh farmers market
that day that you showed up that's six thousand wedding gifts you can steal and you look like a
dickhead for saying no that's right so i don't know maybe who knows i'm gonna let the world the
wind take me wherever it takes me that's the correct answer but thank you bro like
hey frody and weapon thanks for the 250 wow this frog man is really calling you out tonight
yeah yeah he was topac thanks for the three bucks not sure how your brain was able to
endure such brain fuckery for this long if you had any iq before this stream it's surely gone now
and people are giving me shit but not being like i keep like a beat i i got 11 hours of being told
a bunch of dog shit i had to sit there for 11 hours and have somebody berate me on stream
i can't like press the button quick enough i had eight hours of sleep during your stream
that's a full night's sleep when did you start watching the stream was only 11 hours long did
you just get here like 20 minutes ago a full night's sleep oh that's so funny thank you topac
thank you frody and we also had uh kxz thank you kxz for the 30 dollars 30 bucks from kxz it's
almost 9 a.m over here but i don't regret staying up for you easily one of your best streams today
keep on keeping on man man you think this is one of the best streams thank you that's i sleep
through every germa stream yeah yeah thanks for the 30 bucks kxz thanks for the subs thanks for
everything i really appreciate it frody and weapon thank you for the five dollars uh they say germa
heart bible thump bible thump why topac thanks for the 250 i miss shito please show him so i can
know he's okay i've been calling him for weeks and no answer i'm gonna call the child protection
services he's fine he's on a retreat right now he'll be back don't worry and then peeka banana
came in with 30 bucks on top of everything else peeka banana you this is like 200 fucking dollars
tonight but all that is with all the subs too how many subs did you give you gave like 10 20 30
community subs too it's a lot whatever it is it's definitely up there thank you peeka banana and
you say thanks for the stream today germa this is the first full stream i've been able to watch
and it was fun from start to finish you never failed to make us all laugh and you never failed
to brighten my day please keep it up and get some rest this was a really long stream germa heart
thank you the incredibly nice thing to say a bunch of fucking money i am spoiled rotten
means a lot though guys really thank you you've been you've been live for just over 11 hours by
this point you should have consumed at least 44 ounces of water i have not had even remote
one in that 1.3 liters of water i drank a coke how much how much water this is 12 ounces
no i had a i had a drink in here i've had like probably 20 so i probably had like 25 ounces of
water coke is negative water i'll go drink a full fucking gatorade bottle yeah i do have gatorade
coca de sugar detracts your water i'm gonna go drink one of those big goofy i'm sick gatorades
sugar compacts your body maybe you took better care of the frog
killer crockmeyer thank you should raid or host someone
uh i don't even know if anybody's streaming we're still streaming right now to do a host to
do a raid too i like to raid more than i like to host because raiding feels more like hey let's
go hosting kind of just happens i'd rather just like raid and be like this is what we're gonna
do we're gonna raid this person tonight and here we go is kraken streaming right now who the hell
is it i gotta take a look at a list but uh thank you to exifer for the 250 local craze and deranged
streamer plays demonic off tempo song to thousands at 4 a.m it was off tempo and i
wasn't you wasn't even my fault hey rainy david thanks for the five bucks you should play catherine
on stream so we can see you answer more difficult questions i've never played it is that the only
you you cubert up a wall right it's like reverse cubert like you climb walls and shit i don't know
maybe i haven't really given it a look yeah i'm gonna probably say no though probably not
hey novi thanks for the 333 three dollars and 33 cents can't believe you actually finished this
game this is gonna make for a great second germa video well they have a they have 11 hours to work
with let's see if they come up with uh almost only a few more left this washing machine thanks for
the three bucks thanks so much for the late night stream germa makes staying up studying for exams
way easier good luck on your exams and glad to glad to keep you company for a while while you
study you should have played this game connected to the polygraph machine an 11 hour polygraph
you know how you know how much money that would cost get somebody to sit here and fucking make
sure the questions are done correctly that would be like six grand that'd be a long paper hey can
can i take an 11 hour polygraph please so one stream worth of bits
not that much but uh thank you this washing machine good luck for all luck thanks to the
250 if you don't scream into your mic i will donate money you i'm not gonna scream and i'm
not going to not scream no money needs to be involved i'm not gonna do it i'm not gonna get
paid to do it not gonna pay not to do it it's not gonna happen i'm not going to do i'm gonna
neither one of those things are gonna happen clue the sniper thanks with 250 i'm heading out
good night hopefully i caught you right here have a great night so was that a real doctor
during the polygraph stream that's dr schmoyzen just because you don't have credentials doesn't
mean you can't be a real doctor uh but thank you siroc for the 250 kenshi frogman versus seaman
frogman at germa rumble probably probably it's pretty good idea and then finally we had kxz for
another ten dollars thank you kxz and finally tala mac thanks for the 250 at the very end here
hey germa i missed most of the stream can you play it again tomorrow or just do it one more time
hey for all luck what are you doing look holy shit look at these subs these are all the new
subs and all the three subs thank you everybody that's going fast as hell there's a lot of subs
bro look i'm disappointed in you that's what he said to me and frankly i i you know you don't
have to give me you don't have to give me that hundred bucks what for what because i didn't do it
i'm not gonna scream into the mic i'm not gonna do it i didn't yeah i didn't have to give it to you
well regardless that's a shitload of money thank you you've given so much money over the last
fucking decade it's been almost a decade lower the mic and scream no this is a nice microphone
you can really you can damage a mic that is this high quality by screaming as loud as you can into
it you can this is not just like a headset microphone this isn't a cman microphone i
will break this mic and have to order a new one and it's nice and it's why is there a five eight
emote this did you make that just oh okay first i was like what the fuck is going on
i always see you guys on tuesday thanks for sticking around thanks for staying for
this longer stream we saw the end of cman we actually got to the credits see you soon
god damn that's a lot of subs let's see who's uh who's streaming right now who's live right now
let's see uh kraken and joel are both live um let's go say hi to kraken we haven't seen we
haven't rated or hosted kraken in a while we've rated joel a couple times here in the last couple
weeks let's go let's go say hi to kraken say kraken is cosplaying what are you doing what
is he playing for a second i thought it said auto chess no it is auto chess uh joel is ending
yeah go just go scream at kraken loot the loot the loot the right right right uh kraken kraken
also is apparently drunk so i may be sending you to a a drunk stream just be aware of that
i'll give you the loot hold on just open up my dashboard if you have you playing stream legends on
a little dash down there i uh i'm about to give a gift which is every stream pretty much every
24 hours i can come in here and give everybody a present so if you're into it then open it
because it's coming in about 15 seconds and it should be there right now there you go new gear
what level is it what do we look at we look at guild right what level is the guild
is it an extension yeah it's all the way at the bottom of the page i put i buried it so it
wouldn't take up any real estate level 36 damn that's pretty good all right i'll see you guys
on tuesday go say hello to kraken go encourage them to be good at auto chess i don't i don't
know anything about auto chess so i know that people like it and it's kind of reminiscent
of the old warcraft 3 mods i have no idea go say hello let's get it queued up see you tuesday
thanks for sticking around i just hurt myself that was weird all right good night goodbye
good luck see you later queue up ready to raid kraken in seven six five four three two one queue
it up good night guys