Listen to that sound, listen to that sound, listen to this sound. It should. PS2 Slim. Okay, yeah, let's do it.
So this was a guitar stream that had a coliseum in the middle.
Let's do this. This is gonna be called Strummin' Along.
Um, Jammer, Lammy. Did it work? Let's make sure it works first. Reading disc. Is it gonna work?
PlayStation. Alright. Strummin' Along. Um, Jammer, Lammy. Let's do it. Does it work? Come on, work.
I don't have a PS1 memory card in here. Does that matter? I mean, this game's only like an hour and a half long, isn't it?
Like, I'm... It's not like it's gonna be a problem. I'm gonna beat it now.
This is made by the Rappa the Rappa Design Studio team.
Don't cry about this. No, I will not.
That sure was fun. Part one was good too, but this one had more juice.
Wait, was that Beaker?
What's wrong, Lammy? You seem down.
Oh, I wish I was that strong.
Lammy, you're already strong as is. You should be more confident. Nobody beats Lammy when she's on the guitar.
Guitar stream.
But that is the truth.
Guitar warrior!
We are milk cans. With my son's beats, Lammy's guitar, and my almighty bass combined with that distinguished voice, there's nothing to be afraid of.
Square!
Yeah!
We're lunches for everyone, right?
Hey, that's ours. That's our food.
Not only lunches, but a little babe. All dressed up for us. Ain't that right?
Here.
Let's do that around the whole earth.
See? The guitar rules again.
Let's go.
Gotta take it like a stage select.
Gotta make sure load and save, replay, mechanism replay, high score options.
Let's check it out.
Turn off the vibration subtitles.
What happened to this?
Oh, okay, first I'm like, wait, how do you get bites in the middle?
Level normal.
Alright, let's do it.
New game.
It's not easy.
Easy? We thought the bite was on the normal.
What should I tell them?
I had a stomach ache, so I went to the b-b-bathroom.
But there was a long line at the gas station.
I told them it was an emergency, but they said,
Let's rap for it.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Good.
Does this go?
Who's that?
And here's our best choc choc here.
Oh, this is like the third game. I forgot to tell you this.
This is, Parappa the Rapper comes up, Parappa the Rapper 2, and then I'm Jammer Lang.
Just in case you want to know.
You're supposed to know who this is.
Let's go.
Oh, it's up top. It's up top.
Watch this.
Oh, fuck.
Alright, I'll shut up.
Never get cool on easy.
What are you targeting on?
Is L like an L? Which L?
There's two L's.
Oh, shit.
When you see L, I don't know if it was left on the D pad or L.
What, it was vacuum cleaned the whole time?
What the what?
Yeah, L2 didn't exist.
Listen.
I lost my dojo.
I didn't get the bad one.
But the dojo remains in my mind.
It even has a casino.
Dojo. Casino.
That's all in my mind.
I have nothing to lose.
Wait, L2 and R2 did exist.
Did they?
Back in PlayStation 1?
I remember them existing.
They did?
I have a PlayStation 1 controller literally behind me.
Let me check.
Why didn't I just plug that in?
Wait, I've had this. Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. Could I have used this?
For Guitar-O-Man?
No, I couldn't have, right? It's not the same.
No, it's not the same input.
No, it's not, is it?
It is.
Oh, my fucking god.
This is an official PlayStation 1 controller.
I have an official PlayStation 1 controller in my hand.
PS1 doesn't have analog sticks.
This one does.
And they feel great.
I had one.
I had one right behind me.
I'm so infuriated.
I'm going back to Guitar-O-Man after this.
What happened to the Rome game?
This thing feels so much better.
Fucking hell, I have this.
Whoa, whoa.
Watch the electricity to the water.
What the fuck is going on here?
What's going on?
What?
Are you preventing us from...
Casino!
Is this a random person?
Let's go.
Everyone's gone crazy.
Gotta give it double sometimes.
Fuck.
Oh, that was a little better.
Freestyle, freestyle, here it comes.
Oh!
Freestyle!
Dude, you guys are throwing freestyles, aren't you guys?
High score.
The second I put a fucking real controller in my hands...
Come on. Do the math.
Oh, not that pizza.
Flanger?
What?
Why is this happening?
Wait, hold on a minute.
Hold on a second.
What?
What is going on?
I don't remember this.
She's pregnant?
I don't...
What?
No.
Oh my.
Are you in labor?
You don't need to worry anymore.
Get away from me.
What the fuck is going on?
Is this what it sounds like? I feel like I make this noise.
I feel like I do this when I talk sometimes.
Is this what it sounds like?
I know.
Stop.
Disc scratch.
What happened?
I'm so confused.
Jesus.
I think something's wrong with
the disc.
I'm trying not to laugh that
hard because I'm having issues.
And
that was really difficult to not.
The disc is no longer spinning.
The disc is clean.
What's fucking going on?
Go back to the Rome
game.
This thing has damage?
There's no damage on
here. I'm just trying to buff it out.
It might pick up right where it left off.
And I don't have a save either.
Shit. No, I want to play
this. Come on.
No.
Why?
Yeah, I have to restart it.
It's all right. I can get through those first. I want to play this.
This is fun. The PS2 is bricked.
No, it's not. Wait, can I go
into the browser?
Maybe it's something to do with the speed. Hold on a
second. Can't you do
something in the config file
and make it so it doesn't, like it spins the
PS, does something better?
It works harder or something?
Let me, I want to see. Is it
in here? No, no.
What am I doing? No, it's
not here. No, never mind. All right, let's try
it again.
Oh, man. That seriously
hurt my, yeah, it's not here.
I think it's just on automatically.
Well, I
have nothing really to say about what just happened. That was
that was fucking
bizarre. Is this even going to
read the disk now? Okay.
So we're going to skip that cutscene
when we get there. First of all, I'm going to destroy the first
two levels, you'll see.
Thank you, modest narcissist.
Modest narcissist for the
10th period of substance. Thank you.
But in the event that
that happens again.
Wait one second.
I'm getting the
up shit.
Really?
It's like another, I have to go. I'm going to skip
through the cutscenes.
Let's go.
Okay.
See if I can get cool on this one.
Isn't there a level select?
There is, but do you have to unlock them first?
Hold on.
I'll have to go back here and show you.
I don't have to do this again, do I? It's on normal.
Look. Vibration off.
Subtitles on normal.
Stage select.
Yeah, I can't.
Alright, let's go. Skip the
cutscenes so they don't break.
I have no idea where that is.
The last time I did an actual
PlayStation 1 stream
was like a year
and a half ago. It's somewhere in the
blocks.
Alright, let's get cool here.
Skyhide.
No!
Come on!
Why?
Look what you are holding in your hand.
I don't know.
What is it?
I'll get the next one. The next one's a good one. I want to get the next one again anyway.
So it doesn't matter.
Save the game. Save the game. Save the game. Save the game.
I can't.
I can't do it. I have a PlayStation 2
memory card. See?
I can't do it.
My PlayStation 1 memory card's like
buried somewhere.
I'll be fine. Postmates it.
No!
Go find it.
Watch this cutscene
while I look.
Got it.
I'm putting it into slot one. No, I'm not going to touch. Yes I am.
Slot one.
I now have a PlayStation 1 memory card in there.
Oh, I remember this song.
It's like great.
How is that bad?
What the fuck?
What the fuck? I did it last time.
Rock out!
Come on! Give me some points!
Your expression changes.
That's terrifying.
Why are you doing this?
Please!
What?
CD's in my hand.
Well, alright.
What's wrong with this thing?
It looks fine.
Uh oh.
I think our fun's over.
Plug in the PS1.
What? Again?
Again?
No!
Free style. Come on.
There it goes.
Oh fuck, I just was spamming.
I can't do anything.
There's a 3000 IQ play here, guys.
3000 IQ play here.
I did that.
Because I wanted to get rid of the
opportunity for it to crash during
the actual game.
What?
Only 3000 IQ?
That's pretty good.
For a god.
For a being that is just
stepping over every
single human bound.
You know what I mean? I'm boundless in my brain.
Alright, saved.
Alright.
I'm going to skip this.
Don't skip
the cutscene for this one. What?
I have to. What if it
breaks?
It's going to get stuck again.
Skip it, please.
I can't. See?
I told you.
I opened the tray on purpose.
Because I wanted to be right.
What? Oh, a bird!
What? It's in the room.
Alright, that was fucking not even funny. Why did I do that?
Now I am being skipped.
It's the dry
laugh he does.
Every stream. No, I don't do that every
stream. What if I can get
through this, are we? You're stuck here.
And I'm Jammer Lammy.
Alright.
We'll watch the whole thing. I'm going to close my eyes
and block my ears.
Tell me when it's over.
No. Why do they all
do this? I tried to go
down to the menu. Oh my god.
I hit down
to go to menu.
But it was on menu already.
Load, okay.
Load game. Load.
Alright. Apparently
it's been loaded. Stage select.
Level three.
Let's go.
Enjoy.
Here, stock up on this pizza.
Stock up on this pizza.
Skip. You do
realize.
Guys, if I don't skip it,
half of everybody in here is going to
be very upset with me. If I
do skip it, half
of everybody is going to be very upset
with me. It's a double
it's just two edges to
the sword. No matter what happens,
I'm always going to get like cut by the
blade.
The sword of plus two and minus
two.
Skip the whole game. Why would I do that?
I purchased it specifically.
I hate this part.
Alright, it's not skipping.
Okay, it's not
skipping.
Why? You didn't really have a baby, did you?
No!
Skip it quick!
Why?
Alright, I'm going to, I'm washing the disc.
There's nothing, there's no scratches
on this disc. How do you
how do I wash something?
How do you wash this? Toothpaste.
Alright, we're going to toothpaste it.
Right? Is that how you do it?
I'm going to put like a shirt on.
No, don't. That's not how you do it.
Wipe it with a cloth.
Alright, hold on. I'll be right back.
What the fuck? Oh my
god. Is the stream still on?
What the fuck is going on?
Stop! Why do I
have this other controller here?
I have this other Playstation 2 controller that's
on my lap. It's been on my lap the whole time.
Okay, we're good.
Alright, if this don't work, I don't
know what will.
I did peanut butter. You know, if you get gum
on your hair, you do peanut butter.
So, let's see if
it works. Well, I
had to do that because I don't have toothpaste.
I don't brush my teeth with toothpaste.
I don't even have a toothbrush.
So, I have a teething stick.
You know, like your dog chews
on like bone, I just chew on like a
teething bone. And then I hold
my mouth open in the shower just like this so that
my teeth out and just have it just fray my fucking face
really hard.
I just like, I chew on a bone.
Alright, here we go.
Which one is it on?
Why have I done this?
Does red mean highlighted?
Or does it green mean
highlighted? I've already fucked it up. Green is
highlighted, right?
Red is highlighted.
Okay. I'm skipping
that cutscene. We're not gonna give it a second.
Here we go. Don't even give it a
second. What do you mean don't
skip? I'm skipping it.
Done.
Goddamn broken ass
disk.
I'm getting the PlayStation 1. Stay right there.
What does this have for power?
Oh, I don't even know what that is.
I have no idea what the power is for this thing.
I have no idea.
It's a plug with a
yellow plug.
I don't even know what that looks like.
I want to continue playing it. I want
to play this. Where is it?
Come on. It's somewhere in here.
I just cleaned up two.
Oh.
I just cleaned it all up too and it's not. I don't know where it is.
Wait a minute. Is it this one?
What is this? No.
That's the Nintendo Switch.
What the fuck was that? Was it the PS2?
Do it on an emulator?
I mean, I gotta go
get an emulator.
I have to go get it and set up a
PlayStation 1 emulator?
Found it.
Found it. Found it. Found it. Found it. Found it. Found it.
I got it. Hold on.
Alright. Give me a minute.
This is going to be kind of
fucked up but let's go for it. Let's see if I can do this.
Hold on. Stay right there.
I'll be right back.
That was pretty damn quick.
That was pretty damn
quick. Let's see if it
worked. Can you see? That was pretty
damn quick. Here we go.
Let's go. Ah, blue.
Don't skip. What are you?
Guys, I just hooked up an entire
new console in like
41 seconds.
That has to be some kind of record.
Has to be. Don't skip.
Alright. Here we go.
Shit. Wait.
It's already loaded. Right. Okay. Here we go.
Sharper too. This guy's playing on
original hardware.
I'm skipping it.
Let's go.
I'm killing it right now.
I got confused.
Diaper check. What's in there?
Fuck.
The pit rate's going down.
What the fuck?
And she fucking pukes. I hate this thing.
I swear.
I want to do that one again.
Thank you. You got a little...
I only have eight more minutes.
Hates his viewers.
What are you talking about?
Let's see now.
Was it the green button
or the blue switch?
In there.
Have somebody seen?
Where in the world were you, soldier?
Haven't you ever heard the term
punctual? In the Air Force,
a split second decision makes the difference
between life and death.
Don't you know?
Here we go.
Oh, I kind of forgot
how to fly.
Is it the best song?
See, I had to go
repair my denture a few days ago.
Boy,
I can eat almonds.
Look,
I told you we don't have all day.
Get to work now, soldier.
This guy,
another one of those.
Casino?
It's a casino
airplane.
Come on, you can do it, PS1.
It's supposed to be
in there, come on.
Put it back in the PS2.
Oh,
fucking goddammit.
Did I save it before this one?
Come on!
PS1 for cutscenes
and PS2 for when you load it in.
Give me one second.
Let's plug the power in.
Which one is the right cord?
I don't remember, it's this one.
Alright, back to the PS2.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going to plug that in.
I need the memory card, the controller,
and let's go.
I had a save point right there,
so I'm just going to skip that cutscene
and see what happens.
Let's emulate it.
It would take like 30 minutes for me to set up an emulator.
It takes me 25 seconds
to switch consoles.
Let's see, here we go.
Stage left, stage four.
Skip.
Wait, we're rocking?
Alright, cool.
Let's go!
I fucked that up.
Uh-oh!
Get out of here!
And then I run out of oxygen.
I kind of...
I kind of killed that one.
Save it.
That sounded absolutely awful.
Well, some adventure, hey?
Thanks.
I only have two minutes!
I only have three more minutes.
But close enough now.
Thanks, sir.
I think we got over all the problems.
Guitar! My guitar!
Where did I put it?
All the problems are gone, I think.
It was the middle of the game.
Oh, no!
I left it on the plane!
Hey, there's one.
A guitar.
What kind?
Well, um, a cool one.
An awesome sound and has reclining seats,
power steering and door airbags.
I don't have time for jokers!
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I just want one that's cool and cheap,
and of course the sound quality's gotta be superior.
Hmm, a greedy girl, ain't ya?
Oh, please!
I'll do anything, anything, please!
What?
Help! Go away!
You said anything, didn't ya?
You're going to kill me with a chainsaw.
Come on!
Let's make a guitar!
But, but I don't make a guitar.
Casino here, casino there.
Casino in my hair.
Don't touch the top of that thing.
Get your hands away from the top of that.
It's not going to be good.
Go.
Oh, shit!
What happened?
Come on, bring it back.
I just tied the things in perfectly.
Almost done.
Ah, fuck!
Back to the PS1.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's drying.
We're almost done with the song.
It's like this last line here.
Look it, it's done.
Come on, do it!
It's right there.
Just grab the guitar and be done.
It's right here.
Open track, close it quick.
I'm only doing this one more fucking goddamn time.
I ain't doing this again.
This is the last time I'm doing this.
All the problems are gone.
They were though, they actually were.
Put in a backwards compatible PS3.
That's not going to do it.
Here we go.
Skip the cutscene fucking immediately.
You already saw it.
Go.
Please, PlayStation 1, do it.
What is it talking about?
I did it.
I'm not spamming.
It's almost like it takes too long
to get to the next note and you stop playing.
I really need to move on.
All right, we're good.
How many more levels are there in this game?
No, I don't think it's going to happen again.
This is like the last level.
There's no way it's going to happen again.
This is the last level.
For one second, I thought it was happening again.
I thought that was actually happening again.
All right.
Straight to hell.
All right, so I went back in time.
Who thinks you are coming in this late?
Don't underestimate me just because I'm an idol.
Come on, it's time to do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
You see, I was on my way to my own show,
but I ended up here.
How did that happen?
Anyways, I'll help you get to where you're going.
Where's hell?
Can you really do that?
Yeah, only if you play right.
Come on.
This is the original PlayStation 1 version.
This is the original PlayStation 1 version?
And A version.
Really?
Why would they censor hell?
Please, just do it.
Just do it.
Yes, all right, we're good.
Let's get cool on this one.
That does not look very safe.
It looked right.
There's an electrocuting vehicle in the crowd.
Electrocuting!
I can't move it.
I can still go?
Even this one.
Oh no.
Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
No fucking around now.
Check this out.
You guys don't understand.
Fuck.
You don't understand the song.
It's fucking weird.
The beat is off.
What the fuck?
I'm playing to a different song.
What did I do wrong there?
Huh?
What?
I'm pressing the button
when it goes over every time.
What the fuck?
This one.
It's not the controller.
It's this shitty song.
That was so...
That was so fucking bad.
Explain to me.
That was the worst line I've ever done.
And I still won.
I still got it.
No.
I just wanted to pause the game.
Why can't you pause video games back in the year 2000?
Why can't you not pause video games back in 1999?
It's cheating.
What if I have to go to the bathroom?
What if I'm about to beat the level and I'm going to shit my pants?
You have to hold it.
What is this song?
I hate this song.
Guys.
This song is dead.
Guys, seriously.
You don't understand.
Come on.
Bring it back. I don't want to do this again.
Back up. Please.
So bad.
Why was it worth points?
Yes. Yes. I did it.
Unbanned.
I did it.
That was...
That song...
That was not a very good song for me.
I like that one.
That's all I heard.
I couldn't hear the words.
They put this crazy filter on some of these voices.
I can't even hear the words.
You took my job.
My watch is broken. My guitar strings broke.
My costume has wrinkles.
And I don't get any messages on my beeper.
Because of you.
Say what?
Let's see who's the better guitarist.
I'm really in a hurry.
Some other day.
Follow me in.
Get back here.
Hey, check this out.
Live in concert.
Milk can. That's us.
That's right around the corner.
Uh-huh.
That's why we have to get going right now.
How does this look?
This has been a wild ride.
Well, what about this one?
But this kind of makes me look heavy.
You think this one's better?
That's it.
The band's logo's gotta be really big.
My picture doesn't have to stand out.
Oh, come on.
It reminds me of one of those
weird, like, fucked up YouTube kids videos.
I'm really, really sorry. I got caught up in a lot of this.
Okay, this is it.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. Milk can is always on my mind.
Lead it to Milk Can!
Was Parappa like this too?
I think it was.
Parappa being this dialed up to like
1,000.
Here we go.
Oh, here's the title song.
Get up, get up.
That was awesome.
I missed that one.
Something's confusing.
What the fuck is my turn?
No.
That was fucking cheating.
Last song.
Wait, if I hold my hand on the PlayStation.
Okay, I have to have one hand on the PlayStation.
Put your foot up there. Okay.
That's a good idea.
Come on!
God damn it. I can hear it running.
Squared and doing it?
No, it's fucked.
This thing is fucked.
This is fucked up.
Was this the last song?
Do Megalovania? Hold on.
This is the last song, right?
We just pretended that I did it.
Wait, movement.
What if I just don't touch anything?
We want the falls.
Come on.
Just be patient with it.
Turn the PlayStation one upside down.
What the fuck?
It's upside down.
It's not fair.
Come on, stop.
It worked for a second.
Ow!
The sucker baited me.
Oh, fuck.
This is not good.
Turn it back right side up.
What if I just move it?
I think I have to shake the PlayStation.
Just sway it back and forth.
Okay, I'm almost there.
This is going to get good.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
I don't want to...
No.
Do I get extra points?
Upside down again.
It's dead.
Wait, okay. I have a plan.
I have a plan.
I have to get cool.
It should work.
I think the controls are backwards.
I know I can do this.
Doh!
I knew I was going to be able to do it.
I have to start over.
I have to get cool or it's not happening.
What?
It worked last time. Okay, I'll get it.
I'm getting teased, my love is real neat
I'm trying to shift into gear
That's when I see you coming
Trying to sack myself
Cause it seems like it's time to try to get downtown
I'm thinking I can get out now
Getting close, I'm just running, running around
To all the problems that I get through
When the times say no
I'm getting teased, my love is real neat
I'm trying to shift into gear
Trying to sack myself
I'm getting teased, my love is real neat
Trying to shift into gear
That's when I see you coming
Trying to get into gear
Trying to sack myself
Cause it seems like it's time to try to get downtown
Trying to get down town
Come on! Getting cool is just like, you gotta just spam R.I.P. shit.
Burger Boy played Parack of the Rapper 1 and spammed every single group and got cool.
Honestly, I don't stand a chance.
Get cool!
Why?!
It's about to break!
I have to restart.
If I don't get cool on this one, I'm breaking the disk.
Half of my life I'm going to save it because it's worth a month.
Come on!
That was it! That was it!
That was actually it.
I had to just do a huge thing there.
Here we go. I'll get it this time. This is the one.
Okay.
Sometimes you have to get super points.
With PlayStation 2, it's too late.
Yeah!
Oh, fuck! No!
Did I miss the part?
No! What are we doing back here?
What are we doing back here?
Just gotta get it again.
Fighting against like a...
I'm going against the tide here, as they say.
Damn it.
I even got cool too and then I wasn't cool enough to stay cool.
Shit. I'm not breaking this disk.
It's a great game.
It was just sold to me
by some motherfucker
that didn't tell me that it was broken.
I'll be like $50, please.
Dickhead!
I don't even know how much this was.
Somebody look it up.
What's this going for right now?
I had it too. Shit!
Oh, I'm so disappointed.
It's okay. It's alright.
It's alright. Don't worry.
There's no reason to fret over that.
Shit!
I would have had it the first time if it just didn't break.
Okay.
This stream's gonna turn off here
in like 45 minutes.
I'm doing this is it.
If it doesn't solve it here, just pretend I beat the game.
That's how long you're gonna play Dead Rising 1
given how bad it is.
Dead Rising 1's a great game. What are you talking about?
Alright, let's see if we can do this.
Waste of time, yeah.
That's the kind of nature of this whole level, isn't it?
So far.
It's alright.
I'm having a good time.
This is the last level. No, it's not.
Oh, fuck.
The stream thumbnail is a blue screen.
Alright, let's see if for the last time
we hear this.
Don't fuck it up, let's go!
I wanna see some Hawke Champ!
It sucks.
I passed it.
Alright, don't fuck it up. I passed it.
I passed the glitching.
No!
So, it flipped it on me.
And I instantly lost, apparently.
What a fucking trick.
Why?
I even got to cool for like
about 60 seconds.
Oh my god, why?
Why?
I'm about to leave.
I gotta go home. I already am home.
What was so wrong with that?
Is this what hell feels like? No, they censored that.
LR...
What the fuck?
That's so
fucked up.
That part is such a mess.
Even if I do it right.
It doesn't make sense.
It's so slow.
You motherfucker.
Hey!
Did you see that?
He had his fucking game now.
It was trying to fuck me over
at the very end of that.
There he is.
Okay, I did it.
Wait, wait, wait.
I stopped dicking around earlier.
I had to change consoles
to stop the game from crashing.
I would have beat it the first time.
What? I would have beat it the first time.
I didn't mess around and have the game
crash mid song.
I was talking.
You couldn't hear me?
What is he saying?
Somebody said if only he stopped dicking around
in the beginning.
I have been trying
to switch consoles like
five times.
You should have just had an emulator.
Illegal!
You should have overclocked
your Playstation 1.
Alright, so let's see.
Wait, what's going on?
Why is this running at like two frames a second?
He's made a 3D movie maker.
Why is that the post credits thing?
Parappa?
I have a Parappa the Rapper one.
What about you, PJ?
I have a chocolate frosty
and a cherry pie.
No, no, no. I'm talking about Katie's Lime Show.
What are you going to do?
Oh, then I'll have six chocolate frosties
and a large cherry pie.
Here we go.
Yeah!
Get the fuck out of my way!
He needs to eat some fucking vegetables.
Then I'll pour me rain.
And just push the button.
Pour me rain.
Come. Then I'll come.
Then I'll come. Pour me rain.
Pour me rain. Then come.
Pour me push.
Then I'll rain. Come.
No, no, I gotta get out of here.
I have to leave now.
No.
No. No.
Alright, that's it.
That's it. That's it.
That's the stream. I'm out of here.
My stomach hurts.
I have to leave.
No. Okay.
I will see you tomorrow.
I have to...
As the term goes.
I gotta get out of here.
Thanks for watching everybody.
Unfortunately we ran into technical problems
I'm Jeremy Lammydisc.
We'll be back tomorrow.
We're gonna play Tryin' Tomorrow
with Star.
So that'll be just kind of a chill stream.
Solving puzzles and shit.
I think Ashley's gonna come too.
So that should be a good one. And then
we're gonna get away from the PlayStation
1 and PlayStation 2 stuff. We're gonna play The Thing
on probably Monday.
So I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching.
This was a lot of fun.
Guitar Man was awesome.
This was fun too.
Hope you enjoyed yourselves. I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Take care.
If you're sticking around to do the bits.
Hey look I gifted 100 subs again.
We'll get to them. Tomorrow's stream
by the way is gonna be starting
Actually no it'll be
normal. Nevermind.
For some reason I was like, no it will.
Somewhere around 1 or 2 o'clock Pacific.
Dodge? What did I do?
Yeah this shit doesn't work.
It kind of, it just
doesn't make any sense. It's all good though.
Eventually I will fix this.
This stomach hurts.
So.
God damn it. I don't know
what to even say.
What do you even say?
Thank you from earlier.
We had, what's wrong with chat?
Nothing. Don't worry.
Don't look into it. Trust. Don't worry.
Freddie Dread had
10,000 bits earlier. Thank you Freddie Dread.
We caught it but just want to say
thanks again.
Daffy Jones thanks for the 500 bits.
They say, please get well soon Jerma.
Let us pray together for your swift recovery.
Our boomer who streamed from Vegas
ancient by thy name thy
carnival come thy jokes be repeats
on earth as it is in Jupiter
give us this day our daily laughs and forgive us of our
minus twos as we forgive thy late
streams lead us not into Cox
high speed internet but deliver us from
yellow skin. Amen.
Those of you that missed the beginning of the stream.
I had a weird
scare today.
That, just kind of have to go watch it.
It's a long winded thing.
I can't even explain what it was.
It's too long.
But thank you Daffy Jones. Appreciate that.
Tingy thanks for the 250. Jerma before
you get the liver scan go to the grocery store
buy the freshest liver you can and
get the doctor to scan that.
He'll get back to you with healthy results and you'll feel better in no time.
Those livers
Those livers are dead.
I don't think that's a good idea.
But healthy. Deadly healthy.
Thank you Tingy.
Thank you C4G for the 350.
Guitarra Man was
one of the first games I owned and I think the very first
game I actually beat.
I love this game and I can't wait to see you 100%
every level first try. And then they do the
that's me face.
It was fun. It was just maybe the
controller I was using. I still can't believe that I could have used
the Playstation 1 controller and it was right behind me the whole time.
It was just right under my nose.
Moo means Moo thanks for the 500
bits Moo. Kim could probably
save a lot of time and emotional labor
by just buying one of those rubber jar toppers
if she needed jars opened.
Yeah but then I can't be, I can't open it on stream
and look strong.
Hey Spooky Spitfire thanks
for the 250. So first things first
I'm done with Dark Souls 3
on my run. I had beat Orphan first
try. I don't know how you did that.
I've never beaten Orphan before which is even more surprising.
How do you beat Orphan first try?
That shit is like impossible.
They said also I had you muted
your stream and played Ludwig's theme over
it and it made the first music fight a million
times better. Did it match
up though? That's more important I think.
Just don't get hit. Yeah but
that's hard. Thank you Spooky Spitfire
I appreciate it. Yeah Orphan of Kos
what do you think I was talking about?
Good luck for the rest of your
you got anything else to do?
Oh you gotta do Sekiro now. Uh oh.
Good luck. Thank you back in for the 250.
Thank you for streaming as always. You never cease to entertain.
It's my birthday today and I want to thank
Stevie the
xEV
for helping out. Also have a great one chat.
Alright. Happy birthday.
Hope you had a good one.
And thanks Stevie for helping out.
Appreciate it. That guy Tag
gave
twenty dollars
two thousand bits.
They say Jerm hello Jerm this is
one of my favorite games ever made.
The PS2 version has iffy controls
the PSP version does the best. I still
play it to this day. It was awesome.
It was great. I mean back then
that was
pretty well done. But thanks a lot Tag.
No not the Rome game.
Yeah the Rome game.
No he's talking about Gitarro man.
Cause there's a
should I? No.
Rome game. Oh my fucking
god that's funny. Hamtaro
man? What are you guys
talking about? Isn't that
a hamster thing?
Anyways Tag thanks so much for the
twenty fucking dollars the two thousand bits.
Good to see you.
I was watching the tip of the hat
stream for a little bit. Tried to throw you
guys a host on Saturday. You guys
did a great fucking thing so
good on you guys. But that was Tag.
And by the way
go follow Tag. Please put
Tag's channel here.
Really really really
good dude. Alright I'll just do it.
I got it right here. Oh somebody did it first.
Who's today's top
subgifter? Me apparently.
But thanks Tag.
Go follow Tag if you don't.
Vilemi right after that gave
two thousand bits as well. Twenty dollars from
Vilemi right after that too.
Streamer is pretending to be bad.
And then they do Jermis Sauer.
He's pretending. He's always
pretending. That's just what he does. He just pretends
to miss keys.
He pretends to
get hit and fall off cliffs.
That's what he does. He's a pretender.
He's a liar. Don't trust
him. Don't trust anything he says.
No thank you though. Thanks for the
twenty fucking dollars. Thank you
Multitrip for the 250 worst sounding stream
2019. I get it
because of the guitar. Okay.
Thanks for the 250. Appreciate it.
Debockery man thanks for the five hundred bits.
When's the Elite Beat Agent stream?
I need to compile a bunch of stuff
for the DS.
And get it captured.
I think there's a way you can mod a DS and have
it capturable. Because I know
emulators exist and I have used them before.
But there's something
different about them.
And sometimes it can be hard to set up.
Especially when you get towards the PS2, PS3 stuff.
I know that these games are all
emulatable but I like playing on original
hardware. I actually do like doing
it. It just kind of feels better
to me. Modding the DS
is a crime. It is?
Why? Wait I can't like put
a capture card in a DS? Why is that illegal?
Well, but I do
like playing on mostly if I can original
hardware. If it's possible.
Modifying the software.
Well then I'll put my webcam at it. Whatever who cares.
We'll go back to like fucking 2009.
Yet you got a fake PS2
controller. No I have a real PS1
controller back there but a fake PS2
controller because
that's what it came with. And I was
too lazy to go get like the real play.
It's a real PlayStation. It's just an off-brand
one. Thank you debauchery man.
Maybe at some point in the future.
We'll see. C4G thanks for the 250.
I don't know how you managed to do that with your
wonky sticks but I'm glad we got to hear
all the bangers. Most of them anyways.
A couple of notes got lost in the process.
I really wish this got a re-release
for modern systems because I really love
this game. Thanks for showing it.
I think the rhythm game is
due for a big comeback.
And I'm not talking about
Guitar Hero. I'm talking
the original
rhythm game stuff.
And it looks like the
initial tremors are starting
here. You've got Space Channel
5 isn't that making a comeback?
Isn't there a new rhythm heaven game?
Or didn't one just recently release
or one's coming out? Guitar
Hero 1 and 2 was fun. No I
mean those games were so much fun
but licensed video game
soundtracks. You know what I mean?
You're actually playing the guitar
to Van Halen.
Not a Parappa the Rappa style original
songs with a little fun
cute original storyline.
I think you'll see a little bit more of that
comeback. It goes in cycles.
Derma sounds so constipated.
Look I know
that's like a meta joke
reference. That's a meta reference
to the fact that you found out today
that I'm on prescription grade
laxatives. I know that that's why
you're saying that. And you've
turned it. You've turned the key here.
Now I'm angry. I'm angry with you.
I'm angry with you.
What do you care?
First it's just like
what do I fucking care?
Nah I'm just kidding. Anyways
where were we? Over here.
Snowflakes. Am I
right? For 250 thanks for the 250.
Yo Jeremy your streams have been a comfort
of mine for a while. I made some
portraits of you and Kim cause why
not? Here they are. I'll upload them to my Insta
if you are still chill with that.
Thanks for the laughs. Throw these into
the community content night channel.
Toss them in there.
We'll pull them out during that next night.
Which will probably be
pretty soon actually.
Let me see. What day
is it? Today's the 19th.
I would probably say
somewhere. Maybe there's enough to do it
before Halloween.
It's possible.
Monday and then
24, 25, 26.
Let me see.
If I can't do it before
the Halloween stream happens. Then it'll be
early November for sure. But
those of you
that I guess. I actually have to put this
down in the
description down below.
That artwork and videos
are not going to be opened at the end of
streams anymore. They're going to go
into that Discord channel.
If you have anything that you want to
show on stream, we do a community
content night once a month.
Where we compile all
of them and we go through and we have a whole stream where
everybody comes and hangs out there.
Rather than have at the end of
streams, you know
30, 40, 50% of people will
take off because obviously it's like oh the stream's
over. I got all the shit I want to do and
see you later. But that's, you know, that's fine, right?
So
that was kind of the idea is to have them
all compiled rather than have them open at
the end of the stream. But
please, please, please put them in that community content
on the Discord. If you don't know what the Discord is
it's right here. It's a public
open Discord. Join
it. It's a great community.
Look forward to seeing what you do. And make sure
you watermark all your shit
so I know who it's from. Very important.
But thank you so much. I look forward to seeing it.
Thank you for the 250.
Really. Plank V2, thanks
for the 1100
bits. Fun fact,
gladiators didn't die every fight
because they were too expensive to replace.
It's a fact I guess. Is that true?
Interesting. Thank you Plank
for the 11 dollars.
Look directly at the Discord channel when I do it next time?
Yeah, but then I have to like cap
Discord. And you
can't really like full screen Discord.
It's still messages that you have to open.
And I'd rather just do it the way
that I did before. Gladiators weren't
real. What? Hey,
Appleship, thanks for the 250. Hey man, I need to submit my
senior quote for the yearbook by the end of November.
Can you come up with one for me? Choose wisely.
This will be my high school legacy forever.
Um, okay.
Use this one. Start the
quote. Keep your eyes on the prize.
The road to success
is always under construction.
Pretty fucking goddamn good
if you ask me.
Boring, boring, boring, boring, boring,
boring, boring.
That's what my mother used to say to me.
That's a quote from my mother.
You making fun of my mother?
You making fun of my mother? Mrs. Elberton?
I didn't end quote yet.
Oh, well, end it.
There.
That's not a good quote.
That's too long for a yearbook.
You can't use that
one. Use the first part of that that I said.
Not the other end of it.
Oh god. Well, anyways,
congratulations.
Take care. Thank you, Appleship.
Hey!
Heavy Min, thanks for the
500 bits. I would absolutely love to see you play Dead
Rising, genuinely my favorite game of all
time. I even did all the awful
awful achievements for it, including the survive
for 14 literal hours
by doing nothing one.
That's gonna be a really, really
fun stream.
Because don't you have to make choices on who
survives and stuff?
And it's a time limit, right?
Yeah, that's gonna be a ton of fun.
I'm gonna do that sooner rather than later.
That might end up happening before Halloween.
I've never played it. I've seen people
play that game. And me and
Star played Dead Rising 2?
Dead Rising 3? But we didn't even get
out of the fucking first room.
I think we made it 10 minutes into
the game and we were just throwing shit at each other.
I don't remember. There's a video on it.
I think it was 2. Yeah, I've never played the first one.
I've played Dead Rising 3
as well. I've played every
Dead Rising game for like 2 hours each.
Except for the first one.
Dead Rising 4? I don't even remember
which one it was. Hey, Master
Chicken, thanks for the 1500 bits. 15 bucks
from Master Chicken, thank you.
Jeremiah, I almost pissed my pants when the disc started skipping.
There are tears pouring down my face.
I mean, it was fucking crazy.
So, I...
Hopefully you're alright.
Thank you to Funky Chicken for the 300 bits.
If Steve is short
for Stevious,
then Jerma is short for a
34-year-old man.
Nice. Got him. Yeah.
I mean, I'm gonna read it.
Whatever. I don't care.
Thank you JVibs for the
500 bits. Hey, Jerma, it's Josh.
We met in Las Vegas.
I finally used the Prime sub
like I promised. Keep on going strong.
I do remember that.
Kim and I were out to dinner.
We were trying to find new
places to go.
And this dude walked up to us.
By the way, this was like
last week.
No, not VR, Josh.
Kim and I were like, oh, where do you want to go?
Let's try some new places we fucking don't go.
I was like, oh, what about here?
How about here? How about there?
And then he flashed you.
No, that did not happen.
New places.
Right? The Vegas buffet is worst to best.
There's like
700 of them.
I can't do that.
Here's the thing about Vegas though.
Vegas has more restaurants and more places to eat
than any place I've ever been on Earth.
There are probably like
2,000 restaurants in Las Vegas.
It's fucking crazy.
It's overwhelming.
And they're all good.
They're all good except for, well, hold on.
I don't want to get ahead of myself there.
Do I have a Yeti restaurant?
Hash House to Go Go is the best restaurant I've ever been to.
In Vegas.
That's in the link.
Please, please go if you're ever in Vegas.
Do a Vegas restaurant tier list.
It would not happen.
But anyways, no, I do remember Kim and I were just like
walking around and it was just like, hey,
what's up?
And you used the prime sub like you promised.
That's fucking awesome.
It was a pleasure.
I was just saying hello, seriously.
Hope you had a good rest of your trip.
I know that you were on a trip.
You were just going to stop it in and
demand a sub from the guy.
No, that's not what happened.
Now, if anybody ever sees me,
and look, I know that
I currently live
in a destination city.
And there are a lot of places
that you could potentially just see me
because there's so much to do here.
There's a bunch
of stuff to do on strip. There's a bunch of stuff off
strip. There's a bunch of stuff downtown
and some of the other areas and towns
and communities and stuff.
So I know that there's a lot of
people that go to Vegas all the time.
People have said already
that, hey, I'm going to be in Vegas.
I'm going to be in Vegas. I'm going to be in Vegas. So if
you end up just seeing me somewhere,
do not hesitate to just say hello.
It's not going to bother me. Don't worry
about that. I was there in September, but I
didn't see him. What if I try
to bother you? Well, then
I will get security.
They're everywhere.
I will just go,
excuse me, sir.
This person's trying to bother me.
What do you mean he hates us? Somebody just
said, what if I was trying to bother
you? What does that mean?
What does that mean? That means you're trying to bother
me. Shouldn't I be like, hey, security?
What does that even mean?
Psycho
Streamer throws fans out from
the strip. Well, if you're going to
be like a dick
and not like leave me alone and be like
mean and like do fucking
awful shit and say awful, I'm going to be like, get
away from me. Like, oh, get the fuck out
of here. What do you want me to do?
What? That's like a
basic human thing.
If somebody walked up to you and was
like grabbing you and like fucking
screaming in your face and like peeking from
behind corners and like hiding from
you, looking at you to be like,
yeah, I'm coming
for you. You don't think you'd be
like, um, can
somebody help me here, please?
I'll call security on you.
That's not how it works.
Anyways, let's put the credits on. But
no, long story short, if you do see me out,
you know, if like me and Kim are like
trying a new restaurant or something and you see
us at the restaurant, then fucking
whatever. Just come say hello.
I'm totally alright with that.
Shout out to my favorite centipede
stream. What do you mean centipede?
What the fuck does that mean? Wormo.
Oh. Anyways, here come the credits.
Uh, thanks everybody for
your support, your continued support.
It means a fucking shitload.
Gotta bump ya. Sorry.
Oh fuck, I thought that was a webcam.
And I don't have any clothes on.
Alright, I'm good.
We're not watching the frog video again.
What you are gonna watch is
you're gonna watch this pop up.
Thanks everybody.
A couple more bits to do we have.
The ball of koala thanks to the five
hundred bits. Five fifty actually.
Hey Jerma put my broken
umjammer lambi disc up for sale online
and some idiot actually bought it.
Laughing my ass off, I scammed him.
Thanks. Well, enjoy your
like forty eight dollars,
whatever this was. I don't even remember.
Hey gnarly, thanks for the two fifty.
Hey, just making sure you met your quota for one
reference per stream of a certain
thing. I didn't hear one yet and
I don't want you to break your three year streak.
Not gonna happen. Thank you Freudian
Weapon for the five hundred bits.
Thank you. The game glitching out made
my night. My bro and I laughed so hard our heads
were hurting so thanks for the laughs.
I mean it was a shit show. I already
forgot your name, how to pronounce
it. I'm so sorry.
I remember like two days ago
I was corrected on this.
It's Czexin
S and I've already
forgot it. I don't remember.
Czexin? Czexin?
It was Czexin. Okay, right.
Right. Czexin.
I will remember next time, I promise.
Czexin gave five community subs.
Thanks for the five subs, Czexin.
And then we had don't start
let me
for the five hundred and fifty
bits. Play the yeti game, you'll get yeti
nightmares. I don't
know what that is. Why
is there a Terminator emote? Why is there
a Terminator emote? That's like not
even the Terminator. That's like the Mortal
Combat DLC Terminator.
DinoPulseZetta
thanks for the five community subs
right now. Thank you.
Appreciate it. Thanks for the five subs.
Ishanji
thanks for the two thousand bits
twenty dollars. Hey funny streamer
Jeremy. Love your streams.
Never seen anyone so determined to finish a physically defective
game before. Well I
bought it. Yeah look
okay hold on. It's real easy to be like
just like skip this one.
Just throw it in the trash.
Break it. Burn it. I
bought this game. I don't want to just like
break it.
I mean if it was Guy Fieri
the Guy Fieri game who cares?
I've just
look I've only destroyed
two or three games on stream ever in
like six years. Eight. No like
ten years. The Guy Fieri
minute to win it game
I shredded. Okay?
Which by the way do not do that. Don't try that
at home. It's not safe. Do not shred
anything that unless
you are certain that it is a
shredder that is capable of doing what you are trying
to do. Read the instructions.
Don't do that at home first of all.
Second of all Army of Two
was the other one that I broke in half.
I've never broken another game
on stream in at least in
the four and a half years plus that I've done this.
So come on I don't break
games. And then so the
second part here
any chance you'll stream tale of the sun
someday. It's a PS1
caveman simulator where you try to build
a tower to the sun out of mammoth
bones. Well you
just put a new game on the list.
And they say one of the more unique games on
the system. Also here's a clip to commemorate
your legendary freestyle today.
Your legendary freestyle
today. What was my
legendary freestyle?
Then I'll come
Oh right
right. We don't have to
listen to this. It happened already.
Thanks.
We don't have to listen to that.
Thanks for the
Thanks for the 20 dollars seriously. 2,000 bits.
And I'll put that on the list, tale of the sun.
Next time I'll do some PS1 stuff for sure.
Sir Canine, thanks for the
500 bits. They say
Hey Jeremy, here's a funny video.
Videos go in the
community content night.
If it's about the community. But I know it's not.
Because I have
memorized the like
first five
letters of this link.
And I know what it is. It is this.
I know what it is already.
So that's fine.
I'm prepared. But thank you
Sir Canine for the five dollars. And then finally
Colusia, thank you for the 300
bits. The stream made me laugh so hard my
sides are killing me. Thank you Jerma. Also here's a picture
of my cat cuddling my
Andy Mark Goat. What the
what the fuck? Hold on.
Holy shit.
Look. So sleepy.
That's cute. That's
really cute. Well thank you for this.
This is great.
Sleepy.
Thanks a lot though. Seriously.
And that's it. I'll see you guys tomorrow
for Trine. Star and I are
going to play Trine.
We're going to do the three Triners. Expect
tomorrow to be more of just a chill out
stream. I would imagine.
We're just going to play Trine. The new one.
Take care guys. See you soon. See you tomorrow.
Have a great rest of your night.
And that is where we end
this stream. Goodnight guys.