How's everybody doing? How are you? How have you been? You've been good?
Doing all right? How are things? Things going all right?
I'm late? Well, I'm not really. I'm not really. I'm early.
Started to 40 minutes early. Is that you? Is it you from Fortnite?
Yeah, that's me from Fortnite. I've played it before. You sound tall today.
Do I? Interesting. I sound tall today. Do I sound different today?
Would you say that I sound a little a little different today?
In regards to the other few days, few months, maybe.
Yeah. Hmm. No, there is no I don't notice anything.
No, I don't. I don't know. Did you change something? Interesting.
I went back to the other mic and I had someone here
that went through all the audio settings and tried to solve the mystery
of why my microphone sounds so bad. This is the this is the other microphone.
And let's do a scream test.
We, we, we, we, we fixed it, by the way.
Thanks a lot. Audio community, Jake.
You smoked a ball and watched.
Yeah. Can you give me a fix this?
Yeah, I just smoke.
You want money? No, no, you're not getting any of that.
Be honest with me. Are we good?
Are we actually good for real?
Like, do I sound fine? Do I need to be louder? Do I?
Are we good? Finally? Am I finally good?
Can I get louder and can we test it? Do I sound fine?
Am I good to go now?
Do I am I a live streamer after 12 fucking years?
Do I sound OK?
Now we just need to fix the webcam, which is I'm never changing it, by the way.
I did move it about two inches.
Anyways, welcome.
I will be the first to welcome you. Welcome to
what we're coining here on this community as Omega Gaming Weekend.
That's right. That's right.
Just regular streams.
I just happen to be doing them in a row.
Normal stream is streaming normally.
Just happened to be doing it a few times in a row.
That's literally it.
Oh, I get it. This is Omega Gaming Weekend.
I'm your host.
We're going to be starting with fish, feed and grow.
By the way, I've got actually 25 games to play this weekend.
I'm going to read them to you.
And look, I'm not writing them down because if you don't remember, that's your fault.
I'm going to go through them quick
because I don't want I want people to go like, wait, what the wait?
What did you say? Hey, somebody in the discord.
What was the last one? No. Good luck.
Over the next three days, we're going to play for at least 30 to 40 minutes each
or maybe like 20, maybe 10 minutes.
It might suck.
Some of these we might not play at all.
Let me make that clear.
I just put them on here to make people like get excited, but they're available.
Slice and dice from Ichiyo.
20 minutes till dawn.
Grounded plants versus zombies, the original one.
Sorcery part three, Splatoon three, Breath of the Wild, the Zoombinis,
Ultrakill, Disney Infinity 3.0, feed and grow fish,
multiverses, hamster playground, Turmoil, Betrayal at Club Low,
Dead Rising 3, Deadly Night, Bounty of One, Cult of the Lamb,
Puparazzi, Peglin, Pathologic 2, Talk to Strangers and Subnautica below zero.
I hope everybody gets fucking freaks out over those.
We're probably going to play four of them.
We're going to get through five of these.
It's a boring, what do you mean a boring list?
Somebody said, you said boring list?
Bro, boring list.
Breath of the Wild, Deadly Night, Slice and Dice, Splatoon.
I told you I would never play Splatoon.
Why? How come? Why are you not free?
What game would be on this list that you would be happy with?
There's every genre.
Some of these are some of the highest rated games
that come out in the last like five, ten years.
What would be on here? Roblox?
Why would I play Roblox? Why would I play Fortnite?
I'm not going to play Fortnite.
How come Ghostbusters 2011 is not on there?
It's not on here.
This is Omega Gaming Weekend and I picked the game.
Boring list.
Plants, the original Plants versus Zombies is like, holy shit.
I would have freaked out if I heard that and I was in the chat.
And maybe at some point during this weekend,
you might be able to face me in multiverses.
I'll see you in the multiverses.
There's no sponsor this weekend. Let me just be clear.
I'm just like walking around.
There's no sponsor or anything. I'm just I'm being a weirdo.
All right. So here's what we're going to do.
There was a poll in pre-stream. If you weren't here, then well, sorry.
We're going to start with feed and grow fish.
I don't think the multiplayer works. I tried it a few times.
I it doesn't work.
So we're just going to do single player.
And I'm here like 40 minutes early, so relax.
You know, honestly, I really shouldn't even said the list out loud
because I would I could have said, hey, I got 25 games.
And some of you game Andes that I'm mad that, you know,
Mario Galaxy 2 isn't on here.
You might have thought it was on here.
I could have just pretended like, oh, no, there's other stuff on here.
You don't you never know what's on here.
None of these before. I know I'm just I'm being a weirdo.
All right. So we're going to start. Let's go.
This is Omega Gaming Weekend, and I'm your host.
Terminate. How are you?
New angle. What do you think?
New audio, new angle.
It's a little bit over here. It's not as weird, right?
I was told it by somebody very, very reliable that it was weird,
and I couldn't understand.
Somebody told me the camera angle the last time,
the last two times have been fucking weird.
No, there's no way you're saying that.
There's no it's impossible.
Like, no, my own girlfriend says this.
I'm like, there's no way there's no fucking way.
I looked fine. Why was it so weird?
It's just a webcam. It's just a face cam.
Who cares? It doesn't care.
Does it really matter? It's every everybody is against me
from Community Jake to my girlfriend, to my entire community, to my parents.
I had my mother look at it.
She was like, you look strange, honey.
I'm just like, no, everyone's against me.
They don't. Nobody gets it.
Nobody gets it but me. You know what I'm saying?
I don't know. That was supposed to be a neck crack.
All right, let's go.
This is game where you have to you have to eat and you have to grow.
And I don't know. People said play it.
This is what we're starting with. Let's start in the river.
Do mediums. Wait, this is too quiet.
Can you just hear anything? There we go.
Now I can hear it. All right, let's go.
This is a child game.
All right, I got a hatch.
So this is a game.
It's like what's that game that came out like 20 years ago?
You have to don't get eaten, but you have to eat fish.
Eat five and raise four babies.
How do I isn't attacking me? How do I eat?
This is my mouth. Am I eating this?
Is that my mouth opening and closing?
What's that? Oh, it's candy.
Candy. Oh, that's alive.
Was it alive?
Hey, get out of this mine.
OK, wait, there's a little one right here.
Do I eat snails? What can I eat?
Do I have to eat the candies and that's it?
Where's my fish? Oh, there I am.
How could you not like it? Look on the left.
Yeah, I need to eat. Does that mean how do I turn?
Oh, shit. OK, where where do I eat food?
Can I walk yet? Oh, shit. There he is.
He's not coming for me, right? Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, no, I feel bad. That was like horrible.
That was like horrible.
How do I grow up?
It looks like the hunter became the hunted.
Where are we all going?
I don't know where I'm supposed to be going.
I just wait and be a scavenger.
Where's my health going down?
My health is going. What do I do?
Do I eat rocks?
Wait, there it is. Get it.
How do you eat? Am I dead?
Can I just attach to this?
How was the break button?
I'm dead. OK, that's fun.
Now, wait, now I it wasn't enough.
It wasn't even clear what I needed to do.
OK, eat five of those.
I'm not big enough to eat five of those.
Get out of here. What am I even eating?
Dude, I can't eat anything.
What? That's your brother.
I didn't eat him.
We're going to stick together, bro.
Let's stay together.
Survival of the fittest, bro. Sorry.
Where'd he go? Oh, wait.
This is bad. Oh, no.
You're in trouble. OK, bye.
Dude, what the fuck? Nature sucks.
Like, imagine being a little minnow or something.
You've born and you're just dead.
What? That's terrible.
Like, I'm alive.
Gone. You don't even know.
You don't even know that you're alive.
It's crazy.
I think that fish is dead.
All right, I need to find little things to eat.
How do you turn?
Am I swimming upstream? Is that the problem?
All right, this group, but we can hang out with this group.
I'm dead. OK, great.
This guy's a maniac. Are you kidding me?
I'm coming for that guy.
I have to at least get to the next height, right?
OK, what is small enough for me to eat?
I have to find food that's been ripped up already.
And then we just eat it.
OK, I'm going this way.
Don't run into me.
Terraria music kind of sounds like that.
But what do I I can't eat?
Wouldn't that be just what should I do?
Is it stuff on the ground?
What about this? This is like a grasshopper.
OK, you need the grasshoppers. Good.
Thanks. You need the little like grasshopper shrimp.
I can't actually.
Are you small enough? No.
Left, left, left.
No, it's too big.
Top left, top left.
Eat five of those. They're too big.
Why can you eat that and I can't?
I don't get it.
I don't understand. What do you mean wrong button?
It's not left click, right click.
There we go. All right.
I figured I had to play. That was sad.
I don't want to eat the snails.
There are only one XP.
This is going to take all day to get higher.
Wait, there's worms.
Just stay on the ground. I'm not going anywhere.
Yeah, just eat these worms.
If I hide in this area, the big ones won't get.
This is a horror game. All right.
Stay on the ground.
Get over here, you fucking grasshopper.
Don't even think about it.
This is safe in here, I think.
Halfway. You're getting toxic.
I'm just trying to level up once.
Hopefully my brothers and sisters made it.
Wait, I just got a huge amount of experience.
But what? You can do first person.
No, you can't. Look at how dirty that one is.
All right. Come on. I'm so close to leveling.
Level up. All right. Am I bigger?
I am a little bigger. OK.
What can I what can I fit in my mouth now?
I'm going to snipe this. I got it. I got it.
I sniped it. What's wrong with me?
Why am I dying? Oh, that's not filling anymore.
All right. I need to scavenge, I think.
Maybe I can eat the little little ones.
Let's see. I can eat these still.
You know, sometimes my brain decides to think a certain way.
And I was just concerned that I was going to drown.
I was like, oh, do I have to go up for air?
Because where's my air meter?
And I'm like, wait, that doesn't make any sense.
In my brain for one second, I was not a fish.
I was a person down here or I was a different
like an animal or something. Wait, danger.
Oh, I'm not supposed to be here.
Nemo did not show up here.
Oh, how do I get back up?
How do I climb back up? How do I climb back up?
I went to the next area.
OK, wait, I might be able to scavenge.
This is definitely a scavenge scenario.
Look at all these.
OK, here we go. And oh, never mind.
Oh, shit, that's one of my friends.
How did you get down here?
It's all right. I got you. Try to eat them.
Oh, my God. Hide in the, hide in the murkiness.
I just got baited so bad. That was terrible.
This game is scary.
You know where this would be crazy is VR.
Do you imagine having to deal with this in VR?
You're not going to eat.
I'm way too small of a fry for you.
But oh, shit, you ate it in one gulp.
OK, I was going to say, break it up for me.
I'm going to follow you.
I'm following the big chunky one.
Because nobody's going to fuck with the big chunky one, right?
And the big chunky one will leave some scraps.
Don't be stupid. All right, here we go.
There's no chance anyone's going to fuck with the big chunky guy.
Hold on. Did I get any? Shit, I didn't get any.
Ow. I'm dead.
Oh, my God. I was so close.
All right. I'm good. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
What fish are you? I actually don't have any idea.
Shit. Oh, that's so frustrating.
I'm too impatient to play this.
I swam directly into one of their mouths.
I got some. All right. That's a huge chunk.
Deathmatch is quicker.
I'll try this in another couple of times.
You pick the fish that you want to start as, I think, right?
How I understand it. This game's kind of fun.
This is really dumb what I'm doing, but whatever.
But look at the frenzy over here. I need to eat something.
I can't swim down. The current is so strong here.
I actually cannot move. Is that a snail?
What is this snail doing?
Is that a hook? Is it a hook?
He's tripping. All right. Come on.
How am I not getting full from this?
Am I sprinting too much? Get off me. Get off.
Get away from me. Oh, my God. This game's hard.
Fuck. Let's go. What's the strat here?
I'm just going to float on the bottom and just I'm going to coast.
I'm not going to dash unless I hear the scary sound yet.
Please, seriously, get out of here.
Go eat something that's way bigger.
You're really going to come after the one single McDonald's French fry
when there are cheeseburgers in the ocean,
when there are steaks in the ocean floating around.
You're going to eat the one single fucking McDonald's French fry.
Get out of here. Fuck off.
It's true, though. Already leveled up.
Like, this looks delicious.
Yeah. You know, you know, the crumbs that are on the counter
after you make a sandwich.
Hmm. Don't eat the sandwich, though, that literally swam away.
It ran away. It ran by.
I'm not going that way. You look handsome today. Thanks.
Stop YouTube reacting.
You're fine. You actually he's right next to me.
OK. How do I get out of here?
Eat him, eat him, eat him, eat him, eat him, eat him.
He's he tastes better.
He was he was he was dipped in beer, batter, oil.
Well, I'm what?
Why are we all getting sucked into like wormhole?
Oh, no, I'm out of here.
I am out of here.
Go back down to the sea floor.
I'm not messing around now.
Why am I dying? Oh, I'm hungry.
Come on. What?
How many of these do I have to eat before I'm fine?
Oh, God. Oh, it's so fucking hard.
I got better. I got better. I got better.
Look at this. Come on.
Poor little fellow.
OK. What am I doing wrong here?
Let us eat it. Leave some for me, too.
You can't just eat it all. You took two of those.
That's not fair. We should have split it exactly one and a half.
One and a half.
Hey, if if if mom didn't just get eaten, I would tell her I'm to leave.
Can we take this thing? Oh, no, no, brother.
What do I do? Can I stop this?
Brother, I need to tell you something.
If you die, I'm going to eat your body, just letting you know.
That's the way it is, right?
That's the way of nature, unfortunately.
OK, save a seat at the oh, I think he's dead.
No, he's still alive. He's still alive.
He's still alive. This is so sad.
No, not me. He's still alive.
I'm I'm going to die if I don't eat something right now.
You piece of shit. I swear to God.
If I if I go even five feet above the ground,
I'm going to uninstall steam.
You understand? Like this round, don't leave the floor.
Just eat everything on the floor.
Why am I flying around looking at stuff?
This is guaranteed death.
Look at all these scrumptious things down here.
That's not five feet. That's like two feet.
Actually, two feet.
We're talking about the scale of the actual game.
There we go. All right. Nice.
Oh, chop that up. Chop them up.
Chop them up. Chop them up.
I'll level up immediately. Can I help?
He's hit me with a tail.
I got experience for being around that when it died.
Give me some. Give me. It's too big.
I can't eat it.
Oh, OK. Don't be stupid. Don't be greedy.
All right. Get out. Get out. Get out. I'm almost level three.
I need more. I'm hungry.
Eat him in his sleep. Come on.
What the fuck? This game is so funny.
God damn it.
Can we just like latch on to this guy and like attack him?
No, I can't. Why didn't I couldn't break him up?
I have gums. I have one tooth.
Do not leak.
Don't do not even go one or two, five feet above where you are right now
until level two. Just stay on the ground.
Don't get up or anything. Eat the grasshoppers.
OK. Stay down here for now.
Only go up if I see an opportunity.
No other reason. Opportunity.
All on everything.
I just got a ton of experience.
Something big died around here somewhere.
All right. This is huge. This is huge.
I might actually be able to see what the hell level three looks like.
Almost there. I eat that.
Oh, get away from me.
All right. Now you want to go. You want to go now?
Yeah, get munched.
Expect me to grow up, did you?
I'll take you instead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm running out of food.
Just go back down to the snails and shit.
OK, am I right?
Whoa, one of are you a friend?
Why you look at he's green.
I need to help him. Stop fighting.
What are you doing? You can't take that on.
Are you out of your mind? I'll help you.
We can eat this. We need this. We need this.
You're so fast.
You still with me?
He doesn't look so good. He's green.
No, don't mess with that.
All right.
Wait, wait, opportunity.
I don't know what to do.
I'm just floating.
I'm just floating right now.
I don't know what to do. I'm freaking out.
Oh, no, greenie.
Stay with us.
What the fuck? It's impossible.
It's impossible.
That was a new rare species and we'll never know.
Don't go near the big fish.
Oh, the current is just taking me.
I can't. I have to.
The current is just moving me.
Oh, help me.
Somebody, see if you fucking like it.
You like it? Huh?
David and Goliath time.
Did that hurt?
They were just reacting to that.
Did you see that?
He was like, and then just walked away.
I have to get to level four or so.
There's other areas too.
Like, what are you even doing in our spawn?
Spawn camping piece of shit.
Like, get him out of here.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, why can he spawn camp? That's not fair.
All right. Do the same thing I did last time.
I'll get to level two here.
This guy's annoying.
Yeah. Can you please get out?
Can you please like get the fuck out of Angoro Crater
and go to the Northrend where you belong,
you fucking asshole?
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
Oh, I'm getting herbs.
Oh, shut up.
Oh, you got how many stacks of herbs do you need?
I don't know, like six or 7,000.
You've been here since four o'clock in the afternoon.
It is now like midnight.
And I log back on you're still here killing people.
I'm just getting herbs, man.
No, you're not.
That's such a dumb excuse.
Well, not Angoro.
Angoro was contested, right?
I remember there was one of them
where he was just like, what are you doing here?
Strangle, there you are.
Strangle Thornvale.
People just stayed there.
They didn't leave.
They would be there at level 60.
It's like a level 30 zone.
And they would just stay there permanently.
I don't even know if they played the rest of the game.
They got to 60 and went right to Strangle Thorn.
What's he talking about?
People that, no, no.
Oh, I'm gonna starve.
Karin is too strong.
Oh no, not the snail.
Actually, this might be good.
I'm just gonna stay in the bottom.
You just gotta get lucky.
Thanks for the help.
I'm gonna die.
Okay, I need to focus.
This game is just like Slither.io, okay?
You just walk around in a circle
until one of the big people die.
And then you try to inhale as much as possible
and not be one of the 10 people that run into each other.
And then you get to be the big, big dog, right?
For a little while.
We gotta stay.
I wanna do this.
Why are the green ones so aggressive?
You're just gonna die.
Come on, dude.
All right, enough, enough, enough, enough.
We're not fighting here.
We're, you're fighting babies.
You're so tough.
These are infant children that you are fighting
as a group of adults.
Get out of here.
You should not be here.
Imagine going to the like, the peewee leagues
as like a fucking 40 year old man
and full sprint tackling like a fucking 11 year old
and getting up and being like, yeah!
And like high-fiving your other 40 year old friend
that's there too.
That's what's happening right now.
You suck at this.
This game's hard.
Will he reach?
Stop, you don't have to gamble if I'm gonna make it.
This is, all right, when I get big enough,
I'm coming back here and we're gonna bully this person.
Just wait till I type into general,
just wait till I type into trade chat in Ironforge.
Somebody please come kill this level 60 undead rogue
that won't leave.
And you get somebody who's like, oh, help, what?
What's what?
Hey, like get, you get like the party invite.
Oh, it's like a level 60.
It's a paladin.
Paladins in WoW, back in classic WoW,
if it was a paladin that responded,
they were gonna like LARP in RP
and they were gonna help you.
It was always a paladin.
And then they would show up and they would point.
They would do the slash point
and then get absolutely eviscerated.
I already got sucked into the thing.
They would get eviscerated.
It was not even a contest,
but it was long enough for you to like get out of the way
and now it was his problem or it was her problem.
And then somebody would be like,
that person would go, no, no, no, no, no, fuck this.
I'll be right back.
They would log out of that paladin
and they'd come back on like a shadow priest.
That's all decked out in like tier two gear.
All the while, you just want,
God, I'm mad at this fish.
Stop talking.
I know, I know.
All right, no more talking.
I'm not gonna speak this whole time.
I'm gonna get to level three right now.
Okay.
Is there a map?
Cause I want to mark on the map where this is.
All right.
Stop pushing me.
No, don't go that way.
Oh, I haven't blinked in like 40 minutes.
That's mine.
Don't touch that.
Thank God, you idiot.
I got 20 XP because he died.
That's so stupid.
No, I stopped paying attention.
You're laughing at the guy.
Oh, it's all right.
I'm okay.
Please, God damn it, man.
I am so, I can't play this game.
It takes too much focus.
Put both headphones in.
Just don't talk about World of Warcraft.
Don't talk about Mario.
Don't talk about anything besides focusing on the game.
Give me some of my drink.
I moved you guys over here.
You used to be over there, but now you're over here.
I'm going full immersion mode this round.
We can take them.
Did we get it?
You ate it.
Go get your own food.
Is that Carl?
I don't, I mean, there are 400 million of us
that were just born like an hour ago.
I don't know who, you could be, you might be Carl.
Points, what?
Easy money.
What?
What do you mean easy money?
What did you guys just do?
Come here.
These ones are fucking fast.
We have to get this, otherwise we're gonna die.
Don't eat it all.
If you eat that all, I swear to God.
Oh, that's a juicy one.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
Am I, am I all right?
That was, that was bad.
That was very bad.
How does it, I'm sorry.
I'm actually sorry about that.
I actually freaked the fuck out.
How do I repair?
Can I heal?
Get, no, stop.
Get away from me.
I'm so close.
No, I'm so close.
Where's my, no, my God.
I, I know where this is Omega gaming weekend,
but I'm playing this a little more.
I'm not leaving yet.
Not on a note like this.
This guy's such a scumbag.
That fish is on a patrol to just eat children.
Really?
Don't go that way.
Yeah, I'm just gonna come back every few hours
and see how many more children I can eat.
That's a pit stop.
He's stopping on his way back home.
Oh, let's eat some more big children.
I love how they can just like hit their heads.
It's like I caught him and he was so startled
that I caught him what he was doing that he freaked out.
Here's some snacks over here.
Good.
We're good.
Can somebody confirm just dashing?
It does dashing take food.
I haven't really been able to see it.
It's leveling up is what's doing that.
Okay.
I'm not going anywhere without full food.
Where is everybody?
Where'd everybody go?
Did they all go into that waterfall section?
Level three, bro, coming up.
Please die.
I don't think it's gonna happen this time.
Don't get overconfident.
All of the big fish I think have left
to go to the second area.
I think it'll be all right.
I have a never ending supply of bugs.
Why did I just lose hunger?
What just happened?
That was weird.
Honestly, I think I lucked out here.
The RNG went nuts and I think it sucked every single fish
into that second part, except for you.
I'm level three.
What do I do?
Should I go after him?
No, not yet.
I'm still gonna eat bugs for a little while.
What's that?
Oh, it's a shrimp.
Am I ready for the next zone?
Not yet.
What was that?
That big guy is still here.
I just saw him.
Yeah, I'm being complete patient only.
Did everyone left?
I'm gonna go through the waterfall
and it's gonna be mayhem.
I'm almost level four.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
That wasn't, we were trying to kill that.
There was at least a few times where we were biting.
I was biting and attacking this
and it was, I think it was my mother.
It wasn't coming back every hour to eat the children.
It was coming back to take care of us and protect us.
Oh boy.
All right, don't lose this.
Where do I go?
Oh, I'm gonna be on a frenzy here.
Where's the waterfall?
Ow.
All right, let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm so much bigger than everybody.
Let's go.
Oh, hey, what's going on?
Remember me?
It's not fair.
These guys are huge.
What?
Choosing different fish.
It's not working.
That was not working.
Different fish.
So I was screaming like this was a horror game
at the mother coming back every time.
That's so stupid.
Aren't you, no, you're, no.
Where are you people coming from?
Where are all these people coming from?
Where were they even coming from?
I don't get it.
I'm going to the swamp.
What's crab madness?
I don't know.
There's probably different fishes here.
Wait, I can be the dinosaur?
All right, I want to be the alligator.
That was a different species, by the way.
The thing that I thought was a shiny special green one.
No, that's why it was so aggressive.
I thought it was one of my friends.
I should have just eaten them.
All right, let's move.
Is the strategy to stay with the mother?
Yeah, of course it is.
No shit.
Really?
You got to be kidding me.
This is the, okay.
Mom, where'd mom go?
Let me have some.
This is what I should have been doing the whole time.
Are you kidding me?
That's so frustrating.
I'm level two already.
Mom, don't leave us.
Mom, mom.
Oh, what do we do now?
Oh, we got to stick together.
I don't know what to do.
I think we can kill that.
I'm starving.
Drink the blood.
Can I drink the blood?
Do not eat that.
You piece of shit.
I swear to God, you better not get that.
Get him, get him, come on.
Good job, good fight, good fight.
Retreating, retreating, retreating, retreating, retreating.
I'm on him, I'm on him, I'm on him, I'm on him, I'm on him,
on him, on him, on him, on him, on him.
Retreating.
Stunning, stunning.
Consecrating, consecrating, I got consecration.
Stun.
I got to shrink it, I got to shrink it out.
Trink it out, trick it out, trick it out.
I need shield, I need power shield.
Got to stun.
You fucking idiot.
Stop.
I don't even know where I am.
Where am I?
Can I eat you just whole or what?
No, but I can kill you though.
Can't I just grab?
It's so hard to fucking aim.
Dude, eat him.
You're right next to him.
Eat him.
How hard is it to grab?
Just eat him.
Eat, eat that.
Eat that.
Eat it.
I don't think I'm ever gonna make it.
Poisonous fish?
I was wondering, was I allergic to that food?
I don't appreciate you calling me a cigarette, Andy.
I want an apology.
Whoa, is that a catfish?
All right, where's mom?
Mom, are you gonna fight the catfish?
I think so.
Are we gonna get a battle?
All right, this time don't lose the mom.
This is gonna be insane amount of food.
Can I have some or what?
Really guys?
Really?
That's so, you're ridiculous.
I can't, well, that was an entire,
that was like 10 months worth of food.
Where's mom?
That's not, that's not my mom.
That's not mom.
All right, dude, get, really?
I wish there was a horn I could do like.
You gonna let me have some?
I'm gonna starve.
It has to be broken down to eat,
but by the time it gets broken down, she just eats it.
Somebody said, dude, is this what fish do all day?
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
And can you eat something?
Can you please kill something for me?
Did you kill everything already?
And now I'm just gonna starve to death next to you.
And then you're probably gonna eat me.
No, mom, mom, mom.
Ah, I need to eat, I'm sorry.
Oh my God, oh my God, I'm fucking traumatized for life.
I'm traumatized for life.
Is there, are you a friend?
What are, what the hell is that?
What is this thing?
Are you, can you help me?
Can we be friends?
You don't seem hostile, but maybe you can help me.
There's a big scary guppy out there, Lariat.
Come on.
Oh, that was so terrible.
That was so sad.
Oh, I didn't like any of that.
No, I'm not big enough.
I'm about to die.
I wonder if there's a heal.
Maybe if I, it's like Minecraft,
if I have full hunger, I can heal.
Let's test that theory.
That theory testing.
Where's my friend?
I had a friend down here, where is he?
Oh shit.
I did heal, okay.
I'm bleeding, I think.
Oh, this is not good.
You can smell that, can't you?
Friendly?
No, that's the bastard that killed my mother.
No, don't do it, don't do it.
You're not strong enough.
Ah!
What's he doing?
No, he's not gonna be able to do it.
Turn the music down, it's too loud.
All right, this time,
I thought that was a giant whale or something.
All right, this, I need to eat.
Stop eating all the food.
I have to just be quick.
If you're gonna do the mom strat,
then you have to really, really be right.
I'm just gonna spam right click.
Okay, okay, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Holy shit.
That's so much food for everybody.
There's food for everyone here.
All right, we're good, we're good, we're good,
we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good.
Oh my God, I'm level three.
Where'd mom go?
I'm too big to look.
No, don't bite mom, you stupid.
Get that one too, mom.
Nice, nice one.
Yes, all right, I'm good.
I'm gonna stick together though, I think.
Okay, I need to eat all this stuff
and then I need to have children.
I think that's a good idea.
That's a huge grip.
I don't think I need to stick together.
I'm a absolute carnivore, aren't I?
I'm so bad at this.
Mom, I actually still need your help.
There you go.
This is like some other thing.
This is another turf, right?
All right, hold on.
Hey, well, I guess that's fair, that's fair.
What about this thing?
Why does that hurt?
Why does it hurt me?
It has spines?
Oh, shit, okay.
I need to move to a different place.
Who's that?
Oh, that's a meaty fish.
Hey, I can't kill that.
Why not?
Too big?
No, come here.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Depth perception.
It's hard to land hits.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Crab, nice.
You piece of shit.
All right, I gotta hide because I need to heal.
Any more crabs?
Ooh, all right, all right, all right.
Let me help you.
Holy shit, it's an omega snake.
Where are these other fish that I need to eat?
I was level six.
It was rocks?
Looks like shit.
Okay, let's go over here.
What is that stuff?
Why is the music changing?
Mine, my food now.
Where you wanna go?
Level seven.
You wanna go?
Which one?
Oh, I remember you.
You remember me?
I watched you kill my mother.
All right, I'm done, the game's over.
I'm done, I'm actually done playing the game.
That was fun.
That was fun, that sucked.
I'll try a death match.
What should I play after this?
I got a lot.
Anything else you guys wanna see from that initial list?
How do I join?
Fish select.
Wait, you can be a stingray?
Puffer fish?
I have no coins.
Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute.
What's free?
How did I not get any coins at all from the survival mode?
That kind of messed up.
I'm not the brightest, I guess I'm dead.
I thought I could eat it.
The death match, I didn't even need death match.
It just detached me.
What's the first thing you do when you spawn in?
Spike myself in the chest, okay?
What are these, real?
These are not real fishes, right?
What is this?
These are cartoon characters.
They don't, fish don't look like this.
These are fucking cartoons.
A fish doesn't look like this.
Is this like an Easter egg?
Like, oh look, it's something from Finding Nemo
or something.
Are you dead yet?
They won't die.
Smiling at me and die.
Oh my goodness, why?
Some death match, this turned out to be.
I've taken all the skin off of its back.
I guess I can kill you, microscopic plankton.
I don't know if I'm satisfied with that one.
Where is everybody?
Oh, SpongeBob.
He's farming minus twos.
Yep.
I'm sitting here thinking,
they just kind of do the same thing over and over again.
The same thing forever.
I go, wow, what are these things are dumb?
And then I think about the amount of games
of Hearthstone Battlegrounds I've played
where I pick elemental every time.
And I've done that hundreds, if not thousands of times.
We're not so different.
We're very alike.
All right, well, here's my group.
You should stream it.
No, I won't.
Hearthstone Battlegrounds is one of those games
where that's a game that it's just for me.
Because if I stream it, I'll be embarrassed.
I'll think of every play I did.
And I'll think of the person making fun of me
because they played better than I am at the game
and they know way more.
Okay, I'm back.
We're back and we're bigger.
Still won't die.
0.4 damage.
Let's leave.
How is this death match?
It's me and two of these other bluefish
versus the weird clownfish over there.
And a stingray.
This is not a death match.
This is just, we're just hanging out in different spots.
What's going on over here?
Ow, get it off, get it off me, get it off, get it off me,
get it off, get it off, get it off, get it off,
get it off, get it off, get it off, get it off, get it off,
get it off, get it off, get it off me, get it off me,
get it off me, get it off me.
There are whales, help, help!
Who is this supposed to be?
Oh, who's in there?
They were hiding.
All right, new, we're gonna be Bilbo.
Okay, what is this?
You don't have a gang.
Yeah, I do.
Are we piranhas?
I think we are piranhas.
I'm not in this gang.
Why not?
Are we gonna go swarm something?
Swarm him, swarm him, help me!
I was gonna say he eats, like auto eats dog treats.
This feels kind of unfair
that the gang is just free food.
One more.
That's it, I'm done.
I'm done.
Like how are we supposed to fight against tiger sharks?
How is this fair at all?
This is not a death match, this is bully.
What, how?
What are we supposed to do about this?
Who are they going after?
I need, oh, I got a coin, you're right.
This is cool.
Okay, aren't stingrays like the true neutral of the ocean?
Like nobody cares, right?
Stingrays just kind of float around.
I don't have any coins left.
I thought that stingrays just kind of floated around
and if you just left, sharks eat stingrays?
Don't stingrays just like open their mouths
and eat like the dust of the ocean?
Do crab madness, all right.
What is that?
How do I play with that?
I know I'm breaking the rule.
The rule is we play these 30 to 40 minutes,
maybe one hour tops.
I got interested, I'm sorry.
Oh, you can do that.
There it is.
Whoa, there's more too.
Dunklesaurus?
I wanna play with these.
Oh, really?
That's cool looking.
This game was actually pretty fun.
This game was cool.
All right, well, that's cool.
That was feed and grow fish.
Where are we going from here?
From here, okay, I'm gonna give you some options.
I'm gonna decide which one.
20 minutes till dawn.
I kind of feel like playing that right now.
Oh, I could just do this
and make like a few thousand people leave maybe.
I'm gonna play 20 minutes till dawn.
I'm gonna get it out of my system
and then I'm gonna probably have,
there's probably like three or 4,000 people
are gonna leave after that is what comes after that.
All right, that was fun.
That was feed and grow fish, that was fun.
I don't know how,
what the stage of development on that game is,
but it was fun.