Just because.
Alright, so now you're in the party? Okay.
We're getting playstationed. Yeah, that doesn't matter.
Alright, so, join the party.
Here we are. Okay.
Now play together.
Play together is a feature that makes it easy to play multiple games
with a place to play to power up the AI. Okay.
How do you want to play together? Join game session.
What's the method?
And then join friends game.
Oh, okay, okay. That would make sense.
Alright, so I'm just going to look into
free roam and just try to jump into your game.
That would make sense, wouldn't it?
Oh, okay.
So while we're doing this, have you played through all the single player yet in this?
Uh, I have not.
I'm like 40% of the way through.
Okay, so you're on like chapter 3 then?
Yeah.
I just barely am like into chapter 3, I think.
Yeah, there's a lot left.
I mean, there's a hot air balloon.
Really? There's a hot air balloon?
No, that was you.
Ooh.
There's an Elvis impersonator. I love those things.
That's some of my favorite means of travel.
I'm glad you're bringing it up.
Yeah, I want to know all about that in a couple minutes.
But before we, um,
before we do that, I want to also say there's a game called Rust
that just implemented hot air balloons.
Oh my god, are you serious?
Yeah, swear to god.
Alright, let me, uh, give me one second.
I have to say hello to somebody.
Somebody just knocked on my door.
I gotta say hello to them. Hold on.
Hey, it's you guys! It's my stream!
My stream!
I'm half expecting this to be
It's not.
Uh, oh.
I just want to say hello.
Playing Red Dead Online with Vinnie.
In case you didn't know, just want to make sure you're aware of that.
Hey, how you doing?
It's me, Elvis.
Vinnie Vinesauce.
That was fucking really good.
That was really,
that was really good.
I had to come back and say that.
I'm half expecting this to be a skit.
I had to fucking clown here.
I just sent him home.
Hey, that's Vinnie!
Wait, is that Vinnie?
That's Vinnie! Vinnie!
Hey, I made it!
Let me see your character. What is, what is this character?
My character is loathsome looking.
Let me see yours.
Yeah, I hate my character. At least, at least you're a dude looks like.
You're about to say me.
You're about to say looks like me.
You think that's what I look like?
No. Well hey, I mean, if anything, we could be in a band called The Stooges.
I look like Iggy Pop. You look like the drummer.
So I guess we're good.
Let me add you to a posse.
I think we can do that now.
No, this looks like the taxi driver from The Muppets.
Don't make fun of my face ever again!
Alright, so now we're friends.
That was a friend punch.
So, get your hat.
You look like Solid Snake from the third one.
Squeeze the hop.
Oh yeah, I started the cycle.
I got a posse.
You must be able to pay fee to create a posse.
I must be able to pay fee?
Fuck you, Rockstar.
That's like a funny laugh out loud Rockstar
is taking payment joke, right?
Uh huh. Oh, it's real though.
You're on my all temporary posse.
Alright, so invites.
Your tent has been moved
to Vinesauce's camp.
So we share a camp now.
Yeah.
Let's just do a quick test.
Alright, let me use your hat though.
I'm ready for my picture.
Alright, friendly fire is confirmed off.
Which is good because I didn't know if that was going to work.
But I have to figure out which one of our hats
I like better on my hat.
I hate my hat, so.
Where did you get this thing?
It was a default, like jabroni hat.
So is this one.
Then why is mine dirtier than yours?
I don't know actually. What have you been doing?
What have you been rolling around in the mud?
I think so. Last time I played this, I think that's what I did.
Alright, let's go have fun.
Yeah, I don't know where that is.
So this is a bunch of random missions.
Have you done any online at all?
I've done some of the missions online, yeah.
I've done like a death match.
I've done some of the team based stuff.
It was fun, I enjoyed it. Cool, cool.
Whoa, what was that? Lightning?
There's a lightning mission starting.
We have horses, don't we?
Somewhere we have horses.
My horse is coming from behind here.
This is interesting. Showdown series.
Large match. Oh, this is the stuff I did.
This stuff is pretty fun.
You want to just ride off and like...
You want to just lasso people and torture them?
Oh yeah, that's the first thing you want to do when you get online.
Why don't we torture people?
That sounds like fun.
Like this guy.
He's pulling out his gun. Well, we killed him.
He's dead.
I guess we did torture him.
He was tortured in life.
We got a murder trophy?
I guess that means we're bad.
I was wondering why...
Are you a good guy or are you a bad guy in these games?
I'm more or less a good guy online.
Though I've done some horrendously questionable things.
How about you?
I'm always a good guy.
No matter what.
Any opportunity that presents itself, I always do the right thing.
Is that going to be a problem for this stream?
I'm not sure.
We may have some disagreements.
I fed someone to an alligator.
I hear gunshots.
Okay, that's a good deed.
Just trying to do good deeds over here.
Yeah, that seems like it was a good deed.
For sure.
I just ran past that guy's horse.
That poor, frightened, scared horse.
He just killed its owner.
I was trying to help that guy.
There was flies around his head.
I was trying to get rid of them.
This is like his camp.
Oh man, that guy just good-guided me.
Get that good guy down there.
I got him.
Can you help me?
Yeah, let me find you.
Is this left or dead?
I think so.
You're bleeding out and you're dead.
That guy's whole camp just disappeared.
I'm going to do an emote.
I'm going to wave. I want to be friends.
Are you going to be friends with this guy?
I'm going to try to be friends with him.
I'm going to offer the twig of peace.
What's the emote wheel?
You hold L2, you press R1,
and then you get an emote.
You can do an emote wheel.
Please tell this guy
over the fake voice chat.
Oh, never mind.
What?
I didn't try to do anything.
I think he has his flag up.
I don't think we can do anything to him.
I didn't know that was a thing, but I'm glad it is.
I'm going to farewell handshake this guy.
Never mind.
I tried.
It's just like GTA Online.
Excuse me, partner.
You go.
Over the table, quick.
Don't let him get away.
I don't think we can
do a whole lot with this dude.
I feel like the game has
some safety checks in place.
This dude wants to be peaceful
and we're just trying to run him down with all the horses.
All right.
That was fun.
Yeah, I enjoyed that for all
three seconds.
There's another thing here.
I set a waypoint off.
You can see it, but there seems to be a group of people.
What are you doing?
I just figured I was going to come over here.
I'm not a very good driver.
My horse does not have
the load-bearing potential for this kind of thing, right?
It's all right. Trust me.
If I drive one of these cars,
I'm going into a bench post.
All right. Fair enough.
So, you know,
hot air balloon?
Yeah. Pretty much how it works is
you go up in the air.
And why are these people all ghosts?
I don't know. What is this?
They're made of vapor.
Why are they like Metal Gear Solid
invisible? Why are they able to shoot us?
Hold on. We'll take care of this.
Wait, they're ghosts, but they can shoot us still.
How does it
make any sense? Kill the NPC.
Kill the NPC.
Trying.
Fuck their flight path giver.
Just like the Crossroads back in the early 2000s.
The NPC is the Irishman.
What's his name?
Sean.
I don't understand why we can't interact with these guys.
They can't interact with us.
That seems very unfair.
Oh, this is fair.
Wait, wait. Did you just do that?
Why are ghosts?
No, I didn't do that. The ghost bullies
are taking care of all this.
Alright, well, we found
a strange happening here.
This online doesn't make
a whole lot of sense to me right now.
So they're in a different server and they're able to interact with our server.
I don't know.
There's a
mission here, but we can't do it because
we're in a danger zone or something.
That's too bad. You know what? I was going to
sabotage their vehicles.
Vehicles? Yeah.
I can't even sabotage their vehicles.
Oh, that guy got out of
the phase for a second. No.
I saw that. This is really
Westworld shit.
Yeah, it's kind of not fair.
So hot air balloons, you fill
them with air and they go up into the sky.
Yeah, and then you eat all the passengers to stay alive.
Okay, cool.
Oh, I understand.
Like in a video game.
In one of those video games.
What's a video game where you eat stuff
when you're
traveling?
Do you know? Any idea?
No.
When you fly around...
The Oregon Trail. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Except that one you drive on.
You're on an Oregon
on the trail.
You know,
I don't...
That's fucking disgusting. Why would I ever...
Oh boy, what have I done?
I'm assuming there's a lot
to the story that I'm unaware of.
So I'm just going to let you do you.
No, no, I just...
I...
It's been a while since I was in the air, so...
Jerma, do you have a horse reviver?
I think I just killed my horse.
I killed mine too.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I jumped off the cliff. Did you jump off
this one? Yeah, I jumped off this one.
Oh, now he's...
Oh.
I hope you have horse insurance.
I think I do. Well, whatever. These are like shitty
default free ones.
Yeah, but I named mine Oatmeal.
No, don't shoot oatmeal!
There you go.
If anything, at least turn him into food.
It won't let me stab oatmeal.
Well, now we have to walk.
Alright, well there's a whole gang hideout
over here. You want to go kill some stuff?
Let's go light some people up.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I think I can skin my horse.
Can I skin your horse?
No.
I think these are the bad guys.
So we can take this place out.
That guy was like a pinball machine.
That was pretty good.
That was really good.
Earn, earn. We got you.
That's how a cowboy says yes
just in case you didn't know. They say earn, earn.
Earn, earn?
They say earn, earn.
Earn, earn.
Minister.
No more tears.
I just fucking died.
I was too busy paying attention to earn, earn.
I'm sorry.
The local fucking dentist.
You know what I mean, earn?
I've become a bit of a psychopath
it seems.
Ernest, Ernest.
Alright, I'm coming to rescue you.
Don't worry. Don't worry. If you die I got a horse
reviver. I'll take care of you.
Okay.
It works on people too. Same drug.
There's only a couple dudes left
so we just have to like
kill the main dude who's like on the docks
I guess. Alright, so you can stab him a hundred times.
Watch this.
Alright, we got him.
Fuck him up.
Ooh, that was, okay.
He's in the water now.
So we split every piece of treasure
every treasure chest we find, it's fifty-fifty, right?
Yes.
This we do.
Alright, come watch me stab this guy.
Oh, you're fighting the main guy. I'm fighting like his
I'm fighting his uncle out here.
I just slit his throat.
You got the guy with lumbago?
Alright. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't touch anything.
How many hats did he have?
He only had one and it says you cannot store this hat.
Well, we're gonna have to cut it in half.
Because that's the only way that's fair.
It says here you can get your free Arabian
horse from the strawberry stables.
Someone in chat said so. If you want to
get a non-shitty horse in a bit
maybe that'll be a good thing to do on stream.
That'll be a good fun thing to do.
Is there any
loot box in here
or something? There's a cabinet.
It costs three rock star gold to open, yeah.
Once purchased, looted,
or crafted consumables. It's so dark over here.
Oh, I got a guy.
There's a guy in there.
Where'd you get that guy from?
He was in the cabinet.
I guess we just get to take this guy.
Maybe we can sell him somewhere?
Pretty sure we can do that.
Let's do that.
I dropped him in the water and
you have to bring him to the iPhone store.
The water damage is like
you just can't fucking recover it.
I just got disconnected.
And just like that
you're gone.
Did you get DC'd?
I don't know if I got DC'd
but I can't loot anybody right now.
The cycle never ends.
You would think
Vegas would have good internet.
I got
a greater internet at the moment.
For some reason my connection to rock star
I don't know why.
This is what was happening to me before too.
Are you still in the game?
I'm still in game.
Let me know when you're back online.
I can invite you.
What the...
Can I swear?
I swear a little.
Shit.
What the shit?
I'm sorry.
By rights we shouldn't even be friends.
I'm a New York Yankees guy.
What?
I can't believe you
just fucking said that.
The truth is though
I don't really care.
I was told I was a Yankees fan when I was a child.
I was told
I was a Yankees fan.
I was told that I was.
You know
watched a couple games here and there.
I'm supposed to be angry at you
according to the laws of thermodynamics.
I mean that's
okay.
Being a Yankee fan
obviously
there's something wrong with you.
Right, of course there is.
If you go to the doctor
and you tell the doctor
when they do a physical exam
one of the first things they have to ask you is
still a baseball fan?
Yeah, yeah I am.
Yankees? Red Sox? Which one?
Because it's very important.
You get a CT scan for that.
They have to check your whole body
and make sure it's not like an ulcer
or something. That could be what's causing it.
I think
it's the Lumbego again though.
Pretty sure.
What is Lumbego?
So the uncle character in this game
says that he has a killer case of Lumbego
and apparently what that is
is just his lower back hurts.
So it's his lower back pain.
I like to blame a lot of my failings
on Lumbego these days.
Am I in your game?
I might even just be in your game.
Am I in here?
Am I with you?
No, I'm sending you another invite.
Doesn't look like you're in here.
Oh god, this guy is going to kill me.
I hope I can portal out of here.
Lethal hog. Processing invite.
Okay, thank god.
This guy in his whole posse
was medicinally walking around me
with their guns out.
Just portal to it out of the way.
Were they ghosts?
No, they were just bandits.
Okay, because I think that might be
a glimpse at the DLC.
Ghost cowboys. We had zombies in the
previous game and it'll just be ghosts this time around.
I wonder what their plan is.
Do they have no plan at all?
Think?
Yeah, they have a plan. The plan is to continue
implementing weapons and cosmetic items
and selling gold bars
that you can then buy them with.
Did you know that
one of the dudes at Rockstar
or was it Take Two or something
said that they didn't feel GTA Online was monetized
enough? Wait, is that for real?
Yeah, apparently. Somebody actually said that?
Yeah.
And I like Rockstar.
And they're really good to me. And I think
that that's ridiculous. That was a highly
monetized game. What the?
I think I'm in your game.
But I don't think I'm in your posse. Is this you up here?
Hold on. I don't know. Let me just
make sure.
Strauss said that. There you go.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm right next to you. Telling that there's a character
that is a loan shark in this game
called Strauss.
Just want to make sure he was dead.
Hey.
Thank you.
Wasn't there
an Activision
executive that said they wished they
could sell a controller that was like $150
or if they
could sell their games for like double, they would do it
if they could get away with it or something.
I think so. Yeah, I seem to remember.
I don't know for sure, but that sounds familiar.
That was a couple years ago, no? Yeah.
Something ridiculous like that.
It's just it's a gift
that keeps on giving. It really is.
All right.
I'm trying to join your posse.
I got you the invite now.
There's someone mad at me.
So if someone appears over the ridge and tries to shoot
us, then
that's my fault.
All right. So where's this free horse?
Is that your horse?
Yeah, it is. I guess it is now.
I guess it is yours now.
So Valentine,
I'll set a waypoint. Set a waypoint for us.
And by the way, there
is- Wait, wait. Valentine chat?
Oh, okay.
There's like a 90 to 95 percent
chance that I'm going to dump us.
What's that?
Is that the guy that was trying to fight you?
That's my horse.
Why was it just angry? It just had like a
blip on the screen. Really?
Yeah, it was a red blip. No, I don't
know. That was weird.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Watch this, they're going to go
bowling. They're fast
though. These horses are real fucking
shitty. These pins.
So Jeremy, are you going to Pax East
this year, even though you now live halfway across
the country? More than halfway.
I am not.
Not going to Pax East this year.
Unfortunately. I had to
check. I just wanted to know. Are you chasing after
this guy? No, I'm just
trying to head to Valentine.
Yeah, not this year.
Vinny, are you going to Pax East?
I will be there in body
but not in spirit.
So no.
Because your spirit
is what controls the body. The body is just a
big case.
Yeah, it's like
a meat machine.
So you're sending your horse hair cooler master
to Pax.
That's correct.
I need a new keyboard for this
fucking game.
And I need some more memory because, man, I am
running out.
I've got to learn how to laugh without being a disgusting
human being.
Me just laughing right there.
What was my horse doing?
What the fuck?
He just ran over my
head.
That was good. Keep it up.
I need to feed him.
Oh, carrots.
Where's the horse food? Oh, that's right.
I can feed him my clothes.
I barely have anything to feed this fucking
thing.
Are you trying to shoot that guy? Yeah, I tried.
But yeah, what I'm saying is
people must hate
talking to me. Okay, so let me ask
you something. We like hung out.
We hung out in person.
In person.
When I like laughed at something, did I just
like sprinkle or spit in
your face? No. Okay.
I don't know what it is about sitting here, but every time I laugh, I just like
droplets of water just all over my
screen. I'm not even sipping anything.
I don't understand how.
You know, I have a weird
confession to make. Okay.
So my Wii U gamepad, the screen
is like
is kind of gross. That's like
four years of streaming it and speaking
in front of it. And I thought I didn't
spit when I spoke or laugh.
I was clearly extremely
mistaken. So I think this is just being
a human. This is just faulty hardware.
Something that we all share.
No, I think you're honest in there because
it's gonna happen again. Don't you do it.
Okay, we're fine. This horse
sucks. I'd rather just ride on yours.
You can if you want. My
oatmeal is a sturdy horse
firm, I guess. But also the
frame rates are dipping. Are you getting like weird frame rates?
Oh yeah, it's bad. It's like
20 frames a second. Yeah, what's
going on? I feel like I'm playing Ocarina of Time again.
Uh, but I think
that's just like a hill. Let me like transfer.
Let me transfer.
I think that's just a
almost a tree.
Just hang on a minute, okay? Yeah. Where's your horse?
Take care of it.
Wait, you're killing him. You just killed my horse?
No, no, I
wouldn't let me. We're friends.
Tidge wouldn't let me. Yeah,
I tried.
But you haven't noticed that, I don't know, do you have like an iPad
or anything? I don't have
any, um, no.
Even like the Switch or the Wii U,
you're right there, but for some
reason, it's the most embarrassing thing in the world.
Even your phone too. If somebody
ever is like, hey, can I use your phone?
It's just like, oh fuck, and you look at it and
it's just like, oh, and I was like, I was like shitting and like
using this. I gotta like wipe it off. I gotta like
pissing and
There's particles.
There's particles, whether you want there to be or not,
there's particles. And nobody wants, nobody
wants you to, if there's a screen involved,
you never want
someone to touch it or look at it.
Anytime somebody wants to, oh, can I use your iPad
for a second? Well, that person didn't
let us use their iPad.
Fuck. Maybe there are horses
better. I can't steal it.
We can't take it?
Oh, hey.
Calm it down,
calm down, calm down, calm down.
Alright, let's get out of here before they get mad at us.
No, no, I'm talking about the horse. I calmed the horse down. This thing is cool.
We need to take this thing.
I don't think we can. I think it's, it's got a
saddle on it. That thing tried to kick you
by the way.
Well, that person's head is still bleeding.
I can't wait to get our cool, oh, there they are,
they're there. Alright,
line it up. I'm jumping to the horse.
Not even necessary.
Nope, none of this
is necessary. I told you, I'm not a good guy.
I am morally as
gray as you can get. This is your, this is
good guy, right?
I'm a good guy, yeah. No, that's what,
good, we,
what's bad about it?
They are bad. We're killing the bad guys.
That's what I'm saying. So,
oh, oh, oh, here, in regards to the
discussion that we just had about touchscreens,
did you know that they did,
I don't know who they is,
but they did some tests
on McDonald's touchscreens
for ordering, and they determined that
there is poo on every one of the ones
that they tested. Oh,
that's, that's fucking
disgusting.
Nice jump, by the way.
Yeah. I'm
sorry, man, but I'm of the opinion, that doesn't really
gross me out because I feel like there's poo
everywhere. Yeah, there is poo
everywhere. As Bruce Willis once said, there's always
a little shit in the meat. I mean, like
there's probably, there's probably shit on your hands
right now. Yeah.
No, I wouldn't be surprised. I mean, you know, little
microbes.
I mean, if you test the oxygen around you, it's
probably like point one percent poo.
And you just look down and it's like, oh my
god. My hands
are covered in shit. I look
down and my controller is just filled
with turds.
That would be disgusting. I'm getting
someone just said, Vinnie, I'm getting sick.
I'm sorry, chat member. You didn't deserve that.
How much vomit
particulates do you believe are floating
around at any given moment? Well,
to be, I'll be completely honest, at least
a few dozen here because I, when you said you were a
Yankees fan, I threw up into my glass. So
Oh, good point. That did happen.
How did you feel about
I mean, are you, I don't know, I don't remember
if we talked about this when we were in Boston, but are
you a big enough baseball fan to have really felt
like a dopamine hit when
they won? Um, no.
Because I took the ultimate
drug in 2004. Jesus.
Jesus.
I found Jesus.
Oh, no, really?
What did you hit?
When the Red Sox won the World Series for the first
time in like a hundred years. Oh, okay.
That was 2004 was like the magical
year and no other drug could ever
come close.
2007 was pretty good too because
one of my favorite players was on the
World Series with 2007 and
you know, that team
I think was a really great team. But then
2013, it was like, oh, okay.
Man, this is
Red Sox are so good this third time
in like less than 10 years.
And then this last one, it's like the best team they've ever
had in history of the history of the entire
franchise. And it's like, yeah.
Man, I wish I could get that 2004
drug bill.
Right, right. It just gets less. It's like
when the Yankees won a bunch in
a row in the
late 90s and it was just getting boring.
And then when they didn't win, it was like, well, fuck, I wanted a day
off from school.
It wasn't even like special anymore. It was just
where's my day off? Because they were giving us a day off when the Yankees
won. Really?
Yeah, they did. For the parade.
You could choose not to go and they wouldn't be upset.
Wow.
Uh huh. So where's our free horse?
Um, hey chat.
Was that a jape?
Did you guys, uh...
Were you just joking with us the whole time, huh?
No. The free horse is in strawberry.
Jeremy, I have a
I have a confession. What is it?
I took us to the wrong town. Oh.
It's okay.
Because I go to the wrong town literally
every time I play the game. So.
Okay. Um, we have to go to strawberry.
Wait, wait, can we take a, um,
take a fast travel? I think it costs money.
What's this horse? Did I get a...
Oh, this is the horse that I got from... Okay, yeah.
So this is my actual horse.
There's one with the frame rates in multiplayer.
Jesus. Yeah, they're pretty bad.
Um, I'm gonna
attempt to do the stagecoach and see how long that takes.
And how much money
it costs to fast travel. Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's probably a good idea.
It's under buy horses superior.
But it's only in strawberry. Only in
strawberry. How far away is that from here?
That's not that far. It's not too bad.
It's not terrible. Vinny, no. Hang on.
Wait, wait, wait. Only strawberry.
No. In any stables. Only strawberry.
Any stable. Only
strawberry. I hate life sometimes.
Okay, I'm gonna go back to this and I'm gonna let you know.
Eat the raspberries, Vinny.
That's what they say.
Eat those raspberries. Don't eat them.
They're not poisonous. Those raspberries
in front of you are not poisonous. Yes, they are.
They're poisonous. Like,
I've talked about this on my stream before, but let me
see how you feel about this.
If you were in a room and
there were a hundred people
outside, like we're talking like a two-way
mirror, like glass, right? You're sitting in like
a interrogation room.
And a guy comes in and puts
berries down in front of you.
They're like
red. Just red berries on the little
plate and he leaves the room. Are you going to eat
them if you hear fifty
percent of the people screaming, don't eat those.
They're poisonous from the other room.
Or eat them. They'll give you superpowers. Don't listen
to them. What are you gonna do? Are you gonna eat them?
How depressed am I before I enter this room?
Today was a great day.
Like, today was a fantastic day.
One of the best you probably had all week.
Did Smash come out yet?
Yeah, Smash came out.
And Gino got confirmed for DLC.
Okay, I won't eat the berries then. You won't eat them?
Alright. No. Alright, so when you push that
away, half of the people in the other room
are screaming at you.
And they're very upset with you. And like your
day gets worse because as you're walking out
there's like drinks are getting thrown at you.
There's like fruits that are flying by your head.
Like, you should have eaten yours, you fucking idiot.
And like somebody drives by and throws like a large soda at you.
God, this is tough. What would
you do?
I wouldn't do it. No, I don't think so.
I mean, super powers sound cool
and everything, but isn't God much
more cooler?
Alright, I'm gonna sell oatmeal. Goodbye oatmeal.
Why are you selling your
horse? I liked oatmeal because
it was a cool name, but someone else can have oatmeal.
There's a free horse in here, dude. There's a free horse in there?
Yeah, there's a free horse.
Did you just like ram
into the fucking stables at full speed?
Because I saw that on the
cutscene.
Alright, go to buy horse,
go to superior at the bottom,
Arabian, red chestnut,
and you can claim a free
horse. Your stable is full?
Yeah, you gotta sell your other horse.
How much did you get for selling that one?
Next to nothing.
My horse's name is Sean.
Alright, sorry.
Someone said name it Bagel.
Name it Nut. Oh, that's a good
idea. I'll name it Nut. People are gonna be so upset
I'm about to sell this horse.
Yeah, my audience was not happy.
Oh, by the way,
why don't we do a quick plug? I want to plug your
stream. If anyone wants to see what's going on, or
do like a multi-stream and watch Jerma
stream too, you can go to Twitch.tv
slash Jerma.
That's good enough.
They'll find me. Sure. Twitch.tv
slash Jerma. Yeah, it's
J-H-E-R-R-H-H-H.
Twitch.tv slash.
Because there's numbers, right? At the end.
Yeah, I'm one of those idiots that has numbers.
Jerma985, J-H-E-R-M-A-985.
And if anybody over here that wants to go check out
Vinnie. Yeah, you
could go to Twitch.tv
slash. Yeah.
This is like four H's.
Vine. Vine
sauce. That is correct.
You know, multi-stream us.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, there's
gonna be a way to do that natively
soon enough, like Twitch is implemented
or they're working on implementing a way to do that.
So that way
you can just enjoy other
streamers without having to go to like a multi-stream website.
So I think that's kind of cool.
Yeah. That's kind of, that's very
necessary. Yeah. I think it's
a great idea. I'm surprised it hasn't happened sooner.
There we go. Alright, so I got my free
horse. Thank God. There's
a couple free saddles available.
Yeah. I'm looking
at some of the stuff right now. 80
bucks. How are you ever gonna get like
more than five gold bars in this game?
How is that impossible?
Oh, I know how it's possible.
There was a big drama post about how
someone was like, they did the math and to earn
enough money to buy another
stable or like, you know, a horse.
A good horse. They said it was something
like 80 hours.
And then that was disproven. I mean, they got the
math wrong and it was like seven hours instead.
Oh, I don't want to
cause you any alarm here.
But horse insurance
for this horse is five gold bars
that I don't have. Found out that the
horses come back no matter what. The insurance
just makes them more healthy. Oh,
okay. So you can't
if you have an owned horse and multiplayer,
you're good. Okay, that's good.
But yeah, you definitely
want to get another saddle because
there's some really good ones.
So what you do is go to empty slot,
attack one of them, and then
special. Oh, you got it? Yeah, I got one.
Okay, cool. I don't know why these are free.
Are these all for free?
I mean, I can't buy them though. Some of them.
Oh, some of them. Did you get the couple
free ones or? This one's 39.
Which one is the free one? This one's 67.
It should just be 00.
Oh, I doubt it's special. Okay, I see.
Alligator Ranch. Yeah, I'll get this one.
The very last one at the end is really
good. Let's see. Rattlesnake.
Some of them are pretty cool. Oh,
quick recommendation while we're here.
I'd recommend getting some provisions
for your horse so they can eat and not die.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Yeah, and maybe a horse reviver too.
A little expensive, but it's probably
worth it. So it's services, right?
Well, not services. Under
provisions. How much is it? Yeah.
That's a lot of money. Well, the horse reviver's a lot
of money, but the hay is a quarter,
so that's not too bad, and it's... I'm just gonna buy
shit right now. Hey, what about a sugar
cube? You gonna get a couple of those? I'm gonna
get some beets from Shroot Farms, but
yeah, I'm gonna get some sugar cube. I got a horse
reviver, I got some food. You know, by doing this,
we're never gonna afford new weapons.
Never. I've come to
terms with the fact that it's just gonna be
I'm gonna use the pea shooter with the BB gun.
Yeah. Me too.
Should we get our horses? Sorry, I had some
peanut butter. Like a horse would.
That's what they used to feed Mr.
Ed to make it look like he was talking.
The way you said
that too, like the way your voice managed to squeak
out that sentence, it sounded like Mr. Ed a little bit
gush-poo-poo.
So, good job.
I didn't even... That show sucks!
Yeah, I hated Mr. Ed.
That horse scared the fuck out of me.
Why does it talk? I don't like it.
Why didn't anybody try to breed it?
You could have a bunch of... You could start an entire
new horse...
Sub-species. Yeah.
We could have intelligent horses
all talking. Sell them.
They would be so happy. We could...
Horses that just love to sit around and eat hay, right?
Yeah. That's all they do.
Just put a headset on, yeah.
Put a headset on them and they could be like
telemarketers while they're just hanging out.
Where are we going? That's right!
You give them jobs again. Like, because they don't have
as many jobs these days like they used to back in the
old west and, you know, before that, of course.
But I think, yeah, make them telemarketers.
Hello! How can I help you?
They would be so happy.
They would get paid. They would get paid.
Of course we would pay them. Of course.
Fucking horse cars. Of course.
Where are we going? I don't know.
Do you want to kill some things?
Yeah, let's go...
In the context of this video game, yes.
It's out of context.
Hey, you want to go kill some stuff? Yeah!
Yeah, we don't want to do that.
I want to go run over some rabbits.
I can start up a quick join
and we can do a mission.
We can do a story mission or we can do like a
showdown mission.
Let's do a showdown mission.
Why not?
Showdown series. You'll also join as a member of their posse.
Okay, cool. It looks like we're going.
So how's the weather over there, man?
It's beautiful. Do you miss Boston weather?
Not at all.
This is snow season here
for Boston, so
I am absolutely ecstatic that
it's like 50 degrees
every day. It drops down overnight
because it's obviously the desert, so it drops down to like
low 40s.
So it gets cold, but
the days are great.
He's literally talking about
the weather.
Oh god, I just got booted.
Wait, you got booted?
Really? Yeah.
Oh, okay. Why does this game
hate me so much?
I'll just quit out.
I don't know why this game hates me so much.
What's wrong with the weather?
I'll just say this. Lately it's been pretty cold
here, but
considered at times in my life
moving to a place where I don't
have to deal with like
bone chill.
The one thing that I will say
is going to the west coast
is, I mean
there are pros and cons everywhere. I mean I miss Boston
all the time. Yeah.
But you miss bagels. Yeah.
You bet your ass I do.
I miss the bagels. I miss the
sub sandwiches, like the steak and cheese subs.
I miss those.
Yeah. I would miss those too.
I miss the pizza. Ah, that's
right. Do you find any good pizza?
Yeah, I mean there's some decent pizza places
out here, but not like there are in New York
obviously. Okay, I'm
going to try to invite you again. Yeah,
I don't know why
because
every time it kicks me out it says, there's a problem
with the Rockstar servers. It doesn't
like say, you've been disconnected because your computer
sucks. It's, you've been
disconnected but our servers are a problem.
That's like what the error code is. At least
they're honest about it. I don't know
though, I feel like, I don't
know who this is. Who the fuck is this?
I think I just,
all right. All right.
I'm ready for an invite.
Here it is. Hey, coming
to you. Hey.
Hey.
I've been watching The Office like
a dumbass lately. I don't know why. It's a good show.
There's an episode.
It's a good show. I don't know. It's just it was something to watch
and there's an episode where in the beginning
it was cold open.
We talked about the weather and now I'm talking about
I'm describing episodes of The Office.
Your audience is going to be like, can you stop
streaming with this guy?
This guy sucks. He can't even
stay connected to Rockstar's video game
servers and he's talking about the weather.
Anyway, there's an episode
where they go A and I'm going to stop
there. It's good enough.
There's an episode where they go A.
Yeah, they go A.
Here, I'll invite you again.
We have another problem at this point.
I'll just like watch you stream.
No, I mean, I'm down to
try a couple more matches at least.
It's worth a shot.
I think we could have some fun if it
just was stable. I know, I know. I don't understand.
I've gotten
disconnected like three or four times when I stream this too.
But it happens.
Usually from random matches.
I don't understand.
What's the weather like on The Office?
What's the weather like?
Well,
there's an episode where they go A.
I can answer that
because it was filmed in
California and they try to make it look
like Scranton, Pennsylvania, so it's snowy.
But it's really not.
Well,
I got booted again.
Super cool.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. But you're still
like, you haven't had any problems streaming.
Oh, no, not at all. I've got no drop frames at all.
It's something
to do with where I'm coming from.
Why does Rockstar not want to
acknowledge Las Vegas?
Maybe they don't. I don't understand.
No, I'm not deleting the game.
Yeah, I don't know. It's something to do with
how they connect. I figured
it was a problem from three days ago because it was the
first day or two of the beta, but
it looks like it's kind of just a server routing
or server problem
with Rockstar. And
specifically either Las Vegas
servers or
California servers because, I mean, technically
I'm on the West Coast.
Well, maybe they'll get that sorted out in a couple days.
That's what I was hoping for
three days ago.
Yeah, sorry. Sorry this is kind of
impeding on everything.
That's fine. I mean, I'm still shooting people in the
face. It's not a big deal. But I would prefer
to shoot people in the face with you in an
actual match. That would be better.
I'll invite you again.
Let's try again. Yeah, let's try again.
Even though it says I'm on a mission.
Maybe they just hate you.
I don't know, maybe. I tried restarting
it. Moving to the country,
gonna eat myself some
peaches. Moving
to the country, gonna eat
me a lot of peaches.
Look out!
Look out, man!
Peaches come
in a can. They was put
there by a man.
I haven't heard that in a long time. Holy shit.
Yeah, that was
for you. I figured you might know about that. That was
great. Yeah.
I feel like, I feel really good
right now. I was a little sad
about like the Rockstar server issue here, but
I feel fantastic.
Yeah, that just takes
the power of song. That's all it takes.
Alright, here we go.
Don't do it, Rockstar. I know
you want to. Look at them.
Look at them do it. Look at how much they want.
Okay. I'm ready
for an invite.
And this will be the last time because it's going to stay
on. I'm not going to get disconnected from
Rockstar servers. The problem is
I can't actually invite you now because I'm in a mission.
Supposedly. Maybe for the better
so I can stay connected for a minute.
That's what you think. I know.
Let me try...
Explain to me what
you were just doing. Because
you were doing like a randomized Ocarina
of Time? Yeah.
So there's a randomizer
and you can assign a bunch of different
options. It's a really customizable randomizer.
And
all you have to do is
every chest...
Wow, I did what you did earlier.
Every treasure chest.
Oh, Jesus.
Good luck saying it the right way ever again.
Every treasure chest
has randomized content
except for a couple. And
you can find medallions, you can find items,
you can find swords, you can find all kinds of crazy shit.
Really? And essentially
you have to get the six medallions
and they could be anywhere. And then you can fight
Ganon. And you can
make it really hard for yourself
or you can make it a lot easier for yourself.
Like, for example, I started the game
Kakariko Village was open.
I started the game where
Kokiri Forest was open so I could just leave
and go to the world map anytime. Oh, really?
So, but yeah,
I mean, it's kind of cool because you could just play the game
in like six or seven hours
if you're lucky and you know what you're doing.
So could you get everything in the first six
chests of the game?
I got a hookshot in the first chest.
Wow. That's cool.
And you can get some, I got a
medallion real early. You can get really broken
like stuff early on
or you can get five blue rupees.
Five rupees every time.
Which is the worst thing ever.
Yeah, that's like
what is it, green rupee the lowest?
Mhm.
But it's a really fun thing.
I love it. I'm really enjoying it.
No, it seemed cool. It seemed really cool
from what I saw.
You've never done a randomizer stream?
Never. I mean, the only randomizer
I've ever heard of or ever done was something like
Team Fortress
and that just randomizes loadouts, not like
randomizing the whole game essentially. Oh, I see.
I gotcha. So I'm just
kind of, I'm just running until my character
dies.
Is that possible?
You need to feed the character eventually.
Hey chat, does anyone know how to
abandon this stupid mailbag quest?
Oh yeah, I got stuck in
the mail room by the way. You gotta be
careful with that mail door.
Shoot yourself in the head. Okay, now
the timer ran out. Okay, so now I can probably
invite you.
Yes, the mail door.
The door to the mail room. The mail door.
I got trapped in there. Remember when I was
breaking windows? Did someone not
understand? They were like, what are you talking about, Jerma?
They were saying like M-A-L-E, like
mail door. Oh.
Okay.
You alright? You okay?
What happened?
Tell me in minute detail.
I got shot in the head.
Hey, can you invite me?
I see.
Because my invite thing is totally
blocked out for some reason.
Mine is too.
You invites and updates.
Can I?
Yeah, I can't invite you either.
It's blocked out.
Rockstar, what the heck are you doing here?
I guess I'll just die.
Are we in the same game?
I'm playing Red Dead Redemption 3.
Well, because
if we're in the same lobby,
I don't think so.
No, because I can't. No, I don't think so either.
Because I can't even get you into my posse.
R1 on the player list.
Apparently
you're not even online.
Yeah, apparently.
Go to your friends tabs or go to players and hit R1.
And does it say I'm like
online?
I'm just eating baked beans.
You know what's a cool thing to do as a streamer I found out
I've learned over the years?
Eat food while you're streaming.
I can't
do that, man.
It's either the best thing for some
people and they love it.
Or it's like they'll watch
the stream specifically because it's social eating.
Yeah, I've heard of that.
They hate the way it sounds, yeah.
I've heard of like the social eating thing, but not just like
oh, hey guys, just gonna take a break from Red Dead
and eat a plate of spaghetti. Hold on.
I couldn't do it. I don't want people
to look at me when I'm eating.
Yeah, don't fucking look at me is what I say.
I don't?
When I go to dinner, out with friends
or family and the food comes out,
I hate the fact that everyone's just
able to look at me just across the table.
Fuck, you know what?
Let's go off on this. Fuck the whole table
scenario that we have here in the United States.
Somebody's sitting across from you.
They're always looking at you and they're staring at your eyes
like you do the weird eye contact when you both take a huge
bite and you're like, oh, whoops.
Just line us up on the
other side so it's just a giant bench
and no one's across
from you. Everyone just sits and you can fit so many
more people. Like Thanksgiving, except
for the fact that you don't have to sit across from anybody.
That's like the Last Supper you mean, right?
What the fuck are you doing here?
How did you get in here? How did you get in here?
No, no, no. Get off me.
Get off me.
Get your hands in the air. How did you find me?
I don't even understand how
you got in here.
I went into
the menus and I found you.
Easy, easy.
Watch the edge.
Oh my god, you're choking me to death.
Oh shit, I didn't mean to do that.
Oh, that's a shame.
No, stay right there.
I want to take a picture of you.
I want to get like a good photo of you.
By the way, I'm the camera.
Okay.
I lived. I somehow lived.
Oh, look who I've got.
Hey, come on down here.
Come retrieve your body. Who's this?
Oh, that's me. Was that me?
Yeah, I threw you down there.
What the fuck? Hold on a minute.
I know what we're going to do today.
Okay, we're going to make
a bunch of dead bodies of ourselves
on this ledge.
It really will be Westworld then.
I just invited you to a posse though.
Oh, did you?
I don't see any invites.
I think I just kicked the muskrat.
How come I don't have any invites from you?
Because this fucking
service is so fucking broken.
I'm gone.
Here's the wild thing.
This is worse than before. This is worse than it was
three days ago.
Did you get disconnected again?
Yeah, this is worse than it was three days ago.
Damn.
There's something wrong with
what Rockstar servers on the East Coast,
West Coast specifically, has to be.
I'm sure it's something.
Because I have a
stable connection everywhere.
Okay, this is weird.
I'm lagging too because my character is doing the
whistling face, but there are no whistles coming out of it.
He says he doesn't eat on stream, but
there was a time you shoved a bunch of taquitos
into your mouth or something.
The character is going
meme-y.
I'm all lagged out.
Did you eat like taquitos
on stream?
They said you don't
eat on stream, but you ate a
shitload of taquitos when you were shitfaced or something.
What?
Oh, they're talking about
me.
Oh, me.
You don't remember this.
I guess you were shitfaced.
When did I eat taquitos?
What the fuck are you guys talking about?
I ate testiculitos.
Vdub gave me some.
What?
What the fuck?
I have a rival as a pro Call of Duty player
named Vdub.
He's got a thing called testiculitos.
It's a long story.
Testiculitos.
Okay, is your invite
grayed out?
Oh yeah, yes it is.
So, I don't know, maybe there's just a problem again
and we picked the great, perfect day
three days later where it just doesn't work
again.
I mean, I know how I joined your game before.
I went into the friends menu, I went to your profile
and then I clicked join, so I'm going to do that again
and see if that works.
Yeah, I don't understand, man. I wish I knew.
Oh, there's tobacco here.
I was wasted and
Kim brought me
taquitos.
That didn't happen. I've never had a taquito before
in my life.
What did you just crack open?
Is it like a coarse light?
No, it was gum, dude.
I got disconnected again.
Is there something else we can do?
I feel like I've like torn
you away from what you were doing and it's like,
hey, it's been an hour and everything's just shot.
This was the plan from the beginning.
This is not at all
disrupting me or my streaming.
Well, I mean, I kind of have to go soon anyway,
so this isn't really that big of a deal. It's just a shame
that this doesn't work because I was having fun.
Yeah, I really want to play it.
Just watch you play. We're going to
live vicariously through you.
Yeah, but even if you do watch me play, I'm going to get
disconnected too. I've been getting disconnected.
Alert, you have been disconnected
from Red Dead Online due to a fault on
Rockstar Game Services.
When is the beta supposed to be done?
A year.
Alert. Hey, did you
get the alert? I got an alert.
Yep. I got it on my cell phone.
Hey, please ping me.
Please send me a text every time that
the servers go down. By the way,
I think Kraken was playing this not too long ago,
so maybe we can get the old crew
back together. Yeah, I'd
love to actually play this because what's here would
be fun. Yeah.
Maybe not, you know, when the game
is still broken, but when it's fixed,
we can
bug Kraken. Yeah, how many people
can you have in like a squad?
I think four.
Four for a non-paid posse.
You have to pay,
you have to actually pay for it
with like in-game money.
That's kind of weird. That's cool.
Yeah. What about
Critical? Critical is like, he's a bigger
YouTuber slash street, like
I guess more YouTuber, but he's like such a big
YouTuber. I always feel bad bothering him. I don't know.
It's hard to explain.
I would like to get Critical involved.
He's not a very proactive person
when it comes to stuff like this.
He threw
cards at me the other day, and
I was screaming at him and stuff. So yeah,
maybe he'll play. You think he would be
down? Maybe, yeah.
I'll give him a shout. I was going to talk to him anyways.
So how
about we make a plan without
people expecting it to be
like Word of God, that it's going
to happen 100%. But when this
game gets fixed, and when
we can play with a stable connection,
me, you, Criken,
Critical will try to get like a thing going.
Oh, sick! That sounds
good. Cool.
So,
I think,
I don't know what your plan is. Are you going to just
take off? What, tonight?
Like right now. Like
right now? I'm going to invite you one more time because
I think the server's restarted. Oh, the server's
restarted? Yeah, maybe.
Okay. Somebody said,
oh no, it's the end of the stream voice.
Mine? No, I like mine.
Like, all right, do you do a thing when you
stream, when like, okay, let's say you've been streaming for
you know, six, seven, four,
whatever, five. You're getting a little tired.
Do you do like a, okay,
so, do you do like a, I'm going to
end the stream voice? Yep.
Yeah. I think so.
I didn't just do it right there.
Are you in game? I'm loading in
right now. Okay, when, okay, let me know
when you, when you load it in because it says
it wants me to invite, um,
it wants to invite me to watch
your stream. It wants to invite
you to watch my stream? To watch your
gameplay, yes. Oh, you're going to come watch
my gameplay? That's what it wants, yeah.
Share play? Yeah,
it's the end of the phone call voice.
Yeah, that's, when you
talk to somebody on the phone. And you're
like, oh, all right. Yeah,
that's how people end conversations.
You add some inflection to let people know
that, hey, this is like, the conversation
is going to be over here in a minute.
My, my, like, here's mine.
All right. Yeah.
All right.
All right. And then it goes up real
high. All right. Yep.
Mine is usually,
it starts with, okay, so,
or it's, but,
yeah. Okay, so, I
think. How about cool?
You're doing one of the cool.
I don't know if I like cool, because
cool kind of sounds like I'm not interested in
conversation, like a cool, all
right, I gotta go. It's like, you didn't think that was cool.
If you thought that was cool, you'd just stick around a little bit longer, right?
Yeah, it's a little passive
aggressive. Yeah. I think
all right works, because all right's like, all right, like, it's over.
All right. How's
the weather on your phone, by the way?
My phone? It's pretty good.
Yep. All right.
All right.
My invites are grayed out.
There we go. I gotcha. Okay, the invites are still
grayed out, but I can invite you to the posse. We're in the same
server. Oh. All right.
Come find me. Come find me, and
come take a picture with me.
Okay. Well, I think we should try to do,
while we're in a server together, we should try to do, like,
an actual, like,
fight match. Yeah.
Okay. So it starts now,
then. I think we have to be in the posse.
Oh, okay. I thought
you meant, like, you and me are just gonna fight.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I was, I was gonna say
we could do a, like,
you know, like a team death match thing.
Oh, I actually tried to load, yeah, I tried to load into one.
No, that, apparently
the weather is a little too harsh on these, yeah,
I'm disconnected.
No shit already? No shit, yep.
Already, this is way,
we at least, three days ago, we could
play for at least 20, 30 minutes
before it would do this, so. It's a shame.
This is a shame. Well, I mean, this is not, this is
not a bother to me. I want you to know
that this is also affecting me.
That's okay, it's affecting me too.
Okay. I think, let's just wait
a little bit, wait a couple days, and then we'll try
again. That sounds good to me. I wanna, I wanna
actually play this with you, but yeah, it's a
shame that this isn't happening.
It is a shame, but it's alright. It happens.
Nothing to do about it.
What are you gonna, what are you gonna cry, just cry over
spell servers? I can jump off a cliff.
Oh, I just did that.
I love how that's both the go-to
thing, whatever.
Sleep off.
You can't cry, you can't cry over
spilled servers. No, you can't.
I'm just gonna go and do
like a showdown match.
You know, I have like another
10, 20 minutes that I'm gonna play this, so
may as well play.
Oh shit, someone got a jump. Can you
explain, is it, it's
jup or jump?
It is, it is
Jupiter, jup.
Okay, because I've been saying, I think the chat tricked me into
saying jup. They did. I was like, yeah, but it's Jupiter.
It's pronounced jup. Yeah, they lied to you.
They were like, nah, bro. Yeah, figures.
I mean, I've said, I've clarified
it at least a hundred times. It is
Jupiter, the planet is Jupiter, it's not Jupiter.
Oh yeah, there's the moon, there's
the, oh, there's, there's the mon.
There's Murs.
What's back there, oh, that's Venus.
What else? Oh, Jupiter.
Oh, of course. Behind that you got
Plateau, yeah.
Plateau is my favorite, yeah.
So, can I ask you why it
exists? Because it's become a bit of
a local chat, like a lot of your memes have spilled
over into my life. I want you to know that.
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't mind.
I'm sure it's been somewhat vice versa,
but I'll take it.
Well, I don't, I just
one day was looking through
my, my mother got me
a telescope when I was younger, and
I've always been like interested in the stars
and the moon and everything.
And that just, I just, those are
images that were taken. I just
I'm into the planets and I think the solar
system's really cool and just
through the telescope I have a picture
that's able to take photos. It's one of those things
that you know of, oh, you can take binoculars, you can take pictures.
But if you're at like the baseball game
or you have a telescope and you're at the baseball
game, you want to get like a good close up of a home plate
and who's batting when you're in the bleachers.
So yeah, it's a telescopic
view of just, that's just what they look like.
Chat, is he lying? I mean,
the telescope is an incredibly expensive
it's at least like a
it's like $145. It's like
$144.99.
No, that doesn't sound like an expensive telescope.
It makes it the most expensive one you can get on Amazon.
I believe you because
I don't know why I believe you, but I do, but I
feel like I shouldn't. No, that's just
what the planets look like. Go do it.
Wait, your mother got this for you when you were like
10 and you got it on Amazon? No, no, no.
When I was younger, my mother
got me a telescope, but it's what interests me so much
in the solar system. So you bought another one?
Yeah, so years later obviously
I'm a grown man now.
You know, 20, 24 and
decided I was going to
keep my passion going and that's
the solar system and the planets and those are just
images taken from the telescope.
Wait, you're 24?
What do you mean? Chat, how much is Jerma
lying? 85% of the time.
That's probably what it is.
No, he's your age. You're my age.
Yeah, but I got
We're talking about like internal age, you know?
Right, right, how do you feel?
I feel
I feel like 45, but I mean
internally I wish I was 25.
I believe that. Alright, so I've
been in the game for more than 30 seconds
and I'm not disconnected yet.
Wait, in my game?
Am I in your game?
Are you playing a death match?
Oh, I'm not, but I'm ready for you when you come out maybe.
It's possible, it's very possible
we'll get to play for like 20 minutes.
I like the idea that we're doing a co-op match
of Red Dead, but playing separately
in separate servers.
What is Sean doing here?
So here's the thing, I wanted to
actually tell you that I also had a
telescope when I was younger. This is no bullshit.
So when you say that, I was like fucking
fascinated. I wanted to be an astronomer when I was a kid.
And I had a telescope, I had books,
I had the whole fucking thing.
I'm dead serious, which then turned into alien
conspiracies, which was the
wrong way to go about that.
Alien conspiracies.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, think about it.
No, but like honest to God, when you start to really
think about, especially when you're
younger, what's up there? You know what I mean?
You're looking up there, there's like planets and the moons
up there, what the fuck is up there?
Jupiter. Jupiter is up there.
So, if
that's true, and you got that from your telescope,
that's kind of cool. Yeah.
Your emutes don't make any sense.
They don't make any sense. I'm like, okay, go
look. Go look through a telescope
of what the moon looks like.
That's just an image.
There's a lot of people that are
spouting bullshit about me.
They keep using the word doctor,
like doctor. I'm not a doctor.
I'm a fucking streamer.
Wait, you're not? No.
So what are some jobs you've had
that you've had before you were streaming? I'm just
curious. Doctor.
Physician. Mostly.
Oddly enough, I was
a substitute teacher
for a long time. Substitute.
That's cool.
I did wedding videos
for a while. Oh, you have
video editing? Yeah. Yeah.
I did some of that too, actually.
Video editing
video, just making
freelance, just kind of on the
side when I did other stuff.
I got real
gripping, thrilling stuff going on over here.
Thanks for hanging out, guys.
Oh no, I'm talking about on my stream.
How was the weather around those jobs?
It was fucking beautiful.
I'm talking about just on my stream.
I'm just riding on a road, just
holding X.
I got real thrilling stuff over here.
As you can see.
Look at those invitations.
I can't invite you to the match I'm in, but I'm going to try
to join yours.
No, just do your thing.
I've come to the
realization that this is probably just
too good to be true.
And you're going to get in here. I'm going to take
a quality photo of you coming into the stream
into the server.
And then it's going to go
grrrr.
That's what I'm hoping.
No, I'm not. What?
I'm not hoping that happens.
I've become so conditioned to think it's going to.
Am I in your server?
No, I'm not in your server, but I will. I'm going to get in there.
Maybe we get a chance to do
one more match. Let's see.
I love that urn urn thing.
I love it.
Thanks, man. Yeah, I figured that would, you know,
that's the natural evolution of Arthur's
show.
Urn urn.
Pail boss, mate.
Okay, you've
been in a match. You've been in a server for six minutes
without disconnect, apparently.
That's pretty impressive. So I'm going to join
yours.
I want a good photo of me.
This looks pretty good right here with the snowy
mountaintop. Be careful.
Okay, I'm good. So I got a good
spot for you to come on in when you get in here.
Cool.
Enable focus lock.
So are you excited for the Detective Pokemon movie?
Detective Pokemon? Yeah.
I'm excited for it.
I think it looks really
fun.
I think so. I think so, Mr. Red.
Yeah.
Did you play Pokemon Let's Go?
I've never played
a Pokemon game before in my life.
Except for- Really? So you-
Never.
Pokemon, I think I did try
to play
Pokemon Diamond or
Pearl, whatever that was, the one for DS. Oh, there you are.
Look. Hey, mister.
Okay, I got a good photo of you.
That one's going on the album of friends.
Oh.
You're fine.
You just gave me a new face.
Hey, mister.
Alright, so
we're still here. We're not disconnected.
That's amazing. Yeah, neither
of us are ghosts. Holy shit.
I guess join the posse and then we'll
go shoot some stuff and see if that lasts.
Uh, posse.
I see your posse.
I cannot join. This posse is closed
and cannot be joined. And I have no
invites.
This is just
what happens when you go
to the bird exhibit at the local zoo.
Right?
The bird room?
Yeah, this is the bird room.
Oh, Jesus. See ya.
Goodbye. See you later.
God damn it.
You know what's funny? Your horse is still
here. Yeah, he's got a better
connection to Rockstar apparently than I do.
But anyways,
just to follow up on the bird exhibit, have you
been to a butterfly exhibit?
I have, yeah. Well, I mean,
I remember the one
time I was in Texas
in Galveston there was a
butterfly room in some place and I went in
there for a bit. I don't know why I'm telling
you this, but yes, yes.
Well, I mean, it's important because
the bird
room, the butterfly room is like the bird room
.5.
But the scary part about the butterfly room
is aren't you just terrified of
just being in there because there's just butterflies
in every direction. They're above you, they're
below you, they're left and right. I feel like
I'm just gonna like
Godzilla stomp on one of them. Yeah, like
devastate one, right? Or breathe
one in?
Maybe not that.
Breathe one in?
Like throw your nose into your lungs?
Yeah.
I guess that was kind of a
weird thing to say. But yeah, I thought
maybe that was a problem.
Next time I go to a butterfly room.
Was it Moody Gardens? Does
Moody Gardens have a butterfly room?
Moody Gardens, Butterfly.
Maybe I made that up. Maybe I lied.
Yeah, they have them. Butterfly. Rainforest
pyramid, yeah. That's that. Yep.
I've been to Moody Gardens.
Jesus Christ. I was 18 when
that happened. 15 years ago.
That's as old as some of you.
No offense.
Do you forget how long ago 15
years ago is? You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know. That's a decade
and a half.
I mean, playing on the rune of time again is weird
for that reason. Brings back a lot
of memories. So what were you saying then?
I was making a call back.
I was going, okay,
so, Butter.
Alright, alright.
How's the weather around? Let's end this.
Let me
see. What's it gonna be like?
It's gonna be cloudy
with a chance of meatballs.
Why am I typing that in?
Cloudy with a chance of disconnect.
2009. That's when that came up.
Anyone's curious.
Sorry, everybody.
I really figured it was gonna be
fun. I'm sure it was nice to have you
as a special guest. Honestly, my audience always
really enjoys talking
about you, whether it be in a positive
or negative way. They enjoy you quite a bit.
Well,
thank you. Thank you,
everybody in the Vinesauce chat. Appreciate it.
Thank you, Germachat,
for tolerating me for a couple minutes.
Everybody over here loves you, dude.
You are like,
everybody here in Hearns you over here, so don't worry.
That is nice. I like that.
That's a good compliment.
But we'll try again.
Let's see what happens during the week.
Listen, I've been having
disconnects too, so maybe one day we'll both
be able to play this.
And until then, I guess,
you know, take care of yourself.
Go find some good pictures of planets.
Yeah. And you
yourself go look up, go
get a telescope and look, and you'll see.
One day I will, maybe.
Alright. Have a good one. And until then,
I'm gonna go kill a couple dudes, and then
we'll be in touch. We'll meet somewhere in
the middle. So take care, Germachat.
See you later, guys. Take care. Bye.
I wanted to
fucking play!
I wanted to play
Money Player!
I was keeping it so, so
collected the whole time!
I just wanted to play Money
Player with my friend!
Tears are fucking pouring down my face!
You know how hard it is to contain yourself?
No, that's unfortunate. It really is.
I thought this was gonna be fixed.
Uh, Vinny,
Vinny, the great guy.
Highly recommend
If you do not follow that stream,
give it a follow.
So we can talk about one thing here.
The plan today
got a little messed up.
Vinny and Vine!
It's apparently been happening all day.
The plan was
we were only gonna play this for like
two or three hours. So
it's kind of at the point where
the plan was I was only gonna
stream for like two or three hours anyways.
So, I'm sorry guys
that this kind of in the middle
extra stream here turned out to be
a little bit of a uh, you know what I mean?
For tomorrow, the reason why this stream was
not gonna be very long is cause I'm going to
prepare the movie night.
I wanna make sure it's ready to go. I wanna make sure
that it is
uh, perfect.
There are a lot of submissions,
there are a lot of, there's a lot of work
that went into it, so
the plan was I was gonna only stream for an hour or two
and I just, I just deleted an hour for some
reason because it's been an hour or two and I'm just like
I'm like inceptioning that into your brain that the stream
is only gonna be an hour.
Um, I'm so excited for it. I'm looking
forward to it. It's gonna be a lot of fun.
So, I'm gonna end the stream here.
Uh, again, I'm sorry
about the Rockstar servers. I
really, really thought after a few days it was gonna be
fixed. So, I'm gonna go
I'm gonna go fix, uh, not fix
my internet. I'm
I'm so used to saying that.
But, I'm gonna go prepare. I wanna make sure I put a lot of
time into the movie night.
So,
uh, take care.
I'll go through the bits. It's probably gonna be very quick.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. If you don't know what I'm talking
about, we're doing a movie night tomorrow
where I gave
uh, like two or three hours of brain-threat
footage to
everybody in this entire community
and some of the incredibly
talented and creative funny fucking people
that are here have made some great shit
to watch tomorrow. In the stream tomorrow,
probably only gonna be like a couple hours, two or three hours.
I don't wanna have it over states welcome. I don't want it to be
one of those scenarios where it's like, alright, we're like
five hours in and like, here's
another like me keyed in front of Minecraft.
Cause, you know,
it's inevitable.
But there are a lot of really funny fucking people in this
community. And I'm
really looking forward to it. It's been in the making
for like four months. And
um, just really glad that it's gonna be
actually a thing we do tomorrow.
So, let me go.
Uh, let's do the bits.
Really quickly.
If you just showed up.
Sorry, I didn't even tweet the stream
out, I'm glad I didn't. Cause
uh, you know, unfortunately.
There isn't actually that much
Minecraft. I know, I'm just kidding around.
I'm just playing around. For what was there, I hope you
enjoyed just hanging out. Cause we kinda just hung out
and talked about the weather. For like an hour.
Uh, if Vinny is
streaming, go watch him. Metallix is streaming, go
watch him. While I work
on some stuff.
What time tomorrow? Tomorrow at 4
pm pacific time. Is when
the stream is going to start.
4 pm pacific.
Which is 7 pm eastern.
And I am trying to
uh, I am trying
to, cause I've been so used to telling everybody
times in eastern. And I feel like
there's a lot of people that still
um, when I say, oh 4 o'clock!
A lot of people don't know I mean
pacific. Cause I've been so,
it's just, for 3, 4 years
it's been eastern.
So, that's why I keep saying the eastern times
as well. It was fun
watching you two go off cliffs together.
It was. But thank you
uh, thank you again everybody.
Thank you daf. Skeletor for the
10 bucks. No message, 10 dollars.
Uh, coconut, thanks for the 1 buck.
2 bucks actually, 3 bucks!
They say uh, plug
walk. I don't know what that means.
Thank you Divus for the 5 dollars.
No message.
Uh, Hawkeye, thank you Hawkeye
for the 30 dollars Hawkeye.
30 bucks, a little more than an hour ago.
They say, hey there Jerma,
works pretty slow right now. And there's a
snowstorm outside. So I decided to pop in and
give these that have been meeting to
donate. I work pretty late so I'm resigned
to be a slimy
vaude boy. But the laughs
are always well worth it. See you around.
Thank you for the 30 dollars and
slimy vaude
boy. That's
slimy vaude boy. But thank you
so much Hawkeye. 30 dollars,
lots of money. Sorry that the stream
that you gave that money on was
uh, not even, I would even
not even classify the, it's been
like an hour and a half.
Um, don't worry. We got tomorrow
night, we got a very very good
fun stream ready to go. So
thank you. Thank you Garf for the
Monday killer for the one dollar. My name is Garf and I'm here
to say I eat lasagna every day.
Yo yo Jerma, it's Garf the rapper here.
I'm hoping to reboot my rap career.
Yes there's a six minute Garfield rap in the
early 90s. Uh, speaking of reinventing
your image, have you heard of those two Shrek
remakes? Well you just said Shrek so
I'm censoring the rest of this comment.
Won by the guy who made the minions and the
fan made one. The fan
made one called Shrek retold was
released two days ago. Every scene is
directed by a different artist. What movie would you
want remade by fans?
Um, I don't
know. Probably
maybe you could try
Why am I taking this comment seriously? Uh,
what movie? I would
say, uh, crocodile
Dundee. There's some stuff
there that could be done maybe. Uh, thank you
Jess for the one dollar. When I was a kid I used
to say, uh,
Chay Kane instead of Keychain.
I couldn't shake it for years. I would
also say sunshine
every time. I remember this. I can't say it
normally for days after.
Cheshire Trust. It's a Cheshire
Trust at this point. It's not a treasure chest.
It's hard to say it the other way.
But thank you. Thank you ExtraCheesy for the one dollar. He says
he doesn't eat, but yeah, the whole
taquitos things. Uh, ExtraCheesy
thanks again for the ten dollars here. Here's
what you said you never did before.
What the hell is this? I'm
eating taco
You drive dude. I'm eating.
That's not even me. Four?
Eat four taquitos at the same time.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
When did I do this?
I don't remember putting
like five fucking taquitos in my mouth.
Hold on a second.
This is one of the last streams before I left.
Oh. Oh, okay.
You drive dude. I'm eating.
Four? One, two,
three, four. I don't
do this, do I? This is a joke, right?
I'm not doing it.
I knew it.
I knew it. I knew I wasn't
gonna do it. We got a helicopter
dude. We got a helicopter. Okay
I've had enough of that.
I thought you guys were talking about Vinny.
I've never eaten a taquito
in my life.
It's so funny cause that was
that wasn't like five years ago
that wasn't like three years ago. That was like
two months ago.
Oh
How do you guys remember these things?
Good thing you keep me honest.
But thank you Extra Cheesy for that.
Ten dollars, eleven dollars, twelve dollars.
And I want
the red badge. Thank you
Extra Cheesy. Red badge.
Mark Bosh Magali
thanks for the one dollar. The disconnect joke was really
interesting. Not sure what you were trying to accomplish.
Either way, it was nice seeing you
with Vinny. Take care.
The disconnecting from
the game joke. That's too
bad. That's too
bad. But
I would be more upset about this
if, cause I know that he
when we talked about doing this he was like
oh let's do this. This sounds like fun. Like let's give
it a few days though cause there's internet problems. There's like
Rockstar servers are kinda fucked up or whatever
right. I'm just glad that he
was already streaming something. He was doing
something. This wasn't like a okay
here's the stream for today.
He had already been playing like Ocarina of Time
and I'm really glad that it wasn't
just like oh hey let's just
let's just ruin this stream.
So. And
on this end at least that this was
an in between to tomorrow.
And we streamed yesterday, streamed tomorrow
and I'm just glad that this wasn't
you know oh that's it.
Red dead connection.
Yeah. Sorry
again everybody. I wish
I could snap my fingers and magically
have it not happen but
I'm actually going to do a little bit of research
because the stuff that I read
about it there's like workarounds
and I tried the workarounds
already. They didn't work.
But maybe there's some other things to try.
But thank you Marvish
Magali. Thank you Hunter Kane for the one dollar. Have some
bits. Thanks. Mostly lost thanks for
the one dollar. You should host Vinny or
Italics. You do know how the host button works right?
I don't know what
you mean like they
appear like I hope
they appear inside of me.
What do you mean? Like I have to
be inside. That's like a that's like a tapeworm.
I don't think I want that.
That's how the movie Venom starts.
Ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha. Hey thank you
D Jack for the one dollar. I rewatched the Zoo Tycoon stream
and nearly shit myself with the T-Rex not being
able to find his car joke. Keep bringing
the chuckles. Thank you D Jack.
It was a fun stream. Spoilers.
Oh sorry. Sorry guys.
Venom is a symbiote. Sorry.
Sorry for the spoils.
And Smelly Boy right at the end. When are you going to play
Metal Gear Rising? Tomorrow.
No it's a lie. I'm kidding. Not tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're doing the...
No. Tomorrow we're doing the movie night.
How long is the stream going to be
tomorrow? That's up
for potential debate because
after I turn the stream off
here I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to go grab a drink and then sit down
and really get it hammered out.
And I don't know.
I'm going to assume it's going to be
like less than two or three hours long.
Because we're just going to be watching a playlist.
We're watching a huge community
playlist. So
I'm going to assume up to three hours.
It's one minute max. Two minutes max.
I plan on, I'm just going to tell you
just a fair warning, I plan on drinking a little bit
of wine. This is the sun.
It's been a couple of, it's been like two or three
weeks since I've had some good wine.
It's going to be a red blend.
But that is
it. Here come the credits
for the short stream that was
here. Thank you for
subscribing and contributing
everybody. It means a lot.
I wish it was better circumstances.
He's going to eat food and forget.
And there's also
a very, very real
possibility where the
it's broken up into two nights.
You know what I mean? Because if
there are, if there's more than four
or five hours of
videos to watch, then it might,
it'll be better probably to break it up into two
separate occasions. It depends.
I mean, maybe we'll just do the whole thing. It really depends
on how long the whole, after going
through and
making sure that it's cleaned up
and some duplicates are removed
or ones that weren't
following the rules or ones that just didn't make
any sense. Once it's cleaned up a little
bit, we'll find out. I can watch it at
times two speed.
Don't
watch them. What do you mean don't watch them?
Ones that don't make any sense.
Here's what I'm talking about. If there's like
we need to shave time off,
here's the reason why these all had to
be screened and had to be
predetermined if they were
capable of being on. Because the rules
that I set forth were original
content encouraged,
more than 10 seconds, less than two minutes,
like give or take
some people, if you go over by
five seconds or so, like okay,
as long as, or ten seconds, whatever,
if the video was made well,
we're just trying to see how that works.
But, there weren't very many
other rules
in regards to, well, I mean, obviously there was no
hateful shit, there was no sexual stuff,
obviously. But,
the reason why we have to go through them all
is because somebody could just put up
hey, here's my, here's my submission
and it's a minute and 58 seconds
of a black screen and then it flashes me
on the screen for one second.
That one's not going on, we're not putting
that one on the video, you know what I mean? That's not going on.
Like, that shit's not going on.
That's just a waste of time,
you know what I mean? Time is of the essence
tomorrow. And so, there's been
a few submissions that have
just been, just absolute,
just carnage,
just keyed out, just
volume at max,
blasting music, and just
like, and every one of the
green screens just like flying around and stuff.
For like two minutes.
It's like,
there's been some wild submissions,
so we need to make sure that we have
ones that aren't going to be obviously,
you know, blow anybody's ears out.
That sounds amazing.
And if, yo, I didn't say there was
anything wrong with it, but for the purposes of
tomorrow's viewing,
it needs to be at least fairly
structured. I've
I've tried to abstain from watching as many
of them as I can, but there are a lot of occasions
where I do have to watch them,
because I'm not sure, is this one okay?
Is this one kind of pushing the line
a little bit, and I have to watch them. I have to watch
a lot of them, pretty much.
But, because there's been
the mod team has been doing an absolutely
fucking fantastic job
to keep this
where I don't see very many
of them, you know what I mean?
But they do need to be watched, and I go, alright, I don't know about
that. Have somebody watch them for you.
That is essentially
what the mods have been doing.
It's been a huge fucking help.
That they deserve praise, they deserve
all the love you can give them.
And they deserve
compensation.
Because that's a lot of work. Especially this.
Yeah, coming, bits coming
your way.
Because, I mean, I'll be real here for a minute.
There's been occasions where
you know, you just can't do
it alone, you know what I mean?
There's been at least three or four streams that
just
without the help of at least
three, four of these mods.
There's no way that the streams would have even been
in reality, never would have been in reality, ever.
So, big thanks.
In reality.
And thank you all the subs, everybody
that just came in. Get excited for tomorrow,
it's gonna be a lot of fun. And finally,
right at the very end,
we had mostly lost
with the dollar. Also, thanks to you, I'm never gonna be able to drink
a red blend again without laughing.
Oh, come on, it's the best. It's the best.
I should have asked, I should have asked
a video about that. He would know.
He would be like, yeah, of course.
Mr. Picklesworth, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, how you doing today? I think I got banned from the discord
because I said, give,
I give back
a couple of times in the chat
when you took away the image posting.
Sorry, if my messages were spammy.
Hit up one of the
mods in a private message.
They will take care of it. They will
just, they will take a look and see what happened.
I hope it's not too late for you to see this.
No. And just
also remember something.
If somebody gets from the discord
or in this channel,
if you get like banned,
for the, all
bans, like permanent, we're talking like
bans, are
discussed. And it's not just like, hey,
you got banned. And there's usually
a dialogue you can open up to
potentially talk about what happened
or why or
that does happen. So
all hands are disgust.
Can I negotiate
why I should be banned? You could, yeah.
You could. If you really
wanted to. But that's going to be
it. See you guys tomorrow.
Four p.m. Pacific. I'm excited.
You're excited. We're all excited.
Have a wonderful rest of your evening.
Sorry again
for Rockstar's servers
not working. Good night.
Take care. See you tomorrow.