Hi. Welcome. Good to see you.
Come on, I've got my Las Vegas hat on. I'm so drunk right now, you have no idea.
Hi everybody. Welcome to the stream. This is gonna be a very short stream.
Tiny. Like this big. Small. Delay Andy. That's me.
It's gonna be a very compact one. I look so tired. I'm not used to waking up this early.
You look young. I do?
Wait, is it the hat? I know why. It's because I used to wear hats. Like this. All the time.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. So now I look old again, right? Do I look old?
Shit. Alright, so let's put the hat back on and see what happens.
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm. Okay.
Wait. I can look even younger. Ready? Watch this. That's the trick.
You want to look younger? Just have your hat pointing up at the ceiling and have it rest on your head.
Now let's look older. Ready?
Hey. Hey, Sport. Oh, hey, Sport. How you doing?
Oh, hey. Yeah, I'm doing good. School's good.
School's doing good? That's good to know.
Hey, I got you a gift card to Target for this year.
A gift card to Target? Cool. Thanks, Uncle.
Yeah, of course. Of course. You can come visit Uncle anytime. Anytime you want, come to Uncle's.
I'll just fix it for you.
Redneck? No, that's, I mean, that's earnest. Yeah, this is earnest.
If you pull your hat way down on, like, your eyebrows, then you're just earnest.
And you know what I mean, Burn? Oh, no. Look at, no.
No, you can, you can, okay, you can see my crow's feet. You can see my cyberpunk augmentation.
Hold on. No. You can see my, like, cybernetics.
Oh, well. Anyways, there's a dog on the floor.
You know what's really funny about this dog? He, that's a nice dog bed. It really is.
But he doesn't give a shit. He's like, I don't care. What's on your face?
What is it? What is like this? What is this?
By the way, look at his outfit.
I've lost complete control at this point. You know what I mean?
Look at the hat. I've got, like, Dr. Favorite. I've got, like, pajamas on.
I've got, like, pajama pants.
I really am like a fucking 45-year-old.
That's how I dress. This is how I dress. People think I'm, hold on.
Come on. I've got to get away from earnest. We've got to go more, there we go.
There we go. Okay, cool.
Vegas Knights? Yeah, I've, I'm such a, I'm such a fucking piece of shit.
You know why?
How many Vegas Golden Knights games do you think I've been to since moving to Vegas?
How many? None. That's right. Correct. Ding, ding, ding.
Absolute zero. Turn it backwards.
Oh, wow. I just de-aged again.
This kind of hurts, though. This is fellow kids.
Yeah, it is. This hurts my forehead.
No, I don't like it. That reminds me of VR.
And I don't have very much left in the front, so I don't want to do that.
It reminds me of a VR helmet.
So, what are we doing today? Well, nothing.
I've got about 40 minutes.
I figured if we look at the dog, we'd have a coffee.
We'd talk about a few things. A few important things.
This is new, by the way. So it's not, I don't, you notice I haven't been punching you in the face on stream anymore?
You notice that I haven't been just, like, absolutely just hammering your head?
I used to have a big, one of these that was just stuck out and it was a big pop filter. Not anymore.
And now I have this little one that still works pretty well.
A couple things.
This weekend, probably on either, probably Monday, either Sunday or Monday,
I'm shooting for Monday or Tuesday. You know me, though. It'll be Thursday.
The poll for the New Year's Eve.
I'm not going to be live for the next, like, eight or nine days.
Probably ten days, at least.
So, I'm not going to be able to announce when the voting is going to happen.
But the nominations are in. That's closed.
And voting is going to begin this coming week.
And I'm not going to be able to tell you, hey, by the way, go vote!
I'm doing that now.
So, this is a preemptive go vote on that poll.
So, share this clip of me talking about this to all your friends that know that they want to vote,
because it's going to be coming next week.
And I'm not going to be there to tell you about it.
I'm here telling you about it now.
This is a loser. Loser.
Maybe I should get back to fucking punching shit.
Right there!
Uh, stop counting. Yeah, whatever. Get out of here.
Alright, so that's going to... I'll tweet it, yeah.
Look, who even follows me, really, on Twitter anymore?
I make one post every, like, four years.
Like, you're probably not paying that much attention to what happens on my Twitter.
It's like, hey, I'm streaming right now, and then three years go by,
and I do, like, a fucking... I'm in the bathroom, like, washing my hands tweet.
Where's the whopper? Ow! That hurt!
I don't have it. Shit!
I knew I was forgetting something.
Oh, well. Liar. I knew it!
I was like, what am I forgetting today?
This is something I'm fucking forgetting.
Go get it now. I can't go get it now.
I can't go get it now!
Dude, delivery. It's not even going to get here.
What do you mean, dude, do, like, door dash?
It's not going to get here in time.
It's going to take, like, 30 or 40 minutes for me to get...
It always does that.
It's not like it's going to take too long.
It's going to show up here, and the stream's going to end,
and I'm just going to enjoy a gross whopper,
but I don't want to do that.
You only have 30 minutes.
I do? Oh, somebody just said in all capitals,
fuck you.
Shit. I'm in trouble.
Okay. Well, I didn't do it.
And I'll do it when I get back.
I promise. Nice crow's feet.
No, it's a fucking goddamn cybernetic augmentation!
Gives me 10% better eyesight.
He's a redneck fat ass.
What?
I'm like a skinny boy.
I'm not a grown-up yet.
What do you mean, skinny?
You guys don't think I'm skinny?
I'm like 150 pounds.
You are. I know.
I'm like 150, soaking wet.
Do the pancake recipe joke.
I don't have a gun.
I can't do a pancake recipe. I don't have a gun.
It's in a game.
Look, I do a thing in the video game.
Just look at the video.
It's called Secret Pancake Recipe.
I made it like fucking eight years ago.
Tell us your shitstain story.
Oh, also.
Hey. Listen to this.
You guys ready?
I got an announcement to make.
I have an announcement to make for you.
So.
Well, it's more like an announcement of an announcement.
But it's an announcement that
things are coming to this thing that people
were really into.
So you guys remember FTK?
Fuck the king. A couple of experiments we tried to do.
Tried to get like a thousand people in a server.
It was an experiment, right?
It was an experiment. It was an experiment.
It was fun. It was an experiment.
It was fun. So.
FTK has been
killed. The king is dead.
And from the ashes
in the king's grave is going to
rise. You ready?
An official JermaCraft
server for Minecraft where you can go
and hang out with your friends and build all kinds of
fun stuff. And there's gonna be like a survival. There's gonna be like
a bunch of cool stuff. There's gonna be like a map you can
walk around. There's gonna be a full on community
Minecraft server that will
exist forever. It
looks fucking awesome. It's currently
a work in progress. It looks
awesome.
I will share some things with you soon.
But I wanted to give an update on that.
It's going to be, the base is going to be
just vanilla Minecraft.
There'll probably be some additions later
as we add stuff to it.
But FTK is just becoming
a Minecraft server. That you guys
it'll be broken up into a bunch of different
world maps and the hub world
looks incredible. I cannot
tell you how awesome it looks. You'll see pretty soon.
We just get subs?
MysticQuest, thanks for the five community
subs! That was really loud.
And like my chair shocked
me. Tuber voice. That wasn't even a tuber voice.
That was a chewing gum from the 90s
commercial voice. There's over 45
different flavors! Whoa!
Uh, Freddy's, what the fuck?
Freddy Dredge has
50 subs. The last two days has been like
just sub the, just like
sub the fuck out of me! That's
50! Freddy!
Oh my god, dude.
Cry, cry, cry, cry.
There's been like 2000 subs in
48 hours. Something insane.
Sing the cry song.
How do you sing the cry song?
I don't know what that means.
He's in a new tax bracket.
Smash the hand.
Sing it, coward.
Come over here, coward. Come over here, coward.
Hey, you flipped me off.
Uh, Jeremy, please.
Give me some questions. Give me some questions for me
for like another 20 minutes before I leave.
No taxes on bits.
I don't think you know how that works.
But, it's okay.
Hold on a minute.
We've got another five
community subs!
From xparta45, thanks xparta.
This is just continuing from last night, I feel.
Hey, nice to see you. Nice to see you too.
Get that gross thing off there.
Do some ASMR, okay?
People are going to freak out if I do that.
This kind of looks like a pineapple upside down cake.
You know what I mean, doesn't it?
Oh, no.
I'm literally sitting here
drinking coffee.
I don't deserve this amount of money.
I do not deserve this.
I've just made a coffee and put a fucking
Vegas Golden Knights hat on
and sat down and told you about a Minecraft server.
Somebody's like 25 subs.
Who was that?
Who just gave the 25 subs?
Four but just came in with five.
Who just gave 25 subs?
What the fuck is going on?
Is this going to turn off?
This is still going from last night.
Who just gave the 25?
Hold on.
Can I take a sip of this fucking coffee?
I'm just holding it like a wax museum.
Will the Minecraft server be sub only?
No, but you're going to have to get white listed.
You'll get white listed through the Discord.
So no one's going to have to pay
to play here.
But you're going to have to get white listed through the Discord.
So no, there's not going to be a sub
requirement at all. But there will be a Discord
white listing requirement.
No, I don't want people to have to pay for that.
Every time I think about that, I'm like, no.
That's fucking stupid. I don't want to do that.
Like, oh, you've got to have...
Look, it's $5 a month to pay.
If I did that, let's say it was
$5 a month for you to play on that server
and you don't even care, you just want to play on the Minecraft server.
The hosting for that server,
it would be...
That would be way more money taking in
than I should be taking in.
So, no.
Why would I do that? My penis...
Whatever.
You should get a nose job.
You think so? Yeah, I know. It goes like this.
It's all broken and shit.
No, I don't care. It's how God made me. I don't give a fuck.
It's how God made me.
He started sketching.
He got about to be right here.
Somebody grabbed his attention.
God, there's an earthquake. What?
And he smudged with his pencil.
I'll fix that later.
He got down to here.
He sneezed. Oh, shit.
That's all right. That's how I made him.
That's how it looks okay.
Then he got to about here.
And he's like, you know what?
Let's make a big mouth.
I was his funny character creator.
You don't think God made you into a character creator?
Listen to this at work.
Be careful. I don't want you to get fired or anything.
Get out of work.
I don't want your boss to come over and be like, what the fuck is this guy?
Oh, shit. Hey, bro.
I got the report.
You're doing a great job, man.
I'm working here.
You really helped me out here.
You did a huge thing for me.
I'm working here, remote.
You're there.
The work that I have for you
will be done soon.
You've helped me way more than I do.
You do so much more work than me.
I'm just really happy that I have somebody like you that I can kind of
communicate with that can help me
get work done for the boss.
Because he's like fucking...
He sucks.
He is such a fucking loser.
I know you guys, I know you like him.
You like him and you think he's really cool
and smart and funny and stuff.
He fucking sucks, dude.
And I don't even care if I get like, I don't know.
If he ever hears this, whatever.
Which is like, I find fucking annoying.
But, whatever.
I don't think he's an idiot.
You got that guy fired.
No I didn't. The boss is peering over with like
his glasses looking down.
And he hears like, oh you like him.
And I'm like, fuck him.
He stands up for me?
I don't remember that.
This is a stall stream.
There's nothing to stall to.
Are you Ellis from Left 4 Dead?
Oh shit. I mean, a little.
Stall 2 for the Whopper stream.
This is one.
Do the voice.
What does Ellis talk like?
Oh man, that's me Ellis. I'm hanging out here with my gun.
I don't know nothing about that.
Is that how he talks?
I haven't played the game in like fucking 4 years.
What about Community Content Night?
Oh alright, we can talk about that.
So, Community Content Night is
like FTK, also dead.
Sad to say.
The reason is because the Twitch DMCA
shit, there is no reliable way
I can show videos like that on stream
in a row.
Unfortunately, all the
best like possibilities
like in Harry Potter,
you know, think about it, right?
I sat in front of a green screen and said, put this in the Saw
movie. Hey look, I'm a
Harry Potter character.
You can't really do that anymore.
And I don't want to have
insane heavy restrictions on it because I feel like
the best videos are when you guys do whatever the fuck you want.
So I wouldn't want to be like,
it's going to be the original background, original music,
only original character, and only
like an original foreground, and
good luck. By the way,
I say Harry Potter in this clip 35
times. Good luck.
No idea how you're going to do that.
So that's just not going to happen anymore.
And it's sad to say it,
but that was
about a full half of those streams.
So, the idea,
and I don't know,
I think this is okay for me to say,
the idea is maybe to make a mega playlist
with the videos.
A huge one, a mega one.
And queue it up in the Discord
and just have a night where
we just, in the Discord, it's just playing
and we're all there. Somehow.
I'm trying to figure out what to do about it.
Kind of like a watch party, essentially,
in Discord. Because we can't do it
here. And I don't really want to do it on YouTube
either because YouTube also has the same problems.
And I don't really want to stream on YouTube because
I don't want to do that.
What the fuck is a Discord?
It's a service where you can get online and talk to friends.
It's like Skype, but way better.
It's just a way better version of
Skype. There you go.
Disc or mega lol. Okay, whatever.
But the artwork is
essentially started to transition into
the BRB screen. And I know there's
some kinks to work out.
There's things that we have to figure out how I'm going to do that.
Because I think
after talking to Lazy Luke
that the backlog of art
is still slowly
getting chipped away at.
And I would have to do more
BRBs. But
I don't know if I necessarily want to do that.
I don't think I want to have to be like,
I gotta take a break now.
Because if I don't take a break now, let's
do a five minute break. I'll see you later so we can show art.
Although
I could do it at the end of streams.
But the problem with doing it at the end of a stream is
I am doing the thing that I deliberately
removed like four or five months ago.
Where we hang out and sit there
for half an hour,
twenty, fifteen, twenty, thirty, forty minutes.
And we do a post stream wind down and I got rid of that
deliberately. So that's not going to happen.
So what could happen
is during, I guess,
I could do either like an art
stream. But the thing about
doing an art stream is that's just
community content night. And community content night had the videos
and it was like a big thing. It was like, oh we're going to do the art.
Then we're going to do the videos, we're going to do the music.
And it just sucks
that we can't do it all. Could do pre-stream too.
There could be a thing
during the planets, right?
Where it's
and then in the corner for like, you know, five to ten minutes
is, or like big enough obviously
the starting soon would be in the corner.
Do that. Have it run during the starting soon screen.
I think that makes sense too.
He's flustered. A little because it's
annoying that I have to, I have to
remove and delete essentially one of my favorite things
on the entire channel. Which was like the
screen screen community, not content night stuff.
Like that shit was fucking hilarious.
So it's annoying that
one of my favorite things essentially has to go away.
I just rambled for a little while
but you know I haven't talked, we have not talked about this yet.
So, do it on YouTube. Yeah
I don't want to do it on YouTube. No.
The same problems. I like the rambling.
Well good. I'm glad. Cheers to you.
I don't know why I did that. That probably hurt.
I'm really sorry. I just like did that inside of your ear.
Ramble Andy.
Go to mixer. That's funny.
Go back to gaslighting.
You want to see the dog again? Oh what I was going to say about the dog.
So he pulls the blankets off
and lies over on next to the bed sometimes.
It's like he prefers
he's such a Goldilocks dog. Sometimes he
prefers a soft bed.
And other times he prefers like a hard
ground. It's 50-50.
I have no idea. He sees Goldilocks.
No, no. He's the Goldilocks bears.
All in one animal. That's more accurate.
So
anybody got any more questions?
This is just a question stream. I'll answer anything.
I will answer anything.
You could write anything. As long as it was
TOS friendly. I would answer literally any question.
What is it? What's your name? Jeremy.
Done. Easy. Will you marry me? No.
Do I
poop? Of course I do.
That's part of my digestive system. All humans
do, of course. Can I have? No.
How's your day? It's going pretty good. It's going well.
It's going very good. Will I make it through my audit?
Yeah, just make sure
you play by the rules and make sure you give
all the documents and
work with the IRS.
You can work with the IRS somehow.
Yeah, you'll be good. Do you drink Dr.
Pepper? I have not had a sip of Dr. Pepper
in probably four or five months.
Before that it was probably a couple of years.
I just wear it because I like the shirt.
I'm an old fan.
Pirates, knights, or cowboys?
Pirates for fun, knights for protection,
and cowboys for...
No, this is not
like a sexual thing. What are you talking about?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pirates are like... If I was on a pirate ship
it would be like we sing songs and like drink
and sail.
A knight has like a huge...
can protect you. He's got like a sword and a shield
and stuff. A cowboy...
for food! A cowboy
for food. If I want to have
a lot of food. Is there like... they can
get... they're cowboys, right?
I don't know. Farmers? Cowboys? They're kind of...
Cowboys used to have their own
source of food. They had to get their hunt and stuff, right?
They're not eating other cowboys.
Do you... What's your favorite... What?
Do you eat beans? I do.
Refried beans are one of my favorite things. Any news
on the D&D game? Star
is currently working on his project
which is going very well.
So we had a conversation that was just like, hey, whenever
you're... Just you do your project
and do it as best you can and then maybe later
you'll be able to get heavy, heavy
work on the German 951.
So he's got his thing
going now. And I don't want to... I didn't want to be like
oh, hey, well, fuck it. You're gonna do mine.
Forget about your project. No, it's
going very well, so... Do I smell?
Yeah. Do I smell bad? No.
I do... I emanate some type of fragrance
though. What's your opinion? I missed it.
Fucking door spring behind you.
This thing? I would even pick
that up. Touch it. Go flick
it. Okay, fine.
You happy? You made a loud
noise too. I forgot.
You can't... Like on Twitch
you have to just be a torso.
You cannot... People cannot know
that you have anything below the torso.
See, and now Otto's annoyed. I just
like... I just did that thing and he's like
fucking... What the fuck, dude? I was sleeping.
You did that. I didn't.
You have to just be a floating
upper body. When's German Rumble 2020?
New Year's Eve. Oh, hello.
New Year's Eve. Why do I look like a college
kid? Because I have a hat on. You want me to take it off and
be Jeremy again? Sure.
Alright. I'm just gonna... Whatever. I don't even need the hat anymore. Who cares?
Boomer. Maybe
a little. Your hair looks small.
It's... I was trying to hold in
a fart right there and I promise I wasn't. I just was
doing that. I don't know why. Do a wink.
That was Robert De Niro.
I don't think... Easiest impression
ever. Just like crush your face a little bit
and tilt your head around. Any chance
of... I missed it. What does it say? Any chance of...
Any chance of... When are you
gonna collab with Nianers? What the fuck was
that? When am I gonna collab with Nianers?
Nianers is... Nianers is very funny.
I don't know.
I don't know. We kind of did last night.
We were like sent the
clip thing.
We like sent... We went back and forth with like clips
on stream. Mind playing Jet Set
Radio for a stream? I did and I fucking couldn't
do it. I like couldn't do it. I freaked
out. Do a slime stream. I know.
There's so many things that I want to do but I
just didn't. You gonna be a VTuber?
Would I make a good VTuber?
I don't know. Probably not.
Christmas stream.
Not this year. New Year's stream.
Uh...
Nianers believed you could do it.
Well that's a huge endorsement.
What would I... How would I... I don't
know. What about German Direct?
Um...
I don't have much to show besides the New Year's Eve
thing and the Minecraft thing. It'd be like
a Blizzcon 2019.
People would be fucking mad at me.
Oh! But shit I gotta charge like $400
a ticket though. Will you... What does it say?
If you do Mr. Slime, let me
do it. Um... I have no
idea what I would even do.
I would have to get like a... I would have to like get
something blocked out of my brain first before
I even took that step. But somebody
just gave a shitload of money.
That was Chef Lazarus for 25
subs. So many subs.
I think... I think we broke it. Did we break it?
Let's see. Uh... I think we broke...
I think it's an all time high. Let's see.
I think we did it. When I
say we I mean you because like
I'm just receiving this and
sometimes I don't know why. Uh...
The channel has broken.
11,000 subscribers.
Just fucking ridiculous.
Uh... I believe the all
time high is
not very close to... I don't know. I don't like
keep track of this if I'm honest.
I don't like want to keep track of this
because I feel like then it becomes
something I have to care about and I don't want that.
So I don't really pay
that much attention to that.
So that's a lot
of fucking money. He doesn't care about
gift subs. No, I do. I very much
do. But I don't ever want that
to be like a number that I like
chase every day. And it's fluctuated
a lot. I mean it's gone.
It's... It has gone like wham
wham. My schedule is so erratic.
I take a lot of breaks. I don't pay attention
to that. If it ha... Again this is...
I said the word subscriber and we talked about all
I shouldn't have even said it. But this
is a lot of money and I just don't want
to pay that much attention to it. Um...
Chef Lazarus... I can't...
Somebody just gave 50. Hold on. I gotta pull this up.
That's a lot of money.
How much... What did you just give?
That was Wesley. Wesley gave 50
community subs.
We broke it. We definitely broke it.
So we don't have to do anymore.
It's absolutely been broken.
The stream is absolutely... This is the new subscriber
high. Last time it happened
was like this exact time
period last year. That's
insane. End of December into the
first of January. That's what happened last time.
But thanks guys. It's completely
unnecessary. We don't have... You don't have
to give anymore subs. We don't have to do it anymore.
Like you don't have to. This is like
already an insane number. And
we don't have to do like a
sub train today. We don't have to do
that. That doesn't have to happen.
It doesn't have to happen.
I don't need it to happen. I don't like want
you to do that. I know
that I'm just... I keep saying the word
so people are going to do it. But I
will tell you, if you have
other streamers that you watch,
I would rather you
sub to them. I would rather you
support a smaller streamer
or a streamer that you enjoy
that you know might not have 11
fucking thousand subscriptions.
You know what I'm saying? It's
an incredibly overwhelming thing.
I can't believe that this many people pay this much
money. But if you have a
choice between like a few
different people and you know that I'm about to
hit like fucking 12,000 subs,
support them. Because you know that I
would much prefer that. If you don't,
but if it's just me, if it's just
me, then alright. But no, I'm kidding.
He's doing
reverse psychology. Alright, well then
okay. If I do regular
regular psychology,
if I say do it, then that
means you won't do it. There's a burp coming in.
I can't even
count. This is so many that just came in. All
five. Five fifty. Ten
from Captain Dark. Five edgy shadow.
Five anonymous gifted. This is the same exact thing
happened yesterday. Now, and I want
another thing too. Especially
like now. You know
what I mean? Like 2020's been fucked. I'd rather
you spend that money on like you, your friends, and
your family than me.
Take care of yourselves. Make sure you do that first.
Put me at the bottom of your fucking list.
I really hope you are. Put me
at the very bottom of your list of
places where you think your money should be going.
Take care of yourself. Take care of your family. Take care of your friends.
Absolutely. Like I
It's been a fucking rough year. And I
really hope that you guys
are taking care of yourselves. Ban the subs.
Jeremy, you're getting coal for
Christmas.
Are you gonna finish Saw II? Why would
I finish Saw II?
Did you hear how much I was
not having fun in that game?
I'm not gonna finish. I'm not gonna
open Saw II again. I don't know what the
disk is. I think I threw it away.
Yes. Yeah.
But that's behind you?
I know. There's a dog behind me.
Here he comes.
Oh, big stretch.
You missed it.
I really hate to do this
but I've gotta go in like
a minute. I think I'm just gonna
turn the stream on and
hey everybody. Just going
live for like 40 minutes and collecting
subs. Thanks everybody. Appreciate
the fucking 600 subs
that just came in. Alright, see you later
40 minutes. You know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean? I wanna be real. I don't
want that. I don't want to be that.
I don't want this to turn into
that. I don't want to just collect money from you
and that's what I do.
Let me be real. Farming
subs. Where is German
land? It's coming soon.
That's like what just happened.
I turned the stream on to give you a couple of updates
and say have a good holiday.
If you celebrate Christmas, have a great Christmas. Whatever holiday
you're celebrating, happy holidays, right?
Merry Christmas to all that. Cause I'm not
gonna be here. I mean I just
got like a bunch of money.
Okay, I'm gonna update them and
yeah, I guess I'll collect
like fucking thousands of dollars.
You got crusty
lips? How about now?
Better? I know I have dry lips.
You know what? Fucking
mod that guy for five minutes and then
fucking throw his username
into the trash can
with all the other banned motherfuckers.
And then
throw him a life vest.
And take a huge smoke of
cigar.
Good luck getting back to land.
And then drop a briefcase
into the
huge briefcase into the fucking water.
And there's like 20 grand and hundreds in there.
Just fuck it up.
You know what I mean? Like wait, is he trying to kill me?
He's trying to give me money?
I don't understand what he's doing.
There's like a Lyft waiting for them?
Yeah, I'm taking you wherever you want to go.
Why? I don't know.
Mr. Green told me to do this.
I have no idea. He gave me $500
and said take him wherever he wants.
10k viewers? What would it look like
without lips? How do you do that?
Yeah. I can't get it to work.
Disgusting.
Oh, did you know that I was the Joker?
Stop. It was just Elmo.
The Joker kind of
is an Elmo laugh. It is.
You can't tell me that's not Elmo.
It's close.
It's in the line of
different Elmo laughs.
You don't go
hahahaha.
No. Who does a Joker laugh like that?
Everybody's Joker laugh is like extreme
and they throw their head
forward and they get a high pitch at the end.
It's Elmo.
Yeah, but that's different though.
Nobody does
the Joker laugh like
hahahaha. I am the Joker.
No. They all go
I don't know why we do that. Everyone does it
like that. Nobody does it the other way.
It was like 50 faces.
You need a Netflix special.
What the fuck would I even do?
You're going to be late? I'm not going to. I'm okay.
You got a link? Let's see.
Whole VTuber stream.
A VTuber face tracking program is not difficult
to get. Do it. What did you get? What is this?
Explain the toothbrush behind you.
Where? What?
There's your toothbrush. On the bottom shelf.
The fuck did you even see
that? How?
What? I don't know
why that's there. I have no idea.
I don't know why that's there.
I must have been
like, I don't know.
It must have been in my hand. I'm not a
weirdo. I promise. I don't know why there's a toothbrush
there. But I kind of need
it. So that's really good that
you saw that because I wouldn't have
seen it. It's in its case.
It's fine. I can't believe you saw that.
Explain it. I don't
know how to explain that.
How do you explain that? You don't.
Use it right now. No. I need it.
Brush your teeth. I do brush
my teeth. It's not right the second I'm
busy doing this. Unbox
it. No. That's
so fucking funny that somebody saw that.
Like, how?
People just like take every fucking
pixel and they go, what's over there?
What's over there? What's that thing right there? Is that
embarrassing? Let's find out. What's that?
Is that lotion? Is that lotion right here?
Jeremy, why do I have lotion? Why is there lotion there?
Are you zirking off? You must be zirking off.
Jeremy, why do I have lotion? Are you zirking off? You zirked off today.
No, I don't know why that's there. No, I know you
zirked off. I know it. I know it.
I know you did. You do. I know you do.
Okay, cool. Why is that?
What's in that box? The box behind you.
The box behind me? Yeah. What's it?
Was there lotion in there? Inside the box, like the cardboard box
over here. Yeah, you must have been zirking off in that box.
I don't zirk off in a box.
I don't. Yes, you do. Why is it behind you in your bedroom?
Because, I don't know, it's packing something.
Okay, yeah, right, there's lotion in there. You zirked off in that box. I know you did.
You fucking liar. I know you zirked off.
Everything has to do with that. You-
Why is the toothbrush there? What's the explanation
for that? I don't have one. You must be
fucking using that. On your butt.
You're like fucking butthole. No, I'm
not, actually. Oh, yeah? Yeah.
No, you zirked off and used that thing on your butthole.
I know you were. No, I'm not, okay?
Like, I'm not. It all
goes back to that every time.
No one said that? Oh, I'm sure
they did. You're projecting.
I thought there was a device-
Ow! I'm just saying,
it doesn't matter what's behind you,
if you're a YouTuber
or you're in a streamer room,
the thing that's not really supposed
to be in the room is
you must have been zirking off somehow.
It's every time.
Shut the door. This door is
shut. What are you talking about?
You're in a beatbox to meet the medic theme.
No, why?
I've done it like a thousand times.
Close it all the way. I will eventually
when I feel like it. Play with the
door spring to remove one million off the
dead. I already did. I did that already.
You missed it. I did that for free.
Alright. I gotta
get out of here. I have to leave.
I'm not gonna see you guys until next
week. Uh, probably like
I might- I might
even see you on New Year's
Eve. That might be the next time you physically
see me. Uh, I got a lot
of work to do. I've got a lot of stuff going on
and I'll be gone until
that week of New Year's Eve.
So, I didn't want- I wanted to stream
and I've been taking a lot of time off, I know
and that's why I feel even more like
just bad about taking
like thousands of subs
before it's like, well, see you later.
I'll see you like 12 days.
Um, but thanks
guys. We'll have fun on New Year's Eve.
A lot of festivities.
And, uh, I'll see you guys later.
We're not even gonna have an outro.
I'm just going. I'm just going.
No outro, no nothing. I didn't start with
one, I'm not gonna end with one.
Didn't start one, not gonna end with one.
Raid- Oh! You know who's live right now?
Who I never catch live because we're in different time
zones? Is, uh, RT.
RT Game Crowd's live right now.
Never catch him because we're just so far apart
in time zones.
So let's raid RT.
Absolutely. Okay.
Uh, I'll see you guys. I'll give you updates.
I'll be in the Discord. I'll be popping around.
Uh, but, I gotta make this really clear.
Make sure that you
keep an eye on the Discord over the next
like three or four days. Because the
poll, the voting of the actual awards
for your nominations that you've
nominated is gonna be there. I'll tweet
about it, it'll be in the Discord, but I'm not gonna be able to
talk about it until I'm back.
So, good night. Oh, well, it's like
no, it's like noon. Well, it's
noon somewhere. It's noon
somewhere, right? Whatever that thing is.
Yeah. I'll see you guys in like a week.
Take care of yourselves. Enjoy the rest of your
evening. Day, night, whatever.
It's noon here. It's noon here too. And I'll
see you guys soon. Happy holidays, Merry Christmas,
all that good stuff. Uh, take care
of yourselves, take care of your family, your loved ones, your friends,
uh, and enjoy the time
that you will have, uh, hopefully on like
Christmas and Christmas Eve and New Year's and stuff.
We're gonna have fun. Goodbye. Take care
of yourself. And, uh, let's go say hello to
RT. Goodbye. Gotta
go to the end slate here. Ow.