Okay, so let's I'm gonna go over the rules of this challenge
This is super punch out and this is gonna go as follows. No, no knockdowns
Let's see if I can do it. We don't need to bet. Can I do this with no knockdowns for me?
No TKOs or no knockdowns at all. That's gonna be really hard, but we'll see
All right, you ready? I got it up right here. All right, so super punch out is one of my favorite games
Pretty much ever. I'd say it's in the top 20 top 10. Mmm, maybe top 20. I
Gotta remember how the controls button setting mode. Hold on
All right B is right punch left punches Y and then a is the knockout punch power up is yeah, that's fine
Okay, that's all I need a is the big punch you guys ready? No
Knockdowns. What's the penalty if I fail every time I get knocked down I
For every time I get knocked down what's a good thing to put here? I'm gonna say this game sucks. It does not come on
Every time you get knocked down one stream of tears of the kingdom. Oh
No, no, I don't think so it's not that I don't want to do that
I don't want to give people the idea that if let's say I just am completely wrong and I'm just really rusting
I can't do this if I get knocked down ten times
I didn't even stream breath of the wild ten times every five knockdowns. You need to do that
Do you hate Zelda? No, I just I just don't never was really into the franchise really
Like I said, that's the first time I played Zelda since Ocarina of Time
Just kind of let it all pass by me for some reason. All right
Well, it's not gonna happen here so we can figure it out. It's just I'm I might not even get hurt here
Okay, good. Yay fall down. Oh, come on. Oh fuck. I forgot. That's what that move did
I thought I had an extra second. I thought I had an extra second. He's not getting up. Don't worry
We're good. It's knockdowns not taking damage. I got hit by Gabby J, but it's okay
That's not a knockdown who's after Gabby J. It's that's from when I played with me. All right. Yeah
Bear hugger. No punching is a great rule. What?
Okay, could I had it full health play the Wii one? I did a long time ago
I want to say like a few years like three four years ago. Whoa
At why well, it's happening. Okay, there we go
Bear hugger really showed up and nothing but overalls. Yeah, do you think they'll ever do another punch-out game?
Cuz we got a punch-out Wii and then they kind of just didn't really ever do it again
All right. I have to remember the pattern here
Because you can get caught and I think it's either it starts up or it starts down and I don't remember
I might take a little bit damage here
I actually might put on the other controller for this because the d-pad is on this thing stinks
I thought I almost had it in one hit sit down. Yes. How did this guy not beat Ganon?
Oh, you said I did you say beat Ganon or not beat Ganon? Is the game easy?
Not the first circuit kind of is but this is where it heats up a little
The game is actually it's about just patterns and memorization. See I just remember every single thing that these guys do
I have to catch it because otherwise you die in one hit. Can I catch it? What do you guys think?
He charges at you and he'll kill you in one swing. I don't know follow your heart
We might not even have to we might not even see it. Hold on. There it is. Fuck
I just ripped up my fucking power cable
Challenge is over. I ripped it. Hold on a second. I was a little late
Too bad I got cocky you don't have to do that, but I just got really cocky. It's okay
See you have to do this
You do have to catch him though. Maybe no, actually. Yeah, I got cocky. That's my own fault. I just want to that's one
Tears of the kingdom stream. No, I didn't agree to that. Damn it
I was thinking I was gonna get through that without getting knocked down once the other
Germa beat it three seconds faster than I did. I did better than I did before though
All right circuit to this is
Charlie there's who else is in this? Where's the clown? The clown is really hard
I shouldn't even be alternating swinging actually to the gut so far so good. Oh, all right
This is I remember this he goes this way. There you go. See you later. Got a quick. Oh
All right, that's that's pretty rare. Almost 30 seconds. That's pretty good
31 99 that's way faster than I did it before
Look at a minute 30 from when I did it last time forget what this guy does. He's just like a kick
There's like two or three kicks you have to be aware about the timing on this guy's kind of weird, too. Ah
Shit, that's my fault. He's a heel. Oh, it's down. It's down. Yep. Got it
That'll kill you in one hit by the way. I'm not being efficient either. I should be way more efficient than this
This is sloppy. I should be hitting him
Two or three times before it as you can hit him up to a certain amount of times when you do that like one two
Three four, okay, so do three one two, three swing
Whoa, that was close. He really is go to the games with two buttons
I told you just give me three buttons in a directional and I got it better than before
All right, this guy there's nothing flashy
Uh, he just has a ton of health and he hurts a lot and his timings are a little weighty spits in your face, too
I think it's you have to do down. Let's try it. Yep. Spit. Got it
It is funny how that happens, huh? Oh, no, don't sit. Don't talk now try to catch him there. Oh
Don't be silly
Don't be silly about this
Oh, and the d-pad fucked up. Nice
No downs, that's the hell second circuit. I'm even i'm eating frozen grapes right now. They're goaded
They are so good. I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna go for it
I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna go for it
I'm even i'm eating frozen grapes right now. They're goaded
They are so delicious. Honestly
I actually uh, holly and I tried the
Frozen blueberries that a lot of people are talking about. They're up there too and no joking around
I actually really do mean this if you're actually having trouble getting fruits and vegetables into your diet
It's a it's a great way to do it frozen blueberries and frozen grapes seedless
Red grapes, by the way, I look forward to eating these. It's not like oh, yeah
Like I I have to eat vegetables and fruits about it. I eat like a pizza today
Did I even eat anything good for me? Oh, I got frozen blueberries and frozen grapes in the freezer
You they're like a little treat. You look forward to eating them
It's a really good way to get some um extra fruits in your diet. Seriously
Yeah, and when they come out of the okay, this one's gonna be hard but
Uh when they come out of the freezer
Don't just just chomp on them. Let them sit out for a minute or two
Let them get a little bit softer on the outside
I don't know. Maybe you like it like that
I I like it kind of frozen but just don't bite into them. It's like a popsicle. I forget what this guy does
I have to stop talking. Yeah, he does the triple. That's what it is. Okay
Okay, that usually kills you i'm good
Damn it
I thought he did it twice one more hour of tears of the kingdom. Yep. That thing is brutal by the way
How come I can't block what's going on with that? Usually you can block up. Come on, man
What the fuck
All right, the d-pad on the pro controller really is like an absolute piece of shit
It's one gigantic button that when you press left you press all the buttons at the same time use the joy cons
I actually yeah, that's a good idea
No, I think i'll be fine way worse than the other jeremy by the way
All right. Well, that's all right. It's two downs
No losses though, which are good because I want to
Hopefully do no losses
Okay, aaron ryan, this is this guy has it's all about the lower blocking
He's gonna grab
Shit
You can usually catch him right there. Come on, dude. Here it comes. Okay, I got it
Whoa, you're still going
Cool, we're good
All right. Let me get some help back almost had it again. It starts it up. I think come on
Right. Yeah, this is it. No
Shit
Sit down
three tears of the kingdom
minutes
Looking at it on the nintendo shop store page and you believe it
That's actually I think the harder of all the ones in this final circuit something with the hair is a hair flip
There's a hair flip. I forget which I forget which side it's on. I think it's a hair flip on the left side, I think
Find out
Good. It's a good start. I got full health. I'm good
Oh that was started early, okay, which side is it on?
I think it's okay. It's left and then it's down. That's what it is. I got it
All right, get some help. Whoo
See you later. I did it. All right. We're almost there only two more. That was pretty good. That was clean
Not as clean as uh, uh
Here's the clown
All right clown does this just move with the balls. So it's a bear hugger skin, but forget some things
Yep, it's that other way. They trick you. That's a one-hit kill by the way. Good start
Whoo
How fast is the speed run? It's probably ridiculous. Where did that come from?
All right. Well, we did it. No doubts. Would you fight a 400 pound clown in real life if I had to?
That was way better than the last time I played it. Okay, uh, this is the last boss of the game
uh
technically
This guy
Has a bunch of really awful stuff. I don't know if i'll do it, but i'll try he has this
Spin overhead swing move. They have to duck under like three times. Hi
There it is. Okay when he goes i'm out of rhythm. I thought he was gonna spin shit
Oh
No, I got it. I got it. This guy sucks. He does a little hop too. It's awful
Oh, that's it. Can you tell how frequently i've gotten to the end here? We're doing this by the way
It's rewinding. Is it block? How do you do that? Let me see. Is it I think it's just block up
Maybe it is just up. Let me see you do it again
No
Sometimes he does it three times. Damn it. Yeah, it's already over. I I couldn't beat the final boss and without being down
It's over fine. I don't care
This guy is very hard
Shit
It's so funny. You can see you can just tell when you just get so full just so out
This is a rhythm game and it's very hard look at how much i'm getting hit right now
This i've taken more punches in the last 10 seconds than the last 40 minutes playing this game
It's just a rhythm game. It's like playing rhythm heaven. It's that little left jab or right jab. It's just
All right. How do I block that? Maybe just don't move. That's what it is. Okay, you just don't move
shit
All right, so the reason why I did that because if you lose if you actually get a loss
Uh, you are 100% locked out of doing the final circuit ever
You have to do you have to beat every single
Uh enemy you have to do every single fight without losing the only way you can get the last actual
Um circuit. Oh my god. That was really bad from the last time
So now special circuit is open
Now the reason why I said I could get to here without being downed. Yeah
Really age well when I said that because that's uh, that didn't happen
Okay, so uh, but I get to do this now and this is impossible this is actually like almost impossible
This is very very very hard. Actually when I was a kid
Uh, I only saw this one time i've never actually truly played through this part except I did
In more recent years, but when I was younger and I played this all the time
I it was it was rare to even get here because remember I didn't have a safe state
I do remember this is a really cool fight though, because you'll see watch this
He doesn't want you to do something very in particular
You can't hit him in the face until he gets angry
and he loses composure
and he
and gets mad at uh calamity ganon and uh
You will see
Yeah, my experience with this guy is I think i've seen this guy twice ever
Let's do it. I mean if I cheat, I don't care. Let's see the whole thing
All right, no more talking because I can't play video games talk at the same time. That was weird
Those of you that don't know what i'm talking about while you're playing the next game that you play
That's really like kind of a hard game. We have to pay attention. Just start talking out loud
You're gonna get killed you'll get hit like by everything that the monster does
I forget what's after this guy. Oh, that was a cool move
I can only hit him once here. Come on. What is this? There we go. The next boss is so hard. I forget who it is
Why do I not remember?
Well, let's see
I'm, not even on here
I'm, not on here. I must not have done it
Okay
Please take it easy on a poor old man
What the fuck was that? Okay
Uh, oh my goodness
You have to hit him on opposites
Wow, goodbye. That was that was ugly
So you have to alternate I think maybe I can stand still for that
Jeez duck, maybe I can only do it twice. What about hold on? Let me get that down. What is this? Is it up?
One, two, three
Sideways. Okay. That's one two, three sideways
goodness, jesus
Only two. Oh that kick hurts a lot
Can you imagine having to beat go through the entire game and not lose?
And then get to this guy and win or you have to do the whole thing all over again god
Which way does he go? I guess
The movements are really erratic too plus him having a cane
It's kind of like it's hard to tell when he's gonna swing or punch, but let's see what we can do
Ooh, I had power there. No, I want to get that. You know, I don't
I don't think i've ever seen the end of this game. Who's at the end? I'm, really curious now actually
Okay, well this is the first time i've downed him that's good at least i'm gonna I can get downed once
I should do for the health anyways
All right, this guy's gonna have to play so much zelda
God damn it, man. I don't even know how you would memorize this even playing here normally. Jesus. That's a good opportunity. I'm gonna take it
That's a good opportunity to hit. No, no, no. No, that does not count. That doesn't count either
Doesn't count either that was greedy. That was stupid. So it's up up down down
Let me see the whole thing
Up up up up up up down down down down. Okay
Ouch that didn't count now. I know why i've never seen what's after this guy because I definitely got here even while cheating
I probably was like nah, fuck this. I'd rather go eat like a sandwich or something. Okay, I can end it right here
Let's go. I've never seen this before. Yeah, I physically don't even know what the next fighter is
If you had irl safe dates, what would you try to master a professional sport?
Um, definitely something that with repetition not something with pure physical strength. Hmm
What physical sport?
What could I I don't know?
rick bruiser
My brother may be champ, but only because I let him win really I am the best I have seen this before
How come I don't remember? Okay, let's i'm gonna concentrate
That's weird. I don't like it. Okay, I guess I have to hit him in the stomach there. That was a counter-attack
Whoa, no, it's an elbow. Wait, let's go all the way back shit. God damn it
Doing all right starting out
Oh the counter-attack he does it every time oh, come on, dude, stop
It's up down. Hold on. No, no, no. No, it's your brain just wants to dodge so bad
It's don't move and then up and then left. Okay, don't move up left and then no punch
It's the same. No, it's up up down up up. Why'd you dodge up up down? Okay up
left
Fuck I forgot he does it again
This guy's ridiculous
Sit down at the first down of the second
Imagine save scumming this much. Okay, so that one's down up down
What? Oh, no, it's down up left. I wonder how many kids cried playing this like you have to have cried
You have to have cried right? Like I probably cried. Yeah, I had to have cried shit. Oh, that's a wanted kill. Oh
I forgot again
I'm, just trying not to get so bad shit
Okay, that's two up down left. No, it's down up down up left. Oh my goodness gracious
Even when you know it too. I tried to dodge it. It's like a half second window. I tried to dodge it again
No, no, no, no go back. I made it worse somehow. How did I just make it worse?
Oh, you can hit you on the way down too. Oh, it's like fighting margit for the first time, you know
It's like here comes this right you're dead. Only thing is I can't do this at margit
All right, we need to go way back. So before this went off completely collapsed
There we go, can I block it? Let me see if I can block it up. No, I can't here we go
Tried to dodge it too. All right, let's see what happens. I've never seen this before. This isn't a challenge anymore
Well, no, I mean this is
This is content i've never seen before. So what's after this?
Oh, no
It's just hard mode. Uh
Even with superpowers. I still think I don't think I can beat him
Can you imagine that imagine having save states a magical power and you still can't beat this guy?
so quick
No way. Oh my god
Okay
You have to alternate
He just broke my hand running his safe states actually are really tricky because you're just not ready to fight
It's you there's no rhythm with a safe state. Okay, so he breaks your hand if you punch him in the stomach, so don't do that
holy shit, that was
Immediate whatever it was. It's oh do it. Oh, whoa. He does two. Okay the double follow-up
Then is it duck I wonder I don't know
Please
Oh, how can I not? How did I not hit him? There's so much mix up here. Oh my god. He dodged it
Left up. Yep
Left down up. No, it's down up down up down up left down up right down down
Down, okay down up left
Down up down right left. Holy shit, dude. No, no kids beat this
Up up. No, it's different. He changes it every time
I'm done. That was fun. That was fun at one. I'm uh
I mean at this point i'm just literally gonna be saving state after every punch and that's not even gonna help
Yeah, it changes every time it looks like you can't hit him in the middle of this
Fuck can't even win with cheating. That's how you know. This is unbelievable
He just swings so often that you if you're not in the rhythm it's impossible down up left up down left
No, i'm done. I'm gonna play gold die for fucking an hour
Okay down up left
Does it change I feel like I can't even process that he's doing anything down up left up down
He keeps going. Holy shit
All right, you watch a youtube video if you want to see the rest
I'm, not doing this anymore. That was cool. I've it's cool to see this other guy for the first time ever
Um, this is fun. Let's play gold night. I I mean you you want to do the guy that's that's designed
For you to take like 75 in quarters from you with the arcade. I don't believe so
Imagine okay think of it might be putting quarters in I just put in a quarter right now
By the way, I don't think there even was quarters. This is the super nintendo version
The arcade version was back in the regular nintendo era. Yeah, let's play gold night. That was fun
Fuck this guy. I'm not doing that
I want to play one level in gold night that I remember the arcade version was a different game
Yeah, but it came out around the same. Um era as the nes one, right? Is that what I remember?
I want to play
Gold and I I want to get to level two. I'm not going to play this for very long. I just want to do it
Oh, okay. Here we go
Like mission damn. All right, i'm gonna do secret agent
Neutralize all alarms and bungee jump off the platform. You guys remember this game. I remember this game
Cool
Anything else? Nah, that's it. I just remember it. Do you yeah. Oh, all right good
so gold and I
Those this game auto aims
I don't know
Whoa, wait a sec
Okay, so it's left and right
Left and right the right. Okay, that's inverted. We are not doing that. We're not doing that. Can this be changed?
Okay, there we go upright is fine auto aim is on aim control i'm gonna say hold is fine
Okay, already people attacking me. How do you shoot? This guy sucks at shooting
All right
I love the the death sounds
that like
All right, it's left trigger to shoot I think it's how do you change weapons there we go, okay
All right, we're doing fine
The pencil no, that's the duracell battery. That's the double packet of double-a batteries. Okay. Was there anything up here?
Isn't there body armor or something here? Oh, yep. Give me that
sniper rifle
All right, get out of here
Yep, there's a wall in front of me. Where is the glass?
What?
Is there there's no jump right?
Through this game. I forgot how weirdly this game was controlled
All right, here we go. So left right bumper
And then left stick and then left trigger it's like the opposite of what a game controls like nowadays
All right, get him
Grandma put on the vr helmet for the first time ever
Okay, uh, give me the other gun. Yeah. No, no this thing
Nothing up there. That was a really fast knife. Yeah, it was kind of semi-automatic
I'm dizzy
Yeah, me too, but we'll be all right
Uh, I have to press this button. You have to do a bunch of control changes in the menu to make it feel more modern
Uh, i'll I don't mind I get used to it. It's gonna take a minute or two
Thanks roll. Can't you change this game to be widescreen? Oh great. Why are they not aiming at me?
Okay, we're good. Oh, what's this open that up? Can I I just want to do the facility?
That's the only one I want to play open the facility is the best level in the whole game, especially on multiplayer
This is so epic. Hey, i'll be honest with you though
Um, i'll show my age here a little bit here. This was the coolest thing to ever come out in like 30 years. This was
My fortnight guys. This is the shit that I played when I was like 12 13 14
I am holding i'm moving the right stick which is that's just burned in your brain permanently
What I'm with it was something else. Oh, yeah
Imagine sitting around i'm gonna paint it. Let me paint a picture for you
imagine sitting around a
square
like
19-inch square television
Four people huddled around it
four split screen player co-op
You had the amount of viewing angle
That is on an iphone right now
And we loved every second of it. It's already in here
You're gonna play lies of p. Um
Probably not at least not immediately
whoa
It was from all the way down. Okay. I'm just gonna leave that guy
Now enough of the explosion. I might not even get through this level
i'm in trouble
Isn't this this is the end up coming up right here, right?
There are no saves, uh rewinds in um in this game
Although I could do this
Wait, how do I get to it?
We're cheating. Just want to do the first part of the facility. That's it. I didn't win. Um
What is the there's like a side?
Where do I go? I remember it's like a boat
Oh, yeah, you go this way. Honestly vr controls would be easier
Wait, where is it mission status incomplete? No. Oh, is it because I did the secret agent mode?
Do I have to complete everything other side down here? Just jump off the first tower. Why don't you jump off the dam?
Oh my goodness
Yeah
Holding left holding right stick left and not moving left is like I may as well be playing backwards
This is from all the very first tower. You actually don't have to come all the way down here
It's been a very long time. What's that on the other side?
Wait fake fan
Yeah, let me go. Let me go wake up. Jeremy from when he was 17 and be like, hey, dude
Why the fuck don't you remember this?
Hey, you were 14 25 years ago. Why don't you remember where the bungee jump is stupid?
I'll go tell him i'm gonna go tell him
Yeah, i'm gonna tell him right now. Okay. This is the level I actually wanted to play
Oh god, damn it
Do I actually have to do it again?
Because you have to destroy if you can't just beat it. That's why you only that's why you don't do secret agent first
Nobody told him check this out. He didn't pull the shoot
I just want to do the thing in the facility. It's my favorite level
All right, come down. Oh, don't press that. That's the alarm. Give me that thing. I know this thing is good
I remember using it. No, there it is. I love this weapon. It's like the best weapon
When you get two of these it's so fun
All right. There we go
Hey, there it is. All right best level in the game. Let's go so you can really mess this up a million different ways
Um, we'll see how well I do this, but I remember this in particular doing multiplayer
Uh when you got to be up here hiding in the bathroom was always the most fun thing ever because in multiplayer
Yeah, you could screen cheat but come on in. Yeah, come and get me
I know you're gonna open that door and then you and then all of a sudden you see a proximity mine gets thrown up at you
Yeah, come on get the guy that's over here i'm hiding up here with the golden gun and you were just unbeatable
The golden gun killed anybody. Okay. Here we go
Let's have some fun
He's so shit-faced. It's so hard to control this. How do I detonate them?
Not like that
How do you detonate? I don't know. Isn't it? It's like a different item, isn't it? Yeah, it's this one
Isn't there something in one of these I feel like there's something in right here
Okay, the whole goal with this is you're supposed to get down here
You have to press a bunch of buttons and shit and then you have to get through and find one of the scientists
I don't know. Let's just go. Can we open this? All right, we have to do this quick body armor looks good
We made it through here
Why does it explode for 10 seconds? Yeah, the after explosion is huge. All right now this part's important. I remember this
You I need I think I need your key card. Oh shit. I'm sorry. How do I um, I need the key card
Doesn't he have a key card?
Oh the other doctor
That one right there. Huh? Don't you where do you get a key card? You don't need the key card on this difficulty
Oh, okay. I'm gonna do this because I feel like it's very necessary. Okay. Now, what do I can I get the key card?
Yeah, there's a named character that's in this level somewhere. Where are you guys going? Holy shit. That's a lot of people. Oh
Turn on paintball mode. There's a ton of random cheats you can do
I think you have to beat the game on certain difficulties to unlock them though, right? All right
I'm gonna save it here boy
Um, oh no
Keep this out. All right. So there is
There's a lot of people here. Ah, where are you? I think one of these guys has something that I need
Do you guys have something everybody have a key card?
Uh, all right. Well, at least I saved it. No, no, no, no, no
All right, i'm gonna stay right here just for a second. Not you. There we are. Hey, what's up time to leave?
Dr. Doak, you'll need the decoder to open the bottling room door. Look good luck. Okay. He just gave it to me
I think there's a cut scene here. I have the save points right there. We'll be fine
Oh my goodness go in the door
Not supposed to kill that guy only you knew if only you knew if only you knew for england games for england
Alec, I almost killed myself getting here. Alec half of everything is luck and the other half pure skill
Fate of a fucking secret devil agent. Oh, I have to destroy all those. Do I need the cut scene first?
All right, let's go
Yeah, I know for england. All right, let's go. Come on for england james. Yes for england
Completed are they all just get out of fucking way?
Shit-faced vr honestly. Okay. I'm gonna attack. Should I kill let's save it right here. You fucking idiot. Oh my god
I lose
Can I come over here so I can
Detonate this and not get in trouble don't
I can't help that. He's stupid. I how am I supposed to solve that? I gotta get all of these
Dude how do you beat this? I don't remember being that hard you need to get out of the way
two
three
four
eight
Fuck him who cares?
Yeah, I did it
All right. That's all I wanted to do. That was fun though
Yeah, that's why we're gonna wrap it up. I just wanted to do a couple of these goofy dumb things
How about f zero? What's that?
F 099 what's f 099?
F 099
Is it new?
It's a free thing on the switch
I just don't I'll show you. I just don't understand
Dad, stop dad. You just start at the beginning. I start at the beginning. I what I son I can't fucking shoot that thing
Why not? That's ridiculous. This game's terrible
Dad, if you just didn't shoot at the that's not I don't that thing can't even take damage dad
Why not? I should have programmed that in that's why I I don't understand it
Is that what it's like for you guys?
I have a feeling it is that's fun
F 099. What do I get it? Hold on. Can I just get it here? Should I do it once? Where do I go?
It's just free on the shop. Okay, i'll get it free on the shop. Is it featured or where would it be?
Oh, there it is f 099
Okay
Yeah, i'll do one lightning fast f 0 racing with 99 players. Wow, that actually seems really fun
Yeah, 100. It's free download. Sure. So this kind of works like imagining pac-man
Um 99 and tetris 99
Okay, that's right. It sounds fun
Uh, let me go. Let me go pee one more time
I know i'm getting to the end but i'm gonna pee I have to download it anyway, so be right back