Hi. Well, how do you do? More gold, Your Majesty. Hey, that's exactly the game we're playing tonight.
Welcome, everybody. Hope you've had a swell few days. I've had an interesting few days. It's been
very, very fun. Very, very interesting stuff going on. What happened to GTA? I want to play GTA online
with people, like others, like do like a streamer, a streamer night. I'm trying to find people that
would want to do it because I think it's fun when you bring in like four, like three to four
GTA friends to do it together. So I want to, I want to do it with people, 30 to 50 GTA friends.
But anyways, this is a requested game and it's a game that I got very interested in
because it's a game it's called Majesty for it's an old one. And in this game, it's kind of in the
RTS strategy game style, but there's one, one, one very large difference. In this game,
you do not have any control over anyone in the game. You build your castle, your kingdom,
and you don't get to determine what the fuck happens. Is it an anime? No, no,
it's not. But thank you lunch meat for the five community subs right off the bat. Thanks lunch
meat. And then phylactery lich gave 50 bucks. Both you guys, I haven't even done anything.
And look at this. It's already here. This shitload of money. Thank you for the $50 phylactery lich.
Don't you ever leave us again, Jeremy. We need you. You don't need me. It's been inside of you
the whole time. You don't need me. It's a Star Wars thing, right? Who said that? Yoda? I'm the
only Majesty streamer in the history of Twitch. I don't believe that at all. But let me just make
a tweet and we'll get started. Give me one sec. Okay. All right. So this is the HD version.
Hopefully there's nothing I need to do for this version. I don't think there is.
The thing that I have a problem with in these old games, when they do an HD remaster, they usually
just make you hold the binoculars the other way around. And look at the game. It ends up being in
this tiny little square. And it like everything's so small. It's like looking at the back of a
cereal box. You guys know what I'm talking about? When I say that, you know, when there's a game on
the back of a cereal box, it's an elaborate bunch of shit that they stuff on there. And it's so small,
but they had to put as much on there as possible. That's how I feel when they remaster old games.
We'll see if that's the case. There it is. Let's get the audio on. It's got a nice little little
jingle. What's my favorite? What's my favorite egg flavor? There you go. Here's your cereal box.
This is the back of the Fruit Loops box. No, it's not good. That's not going to be it. This is going
to be bigger. It's going to blow up a little. That's my favorite egg flavor. Yeah. Yeah. Egg.
What are you talking about? All right. Play game. Please enter your name, your majesty.
Um, you're going to have something interesting, right? Am I a king yet?
Well, the crown implies yes. Uh, how about, no, not Jax. Not every character has to be Jax.
How about, um, I mean, like, that's the person that just gave five community subs. We're going
to have to thank him. Thank you, King Ryan Goodstream. Thanks for the five subs. Uh,
I'm going to see this for the remainder of this whole game. So we're going to have to, uh,
sounds like an old name. No, I don't want to do one of those old jokey names like
this. No, no, no, no, no. It's something easy. No, I don't want to write like an actual Senator's
name here. Uh, King Senator. King Senator Jeremy. I kind of like that. That looks good.
King Senator Jeremy. Your Excellency, I offer my most humble introduction.
I am Lord Van Fairweather. I was your mother's most trusted advisor. Why is his pitch going
higher? I submit my services to you in that continued capacity. That was like, it's me.
It's me Cornelius Bartlebus. I forget the name already, but what happened is my voice got pitched
up as I was going through that. I forgot his name already. I'll play the epic quest, the bell, the
book, and the candle to get an introduction to the game. There's three different actors.
Okay. The bell, the book, and the candle. And they are doing the fucking cereal box
bullshit. This is the back of the cereal box. Turn, go, go, go right now. Go get a box of cocoa
puffs right now and take a look at the back. They have like, oh, over here is like the fun dome of
interaction. This is like two word games over here. Oh, can you find the, the, the four, two can't sams?
I've seen this before. This is a secret quest. What was the bell, the book, where the fuck is it?
This is, it's okay. Am I stupid? It's, this is its own game. The bell, the book in the, this one?
Find all the hidden objects. It's the spider. The spider down here. I found tree. The forsaken land,
the barren waste. Quest for the crown. Rescue the prince. The bell, the book. Where the fuck is this?
This is huge. That was it? Quest for the crown, the forsaken land, the barren waste. Secret
quest. Is this the crown, the quest for the crown? Quest for the chalice? Is it this one? You just
read it. No, no, no. I said what I was looking for. The bell, the book, and the candle. Okay, there it
is. Forgive the intrusion, highness, but we've been robbed. Someone has stolen the magic bell,
the holy book, and the eternal candle. Right from under our noses, they were whisked away from the
royal treasury by some scoundrel. We must do something to recover them. They are treasures
beyond value. Okay, so we've been robbed. Somebody stole the book, somebody stole the bell,
somebody stole the candle. Let's go. Goals. Recover the three items which have been stolen from your
palace and hidden in the lairs throughout this realm. No warriors or wizards available in this
quest. Remember, I can't control anybody. What the hell am I supposed to do? All right, so here's our
city guard one. This is the buildings. Blacksmith gnome hubble. Where's the vehicle depot?
Wait, what? What's going on? Is this a spider?
Okay, there are rumors that thieves who stole the artifact from your treasury have fled,
but were forced to hide the artifacts as they left. Find the items before the thieves have a
chance to return. Okay, so find the artifacts before the thieves have a chance to return.
What's going on over here? Guard house? The need and haggis.
Heroes. Okay, so blacksmith rogue's guild. Didn't it say that it was going to teach me how to play
the game? Am I like mistaken or was that like, hey click on this one if you want to learn? There we
go. All right, heroes visit the blacksmith in order to purchase better weapons and armor.
Once you have researched those skills, upgrade your blacksmith and even better items will be
available for you to research. Okay, heroes visit the blacksmith to purchase better weapons. So
once you have researched those skills. Okay, so what do I research those skills?
Level one. Oh, there we go. Guard house. Guard houses host a member of the city guard and can
fire arrows at nearby enemies. Your highness, if our kingdom is to prosper, it needs more heroes.
I'm reading. You just like dragged Ebeneezer Scrooge out of bed before he was Ebeneezer
Scrooge. I'm just thinking of a guy with that fucking hat on with the thing on the top.
And you just put me in the slot as a king. And I'm like, you know, fuck that whole reference.
I can fire arrows at nearby enemies once you research that skill. Use them to protect vital
buildings or far-flung outposts from your city. Hence men also rest at guard houses if they are
closer than the palace. Okay, what are we doing with these things? You'll get it next time. Yeah,
I was like gonna go somewhere with that. Okay, so guard houses can fire arrows at enemies. Sounds
good. You need to peep. Oh, you want better stuff. But why are they just random people coming over
here? And why is the city guard walking around? Is there no these? Is this like another NPC? Is
this like a person controlling this? Or are they just wandering around? All right, where's the next
note? Your highness, if our kingdom is to prosper, it needs more heroes. I know. Inns are gathering
and resting places here for heroes and allow them to extend their range of their wandering.
If you build them outside your main city. Okay, so you want to have inns further out. It's a way
for you to continue to have heroes kind of come in and say hello and say what's up. I have no idea
what that means. I know that means something. Okay, 120 HP, coffers hold 57 gold. Oh, tax
collector. Henchmen, minimum minimum return. Decrease this tax collector's minimum return
amount. Maximum pickup. So this guy just walked around and collects taxes. Okay, cool. What's
down? What the hell is this? Trading posts are a place for heroes to purchase healing potions.
Healing potions. Your highness, if our kingdom is to prosper, it needs more heroes. I know.
I'm gonna try. I need to, hold on. Trading posts are a place for heroes to purchase healing potions.
Build a marketplace near your palace and the trading post will periodically send out caravans
to them. Okay, so you have a marketplace near your palace. We can get caravans to them. Bringing in
a bunch of gold to your treasury. Forget about the random snake ladies that run around. That's
just a problem. They're just, they're like bugs. There'd just be much to watch out for them.
Okay, we need more heroes. I'm working on it. I'm waiting for the next thing to pop up. All right,
what, what do we got? Cast farseeing. There's no wizards allowed here, right? Palace. Who builds
shit? Oh, I do. Okay, buildings. Guard house in marketplace, right? Do we have one of those
already? Build a marketplace. Your highness, if our kingdom is to prosper, it needs more heroes.
Who builds the marketplace? Do the guards build the marketplace?
Peasants at work on site. How long does this take? Oh, I only have one peasant? No, we need way more
than that. Roster. Buildings. Henchmen. City guard. How do I get more peasants? I only have like five
people in my whole town. What? Somebody just like crashed. A new thing is complete. Who just crashed?
Okay, got my marketplace. So then that means that I can... Your highness, if our kingdom is to prosper,
it needs more heroes. Okay, how do I prevent this from happening? Oh, the tax collector. Yeah,
throw the bag of money. Uh, how do you turn around? Okay, cool. Uh, something, something,
your highness, something, something. I need a hero. Recruiter rogue? Why do they just stand
around over here? Don't I have a tax collector? It's me, Roger from American Dad. Uh, is this the
zombie following? All right, so we're not gonna make money. Do I not get to determine who gets
made in ranger's guild, rogue's guild, trading post? Scott the snitch. Scott the snitch is stealing.
Who the fuck is this? Kill him. Get him. He's just taking money from every building.
He's actually doing kind of good. This city sucks. All right, where's my rogue? Don't I have a rogue?
Oh, there we go. I can actually drag this around. All right, get this off. I don't know why this is
even here. Oh, there's the rogue. Scott snitches. My mission has paid off. Hold on, is Scott the snitch
killing things but helping me? Is Scott the snitch the rogue that I just hired? What? Hold on a second.
I just hired the guy and he just went off to start stealing shit. Okay, we need police. No,
sorry, the police are currently dealing with medusas. I need a hero. I need another one of
those things to tell me what building I need to make. Guard house? No, I don't have any heroes.
Blacksmith research. Let's see, level two weapons. I got plenty of money. Ranger's guild,
rogue's guild. All right, I'm going to build like a ranger's guild over here.
Majesty, the local blacksmith offers new services. Yes, I just did that.
How do I get that off? So are you a hero? Peasant one. Majesty, the local blacksmith offers new
services. Scott the snitch. Yeah, this is this dickhead is the one that... Okay, so how do I
tell him to go? Oh, we need more. We need more. Let's get some more. He's a peasant right there.
Let's build another ranger's guild. Okay, this is a message to Mr. Titegold. I'm out of here.
Kill this thing. Did he just win it? There are monsters attacking the kingdom right now.
Killing peasants. There we go. Nice job. Dave the screamer. All right, I like Dave the screamer.
Your majesty, our new building is complete. Spells stats. All right.
All right, there's the ranger's guild. Arranger. Let's get a ranger here. How do I get them to do
anything? Like go explore. I guess I have to build the buildings and see what happens.
Use the flags. I don't even know what that means. Use the flags. Use the lid. This is supposed to
be the tutorial and all they've said was, welcome, you need a hero. What the hell? Okay, good. Get
up there. Let's do what we got. It's you up there. So I can keep them in little windows here. Let's
get another one. If you double click monsters, you get a bounty flag. Okay. All right, Scott
the snitch is doing a pretty good job over here. Is it attacking the caravan? Finally. I killed
something. Kill it. Thank you. $350. All right, deposit that. Are you exploring over here? Oh,
you're doing a good job. Kill it. Nice. I feel like I'm just looking at a top down view of World
of Warcraft. I'm just looking at Goldshire right now from a top down view. That's my fourth tax
collector. How much bigger is this map to not find this stuff? Visitors. Who's even there? Okay.
Seeking. Okay. All right, so Scott the snitch. No, I don't even know what the fuck I just did.
I need like the game manual in my lap right now. Sewer entrance.
Okay, let me take a look at what this stuff even is. I don't even know. Trading posts. So let me
research something here. Healing potions. They need those. We're getting overwhelmed. I need more
heroes. Thank you. Jeeves, whatever your name is. All right, recruit a rogue. Who's in there?
Two peasants are in the guard house right now. I need to find the book. The rabbit and the
candle. Whatever the hell it is. I wish I understood what was going on here. Like,
I'm following him. If I double click on you, I can like follow two people at the same time.
All right. And then they have different things that scan through buildings, scan through henchmen,
scan through heroes. Okay, here we go. Scott the snitch. Okay, I'm gonna keep my spy camera on
Paul the explorer and Scott the snitch. You need warriors. Warriors were not allowed in this
mission, I believe.
What? Is it a rat man? What? This is the tutorial? Yeah, and it's not
tutorialing me anything. I got three notes left. Sticky notes. I haven't been tutorialized at all.
Reward attack flag. This guy's killing everybody.
Heroes are often motivated by rewards offered by the sovereign. Oh, what the fuck? It's just a
thousand dollars to kill this guy. Kill a ten thousand. Somebody will kill him. Yeah, you don't
have to worry about that. My god. All right, so where is this? Okay, I got that concept now.
You got to double click on somebody and offer an amount of money to kill it. Okay, offered by
Senator Jeremy 100 bucks. What does that mean? Offer? Okay, so if you go over here, it's money.
Okay, I get it. Would have loved to have known that like 10 minutes ago. You got to give people
incentives to explore. Okay, so I want you go over here. If you go up here, that's worth 300
bucks. No, that's worth 500 dollars. Whoever wants to explore up there. All right, so who the fuck's
going up there? Who's going to take that bounty? All you have to do is walk over here. Are you going
to take that bounty? That's easy money. I don't blame you. Okay, research these. How do I get
this? Research level two weapons for sale. I can't do that. What else can I build? What's a gnome
hover? I'm looking for three items. Let's go down. Look, somebody needs to. No one's going to claim
this for some reason. What services may help? Oh, it's marketplace rangers guild. Recruit another
ranger. Let's get like five of these guys. You going up there? Oh, you did it. You did it. You
claimed it. Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no. A new building is complete. Here's another 200
bucks. Just go up there and go see what's over in the top left. Recruit a gnome. Extort? What does
that mean? Collect 226 gold instantly for a cost of 100 gold. You just pull it quick. Okay.
Anybody going up here? Let's get a tavern. It's a inn, right? Yeah. There's nothing even up here.
No, I want to, I'm going to put this over here down by this way.
This is, I dig it. Okay, so I kill these things. Somebody kill it. What have I got here? Let's see.
I still don't understand how you get like shit on the main screen here. Okay.
Are they going to be okay? Can they build this down here? It's a bread and brawl.
You can put the explore flag in the fog of war. Okay, that's cool. Um, no, go get this.
Look at all this shit. Is it all taken? It's all empty. Somebody go get this. Somebody get this
fucking money right there. Get it. Open it. No, open it and run.
Nobody's there, but they go, they'll come down here. Peasant six is dead.
Big bits. Oh shit. I missed big bits like a minute ago. This guy's dead.
Sorry, Paul. I didn't want you to go hang out down here. Uh, thank you agent dark
for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits from agent dark agent dark booty.
Dermot can't tell you how much joy your streams have brought me. I have ADHD and you've honestly
been an inspiration for me. Keep up the amazing work. Thank you so much agent dark booty. Uh,
I have it too. And you're seeing in this stream right now how, how I'm dealing with it. So thank
you for the five fucking thousand bits. Really appreciate it. Thank you. Uh, he's dead. Okay,
so I need to do, uh, should I go in the sewer? Indestructible appear as your kingdom grows in
size, grants, giant rats and rat men access to your town. The wild spirit is needed for larger
towns and therefore will not be destroyed. So it just happens because we have too many, uh,
people using the suiting. Okay. I'm gonna say let's go down here. That's worth 500 bucks.
Someone to explore down that way. This person just at the front, kill, kill this fucking person,
please. Just now, right now, anybody. She's just sitting at the front door camping our like newbies
coming out. My services may help. Where are you? Somebody going down there? My services.
Why is Jeff Goldblum in our camp?
Tough fight. House one to build more houses. My services may help range skills. No,
I have everything I can do. Unless it's a, I can research something else somewhere.
He's going down and going down. We have found an abandoned keep and the missing candle. Destroy
the keep and you will recover the candle. All right. I want everybody's attention right now.
A thousand dollars to go in there and get that. No. Fuck that. It's $2,000. Oh shit. I'm getting
over there. $2,000. 3000. Where's Elbrey? What are you doing? Oh, he's, he's shooting at it.
He was like, I was like, where is he? Why is he not listening to me?
Okay. He's going to get this free grin. Okay. What happens if I click on this and I drop it
right before it dies to like a five dollar bill? Who's this? Is this a gnome? What do the gnomes do?
He's going to get it. He's the one annoying unit in command and conquer that you don't,
you're not prepared for. You don't even realize it. Anytime you played like Warcraft or command
and conquer or red alert or whatever. Once the towns got big enough, you could sneak in and just
drop one unit to attack like a farm on the outskirts and they wouldn't even know you were doing it.
And that was the best strategy. Our town is under attack. And they'll be, you have like a
fucking extra large map and you don't even know where it is. You have like five
Citadels at that point. You're just like, where the fuck is this guy attacking?
That was my strategy. Send one guy to attack the bottom of their base every single time.
All right. So I almost got this. What happened to the guy that was, he's running away. He's fleeing
in terror. Somebody will get it. All right. I need more heroes. Can I queue them up?
I need more than two. Well, they keep dying. It's impossible to make the left side bigger.
It's hard to read. Yeah. I know we've got a cereal box scenario over here on the left.
Sorry about that. Guild is full. Guild will be full here. All right. Let's take a look.
What are they doing? Will you attack the things that are outside the door?
Do you still have a $300 bounty? Somebody said, is this just constant noise or am I really high?
Kind of. All right. It's time to, okay. I've had enough of this shit.
We're making it way more expensive to kill these things. They're just running absolutely rampant
in the town. Like you have to die. Everybody focus. Whoever kills them gets $1,000.
Who's even in here? Guild is full. Get out. Are they all dead? Where are all my heroes?
Get the fuck out of here. Get out. All right. Are you guys finally going to do something?
Should have had more heroes. I apparently, who is this? Naked Shrek.
I'm going to lose in the tutorial, but look, I'm going to be really fair to myself here.
This was not, I was not tutorialized at all. It was just like here. I get overrun by snakes
and monsters. One of you guys in chat told me about this. There's so many of them down there.
Level nine is just sitting in there. Arrows, better arrows. Span guard houses to survive.
This is because there's two sewers. I don't remember this. All right. I'm going to have like six
towers. Look, it's already getting better. How much health does this have? This thing's going
down. There's one. Okay. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. Scan through buildings.
Scan through henchmen. Scan through. Okay. So this is just what the camera. Okay. So when I was
looking at this before, I thought this, I didn't know this was like scan through a building.
I thought this was commands I could try to give to this person. Okay. I get it. I understand.
I get it. Scan through reward flags. Yeah. I get it. I understand. I understand. I do. All right.
Double click to zoom to the hero. I can do this too. All right. We go. Is he going to get the
bounty? Kill this thing too. That's a thousand dollars as well guys. I have money.
There's too many houses. Why don't you build a house right here?
A new building is complete. How dumb are you? Why would this be built here?
It's right in front of the gate. This is the equivalent of having your house
directly under the airport. Like right when the planes come out. You're going to hear this like
five, 10 times a day, a hundred times a day. The bridge dropping right next to your bedroom door.
Okay. Tax collector. Is somebody going to destroy this building or what? There he is.
Sylvis Broadview is going for it. Get out of there. Get out of there. It's not worth it. Why
don't you work together and split it? You're not going to kill this thing alone. Get out.
Sylvis is berserking. Are you going to berserk right into the dirt? Wait. Maybe not. Nope. Nope.
Run away. Somebody will get this. This is almost half the money in the whole kingdom.
And you know what? Fuck that. No, that's I can't, I can't take that off. Minimum,
minimum return. Let's go with like 500 bucks. The rat man. What the fuck is happening?
We're about to get the first triforce down here. Well, now that I know what's going on,
the next thing I do will be a little bit easier. I don't really have enough money.
How do you still have a thousand dollar bounty on your head? I don't know how it's impossible.
I'm going to scan through the flags here. Attack flag. No, get rid of that. You won't get your
money back. Oh, fuck. No, nevermind. I didn't know that. Really threw a bunch of shit at me here for
teaching me how to play the game. All right. Join the explorer is going to get it. Trading post. Let's
see. He's going to get it. I think this is like a TF2 server. It kind of is. Yeah. Yeah.
It is level 11 though. Not bad. All right. What about the blacksmith?
No, no, don't attack the blacksmith. Get that off. I want to upgrade more. How do I do better
research in marketplace rangers guild? I don't think I can do anything else. You always need
at least 10 heroes. Okay. Well, I had like five here, but they died instantly when they came out.
Oh, who's going to get it? Is it going to be Feteth the Explorer? Let's see.
Medieval Lemmings. That is kind of what it's like. You're right. All right. We're good.
We have as many as we can have. This thing is still going down.
Let me see. Where's that spider? Okay. Nobody's explored down there yet somehow. Weirdly enough.
All right. Uh, everyone's okay. Kill it. Does it really take three of you? Oh, somebody got it.
Who got it? Who got it? Who did it? Pick up the candle. Pick up the candle. Heroes make use of
many magical items in their quest. Heroes will pick up any items left unattended. Are you sure
they will? Somebody get it. So many voice lines. What is this thing? Oh, Medusa. Okay. We still have
the same amount of heroes, but the roads suck. Somebody graveyard. Here we go. 14 heroes buried
here. Somebody get it. Look, do I seriously have to pay somebody to walk over here? Somebody go
over there now. Here comes the screamer. Somebody please pick this up before I lose my mind.
Why are you afraid of going over here? Get it. Get it. It's a free 600 bucks. You fucking idiot.
I guess I deserve that. I got plenty of money. I need to bring people down here
because I got this one item just sitting there. Just extort the rogue's guild.
Sorry. Uh, there's construction going on outside. I don't hear. I can't even hear what you mean by
this. Research this upgrade. Market day generates sudden revenue, but temporarily closes the
marketplace. Healing potion. Did anybody pick it up? No, of course not. Your marketplace now
serves you better. Thank you. So nobody's claimed that yet. Weirdly enough. Your marketplace now
serves you better. Uh, henchmen. No, no heroes. I want to follow who's like the level mayor,
right? My bar was my bar. There you are. All right. I want to follow you and you.
This is going to be hell going over here. Should I drop the audio? Should I make it like,
maybe is that whatever better? You know what I mean? Maybe it won't be as chaotic and horrible
sounding. That's better. It doesn't sound like four construction yards at the same time.
My ambition has paid off. It's the same. No, it's not. Kill it. Oh, tough fight.
Oh, tough fight. I can't believe no one's picked this up. I'm never going to be able to complete
the mission. Well, it's obviously not top right and obviously not top left. So it has to be like
bottom left and bottom right. Do I have to make this more expensive? 1000 bucks. All right. Come
on, Kevin. Claim it, Kevin. Come on, Kevin. No. Upgrade the buildings. I have been, haven't I?
No, I've been, I've been upgrading the building. Yeah. Wild adventure builds character. What?
Build more hunters guilds. All right. We're going to expand our influence over here.
My services may help. Wait, this is level. Click the arrow. Level. This is like a troll
walking around town. This town sucks. Why don't we have a fucking wall or a gate or something?
Why is this so normal? This should be completely abnormal. Next to the picture. Level. Okay. Level
two. I'm reading the goddamn cereal box. Oh my God. All right. Okay. All right. All right.
We're good. We're good. We're good. Everybody relax. This is, this is the tutorial we're learning.
Oh Jesus. Give me a break. I didn't even know. There was no way I was supposed to tell.
I didn't know that. I don't know. All right. Now we've got some real guards out here.
This is the 22nd tax collector. I've had a new tax collector almost each day.
All right. Who do we got? Message. Message flag. Oh, did they find it? A hero has discovered that
the book lies in this ruined altar. Raise it. Eh, okay. Raise it. No, I don't want that.
A building has been upgraded. We're going for a $2,000 bounty. Go for it. Good luck
to all of you. Can you upgrade houses? No. Okay. I thought that was a dog downstairs.
Okay. Rogues guild. Let's get some, let's get a couple more. Keep a building on fire.
Yeah. Well, what do you, what do you want me to do? I can't put it out.
I need more palace guards. Level three. You need 12 heroes to get to level three.
Blacksmith. Let's do that. Research level three weapons.
Let's take it down. We got broad view. Level 10. Three grand to get that. What happens if you
don't have enough money? What happens if I put the bounty up for? Nice. Look at this shit over here.
How the hell am I going to do that? There's too many people.
My services may help. Look up here.
My armor in the rogue. Arrows, better arrows and all these
build some more trading posts. Your highness, we've improved the god house. Your highness,
we've improved the god house. Your highness, we've improved the god house. Your highness,
we've improved the god house. Who's going to get it? The local blacksmith offers new services.
There's the holy book plus 20 intelligence. Somebody, okay, who picked up the, who picked
that up? Do I know who has that in their inventory? I serve with pleasure. Let's go. What the hell does
this shit do? Statue. What does it do though? This does. I'm gonna put it over here. I don't know
what this is. Your majesty, our new building is complete. Statues raise the loyalty of the
heroes in your kingdom. Okay. Assured that their deeds will not go unrecognized, your heroes strive
to complete their quest with room. Okay, so you need a bunch of statues. So statues make people
more happy and more willing to do what you want them to do. They'll listen to you. They'll hold
up. Let me clear that. All right, let's do what else we got. Temple of Agrilia requires no temples
to Purvis Cryptochrome. Temple of Doris. Temple of, are these like elements? Is this like water,
earth, fire, metal? I don't know. My ambition has paid off. Let's do this one.
Let's put this down here. Temple to Chrom. Not Chrom. Why? What do you mean why? What?
What's wrong with Chrom? Wait, can I not have any? I can't have any other temple. It requires it.
Give me another trading post up here. You can't build any other temples to build Chrom. Well,
whatever. That's fine. I need a garrhouse down here. This is bad. You can now not build any
temples. Yeah, well I'm almost done with the tutorial. I just have to clear the spider den.
Why would you do that? Why are you guys coming all the way down here? No, don't aggro all of
them. Don't you know that's the biggest mistake in Talked Out Goldshire? Don't do that. You're
gonna aggro everybody. Biggest mistake. Level eight. That's why you can tell. You're new to the game.
Don't do it. Oh, he's gonna do it. You did it. You fucked it all up. Sorry, you're like older
brothers not here to power word shield you to make sure that you have fun playing the game
because you're doing so terribly that your older brother knows that he has to fucking play priest
to make to and he's doing everything possible to keep you alive while you just dick around
and shoot at uh like monsters. What? I told you. I told you you got an older brother with you.
Oh shit. I don't want like I don't want Michael to die because he's fucking gonna be sad.
Power shield's on cooldown. Fuck. Just top him off. He's dead. No way you're gonna live.
He actually has it. And all the brother hanging up behind the tree over here casting like greater
heal. What about you? Do you have like a brother playing with you? What are you guys doing down
here? Oh, okay, then brothers out of mana. So comes up and tries to pull aggro. It's all right,
man. It's okay. What happened? Well, you you stood there a little too long. But it's okay. Just run
back. Do you see the mini map? I don't see the mini map. Okay, hold on. Wait, fuck. Okay, let me
move. Let me go in the other room where you are and like do it for you. There it is. The bell has
been located in this ruined shrine. Destroy this shrine and reclaim what is yours. How am I gonna
do this? This is tutorial. This is a fucking tutorial. And you're gonna surround this with
enemies. They ain't enough old brothers in the world to be able to protect me.
Let's go. Oh, he found a bunch of stuff. They're gonna go down there one by one. How many heroes
do I have? I'm going with I'm going all out. We're just recruiting everybody. I serve with
leisure. Oh, right. This thing. What's this? Recruit barbarian. Rage of Krom. Enrage your
heroes with Krom's power for 1500 bucks. You guys get something wrong. You don't like them?
What's wrong with the barbarian? I should just do all barbarians. Makes me stronger. Okay.
These guys are expensive. These things are level one. Why? They're only level one though.
Where are they going? I don't know. Where are they going? I'm not going to click that right now.
Is anybody? Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's going on over here?
By the way, guys, this is a $10,000 bounty on this. 6000 bucks. Who's going to be brave enough?
Level four. Oh, me. I do. Level one. No one's going to go over here.
This is gonna get swarmed. This is impossible. This is impossible. There's no way I'm going
to be able to get this. I need like 100 people. Where is this guy? Oh, here we go. We've got a
bandit here. It's probably going to defuse to leave too. I hope this guy comes over and just
snipes it. Tough fight. Tough fight. Tough fight. No, they're not ready for this. I gotta pull the
bounty. Wait a minute. Come on. You can do it. Send to the barbarians. No, you're not going to.
You're dead. This guy's level three. All right, hold on. I want to see. Keep an eye on that.
And then I want to go to a palace guard. What? Shit. Okay. I have a level 11 in here.
Who's killing the tax collectors? Everybody. I'm going to extort this graveyard with 15 heroes
buried there. They're coming in. Here we go. This is where it's going to get interesting.
All right, let's do it. Let's do it. Rage of Krom. Get it. End the tutorial, please.
Tutorial over. You guys told me not to build Krom. Krom is the best.
Just use this movement speed increase to get over here. Is it just last hit? Whoever gets the last
hit? No, it's spread out. That's cool. That's it. Thank you. Now I understand what's going on.
The bell, book, and candle are back in their rightful place. We also found the thief who
stole them from the castle. A rogue identified as Cherik of Keldurn. Unfortunately, he escaped
while being returned to the castle with a 15,000 gold piece reward on his head. I'm sure he'll
think long and hard before returning to our kingdom. All right, Cherik. Total gold, 55,000,
9800. Almost 985 would have been interesting. Total gold spent. Spent on research, spent on
buildings, spent on heroes, spent on spells. Cool. Visits to Elven Lounge or gambling hall.
What? You can do that? 49 heroes recruited, 42 dead. If I had like no... Look, now I understand
to like keep them leveled up, keep them happy, get some guard houses, make sure there's some taverns,
make those some gambling halls in case they feel like playing a couple of games like working
Keno 157 dead for Henchmen. All right. Cool. No, no, no, no, no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no I want to menu
yeah what I can pick missions what what happened it saved uh it was saved yeah but
what it wasn't our map click on the map click on the map click on the map okay here we go
go. play another beginner quest to learn more about different aspects of your
game or strike out on your own and pick another quest. strike out on your own.
this one's done. okay let's see. I'm not doing anything advanced. I don't care
what you guys say. do the advanced one. do the event not in a million years. okay
let's see. the wizards curse the forsaken land. rescue the prince. I think I want
to rescue the prince. rescue the prince. I'm going for it.
this morning while cleaning out the royal courier pigeon roost a servant
noticed an unfamiliar bird. attached to its leg was a message. it reads I'm
trapped in a tower of an evil wizard. please please please rescue me. my mother
the queen of Val Morgan will richly reward you. scouts confirmed that the
young prince of Val Morgan recently vanished while on a hunting trip. the
reward and goodwill generated by this rescue would do our kingdom well. game
glitched. what do you mean? we heard the voice twice. that's weird. I'll tab
for a second. I think that's what happened. that's weird. all right so this
morning yeah yeah yeah I'm trapped in the tower of an evil wizard. please
please rescue me. my mother will reward you handsomely. okay. vanished on a
hunting trip. here we go. I'm ready. destroy the tower prison in which the
prince is imprisoned to... that's a mouthful. destroy the tower prison in
which the prince is imprisoned to win this epic. use the magic spell of your
wizard's guilt to help you. I'm getting older every day. old people do that shit
and like I always wonder why. even like just you know the person's talking to
you they're like yes I remember when I was your age. it was very fun. and you're
like holy shit how the fuck are you out of control like that? it happens. it just
does. okay here we go. no temples. use the magic spells of your wizard's guild. I
don't know what that means. I'm sure we're gonna figure it out. no temples, non-human
races, or rangers guilds are available. so I can't have temples. I have to have
only humans and rangers guilds are not allowed. rangers guilds are available. no
no they're not. none of this is. okay interesting. let's go. alright I'm ready.
I'm gonna go easy easy. I forget everything. I forget fucking everything.
no I don't. pause it. I don't care. I'm pausing it. cast spells from your
wizard's guild to help find the prince and defeat your enemies. upgrade your
wizard's guild to get access to more powerful spells then expand their range
by building a network of wizards towers. okay so wizard spells, far-seeing,
invisibility. all right let I first of all this let me I've got to just we've
got to get this shit going right right now. get a guard house here. since you
can't hold on. since you can't use rangers to aid you in this quest rely
on the far-seeing spell from your wizard's guild to explore the hidden
areas. okay yeah I get it. okay so I need to get some people here. we need a we
need a we need a warrior's guild. let's get it up there now now now now now now
now. how much is that? far-seeing? okay. far-seeing. do I have to do that? oh okay
okay. how much? your highness if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more
heroes. holy shit that's a lot of money. all right stop counting. how much is this
cast? how much does this cost? okay I got it. I said I get out there. did the rats
are the rats sell hostile? I need a we need an inn. let's get an inn over here.
right here. we got a we are. we already have some shit here. marketplace, guard
house, library. arrows better in this guard house place. research the library.
what's in the library? all research costs are reduced by five percent. pretty sick.
teaches wizards powerful spells. got it. increases wizards intelligence. study
here. we've improved the guard house. increases the intelligence of newly
created heroes in your town. okay. upgrading this library adds a plus spell.
so it just makes everything better. wizards can learn powerful spells at the
library once you have researched them. intelligent heroes may also learn few
spells at higher levels. okay cool. got it. all right. your highness if our kingdom is to
prosper it needs more heroes. I know I know I know I know. your majesty a new building is
complete. guard house. arrows. okay. wizards tavern. I'm just gonna making
warriors. your highness we've improved the guard house. I'm gonna make a wizard. I can make a
wizard. wizards. they're expensive. they're 500 bucks. are they gonna get just
instantly killed? the rats have to be like level one or something right?
wizards. there we go. nice. don't get killed by this. I need we're gonna I'm
gonna just put at least like three or four wizards out here. it's dead already?
you die instantly dead. you only got hit like once. no. all right. I need warriors.
quick quick quick quick quick. all right. can you like just kite them over here?
your majesty a new building is complete. I'm gonna make another. oh this is a
fucking warcraft reference stream. I have to do this. you know this is like when
somebody that's like level 40 comes to Goldshire and just follows the fucking
level one around. from the other. this is from the other faction. just being like a
trolling weirdo. and that person doesn't even know what why this doesn't make any
sense. there's a person a player following me. I have to keep making that
reference. and I'm gonna continue to. and there's a just a fucking werewolf here.
can you do anything else? spells. energy blast. all right. that's you. you are the
reinforcements. that's you. all right. I've had enough of this. 1500 bucks.
whoever kills this motherfucker. oh another tax collector. hey. the city
guard kills this. get in there. more wizards. more wizards. more. more. nice job.
work together. good. very good. that's a lot of money. now go now go spend it.
in the town. we got to get our economy rolling here. all right. level two. I can
do level two. let's go. let's go. go. go. go. no blacksmith. fuck. wait. what's over
here? no. you guys doing good? keep it up. we've got spells. invisibility. farseeing.
let's go with. no. I already have. stop. don't. well don't abandon the one person.
all right. what does this message say? upgrading your marketplace. increase the
rate and amount of money they bring into your realm. be sure to keep up your
income so that you can pay for your spells from the wizards guild. okay.
healing potions. another wizard. get this money. smart. thank god. all right. turn
around. get out. get out. get out. don't be an idiot. 16 gold off. okay. should I do
level two? not yet. not yet. I don't have enough money. all right. the warriors guild is
going fine. I get my blacksmith research. level two weapons. level two armor. what
are we doing over here? library. research. fire blast. magic resistance. train
intelligence. fire. don't really like already have. don't the wizards have fire
blast? majesty. the local blacksmith offers new services. very cool. all right.
let's go. level this up. marketplace level two. guard house level two. your
highness. our research in the library is complete. get this out of here. 500 bucks. kill it.
somebody. creature daddy. I'm gonna go for the bear. did they get it? he's dead. okay.
let's go to heroes. let's change to just have two people down there. all right. so
I got pretty good people here. a market day. sudden cash influx. all right.
guard house is all alone up. all right. we need to build a couple. I need another mage
tower down here. destroy that creature den. let's give it a thousand bucks to get rid of that.
this is good. all right. I need to make some more. I'm gonna make like another blacksmith
tower or something. I don't know what the fuck it's called. you know what I mean. library.
magic resistance. no. no. no. no. no. no. no. I need to get a statue up. right here.
trading post. get it up. right here. that's a lot of money for the war. wow. 5700. wizards
tower. what is that? wizards guild? wizards tower. I don't know what this does. all right. watch
the bears. watch the bears. the bears. the bears. kill the bear. kill both bears. get rid of these.
don't let them just like run absolutely fucking. is this rat gonna kill the rat too? 100 bucks.
200 bucks to whoever kills the rat. all right. what does this do? I'm done for. all right. repair
this. level it up too. all right. I got plenty of. what's going on down here? all right. he's
collecting. what's in that chest? don't do this by yourself. that's a mistake. don't be an idiot.
trading post. healing potions. fuck. I need healing potions over here too. protection rings.
ooh. that's cool.
wizards guild. level two. let's go. good.
I want the bounty flag to be this camera. this camera needs to be just following with the
health care. he's going for it. level two though. that's bad. kill it. together. work together.
all right. get it. take out this creature then. statues there. this is just. oh here we go.
that's a level five right there. good. anything else going on?
watch it. all right. we got aggro.
take it out. kill it.
holy shit. it's one swipe to kill. how could you do that? I mean that was a pretty ballsy play,
but it was pretty. it was dumb. anti-magic castle. okay. I can just cast a lightning
bolt down here. can I? all right. this den is dead. get rid of this one too.
that's where the bears are coming from. obelisk. turn back. okay. how we doing?
how much money do I have? not a whole lot. how do I fucking make some more money?
market day. that was not a whole lot of money. all right. my trading post is here. I gotta get
down here. we have to explore. I need to build my influence. I probably shouldn't have done
level two phallus that quickly. all right. in the marketplace. let's get it down here.
nice job. don't let it kill you. you're like my biggest hero. you're the best hero I think so
far. quick parry. yeah. I gotta get this guy to like level 10. nice. he's confident. he's good.
all right. I need to do. where's my? uh-oh. rat men. bounty. 500 bucks. the person that
kills this guy. quick. he's gonna kill all the peasants. uh. veteran guards. level two armor.
and then I gotta level this up right now. come on. get up there. come on. please. more bears.
marketplace. done.
done. healing potions. I'm gonna be running out of money here. oh shit.
not good. no. no. please. not my levels five and sixes. get over there. quick.
and kill this guy. I'm just doing only upgrades to the uh to armor and weapons.
kill it. marketplace. uh. that's fine. marketplace. good. uh. magic resistance.
train intelligence. increase the intelligence of wizards. what's down here? sovereign. your
marketplace now serves you better. sovereign. a building has been upgraded. don't let him kill
it. he's gonna kill you. kill this guy. please. there's two of these. oh god. everybody get down
here. our research in the library is complete. why? look. everybody's fucking running down here.
good. at least you're protecting your town. come on. no. just please repair it. don't let
it. you idiots. oh my god. build another one. how much was that? how beast approaches. just
go look over there for something. I need more guard towers. yeah. let's go. let's do guard
towers first. guard tower here. guard tower here. he's gonna die. are you not gonna die?
lightning strike. lightning strike. not far away enough. I can't believe you still let.
come on. these mage towers. the wizards towers increase range. okay. he's just still running
around. all right. I need another warrior's guild. fuck. all right. I need other shit. what else do
I need? I have no money. I need like a rogue's guild. broadsword. full plate armor. he doesn't
have any. he has 900 bucks. finally. get this shit built up. your majesty. a new building is
complete. I only have a thousand bucks. where are my tax collectors? tax collector. your majesty.
our new building is complete. no no no no. did not kill the tax collector. all right. minimum
return. he will not return to palestine unless he carries at least this amount in gold. minimum
amount of building must hold before visiting. that's fine. pick up like 500 bucks, man.
holy shit. that was 1300 dollars. all right. don't let this guy die. please
protect him. he's gonna get a ton of money. more gold, your majesty. all right. who we got? level
six. what do you have? fire shield. wooden staff. no armor. why do you have no armor?
what the fuck is wrong with you? level three weapons. level one. you're dead in one hit.
what a waste of money. no. you're just dead. your highness. we've improved the guardhouse.
the local blacksmith offers new services. level three armor. level three weapons.
again. I need to look at this. and here's another one of these idiots. bounty. all right. somebody
has to go this way. we need exploration down here. you're actually not doing a bad job.
that's quick parry. he's pretty good. what's he got on him? the local blacksmith offers new
services. ring of protection plus 10 dodge parry. well, I mean his name is quick parry. so that's
why he bought it. okay. what about... idea. all right. good. you need to stay alive.
don't die here. level seven. don't die. somebody get over here. where's quick parry?
actually holding your own. how many potions do you have? no. no more. no more. come on. come on.
kill it. this guy's level seven. does he have normal potions? he has normal potions. kill him.
help him. you idiot. why would you just turn away? you don't deserve the money if you get this.
fuck. all right. I need... I got 2200 bucks. that was my best mage. yeah.
do I get the money? okay. I need another warrior. level three. I'm going with... I gotta get more
armor. I need another trading post too. how much money does this put out? I'm doing a trading post
down here. is that stupid? is that dumb for me to put like another trading post down there?
is that dumb? yes. okay. that's dumb. it's very dumb. all right. because it has to be near one
of these. right. I'm gonna do... oh god. how much money do I got? let's see. all right.
quick parry's going down here. keep exploring down here. I need another wizard's tower over
here to do like the... all right. you know what? just go look over here. just go down there.
have you? veteran guards. future guards are tougher out of here. good. warrior's guild.
that's upgraded. call to arms. oh! that's helpful. that's really helpful. here they go down here.
we're looking for the prince, right? they should kill this. at least I hope they do. where are you
guys going? I like this team here. level seven. level six. get that bear. don't do it alone.
don't do it alone. oh. he was going to get the bounty. shit. okay. well. go explore. how much
money do I have? 5,700 bucks. I wanted to do this, right? research level four weapons.
and I'm doing another... we're doing another inn over here. so they hang out over this way.
and also I'm gonna do a... a rogues guild over here. get out of there quick parry. bad move.
he's actually pretty fucking unstoppable. the local blacksmith offers new services.
uh yeah. quick parry unstoppable. he's doing great. he's so dead. no. he's just fine.
he's gonna get this. don't let him snipe that from you.
I'm bored. your majesty. our new building is complete. get it quick parry. it's yours.
you're the best of the whole team. get... just collect the bounty so you have some money. get
that bounty. get it. okay. you got 200 bucks. good. quick parry. quick parry. you're kind of
concerning me though. I don't want you to run into death. he is kind of unbeatable though. although
two bears. I don't know. I can't tell him to leave. he's gonna do his thing. okay. um. what the fuck
do I want to do? another guard house? let's put in the guard house here. I can't put it anywhere.
come on. I need it like over here. right here. this is bears walking around. all right. what
have we got? okay. good. rogues guild is here. upgrade it to level two. I'm gonna build a guard
tower down here. guard house level three. guard house level three. I want another guard house
down here. looks good. looks good. level four armor. get it. I fucking love rats.
okay. marketplace level three. teleportation amulets. pretty sick. your majesty. our new
building is complete. your highness. our research in the library is complete.
majesty. the local blacksmith offers new services. give me your money. sovereign. a building has
been upgraded. all right. I'm gonna put a wizard's tower down here. they're just going. they're going
right from the guild into the inn. these guys suck. dumbass rogues. all right. so this is level
three now. I just went out and got a shake shack burger on your recommendation. and what do you
think? pretty pretty great, right? I would say that's... I can't wait to hear your review.
this is a terrible place for that to be. all right. level three. I need 12 heroes. these guys are
all the way down here, huh? they gave me... no. I'm not gonna say that out loud because it's bullshit.
sovereign. our marketplace now serves you better. I'm gonna put another wizard's tower down here,
right? can I do that? it has to be like within the distance of this. you can go down here.
that might have been really dumb. I don't know.
quick parry. just farming levels on bears. not a big deal. has to be in range of the guild tower.
okay. so then now that this is here, I can do this, right? yeah. well, nothing over here.
nothing over here? well, let's get down to the right and enchant the tower. you can make it a
turret. oh, shit. let's go down here. 300 bucks. 400, I guess. and then like 200 bucks to go down
here. oh, that's nice. that actually works. I'm just gonna make like... okay, I gotta build something
here. I gotta have something right here. I don't know. another wizard's tower, maybe?
quick parry's level 10. yeah. he's gonna be... he's gonna carry everybody.
there goes sharp wood. where's quick parry? I want to always be following quick parry.
it's the second one. quick parry is hanging out in the inn right now. okay. just always have a
camera on quick parry. and he has like a teleportation ring. oh, creature down. get it.
kill it. well, you got... you did what you were supposed to do, but I didn't have to pay you
any money, so that's good. trading post? down... where? down here? that's actually not a good
idea. let's see what we got. put it close to one of the guard houses? oh, fuck. who just died?
that was in quick parry, right? fuck. get those taxes. more. more money. all right, quick parry's
going down here with his like... he made... everyone wants to follow quick parry because he's just so
good. how much... how many potions does he have? five. you need more than that, don't you? fuck it.
get him out of here. this is as far as it can go. we'll go to level three. not yet. need more. rogue
skilled. five is the max carry for potions? oh, okay. makes sense. the burger was good, a little
too salty. definitely an s-tier though for fast food. oh, yeah. yep. we got the official review.
fries kind of suck. yeah, that's... they do.
all right, i can almost do level three. what are we doing down here? oh, look at this fucking party
down here. keep going. i can do... i'm gonna beat it right now. stay together. take the whole thing.
ash house in vegas was great. i'm so happy that somebody ate there.
quick parry gonna go and just kind of take this whole thing by himself.
go rescue him by yourself, dude. he even helps out his teammates. how do i keep this guy around
forever? uh, ash house or gogo in the link is... the burgers are just unfucking believable. the
food's unbelievable. it's up in 24 hours. if you're ever in las vegas, do yourself a favor
and eat that. just eat at ash house or gogo. it's like the best fucking... like at least
late night restaurant in vegas. uh, where the hell is this prince? okay, i'm gonna build down here.
this... we kind of cleared this out. let's do, um... there's an inn here. let's do... can i build
another, like, citadel? like, i can't, right? level three, let's go. do your best jay Leno impression.
oh, okay. uh, okay, recruit rogue. i got pretty much full on all that. marketplace is good.
beast approaches. what do i want to build down here? another... i'm gonna build another wizards
guild. or a marketplace. yeah, fuck it, let's go. just, like, get it, like, right here.
fairgrounds? all right, hold on. royal gardens? i need a wizards tower. i need some, like,
i can't. i need a wizards tower. no, it's so expensive. i need a guard house here.
keep quick parry down here. uh-oh. oh, shit. what is this? oh, fuck. that's a minotaur.
quick parry, get him! both of you together. work together. that... i haven't seen that before.
come on, quick parry. do it! oh, fuck. he's really strong. quick parry, run away!
run away, quick parry! you can't... not gonna be able to do it. oh, no, he has healing potions.
all right, good. keep it going. protect this area, quick parry. try to keep the marketplaces
close to the palace, because the tax collector needs to get all the way to them. that's true.
all right, the peasants are down here. let's do a mage guild tower. Your Majesty,
a new building is complete. no, no, no, no. stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
let's do a... no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. a... an inn. put an inn
down here. quick. come on, come on, come on. stay, stay, stay, stay. it's down here.
I'm gonna do another an inn. I'm gonna do a trading post. That might be dumb. I
don't know. Statue? We're building a whole other town down here. Wizards Guild
right there. Got it. Creature Den. Get rid of that. Got the inn. Nice. Now we can hang out in
here. Got a guard house. Put those arrows. All right, this is gonna be a victory
here. There's so many bears down here. I got it. Trading post. Complete. Wizards
Guild. Complete. Let's get some wizards. All right, I'm almost out of money. Creature Den.
Get that for 200 bucks. 300 bucks. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. What the hell are you guys
doing? This better save. This is gonna crash my game. All right, what the fuck are you doing?
What are you guys spamming? Piss on me. Piss it. Piss in my face. Do it. I'm fine. I can hold my
breath. The second I start to smell some pee, I can just boink. I don't know what this is. What
is this? This is on camera. Piss on me. Piss it. Piss in my face. I don't know what the fuck this is.
What's the con- I mean, it's clearly on like a stream, but I don't know what the context is.
This is probably a deep fake. Do it. I'm fine. I can hold my- Is that a deep fake? It might be a deep
fake. Breath. The second I start to smell some pee, I can just- No, this is from- That's a- I
think that's a deep fake. You tried though. That sounds like something I would say. And maybe. It
depends on the context. Does anybody know what that's from? It was from Super Fight. Oh, okay.
That makes sense. Yeah, Super Fight was you had to come up with insane scenarios as to why your
character would beat the other person's character. So still no sign of this prince. I don't know
where the hell he is. Context being behind you wanting someone to piss in your face.
His superpower was probably like pee. Can I keep exploring down here? Find this prince.
There's a hundred dollars in it for you. Okay, I'm gonna do- Can I do Farsight from here? I need
one of those hands out of the ground. Halt! Where's um- Quick Perry is over here. Just hanging out.
Alright, let's uh- Somebody kill this troll, please. What do I need? What do I need? I need to kill him.
He's gonna cause a problem. Extort that money. Alright, now I'm gonna do a- What the hell is Fairgrounds?
I'm just gonna put it over here. I don't even know what it does. Set the agenda for royal tournaments by
choosing magic, melee, archery, or combo. Heroes may purchase training to enhance their abilities.
So it's just like a training ground. Can you do an impression of Elmo impersonating Seth
Rogan impersonating Beetlejuice impersonating Tommy Wiseau making fun of Dan Aykroyd trying
to sell you crystal skull vodka? What at home? What is it? What does it say again? I don't know
what that means. I'm not gonna do that. Anyways, let's go down here. Let's get up wizard 2.
That's too much to think about. My brain stopped comprehending what you were saying after
the word Seth Rogan. That's it. I don't know. Alright, where is this prince? I've explored
everything. Alright, you know what? We're making it really worth people's while. Get over here.
Let's go. 1,500 bucks. Who's on their way? Where's Quick Perry? Message. Oh, there it is. Where? Hold
on. Did I skip 1,500 bucks for no reason? There was a message flag. Wait, wait, wait. Where is this?
Oh, there it is. Alright, release the prison. $2,000 to the person that can take this now.
Quick Perry's just gonna do it by himself. Well, hold on. We got level four. These guys good.
Quick Perry's gonna just take it all. Get in there. Save the prince. Sick. He teleported behind
the bear. That's some next level plays by Nelson Quick Perry. This is a victory writer.
Do I have to bring him back? Here's the worst part about this. I could have finished this
mission in like five minutes if I had just gone down over here. It's right next to the town.
I went in a full horseshoe around. That's kind of bullshit, but whatever.
The obelisk was a hint too. Was it? I kept seeing it. Turn back. Oh, it was one of those stupid
this is the evil lair. Turn back. Don't come into the evil lair. Promise nothing bad over here. It
was one of those scenarios. Alright, we saved the prince. The prince is a rat? We saved the
rat prince. Majesty, your heroes have returned the prince of Val Morgan to his kingdom.
A caravan from the queen of Val Morgan now waits at our gates. Cool. The treasures it carries are
most glorious to behold, but more important is this brief note from the queen herself. What was
he saying? She writes, my thanks for the recovery of my son goes beyond any material reward I could
offer. Your compassionate leadership is an inspiration to all of Ardenia. That was
pitch shifted. It was. Clip that and just listen to that again. That last three or four sentences
were a little higher. Strange. Getting better. The last time I had 47 recruited heroes and
42 of them died. Now I've been much more focused. Standing buildings, gold balance, okay.
All right. Quick carried. Let's see. Yes. Senator Jeremy's fine. Nice. Now try another quest.
Advanced if you haven't yet. Don't tell me to do that. Oh, I'm not ready for advanced. I still
don't even know what half the buildings do. Do it. No. Look at this one. Expert. This one's beginner.
Valley of the Serpents. Vengeance of the Lich Queen. Put a bounty on Quick Perry so everyone
has to attack him and he solos everybody. Put like a $50,000 bounty. Okay. Oh, the dark forest.
The wizard's curse. Now that sounds really boring. Quest for the crown. Quest for the
crown. I'm not ready for this. Not ready. I'll try it. I'm not ready though. An enlightening
discovery, your highness. The crown of Sidrian, the long lost symbol of your family's power,
has been located. It's being held in an evil fortress on the frontier. The recent waves of
monster attacks have left your people dispirited. Reclaiming this item will doubtlessly boost your
subject's faith and renew the support of your family's house. I greatly urge you to take
advantage of this unexpected opportunity. Okay. So we have to go get the crown. Find and destroy
the lair that the crown rests in. Pretty simple. Pretty simple thing to do. Okay. Let's go. Let's
go. No fucking around. Right back. Get a ranger out there. Were there any stipulations? In the
name of the sovereign. Market. Immediately. Blacksmith. Immediately. Level two weapons.
Immediate. Wizard. Immediately. Rogue's guild. Immediately. Warrior's guild. Immediately.
Hurry up. More. Get him out there quick. Now. Okay. This is already, I'm already dead.
Majesty. Oh my god. Blacksmith offers new services. Oh my god. I didn't know that we're
gonna be here right now. They're already, this is, is this possible? Is this possible? This is
impossible. It didn't even get 30 seconds. What the fuck are you supposed to do about this? How
are you supposed to beat this? In the name of the sovereign. It offers new services.
Uh. Um. In the name of the sovereign. What the? Um. Uh. In the name of the sovereign.
Why, what happened over here? Who, who sprinted? Somebody was like, I'm gonna get away from the
town. I think what's left or right? I don't remember where I'm lost in the forest. I think
it's the left here. Oh shit. I'm back in town. I just lose. Uh. This is interesting. So what
do you, how do you do this? Um. It's not over yet. In the name of the sovereign. Your majesty. A
new building is complete. I'm good. Let's go. Your majesty. Rebuild. Rebuild everything. Uh.
What do I need to rebuild? I don't, they killed, they killed everything. Um. I don't have any
money I used to every cent. Where's the tax collector? Your marketplace now serves you
better. Uh. Oh shit. Here comes another one. Okay. It's no way. It's too hard. Um. An inn?
Royal treasury is nearly empty. The royal treasury is empty. They just keep coming.
I don't think I'm gonna be able to do this. I'm gonna have to restart it. An inn? Well,
it doesn't, you don't have any heroes. Oh fuck. Um. I don't have any money.
They killed everything. All right. Redo. Redo. Redo. Your majesty. A new building is complete.
I have to immediately just start melting everybody. No. Restart. Here we go. Right off the bat.
Bingo. Wizards guild. Right now. Quick. Another one. Hurry up. Go. Because I'm gonna be like.
Oh. No no no no no. Shit. What do I need to, immediately. Uh. Okay. Um. Heroes. And then zap
the fuck out of everybody. Anybody that comes over here. Just, just.
Who's left? Anybody else? Okay. Where that, coming from the bottom too, right? More.
Again? All right. I've got no more money. I don't have any more money. Oh my god. I'm out of money.
I don't have any more fucking money. How the hell are you supposed to do this? This is like
30 minotaurs that come up here. I don't even have money to do this. It's over.
Get out there. It might not be completely over. Hold on.
Just raise taxes. Actually this is not. If these guys level up down here.
Call to arms. Come on. Get everybody back here. Right here. If they can level up. If I can take
this for a minute. Where's my tax collector? That's okay. Level four. That's not terrible.
All right. Hold on. I need to build a. Where's the blacksmith? Level three armor. Level three
weapons. And hopefully these. The warriors can carry it. Where the hell did they go?
They're all in the inn. Just sitting there. Get out of the inn. Inn. I need a. No. I need an inn.
No I don't. What do I need? A guard house? That's not going to do anything. What is that?
What is that and why is it here? Are they going to be able to kill this?
No way man. No way. You get that. This is too quick. Too fast. Too happening.
It happened way too quickly. How are you supposed to keep up with this and not lose all your money?
New building. You just get overwhelmed and you have money but. I wonder.
I feel like this is like a puzzle level where you just need to do something in a very specific
order. All right. We're not doing this one. Let's go to. How the hell are you supposed to do that?
For the slaves. Quest for the magic ring. A deal with the demon. Wizard's curse.
I'm not the beginner. Should I? Yeah. We're doing the wizard's curse. I'm not going to skip.
Great tome is beyond measure. You and your realm must now pay a price for its loss.
Until such a time as sufficient good deeds have been performed I curse all the dwellers of this
land to be as stupid as the dead. We can have a permanent debuff. Okay hold on. There are two
different ways to rid the curse. Method one. Arrest the hooligan who stole the book of spells. Return
it to the wizard and then perform whatever the wizard deems sufficient good deeds. Method two.
Destroy the angry wizard. Your heroes are cursed so they won't act like their regular selves.
Wizard's guilds and temples aren't available in this game. Arrest the hooligan who stole the book.
Okay. Who stole the book? In order to guide your kingdom to prosperity and shed the wizard's curse
you have two options. Either find the idiot hooligan who stole the book and then perform
what the wizard refers to as good deeds. Or confront the wizard and destroy him. Send all
heroes to arrest all of the realm's hooligans so they can be detained and searched at the palace.
What? Okay well we need we need a marketplace. We need how much money do I have? 13,000?
I serve with pleasure. How do I um how do I question? Not question um your highness let's do
if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes. Let's do warriors guild. Warriors guild rangers
guild right next to each other here. Where are the hooligans? Actually I want two rangers guilds.
I want a bunch of rangers in due time apparently. All right so your majesty a new building is
complete. Healing potions are important right off the bat. Let's go with a inn as well over here
somewhere. Your marketplace now serves you better. How do you detain somebody? The heroes will. Okay
okay rangers guild let's get a bunch of rangers. Your highness if our kingdom is to prosper it needs
more heroes. I know that's what I'm doing. A new building is complete. Your marketplace now serves
you better. There's the tax collector. All right go find some thieves. Explore. Your majesty a new
building is complete. Let's also put an inn up. I'm actually gonna have you on camera one and you on
camera two. What's wrong with them? Oh right they're like idiots right? They don't they're
stupid right? There's something wrong with them. Yeah they don't listen to me. They just like kind
of walk around in circles. All right let's get a blacksmith over here. Yes ruined keep demon wood
150 gold in there. Tax collector. Uh oh. Uh oh. That guy looks pretty dangerous. I need some
guard houses. How you doing? He can't can he not see you? I want another one down here too.
Don't do anything stupid. Don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't do that.
What do the gnomes do? I haven't figured that out yet. Let's see. Recruit gnomes. Additional gnome
hubbles are automatically built as you recruit gnomes. Destroyed hubbles will be rebuilt
automatically. So just they just keep going all over the place?
That's cool. They just help build stuff. That's cool. All right let's get another
building is complete. What's that blacksmith? I need to get better weapons.
They're super fast. That's cool. Anybody level one level one? Finish building this. What are you
doing? I don't even know what's happening over here. There's more of this shit over here. All
right. Your majesty a new building is complete. Quickly come on. Finish the blacksmith.
Where are these peasants? What are they doing? Your majesty a new building is complete. Your
highness we've improved the guard house. Your highness we've improved the guard house. Your
majesty a new building is complete. All right sewer's here now. That's not great. That's not
good. Your highness we've improved the guard house. Your majesty. Nice. All right level four. Not bad.
Don't die. Don't get yourself killed. Now I need that blacksmith. Let's go. A perfect game for
Jerma. No micromanagement at all. You just like let people do whatever they want to do.
He's actually pretty fun. Your majesty the local blacksmith offers new services.
Keep it up. If they just did just stop running to randomly play. Come on. You're only level four.
Would you have any potions or anything? Nothing. So don't go up here. Your majesty the local blacksmith
offers new services. Thank god. You're not an idiot. Top five. This map is pretty small. All
right. So let me build. I serve with pleasure. I don't have an inn. Who died? Somebody's dead?
Unwelcome guest. Who died? Your majesty. Sovereign a building has been upgraded. Tax collector. All
right. Let's let this guy's got to go. He's down here too far. Somebody kill it. Friendly lodge up
here. Your majesty a new building is complete. That's too tough for me. At least you're smart
enough to know that. We've got to get rid of this thing. No the level one is going to go and fight
it. No. It's just sitting outside the door staring at us. Oh get these. All right there's a hooligan
right there. Go get him. Open these treasure boxes. Guess that's the guy right there. Collect him.
There he is. One of your heroes has arrested a hooligan. Maybe this is the subject who stole
the book. He's on his way to do your palace to be interrogated. Nice. Hopefully he doesn't get hit
by like a rock. We're good right? Is it him? I want to like keep my eye on him. What's going on over
here? He's being leeched of levels by what? Okay in the palace. Who's in there? What's that ring
thing? Was it him? Oh what? Another person arrested. Get him in there. So this is the second
person we've arrested. Who is the one? Who's the illegal guy? All right let me focus on this again.
Go to the blacksmith. Get uh level three weapons. Message another one. Arrested another person over
here. They're all on this side. Explore over here. They seem to all be like hanging out over here.
Majesty the local blacksmith offers new services.
How are we doing on this? Good. That's not good. That's pretty bad actually. Get rid of that now.
That's scary of enemy. 700 bucks kill it.
New services. You have arrested every hooligan in the land except one. The other hooligans have
confessed to his whereabouts. Unfortunately he has learned some spells from the spell book
and is not likely to return it without a fight. Where is he? Is this him? Is he level 10? Wait
he's just like coming up to the city. Kill him. What is he dropping? He's dropping like a nuke on
us. Oh my god. A thousand dollars to the man that kills him. Do I have anybody that's like
level five or 10? All right here we go. 1100 bucks kill him. My services may help. Oh no
and a rat just came out. Does everybody get on him? Level four. Level four. Level four.
Why would you not attack the guy that's over here? Get him. Get him. Kill him.
He's learned a few spells. Got it. Get the book. There it is. Now what? Now what do we do?
What's going on? I'm confused. Do we have to return the book? Wooden sign. Peasant. What's
a peasant doing over here? All right get rid of this. Fancy iron sign. Okay. How do I give
him the book? That's a trader peasant. What do you mean trader peasant? Is that a trader? I don't
have enough money. I need more like uh I need a trading post right? I wonder if I can no no no
don't attack it. Now that you have recovered his spell book the wizard who cursed your kingdom
demands that you perform adequate good deeds in order to atone for your citizens blunders.
There is a peasant who has been taken captive by a few crazed werewolves. Free her and dispel
the curse for good. That's her right there. He's almost dead. Level seven. How do I free her?
I serve with pleasure. Call to arms. Get everybody in now.
What do we how do we save her? Um what do we do about this? She's just walking around the town.
Kill the werewolves baby. All right well don't nobody kill her.
I'll get to build it again. All right here we go werewolves. We're not ready for this yet.
I need some more level heroes but you're the only one that's worth anything right now.
You just keep exploring. I'm gonna destroy some of this shit over here.
Where's the um building has been upgraded. What the fuck is the we gotta wipe out some of this
trash down here. Yeah ruin shrine. Get rid of this. Okay I need some more uh I need more warriors.
Some more rangers. Some more maybe some rogues. Getting rid of this creature den too. My services
may help. Level four armor for that first level four weapons. You're gonna take that on yourself?
Okay good. How many werewolves are there? There's probably like looks like four or five.
You're not doing too bad. Somebody died. Um palace is really expensive. Majesty the local
blacksmith offers new services. All right level four weapons in armor are available.
I didn't even I'm just gonna recruit like five ten gnomes. Just bring them out here.
Uh oh. House is full. House is full. Those things aren't as dangerous as I keep thinking they are.
A local blacksmith offers new services. Level seven. This guy's just been farming this building
and leveled up like three times. All right uh marketplace down here. Trading post. I don't
know how I need a trading post. Trading post you need to needs to be close right.
Let me look at this one more time. Here is my purchase healing potions. Caravans periodically
depart from your trading post bringing gold to your marketplace. The more further away the more
gold it makes. So so like if I put it all the way down here then it'll be a lot of money.
So you want your marketplaces to be close but you want your trading posts to be far away.
Well level nine get back. Don't kill yourself here. Don't like get killed.
Teleport back to town. All right. A new building is complete. Take this out. 200 bucks.
All right. Your trading post now offers healing potions.
Always upgrade your marketplace level three as soon as possible.
Just tech. Yeah that's true. All right trading post is here. Another one of these uh
the gnomes are actually kind of cool because they just they kind of just like run around
aimlessly in random places and help. So that's cool. I'm gonna keep as many of them as I can.
100 bucks whatever kills that. All right uh I think it's time to go and kill the werewolves.
All right. They're gonna kill this. Oh shit. A level seven died here.
Why would you aggro the tree when just kill this? Don't kill her.
1900. I need to get this level three. I'm on my way. Yeah they're doing all right. After this
I'll have a couple of leg level nines. How beast approaches. You idiot. I knew that was
gonna happen. I knew that was gonna happen. I just knew it. All right. Now here we go.
300 for you. 300 400 for you. 400 for you. Go for it. Take out the werewolves. Do not attack this
building. That would be a very big mistake. Heroes can be resurrected if you build a mausoleum.
Really that's cool. Get out of here. I mean that was a lot of money but I haven't been able to do
that the whole game. Oh shit. Too much confidence. Too much confidence. How many healing potions? No
more healing potions. Why did you do this? Level 10 is about to die. Oh man. Get out. Don't be an
idiot. Don't be an idiot. I did it. I did it.
Back in storage. All should be well.
That was a pretty good Disney goofy thing.
All right cool. My ladies it's good to see you again. As you're well aware
Ardenia's heartlands have flourished under your steady rule. Indeed your leadership has ushered
in a new era of prosperity. Ready for expert. However the untamed frontier of the northern
reaches remains a haven for chaotic forces that still threaten our fair land. It is my council
that you begin a northern expansion to dwell these agents of turmoil. While this adventure presents
great challenges it offers even greater rewards. I'll now take my leave majesty so that you may
consider this undertaking and decide where to begin. So here's something that I'm not I don't
really understand. So am I getting something for doing this? The rewards will be in my or is it
just missions? Because is there a reason to do anything? It's just the campaign okay. Well
let's try another advanced one. Hold off the goblin hordes. I don't like those ones.
Trade routes. Clash of empires. Legendary heroes. Rise of the rat men.
Sovereign the rat men grow bolder day by day. Their numbers appear to increase and strange
new sounds can be heard issuing from our sewers. Rumors have reached our ears of a new ruler among
rat kind. I'll road it with a taste for surface conquest. We must be vigilant against a potential
rat men invasion. If they choose to strike we must target their new leader. Without their ruler the
rat men will not be able to maintain such an onslaught. So destroy rodent the rat king and
all broken sewer mains in the realm. Now I get to be the giant rat. So we gotta kill rodent the rat
king. Look at all these sewer entrances. What? There's a ratapult. Oh my god um level two level
um elven bungalow. I need some guard houses I think. Embassy.
Is it gazebo? I don't know what any of this shit does but look at all these
sewers. Gazebo. Heroes may rest here for a time. Okay fountain. An extra tax collector has been
enlisted to your service. That's pretty good. And then what was the other one? Your majesty
a new building is complete. Elephant bungalow. Your majesty a new building is complete. I don't
want to blow all my money here though. Fill the sewers with lava. I could. Your highness
we've improved the guard house. These guys just. Your highness we've improved the guard house. Get
rid of it. Your majesty a new building is complete. I have so many buildings. How many buildings do I
have? What the hell? Holy shit there's a lot of stuff going on here. Your majesty a new building
is complete. There's a sewer here. The sewer entrance is here. Uh. Majesty your trading post
All right this is what I wanted to say. This is why I did this. A local blacksmith offers new services.
Oh damn it. What is that? Elven. Your highness we've improved the guard house. Elves doubles the amount
of gold generated by your marketplaces. An elven lounge will soon be built in any settlement
containing an elven bungalow. Okay that sounds pretty good. I need uh what do I need to do here?
Are the elves good? Yeah I'm just gonna fill this place with elves.
What's wrong with this person's voice? Are we taking this out? Get rid of this. This is like
the sewer main. Okay I need to do what we got here. Arrows arrows arrows. You uh.
Uh. I need to. Shit.
There's so much going on. There's two. Okay the rats just all came up.
Is this the guy? Where's the guy I have to kill? Rat man champion.
Rat man shaman. This is really bad. Very bad very bad very bad. Um. Uh.
Where are all my rangers? I need the big warriors. Magic bazaar marketplace mausoleum outpost rangers
guild. Temp. Oh there's a lot to look at here. Warriors guild. I'm dead. There's no way I'm
gonna do this. This is an expansion level because it makes sense that I don't know what the hell
any of this stuff does. Elven lounge. I think I'm gonna lose unless I can. What's going on
over here? Midbit is all over the place huh? Probably shouldn't have had the bounty on that
but that's where they came from. Yeah this is game over.
This is game over. Fuck. Um let's see. Okay let's go quick quick quick quick quick quick quick.
What do I want to uh. Let's do um warrior guild. Like two of them and just build like fucking like
10 people right back quick. Hurry up come on. Your highness the elves wish to join our prosperous
kingdom. That's fine. All right what's up over here? Ratmane with the houses. Blacksmith research
level two. Trading post research healing potions. Where's the first spot they're gonna come out of?
Royal gardens. What the fuck is this? Heroes may meditate in the royal gardens to gain a beneficial
enhancement. Gold generated from the increase in water. Your trading post now offers healing
potions. Majesty the local blacksmith offers new services. Hurry up go. Temple of temple of crom.
Right here. Your highness. Come on get up there. If our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes.
Majesty. I know. The local blacksmith offers new services. Hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry. Come on
come on come on. Recruits more more people. Your majesty a new building is complete.
And get them more uh more blacksmith shit. Level two weapons. Hurry up.
The invasion is about to happen. More rangers. Go. Majesty the local blacksmith offers new services.
Your majesty a new building is complete. Get rid of this now. Attack it. There's plenty of you here.
Fuck. Are they already here? Need more. Hurry up. Come on.
Yes I'm very aware. Your majesty a new building is complete.
Are they all right? Okay more warriors. Crom warriors. Blacksmith. Oh come on really.
What? Shit. I need. Get rid of it. Okay okay okay that's good good good very good.
Fuck that lower part of the town right now. I have a pretty decent army right now.
I'm using all my money but hopefully we can at least farm the guys coming out of the sewers here.
That one's full. That one's full. Good. I now have an army. We've got our tavern.
Another one. Caravan. This is not good here. This is bad. I think I'm gonna lose this time.
Oh Jesus. Okay.
This is so bad. Oh what? Is that him? Where's the guy? I killed the guy.
The local blacksmith offers new services. Yes I'm sure they're very useful.
Need healing potions. What about blacksmith? Level three weapons.
There they come. I need.
They're just gonna slowly come down here. Tax collectors.
We got people walking around in circles. Farm these guys.
We're getting surrounded at all sides. Call the arms. Get everybody here.
Go. Protect your kingdom. Protect your king.
Did we do it? I think we did it. People are doing all right. Just keep leveling up.
Krom is the best temple. Level four. Level four. Five five five. Keep leveling up.
Where the fuck are you going? Why are you going up there? What are you? Are you stupid? Stay
with the team. All right. Blacksmith. Good. Everyone's got a decent level right now.
I serve with pleasure. Four four. As long as I can get everybody for like four or five.
Shit. Here they come again.
Good. What else do we need to do here?
If they come. Forget about the bounties. They'll just do it on their own.
How many warriors? I got no warrior has died.
This is not. I held off that very first ridiculous wave. Now I'm going to do.
How is this unmatched? How much money do I have? Not a whole lot.
Robin, your marketplace now serves you better. A building has been upgraded.
They're just kind of going on their own now. Where's like another one of those rat kids?
Oh shit. Here they come. Your majesty, the royal treasury is nearly empty.
Your highness, the dwarves are offering to move into our domain in the name of the sovereign.
I don't know what the hell I need to do here. I have no money. A local blacksmith offers new
services. Is there a trading post down here? There is. There already is one down here.
Don't get overwhelmed. Fight together. I take the path less traveled.
All right. They built up this one. This is still okay. I have all level four stuff.
I don't have enough to do the the chrome thing.
Come on. Stay alive. Please stay alive.
I can't do it. I don't have money. Are we losing people? We have not lost
any knights. We haven't lost anybody. Everybody's still alive.
Come on. Do it. And then I gotta go up here. And I'm gonna put a bounty on this.
We have to start clearing all these rat holes. I need to put up though. I don't have any fucking money.
Tax collector. How much you got? $40. The guard tower. I'm just trying to see.
Money wise. I don't have very much. All right. I gotta fucking get rid of these.
I gotta fucking get rid of these. $400 to get rid of that. Take out that that rat hole.
Kill this thing too though. Don't just like leave the town completely abandoned.
Somebody kill it. Somebody go up there and kill it. I don't know where they're going.
But they're going over this way. This has to be killed. I gotta do like an...
I gotta build some shit up here. But I don't have any fucking money. I did it all wrong.
I'm gonna say a dwarven settlement. Just put it like over here. How's everybody doing?
Here they come. Another big rat recruitment. Well they all have good weapons. They're all
leveled up as high as they can. The royal treasury is nearly empty. Do I need more? I still I kind
of don't understand how this works. I'm still trying to figure because it's almost like rise
in nations. Are they actually gonna go up here? Marketplace level three.
Oh they're doing it. No they're not. He's gonna die. Why are you the only one up here man?
How could you be the only person up here? And you're very strong too. This is bad.
Why would you go up there by yourself at level four? Shit. No. No. Everybody come back.
Beast approaches. We gotta get rid of this shit. I need to make a...
I don't know what would be... a wizards guild? I'm gonna make a wizards guild I think.
Because I lost a couple people I think. They're gonna level up.
I don't know if they're gonna be able to hold us off. Come on kill it. They're just pouring people
over here. Never ending. You have to kill those little rat dens immediately. Like within five
minutes of the game starting or you lose. I just don't know like the all the tech trees to be able
to go that fast. It's still possible if I can level these guys up to like level eight, nine,
ten. At least most of them or half of them even. Still have only 1300 bucks. Marketplace is gone.
Majesty! The palace is under siege! You did it! All right. He did it. He did it. He got that one.
I think there's only two more. Stay alive. Keep this alive. Please. You can do it. The critters
are under attack. Okay I need my marketplace back. Marketplace. Marketplace. Marketplace.
It's literally all my fucking money. Oh shit.
All right. No.
There's the one down there and there's one up here somewhere too.
Your majesty. Your treasury is nearly empty. No damn money. Our new building is complete.
Level six. All right. What do we got? What do we have? Level seven. We got a level seven.
It's Sir Stahl. We just need one of these guys. Sir Stahl. Sir Stahl where are you?
You're just doing your own damn thing aren't you? Get back down here. We need you.
Very very badly. Looks like they're making their way down here. Very good. Take this out.
I don't have any money. Your marketplace now serves you better. New wave is going to be
coming here in a second. Where's Sir Stahl? What? Don't kill the warrior's guild. This is it. All
right. Take him out. Get rid of this rat cave and then I should be all right. I might get a minute
here. There we go. Take it out. Nice. Keep doing it. You guys can do it. Yes. I need an inn.
They killed the inn. They also got rid of the dwarf thing that was over here. All right. I need
an inn for people to hang out and rest. I need to make money. Don't go all the way over here.
Please guys. What are you thinking? Don't do that. You're just going to die. There's no reason for
you to go over there. Level six. Level four. I need you guys. Your marketplace now serves you
better. Better marketplace. Good. Market day. There's nothing even in there. I haven't even
explored half the map. No, I know. Are these two just going to be like a team here and go take a
bunch of shit out? Sewer entrance. I think they're just going to be on their own. Hopefully they stay
together. What do we got? Level seven. Level six. We have a couple level sevens now. All right.
Kill this thing. Please. I need the marketplace down here.
Forever penniless. I need an inn though. That's more important because I just I need an inn over
here. Who's had that? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. What did you guys do over here? What did
you guys step on? Where is he? Where's rat man? Oh my god. They're attacking from every angle.
Where's the king? Where's king rat? Did I hit the enrage timer? Where is he? Oh are they doing it?
Please stay alive. They're destroying the palace.
Holy shit man. This is hard. This is insane. I don't know where he is but I think people
are dying. Level eight. Where's uh stall? Stall is in the middle right here.
Come on. You can do it. He's got one. They're already at a 65 HP. Come on.
Get everybody over here. Call the arms. This is over. I'm dead. Unless like actually stall does
this on his own. What am I supposed to do about this? I hit the enrage timer. I had to have.
Majesty. The palace is under siege. Stall dead? He's dead. Wow. This is really really really hard.
Wow. You gotta be bang bang bang bang bang bang bang. Go faster. Yeah I know right.
He's alive. Take that. This guy is. Your actions permitted or two. Well beast approaches. Well I
mean the palace is under siege. I probably. These guys are still alive though. They're
this might not be a total loss. Well the palace is gonna explode but can these guys do it? Look
they're kind of melting this thing. I got a couple level. I got a level eight in here.
Well of course they came out of the sewer. Level seven. No level eight's dead. I just
don't have enough money. Name of the sovereign. Oh well. I'm kind of surviving but I don't have
enough money to supplement anybody here and I don't want to build anybody. I don't want to
because this is gonna be level one. I need an inn for them to go into. Somebody please build an inn.
In the name of the sovereign. My prowess is unmatched. They're kind of doing it but
it almost feels like it for nothing. There's another broken sewer man over here. They're alive.
They're alive but they just never-endingly pour in. I need an inn. Please build an inn for these
guys to hang out in. Level eight. Level eight. Level eight. Level seven. I think this is possible.
They're all gonna be leveled up. They all have the best armor. They have the best weapons.
I just need potions. I need a marketplace so they can buy potions.
Your majesty, our new building is complete. Okay the inn is done. Marketplace.
1400. Come on. I lived. I actually lived. These guys are actually really really high level now.
Come on. Where's my money?
I'm just getting free levels.
You know what I'm telling you at this point I think I gotta just go.
I gotta just go take this band of people and have them explore up here and try to just kill
the rap king. I think that's the plan. That's the strategy. I got two one two three little eights.
Maybe just let them just hang around here and just gain.
Is my blacksmith gone? Kind of. All right. Thousand bucks.
I wouldn't go all the way down there if anything. Go this way. I didn't know you
guys were still alive. I still have these random explorers. No! Okay that's just-
All right. I'm done. Instead of every single person. Let's go.
Majesty the palace is under siege. Oh my god. I can't believe you just let the fucking happen.
Let's go. Everybody up there now. Explore. Go. Forget it. Beast approaches.
I have no- I just have no money. I can't do anything. I'm just constantly putting
my fingers in holes that are spewing out on the side of the boat.
Name of the sovereign. Granny. Granny Nash is going up there. Good. Go up there grandma.
And everybody else going up there. Besides one person. I would laugh my ass off if you just like
threw an axe at the guy's head. Only one person going for that bounty. The rest of you are just
walking around in circles. Come on granny. Just find him. Level seven. What do you got for potions?
Zero. I'm gonna turn back down here and everyone's gonna be level 10.
Why is he the only person that cares about this? This is very very concerning.
Nobody else cares. And he's gonna get lost up here and he's gonna die. Good work. I don't have
enough money to pay the bounty. Where is the king? Where's Rat King? I think they're gonna
do it though. I think they'll be okay. Are they? Who's still alive? Level eight. Level eight. Level
seven. They're all right. He's not even going for the bounty. All right. Find it. In the name of
the sovereign. Get this thing out of here. Holy shit. They're literally everywhere now. Everyone's
still fine. The palace is under siege. Our foul beast approaches. Eight eight eight seven seven.
Is this still all right? No. No. No. No. Please just stay up here. Don't come all the way back
to the castle. Somebody please. Level eight. Level eight eight eight seven seven seven.
They're all still alive.
Why won't you just go over here? What? You're gonna walk all the way back down because you
want the bounty that is already down here that's being claimed by everybody that's already down
here. There's a scroll? Where's the scroll? Rodan the Rat King has burst up from the sewers to take
over your kingdom. Destroy him and all the broken sewer mains to end the menace. Wait was he? Where
is he? In the name of the sovereign. Where is he? Majesty the palace is under siege. Where the hell did he go?
Where? He's here? I don't see him. We've got two level nines. Every single sewer is a broken sewer
main now. Um. I serve with pleasure. Destroy them all. Destroy all the broken sewer mains.
I mean I have a couple I have some really strong units. I don't even know. Man shaman.
Oh fuck a level eight's dead. Majesty the palace is under siege. Take that. In the name. This is bad.
Uh this is I think Rodan's unfortunately. We only have like five people here.
Take that. Is he over here? Kill him. Kill him. He's right there. There he is.
Somebody kill him and then destroy all of them. Majesty ill treasury is nearly. He's just walking
around in circles. Uh this sucks. It's over. Hold your majesty. Anybody gonna go get him? No.
No. Tax collector number 31 is about to become tax collector number 32.
Anybody going up there? No. He's just wandering around in circles. At least we got to see him,
right? Majesty the palace is under siege. In the name of the sovereign.
Day is lost majesty but there's always tomorrow. Well maybe it had something to do with the fact
that at least 15 to 20 catapults just instant spawn. All right that one's we're not doing that
one. Victory for the rats. Hold off the goblin horde. All the ones where that is a horde.
Quest for the magic ring. That's the one I'm doing. Majesty I fear my vision grows alarmingly dim.
The dark plague which grips our land does not respect the boundaries of these castle walls.
This epidemic sweeps through our land leeching away the very life from your royal subjects.
Our best doctors seem unable to slow the pace of this dread disease. Before slipping into
unconsciousness the mighty wizard Brezenthal insisted that there was only one way to halt
this affliction. You must recover the ring of healing which the legends say is located somewhere
in Ardenia. Please your majesty act with greatest haste. Okay recover the ring of healing.
Get a quest for the magic ring. Here we go. These these guys are evil. Saruman the mumbler.
Temple to Helia recruits Solari grants temple spell fire strike. Holy shit this is too much
going on. Let's get some gnome hubbles right now right off the bat. Marketplace. I serve with
pleasure. Marketplace I want a warriors guild. What's this? It appears that there is another
kingdom in this realm. Your majesty a new building is complete. The last resort is in a kingdom
in the realm. So what should I get a Solaris? Your highness if our kingdom is to prosper
it needs more heroes. Okay let's get some gnomes out here. Quick. Your majesty a new building is
complete. Where you going? Where you going? Where you going? Where you going? Where you going? Where you going?
Where you going? Slow down. Your majesty a new building is complete. Get that Marcus blade.
Okay looking good. Good good good good good good. Get the arrows. A new building is complete.
Another Solaris. Marketplace. Quick. Your majesty a new building is complete. Your highness
we've improved the guard house. Nice that's what I want to hear. Your majesty a new building is complete.
Saruman your marketplace now serves you better. Good. Your highness we've improved the guard house.
Do you have any potions or food? Saruman your marketplace now serves you better. No it's not.
Liar. Get another Solaris. Out of money. Any more gnomes? Good. Okay more gnomes. More of them.
I want to just spam this whole entire world with gnomes. Just continue your influence.
A new building is complete. Okay what do we got? Level two weapons. Go.
How many more Solarises do we have? Marketplace. Go. Your majesty a royal treasury is
nearly empty. Shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up. Your majesty a local blacksmith offers new
services. Good. Come on we need some more gnome huts over here. Come on 950 let's go.
Who's this? Who's this? Kill it. What are you doing over here? Is it is it diplomacy? Hey wait hey hey
hey hey excuse me did you just go in my house? You just went in my marketplace. Who are you?
Diplomacy? Are you stealing or are we trading? I don't know if they're stealing or not.
Follows into the monarch level. Plants healing herbs throughout the kingdom. Follows and heals
heroes as they battle. May be reborn after dying. Majesty a local blacksmith offers new services.
Okay that's fine. In a gesture of good faith the neighboring kingdom deposited gold into your
treasury. Holy shit okay I was both well that's nice of you thank you that's really cool what a
what a good neighbor quite the neighbor thank you a building has been upgraded nice wow
gotta get this to level three immediately a building has been upgraded uh somebody gave
another fifty dollars just donate to germa gave five thousand bits
just to donate to germa is the name of this
uh oh blacksmith offers new services just stay protected uh thank you for the 50 bucks
just donate to germa i made this account uh to buy at any prices you use 50 more expensive take
my fucking money you boomer what would the price difference between NA and EU is what
50 percent they only just said it i serve with EU taxes all right these guys are friends are
they gonna turn on me or something that's what this mission's all about i guarantee it all right
so i got level three teleportation amulets sovereign a building has been upgraded where's
my blacksmith i want to be ready yep level three incoming where we're just we're friends we're good
tax collector this is fine majesty the local blacksmith offers new services can i have some
more money sovereign your marketplace now serves you better all right we need i need to build out
let's go with a i'm gonna build this way sovereign in out here building has been upgraded
how do no no no not like not you guys i'm talking about in the game
name and let's get let's send out some people check out out here building is complete check
out like go this way just a little bit nothing much just to go check it all right that one's
done let's build out some more i want to do this is good halt what happened what's going on
oh is it rat i thought we were just attacking each other i was like oh shit don't do that
who's in there now okay go check out up here we're gonna fight each other over this rim
all right i got money good majesty the local blacksmith offers new services i know uh rangers
guild there we go all right where's my uh where are my gnomes now how come the gnomes are not
building more huts i was told they were gonna be building huts we need more of those everywhere
a new building is complete they only build three oh that's unfortunate majesty the local black
smith offers new services we've got a level four shit let's get a ranger out here you're not
trading with your neighboring kingdom what am i supposed to do i double click this yeah i am i'm
going in there and buying beer in their um in their hub give me some ranges another one please
thank you this looks like a roller coaster tycoon well it is like more than 10 years old
it's probably just a couple of rats don't worry
i'm out of here i want nothing to do with that still nobody going out there the rangers
explore go explore what are you doing max upgraded i'm gonna go with a hmm what do you think i should
do over here i don't know what do you think that's a good idea person in my head that just said to
build a uh another guard no i need a trading post i'm gonna put a trading post up here
by them you know near them trading post you know what i'm saying come on hey hey whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa are they fighting are they did they turn on me how beast approaches don't kill my tax
collector i god damn it another 50 dollars just came in from lacronda thank you for the 5 000 this
lacronda your dog is howling from loneliness and you're buying beer on a pixel game we want auto
no you talk that's what you're talking about i don't have i thought i was doing just fine he's
downstairs lying down all right good finally confused ranger get out there i need to keep
building out i need another marketplace i need to trading depot i need too many things way too
many all right let's go with trading post i'm gonna put it all the way up here you know what i'm
saying like i'm gonna put it as far away as i can is that a mistake i need money i need one of my
tax collectors what are they doing kill the city guard that doesn't matter good more money
deposited spend it i need a trading post it's fine as long as you have something to protect it
yeah we're going all the way up here i need more taxes this is gonna be so fucking far away
570 you can do it come on good you fight it not me tax collector there you are
how much money do you have on you tax collector yes more please there we go finally build it
up here in the corner this is some warcraft shit going on right now i'll tell you
all right you're going exploring good good for you i'm helping out my ally nice work guys
you have a long journey to get up here funny streamer entertaining gameplay not enough
auto two out of five stars
two out of six no yeah two out of five stars come on what is happening who is this goblin camp
oh i'm up here am i up here yeah i guess we're taking over this camp
kill that thing please all right got the gold let's go upgrades build level two palace hurry up
i ain't fucking around here i ain't gonna sit here and listen to this
i'm going for it fix the house please your highness we've improved the guard house nice work
your highness we've improved the guard house it's gonna take you uh-oh also speaking of guard
house renovations are finished i need 1100 you're not gonna die nobody's gonna go up here
no you're safe up here the computer the ai is this this is the very top right corner
okay level two we got i want another inn over here yeah put like an inn like right up here
like all the way out in the fucking middle of nowhere so heroes want to go up and explore
my twitch stocks are booming good okay i need them in the marketplace get a guard house up
there too what do i want it like right next to it right here get that up yes
oh we're gonna help too i'm gonna put another i'm gonna put it in over here too yeah give just
give them okay put them everywhere just give them a reason to do anything oh your majesty a new
building is complete your majesty a new building is complete no no no no no no no no no don't
leave it alone let's get a um let's get a rogue's guild up there your majesty a new building is
complete we're good there's no way a tax collector makes it up there alive you'd be surprised
a new building is complete your highness we've improved the guard house your majesty a new
building is complete five rogues up here the royal treasury is nearly empty once i have a caravan go
from here to there i'm out of here really he died in one hit why do these guys suck so much
will you please go up there and kill that ai friend of mine okay this has arrows now it's
the trading post healing potions let's go this person's level five not bad majesty your trading
post now offers healing potions okay two thousand good thank god kill it get rid of it this is the
trading post is good here so i'm gonna put a marketplace over here i think i'm gonna
marketplace this like up here i don't know the tax collector then has to come all the way over
here right yeah you're right nice work take this out hidden this i found the ring building has
been upgraded this is the ring the hidden ring site this is it i found it that's where it is
this person just kind of accidentally went and found it what so what happened wait what happens
if i take this should i not do this yet what if they become hostile that's definitely what's
gonna happen it has to be right i'm concerned that once i destroy this site this all becomes
yellow level eight and what's in there the phantoms have returned i knew i shouldn't have done it
a hero has recovered the magic ring and with a terrible curse suddenly find yourself at war
with the other kingdom in the realm if the other kingdom manages to return the ring to their
palace the curse will not be broken and all will be lost also you have incurred the wrath of the
black phantoms it'll smite any hero who holds the ring right i told you this is gonna happen
i shouldn't have fucking done that a hero must return the magic ring to this pedestal in order
to end the curse where's the ring who took the ring didn't everybody see where the ring went
somebody get this ring get it this is so bad somebody get that ring it's just sitting right
here thankfully the ring rates are attacking his town get it get that ring it's right there get it
get it pick it up and bring it over here and win i need to keep i have to keep my eye on that
take it nobody go go go go get out out out out out go go go go go go no no get away
crap where's the ring beast approaches nobody will miss this come on you can make it
hurry up and get to the the temple do it oh it's almost there you're almost at the end zone
touchdown touchdown touchdown touchdown touchdown touchdown touchdown
we are victorious your majesty the ring has saved us all majesty as your heroes carried the relic
back into town it was as if a deep winter snow had instantly lifted the town literally sprang
to life once again your enlightened leadership has led us to safety cool um so that one was
i would say 100 times easier than the rat one and they were both advanced okay all right i'm gonna
pee i'll be right back we'll take a break i will return very short uh nocturne just gave 10
community subs right before i left oh i mean i didn't leave yet i'm still here but that's a
shit load of subs thank you for the 10 community subs i'll be thinking about that when i pee
i'll see you in a minute thank you though for real secret quest dark forest holy chalice
free the slaves a deal with the demon sounds interesting what happened after the tweet oh
right right right yeah i ended up just putting hand sanitizer all over it i got a paper towel
they got hand sanitizer and i poured the hand sanitizer like in the paper towel like a little
bit of it while i was cupping the two strings and just kind of squished it in with the paper towel
and rubbed and squished and then kind of made sure it was completely and totally submerged
in hand sanitizer and then left alone let it just dry and that was it keep the drawstrings
inside your pants i was just wearing pants it wasn't like put the drawstrings inside like what
your underwear like what do you mean like stick them in your pants not only does that not work
it spreads the germs way worse you may as well have cut them off if it bothered you yeah but
that was another thing where am i gonna get a pair of scissors in a public bathroom at an airport
i already covered that i'm just gonna walk into a random store and ask for okay can i borrow a pair
of scissors please uh what okay here thank you and then i just cut the ends off of my drawstrings
and then thanks i'm gonna be like what the fuck did i just watch use your hands i'm not gonna put
my hands all if it dips into the urinal that's over the i don't know why the strings was so long
in these pants i want to see what an expert level looks like majesty i'm here with the latest report
from the chief tax collector he reports that the fiscal quarter will soon be ending and the treasury
reports a deficit of one you dare interfere with the thumbs of the lit queen
he did that was the burp that was that was the all right listen ready that was what i did he
was like drinking a coffee and he was like majesty i'm here with the latest report from the chief
tax collector he reports that the fiscal quarter will soon be ending and the treasury reports a
deficit okay i'm here with the latest report from the chief tax collector
he reports that the fiscal quarter will soon be ending and the treasury reports a deficit
okay let's see what is this one mighty leader forgive this intrusion but a terrible presence
has visited our castle a demon he claims he's going to collect on a debt owed to him by your
mother since we were unable why what's another one um hold off the goblins dreadful news scouts
from the frontier report that goblins have been seen heading this way in massive numbers we must
stem this dark tide before they overrun and utterly destroy the kingdom i suggest you put out a call
for heroes as many as we can muster to protect our village and keep this vile swarm at bay
i implore you to act quickly the most recently sightings were not far from the village and we
are ill prepared for such an invasion here we go destroy all goblin settlements rangers guilds
cannot be constructed go i serve with pleasure a foul beast approaches prowess is unmatched
let's go this is unmatched kill it your highness we
i want uh i want um
i want um your majesty our new building is complete your majesty our new building is complete
let's go hurry the fuck up let's go i'm i'm stacked right now
your majesty your market place now serves you better come on more where are they where is this
what's going on here where are they get over here get up there what are you doing here majesty
the local blacksmith offers new services your market place now serves you better
get up get up here what is taking so long
what are you going no that's because the bounty is on this stupid thing
uh don't do this to me you idiots hurry up and protect this
oh you're gonna ruin everything you literally you're ruining it this is
how the hell do you do this shit this doesn't even seem like it's possible
your majesty what the fuck i serve with pleasure
we've improved the god house your highness we've improved the god house name of the sovereign
hurry prowess is unmatched in the name of the sovereign this item looks
useful in the name of the sovereign i need uh another one three warriors guilds
i only want warriors for this in the name of the sovereign marketplace going up hurry
come on i know you can do it shads only your majesty a new building is good hurry come on
i don't have much time for this your market place now serves you better your highness the elves
wish to join oh the elves do they if prosperous elves just hurry up and build this you're making
me so upset right now your market place now serves you better your majesty a new building is complete
good more your majesty a new building is complete they're gonna destroy
get out there i want 15 heroes sovereign a building has been upgraded the palace is
under siege where's my uh gnome headquarter the palace is under siege no go go go go
my prowess is unmatched i have a ton of people now all right i'm almost out of money
so i have all yep i am stacked up on heroes your marketplace now serves you better fight
where are you going what was up there what i can just call to arms right here in fact i think i'm
going to the allied wizards guild has contributed gold to your treasury hey thanks new building is
we do we're working this together a new building is complete dude
in the name of the sovereign sovereign we gotta go so game for
these males approaches your highness we've improved the guard house
my prowess is unmatched good do i have an in nope i said with pleasure
i'm out of money a new building is complete okay i need to put i'm gonna put a trading
folks on here refreshing victory is not in the card all right anymore elves another elf out here
okay our new building is complete it's not going so bad this time sovereign your marketplace
now serves you better good was the tax man call in the reinforce elven lounge all right that's
good i still have everybody i want the tag i want this guy too more than that like minimum
return 500 bucks at least your majesty there's a sewer entrance over there why is nobody killing
this thing what are you doing why is this just walking around like it's a citizen
tax collector oh i don't understand that
oh come on get over here oh for the love of god get the fuck over here please
your highness we've improved the guard houses sovereign the building has been upgraded click
up wait wait wait click click on click on wait wait click wait wait wait wait what
what are you guys talking about click on it click on what click on it what do you click on what
click on the bounty the big guy i said fulvis the un what sovereign a building has been upgraded
sovereign a building has been upgraded oh he's a good guy oh well that makes sense then doesn't
that makes sense i guess fulvis hold your majesty get some better guards out here
uh i'm gonna build a trading post over here with the friends i think that's a pretty good use of
my time your highness we've improved the guard house trading post your highness the palace
renovations are finished your majesty my royal treasury is nearly empty what's going on here
this independent wizards guild pledges to help defend the realm better yet
the local magi have enchanted it so that the building is invulnerable for duration
your allied wizard guild has lost its ward of invulnerability it is mortal again and may be
destroyed by those goblins so i gotta go down there and help in order to further aid the cause
the allied wizards have deposited more gold into your inventory okay thanks okay i have to protect
these guys then all right let's we gotta build down here what the hell should i put down here
how about a temple of uh wrong what's another good one lenoord temple of lenoord
all right how are we all doing good don't go up here and start attacking this fulvis
actually you know what no do attack that get rid of that shit it's like running the edge
your majesty our new building is complete where's my blacksmith do i even have a blacksmith
hey hey hey get rid of you where's my blacksmith where's my blacksmith stop this
do i have to call to arms here right now please don't tell me i have to a new building is complete
adept oh sick this is nice your highness winged feet prove the god house cast winged feet oh no
that does but cool beast approaches what's going on over here do i gotta get rid of this
goblin camp take this did you kill it you did nice job get this one too good do it get rid of
this one too four five hundred bucks anybody that takes that out to protect the wizards
and this one 200 for the the the brave soldier that takes out the one behind it
all right i need trading post fairgrounds let's do it let's put a fair over here kill all this
protect them keep them around how beast approaches how are we doing palace guard
all right we're cleaning them out a little bit they're losing uh hovels quickly
windstorm watch it i need some help over here go get them i think we still have all the this
thing needs to be repaired though i think everyone's still alive they are coming back out here though
no come on ah they're gonna kill the end again aren't they dicks how beast approaches
all right they'll take care of this and then this is gone now
all my guys can come back up here building is complete fairgrounds tournaments yeah let's do
tournament uh let's put a trading post somewhere i wanted this a long time ago down here
shall we host a tournament now yeah yeah let's go um melee contest let's go
is it happening
i think that like people are gonna go in there eventually okay i thought there we go
i think they train in there there's a smash tournament going on in there
the inn is destroyed again i'm putting the inn over here okay
that trading post majesty our new building is complete good
i mean i only have we good all right it's time hundred bucks for over here
200 bucks to go up there 100 bucks 200 go explore
your majesty our new building is complete i don't know what the adept should look like
your majesty our new building is complete see what they look like
okay that's what they look like i have everybody i think one of the healing healers
majesty your trading post now offers healing potions oh that's it thanks for the update
my prowess is unmatched up there i gotta destroy all the goblin caves right actually he's in trouble
maybe not can you do it by yourself is one beast approaches give you 100 bucks if you kill it
yeah run away that's not that's a losing fight there's a couple over here i think i'm doing it
i'm doing it quick bit of gold check down here too i got tons of money let's go let's spend it
word has arrived that the goblins have begun to recruit trolls you must wipe them out now
before all is lost um your highness we've improved the god house okay i'll try i don't
oh what is whatever let's do another um let's get some rogues in here
viewers may purchase training to enhance their abilities okay so just
you just get to do better get to be better oh found one beast approaches take it out
clean it up uh here it looks like there this is one of their i don't know how you got up here
but good on you you make 100 bucks here you'll make 100 bucks 200 there a building has been
upgraded i'm kind of killing it right now guys i'm not gonna lie new building is complete
let's do what else should i do another marketplace
royal garden i'll put a statue of me up here
okay uh this is what they were talking about sovereign a building all right all right all
right this is where i'm getting a little too overconfident call to arms over here right now
go beast approaches this is bad news very bad news kill them your majesty a new building is
complete i was doing so good too i got money more guard houses a wizard's wizard's castle
holy shit this is really bad okay am i good i think i'm okay
no i'm all right i'm fine i think one person died
shit come on you got they're right here kill them good look at you good job building is complete
go collect that bounty i need more i serve with pleasure this will be a quick bit of gold
gold i'm shit faced yeah they're only spawning the trolls now this has to be worth more money
take it out build it your majesty a new building is complete beast approaches hurry your highness
we've improved the guard house all right we've improved the guard house
your highness we've improved the guard house your majesty a new building is complete no
good i got you up here cleaning up kill all this level five not enough high enough level
beast approaches i gotta build some more uh units i already really you'll get it you'll get
i need to upgrade this tower an ill wind blows near i need some wizards all right we've uh stopped
that invasion good beast approaches everybody relax for a minute what happened to my uh
where's my uh was my um i don't i can't tell you what i'm trying to find
my i don't know i don't know what it is your highness we've improved the guard house
oh my ambition has paid off all right you got it majesty check
oh i don't know there's a cave thing over here get it find it and destroy it let's do some more um
warriors more warriors more in the name of the sovereign we got goblin hubble kill it
destroy there's a big one destroy it 500
we're good it amuses me that nobody but one percent of the chat know what's going on i feel
like a special boomer here we go i think i've almost completed a new building is complete
that is funny all right oh up here they're still coming from over here
nobody's explored up there yet keep going over here more gold
oh there's too many called arms no yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh-huh way too many
somebody's the people are dying
oh i don't even have a library windstorm he's dead got him he's gone this is where
they're all coming from kill it this way too many of these things well you guys are on your own
you know what like a new building is complete actually i do care i can't just let my ally die
like that that'd be so mean i kind of like can't listen to this anymore tax collector this will be
a quick bit of gold this will be a quick bit of a tax collector your highness our research in the
library is complete your highness our research is complete this will be a quick bit of gold
it reminds me of um you know those old kind of thought uh experiments not thought experience
when you were like 15 years old no younger than that when you were like 10 and there was like the
a trail of sentence that you had to connect over and over again they wouldn't one of them was like
there's a there's a frog in the bottom of the sea or the frog in the bottom of the lake or whatever
there's a there's no no there's a hole in the bottom of the what what's it called there's a
log on the frog in the bottom of the hole or something i'm trying to figure it out i'm gonna
take my headphones out i can't i'm getting speech jam there's there's a no no no it was there's a
hole there's like a flea on the hair on the dog and the frog and the log in the bottom of yeah
i won anyways there's like a hair on the flea on the dog and the log and the frog and the
bog and the log at the like bottom of the sea you keep adding more and more things that you
have to remember that's what this is this is a lot of noise in my ear
day is your majesty there's a
while many lives were lost our kingdom is safe once again the goblin king will think twice before
trying another such futile assault that was advanced wait do i want to go down the demon
oh he said he's gonna yeah where is it a deal with a demon but wait yeah okay mighty leader
forgive this intrusion what a terrible presence has visited our castle a demon he claims he's here
to collect on a debt owed to him by your mother can this be true since we were unable to immediately
deliver the requested bounty he said he'd return later but triple the amount of gold or he cursed
the entire village he then vanished in a cloud of foul smelling green smoke your majesty i hope you
have a plan something must be done before he returns what does he want to do he
foul green smoke make a hundred thousand gold in 40 days huh a hundred thousand gold
so what do i just only have tax collectors i sold spin gambling hall gold your majesty
a new building is complete what it's not even possible oh dude that was so much
your highness oh i'm gonna cut you off here this is getting a little ridiculous uh your majesty
we just had 20 000 gold and you just lost it all of it so it's red and hold on so gold happens like
way less percent of the time if you guys don't think i'm gonna beat this by doing just this you're
out of your mind fucking come on that's it's been blue fucking five times in a row your highness
if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes
no what is this stealing from me shit come on no don't do this gold gold it's gonna be gold
gold right now gold gold gold gold gold gold gold gold gold gold gold oh there it is gold
again back to back gold right now gold needs more heroes three times in a row gold again
give me gold gold again here it comes gold gold here it comes here it is right at this one
this next one is gold gold right here gonna be gold i promise guaranteed gold gold guaranteed
right now gold right here guaranteed gold gold right now gold red red blue blue blue gold gold
right now gold okay how do i okay how do i make money let's make some money i have 42 000
dollars okay how do i get there your highness if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes
okay just do blue just do blue come on too cold again it's gonna be gold three times in a row
okay um what okay we need what do i do okay i need to pick some marketplace right marketplace
and then miss this now what your highness if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes
okay shit all right that's a lot all right let's make some money
i gotta level this building save the game all right save game i power i need um i need to make um
some gnomes
your majesty our new building is complete your majesty our new building is complete
i'm out of here my ambition has paid off
i'm gonna laugh my fucking ass off if i just do it by gambling on gold every time
this is destroying the kingdom
the king's just sitting in the gambling hall i want all the guards posted out the door
i can do it i can come back no not my gambling hall your highness if our kingdom is to prosper
it needs more heroes they're leaving
your majesty our new building is complete i'm out of here i'm out of here all right i'm done i'm
done i'm done i'm gonna reload and just go in it the regular way i promise not yet hold on
my ambition has paid off i'm out of here
saves the game okay go red red fuck watch me go to zero oh god okay hold on i win oh fuck
yes your majesty i thought i had to wait 40 days i did it i won you did it majesty once that vile
creature was given the gold he vanished in a puff of foul green smoke again all in attendance
felt compelled to immediately wash the stench from their clothes may that repellent manifestation
never again threaten our kingdom i just like come out of the game at the casino and i got big
bags under my eyes i did it i did it you fools but i know now i spent 180 000 in the casino
i'm really happy that i get my free voucher for free parking on thursday that's worth it to me
oh and i got one free night stay okay i'm glad good you cheated it still did it all right there
was that one all people above the age of 25 are boomers no they're not sorry what okay what is it
with the younger generation if you're like okay what is the younger generation then you know a
generation is like a huge amount huge range of people right zoomers the younger generation
yeah there is a younger generation but we're not every single person that's over the age of like
like 22 is a boomer what are you only a zoomer for like four years you go from oh yeah
generation z zoomer sure whatever that's uh 15 to 19 and then everybody's a boomer huh where
we going i can't do this one yet should i do the burp one let's try the burp one majesty i'm here
with the latest report from the chief tax collector he reports that the fiscal quarter
will soon be ending and the treasury reports a deficit of you dare interfere with the plans of
the lich queen your meddling presence has been like a thorn in my side i will soon remove you
just talking into a fan
sorry never mind uh i was wrong it was just it was uh it was my wife leading into the fan
just really trying to scare me there adventurer uh never mind about that one uh we'll go back to
your normal business majesty i'm here with the latest report from the chief tax collector
he reports that the all right i already know how to do this and the treasury reports
you dare interfere with the plans of the lich queen okay drive the lich queen from her rocky
lair and then defeat her i'm gonna lose no temples to crypto available no blacksmiths what
no blacksmith inns dwarf settlements no rogues gallery no that's not what this is rogue that's
spider-man's rogues gallery or batman whatever the fuck it is um i can't do okay let's try it
first things first marketplace second things first god houses a couple of them at least two or three
of them third things first warrior's guild two of them one two and lastly firstly the ranger's
guild right here go go hurry up the faster you move your fucking hands the faster they work
okay that's starting to hurt let's get some healers probably gonna need them
what do they have spells healing do they do it on their own
get out of here your majesty a new building is complete thank you i don't like this king he
gambles too much a new building is complete yeah i saved us from satan okay so if i hadn't done
that there would have been tons of like destruction across the whole world the god house my
gambling saved everybody not your marketplace now serves you better not a sword was raised
during that conflict with satan your majesty our new building is complete
sovereign your marketplace now serves you better your majesty our new building is complete your
highness john doesn't even talk like that the god house it's kind of funny how isn't it weird
that if you just say shawn that sounds like that's not the same guy build it hurry up come on hey
shawn yeah shawn that's shawn connery prove the god house i need this built now your majesty
you're boring me hurry up can we talk about why shawn shawn shawn well if you didn't say the h it
would be just seen seen seen connery where you going where you going what are you dope
why are you going all the way up here these people end up here to plant a flower your majesty
our new building is complete oh good at least you mean that's i must find a haven
well they can't fight they can't fight i get it come on get out there no one they don't
you won't even build my goddamn rogues gallery
uh-oh does that mean she's on her way
a foul beast approaches she's already on the way a new building is complete
your majesty a new building is complete good hurry up
sovereign a building has been upgraded
finally beast approaches come on get out there i wouldn't never mind i'm gonna say something
stupid get out there i need more healers now serves you better they heal automatically right
good your majesty a new building is complete this is a thing is that a thing over there this is a
thing from where they go down there i don't have any money oh come on don't let them do this you
got this so many you guys right now don't do this shit don't be stupid
thank god no they just walk around circles over here i don't know anything about what's going on
i go in my gnomes these are considered heroes somehow the little gnomes are considered a hero
what a dumb fucking game like i'm gonna uninstall it i don't even want to play it anymore
everyone's just like whoa hey i need a trading post like up here or something i need money
what the heck man it was just a joke i don't mean that i don't mean that
healing herbs can we just pick them up the royal treasury is nearly empty majesty a newly
discovered outpost has agreed to join your kingdom the inhabitants of this building have agreed to
join your kingdom you got any money well i mean if you don't have any money then what do you want
to do i need money trading post get it up there then all right well i see something here who's
that vampire vampire don't get yourself killed you're level four you're one of the highest
levels i have right now don't be stupid level four how badly is he gonna get your ass kicked
here pretty badly the rogues don't do anything i'm never making one ever again they don't do
anything they run up and they go i'm scared and they run away i must find a haven what's my
favorite color green um okay he's walking around seamlessly good you will serve me
we have a new uh goblin cave where is it there it is nice who's dying so many people are dying
right now what the hell oh and this is expert mode sovereign protecting has been upgraded
protect your area please where are all the other assholes that are like you and like i have i had
so many where are they he's just attacking he's just killing people great a rat king hopefully
the tower will actually kill it eventually in the guard take your time quick parry oh
no that's not that's that's they're from the same time i know that's why that has kriya's quick
parry that's not the same person well this is bad uh this is very bad um i think this is done
i don't have enough money i have to if the caravan can go back and forth once or twice then fine
but she's just dumping people over here on me yeah this is not good so your majesty it's almost
over the royal treasury is nearly empty i know what i did wrong though i made like 10 priests
for no reason shouldn't have done that
i hate the tsk tsk tsk sound it does get a very very very clear point across though
well caravan seems to uh majesty a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your
kingdom shit okay get the treasure chest what are you doing what are you doing what are you doing
this is game over open the gates open the gates a local blacksmith offers new services
close the gates
beast approaches actually still in it if i can if i can hold this off and i should be okay
looks like in my why are the priests in the front lines they should be back here
here hold them off um i'll pick up the vampires g
not a second g is good you know what i mean oh here come the vampires good
yeah look at us they're on they he's taking all they put yeah bye
that's kind of creepy i'm not gonna lie where'd i get the money
hold on somebody's deposited oh it's the caravan i think quick get him out here come on
the local blacksmith offers new services
my prowess is extort the rogue's den it's gone it was destroyed i had along with my blacksmith
your majesty the royal treasury is nearly empty
yep
yep i think we're okay uh i blew it already no it's already blown caravan's dead and here comes
like another 50 skeletons good yeah there's a loss this is the last cause at this point
that's the dark forest brash nards ultimate sphere of power what's this one requires the
barren waste oh it's a secret this one's expert all right hold on wait requires the forsaken land
where's that one because then i can do the secret quest the forsaken land i didn't do these let's
do it my liege while this land holds great promise i should point out that there is much
that requires your immediate attention our town is still beset by the marauding monsters who lurk
in this forsaken land we will only know true prosperity when these interlopers are kept at
bay it's in your best interest to employ the services of a variety of heroes with their
skills and the blessings of the gods we may be able to safeguard this community destroy the
evil castle to win this epic quest no wizards guild uh non-human races palace level three or
any temples are available all right let's just let's go well look at how small this is we got it
it's already level three oh they're just making it easy you're just making it okay whoa so hard
i know i shouldn't do that your marketplace now serves you better let's get a bunch of
rangers no two warriors guilds two warriors gives two rangers guilds and i get some more
ranges up here where's the uh goblin house guard houses get them up here i'm not fucking around
sovereign your marketplace now serves you better
let's do what does it say welcome to the forsaken land use the reward flags i know how to do that
we got rats we said that
build it blacksmith as well get it over here just please don't kill him
the tax collector can't just turn around and your marketplace now serves you better
don't die i just need one
just kill the dumb thing don't please a new building is complete don't embarrass me
your marketplace now serves you better your majesty a new building is complete
where's my blacksmith more gold more gold i'm going for it your highness we've improved the
god house there we go all right is there a way to get more peasants put this shit down here
too oh it's too close to the marketplace put it up here then
more gold still waiting for you to actually build the halls for the knights
it's good fine creature den i'll get rid of that i don't want to deal with this shit 300 gold
what do you want what does it want to look at here your majesty a nearby monarch king
randolph admires your cause and offers his aid he has sent a caravan to bolster your economy
i think randolph is this is this randolph's okay this thing is being under attack your
your majesty a new building is complete
this guy is starting to sound like bane
why did you have to say that i'm not going to be able to hear that no
blacksmith offers new services bane just is sean connery i didn't even think about that
you're like spot on with that one oh my god there's a lot of things coming down here right now
and um i'm not ready to fight three trolls i just put this up your trading post now
offers healing what if i had more than one fucking peasant like why do i have one person
i'm gonna lose on beginner they took them the 12 minutes to build this what the hell is wrong with
you your highness the palace renovations are finished finished this building my prowess is
unmatched oh my god annoying we killed the peasant is that what happened my prowess is unmatched
you just killed the peasant a new building is great i'm glad you finished took you fucking an
hour my prowess is unmatched my prowess is unmatched your highness we've improved the god house
there we go eight thousand majesty a new building is complete
okay i'm not i'm not sharp anymore your highness we've improved the god there's a dark castle
found it just gotta have like a bunch of people level up a little bit and then send them in and we
went not that hard it's fucking easy you destroyed that don't even uh go after the bears no reason to
you know what just get up there just kill it just send the whole damn troop over there
wait how did you get up here how did they get up here this quickly
is unmatched this item approaches did they just get up here all of you there we go
watch this shit this item looks useful prowess is unmatched somebody's got to claim it i just end
this one so i can do the secret mission i want like the tax collector to come up here
7300 dollars i'll be up there in no time my prowess is unmatched they got it please don't
let this guy kill everybody here it's almost dead
nice job the horrific incursions have ceased majesty children may once again play in the
streets and nearby meadows hunters and peasants may carry out their work without fear may the
bright blessings of the gods continue to shine on your wise rule time for the secret mission
it has been unlocked that's it right no what where is it which one was it this one right
elvin treachery is it the secret one majesty it grieves me to be the bearer of such intolerable
news an elvish miscreant has just slapped the castle he came to deliver the message that his
disreputable brethren have taken your son hostage apparently they see only the size of your treasury
not the depth of your skilled leadership these foul opportunists demand you pay a ransom
or they say you'll never again see your son alive how shall we deal with this elvish impudence my
liege hmm make 50 000 gold in 30 days to pay the ransom or defeat the elves all enemy heroes in
buildings before that time no elves will join you i think i can handle this you can't gamble
because no elves oh are you kidding really shit that's not good what that's bullshit
why is it only the elves that gamble all right let's do palace level two i need uh four heroes
let's just get them and go to palace level two immediately i need some guard houses all right
go get paladins get paladins what's the tech to get paladin what's the tech tree your highness
if our kingdom is to prosper it needs more heroes i know i know i know your majesty a new building
is complete your majesty a new building is complete hey hey yeah you got god damn it no
you built a one unit this is the shit that happened in warcraft 3 marketplace now serves you better
no go up here why stop where did he put in the marketplace why is he allowed in my marketplace
what did are you kidding me right now
he went into my marketplace and was just hanging out in there and nobody saw him marketplace now
serves you better nobody decided they were going to kill him a new building is complete
your majesty a new building is complete a crock of fucking dog shit all right we're good
yeah yeah yeah more i got everyone here we've improved the guard house start firing the arrows
come on get the gnomes out here too
quickly level two palace
a lot of you seem to be joining the wilds your majesty a new building is complete
i feel like that's an ai doing that your majesty a new building is complete
all right we got it come on level two go go go hurry up refreshing attack him attack
why are you just standing there you've just taken arrows in the side of the head and didn't even
react sovereign a building has been upgraded okay good palace level two get it out
next collector the palace renovations are finished good i want who were the paladins
crypto chrome what's the paladin's one refreshing which is the paladin's one
victory is not in the get a doris guild and then you can build paladins in the warriors
guild the doris guild warriors guild get it up victories not in the cards okay how we doing
how we doing how we doing i'm out of your majesty we're doing good sovereign a building has been
upgraded i need a trading post hurry up a building has been upgraded we just need something down
here there's nobody down here just get it built here sovereign your marketplace now serves you
better your majesty a new building is complete recruit a monk okay
your majesty a new building is complete paladin in the name of the sovereign get some paladins out
here oh yes noble paladin always want to say that i need blacksmith
paladin what do they got for weapons victories level one paladin oh they're running away
this is perfect i'm gonna make like only paladins a hundred of them paladin's and monks
your majesty a new building is complete i'm gonna do our money not good victories
the shit's gotta get built hurry up oh there's the town
don't follow don't follow stay out of the tower what are you doing you don't just go right into
the back of their base this is the first time you've ever played dota you fucking idiot what
are you thinking you're just diving this is feeding intentional feeding that was like fucking a
thousand dollars victory is not in the car you're not seriously just kill these things are you
leave get out of here you just oh i hate you turn around please now this is the last chance
run run away huh what are you doing
i can't fucking believe you're still alive you did not listen to your coach
and you're i'm furious right now your trading post now offers healing potions good
all right i need more money let's get some more paladins veteran city guard good i need more
units what the hell's going on over here level seven damn okay good good for you
just don't die how we doing everybody all right i need more money though
the paladin comes out what happened to my other paladin no why are you all like this
i could probably kill this oh uh no all right no more paladins i'm going i'm getting weird with
this victory is not in the car of course there's a random fucking like a rat in here
tax collector where are they three one i gotta keep tracking them
are you taking my are you stealing my money good fucker oh god damn it where are my paladins
victory is not in the car i spent my money too early on the paladins that was like four grand
victory is not in the car praise doros
what are you doing why are they so dumb and i'm not i guess i don't even have to do anything about
this are you gonna take this whole city by yourself your majesty a new building is complete
refreshing your majesty the royal treasury is nearly under the cards
what a pain in the ass look what where did you come from your highness we've improved the godhouse
turn around fight kill them you can kill these oh no you can't run i need a blacksmith what happened
oh i got money i i i uh i uh i need a blacksmith um there's a there's one here
seven don't get yourself killed okay at least i have this somewhat protected
so i can at least make some money majesty the local blacksmith offers new services
in the name then upgrade this once this is done
you guys are fucked oh yeah fucking let's get in there the local blacksmith offers new services
all right this will ease up some of the pressure i think victory is not in the cards
how much money do you get for doing this for raising a building zero cool
that's gonna i want these to get a level up don't just run around aimlessly like this person's
doing victories not in the cards yeah you know you're dead you know you're not gonna do shit
victories not in the cards this thing you're gonna attack anybody all right level up i want
you guys a little five this is like their main base over here in the top left i don't agree
with this course of action but that's okay victories not in the energies of light we did it
we raised it all right now let's expand okay time to expand we're gonna do a in over here
expand and then on the trading post tax collector ice why would you do this why would you throw
yourself away like that refreshing why would you just throw it all away i don't understand it
your majesty our new building is complete your majesty our new building is complete
i'm gonna upgrade this 570 as long as no paladins die i'm completely happy
this is good fine take over there i need uh i need to i need a guard tower here
your majesty our new building is complete your majesty the royal treasury is nearly empty i know
i know i know i know god damn it congrats i need a guard tower right here a stupid sewer entrance
they can take the they can handle it all right i need oh i need shit here i need uh i need some
i need a paladin quick no i i don't every unit i have is gonna be a paladin i need money caravan
hurry up come on get in here hurry i need the money i need the money now please please victories
not in the cards all right but don't just okay i guess you're just gonna you're just gonna do that
chase them away guard house i need one right here what no i need a money come on just throw
your life away like that you're driving me crazy with this you're driving me crazy i don't know
what you do i guess you're just gonna do it i guess why would i stop you here oh wow they all
teleported and they won't fight they're like insects don't ask me what the hell's going on here
level five i'll take it you know fuck it let's go fuck it come on go on i don't have any money
i just gave you 500 energies of light they they can she can two shot most of people here i deem
your mandate just your majesty a new building is complete here they come take it all over
yeah this is it this is game over not in the card this is definitely game over at this point
isn't that they can't they can't do shit they can't do anything i'm gonna have like six paladins
over here right now we've improved the guard house very nice very good job i'm gonna put
another trading post up there tax collector over here the law of doros is above all others
you get what you're doing victory is not in the cards trading post and upgrade just to do it
your majesty a new building is complete energies of light this is where it all is i deem your
mandate just i can do this with just a building has been upgraded victory is not in the cards
advance okay take it out expand up here let's grab a couple people i would say
let's do uh another end let's put it in over here
like somewhere in the middle in between let's do a
energies of light another trading post over here too yeah fuck it let's go
take a look up top left victory is not in the car energies of light i just can't do anything
so they don't have any other units besides the else wait wasn't i supposed to make
about like thirty thousand dollars how many how many days do i have before it's all over
what i have four days your mandate just i only have four days no way take this shit
no no stay up here guys energies of light stay up here oh okay no i have 40 a new building is
complete well i'm about to win refreshing i think everything's dead up here no don't no no no no no
you need to go look you have to please there you go i knew you should have looked your majesty
a new building is complete game over everyone yeah the the paladins are
crazed unstoppable although i might get one killed here yeah level nine
we still good i think so where you guys all going why would you leave this all this shit up here
why would you leave go claim it somebody claim it this what the fuck are you doing
i deem your mandate just you still alive yeah you're good well no no you can't even
yeah there's two people up here this game will unless they have something down here which i don't
think i do the unholy are new i think i surrender i can speed the game up um refreshing i mean i
easy to understand what's going on
are you gonna build this shit or what a new building is complete
i'm still alive your majesty a new building is complete
all right towers are here i'm old and need a slow game adventure builds character
your highness we've improved the god house your highness we've improved the god house
there's a game over right there game over level 10 i didn't know you were level 10
my services may help here come all the paladins i deem your mandate just
somebody's who's gonna claim the 1500 dollars there's one energies of light
there's melt in this praise doros and made building too just a melt fest i deem your mandate
just they had a huge huge town too with here here here here here i do just what year is this game
from 2001 2002 something like that 2000 there you go well i have another 20 days to get rid of this
town up here and i'm pretty i'm pretty much good to go might as well no everything is dead up here
isn't it yeah that's it i win game over game over paladins win energies of light i think mvp this
game is energies of light hilltopper level 10 was scouting around doing a pretty damn good job
pretty damn good job energies of light we are victorious your majesty
awesome your son is returned to you your highness though we were unable to catch the nefarious elven
kidnappers the new head of the palace guard promises that such an intolerable breach of
security will never occur again rest well my leaves security your family is safe at last
nice very very very cool so what else is this left down here all the ones with stars are the ones
that i've beaten so i there's still a lot am i ready for anything am i ready for the siege
no no way there's not a chance in hell i'm gonna do the rise of the rat man no that one was too
much can i handle this now i don't think i could slay the mighty dragon forgive the intrusion your
majesty but you must awaken the day that julek the prophet spoke of is upon us the mighty dragon
vendral has awakened from his thousand-year slumber in the mountains of doom and is attacking the
realm oh no there is little time you must recruit forces to find the weapons that will help destroy
this threat before the kingdom becomes a scorched barren waste send heroes to find the sword of
byron the dragon smiter this manner of blade is the only known weapon that may cleave vendral's
hide but hold on sent heroes to find the sword of byron the dragon sniffer or whatever it is
this manner of blade is the only known weapon find the sword of byron the only guild you have
is the temple of helia you do not have the means to build any guilds or temples what
you'll have to find and organize the locals in order to defend your establishment use solari
to rally the guilds lying in the countryside find the hidden sword site and destroy it in
order to obtain the magic sword which will make vendral mortal who has disturbed my slumber
uh level two weapons go he's he's here now he's already here
what the fuck how am i supposed to do this sovereign your marketplace now serves you
better he's destroying everything blacksmith offers new services i need to send a a solaris
somewhere majesty the palace is under siege uh where do they go just hurry up i guess find a
new home
darkness is one day it's just like i'm reading i'm reading a line darkness
whatever i don't care can we kill this thing i don't even kill this
my soul blazes brighter tax collector
your marketplace now serves you better and will live thousands more he's leaving
okay he's gone he's gone he's gone let's go build quick i need um i can't build any of the guilds i
just
why is there a werewolf over here why is there a werewolf in this town
this is just not fair it's not fair what on earth are you doing here with this
bullshit
doing what's this doing why is it spinning sun scorch
sovereign a building has been upgraded i'm out of money all right tax collector
can somebody go up there your majesty it's been a 400 dollar bounty to go up there for
a bud since i started the game your marketplace serves you better your highness we've improved
the guard house
open the chest there's like five of them finally are you actually going to go up this way
your highness we've improved the guard house what the hell
what the hell get it open the treasure please your majesty our new building is complete
oh here he comes here he is your majesty our new building is complete that's one of the many
sons or daughters i guess a little five though not bad our new building is complete not bad
majesty the local blacksmith offers new services someone go up here your highness we've improved
the guard house your highness we've improved the guard house tax collector killing me majesty
the local blacksmith offers new services good that's really awesome i would just i would love
it if you would go up to the the 600 dollars would be great if one of you did finally one
fine go took a thousand dollars to get you to move all right we're gonna find new recruits
a new here we go there it is a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your kingdom nice all
right they've joined your kingdom you've claimed this you've claimed you've claimed it all right
we got uh another marketplace good more not bad keep going oh please your marketplace now serves
please don't this is guy's level 30 don't kill him get him to run away please he's level 30
what are you doing do something you won't get my no no get out of there is there a retreat button
level fucking 25 i thought they're gonna get to level 10 please run away don't get yourself
killed i need to delete the bounty on this guy wind blows me here or i uh i'm gonna lose you
all right just get up there everybody um kill it don't let that guy die there's like there's
like two level 25s here run run run run run run look i that's huge to collect 25 level people
they joined in the kingdom very awesome good i've got some high level people take this out
a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your kingdom good nice nice nice nice very good
very good very very very good more delicious looking reward how much money do i got i need um
i need more trading posts your trading posts now offers healing potions good
i need posts everywhere your marketplace now serves you better over here a newly discovered
outpost has agreed to join your kingdom all right keep finding shit not bad over here check this way
too
yeah where are they here in the library
is that level 30 i gotta track this guy has deserved my slumber oh give me a fucking break
like did i seriously just pull him i just pulled him his entire his entire crew uh all right
everybody everybody attack it where's he going which town is he going to majesty the palace is
under siege wait what kill the dragon i have a bunch of like level 30s and shit everybody get
in here kill it kill it oh i need the sword damn it no that's 2100 bucks an ill wind blows
no i forgot about the sword i forgot about the fucking sword all right
waste of money i'm so pissed off right now about that stupid fucking sword
forgot about the dumb sword it's just somewhere on this map too this sucks blessings to the phoenix
i'm out of money now because i did that i don't know why but for some reason i thought like i
could entice the level 30s to come over and start killing it but uh yeah yeah like you for instance
you're dead now give me speed lunard i lost my uh trading post and this is this is just a wash
at this point so thanks kind of still here speed i don't want to i don't want to go looking around
the palace is under siege i don't want to go looking around this is a big level big sword
unless it's in here if it's in here then i'm gonna go and i'll do it fire strike no i don't
why would i even attack him he eventually goes away right mission has sword not in there
big sword small voice
soul blazes brighter i serve with pleasure majesty the palace is under siege
do i throw in the towel i think it's time to throw the towel and i lost a level 20
no one's listening to me anymore and i want to well this person is dwight all right dwight will
you find the legendary sword doesn't look like it i have lived thousands of years and will live
thousands more where are you going leave but who are these people
all right somebody go all right dwight dwight's going for it again
where you at dwight did dwight die i think dwight's dead no there he is
the royal treasury is nearly empty i was gonna do it but then i got attacked i got scared
what's that oh a dead body you won't get my gold it's so dead nobody's taking it up on that offer
all right maybe 800 will do it somebody will run out there the town's dead yeah i mean this whole
this run is done the only way this run is saved is if somebody accidentally stumbles across the
sword and i throw it at the dragon and kill it right dwight you get 1500 bucks hurry up
where you are dwight he wants to leave someone just threw dirt in his face how he's still alive
dwight he says he's on route don't ask me why he's not there yet i don't do i even have any
heroes left pleasure i'm not sure there's even any here no i don't have any heroes thrown in the
cell all right let's do we'll do like one more scenario i think that'll take us to the end here
clash of empires ultimate sphere of power the valley of the serpents why would this one be
beginner the siege should i try it let's see what happens i'm gonna go for it majesty our battle
with the hostile and barbaric kingdom of borg in the conqueror has brought us to a siege of his
stronghold we must either force his surrender by blockading his supply caravans or storm his
this game is complicated by our local wizard skill which has chosen to side with borgens forces
still i feel we can prevail if you act decisively
okay what's the plan destroy borgens palace or cut off the caravan routes supplying him with gold
if they run out of resources they will surely be forced to surrender to our forces
no wizard guilds may be built okay what i got in the front here guard houses upgrade them
immediately okay what do i have can i do paladins that's what we're gonna do we've improved the
guard house your highness we've improved the guard house your highness we've improved the guard
house i serve with pleasure i got a wicked warriors guild here like let's do some warriors
i can't do any temples but no temples oh shit blacksmith get it out no
your majesty a new building is complete i fucking didn't see it your majesty
tax collector i need to build some more shit over here should i do a line of towers
i'm thinking like at least like a few towers in each slot blacksmith offers new services
right but that makes sense doesn't it i need some more uh knights just build 25 towers might not be
a bad idea it's kind of half versus half and it's this is their uh they're gonna have a
warriors guild who are these people are they gonna give me money we're gonna be friends
because it looks like we might be friends here all right i'm okay with this this i might have a friend
tax collector your majesty a new building is complete your majesty a new building is complete
your majesty a new building is complete your highness we've improved the guard house
damn it they're bad that might have been good your highness we've improved the guard house
it turns out it was not a bad idea to do the double bit up here help majesty help me
what are you doing we've improved the guard house what is wrong with you why would you go over here
there's no reason to do this right now you're just walking right into the front door of their base
oh you're so dumb no call back you is what i'm doing okay that's good
let's get some more gnomes don't have enough to go to level two yet i need a couple of training
guys we've improved the guard house i don't let me get one healer two healers and then
i'm gonna do a trading post over here god i'll do a trading post that's not good
tax collector that's really bad i can't make a trading post
the radar fog that looks like a spider i mean i was gonna say it looks like uh
like like a bear with a jet pack on with his knees and his legs kicked up and he's like flying
forward uh where we going up here your majesty a new building is complete
uh i can't make a trading post we've improved the guard house
just i'm just gonna spam knights i think that's what the plan is here is just spam knights
go in now get in go in go get in everybody my prowess is unmatched get in there if they're
stupid enough to do this and we might be able just to take this now can i go in the building
my prowess is unmatched look at how many are here wait is this mine or there is no it's mine
i think i can do this right now they might just do it i could go up to the caravan
people are kind of flooding in let's see what happens uh guys guys what are you doing
fellas uh might just be able to overwhelm them no they have skeletons where'd you get the
skeletons from who the hell is this it would be great if they these guys are idiots so you
want to know what happened there that's really cool so they your majesty the royal treasury
they spent the time to i go go attack this thing if you feel like it no no i'm going
we're gonna all walk down here while taking damage and then turn around and walk this way and die
the gnomes are the only ones doing anything well um okay didn't help at all and now i have no more
warriors and there goes all the money what is going on why is this 500 bucks to attack my own
building what why do i have this here why do i have this here is that their bounty what
that's the enemy's bounty oh shit stop yeah oh this is it this is bad bad bad bad is the kind of
counter attack what is this what's a rat bullshit i hate this in a game where you don't have any
control over anybody let's spawn rats in your base all the time why i'm gonna lose
i have no guard houses i did there was one here i don't like this rats to spawn in my base because
i made more buildings i don't even be able to take this i'm not even certain what's going on over
here so the gop the goblins are attacking them too right why wouldn't we work together and get
the goblins out of here no delaying the inevitable it's game over uh your majesty we have intercepted
very few of gordon's caravans over the last few days our spies report that his gold reserve is in
excess of 40 000 gold that's it that's it he had way too much money that i need so much more money
the siege expert not gonna happen hey thank you germa sucks for the five community subs
i appreciate it thanks for the five subs uh let's do this one disturbing rumors have reached my
ears majesty there are many reports of villagers gone missing near the edge of town
fearful whispers speak of some foul creature who has been harvesting the unwitting as slaves
for its diabolic schemes panic is beginning to well within the village something must be done
your highness or we face a grave crisis okay i suggest you initiate efforts to recover these
people and to rid the land of this frightful menace all right destroy the four slave pits
kill earl shek the three-headed beast i can try all right we got a guild we need uh
guard houses at least one or two i want a marketplace quick let's get a rangers guild
over here no like i need some exploration here i i a bird house did i say bird house
i didn't say bird house did i that built hurry please marketplace going up
let's get a rogue out here your majesty a new building is complete your majesty a new building
is complete okay so far so good i need a sovereign i need a marketplace now serves you better your
highness we've improved the guard house good appreciate that okay no more gnomes
i need let's do another let's do a warrior's guild your marketplace now serves you better
get the marketplace level two we've improved the bird house that was a good one i like that one
hard place level two i have all my
your majesty a new building is complete get some rangers i need money i have zero dollars but i
have like i have like eight people got a guard tower here waste the sewer because i want to put
a all right good explorer treasure chest get it 80 dollars a little worthless treasure chest
of your majesty all right thanks for the money let's get uh let's get a warrior let's do all
warriors from here on out need to explore head down here it's worth it for you to go down that
what's going on here all right fight fight there's like fucking eight of you here where what's going
on everybody fight just like just like 10 of you what are you doing fight them your majesty
the royal treasury is nearly empty here we go 2,600 bucks the queen of a nearby kingdom sent you a
healthy sum of gold and pleads with you to help find out what has happened to some of her missing
subjects majesty what are you talking about your majesty my ambition has paid off
oh where's this person okay i got plenty of people i've always my blacksmith but i have a
blacksmith yet get a couple over here but sewer i need to get good finally you're on your way
over there it's took you long enough nobody will miss this no don't just just
a new building is complete good i have i have all my heroes full your highness good we've improved
the guard house trading post over here find something find anything find anything there's
nothing down here i thought there was a neighboring kingdom there's nothing here
i guess until you find something i don't even mind found something what you find
an unwelcome guest slave pit take it out oh uh okay guys guys guys guys guys it was just
slow down here i found one but i gotta go back i need to level up the marketplace again and then
i need to put a trading post i'm like over here somewhere this is like is a whole town here you
guys handle this
you can't handle it it's okay majesty a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your
kingdom you did where oh okay well get back up there throw everybody in the pit your majesty
the royal treasury is nearly empty where the fuck did you come from how did you even get in here
did you come out of the sewer the queen of the nearby kingdom has again sent you some of her gold
to aid in searching the same heroes new building is complete she will no longer be able to aid you
because the goblins are making a heavy intrusion well that's not good just kill this thing please
all right what we got a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your take it out if you find
take it out what do you take it out you're standing next to it 500 bucks to protect that
do it it's just sitting right in front of you there we go nice trading post my mission has paid
off majesty a newly discovered outpost has agreed to join your kingdom good shit majesty your trading
post now offers healing potions good i have a trading post now up there didn't even need to
build one all right uh guard house let's do another guard house right here you guys good
doing some uncharted territory up there what happens when i destroy this
your majesty a new building is okay you've destroyed a slave pit and freed the nearby slaves
and now i got all these people and that i just won you won't get my gold that's an immediate
instant recruit pretty sick okay um all right get everybody back to town
what's up here i'm gonna build a trading post down there let's get a little uh village over here
don't just go up there what are you thinking don't do that nothing down here at all that's
because everything's in the top left trading post there trading post over here how much money do i
got i need this level two palace for god's sake your majesty a new building is complete
your majesty a new building is complete another trading route i miss the old germa who used to
eat baby food and shit his diapers majesty your trading post now offers healing potions
it your majesty the royal treasury is nearly empty
good there we go good good all right more money level two palace you're just going for it they're
going for it don't get too overzealous there's a whole entire kingdom up here
they're all running away don't just run away keep the paladin alive don't just start attacking
your highness the paladin renovations are finished all right we'll do it take it out more recruits
one step closer to oblivion in the name of the sovereign we're good
i think they can get it by themselves here your highness we've improved the guard house
your majesty a new building is complete one dollar nice uh that was chevus the awfully mad
ultra chaos blade stick 19 plus one this guy could probably play the rest of the game
energies of light praise doros let's see what we get from this
because i'm putting another trading post up here you better believe it
so nice even more looking good get a trading post get it up there oh yeah i'm excited about
this one right here we can go so uh there's a lot of things over here i think it's still
okay they're gonna attack uh i we need to be not so spread out they're coming in from the north
right now hello everybody uh come over here and just start start killing things
start fighting over here because your majesty a new building is complete
start fighting i need we're so spread out look at how many people i have but they're too spread out
majesty ill treasury is nearly empty we're good energies of light oh
fuck okay um did they kill everything up here i had oh my god i didn't even see this
i didn't even see this happening ah i need everybody over here bring everybody back here quick
please
energies of light we're gonna be fine
i have so many units they're all slowly but surely i have another post up here too
and by the way we're going right up the front door after this go right front door
uh
house level three send everybody up here thousand bucks this is a counter-attack situation
fairgrounds i can do temple of what's what i haven't done crypto i think i'm gonna do crypto
sounds like a plan don't spread out go right in i feel revitalized with btc back at 12k
oh sick keep going keep going keep going keep going this is gonna be yeah i'm gonna complete it
right here this gal game oh it's game over here yeah this is game over yeah i'm pretty sure this
is gonna be game over here is there any more there's one more little time an item of holy
significance holy significance this is it you guys just start saying it just say this is game over
until the game ends i think this might be game over here found it an unwelcome guest where is it
get it keep going it's right here somewhere the final hole we die oh well kill that
minotaurs up here go more people get up there i want the whole i want everyone to be
this is where the last thing is i was gonna get three grand
there it is final slave area to get energies of light
so
42 43 4400 dollars whoever kills this oh jesus what if i what the hell oops
that's a lot of money very cool
reward you destroyed you won't get my gold what is that
energies of light am i missing something here the whole i can see everything what do i have to do
oh it's this thing
kill it everybody stack he's just coming to kill he's coming into my town
um this music is where holy shit okay kill it everybody uh please he's kind of killing everybody
get over here everybody needs to stack and right now energies of light
energies of light no shit but we're good we're good we're good everything's fine everything's
fine who's gonna get the big big payout i'd love to be the one person that's not on this list of
heroes that doesn't care about the fixed 16 000 dollars energies of light praise
this work
yeah nice let's see what the end credits say our people are freed and the url check is dead
vim the hunter had offered to stuff and mount that insidious beast for display in your trophy room
but its body decayed at an alarming rate leaving our caustic ooze what made this terrible presence
never again threaten our people we will be vigilant your highness excellent awesome awesome awesome
awesome is this the hearthstone guy me uh i did play hearthstone once and it was a very very
embarrassing stream uh i think that's a good uh place to call it right at the six hour mark
i think that's a good place to go so i've got to tell you that's pretty fun there's a little
you know just it was cool i vaguely remember playing this a long long time ago vaguely
and not understanding what to do and i still didn't but no that was fun so i have a list of
games that i would like to play over this next few days and those games are gonna be where the
hell are they oh also this weekend i'm gonna give some details on that highlights activity book
stream we're gonna lock down uh kind of how that's gonna play out gta online i want to get some
friends together for that so i don't really know when that's gonna happen but it should be
fairly soon also uh there's not going to be a stream tomorrow i know i have so many things
to do tomorrow that i just can't this is not gonna happen but on saturday and sunday we will
go extra long saturday and sunday will be very long streams we'll probably play at least a couple
games on each of those streams not 24 hours but those streams will probably be at least
eight to ten hours long i would say because i had there's a lot of games that i have queued up that
i want to play but i was gonna stream tomorrow but decided to be just way too much shit to do
that it was just nowhere i was gonna be able to do it so i'll see you guys on saturday
and sunday we'll do a weekend long weekend thing the games list is let me just go over here let's
turn this off exit game i thought that was fun once you understand how the actual game works
it's kind of interesting to see what they do i wish there was a little more variables and
variants to what they did but we're also talking about a game that came out in 2000
so i have where's my list i'm gonna go over a list of things that i'm gonna do
i want to try to get this game ripper to work it's an old fmv game with christopher walken and
i think like paul giamatti it's an absurd fmv game that i want to try on saturday
okay i also have ordered and should be here in the next few days this is not going to happen this
weekend um actually no that's a little that's that's a little bit of a surprise i won't talk
about that but it's going to be something fucked up that you'll see on the stream in the next few
days the rain screen no uh there's also that new um that from software game that came up
um the mech one what's it called metal wolf chaos it looked interesting i kind of wanted to play it
is bad is it worth playing it's really bad really bad well that's on the list uh i have maximum
action oh maybe i see if i can get a few friends to play half dead two that game looks ridiculous
maximum action is that um okay i'm just i'm freaking out right now because on my steam list
while i was saying these names it was putting them in a different category and i was like
what the fuck is happening they're going from today to yesterday and it was happening as i was
clicking them but it's because it's midnight now no this is weird why hold on i'm gonna say something
hold on i'm gonna say something here yesterday this week this month what is going on right now
it's change it's moving all my shit around anyways um yeah so there's a lot of things
i want to do over this weekend we will hammer down the details on the highlight stream
there's a few other streams that are gonna happen for that carnival that might be really fun
uh but let's go back uh six hours ago let's do the bits and throw those subs up earlier we had
a freudian weapon came in with 250 thank you freudian welcome back hope all is well happy
thursday happy thursday to you too uh germa lied about near automata thanks to the five dollars
uh you know what must be done germa fear i never said i was gonna play near i may have showed
interest in near but i never said i was gonna play it somebody will clip it music's too loud
that's weird near automata is literally the best game ever made all right i don't i don't have a
plan to do that uh thank you chalkasaurus for the five dollars hey germa my cat just died
and i never thought it would make me this sad thanks for filling the hole with dumb jokes
i'm really sorry to hear that rest in peace to your cat hopefully your cat lived a very long
and and loved life because that's what you can do is you remember how much you loved each other
right i'm really sorry though take care and thanks for the five dollars we have five dollars from
psionic magnet here's some bits take them take them from me they are cursed and they're yours
now and there's nothing you can do about it well shit when you put it that way thanks with five
dollars appreciate it shimpa thanks for the 30 bucks 30 doll 3000 bits from shimpa much earlier
in the evening they said seems good you did it here's your bounty for defeating the tutorial
appreciate the 30 bounty for completing a 20 year old game's first level
uh thank you avery dropped thank you avery dropped dead for the five dollars germa i'm
the high person from earlier um my munchies tonight are a pint of cookie dough ice cream
but it sadly is not mom's making cookies love you jarby and i hope you have an awesome week
month you the best i'm taking my next hit for you my funny guy what are you like smoking a bong
ha ha thanks hope you enjoy your ice cream don't eat too much of it give you a stomachache
i don't even like taco bell gave two dollars and 50 cents attention sovereign the drawstrings of
my pants just flopped directly into a urinal what the fuck do i even do now i've been walking
around like i'm wearing a diaper because i don't know i don't want them to touch me
get some hand sanitizer and dump it all over your hands and rub it all over it and then
or cut them with scissors or whatever somebody will give you the right answer
uh crow rad thanks with five bucks a foul beast approaches thank you for the five bucks
appreciate it walrus incarnation thanks with 10 bucks no message just ten dollars thousand bits
it's a lot of money thank you will game for dinner thanks to the five dollars thank you
playing this gem wizards are op if you keep them alive oh it's a good one this was really
heavily requested i saw this pop up in the recommended channel at least probably three
or four times over the course of the last like year or something a long time ago people were
saying to play this so sometimes i just kind of scroll through and see what recommendations
people want to see for a game and we just blame thank you to uh first row boto for the four dollars
here's two dollars two dollars but you owe me a hundred thousand percent interest on this
this is a loan what is what is a hundred thousand percent interest on a four dollar loan
is that over a year is that a 10-year loan is that a 20-year loan quick pay it okay yeah if
you pay it within five minutes it's only going to be nine dollars and 12 cents well thank you for
the four dollar uh opportunity no just thanks for four dollars why dna thanks for the 10 bucks
hey germa i've been going through a rough time recently just want to say that your streams have
really kept me going thank you for brightening mine and everyone else's day
to my heart it's my pleasure thanks for allowing me to do this three four times a week thank you
10 bucks and hopefully you get through whatever you're going through you will thank you so much
for the 10 bucks four times a week kappa i know i was i was up until the carnival up until uh the
carnival stream really started to get work done on it i was doing four times a week now it's been
kind of brought down to like two or three but all things patience patience all things you'll see
despite your big projects i always enjoy the small streams i'm not i'm not gonna stop doing that
i said that a long long time ago this is like probably two or three years ago
i said that i want to start to move more focus onto stuff that's not video games i did say that
and slowly i've been trying to find ways to make more interesting things potentially happen on
streams not just playing a game or not just kind of hanging out trying to figure out what would
be fun to do with like a live broadcast and i think over the last year or two i have been
throwing in a lot of stuff that's not me just playing a game but no i don't i don't think i'll
ever not do stuff like this because i have fun just sitting here hanging out and talking
and you can't really do that with uh some of the streams that i've done in the past
it's fun just to talk and crack fucking jokes and have you guys like chime in and say shit
and it's fun it's funny i don't think this will stop but i will definitely be putting more time
and effort into that other side really depending on how well this stream is received will be an
indicator of how hard i want to pursue continuing down that road which i think i i i really don't
see how this wouldn't be a really fun stream we'll see but thank you thank you apple ship of the 250
hey man this is gonna be sappy uh but you're kind of the best thing that's happened to my mental
health in a really long time and i want to say thank you for that your old tf2 commentary videos
especially are indescribably comforting i have ptsd and it could be hard to calm myself down
sometimes but putting on one of those has been just what i needed recently sorry this is kind
of long but yeah you help a lot of people in a lot more ways than you realize have a good one
that's moving in a million ways that i can't even i can't even express i am so happy that people can
get much more out of this than simply just you know watch it and laugh and and then that's it
if this helps if it does i i i there's not much i can say i'm so fucking glad that you have
something here take care of yourself thanks for watching for as long as you have
i'm just gonna keep trying to do things that people might think of fun
um that's all i'm gonna do that's all i ever wanted to do and that's all i'm gonna continue
to do however you receive that is awesome to me i'm really happy to hear it but thank you with
the 250 apple shift take care we had a wave of subs and huge money that came in after that
we had 50 from just donate to germa we had 50 from macron to 10 community subs from nocturne
germa sucks gave five subs i'm not a big fan of your name but uh thanks with five subs uh thank
you miresca for the 10 bucks just thousand bits thank you just dropping just 10 bucks and no
message or anything that thank you i'm shocked and floored that people would even do that in
the first place thanks for 10 bucks vachi lala thanks for the five dollars congrats on reaching
a million subscribers on your main channel what that didn't happen no that didn't happen if
anything people probably been leaving that channel no that's not a million i don't need some dumb
number to tell me how i'm doing millions i doesn't matter i don't need some number to like whisper
in my ear that oh you did a million subs you win no no no that's not how this works top 1000
streamer you know i bet it's somebody's from five six how do i do i'm deleting this birthstone
i just i just i timed you up for 10 minutes i did i i thought it was gonna be like 10 seconds
it's 10 minutes i did do it i don't i that was a just a knee jerk reaction 10 minutes oh well
stop stop i don't want to start banning everybody you know what you're doing you know exactly what
you're doing you're not a knee jerk you're just a regular jerk i just shook my head side to side
you can probably hear it but thank you uh thank you spicy mexican taco for the 30 cents that i'm
not supposed to read that they wrote if i donate 30 bits will germa read a third of my message
fuck why why did i do that i'm not supposed to read these i'm seriously like that was
i'm not even that's not even close for what i'm supposed to read walrus incarnation thanks to
the 10 dollars right at the very end here hey it's walrus again you're great and i'm a long time fan
really hope i can make the carnival stream if you can awesome if you can't then it'll be a vaude
there'll be a lot of places to watch it hopefully you can participate if you can't then
you can enjoy it later on it should be a fun rewatch also thank you wing thanks for the three
bucks wing are you planning on the bionic boomer stream still also what's the best dark souls item
the estus uh bionic boomer kind of evolved into this stream i think the robot shit sort of evolved
from a lot of different ideas at the same time you would have to come later much later
i have not forgot about it it's hey it's still listed on okay i'm gonna let's go over um
i have my my streams ideas uh i just have like a little notepad over here i'm just gonna read
it uh out loud just to you okay we got an easy bake oven stream uh custom family feud with chats
answers the community uh gives answers and we do a live family feud uh hire an actor to be
germa while i sit in and coach them uh i can keep going the bionic boomer stream the asmr stream
there's all there's all there's like 30 more of those listed down here you don't think i got
shit going on come on spoilers that's not a spoiler you're gonna know that's gonna happen
the second that happens you're gonna fucking know it's happening more no i'm not gonna do that
read them all that's not gonna happen you got like a point two percent of all the things that
might be in the process of being made custom family feud where you know top 100 things that
people said in discord that's gonna take a lot of interesting planning but i want to do that live
like with um two families hire like just two full families to come in like they how they even
gonna know how much that would that cost it doesn't matter a lot did you like majesty yes it did
let's get the subs on here i will see you guys on saturday nothing tomorrow i've got a lot of
fucking things going on i'm trying to juggle them all at the same time and so far i'm doing pretty
damn good juggling some shit i'm not just juggling three pins here i got like probably
seven or eight chainsaws that i'm juggling and i'm not missing a beat right now and there's a lot
going on so there's a lot of subs that are about to show up here too is terraria still gonna be
saturday oh damn probably yeah but the thing about terraria is once um that could be part of it yeah
once star is a kind of done playing which i have to usually about five or half five hours or so six
hours or so we can move on to something else because i'll be around for a long time on saturday
we'll do a nice big chunky stream on saturday we could move on to dos after that too or sunday do
sunday on dos do some of the yeah i'm the whole the gates are open there's lots of stuff we can do
it'll be a juicy one scarce saturdays didn't a new horror game just come out on steam
i swear there was one that came out i don't know if it's any good but where the shot maybe
i just saw a sub name just i was hungry until i saw the name and i'm not hungry anymore i was
really really hungry i don't i i i'm gonna go to bed without eating now somehow what was the name
i don't i'm not gonna even repeat it i made some chicken hey thanks why are people getting nuked
i don't know but we have do any more bits no we got them all what everybody what if i watch this
watch this watch this watch this watch this watch watch watch watch this don't ignore the link stop
it i'm not ignoring the link look when somebody puts a link in the chat i don't just click
immediately what is it what oh click it quick all right this is called a sad story germa animated
what is this let's get this on the screen this has 150 000 views there's 150 000 views for
something that was uploaded like fucking yesterday today let's take a look this is called a sad story
hold up i don't want youtube fucking premium hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
let me tell you i hate fucking internet i fucking hate the internet all right here we go
ready three two one let me tell you a sad story there was once a young boy who was not well liked
the older his friends became the more bitter his hatred escalated every day they were beaten up so
badly he lost half of his face his eyes were swollen shut and he was covered in bandages
to see how he really felt was beyond words and every time it seemed they could just keep going
the punishment would get worse one day a woman stopped in to buy some bread he didn't listen to
he didn't seem to care what then one day he walked right into her bedroom she screamed and ran out
screaming what the next morning she said to her parents i don't know what i did to him you're
useless he just stood there and didn't even move all the while the old man tried to comfort him
then one day there was some sort of accident a boy was playing with his friends and the big
wooden hammer fell on one of his friends and knocked him down as well at the hospital the
nurse looked on but still as she said not that bad and then something
let's talk to transformer hey what's going on guys log dot zip here hello armor smelting to
sherry snowman here's a list of 50 updates you've probably never done or used why is this happening
now there's a good chance you've used a few of these updates this i don't have my there's no
browser tab it's taken off my computer so stick around to the end of the video i don't have a
browser open and special thanks to blue commander for today's world number one made guys stew
there's nothing on here you can make beetroot soup using six beetroots and a bowl but you've
probably never done that okay there we go uh all right that was weird the browser tab wasn't even
open anymore i closed it he's right behind you all right that's it guys i'll see you not tomorrow
i was gonna say tomorrow i really wanted to stream tomorrow but i just can't it's not gonna work
i there's no way it's not it's not gonna work chunky stream on saturday chunky stream on sunday
you need the link to that vid absolutely that was very very very good thank you too that was
um cast van cast van to pull was the person who made that it was great i'll just watch the
vod tomorrow and pretend that you're here that works too i'll see you saturday guys same time
we actually may start a little early on saturday not sure to try to get some more time out of it
but uh good night take care see you saturday have a great start to your weekend a great end
to your week as well see you later guys by the way uh we have zero drop frames in six and a half
hours if by sunday if by sunday end of stream we still have zero drop frames i'm gonna literally
just just just shoot and shouting out like like shooting the shit with my mouth about like
who's gonna you know we're gonna talk about hopefully it works you never heard the term
shoot the ship that means you like talking and is cox better than concast no they're both
dog shit there's literally no isp that is worth having in america but this vpn i think really
has completely solved the problem we'll find out we'll probably talk about this company on sunday
if it's a real see you guys on saturday take care
um i've been sitting here trying to find the perfect
sean connery quote i'm just sitting here trying to find them because the guy sounded like sean
connery and there's really nothing even worth putting on this room it's all like james bond
he just goes yes yes chicken mustard yeah i'll cut out the red meat sir too many dry martini's
then i shall cut out the white bread that's it that's like all of his lines all right uh bye