Hey everybody. How are you? Hi. Don't upset him. That's right. Don't upset me right now.
That's not one out of ten. You'll know when it's one out of ten. I'm giving myself a way to relax,
you know? I'm giving myself a cutoff, because if it gets, if it happens ten times, then I've,
I've got, I'm gonna, I'm going to leave. I'll see, I'll see you later. You know what I mean? Like,
you can't, you gotta, you gotta give yourself a, it's not healthy to get angry and then bring it
down like 50 times in one day. It's not good for you. It's not good for you. So we'll get a cabinet
ten. I got a mold meter. That's right. Oh, by the way, I actually have to change that to two.
My coffee got fucked up this morning and I was, I was very upset by it. That's, and then I stubbed
my toe coming out of bed and I screamed into the pillow. So, I mean, so that's already two out of
ten. Anyways, I want to talk about some stuff before we go forward. I want to talk about last
night. I want to talk about the game and I want to talk about some stuff, because that was the
first time we even turned that server on. We got a lot to discuss. First thing to discuss is,
uh, well, hold on. Let me tweet this first so people know that I'm live and how they know.
By the way, where's the, uh, oh, there it is. All right. Let me tweet this beer back. Okay. So last
night we did, uh, the Minecraft FTK experiment and it was very much an experiment because
none of the systems were in place last night. Uh, there was still some more development time.
Thing needed about like another, at least probably four or five days in the oven.
And we just said, you know what? Fuck it. Let's just open it up. Let's just essentially make this
stress test 2.0, uh, stream was an hour late and we just were like, let's fucking go and there's
no permadeath and no systems. Let's just see how many people join and let's just see if we can have
any fun. So, uh, it came out undercooked. Yeah, I did. And that was to be expected because we did
a stress test the day before, but you, you can never, you can never have that exact experience
that you're looking for with like even like a stress test, because if I go in the discord
and I'm like, Hey, can we get like a few hundred people to connect to the server? And it's like,
all right, yeah, let's go. Uh, times that by like 50 is hard to get that, uh, to get that to work.
Time's upset today. I'm not upset. What are you talking about? I had fun last night.
I mean, it was, the whole thing was a shit show, but I think that was to be expected at some point,
but that was not what that game was going to be. So I have seen a lot of people look, I'm taking
the people have been writing about, uh, here's what I didn't like about it. Here's what I would
like changed. Yeah. What, what was up with this? What was up with that? I totally hear you. And
none of that last night was what the game was supposed to be. So we're going to put it back in
the oven for like another week or two and try it again. But the data that was collected yesterday
was so important. There's no way we could have ever had any of the data we had last night.
Unless we had a shit show last night. You know what I mean? It's almost like you have to take
like an arrow to the arm before you're allowed to, you know what I'm saying? Like I sometimes,
no, you don't have to take an arrow to the arm. You could just dodge, but just know that the arrows
coming, you have to get an arrow shot at you first. Just dodge long story short. Yes. Uh,
there's going to be a more time is what we needed. Now let's move on over to jump king.
I still had fun last night and I know a lot of people did too. And I know there was some
dumb shit that happened last night and it was fun, but that was a glorified stress test too.
So don't worry. That was not the game. It's not like, oh, that was it. Okay. Well, that was
not what he described. Don't worry. Don't worry. Jump king. There is a smoking hot babe at the top.
Okay. So this is a game. Uh, this is a, what is other babes? Was that even here? I don't
remember that being here. It's a porn game. New game. All right. So I'll be playing this
with the controller or is that a bad idea? No, it's fine. Okay. You've heard the legend too.
So you're gonna get that babe, right? Go on then get up there.
All right. Is it just jump? You hold the button. Oh yeah. If you, it's like Luigi,
does down also do it? So it's just hold button. I get it. All right. So you, it's like,
it's like playing pool on it's like a pool video game. You have like a power and then a spot that
you move the bar to. Yeah. It's like playing a video game pool. I get it. Yep. The red crown
wood. So this is the game because I can't move in the air. Whoa, boy. Okay. So how do I get these
ones then? And if I press right, I'm not upset. I'm fine. If I, if I press right, how much does
it go right? Does it go all the way? If I like hold and press right, it's okay. It's the whole
thing. It just launches you. You can't do a small left or a small right. Okay. This is going to be,
oh, this is going to be something. All right, let's go. So I have to go like this. No, like this
from here. There it is. This is like the first five seconds of the game. I'm not upset though.
You can tell I'm, I'm laughing. That means I'm not upset. Oh, for the love of not upset about
anything. I'm just fine. That's not one. Just not that hard. There we go. Okay. So is there
checkpoints in this game? She must really be something. No, there's definitely like little
safe spots like there are in getting over it. There has to be. It's that once you get it down,
you really get it down. All right. I'm thinking probably from back here. Yeah. Okay. Good. What
the hell am I looking at here? I have to hit what? Okay. So I've got to get in the middle.
Oh, shit. Okay. Now from here, I'm gonna hit my head on the ceiling though. All right. I'm
starting to get the hang of it. Don't go too far. Don't go too far. And then let's go.
Uh, from here and then hold it down. Let go. All right. Don't hit your head. Good. All right.
From here, I got to go. I got to take this very slow. I have to go slow. And then I'm thinking
on the left side here. Yeah. It's got to be like this. I might fall here, but it's attempt. It's
a good attempt. No, no, I'm not going to fall. What the fuck are you talking about? It's all right.
Oh, okay. Easy, easy. Don't get too confident. You're in the middle of the oak tree. Oops.
All right. I had it. Fuck. I'm not mad. What was this one like this? Yep. All right. Easy,
easy, easy. That's not too, that's not dropping too far. It really isn't. Oh, okay. Slow down.
I had the right idea though. That's the right idea. Just not as long.
Yeah. Oh, my man, slow down. My man, slow down. All right. I'll slow down. I'll slow down. I had
it. What am I doing? Okay. All right. All right. It's not even that bad. I, I really just fucked
it up though. Bad. Faster. Don't tell me to go faster. That's not a good idea. Oh man. Okay. I
really do have to slow down. All right. That's fine. And then this is the long one. Don't you
dare. And then up here. Okay. Then like this. All right. How do I get through here? Reliably.
I have to like fall into it. I got it. I got it. What's this? How am I supposed to get up here?
Do I have to bounce off the wall? I think I have to bounce off the wall. Just jump. I don't have
to go down from, hold on a second. From here? Is there any music in this game? The ledge on the
left? Wait, what do you mean the ledge on the left? Wait, what? You mean like over here? What?
How am I supposed to get over there? That's not even a ledge. That's a, it's like two pixels.
Oh shit. Oh, all right. Good. Good. Just breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe.
You got to go from far away here. This is, look at how small that area that is. And I don't want
to fall. Holy fuck. Okay. Uh, save it? There's no saving. Wrong one. Why is it here though?
I can't, I don't, I don't jump, I jump from here, right? If I do a huge jump from here,
will I make it to the bottom one? No, I don't think so. I don't like this. I don't like this.
Oh, I don't like this. I'm a Nancy Drew streamer guys. I don't like this,
but I'm, I kind of addicted to it. I'm not, that's me. That's not upset. I'm not upset.
I'm just stating that I don't like this. That's not me being upset about something.
Look, I can go to a restaurant and order food, take a bite out of the steak and go,
I don't like this steak. I don't think I'm a meat person. I don't like meat. I'm not like,
fucking meat shithead. I hate you. Meat sucks. And like stabbing it with my knife. That's,
I'm not doing that. I'm just simply saying that I don't like meat. That's not me being upset at
the meat. That's been me just telling you, but I don't, I don't like to, I don't want it.
Vegan. Stop it. Oh God, no. This ain't even like the first five minutes of the game too.
All right. That was pretty clean. All right. That's clean. Clean. Clean. Oh no.
Oh slob. Okay. How do I get over there? Some of you guys right now are sitting there going like,
oh my, he didn't even know. Just wait till he gets to the broken down helicopter. Oh fuck. Okay.
I've actually got mad there. I really did. I, that, that was, I'm, I am upset about that part.
You can put one down. I have to change the stream title. This is going to be,
this VOD is going to be eight or nine different VODs. And there's going to be a number on each
one. So you're just going to be able to skip to your favorite chapter of angry, of angriness.
That's one. I actually, that did piss me off. Scroll down the VOD listed seat. Oh, well it looks
like angry eight to angry nine was six minutes of two different VODs. Wow. That's interesting.
He really dialed it up there because from, from one to two, it was an hour.
I wonder what happened here. I'm down to the beginning. I'm going to go down to the beginning.
Oh my God, man. I'm the, I'm, I'm even slowing down. I'm even slowing down too.
I was up there. I had it. I really did. I'm doing it way too long. What the hell am I doing?
That's not upset. That's me asking a question. I'm just simply asking a question.
If you think it's hard now, you will not beat this game. I didn't be getting over it.
I got like 40% of the way through getting over it. And then I think I remember actually saying,
why am I playing this game? Like, what do you get from this? This is me. I'm not upset about
anything. I'm just asking a question. What do you get? What do you gain from playing this game?
The taking up a smoking habit. I don't know. I don't get it. You get gamer points. Well,
I don't need any more of those. All right. Here we go. I'm going to get out. I'm going to get
through this tree right now. I already have a gamer license. Yeah. I don't, I don't need a
different gamer license. I already have one. I already have mine. All right. Slow down.
How I don't understand how that was wrong. Dude, come on. My webcam is the best part.
I don't even have my webcast on. He can't jump omega law. Yes, I can. I just need to get,
I got to get used to the control system. This one is just, this one's fucking me every time.
It's just fucking me up every time. You got to be so good with that one. He sucks. This game is
fucking hard, man. Dude, the jump King is hot. What the hell are you talking about? All right.
What am I doing wrong here? I got it. I got it. All right. Everybody can relax. I got it.
You know, the worst thing about playing a game like this on stream is if I, if I was just alone
in my room and no one was watching, that doesn't bother me at all. Fall and death, whatever. That's
just going to happen. The whole, this whole game was designed for you to fall a thousand times.
Right. But when you, when you're in front of like a bunch of people, everyone knows you just fell.
Even though even in my mind, whatever, who cares? This is a giant microscope being pointed down at
my house. There's a bunch of alien scientists looking through my window right now with a fucking
microscope. Damn it. It's because you're so small. No, you know what I mean though? It's like,
if you play a game like this, you're going to, you're going to, it's going to take you
50 hours to get up here. And it don't matter. You don't have any alien, you don't have aliens
with telescopes looking through your window and then go and they go, Oh, did you shoot that one?
It's just you and your Eggo waffles. Fuck. Okay. Fuck. How am I going to get over there? How do I
get to that one? How do I get to that one? How do I get to that one? How do I get to that one?
Oh my God. I got it. Um, now what? All the way over to the right. But is it all the way? I'm
going all the way, going all the way. I made it. I've made it. I did it. See right now, the aliens
are looking down. They're going like, I can't believe he did it. I'm the laser. There's no
reason to watch earth entertainment anymore. He beat junking chapter one. Got it. Oh, I got,
this is a safe spot right here though. That's okay. That's fine. I'm, I'm, I'm glad I cannot
fall down this unless I really fuck this part up right here. All right. That fucking guy driving
the car, the guy in the fucking car that just sped by at a thousand miles per hour, it's just
screamed in my ear. What the fuck, man? Look, that's so annoying. That's so annoying. Whatever.
That's two. That's I, give me a break though. Seriously. I get to be mad at that.
I get to be upset about that. That's so annoying. And somebody just screaming outside your window
as loud as they can. Like somebody just threw a glass bottle at my house while I took that jump.
I'll get back up there. That was the alien laser.
We missed. Fuck. Don't make me laugh. Don't make me laugh.
Okay. Please get me up there. I just want to get past chapter one.
Oh no. No, no, no. The guy driving the fucking car, man. He's so easily distractable.
Oh, I'm so easily distractable. I'm so distractable. I get so upset.
It's like so easy to like turn me around. All right. I got to relax
because right now in my head, I can't stop it. I can't stop it.
There's a voice in my head that continues to say, fuck that guy. What's that guy's problem?
That guy's a dick. Isn't that guy a dick? Don't you hate that guy? That guy sucks. And I'm just like,
yeah, that guy sucks. I have to make a jump. Hold on. Hold on, Larry. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God. Okay. I'm back. This one actually is, this one's a challenge. Actually, it really is.
Now if I just get, okay, relax. There's no cars now. There's no speeding.
All right. Just make it over here. Got it. Done. Got it. Okay. We're good. Colossal drain. I got,
oh yeah, but this channel points on the channel now. If you want to redeem them, I guess. I
haven't done anything to them. It's just whatever they have for default. So,
okay. I definitely can't, that's going to, I can't stand on that. That's a tiny little,
oh yeah. Really? How am I going to, oh shit. Okay. Do I, is this, is this, is this a jump up
scenario? It is. I need some trajectory here. All right. Oh, oh, oh, oh, all right. I haven't
made a mistake, a major mistake in a little bit. Yes, I did. Oh, that's, that sucks. That sucks.
That sucks. I'm not upset about that, but that sucks. Okay. Stop. Okay. Good. Same deal. Oh no,
God. Oh no. Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah. That would have been three. That would have been three. It would
have been, that's not though. Okay. I'm going to, I don't know how long to hold for that one though.
If you're not with you, it's the end too. I'm good. How are you? This game's addicting though.
That's the one problem. Thankfully, this part's very easy. This one though, it's just,
I can get this one every time, but this one, not every time. Don't you dare. All right. Let's go.
Ah, got it. Ooh. It feels so good when you get it. You know what I mean? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Um,
let me take a minute here. So I have to bounce off the wall. Or do I? Or should I just jump
straight over? Is the, is the rain going to hit me? Is there obstacles in the game? Is there
hazards? That's not a three at a time. It's not, it's not that bad. Okay. Now it's bad. Now it is.
Now it will be. It will be in a minute. It will be here. It's going to be in a, oh my God. Oh my
God. I'm not mad. I'm not upset about it. Oh my God. I'm just surprised and very, very sad.
I'm just surprised about what happened. Oh man. I'm just surprised. I went too far. I went way too
far. Oh, hold it in. Hold it in. Hold it in. Hold it in. Hold it in. Hold it in. Uh, hold it in. Uh,
yes has, is online gave 5,000, gave $50 right now. Good job getting past chapter one.
Thanks. I'll take the congratulatory $50. Thanks with 5,000 bits. Uh, yes is online. Thank you.
Are there save points? No. That's not mad. That's laughing.
Okay. It's all being bottled up. Get off there. Don't make me mad. Okay. He's evolving. No,
I'm good. Okay. We're good. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
Okay. Crisis averted. Sorry. Sorry. I sat down. I sat down with thumb tech. Sorry about that.
Why is this? Is this on my chair? This part just sucks. It just, I know. I know. He doesn't know.
Broken out helicopter. I know. But for my, my current perspective in the current environment,
I'm in right this second. This part is hard for me. Just jump because if you get this wrong,
even if it's easy, is this a shovel night guy? I'm just realizing this right now. Somebody just
used the channel points. What did you do? Don't you dare. That's exactly what I thought when I
saw this. Somebody said, highlight my message, pee pee poo poo. That's a good use of channel
points. I don't even know if they do. It's gotta be longer than that, but you get it's scary because
don't you get, it's gotta be longer than that. I'm just so scared to do a jump there. Uh,
at the starfish. Thanks for five community subs. Appreciate it. Thank you. Get me over here. Come
on. All right. Come on. Come on. Now I'm good. I just have to figure out what they want, what,
what they, what they want me to do here. Adventure MF Dan, five community subs. Thank you, Dan.
Thanks a lot. Both of you. Is it, is it? Okay. All right. All right. Okay. Now these are going to
fall, aren't they? These are going to fall. I'm going to jump on them and they're going to fall
down. No, they're not. Why did that, why did that go longer? Why did that go longer? Why did that
go longer? It's like, why did it go longer? Why did it go longer? What was that? Is that one
different, these paste? I'm not mad. I'm asking a question. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not
upset just asking questions. That's just, that's like, that's, I feel like about like a politics
show. No, no, no, no. I'm not, I'm not upset. I'm just, I'm simply asking a question. Like,
no, you're very clearly very upset. We have more subs coming. Fitty gave some community subs.
Just farming channel points and emotes. Ignore, please. Well, thank you, Fitty. Friends are fun
when you hang out together and you don't get upset about anything. I almost blew that one.
He's malding. I'm not. You'll know. You'll know. It's been very clear when there's been a two and
there's been very clear when two and three have happened. So three, that's cheated. Oh, no, no,
no, there was no three. Yeah. Yeah. You got, you got, you guys are just like, you guys are gas
lighting. We didn't think that I had a third month, right? Witty username. Thanks to the five
communities. Oh, I like this game though. It's fun. Even though I, I'm not a big fan of steak,
but if it's, if it's prepared, well, I'll, you know, I'll lead it. All right. My hands are,
wow. It's that spot up here that just killing me. Cause I can do this without a problem. Now
this area is not a big deal to me at all. As I'm very clearly showing, not making a single mistake
getting up to that point. For instance, like here is fine over here is fine up to this one.
And then over here. So as you can tell, shit, I'm just, it's just this jump here. That's causing me
any problems at all. Why did it go to what happened there? What? Hold on. No, I couldn't
put my hands down. What happened? Did my analog go the other way? Lots of community subs get the,
the acidic vengeance. Thanks for five community subs. Okay. Seriously. No, no, no, no, no. What,
what, what happened? What's going on? I don't understand. Okay. It's not, I'm being dead
serious. Why does, what is going, why is that happening? I'm not crazy. I don't know why that,
why would I do that? Why would I do that? Why would I get all the way up there and just then do
that? Use the D pad. That's adding, uh, that's fucking it up for me. I can't use the pad now.
I'm too used to it. What did I, I don't, I just wish I knew what, what was going on.
Mark, Marks, Marcus, Marcus, five community subs. That's another five community subs.
I just asked, I'm just asking a question. Don't you guys know that as long as you tell people,
you're not mad, you're not bad. It doesn't matter because you know who you, you know,
you know yourself. And even if your face is turning bright red, I'm not, I'm not upset about
this. You're only mad when you actually tell people you are. All right. Now what the fuck
is going on over here? All right. I got to use the D pad. It's, it's getting in my head now.
It's good. The D pad things get in my head too long. I know, but then it was too short.
It was too long. Then it was too long. It was too long. Then it was too short. Then it was too long.
It was too short. Then it was too long. If you're going to do the impression, you have to raise
your voice in a couple of octaves. Nope. I can't do the D pad. Shit. I can't devolve right now.
No, no, no. Okay. I can't, I can't just evolve. You know what I'm saying? Yeah. You know, it's,
it's happening and I haven't even been playing for like an hour. Um, the controls don't work.
I'm playing a dream and I'm going to dream right now. I'm pressing the buttons in the wrong order
and shit. Yup. You guys know what I'm talking about. You know, when you get like to a point
where you're devolving and pressing buttons in the wrong order, I'm pressing buttons in the wrong
fucking order and I'm, it's over. Somebody came over and shook me and I'm not even, I'm not even,
I'm not even actually like upset about anything. I'm just devolved. God damn it. I was fucking
devolved. Oh, all right. Add it. That's three. No, that, that counts. It does. No, fuck that.
That's I'm, I'm count it. That's fine. I actually am annoyed by the fact that, but I'm not, is it
count? I'm not mad at game. Okay. I don't think I did. I, I, I, somebody came over and hit me
in the head with a wrench. I can't, like the buttons, the controls of a foreign to me now,
like left, right. And then a, or like a, and then right. I, it's foreign to me. God, I know it's
just three buttons, but when they, they, they bleed together. Relax. Cause like in my brain,
it's like left and a, or a then left, or a then right. No, a then right. A left and a.
I'm doing moving and then jumping instead of jumping and then moving the analog. And I'm just
doing it backwards. I'm fine. Next up we have, oh, hold on. Let's like, I can't do this joke
unless I have a face cam. So I can't do this yet. Maybe later. Cause I'm too focused. Why can't I
do this one now? I was doing it. Okay. Stop it. Okay. I need to, no, don't. Whoa. Look at how
many fails. 62 fails. Where's my cam? Is it even plugged in? No. Hold on.
All right. Let me, let me get this ready.
This is my break time. This is a show. What are you talking about?
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome back to around politics where we talk about politics.
We go over all the things in politics. Joining me now via satellite who claims he's absolutely
not angry at all. Fire satellite from Las Vegas, Nevada. We're going to get the state of his
political party. German nine eight five. Are you with us? Yeah. Yeah, mom. What are the questions?
Just, uh, just have a few of those myself. Why is your face so red? We don't know. I didn't tell you.
I was angry. I just kept, I was just coming on the show to answer a few questions to give you
some of my own. He's so livid. Mega milk. What's that? Stop. Stop. Oh yeah. Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen, hold on a minute here. I'm getting, I'm getting word.
Oh, what's that? Uh, this just did. Ladies and gentlemen, if, if you are wearing a white shirt
with blue sleeves on it, just getting the word right now, then you have to absolutely be
referencing. What am I getting on my desk here? You absolutely have to be referencing some fucking
weird anime shit apparently. Yes. Anytime you wear a blue sleeved t-shirt. What? I don't know. All
right. Let me at least get through chapter two. We're just having fun today. Where am I? Where am
I? Where am I? Where's my character? What happened? How did I get over here? Is this a secret?
Where? What happened? Yes. What do I do about this? Can I get anywhere from here? I think I have to
go back up. Go down. Oh, what? I didn't know there were illusory walls in the game. What?
Okay. Now that I know that, that doesn't really help me though. This just kind of makes it,
this makes it harder. Why would I do that? That makes it harder. I just like burped and acid went
up into my throat. Is that me being mad? That's my body being mad, right? Or I think that's my
hernia. I think that's just a symptom of a hiatal hernia. Yeah, I think so. Okay. So no, then no,
that doesn't matter. Five? All right. I was up there so much. I just got to get back to what I
was doing. Just back to where I was. Holy shit. I almost just blew that. No, no, no, don't go
straight down. Oh, man. I had it too. I'm sitting at the roulette table and I put a thousand dollars
on like red 21 and it landed in the space next to it. So I was like, that's like, that's,
that's $35,000. I had it. I mean, it was right there. I thought, you know, it'll happen again.
If I do it again, slow it down. Take a minute. That's Vegas humor. Stop. Why did I even read
chat? What was the point of reading chat? Why did I look over? Why would I look over there?
What would I look over at chat for, for that reason? At that moment? Why would I do that?
There's no, there's no reason for me to look over the chat room when I'm in the middle of holding
down a jump. Like I'm just asking to lose. There's no reason to do what I just did.
I'm not mad about this. I'm just stating a fact. Okay. Mad.
Hmm. Quiet. Quiet. Good. Good. Good. Now get over it. All right. Took me long enough. No,
just not that. It's something about, there's a bug in the game. There's a bug in the game.
There has to be a bug in the game. There's a bug in the game. There's a bug in the game.
There's a bug in the game. There's a bug in the game. That spot right there. There's a bug in
the game. That's the third time that's happened. It's the only time it's happened the entire time
I played the entire game for an hour. That's the only time that's happened. It's only in that spot.
Why is it only in that spot? Makes no sense. That's the only time that's happened.
Like I'm trying to get that to happen right now. And it won't.
You understand? Why? Why is that the only spot where that happens?
There's a bug in the game. Five. Maybe. I'll put it to the judges. We'll see. Get out of here.
Is this a British bake-off?
I just need to determine if he was actually angry or not.
Now what? What's up here? I did it. I made like this shop. Okay, there's a shop right here.
Now what? I did it. I'm so scared to do this. Oh, look at this next part. Look at this next part.
Foss King's Keep. This doesn't look that bad. You're right. It really doesn't. As long as I
slow down. I mean, that's I think that's what I have to do. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
It's not that bad. It's not. Get the bird. Get the bird. No, I don't care about the bird.
Why would I get the bird for? I'm not getting the bird. You want to go get the bird.
Why would I do that? Just to get the good ending. All right. The judges have determined that I was
actually upset. Oops. I didn't mean. Okay. I meant to change it to 20.
I'm sorry. I meant to change it to 20. Yeah, I guess I leveled up. I guess I got more. I leveled up.
Every time I go another floor. I get another 10. I leveled up. No, stop. Okay, just just do what I
was doing. Every time you fall down, you lose. No, that's not how it works. You don't get to take
you don't take levels away. You just gain levels. You don't d level in any video games. In what
video game do you d level for doing poorly? No, you just get stronger. How's that wrong? You d
level. Okay. Don't be stupid. These little jumps make me want to go to the dentist and have them
just drill without novocaine. Am I mad? No, no. Okay. No, you're just a psycho. Yeah. Okay. That
doesn't mean I'm mad. How am I going to get up here? I have. Wait, what? I see. I know. I know
all you guys are secretly rooting against me. That's the thing. You know what I mean? I know it.
I know. It's like I'm the bad guy. I'm the I'm the guy that comes out during the wrestling event
that knows he's going to get booed when he comes out. I'm the heel of the stream. You want to see
me fall. You want to see me fall down. So these little jumps that make me giggle. Okay, stop.
Stop. Stop. I will actually fuck this all up. That's not mad. You guys have been around this
channel for long enough to know what that actually means. Right? You guys are just waiting for someone
to open the door and hit me in the back of the head with a fucking chair. You know how many
pog champs would happen if somebody just give guy in a speedo came in the back door here
and just smashed me in the back of the head with a fucking folding chair. I oh my don't do it.
I'm gonna try uh see if I can get to the next level.
I fell. Why is the audio so bad? When was this video uploaded? Or this video was
uploaded like two years ago. Why does it sound like a cell phone video?
There are a lot. Like can I just say there are at least like three or four very large viewed
WWE best chair shots. This is happening to me.
I was reacting. Oh dude. Oh what the oh holy shit those are brutal. That wasn't
bad. I was reacting to the video. You know you do something enough times that you probably have to
figure out that it's not what you're supposed to do. I think I've hit that moment right now.
No you don't go that way. Is it mad if I tell that person to shut up
for spamming another streamer's stream in here? No that would just be me. That's not mad.
Okay slow down. Now I gotta go from here to there and then damn how am I gonna get from here?
Oh that's such that's that's very very very difficult. That's very very very difficult.
I got babies. Oh this is hard. How do I get this one? Oh that was close. That was very close.
Oh man that was close. Why did I hold it for that long? Okay slow down. Get the get the get the bird.
Okay fine. No no don't I'm not getting the bird. I don't care. Don't don't don't don't get bird.
All right I'm not gonna get the bird. I'm not I don't even have the confidence to get the bird.
I don't even have confidence to go up this way. I'll have confidence. I will. There'll be that
moment where I play you say run. You guys know what I'm talking about. I also would rather fall
down the whole thing and have to go up because I'm just seeing this on repeat and it's killing me.
God get. All right one two three go. No no no no no no that one is too hard.
I'm gonna make a steam review and it's gonna say I like the game a lot.
It's very fun but some of the jumps just feel like they're unfair and I would know
because I have I'm gonna write seven paragraphs about this game and all the things that I don't
like about it now it's stupid now I don't like it with 0.2 hours in game. I'm gonna have a
full steam review about all the things I didn't like about it and I may have not even gotten
past the menu screen. I gotta try this. No what a mistake. It's fine. Oh it's just I don't know
what it is about this. I don't know what it is about this one. I just I'm stuck here. I'm stuck.
I'm just stuck in this one. Thank god I can't fall. I said I would rather fall but no I don't.
Imagine if I had to come up here and do this all over again just to get to the top to miss that
jump like five times. No no no I don't want to do that. Okay now what do I do? Should I jump up
to the right? Don't click link. What's what do you mean don't click link? I have to go left do I? No
I don't. I'm not clicking the link. I'm not clicking the link. Are you guys about to get like
banned? Why did I jump this way? I have to jump this way. No I don't. What about what's going on?
Do I? Oh no. Click the link. All right get that fucking link out of here.
Get that link out of here. Get that link out of here. Get that. Get the link out. Get that.
God I don't want to see that link again. Another. Get rid of that. Somebody just posted it. Ban that
person. Right there. Ban them. Good. I saw another one ban. Good ban. Ooh. Ooh. All right a lot of
people getting banned right now. Oh. Watch out. Oh that one was in the mouth. All right that
person's not gonna be back for like four hours. Oh shit. Banned. Banned in the mouth. All right
what happened? Oh I did it. I actually did it. All right well I did it. I'm gonna do it again.
Oh my god I had it. I had it. I had it.
No. No. Ladies and gentlemen. Fire satellite. Let's see how he's doing.
To discuss all politics. Larry Stevenson. I'm okay. I'm not red. I might have been red for a
little bit. I'm all the way down here now though. Okay. It's not that bad.
Milk thing. You want me to get the chairs? All right guys so I so I guess so I guess the Toronto
Blue Jays need a new uniform. Which Toronto Blue Jays have to have all new uniforms now because
they're the milk team. That now that counts. That does. Yeah. That counts as two. Toronto.
I don't even want to say this out loud but how fucking stupid would that be if they were the
Toronto Mad Mecham. That would be so stupid. Wow. Oh that hurt my back.
The Toronto. Imagine having to fucking say that as an announcer. How embarrassing.
I can't say it out loud. I refuse to say it out loud. I don't even know what it is.
I don't even know what it is. Why would I just talk about something I don't know anything about?
Fuck. Okay I need to relax. Here's your Toronto. Your Toronto.
Everybody just screams. Cheers. All right stop. I have to do this right.
Why does everything have to be funny? You know what I mean? Everything is funny.
Why does everything have to be so funny? Turma why do you laugh so much? I don't know because
everything's funny. What am I supposed to do? Thank you Bible Black for the five community subs.
Thank you Bible. Appreciate it. That's apparently the funniest thing I've ever seen.
What? Why is that so funny? Whatever. Google it. No. Thanks for the subs though. Appreciate it.
No.
Okay I'm gonna lose my mind. You guys are an absolute menace. I didn't say it either. All right
I keep having trouble with this shit. This one that jump right there is one of the hardest. I've
read the Steam review. I remember them saying that part right there is the worst. Nondescript
civilian. Thanks for the 10 community subs. 10. Just dropped right now. Thank you so much.
Appreciate it. 50 subs? What are you talking about? When? Dude Pog. What? He said that. Oh I don't
know. How am I supposed to differentiate between what you guys have for like porn usernames? I
don't know. Am I supposed to know the title of every porn ever invented? How am I supposed to
know that? How am I supposed to do that? Yes. Damn it. Oh nah. This one sucks and I'm not
good. Okay. Holy shit. All right. I gotta get on that. How am I gonna get on that? How am I
gonna get on that? There's no I can't get on that. I can't get up there. This stream is erotic. It
is not. It is not. Jump up there. Um can you like jump backwards? Guys is that jump really that easy?
I don't think it is. Oh fuck. Go right. Go right. Go right. Let me go right. I can't make that
right. I can't make that jump right. No I can't. Can I? Holy shit I can. Oh my god. I was gonna
jump on the left. What is this? Shop? Greetings. These boots are fit for a legendary hero.
Crafted by a distinguished master with these you'll get to that babe in no time.
Upgrade? Since I like you I'll cut you a deal. For only one measly coin they are yours.
What do you say? Eh? Yeah. You don't have one coin. I'm afraid the price point is that the bear
it appears there aren't many other customers around. You don't happen to have any rich friends.
It's the bird. I'm ready. The bird is right here. Is it right below me or is it to the left?
The gold bird with the gold coin. Wait what everyone thinks I'm insane. No I didn't just
like fall off the edge for no reason. I'm coming to get the coin. It's all the way to the left edge
right oh yeah oh yeah yeah oh yeah all right i'm like pumped up right now like don't fuck it up
i'm losing it i'm losing it i'm losing it no you think i'm losing it i lost it a long time ago
nobody tell him okay that's a level up by the way no it's not i didn't make it is it no i didn't
i technically did make it didn't i yeah you don't go back in levels i know some of you guys are like
well i play on a modded i play on a modded wildstar server and we have negative levels
i don't that's not i don't play that i don't do that all right my body's like a lightning
rod right now if you're getting that goddamn bird coin i gotta relax wait a minute i can just jump
that whole thing all right cool i love when you get when you find something out about what you're
doing i love it you didn't get it it took it it flew it away what do you mean it flew it away
what are you talking about i didn't get the coin there we go i should have done that from the
beginning and what do you mean i didn't get the coin you know i have it i should right where's
this shop right here give me that coin give me i got it never slip with these expert coins up there
give me that thing you little shit how do i get over there do i have to oh my god
oh did i get it oh come on no way it's up there now you little dick oh shit oh shit oh shit i'm
fine no i didn't mean to do that oh god i didn't mean to do that okay you gotta go way lower than
that okay look look look look look look look look look look look okay let's see what's this
what's this image that i'm gonna be very very mad at pogchamp look at the picture pogchamp
yeah that's funny yep oh yeah i got a t-shirt i like i can't wear this ever again shit okay
oh no i have to try oh what the fuck was that i can never wear that shirt again
thanks guys he's seen it already yeah i've that was after twitchcon i have seen it already
you should thank us town hall board of notice this abandoned town which is clearly abandoned
and which no one lives in is henceforth irrevocably eternally foreverly uncancellably
and undeniably claimed by right of previous owners blatant abandonment as the sole property
of merchant maligdous something in addition i maligdous dreig shall rename this new shining
center of commerce it should be known as bargainberg should any legal inquiries or
complaints arise contact unintelligible thank you for your cooperation they're just they're slowing
me down okay do you understand why would i do something like that that's what i'm saying why
would i do that there was no why would i go that way what would i do that for that's gonna be
fucking hard that's gonna be hard to do man it's gonna be hard no no no please don't go all the
way down okay slow down i actually have to take a break like i have to take a mind break
germa is mega bad at this you guys are getting channel points too quickly i'm gonna have to slow
that down i was told to speed it up he's still not gonna give me the fucking coin
ah what do i go from here i can't tell do i have to not up right no to the right
can i land on that oh my god oh my god oh my god i i almost didn't okay oh my god
i did again i'm telling you something's wrong okay i'm my heart hurts right now because of that
then what we go huh i have to go through the middle
fuck man this fucking dumb ass controller i swear to god why would i ever intentionally do
something like that what would i do that for this like just jump the wrong way on purpose no this
thing sucks all right yes yes yes i know i know go ahead add it go to keep a tally that's fine
hold on hold that thought why didn't i just use the d-pad from the very beginning
i can't even use it now because it's too okay everyone relax i got it i got it i got it done
done done he did it he did it he's done he did it he's done it i did it what are you doing funny
discord lane we stop i'm trying to be focused i hate this i hate this i hate this i hate this
i hate it i hate this okay okay cool thanks for that am i safe in here okay i can fucking jump
into walls and stuff i'm safe in here that one's going in the folder is the coin again
how am i going to get that coin how am i going to do this sorry i can't i can't i can't i can't
get the coin is the coin that necessary and do i actually get the damn thing when i how long does
it take i that's i fall so far if i miss this that's too far to fall what the hell is this
bright crown woods snow i can't walk oh man this sucks you need snowshoes read chat read
this is dlc this is dlc okay well i know wait you shall never make it to the babe of legend
even if you succeeded she would refuse you i know this because i've been waiting for her to call me
back for 200 years i'm fucking dust at this point dlc got it yes okay now give me that
get up there okay shit don't fuck it up oh no no no i'm slowly slowly slowly going down into this
into the hole um uh okay don't go in the fucking hole oh god please i take it i can't go that way
oh my god oh why would you do that to me oh shit just fall that's a bait that's trying to kill me
you know what what's my favorite bird uh a crow i have probably i don't know thank god
i hate this part no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no it's all right it can be
salvaged no oh it's and they do it they put it there they put it there specifically because
it's going to drop you all the way back and they know what they're doing they just they dump you
all the way fucking back here it's not that far it really isn't it just looks like it is it just
looks bad it's okay i'm still back here okay we're good it went the other way again 11 11 11 12 12 13
14 15 16 why is it going the other fucking way it doesn't make any sense i got them all i got
them all out in a row am i using a nintendo controller no i'm using an xbox one controller
i don't understand i almost want to turn i'm gonna try to turn on a handcam on so you can see
because you guys can be it doesn't hand it doesn't a handcam imply i know what i'm doing
for you to see like i'll just how fast i press the buttons are using a claw grip no i'm just
using my big sweaty disgusting hand he's using his toes i'm not okay i mean this is i gotta get
through this i'm close to tilton i am close i'm not gonna let it happen though because once you
let once it happens it's over and then you um i feel like i'm making some decent progress so why
would i just go full shake the pinball machine you know i mean yeah i'm making some pretty good
progress
stop making jokes and play one more joke and i'm trying not to but sometimes it's i that's how i
cope with this kind of shit it's okay it's okay too much too long okay
okay i just had to get somebody to get hit in the head with a chair i think i'll be all right
this is a psycho actual psycho
oh
this game looks easy
stop get out of here what this game looks easy man
i can't okay i honestly i did this part 5 000 times already i'm just laughing about watching
the undertaker hit somebody in the head with a chair to calm down yeah guys sorry i just i
kind of need to relax i just gotta watch them to get hit in the fucking head with a heavy object
ah that really just like it makes me comfy is that a real picture i don't know uh sure
this is real i guess all right do you ever do you ever do you ever look in the mirror
and you really think that you look like this sometimes i swear to god there has been times
when i've looked in the mirror just like kind of like i'm getting ready like maybe when i'm
going to go out or something i feel like i look like this in the mirror sometimes uh it's like
weird imagine how big your brain would be though you would be so smart that's a brain that's two
or three times oh what if it was just skull only you know the brain is the same size but the skull
is is is uh is just four times as big or it's just just how my head has hardened because of how many
times i've been hit in the head with a chair lots of calcium um all right hold on i almost just
lost but it's okay this is the this part's really actually sucks so hold on no fucking come on man
come the fuck on come come the fuck on come on it's just like so easy to fuck that up okay
okay it's so easy to fuck that one up it's a tiny little window i'm not mad i'm just spitting facts
he's spitting on us i'm not spitting i nobody said that why did i just say that oh my god what
am i doing what how does that wrong huh the little ones are the worst because you just don't know i
it's hard to determine what a tiny jump is you have to do it with such a small amount of time
but at the same time you have to still hold it down long enough to do it it's like a it's it you
don't mean oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah too much jump make 18 no 17 whatever it is just let it out
i just did did this guy fart on stream how disgusting i you know how it's bad channel
i got to delete channel points you guys can now get my attention insanely easily by having this
bright highlighted text that i'm guaranteed to read guaranteed guaranteed to read it all senior
citizens should have life alert it's like i'm guaranteed to see it guaranteed but what happens
with when people just only chat with channel points there's no more regular chat all i see is
channel point chat if everyone's using channel points then nobody i'm reading chat again i'm not
reading chat until i get to the next area what does it say all right how many look look i gotta
ask you a question how many channel points do you guys have right now on this channel
like 300 400 300 900 i earned 1300 today and you get it by watching just simply by watching the
channel nope that's uh that's not kind of cool actually that was i got it i did that did you
see that i i clearly i was going in and it just threw me out can this guy stop pretending
like that wouldn't you oh my god
i have to pay attention stop stop stop stop stop jumping jeremy stop stop stop moving
stop moving i know you don't want to stop and stop moving so i can get my bearings
jeremy stop playing the game jeremy stop playing the game i need to fucking get my
bearings stop jumping jeremy stop jeremy jeremy listen yeah stop jumping okay wake up wake up
wake up you're psycho i'm not a psycho well you know you never been like driving in the car
monologuing to yourself as yourself you've never done that before no bullshit yeah right you're not
like on your way to your job interview talking out loud as if it's you talking really you never
like practiced asking a girl out in the mirror or asking a guy out in the mirror yeah you have
you never pretended to accept an academy award and give your speech into the mirror
i have still waiting by the way no please god i can't get over it okay stop stop this is not
look i'm not this is not bad this is mania no it's not i'm fine i'm fine you've seen way worse
you stupid motherfucker i swear okay that's counts i gotta be careful let's go i'm getting close
i'm at 18 i have to level up or i gotta level this shit up quick no no more i can't make this
jump it's actually impossible i have to do that instead i'm good i'm good i know that i know i'm
up against a a unfair point system yes i know i'm aware that i created this point system
that doesn't mean it's fair come on good now let's get back on track streamer is
whatever this is the part that always fucks me up okay
sorry i couldn't breathe there for a second
oh no
i don't want to do this again please just get up here what the fuck are you doing i'm just asking
a question what are you doing i just have a sim i just have one simple question no i just have
how are we on each other's tvs
that's not 19 that's not 19 i don't i don't remember is it what the hell is going on
what is going on somebody's calling me wait what what's this what's this weird ringtone
i don't understand how are we on each other's tvs
guys no all right i seriously might have to i might have to just i'm not done streaming
of course i'm not even at 20 yet yo i'm not even there yet
i'm gonna mess this up i've had so many chances and i keep blowing it and i'm doing it so wrong
holy shit i can't believe i'm still getting these chances i need to see okay it's that way got it
okay fuck off with this okay okay now what i have to bounce off the left one or off the right one
off the left one or off the right one off the left one or off the right one
off the left one or off the right one off the left one oh boy i get 10 extra points by the way
this is a new zone i don't think it's possible for me to get so i don't know i have this like
theory where sometimes you just like you just have to go for it you just have to you just have to
stop talking figure out what the heck you're doing on somebody else's tv and get over there
you know i'm saying like your greed's gonna be your undoing i need the coin though to get the
special boots that's the whole purpose this dude doesn't even have boots oh mega lull yeah you can
omega all you want you can omega all you want you can omega lull you want not gonna change my theory
don't you fucking dare yeah that counts that counts you know i have i have some bully way here
i have some fuck okay i got one out i have enough points that look at how hard this jump is are you
kidding me how do you get that it's got to be perfect and how do you get back i was trying to
get the coin but i missed it's too small i just i'm not getting the coin i don't care
oh i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got
the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got it yes i was just a disney side character during one
of their important end of the movie missions where i comically go pick up the item that needs to be
picked up and somehow i end up with it and like you didn't expect the little squirrel fuck to have
the coin you thought it was going to be the big main character no it's me i got the coin i did it
i'm gonna left side's probably easier oh jesus oh jesus oh jesus holy jesus oh jesus i almost
just screwed that all up jeez all right now from here i gotta go um what i don't have to jump from
here i can't that's not possible a left bounce will not do anything for me do i actually have
to go right well this sucks use coin for boots i didn't get the coin i don't have a coin
bird flew up didn't it i don't have the coin what are you guys on about oh no we gotta go way
shorter than that one go up careful careful it's a little too long it's death see what i mean by
that yeah yay jesus and then we gotta go from here we're gonna go just jump left all the way
oh okay i didn't want to jump that way my computer something wrong with my computer
i had it okay you don't understand i'm turning on a fucking handcam i'm turning on a fucking
handcam seriously like that's so i like i'm turning the handcam on eventually not right now
oh okay everything's fine i swear to god i'm turning it on i'm turning it on how am i even
gonna do this is this even possible this is not possible without like a mount i don't have a mount
guys and i have to like put my hand in the screen that's not gonna work tape it to my forehead
just mount it i don't have a mount it what on my teeth look all you need here's what we're gonna
do okay all you need is just the thumb anyways so that i'm not like this fucking matters
this is i just there's no way i can really reliably do this hold on let me get my camera
you just need the thumb so i'm gonna go like this no this is this is not gonna work is uncomfortable
it's uncomfortable this is so this is so shitty i'm gonna try though
so i got like really long ass fingernails too this is like disgusting this just looks
gross i don't like this this looks gross you just need to see all right i'm almost ready you just
need the thumb i'm trying to get it in a spot where it's going to be like at least comfortable
for me to play the game put it between your nope not reading that okay you can see that now
hold on can you see look at how like fucking dirty this is this is so dirty i just cleaned it too
hey remember that alien microscope okay can you see now this lying on my lap right now this is all
you need to see i'm ready see look at that fingernail god damn it it's disgusting it's
no it's not it's fine it's fine it's fine just pretend it's like not even it's
it's it's this it's i can't play like this no i don't care i'm un-fucking-believable
un-fucking-believable what the hell man i'm like i have my camera like sitting on my on my fucking
dick pointing forward while i'm scrunching my arms together and like going like yeah i dare to put
my arm just so i can prove that there's a bug in the video game there's a bug in the video game
why would i why would i use the stick because i'm a moron and when the game first started it i
started using the stick and i got so used to the stick that when i went to the d-pad it yeah i
couldn't do it and it was freaking me out i'm just a stick user now did you see the new gorillas
movie no i didn't i didn't okay wait a minute okay oh my god no god i was up there i was up
actually was up there and i did they're like look at my hands thing and look at my hands guys
cool huh if i didn't balance the fucking webcam in between my legs i would still be up there
and now i'm all the way down here yeah can we get like an actually mad counter
okay i'm gonna put it in brackets how many like actually actually angry there just once yeah
thank we'll tally it up at the end that was in there it was in there what was wrong with that
finally finally you know the game gets harder right oh i know that's fine hey i've i've made it
this far i've made it this far get me up there let's go let's go let's go that i don't i don't
get it i don't understand i don't get it how do you do that how do you do that how do you do that
and give me a break that's a huge channel point message what the fuck you you you you you you you
you mad no no wait just what what am i doing what am i doing why am i trying to jump just jump to
this what the fuck am i trying to get on this little tetris platform for what what are they
doing what's wrong with me what oh yeah okay i got the coin got it that's all i care about
this is safe right um i don't know up on the like on that and then over okay now what
fuck yeah here we go here we go here we go yeah here we go that's the play that's the play
that's the play right there oh micky oh dr phil that wasn't dr phil
oh no stop making me laugh stop making me laugh that's worse than being mad because when i laugh
i'm like my butt been down in my arms when i'm mad i just lock in and go
shit oh man oh man i'm almost at the top of the mountain almost at the top of the mountain
hmm a fellow jumper how unusual i salute you for coming this far but i am afraid this is
the end of the game thank you for completing jump king just wait until you see what is ahead
pepe face i will wait here cool how do i get out of here now i don't know why i thought that was
gonna work this one's this is not too terrible it can be very quickly though that shit shit shit
shit shit shit shit shit that wasn't angry that was terrified oh no too far don't go too far
okay not bad not bad now clean it up clean it up jeremy clean it up clean it up or i will punish you
clean it up or i will punish you with some terrible 80s theme song from a cartoon
you had it too just don't move i'm so paranoid to jump too far
keep happening it's like i have no confidence that i'm gonna land on it so i just turn
and now i went over it oh good good job hey excellent work man hey hey you want to party
later yeah party for fucking idiots that counts yeah it does how was that a sans voice
sans why is there anybody that talks like this gotta be sans no uh it could be a bunch of different
characters uh like barney rubble from flintstones that's the original sans a guy that wears a
leather jacket in any live action movie or tv show from the uh you know like the 90s or the
early 2000 yogi bear oh yeah he was the original sans all you have to do to do yogi bear is instead
of you just elongate uh the end of your words it's pretty easy to do
no okay stop stop you have to stop i need to find a new area before this game turns up
it's don't stop stop i'll fall i'm gonna i'll fall and if i don't okay see i knew i was gonna
i'm right now uh okay no no no no no no this is i cannot let this happen
i was doing pretty good actually until i don't even remember well what happened i i started
doing like cartoon character voices for some reason oh my god jeremy i you're gonna get punished
it's time to get punished yeah yep yep you deserve it you deserve it you deserve you deserve like
abc mouse songs you deserve the four hour long put your baby in front of the ipad
children's music channels no please oh please yeah actually that would be me punishing you
but you don't deserve to be you don't deserve that all right all right all right seriously this is
the one wipe my hands of the oil like my body just has oil come out of it oh my god oh you just want
you you just want you want to go so fast when you fuck it up you want to go so fast when you
just fuck it all up you know what i mean it's just human nature you screwed it up go harder
you lose go hard go more more more more okay i stop stop stop stop this is the point where you
have to stop because when you hit i would say this area down here where i am lying right now
face down on the ground this is if you're if you tilt it and you're just out of control you stop
pause it immediately because after this is when it all goes to shit you know what i mean if i if
no if i keep going like stop that no fuck dumb and i'd go all the way down then i'll turn the
stream off because that'll be that'll count as like 10 you get your bearings if you come down this
far you get your bearings do it again see it's always in that spot every time that spot every
time the analog i just i'm biting my mouth right now to make sure i don't scream he's blaming the
controller well why would i hold right you know why would i ever do that well it looks like i need
to jump to the left because there's not even a platform on the right i think i'll hold right
there's there's a there's a wall over there hold right and like you know what you when you start
you uh no i'll count this because this is this is what yeah count this seriously count it because
uh the the cord of the controller just touched me and i was like get the fuck away from me like
get the fuck out of here get away from me i moved it out of the way hard now it's like the cord is
pissing me off it hasn't for the last almost two hours and a half all right just i touched my leg
and i was like get the fuck away from me and when you know when you start to get angry at things
touching you that are not that inanimate objects that are just then that's when all right i'm good
i'm just gonna get to another area before i have to i'm i'm at my last two um yeah they won't happen
i'm just gonna be quiet if i'm quiet you guys only won't even know if i'm upset about something
take a break and play getting over it i don't think i'm gonna do that okay
shit
this game is nothing else what does that even mean this game's nothing else man am i high
what the fuck am i talking about that's all right i haven't i act like i've been here for like 10
hours it's been two and a half please don't don't don't don't don't don't oh it's his blood
let's go what is that oh no sorry sorry that was a piece of chicken in my mouth
hey look a piece of chicken stuck in my teeth from like six hours ago chicken in teeth goblin
nails but you can't think of like i just get go grab a chicken in the woods and like go on all fours
like yeah no i swear just get me in there i don't like this jump at all get over there okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay are you speaking in tongues
speaking in tongues what a strange thing by the way can we just like address that
what is that even supposed to mean what it's speaking in tongues i don't get like what is that
you just kind of go off and do like adam sandler gibberish right
what's the difference between is that's what i'm thinking that's right
yeah it's like this
that's adam sandler speak that's the same thing right
by the way up for uh probably uh best actor of the whole year i know i've said this before and i'll
say it again everyone's like oh hey you're the adam sandler of twitch and it's like oh lol lol
oh really that guy's up for probably an academy award this year for being the best actor out of
any actor in the whole year okay good compare me i that's a grout take that comparison any day of
the week and the thing is people just can't believe it people just can't stand it it's like they're
being shown something that they're like no no no no it can't be no adam sandler adam sandler
suck no no he can't no okay please just get me out of this world oh i like i hope he wins
i hope adam sandler wins the academy award for best actor and then everybody on twitter their
brains are gonna like just explode no it can't be they can't play i burnt my copy of attack of the
pixels whatever the hell that movie was he can't win all right i gotta pay attention again adam
sandler is nominated for literally nothing now go look up the movie uncut gems and uh you'll see
there are no oscar nominations yet there's no nominations yet they don't give there's nothing
we're talking about the oscar buzz is around that he's going he will be nominated for his
performance in uncut gems okay can i please just get this jump before i start to have a little bit
of a problem i'm gonna have a okay okay okay okay video games suck video games suck video games suck
video games suck all video games none of them fun all of them suck all video games suck i'm
never playing a video game ever again hey the last good video game i played was doom back in like 86
they haven't even come close to another good one by the way how dare you fucking doubt adam
sandler that's what happened that doesn't count as a getting mad i got mad about adam sandler
and people thinking he doesn't deserve it so that made me angry not the video game all video games
aren't fun but i mean we all we already know that it's the adam sandler thing that threw me off
why would i stop playing this game i'm having a great i'm having fun playing this
wow wow i'm having a fun time look i got back up here look at that i it's not that bad when
you know everything see i'm good next person that says anything bad about adam sandler i'm getting
rid of their channel points oh no not my channel points i need those we're good i knew that was
gonna be a problem i hadn't done in a long time i haven't done that one a very long time as long
if i can get up there though i'm not gonna let it beat me you know what i'm saying i'm in this still
at least chapter three he's evaporating i'm fine if i was truly evaporating you would know
i knew this one was gonna be tricky there it is there it is there it is all right boys and girls
we're back it's like it never happened look at that we're back i could have just like bolted and
had new skin no new shell whatever the hell you want i'm back it's okay it's not it's been
a while since i've been up there we're fine what was last time you guys had a chocolate malt
i'm talking like actual chocolate like malt not like a milkshake a chocolate malt can you
even still get those no there's some specialty places that do it still i like i want one right
now is that weird that was in the middle too it was pretty close the thing about a chocolate
malt it's strange i don't know why i want it just tastes like a gross sour milkshake but i want one
looks like it's going in man this jump actually sucks it just does and i know all of you sitting
there going like yeah fuck that jump like yeah fuck that one it actually is really easy scrub
ban that guy for life those of you that might be new to the channel a lifetime ban on this too
well that's not true that's it that's me making that up i don't want to be like a lifetime ban
is five minutes uh that's not true you uh you can very very very much get banned from this channel
for life uh so don't think that that's reality hey hey that was funny fuck it was funny so i
fucked it up no too far too far too far man too far slow it just come on no i'll tell you one
thing i'm so glad that i had like a full lunch before playing this game i would have been gone
like 30 minutes 30 minutes 30 minutes ago i would have been gone i would have been gone 30 minutes
ago if it weren't for that steak and cheese sandwich i had earlier i would have been gone 30
minutes ago what am i doing the sandwich sandwich was so good you turned irish for a minute
get it coke gaming oh my god thanks hey did you just see the coke gaming ad
is that why you just said that that has to be why you just wrote that you just wrote that without
any prompt you just said that flying fuck that's not angry
okay coke gaming omega lull why are the easiest jumps here causing me so many problems
like seriously look at this shit it's like not even fucking hard it's not even hard and i'm still
having problems like shit's not even hard i was about to be i was about to say i was about to just
scream like i was about to be like fuck that no we're not doing that though because i'm not done
oh god this is you need the patience of you need rock solid patience like
i didn't even hold the button for that much longer oh that's far oh stop stop stop just don't
fucking move bro is this so hard it's so hard
all righty then
this new trend of like i'll tell you then you know there's a new trend in video games
would you like to know what it is our game is so fucking hard you won't be an idiot it's too hard
for you you fell rage got you and guess what i'm a sucker because i bought it and i like it
this is the equivalent of eating hot peppers why would you do that why would you put hot sauce on
everything oh yeah let me put like put some hot sauce on this on my eggs oh that's a lot that's
a lot of hot sauce oh let me eat that oh my god oh this sucks so bad
oh i'll do it though again tomorrow these these games are just the hot sauce of video games
like i don't need half a bottle of tabasco on my eggs but i like used to do that so they're great
why did i jump like that there's no reason for me to oh no okay so i gotta stop moving stop stop
stop stop stop stop oh my god putting a goddamn half a bottle of hot sauce on my food and then we
get even further where in a lot of these games people have competitions as to how much hot sauce
they can fucking eat in a row give me that bottle i'll chug that fucking thing okay i did it
now fuck you man i'll be able to do more hot sauce than that no you won't yes i will
oh my my insides are burning my insides hurt they hurt so bad
so let's take me to the hospital please and then somebody in the hospital bed next to them
what are you what are you doing here i tried to you know drink a whole bottle of hot sauce
it was super duper bomb hot sauce and i've i've got internal bleeding wait what
that's what you tried to do yeah and it wasn't very good i i got through the whole bottle though
you did yeah oh really nurse bring me in a bottle of hot sauce and make it nuclear are you
you did the whole bottle i did the whole bottle i did it all i did more hot sauce than you did
it's something that doesn't feel right though i
something feel right at least i got it i drank a full bottle of nuclear
hot sauce all right um
i am the best i am unstoppable so stream chat what's going on guys have you guys seen
the new marvel movie oh i heard it was epic i like i loved when captain america flew by and like
and threw his shield oh so cool what do you guys think okay
it's like oh damn it i'm i'm so i can't i'm not gonna stop playing i'm obsessed with this
game i'm not gonna stop i can't stop it's too much fun this the hot sauce is too good i woke
up in the afterlife and like i just wanted to play this again he's getting the nuclear sauce
but all right let me let's be frank though let's be real why why do those exist i know i mean okay i
get it like oh it's the hottest but why do you want to eat who eats that you eat it it's to
incinerate your butthole i don't eat i can't eat that stuff i just have to get i don't even know
where i made it to i do i do enjoy heat i do enjoy i like you know tabasco sauce mild tabasco sauce
stop talking stop talking just stop talking i'll we'll go back to that thought about five
minutes just hold on hold that just hold hold tight see just hold tight don't just quiet
you see there way it's a little too far or it's like just guess just guess how much hot sauce
you're going to put on your sandwich at that jump gallon this was destined to be a melt downstream
my why am i why am i wow it it it it's just it's just such a dice roll if you're going to get in
there it's just throwing dice in the earth i'm going to land in that spot i i want to be in
control of who's putting fucking hot sauce on my shit i went in it that was i was inside of it
and then just pushed me out sick pixel art okay yes cool can we move on from that shit
already he's doing it pepe he's doing it pepe he's doing it pepe pepe look he's doing it pepe
he's back oh no i'm not oh god that sucks such asshole that sucks asshole it's kind of like this
pixel perfect jump king and i have to do that stupid ass tube shot again oh this is fantastic
yeah cool you know the worst part about this is i'm way the fuck up there but i somehow
fucked it up and now i can't even get back to like six screens above where i am
that's just come on i've done this like 600 times i can get up here you fucking piece of shit
you piece of shit there's no fucking way seriously how do people how do we play these games
you know what i mean how do we do this how do we do this to ourselves have we gotten so
bored as a species that this is entertainment to us jumping and falling down a hole for three
hours straight with a controller in your hand jumping into holes super mario is rolling over
in his grave right now that's right he's dead he's been dead super mario that they've just
it's cg now guys mario's been dead since 1997 what does this say i'm a certified backseat
no i don't i'm not upset anybody here what i'm having a blast i really actually am this is like
fun to me stop i just have to get out i'm sick of seeing this stupid ass town just this is the one
right here okay don't fuck it up again and and what is wrong with that what i'm doing
don't go that far don't don't go that i haven't updated the mad meter in a while what are we at
like fucking 20 oh shit oh shit i just jumped scared you i'm sorry i don't mean to be like this
i really don't he sounds exasperated uh maybe a little that's that one's hard to judge that one's
hard to judge oh fuck that's hard to judge that's the one i'm gonna have trouble with this whole
time that one is so difficult to judge you know what i'm gonna stand all the way in the back
in the jump that's a that's an insane jump i was expecting a skinny person to beat this game
what on earth are you talking about quick german on 85 pull uh do you guys think i'm gonna beat
this game what if i do though what if i did i want at least this 6600 people watching right now i want
at least 2 000 of you to guarantee me that if i beat this game then i get if i complete this game
then i get at least two nancy drew streams that's far it sucks but i'll get nancy drew
streams out of this i have to try like are you kidding me what a pog moment that would be
wait a minute wait wait wait i'm trying to get the coin guys i'm trying
what is stop stop please stop jeremy stop stop jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy
jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy i did the thing i did the thing i needed to do and i i i exhaled
all of my energy and i fell off the mountain you know what i mean i just oh fuck oh no
fuck i know i fucked up everything i literally fucking got the dumb coin and then like
oh it's fucking deflated oh fuck me fuck me fuck me fuck me fuck me
fuck me forget me forget me fuck fuck fuck i was there and i was up i got the coin fuck the coin
i don't care about the true ending i don't need to read the back of the hot sauce label to know the
game is fucking hot i don't care what do i care well you have to get that coin so you get the true
ending by the way uh it's probably three lines of dialogue at the end credits oh okay cheers to you
no cheers to you doesn't work anymore cheers to you doesn't work it only worked on the last boss
in dark souls 3 dlc that's the only place where it's usable give me a goddamn break how many times
have i tried this well kim i've fallen down 340 times and i've jumped 3657 times
i fell so i fell down for lilly thanks for 10 community subs thank you for lilly listen to my
voice i mean this is like this is this is like real life you know what i mean i don't know you
might you might you might say well maybe he's like now this must be acting he's he's a phenomenal
actor this listen to me this is real life i mean you wouldn't be wrong if you said that actually
so i mean i do appreciate the i do appreciate that isn't this real life please music germa i
recommend gwyn lord of cinder come on okay you come on you think i'm gonna put that on fine
all right i just typed in i just typed in come on gwyn into that's not uh that's not
it's called the gwyn lord gwyn music i feel like this is gonna make me more tense
you know what i mean that's what what what somebody's giving a shitload of subs i got
distracted this 20 community subs just came in amnestic ow thanks for the 20 community subs
20 20 20 20 20 for every community sub that i get i get the minus one point for my bad meter
all right i'm gonna die if i don't seriously though thank you all right i the music's not the music
and the music's fucking distracting me my god like i had it too and i was going good
i'm so glad i've eaten today fucking finicky ass thing no it's actually fucking me up
all i hear in the background in my brain is somebody behind me playing a piano
just stop playing the piano it's a great song but not right now my fucking god all right if i
don't do this right now i will not stream for two weeks okay good we're good now i i can scream
again i had it too i really did i know all of you are probably going like oh pepehands pepehands he
was up there this motherfucker was up there this motherfucker was up there and i'm like i know damn
okay it's time to like get this over with oh i know right dude damn geron mode what yeah we
don't we don't you know you know what yeah we don't need we don't need jacks right now
forget jacks it's it's time for jeremy oh jeremy sucks ass jeremy sucks and i have to and i gotta
do this shit again yes yes okay now get it together get it together get it together
get it together get it together get it together stop talking about getting it together and get
it together no more mirror monologues you gotta actually do it now jeremy buddy you gotta go accept
the award now oh i'm not ready yes you are okay i guess so hard to tell it really is like if it's
not perfect then gtfo still in great frontier omega lull incoming fall joke resident sleeper
do you hear the way that i sound right now you think i want to do like an intentional
joke where i fall the fuck down no more talking till i get up there i'm serious
so fucking hard it's so fucking hard i bet you if i played super meat boy after this you see
i feel like i would probably have 100 every single level you know what i mean where do we go from
here how do you top this where do we go from here are we like just pull your teeth out put it in
your cd tray and it'll determine if you ripped out your teeth or not what's the next step it
sounds like a new genre you gotta just jump back around yeah yeah yeah this is not i ain't
gonna try jump on that one from here what do i do from here i have to get on that one on the right
go up i can't go left i can't go left pull the pole yeah the pole over here on the right i know
but i this is gonna be hard go right there i know i know right i know right and then left but
it's gonna be tricky oh my god oh my god this one's tricky oh my god okay what do i do from here
i don't know what to do up into the right i made it i made it to wind swept fluff that's it that's
a wind super crow for the fucking one line of dialogue at the end of the game congratulations
you got the coins who gives a shit oh my god it's actually fucking ridiculous
but don't you know that'll be on your steve achievement list
i haven't opened up my steam achievement list in seven years guys i don't even know it's on there
let's check it let's check it
uh i don't even know where it is oh man i'm so but i have to get the coin right i can't
i can't do it somebody i'm about to look up what happens if you get all the coins
i'm just gonna go over the whole thing i think no you can't less than four percent of people have
beaten this game so four percent of everybody that's bought this game has not beaten it
no no other way around
the thing about those tests is one fucking goddamn mistake and you do it all over again
one tiny little fucking tiny pixel of a mistake can't wait to rip my teeth out in 2060
it's i got this new game yeah it's called rip out your fucking teeth oh oh oh oh shit
oh how many do i have left i took my front two out oh it's got achievement popped up it's called
imbecile oh dude what's that mean i don't know what that word means we're so stupid in the future
i'm not getting the coin i'm not you know you just you i know i'm not capable of it i'm not
capable of getting that coin you all know it and i know a lot of people are gonna be like no dude
you might be just like sure you sure oh my god this game is fucking 10 out of 10
10 out of 10 in like what the fuck oh my god i and i have to do that all over welcome to the
beginning of the fucking game oh my fucking god why do we do this to ourselves i can't even man
i can't even this is dog shit this is dog shit dog shit dog shit this is dog shit
i should i hit the top this is dog shit and you all know it i shouldn't have fallen that far
dog shit this is dog shit and you all know i know it i should not have fallen that far
we know we know we know do you fucking absolute dog shit absolute dog shit i can't believe i fell
that far i am so angry this is what this does though this is what i'm just gonna say hey dude
that's such a dog shit they make these little
just fuck that they make these little slopes so you you pinball down all the way
and they did they did it on purpose and it's dog shit okay stop okay i can't even i can't do it
i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it the other dog shit that was what just
happened and i'm gonna i he's repeating himself that's what happens if you get fucking actually
upset about something you just start repeating words now my face is itchy shit man i can't get
over it this game is handles just it's all right just go just go just go just go i can do it just
go i've done this fucking a thousand times how did i even fall down the left or right how did
that happen that how does that even happen oh come on like i would pay money for a checkpoint
you want to monetize the fuck out of this game uh let me buy like fucking checkpoint gems and
place them that's the new meta dollar 99 for each checkpoint gem they would make a hundred million
dollars how much would i buy as many as i could afford to wipe out my bank account i would get a
call from the bank sir it says here that you'd like to spend
1600 on am i getting this right checkpoint gems are you sure your son doesn't have the ipad
no i have me okay you're confirming this purchase yep how did i end up here again
so dude i don't even ask don't even ask don't even ask don't even ask why would you ask me
that question that's like just mean you know what i mean like why would you ask me that question
that's like it's like of course i did something wrong of course i fucked it all up somewhere
and i had a meltdown and i screwed it all up what do you want me to explain it to you
it's like i know there's mustard on my shirt i know because i opened i it squared it all over
my shirt i have a huge ass mustard stain you don't have to point at it and say hey uh you
got a mustard stain on your shirt huh yeah yeah i do i i was here when i did it and i'm embarrassed
about it thanks for bringing it up at my own wedding even you're gonna talk about the huge
mustard stain all over me god damn molting them right now i don't even remember you know like i
don't even remember half the words i've said this stream you could play back something and
i wouldn't even know what i wouldn't i would say it wasn't even me talking dog shit i remember dog
shit because i fell down and bounced like three times i remember saying that there was dog shit
yeah like that except i did that how are we in each other's tvs you know i do i remember that
one too and i'm like not even making progress anymore all because of the dumbass coin that
doesn't fucking do anything it just is there it's only there for you to blow your run that's the
only reason why it exists and i know it's gonna be some like oh you really wanted that coin well
chasing the coin is it was the detriment the whole time you didn't even need the coin you don't even
need those boots the coin it was the fucking variable that you don't need the boots to win
you had it in you the whole time i can't find it never mind is he smoking crack nope
you know how did we get here how did we get here i was up all the way how did i get here
how did we get here you're supposed to go up you're absolutely shit at this game go play nancy
drew it's your pace apparently everyone's shit at this game because only four percent of people
have completed it so by that logic if there's 6,500 people right now only four percent of you guys
are any good at this what's that number what's that number what like fucking 60 of you look at
me look at me no why did i look at you i'm all the way back here i can't give up there though i
can't i refuse to give up here you know what i mean like this is it like i would i can't do that
you know if i gave my if i called my father with the portal app from facebook he first of all he'd
answer it and he'd be like son what are you on my tv and i'd be like that's the guy in the new
technology dad but i uh i'm not gonna complete jump king he'd be like wait wait a minute
you you get your ass back there and you finish it that's what us albertsons do the first albertson
was a blacksmith and all of his swords broken they sucked and they weren't you're worth using
in battle and he overcharged for all of them but he still beat them he still completed them
i'm like yeah you're right then you know no matter how bad i'm terrible at something and how much
worse i am than everybody else has ever played this game i could still complete it that's right
son oh thanks dad thanks for the advice yeah it doesn't matter how much you suck at something
just finish it oh cool thanks dad and then we both i don't um do you how do you hang up
you've called me i don't know is it is there a button i don't use this stupid app from facebook
what is this i i'm gonna turn my tv off yeah try turning off your tv like you actually
physically turn off the television can you hear me yeah i can still hear you
oh but if i i'm gonna call you from my phone and see if it like cuts it off
yeah there's no button to press i found it it's here no i
now i'm stuck at this stupid jump this is the this is the wall now
this is the wall here i can do it i can do it just fail a million times how far has he gotten
i don't know up until the snow level whatever that means no no no not yeah the windy windy level
jeff thanks for the five community subs jeff thank you i got to windy level that's 25 through
that's not bad i think i can do it i think i can do it all right get me in here let's go
let's get some actual fucking music some actual good motivational music
i'm gonna go for it workout motivation music
uh rip thot
is
i don't i don't like this song new song this is the song i was doing this is the song i was
doing earlier i was doing this all this for a loaf of bread start singing
this is the song it's not even the right scene trouble no way you're only in trouble
and i want to like watch aladdin i don't want to watch aladdin did i just get sued by disney
hold on i can't get by this no matter what i fucking do it's this it's this one jump it's
this one jump and i can't do this one jump that's so excruciating for some reason that
jumped to the left and there's nothing i can do it's just a random event if i hit it or not
i've never been able to do it the whole time i've been playing not once it's just been a random
fucking guess to hit that jump every time all these others i'm i know the timing for them
this shit's just a guess it's a guess just guess guess
it is with deepest pride and greatest pleasure that we welcome you tonight and now we invite you to
relax let's pull up a chair as the dining room proudly presents just take a guess like half of
the fucking jumps in this whole game that was a guest take a guess put our service to the test
tie your napkin around your neck sherry and we provide the rest soup to jewel hot or dirt
why we only live to serve try the gray stuff it's delicious don't believe me ask the dishes
they can sing they can dance after all this this is france and a dinner here is never second
i don't want to get sued by disney let me get by this and we'll put another song on
take a fucking guess it's just a it's just a guess every time i can't even get by this shit i'm like
15 screens up the stupid part of the game you need to hold the button down exactly
2.3.1.45255555 seconds okay for the love of god i am never doing that again if i come back down
here if i fall back down here then i'm just i'm not doing that again i'll have somebody else do
it for me i will screenplay share this and somebody else to just do it for me okay for the love of god
it that was so that was so painful painful that was so painful listen to me
oh
oh just bang on the door and scare him that's the what why would you stop making me laugh
think fast think fast and when he jumped the wrong way again for the up thousandth time
what am i doing why did i just do that you gotta be fucking kidding me
all right yeah i want to beat them i want to beat the people that that completed this game
like on completion i wonder how fucking red their eyes were and if their back hurt
hey that didn't make it up it consumed them oh god zoom in on that one because that's the worst
jump in the whole game so far absolutely without a doubt that is the worst jump in the entire
fucking game without a thousand doubts like without a single doubt in my mind i don't even have to i
think about that for a second hey what was like the dumbest jump in the whole game oh uh probably
the one where you have to basketball yourself down a hole and it has to be exact or you fall
down the whole thing he doesn't know about the broken down helicopter like the margin for human
error we just don't give a shit about any of that what do robots have to play these games
fucking jump king somebody else is doing it for me no they're not oh my god how did i keep that
enough down here because they have these they have like three jumps that are so fucking finicky that
if you like why are these not like that why is this jump right here not why is this jump right
here not like that i don't understand it's fucking ridiculous and it sucks because i know it's
intentional like there's a person right now standing in front of me and i'm not i'm not
supposed to get mad at this person right but this person is going in my face la la la la la la la la
hey hey la la la la la and i'm he's doing a look at what should i do you have to be like
get the fuck away from me like that's what that's what this game is doing it's just like hey hey
hey like right in my face it's like dude get the fuck out of here no it's intentional therefore
see i got you i wouldn't say sorry i got you did he make it yet no not even close it's just so
uh like humans humans are so imperfect you know what i mean
this game goes against everything we know as humans humans are imperfect we can't do perfect
fucking things we're not capable of that you can't the speedrun is five minutes and that person
probably spent hundreds and hundreds of hours playing this those are some red ass eyes it was
five minutes don't make me laugh i'm trying to get out of here by the way this guy wouldn't
last in the fucking mcu i got news for you he would do this and then get liquidated that was
just so long ago all right can we agree that if i'm not gonna i'm not gonna get the coin
i don't care no coin i don't this is a coinless run what was wrong with that what was wrong with
that who just gave money lots of money uh pigums gave ten thousand bits thank you pigums
for the huge amount of money and there was also community subs too from uh flies and flinzenberg
five community subs but pigum says i've been watching your content for years now and the
laughs you've given me have carried me through undergrad and dental school we got a dentist
here's your cut from one of my first paychecks don't stop being you we got a real dentist in
the chat you understand well that's awesome to hear do that dental work do the good dental work
and thank you so much for the hundred bucks for ten thousand bits that's a lot of money thank you
and good luck with those with those patients and everything has to be one hundred one hundred
percent perfect every fucking single time you can't there's no margin zero zero you do it
perfect every time or delete the game turn your facecam on no you don't want to see me right now
i look like shit check for his red eyes hold on hold on let me just get back up here
let me just get up here again like this is dog shit hold on
you look you fell 50 000 times now i can't get that one it's just
oh my fucking god you can't be kidding me man no fucking way this is unbearable
unfucking bearable unbearable it's unbearable i can't bear it any longer
but i'll continue to do so he's too impatient it's hard to stay patient when you've fallen down the
same ledge 500 times just just stay patient and come on just relax you've been hitting your head
against a wall for three hours hey just sit down just do it you're cool you got it i've been hitting
the head with a chair like five times germ is going to be great one day oh i know one day that's
another thing when if you're really patient you lose your flow and then you fuck it all up
you all know this don't suck well explain that to the other 96 percent of every human that's
downloaded this game we should we should we should get them in a call let's call up let's call up the
96 percent of every living person that has downloaded jump king and let's let's ask them
that let's tell let's tell them that let's do it am i using it i'm using a controller most probably
haven't even played the game but they probably got on a steam sale and oh boy they probably can't
wait oh jump king that sounds like kind of fun and then they got four hairs left jump king
i could i could have i could have been i could have been like i could have been somebody god
damn it remember hey remember boys and girls i'm like 14 screens up from here in progression but
look at me stuck here he's so mad what should i not be what should i do
it's that same stupid ass job they always put one one one jump that's just you gotta get it
perfect or you're falling all the fucking way down did the people talking about sakiro easy mode open
this game i feel like they'd have a heart attack do they know this one exists i feel like they would
turn like green when they if they played this okay can we get this back on track we can get this back
on track this game is designed to make you mad oh yeah i know that's why i'm not done playing it
i know oh i know that doesn't mean i'm i'm not slightly a little bit irritated i only caught
the last half of the incident but during seriously went off the rail what you're a masochist
no we already went over this if you like hot sauce then you then it's the same thing all right i can't
fuck this up i really can i i cannot fuck this up i have to get the hell out of here and go back to
where i was progressing through the damn game blame the bird blame the fake true ending no and
i should have known that was gonna happen what just happened right there it's designed to fuck
with you it's built meticulously this mad scientist game developer sat at every corner
every single little corner and was like they had cauldrons bubbling behind him it was
meticulously crafted to fuck with you grunt hilda yeah this is the this is the this game dead is the
grunt hilda of game development i've devised this is such a fun game
no no a stupid basketball jump let's just take another guess try to remember the exact well it's
not the position it's just the time holding the button because no matter what you'll you're never
gonna do it the same length every time you're all you'll always miss it by like a quarter of a
second like a tenth of a second it's just like all right no that was a little bit too high but
i still made it this one you know i'm gonna stand right on the edge and go one two no it's way too
hard way too long way too long i'll just guess how do we go no no no we're not no we're not down
we go we're good fuck off with this i'm done with this let's get out and get me to progression where
i was before i'm done with this part i was done with this part two and a half hours ago what are
we doing here again what happened to that jump what happened there why did it go why did that
happen why did that happen why did that happen and why did that happen again why did that happen
what the fuck i didn't even press anything why my god you gotta be shitting me you've got to be
shitting me what did i press the a or something how what i like pressed it too early and hit that
here we go again no not even close i can't believe it i can't believe it i can't fucking believe it i
can't believe it oh like you gotta let me in man why like why is it to have to do that
yeah i don't understand fuck oh you got to be kidding it's ridiculous and now we're down
here again oh my fucking god there's there's no reason for that it's it's 100 out of 100
in difficulty 100 dude sakira was like for me sakira was like an 88 this is a 100 this
game's not hard yes it is this is a religious experience yeah i feel like i feel like i'm going
to start to see hallucinations here in a minute go eat something i've already eaten i have steak
um steak steak is it pretty fucking good genuinely are you okay don't make yourself unhealthy
i'm good guys we're at like did you see the simpsons hit and run stream this is like a six out of
simpsons hit and run i mean that really we're approaching it maybe guys guys i'm
it's been four and a half hours why does everybody act like i haven't drank water in three days
what oh hey don't mind me just germa 985 uh 15 screens up is progression but i'm still down
at the tutorial hi hi good to meet you good to see you because this tutorial zone has
three jumps in it that suck balls that sucks asshole oh he's getting crude i'm laughing too
hard right now what did me or did somebody tell you a joke seriously i've been i've done this so
many times why do i oh god damn it that person that person screwed it all up i was how
oh god damn it you gotta be kidding me man you come on like really
really where's the system in place so i don't have to fucking do this
use a keyboard no way not four and a half hours into this no not a chance guys
all my memory on my muscle memory i can't go over that i can't do that now i just got to get back
up to where i was before it's all it's all this dumb bird coin that's i got a prediction in like
the alternate metaverse i don't collect that stupid coin on the right i'm probably it was still there
progressing fuck that coin you ain't ever gonna see me get that coin again unless i get it on
unless i get it on accident it's the worst jump of the whole game it's the worst like look at
just look at how fast i'm just going through all this shit and then i hit that dumb ass jump
and it all falls to shit no he's still here omega low yeah
all right quiet i keep overshooting it yeah when i try to undershoot it when i not when i try to
not overshoot it i undershoot it and sometimes i even go in the fucking thing and then it spits
me out do the dlc why would i do the dlc when i haven't done the original game some of these
should be landing like come on what the fuck and then immediately after is that stupid ass fucking
jump oh my god guys like right after it is that other like tiny little perfect baby jump give me
break i can't get out of this zone i'm stuck here forever i'm stuck here forever i think i
might be stuck here forever i believe in you i don't you fuck you game fuck you game fuck you
game really let's be honest whoa whoa dude what the fuck i'm sorry that was uncalled for
i screw this up every time and i got it's got to be far away
right uh no no god damn it stop it has nothing to do with tilting it has to do with that jump is
so fucking precise it's the only one in this whole zone that's like that and even if you
think you got it you don't oh you don't don't worry you don't my sanity meter is low don't
read chat nothing to chat it has to do with i'm a mean game designer and want players to suffer
that's what it is that's that's the deal that's the goal fucking analog sucks i don't think i can hit
it from here i'm just i'm gonna i'm gonna just launch over yep you just can't from there maybe
you can can't hit it from the back no no no no yeah yeah i just want to get back to where i was
why did that happen it's not about destination it's about the journey now it's about the
destination at this point it's about the destination i want to get there it's about getting there it's
about getting to the top that's that's what it is that's about oh really so i'm driving we're
driving uh cross uh country trip to go to like disney world and i got four kids screaming in
the back singing songs while i got everyone's yelling and i my wife's in the passenger seat
with a map in her hands going like i don't think you went the wrong i think you went the wrong way
i didn't go the wrong way no you want to get to disney world fuck the car ride to disney world
you want to get to disney world and go see goofy
get the coin don't get the coin don't get the coin don't get the coin don't get the coin it's
death it's guaranteed to lose you're guaranteed to lose if you get that coin in this wind now
mean game developer i told you i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got the coin i got
the coin okay coin got it i got the coin i got the coin what happened there what the fuck was that
man what the fuck was that man what i've done it the same way every single time man what do you
what i done it the same way every single time man it was a fun ride i ain't driving disney world
fucking ever again we're ubering next time the same fucking time and like the two times out of
like 60 it doesn't work apparently with the same exact approach no don't even do this
i'm doing it in the wrong direction no i'm not no are you kidding me they make these little jumps
such a pain in the ass like what a pain in the ass what a pain in the ass it's because of the
fucking coin again i'm gonna break this disc in half and i don't even own one i'm gonna go buy
the disc version of this game and then break it back to the tutorial hi guys welcome all because
i picked up the fucking coin oh all right time to time to and we got to do all these pains in the
ass jumps again when i bet you anything that all we would need to do is just simply go up like one
screen at the wind level and we never ain't ever got to see this shit ever again i would guarantee
it boots boots what are you talking about boots i can't buy the boots what do you mean use the coin
i don't have a coin i don't have any coins what are you talking about really in the state i'm in
right now you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna do this to me in this my current state i can't
fucking believe i'm down here again and i was already we saw it twice i got i got a second
chance to get back up there at least there was progress there was at least a little bit i did
get i picked up the coin i did make the bird move can you imagine if i missed dude that jump
sucks such ass it sucks to do that jump it sucks it's got to be this little perfect fucking jump
man and if you don't get it you are fucked i'm trying no challenge joel to beat this no no i i'd
like to see joel live a nice healthy life and not delete like three years of his life because he had
to play the hot sauce game no no no no no god joel don't play this don't do don't do it do not do
this don't don't do it and then and then when you get when you get to this part where you're going
what's with this fucking job this job is to replay this clip and just listen to my voice
so i tried to tell you not to do it i tried don't do it don't do it just play nancy drupe
that's more our speed you know that's more our speed just a quarter of an inch too small a
quarter of an inch too long it's like come on there's no egg it's just like so it doesn't make
any sense to me like what the fuck man give me a break give me a fucking break that's just unfair
that's just unfair it is that's unfair why are those the only two places where i have trouble
why why i could do everything else why are those two places tweedledee and tweedledum of annoying
jumps back to back right there what the fuck mike no no no no no you don't understand you
don't understand you don't understand you don't you don't know you don't know you don't know what
happened you don't know listen for the thing listen listen for it look at i i ripped the
controller uh i ripped the plug out of the controller the controller that i ripped the
plug out of the controller i uh and then i press the uh and i press right i can't believe i'm
fucking down here again i i already beat this don't you understand just how stupid this is
two coin attempts and i was there already why did i have to do that again what was the purpose of
this can somebody i don't just spoil the whole game i don't care what happens if you don't get
the coin what happens if you what happens if you get the coin just i don't give a shit spoiler
you get the boots who cares wait man is all this pain worth the game uh it depends on how you view
pain um it's up to you if you uh if you like the feeling of all of your teeth falling out
this game's for you then if you like the sound of nails on a chalkboard while somebody is is
punching you in the chest as hard as they can i mean it might this could be yours could be a
game for you if you like eating ice cream like just yummy chocolate ice cream i've got a game
series you might like nancy drew i can't believe i'm back here again like you could rewind uh this
stream so when i made it back up to the wind place like you gotta be kidding me what am i
doing down here again for a third fuck what's going on you gotta be kidding me like seriously
i can't even believe it like i'm like oh and we're gonna hit the bottom of the game
why did i get the coin what was the purpose of me getting this is the beginning welcome to the
beginning of the game hi stay screen one yes yay we did it boys and girls we made it to the end
and we made it to the game the end of the game there it is i did it i saw it like can i go back
in time and like belly to back suplex germa from fucking an hour ago all right i think i'm gonna
go get that coin can i like fucking scoop slam him and take over his place like i don't care
it i if i'm the new germa like germa if you're listening to me in the future just come do it
and be the germa that's fine that would create a time paradox worth it that'd be worth it okay
here we go just get me uh i will get back to the snow you guys know if it's gonna happen
hey just got back from a four-hour gaming session how's the progress going um not bad actually
pretty good i think i'm doing okay i wouldn't say i'm doing terribly you know what i mean he's on
new game plus yeah i mean this is the new game plus version well then i just there's no more
coin to get and we can be over this pain it'll be so great the second week i can't wait till we all
start pogging our brains out dude i'm gonna pog so hard i might pass out when i actually get
to the snow level and go up once i'm gonna pog my pants and i missed it i messed it up thank
god the game had mercy you got it you got this i know you do everything's cool it's not i wish
there was a megaman indicator like the longer you held down it was like no no no no rather than just
you know what i mean i wish it was like a it's like an give me like an audio cue
happened there oh my god what the fuck happened there man what the fuck i'm getting sad
not even angry i'm getting sad he's getting sad he's gonna cry our dreams
it's okay it's all right no don't worry somebody just wrote somebody just wrote dude you can play
something else it's okay i feel bad for you don't it's um don't worry i'll be fucking around don't
worry don't worry all right that's like making me laugh dude just play something else man like i'm
like feel like really bad for you you guys that's all good i feel bad for you oh don't feel bad
just quit streaming it's not for you yeah i'm just fucking kidding
i just want to get up to the snow part and then that's that's like my i suck at the game
like i suck asshole of the game like if i get to snow level three times then i went did you know
what like you have like a like a child play game and they get to a portion and you just want to
play so you just go oh you beat it you won you did it i did i won yeah you won nice work
oh yeah good job and then you take it back you're just like i gotta get this away from this kid
it's like hands are like bright hello what's up what the internet died oh yeah that makes sense
it is conked internet you know well don't worry that's that's just like another vod
actually no it shouldn't be okay same deal get me up there let's go baby this is the one chat's
gonna be delayed on the vod yeah i know that sucks i almost wish with that feature i wish
that that feature didn't have maybe maybe if it like paused the chat for like a few minutes or
something because it throws up the whole thing doesn't it ripvod watches yeah sorry guys sorry
fall down if it's live well you think i'm pumping in like pre-recorded footage
it's too far and it's too short then it's too far then it's too short then it's too far then it's
too short then it's too far then it's too short then it's too far then it's too short then it's
too far then it's too short then it's too short then it's too far then it's too short then it's
too short then it's too far then it's too far then it's too short then it's too far then it's too
short it doesn't matter what you do like you'll you'll fuck it up every time did you hold the
button down for like a tenth of a second earlier you missed did you hold it for a tenth of a second
longer you don't you butt jumped into the wall idiot i want a super cut of every fall now that
actually would be kind of interesting considering there's been a 581 of them just skipped through
the vod this is the super cut oh yeah yeah i really i think this part is way harder
than the next part the part with the platforms like i wish i could just fall down to that spot
and not have to do this jump like that like why why why is why why like why
i would rather do the top the screen above that a thousand more times all right ladies and
gentlemen let's go end of the stream what no no no no no no no not even close
if he didn't make that jump he would have turned off the stream
no don't laugh at what that person just said it was i almost just fucking started laughing
somebody said uh somebody said please show face came i want to see a crying face
i have to laugh now it's just tears just tears coming down my eyes
okay that's i haven't been here in a while i haven't been here in a while
oh i haven't been here in a while what stop playing badly what are you talking about i had
just had i'd spin i has been like 40 minutes since i've been up at that screen
it's okay it's all right it's all right don't overshoot it it's okay it's all right no god
damn it that's the worst thing that could happen oh damn it what was wrong with that what was wrong
with that one get out of here fuck off i just pogged no hold your pogs hold your pogs hold your
pogs hold your pogs don't no pogging hold them
i was doing the pumped it up get pumped up thing and i slipped and pressed the button
and i jumped off the fucking edge oh god oh my heart is racing right now i thought i was going
all the way down it worked for a minute you it's like i seriously thought i was going all the way
down i was like no please not again okay relax i'm not playing any more music i'm just gonna
fucking do it premature population man there again and i just like sweat you know what i mean
like i i just by i get my i'm covered in water like my hands are just covered in water
like where's my compensation for like where's my water compensation well i'm like a water player
sucks too this one this one also sucks please beat this game it's all i'm asking
we'll see we'll see in another we'll see when i get up here now the answer is probably going to be
no fuck off with this all right this is it i didn't even know you could hit your head on that slow
down slow down slow down slow down slow down i don't know why i didn't realize you could hit
and we're okay uh and it's so precise it's so it's so it's so much it's so much
what happened there he thinks falling is funny god damn it man it's just so hard to tell a lot
of times what is and isn't going to land on certain things he thinks this is a joke
uh is it i don't know what do you think it's that's that jump right there oh it sucks because
you have to get the right on that left edge to be able to make the platform on the left
no god damn it i've had it you can't go that fucking far with it you can't go that far with it
oh god damn it oh slow down slow down stop stop stop oh it's oh my god it's so hard
this is the hardest thing i've ever done in my whole life and i've done i've done open heart
surgery on somebody guys i'm a fucking surgeon i didn't tell you that that's a lawyer that you
never had or i think i'm late all the time doctor strange hold it down for long the set i i swear
to god i held up for the exact same amount of time i did last time but there's no way for me
to tell because there's no goddamn feedback as to how long you're doing anything pug in ball
torture puh puh almost almost there stop missing um i'm guys i'm trying i'm really trying i'm
trying it's just it's a lot it's a lot for my brain it's a lot i'm still here i'm still here
you know oh it's it's just that is the hardest jump here the fuck i my foot my my fuck my hands
listen to this that's oil that is oil all over me that's fucking oil covered in my i'm covered
in it it's like disgusting and i missed that because i my hands slid around i'm actually
covered in oil i wish i could just play this with my eyes when's that technology going to come out
that i don't use my my greasy ass hands anymore like i need to i'm gonna you know what i'm gonna
install in my house one of those in the bathroom hand dryers like the like i i need it i actually
need that i really do those things get germs everywhere i i don't care about germs as much
as not having wet hands yeah i have to go dry my hands i need i need powder i'm gonna cover
my fucking hands in talcum powder you think this is bullshit i'm doing it right now that's been a
major problem this whole stream you blame your biology for your skills yeah guys sorry if i'm
reading a book and the book is wet i'm the pages are gonna be fucked up i'm back i'm going to dry
up these fucking hands i'm i'm gonna cover with i'm gonna with a comical a hysterical like jerry
lewis movie amount of powder all over my hands i'll be right back all right better let's go
better let's do it do a hand cam no no no you're not getting a goddamn hand cam
no hand cams you've tried to do that so i'll blow it all and we'll go back to the tutorial zone
again it feels a little bit my grip is a little bit better if i didn't that one always gets me
because it's such a such a fucking weird angle the angle there sucks so now i'll tell you something
that's disgusting that's going on this made it worse because now the powder is turning into this
disgusting clay substance on my hands it's now a uh like molding clay i'm gonna do i need to go get
winter gloves no because it'll be slipping around
molding clay molding clay that's correct can i retract my pug yes yes you can you only pog if
we get up here that if they fuck with the background fucks with you it's intentional
that's dash jumps i guess it's not called walk king right it's called perfect ass no room for
any pixel of error jump king let's just just call it pixel perfect king it's the same damn thing
greasy man covers hands in clay out of frustration with children's game no children is going to play
this game no child is going to get past the first they're going to be stuck in the bottom
kids beat this game it's sick so much worse it's all i have to like wash the controller
oh damn it you motherfucker it's so it's too much it's too much it's too much i'll be lucky
to get through this i'll be lucky to get to even 10 away through this fucking game
four percent of chat beat this game why i know i'm trying to be one of them i'm trying to be one of
them i told you i want to be somebody here we go it's my opportunity just bounce so i do it again
make a good luck charm out of my clay i can't hold this pog any longer well you're going to
have to because i don't know when that's going to be available to you i don't know i have no idea
now looks like you'll excuse me i'm jumping on four pixel wide popsicle sticks give me one moment
please don't pog don't pog don't pog just hold on man don't pog yet hold on it's no don't you're
going to jinx me damn it man are you fucking kidding me why do they have to make it like that
why does it have to be like that like so jumping on fucking popsicle sticks and if you fall it's
over what the fuck were they thinking what are they thinking don't release the pogs don't do it
there's no reason for it those are those pogs are illegal
germa continued to lie about jet set radio i played jet set radio and i got really angry at
it and had to rage quit it you remember that it's either like you go way too far or you go
not far enough it's like that exact jump you have to do you gotta get it right or it's never gonna
happen and now you're like you get like so there's just the zero feedback makes me want to puke
please stop blue pogging me i'm sorry i'm sorry i have to get to the top of the mountain first
before you're allowed to pog might as well like he wants to do it so bad i know i'd like you to
as well trust me i would oh too far too far no no no no no no too far too too short too far too short
too short too short too short too far oh wait look at me oh what's that the room for error here is
point one seconds oh that's too far i ain't ever getting back up to that
fucking dumb raven coin area i ain't ever gonna get up there again am i am i just never gonna
get up there again remember bandages and meat boy and how fun that mechanic was
i loved it i thought it was awesome this ain't it not even close my fucking god oh my fucking god
oh my god oh my god i'm turning the stream off i don't care i don't care if i'm one of like
640 people on earth that have beat this game who cares who fucking cares where's the redemption
arc i know that's why i'm doing that that's why i'm saying that so i can fucking have a redemption
arc well the redemption arc is uh has to happen literally away welcome to the beginning of the
game isn't this fun aren't you having a fun time i have to go all the way to the beginning
to go all the way to the end again yeah you know you know like don't you know like you just you
have to go all the way to the back of the beginning of the game before you can do a full
true redemption arc for here's the problem guys i'm sorry to uh to make this uh you know about me
here uh we've had like six redemption arcs i don't think my character is gonna live
i don't think i'm making it to season two because uh we've had about six uh redemption arcs
and none of them worked out to do this all again god damn it man like why do they why can't they be
even anything why does it have to be like this why not like this because now what happens is you
you all of my my like memories all my shit is from like spending two hours up fucking there
not down here i haven't been down here in like an hour and 20 minutes so now i'm like okay let me
oh wait i forgot i have to do this whole thing again fucking any memories i have a few just cheat
no no it's just the dumb bird mechanic stupid ass bird and that i thought i could fall straight
down i technically did and i gotta go all the way back up through that stupid bullshit oh man i am
oh i i might be defeated here very soon i may be defeated it really depends it depends how many
times i have to do the beginning of the video game again streamer defeated streamer defeated
oh yeah fuck man this sucks i don't want to do the green ninja turtle level again
but i have to remember when i was playing uh simpsons hit and run and i spent what like maybe
two hours on that last two levels know what i say i was like oh fuck this i'm out of here this
stupid fucking dumb i hate this and what did i do continue to complain for like three hours
at that same mission but after that after about four hours what did i do that's right i beat it
i finished it i think this is a lot different than simpsons hit and run though
because i don't have to go back and do the first mission of simpsons hit and run i don't have to
go back uh to chapter one in simpsons hit and run it might be a little different i just want
to get back up to the wind i just want to see new content i just have to get up there i just have to
get up there for a third fucking time oh i can get the coin oh my god and that's what this all
stems from all of this stems from get the coin forehead all of this let that be a lesson to all
of you watching don't chase the money we will fucking destroy you remember that's the message
that was i like it's just why i don't understand like i don't understand man
i don't understand like why is it fucking come on man what the fuck what the fuck
it's just like you can't what the fuck man what the fuck man what the fuck man take the dev
path yeah i want confirmation that the dev could beat his own mario maker level is there a hidden
dev door in here the only shortcut is in the sewers the dentist believed in me yeah well i'm
sorry if i get into a race with a horse i'm gonna lose you can believe me all you want
get me the fuck up here so i can at least accomplish the thing that i had
you got to stay calm i know i know i'm gonna get this i'll get this i'll get this i'll get
this i'll get it i'm gonna get it i'll get this hey you know uh i think maybe we should have some
music
play oh my god play play play play play what is that play play what's that what's that mean what
is that from play it's from a game what it's from raid shadow legends why is that is that thing a
meme because why is that such a meme okay does somebody explain that to me is because it's about
like a sponsorship thing i'm pogging not yet it's an adventure game and that jump sucks such an
asshole it really does you got to get like an exact perfect fucking spot i shouldn't have grabbed
the fucking coin i shouldn't have grabbed the coin you know what i'm saying this whole thing
is avoided like the last two and a half hours if i just don't touch the coin i will say it like a
broken fucking record get me the fuck up here give me a break i can't take it anymore yeah play it
play it you'll see okay all right i'm ready let's go no more screw ups
i didn't know that was i didn't know i didn't know i didn't know i didn't know i actually didn't know
i didn't know what was over there i didn't know what i don't know what wait what then now now we
go all the way back down like yeah now we just go all the way back down because oh hey welcome
to the new area you're gonna screw up go all the way back down hey there's like a brand new
zone but like the who knows where the fuck he's supposed to jump did you miss go all the way back
down haha got you maybe charge trial and error maybe some some some some progress maybe maybe
no no just go all the way back down do you miss the jump that you didn't know existed and that
you haven't seen before go all the way back down the beginning of the game go go go idiot go go
what are you stupid haha god and i actually got fucking stuck now here we are again hey i made it
to the snow level no go all the way back down to the beginning of the game what are you talking
about progress and no no go back down to the beginning you don't what are you doing
do you want to do all this again oh he's mad yeah he's mad
and the career i can feel his rage i'm not even sure it's rage i think it's just why like why
why it's a i'm just
ladies and gentlemen we have uh breaking news here let's see how turbo 985 how he's doing after
six hours he's here with us now he said he's not angry at all so he's asking a question
let's see what that means yes yes i am i simply am asking the question of why i'm not even red
like i wish that you could just not have to go down this far like you've game you know that i
beat this part you already know you know i beat this part like 20 000 times do i have to jump
through the chimney again do i have to do this again i've done this already this game doesn't
care about your feelings yeah i know we already talked about that new genre of video game right
this great new genre called i don't care you do it or don't do it eat the hot sauce
he's still talking about the hot yeah all right all right uh the snow level looks like it's a new
mechanic that's been added to further frustrate me so uh i don't know we'll see if i at least
i got to play thunderstruck for like a fifth time and delete my whole vod so you know
you know yeah at least i got to delete my entire vod by playing a thunderstruck five times
that was various look i went like this done done right that that's transformed if it's various
become one with the game get in there german we why couldn't we have played mario you i don't
think you want me to play mario i just it's like so
so
you should watch other streamers rage at this that's that's what i've done i've just i'm just
marketing bait for this game don't you guys understand i can end up in a compilation now
somewhere that's just like no fuck this fuck this game this game fucking fucking stupid fucking
i just ended up in a fucking marketing compilation that's the long game that's the con have you heard
about that fucking game that's so hard that it made germany five shit his pants on camera
and then it's cuts to me like dude i i'm i fucking fell down for another time guys i shit my pants
i gotta go fuck this game it's not a compilation it was just six hours of me
so fucking funny it's just me
why would it just be me hard jumps this is fucking stupid up to 10 hours of in-game content
escape sucks secrets don't get the coin don't get the fucking coin you're gonna get mad
i've covered my hands with with with talcum powder watch this asshole screw it up over and over again
jump king get it on steam where i guarantee you half of all these reviews are meme reviews
talking about how much they hated themselves while they played the game
jump king get it on steam get it on the steam sale at least take a breather or play a relaxing game
so you don't have a heart attack all right i'm not gonna have a fucking a heart attack
i'm gonna be fine don't have a heart attack imagine you had like a heart attack while you
played this is this like a oh no heart attack i'm not having a heart attack fucking time man
it's either a hair too short or a hair too high and then you end up all the way back down here
and then like the whole thing's fucked up we're talking hairs we're talking literal hairs
on your head are if you fall down to the beginning of the game or not i think that deserves a fucking
meme review just link this stream like i i make a steam review this is linked this whole stream
this is kind of what you can expect ah the music's good uh the sound effects are good too i guess
dude this game's not that hard lol that's all right whatever all right okay okay i guess it's
not do the fit will you fall at the beginning again i love that it was very funny dude go do
do the fit will you fall to the end again that is my favorite part of the stream god damn it
uh come on why if i go that far down again that's it this jump right here fucks me every time
okay don't let us get down there again i don't i don't want to even see those platforms
those platforms that are up here after this part oh yeah and then the snow shit if you fall you go
all the way back down what is wrong with i've done that the same way every fucking time what the
fuck man i've you hold the button down the whole time i've done what the he's beginning to believe
no i'm not even close i mean i'm beginning to believe to turn the game off and turn the stream
off if that's what you mean i'm beginning to believe that one i'm believing that one again
it happened again again for the second time in a row you just hold the you hold the jump
the whole way and go left why did that not work twice in a row now hold the button what is going
on what the fuck man four percent how many people have beaten dark souls like on like
playstation trophies because i'm too far to the edge at least three probably least three
we are let us pog oops i'm gonna take this so slow have i eaten anything yes i have
i ate earlier today like right before the stream started that's uh i don't even know what did i eat
something i have no progress i have no progress and i must pog that's a pretty good one actually
okay for the love of god omega lol not like this don't give into cynicism
uh in this whole game based on cynicism and torturing yourself that's the whole point of the
game pog and what was it torture what was it i'm starting to move with the controller now which
means i'm really trying are you having fun uh kind of i was and then that fun like translated into
just accepting that i'm here i'm just here why if it's not if it's not fun no it is
i'm having fun i'm at stage five fun acceptance stop that's that's funny but no it's don't go all
the way down me man we're bound to fall okay i'm reading chat and not playing the game let's stop
that for now just do the dlc you can't fall down as far so is the dlc just better than this
it's harder oh god i don't want to play it relax very funny new level you won't see just unplug the
pc that's a great spam that's it that's a really good just like spam the streamer far i wish i
could just have a system where i could just be able to attempt it again just bounce over here
yeah once i get to up to the snow again we fall down again it's over i'm gonna go eat like a bag
of mcdonald's gross actually yeah no no no no no that's a bad idea that's not even that yeah
that's not how would i do that all right snow level time just get up here all right all right
all right it's time to go it's time to go it's time to go okay this is this is just i it's just
this ain't up my alley you know what i mean like it's saying up my alley this is not like this
ain't up my alley it's saying up the alley it's saying up the alley what did i get 25 percent of
the way through this game gamer license gone no this is not a game this is a non-canon gamer
license game not even close this is this is this is like the extended universe for like getting
extra stamps on your gamer license not even getting one i'm halfway through the game what
no i'm not you are what are we talking about i'm halfway to my gamer license what are you
kidding me no fucking way we're halfway halfway no i just i don't believe you i don't believe you
i could we be that close though i mean what would we do if we were that close
we would probably maybe get a couple of little bit again maybe we get some tunes on
guys this game is this game's way too hard for me it just is and i've been trying to fight with
saying like hey is this game like nearly impossible for me to complete oh no no only four percent of
all humans now i'm one of those four percent of all human beings yeah that's me that's me i'll be
up there with the trophy no i mean my gamer skill at this point is literally like being able to read
kingdom hearts 3 dialogue so like no i don't think so you yeah you want the trophy you go get it you
go get it and then we can have a conversation about about how how many teeth you have left
because they're all gonna be gone when you've done playing this one fuck that jump and fuck this one
too oh what's that let me let me what's what's on the top of my head oh that was a hair oh uh
jump king the video game there just put it down on the table you're gonna play this next stream
right no i will never play this again what you see tonight is what you get i ain't i am ever
ever going to open this game ever again um if somebody came in the stream right now and said
hey dude i'm like a huge fan of jump king i'll pay you fifty thousand dollars right now to
continue playing it tomorrow i'd say no i'd say yes i'm just kidding definitely would say yes
i would absolutely say yes like immediately you can probably be less way less than that
it'd be like a way way way way less than that 24 hour jump king stream are you trying to kill me
that's how you kill someone that's how that's how you die no you guys are trying to truth serum me
you think that like the more that i play and the more of this like drug game that i take in
and the more like fucked up i become oh there we go now let's get some secrets out of them
this too far too i need to be up there god damn it like it's it's so easy to fuck this up
it's so easy to fuck everything in this game up it's so easy this is like playing getting over it
but you're sitting on a bed of nails like it's really easy for you to shimmy and be like god
oh i just want to see the snow one more time i'm not going to be able to i'm not going to be able
to i got memed in the meme game yeah yeah i'll see you guys tomorrow see you guys later
see you tomorrow it's been fun see you guys tomorrow uh lots of exciting things going on
tomorrow uh absolutely not jump king literally ever again just like i mean like like actually
like actually just never fucking again ever ever again like just like i mean we're talking never
again like like a zero percent chance you know take that 50 grand shove it fuck it i don't want
it i'm not taking it uh so let's go ahead and get back up there if i tilt my if i tilt my monitor
upside down you've been doing really well uh i'm telling you you guys you guys are fucking hilarious
you guys say some of the funniest shit i swear to god
it's like i'm you know when you get deja vu just like over i'm just over and over again getting
deja vu like you've just you've been here before like motherfucker you've been here before you've
done this already a bunch of time you've been here before and even though i've been here before
it's got i you still get lost watch the speedrun um i don't i don't want to watch the speedrun of
a game that i can't i can't do because then i i it's spoilers and i mean i'm never playing
this game literally ever again but tonight i'm still here because it's all bullshit i'm just
trying to make myself have to focus you know what i'm saying i'm like i'm like bargaining with my
own body my own brain that's that's where you yeah if you fall there uh yeah yeah if you fall there
you said you fucked the whole thing up remember if you do one mistake on one jump is specifically
some of the it ruins the entire thing you know can't wait for it in 10 years competitive e-sport
teeth pulling yeah it's gonna be great or who can hit themselves in the face with a chair harder
looks like wow we got uh me if me the new episode of the mandalorian looks great
yeah i'm gonna have to call it here soon i'm getting to the point where i don't want to see
these images again you know what i mean it's getting close it's not cool it's not there yet
but it'll be there probably soon i don't want to see the fucking birds in the background here
anymore like i don't want to see this anymore you know what i mean it's like i'm replaying the same
level over and over again it's like i i played level two i don't want to see what two no more
if you start winning you want that's not true because even if you do start winning that's the
beauty of this game even if you do win eventually you're going to miss a jump and come back to level
two you will see level two again my friend oh yes you will many times he thinks he thinks he's not
gonna see level two again you're getting better i i don't think so i think i've devolved am i
getting better do you think you actually think so am i getting better i think and am i 50% of the
way through the game what's the point of leaving that no no no no no no no no no no why i did the
same thing i did last time i did the same thing i did last time i just wish it didn't go that far
down like i did i did the same damn thing i did last time just overshot it and now we go all the
way back down and now we go all the way back down again hey back to back to level one that's that's
it goodbye that's it goodbye i have to leave i don't want to do this again this is dumb i don't
want to do this again somebody came in and said dude this game is literal insanity now i see what
you mean by that your concentration gets maxed out yeah you get to you just everything just starts to
blend together you don't want to see the crows anymore you don't want to see the green sewer
anymore and you yeah everything just maxes out there's a finite amount of human brain energy
oh man i why do i want to beat this what is doing this to me i don't want i don't care what i what
do i care i don't even care let it go jerry let it go i can't i can't let it go well it's only
been six and a half hours it's not that long oh my fucking god like just oh it oh that's just
i'm gonna be i'm gonna be in bed tonight just i'm gonna be fucking furious because i'm just
gonna be like god damn it i don't i could have gone farther i could have gone further you know
what i mean i could have done it and i'm gonna have nightmares we may have reached the maximum
brain capacity though on the second or third thunderstruck that i think we were at the end
yeah like that that thunderstruck replay number two is when i i maxed out every ounce of my
concentration so we did play what like three or four more times you know i bet you don't say
it jeremy don't don't do it don't do it don't say it don't say it don't say it yeah i'm gonna say
it i'm gonna say it if i had if i had sleep and i came back and i had i would might probably i
don't say i'm not gonna say it don't say it don't do it if i slept on it if i if i
yeah if i slept on it i was 50 if i was 50 of the way through the game
if i sleep on it i come back with and i'm gonna eat a bunch of fucking cereal and shit
i'm gonna eat like i'm gonna i'm gonna take like a riboflavin extract i'm gonna take it like a b
vitamin complex multivitamin we're playing it tomorrow i'm gonna take b vitamins and i'm gonna
and i'm gonna do it i will beat it i just i need i just need energy i need just like brain energy
you know what i mean because look at i as much as it's hard i know i know this shit and if i came
back if i listen to thunderstruck on repeat with just earbuds into my as far as i can shove them
into my ears on max volume on repeat for the next 12 hours in bed i think i could do it let me just
get up here but i have a question if you save and exit does it start to go where you are
like will it remember where i am or is it do i have to start from the beginning
doesn't matter i mean kind of don't let the game defeat me no i'm not no no no i mean i'm
i'm just talking bullshit you know what i mean like i'm just kidding around this guy uh
there's two people talking right now i don't want to play this tomorrow
i don't want to do that i'm not i don't want to play this tomorrow uh somebody else is talking
don't listen to that person they're absolutely incorrect i don't want to do this i don't want
to play this why would i play this tomorrow it's fight club what you know what i mean i don't
well don't listen to that guy holy shit uh amnestic ow just gave 50 community subs
so my goodness that's a lot of subs thank you seriously dodged again damn that's a lot
that means you have to keep playing tomorrow we will let me just get to a position where i can
save it uh amnestic you also gave shit earlier too so that's a lot of subs which one's the real
jeremy i told you that somebody came back in time and tried to stop me from getting the coin
we've been switching controllers ever since let the good jeremy play the game um good as in like
a good person or like good isn't good at the game because it's good and evil
there's two of us here i have good and evil in me fuck i'm sorry i have yeah i have i'm good but
i'm also evil too that should have been it you know that should have been it dog shit dog shit
dog shit okay i've got a new emote called dog shit what the fuck was wrong with that one dog
shit all right i've gotten back up here what is it six and a half hours damn okay that's pretty
long that's not that long though am i all right yeah yeah okay all right let me just try to
hold on why am i so addicted to this game all right we're back up here not enough you think
you're on a flow but then the game's just fucking unbearable it's fucking on base it's unbearable
this is unbearable right jeremy from four hours ago oh it's on right yes thank you for summoning
me it's unbearable jermis didn't stop playing no i think i won't do that why would i do that
i knew i should have held it for a tad longer yeah okay so now at this stage here if i fall
down again it's done it's over i will if i get up to the snow area we can stop and i can just save
it and please tell me that if i haven't met that snow area that that's it and i can save it there
right will it actually open up tomorrow there it does not really it says you can save the game
i'll be surprised if you can't do that it'll it will open up wherever you are yeah okay i was
gonna say why would there be a save button too much too much too much oh damn it yeah it's it
that's it okay that's it all right guys i'll see you guys tomorrow for we'll see who wins the
we'll see who wins the fight tomorrow in my nightmares is rational germa going to win this
battle or is jump king germa going to win that battle you know what i mean i don't know at this
point that it's completely up in the air they're going to be fighting all night it ain't gonna end
well hey boys heading up just kidding okay so i just want to get up here just want to get up here
that's it just want to get right here now what's the worst what's the way to go save you idiot i
know i know this is a mistake i'm up here but hold on where am i what was that explosion what
was that explosion for okay so i go you jump up and then just get carried into there probably from
i got an idea i bet you should i but should i go do with the wind or without the wind yeah
you shouldn't have gone i'm fine um that fuck yeah fuck yeah fuck yeah now with what about straight
up yeah i think that's the play straight up in the air fly oh my goodness i did it i did it i did
it but i don't know what's up here oh my god okay it's going well 50 of the way through the game
release the pugs that's not snow though
that's from the ninja turtles uh turtles in time that's how shredder laughs i can't walk
i gotta get over there i gotta get over there but this is gonna drop me straight down
um i don't know the trajectory i really don't
fuck will i make it into the snow okay then we go straight in the air and get carried over to that
side oh my fucking god i can't walk okay
fire fire fire shut up idiot yeah if i get stuck i'm not sure i gotta jump into the wind
i just got raided oh shit i just got raided raided right now during the middle of of of of me
trying oh god well thanks for the raid that was ludwig holy shit welcome everybody now i can't
stop uh thank you i don't know i'm not sure where where you guys came from what you were doing but
welcome what's going on i'm currently playing a game called jump king it's really really fun
i can promise you that it's a fun game i was not 10 minutes ago talking about how i hated the game
and i was not going to play it ever again and i was going to end the stream uh that didn't happen
none of that happened don't listen to anybody in the chat that says otherwise they're just a bunch
they're just a bunch of fucking goofers you know what i mean but thank you ludwig uh really
appreciate that let's go pause the game oh you would like to see yeah there you go i appreciate
it though welcome to the stream 800 in the that's actually kind of an interesting number eight eight
one one eight one one i have to make a move here otherwise i gotta make a move here i'm gonna jump
into the wind from here a big one and now i'm going from here i'm gonna say it's gonna have
to be a big one oh yeah yeah up in the air straight in the air okay now what the hell do i do um
shit are these enemies i don't i think they just watch the re i tried to jump into one of them and
talk to them and i fell down all the way to beginning again so jump on the left one first
let me just do a little hop so i can i wonder if i go the one on the left oh yeah yeah hold on save
and reload quit the game wait what why i'm gonna i think i think this is a good spot this is a good
spot good spot good spot good spot almost i think this is the one i didn't jump high enough pay
attention to the wind um i am i'm just trying to get in a spot where i can get up there here we go
already let's try it ladies and gentlemen i just did that i just did it i'm up here now what the
hell do i do uh to the right a huge jump to the right the right bot to the right the left or the
right right jump with the wind to the right big huge full jump all right i'm gonna go for it
i'm going for it max jump with the wind
i could get up there no jeremy what are you thinking
jeremy what the hell are you doing what am i doing what am i what the hell are you doing
fuck are you doing stop stop stop stop relax i really want to get over
jesus there it is all right we're good oh my god what the hell are you thinking
choke well don't choke and quit choking um what do you mean i'm at the snow level
this is the longest i've been up here those of you that just joined the stream
i've had i had a lot of problems down there i don't want to go back down there
i'm doing everything possible to not do that to not fall down there
all right let's do this again so you're saying more community subs non-descript civilian
10 more community subs thank you damn i'm scared to a full jump thank you so much non-descript
civilian this is the spot right fuck is this a good though maybe not a full jump
fuck it's it's not a full jump it's not a full jump it's a little bit it's a little less than
a full jump it's not a full jump damn it creatures thanks for the five community subs creatures rule
five more coming in oh dear more subs yeah see that's not good for me that's not good for me
i gotta catch it before there's no move like for instance one two three go now
there we go okay is this good i feel like it's not good enough
oh shit okay not a full jump not a full jump not a full jump not a full jump not a full jump
oh now what straight up in the air i don't know jumped to the left or jump up i wonder if i can
make it
i'm panicking that was a full that was a panic attack well i know i just i fucking panicked
it's okay we're good god damn it oh am i up i don't know straight up trying to get to the right you
think but then okay hold on i don't know when to go oh my god it saved me ready
nope now you gotta wall bounce hard you gotta wall bounce real hard do you though
i don't know i can't go up from here uh up into the right i know but i i don't
try jump up with when it goes to the when the wind is blowing left is when i should do it
right here we go let's see if it works cross your fingers god okay um i think i go
just a little bit just up or small little jump to the left done and then we go all straight up in the
air holy shit it never ends it never ends this is horrible god damn it man i don't think i'm in a
good spot it's just a small just a i'm gonna hit my head on the ceiling here we go oh my god oh my
god oh my god i went way too far and i made it to the other side this is a bad spot i could take
my chances of trying to go to the right without any wind you know i'm saying just like try to get
right without when the wind stops go upright i'm going for it it was the one it was the one it was
it was it was correct just didn't go high enough oh man it's over i didn't want to go with the
wing because i didn't want to get blown too far i just didn't hold the button long enough
sorry it's all right i'm not that far back oh i can i could get i could just say scream
fucking swear i could just say like shit okay hold on oh it's so oh okay i'm gonna stay calm
don't do a full jump it's close same deal how the hell did i even get up there i don't remember
it was a full to the right but i gotta get over there first nope shit i was in that was a bad i
was in a terrible spot it was a really bad spot this is not a good spot either i'm smiling i'm
smiling little jump just a little one yeah it's in a bad spot uh-oh i don't think i'll it's not
gonna take me up there i don't think it'll pick me up here we go again full jump to the right
into the wind let's go y'all gonna think i'm crazy for this oh god damn it i was way i was
just trying to get over there without the wind this is hell this is actually hell are you serious
what are you talking about what are you talking about what are you talking about
jerma please you got this i don't know i don't know all right now can i please
please no why the wind won't grab me why won't it grab me in that spot do i have to go up
i don't understand the shitty spot i have to just go for it i can't really get out of this
i'm trying to get in that spot over there go eat a brownie that would be pretty good i
i'd like that but again can i do this shit again please here we go i would that was in full what's
going on i i just did a full jump i didn't do anything else i just held down a i think i have
to get to the second ledge i think what the fuck just keep jumping just keep jumping jumping the
air is neutral that's not bad i have to get in a better spot than this that's not a better oh man
there's so many opportunities for you to fall in that snow level holy shit man this game is
something else i'll tell you this game is something else oh this game is something else
ah see you tomorrow that was that was as close as i was gonna get see you tomorrow yeah that's it
that's it we'll see what i do tomorrow well i'm gonna get in a fight with myself and my brain
i don't want to fall down from here i don't want to do that bullshit again i don't want to do that
bullshit down there again you saw how i acted you know you can always tell when i like i'm at
okay i don't want to fall down here save game exit done bye
i just wanted to see what happened i just wanted to see what it looked like i just wanted to make
sure if you weren't lying to me i had lost progress too fuck me
wait what do you mean why did i save
it's not that far it's like one screen down it's not a big deal you know how much how many times
i did those two screens way too many times what you can save scum the game what what what are
you talking about hold on what do you mean if i fall down right now and i exit the game and
don't save will i come back here you don't you can't don't get your baby okay fine
we'll see if i play it tomorrow i don't know we're gonna have to be in a mood to play it
we'll see what we do tomorrow thanks for watching though it's been fun
let me exit the game though
that's so many falls oh my god i feel like i get hit by like a train
what's the achievements um i don't even i don't even know what they are the last few stages are
incredibly difficult no that's that's i'm as it was that was fun but i'm dead that's you're in
world one i can't believe you kept going well sometimes you just have to go you know what i
mean he quit streaming six times don't feel pressured to play it tomorrow you can always
take a break and return another time i know i know but 95 of the stuff i was saying was
bullshit anyways you know that all right let's go back uh to let me make sure here
we are going to do the the the couple hours that we played that minecraft event i do want to go
over some of them at least the ones that i didn't get to catch so these are from the minecraft
stream uh so from yesterday we had 500 bits from trident jacks thank you trident jacks said what the
fuck germa sad vega 250 yesterday i greatly enjoyed this you kind of went a little mad
with power here though yeah that if you if you didn't uh catch the beginning of the stream
that what we did yesterday was a glorified stress test beta test none of the systems were in place
the twitch integration wasn't in place the server had some issues and um there was no permadeath
we just were like you know what let's just go and just have collect data because even
if you do a stress test when potentially thousands of people are trying to do the
same thing at the same time uh there's a lot of things that you need to collect
in regards to how that's even going to work the next time we do that it's going to be put in
the oven for a little longer so it will be more of the game that we were going to play
rather than the streams an hour late let's just dump on a bunch of people with no whitelisting
and like in the future the guards aren't going to be that powerful they're not going to be able
to teleport that it was really just to keep the peace for a stress test essentially they collected
our data no no no i'm saying like for the server to be hit that hard keep the peace right so thanks
for helping us do that because the next time we do it it'll be a lot more fleshed out
uh thank you nat for the 500 bits creatures rule gave five community subs yesterday as well
siku gave ten dollars yesterday ten thousand bits they said it's 4 a.m i've been up for a good 24
hours good morning apparently i get to catch the stream start for once damn yeah none of the guards
were in creative mode they could just move around and when the game is actually played
and there's actual permadeath involved and this actual stamina system is actually working
correctly and everything there will be things in place to make it so it's not just messy the
first like hour that you play the game yeah the the devs were in creative not the guards right
yeah is my minecraft mod going to be more or less disappointing than star citizen
well i'll give you a couple of quick strong differences here uh my minecraft mod events
uh did not cost 150 million dollars and i didn't start making them 10 years ago
so there's that oh sorry 280 million dollars right but thank you siku dark soul thanks to
the 250 bits here's some bits someone apparently stole my minecraft account i haven't used in eight
years four days ago what can we play cube world instead cube world that's not cool siku again
thanks to the 500 bits buy a five dollar mic for an upgrade that will be fixed next time as well
we were trying a different streaming setup so we could show different perspectives of cameras
but there's probably just going to be two streams next time and i'm just going to squad
with the other streaming account that's filming stuff so there'll be a squad stream of all the
stuff going on but it'll be on a separate stream so then you can get like my actual full perspective
if you don't ever want to see anything else i'm guessing you were talking through discord yeah
we've been to that i had like a line into my ear where they could tell me things that were you
know problems that were happening or whatever will that work for a vod um you would just have
to go to both channels and just queue them up at the same time and just play them at the same time
because that seems like the best way to make it so i can actually just show my perspective
always turn off channel points they're garbage this is not the jeremy i love
um i i didn't even know they were on until they turned on into beta uh like six hours ago
i don't i didn't even know i had them i didn't even know i had them i'm just going to change
them to be something it's going to be like 50 000 points to get me to do something i don't know
i'm gonna up the value i'm gonna up the values and add like three things like you know oh you
can use like the emote i think that's interesting use emotes for a while you can unlock an emote
also um for a hundred thousand for for 500 million channel points uh like the old pepsi
commercials you get a jet remember that for for for 500 million germa channel points
and then the thing flies down and lands and it's like you could be an owner of a jet
didn't and somebody here's the funny thing somebody actually that was like a joke
that pepsi did and i think it was so out of reach that no one was ever going to be able to do it
somebody did it and they didn't know what to do because they didn't have a jet
right am i remembering this correctly yeah they got sued and they got a monetary prize instead yep
that's so funny some dude ended up with 10 000 pepsi uh 10 million pepsi points whatever
how would you get that many got sued over it but no i'll have something stupid maybe
maybe you can redeem like 10 000 channel points and i'll like turn my face cam on and like give
you a wink although that would probably get kind of annoying you would have to be high enough
where it would not ruin every stream so it would only happen like once in a while but anyways uh
thank you tingy for the 250 it sucks that i wasn't able to join the server but the stream was
enjoyable nonetheless hopefully in the future everything will be sorted tons of love to you
and the devs for putting so much work into this yeah once we actually get it off the ground
i at least want to do i want to do one or two of them at least with all the rules in place and
all the stuff in place last night is not an indicator of how those streams are going to go
so just you know be aware of that peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hey germa so glad
you were doing a minecraft stream it was a ton of fun the two times i got in but i can't wait till
we get twitch authorization in so we can have organized fun but this was still awesome happy
i got to play in the server with you in chat have a good night yeah because it was there was like
you said there was no white list it was anyone with minecraft could just join that server
we had two there's like three four servers yeah we just we got this kinks to work out and i knew
that was gonna happen should be fun once we get it truly off the ground though oh also important
over the next couple of days because we're getting to the end of the year here
there's going to be uh i feel like once every two or three weeks there's another channel that
gets opened up into the discord i have more channels in my discord than i think most people
do i just open up new channels every fucking week there will be a new channel in the discord
to discuss nominations for the end of the year for the new year's eve stream i want to get that
ball rolling because i want to be able to get the nomination videos ready and not scramble to get
them done in three days like last year so expect some nomination discussions i am going to put
a pinned message in there to make sure that people know the nominations and you can discuss
them and nominate stuff that stream feels like it was yesterday yeah that was almost one full year
ago 365 days ago do your best to ignore the pin the passage of time yeah but uh volemy gave five
thousand bits fifty dollars yesterday and want to make sure i talk about it because that's a lot of
money to give and have not been addressed they said chat now is the time to rise up viva la
revolution i may have even caught it but i don't think i did and i want to make sure i did
i was kind of locked in thank you volemy sad vega thanks for the 250 i can't believe what a violent
wretched king you became so quickly mad with power telling people to die simply for voicing
their opinions about bread and the king's age your kingdom starves and you cackle with glee
uh did i you know did i cackle all right this is not even this uh this is really this is really
fucking funny this one this is not at the the bit threshold but i'm going to read it because this
is actually really funny um it's just funny this is funny ultra levin said i managed to throw an
egg at you and land it three times the first time it almost crashed the server i got really worried
throwing an egg and going oh shit did i do that it did crash the server oh yeah because there
were chickens that were spawned everywhere right yeah it spawned five chickens and the server went
down that's right i'm surprised at what you guys would have could accomplish and like all right
let's be real here the amount of stuff that you guys did i didn't even know what's going on outside
the community i was we would we were like killing people and i was trying not to die and we were
walking around i was putting people in fighting pits and shit and then we walk around the
community there's like a whole this is like farms that were done there was a secret town
i was just running around like an idiot make a more static secondary server yeah i i'm trying
to toy with the idea that if this goes well for a couple times we just have fun for a few
like the event the event of permadeath and fighting and taking on each other and having
stuff happen and if you die you're out and come fuck the king right it might actually be kind
of fun just to have i can i'm not going to guarantee to have something like this permanently
right but like you still have a secondary server that's not as big that's just a for fun server
it may be like to have it up for like a few months and just have people go in and play and
do whatever they want and just put some interesting rules on it and then we could go in and you know
take a take a look at it every now and then but i don't i don't know last time i did that i had
a tf2 server for a while and it just i just couldn't manage it and i would have to like
bring on people to manage it and keep them around and they'd have to be the ones managing everything
they would have to be people that were like on call to run that server and i don't know if i
am ready to make that commitment right now because there's a bunch of other stuff that
i currently want to do and i wouldn't be able to keep up with it really at all
just make your mods do it no i would why would i do that hey all right now you guys now have to
manage a minecraft server thanks bye the mods are people man they got stuff going on they got
shit to do they live lives why would i want to tell them to do that volunteers um yeah anybody
that volunteers time to help run a community i'm not going to be like oh hey thanks oh by the way
you're doing this stuff do this now too but and for free as well do that for free
manage my entire minecraft community every day no i'm not going to do that
jerma they're saying there's volunteers for the minecraft server yeah i mean maybe some some of
you guys were into it and interested but we would have that to be a process to pick that you know
i wouldn't want just to be like it would have to maybe we'll go and get into that another time
let's keep going almost done with yesterday and then we'll go through the next day quick
because it's getting late 1500 bits from throwaway girl thank you thank you throwaway girl
appreciate they say hey you've been a big help to me as i'm about to begin my transition
i haven't told my family yet not all of them whenever i get nervous or anxious i always have
your streams to watch thanks so much for being a real funny dude good luck be the best person you
know how to be i've said that before and i'll say it again it's as simple as that thank you
so much for the 1500 bits i wish you luck take care damn i just woke up it's vaude time it is
vaude time how how many vods were there by the way that was the vaude muted are there 12 12
there's 11 vods no there's not are there really 11 vods what have i done why did i do that oh no
is it one okay this one you just scared the shit out of me i knew what was happening to
sound waves park thanks for the thousand bits germa i've been having an awful day and hearing
you acknowledge the garfield copy pasta which i started made it a lot better thank you boomer king
i hope your day got better i really do thanks for participating if you're a viewer or you were a
participator in the events last night thanks for watching thanks for being a part of it
and thank you garfield for being the worst comic book character that has ever existed
two scoops thanks for the 500 bits 510 hey germa had a lot of fun tonight even if it was a mess
all the way through sad i didn't get to fight john comcast i really wish you did actually you
did but i think that he he killed you instantly right oh yeah yeah you did fight didn't you die
you died instantly right john comcast hit somebody once and they died immediately because i think
they were two they were they were like three what happened i remember oh that was joan that
was jonah's bonus right yeah they were two years old they had three health yeah they died in one
hit that's so fucking funny and we were walking around and like enchanted diamond armor that's
yesterday was not an indicator of how that game is going to go stress testing data collection
things breaking things being fixed oh yeah yeah i like 40 hearts and i still died from a stone
sword how oh yeah i took all my clothes off and went swimming i forgot but thank you two scoops
they say honestly i was really just trying to become your queen instead why won't you love me
also have you thought about doing creative multiplayer builds similar to rt um probably not
minecraft to me is i i don't think i would want to just kind of play minecraft and build stuff in
minecraft i mean it could be fun if look if i'm gonna have a server that can hold more than 200
people at the same time maybe it'll be fun before i get rid of this server to just get a bunch of
people on and build a dirt dick like the biggest dirt dick that anyone's ever built in minecraft i
don't know because i mean i mean this the server the server is fairly expensive so i'd like to use
it we'll see thank you for the uh five dollars two scoops appreciate it thanks for participating
dark soul thanks for the 250 now a story i made a cube world joke during the jackass ps2 stream
i was a newer viewer of only a few months but realized later you had a cube world video
i do i have a cube world video no i don't what the fuck is this i have a cube world video
i've never played this before i don't remember any of this zero it's a grandpa video
i get it and what
well you have to put you have to put it on in the pot for two hours yeah but what's the temperature
it sits in the pot for two hours you have to cook it for two hours otherwise i get it what
temperature does it have to be so we're going to watch this video on stream i know everyone's
tired and wants to go to bed but we're watching this video on stream right now i have no idea what
this video is can you see it what's this doing no no fucking ads get out of here all right there
we go let's see well you have to put you have to put it on in the pot for two hours yeah but
what's the temperature it sits in the pot for two hours you have to cook it for two hours otherwise
i get it what temperature does it have to be set at it's a fucking fart roast you can't screw it
up get out i'm doing a video what's the i need to get out oh jeez hello ladies and gentlemen
it's grandpa here and today i've got a special fucking video for you because i got access to
cube world okay so this is germa's file we can go ahead and fucking delete that start a new file
for grandpa's character let's get going there create click it baby was that a guitar i don't
want to play the musician well it was as a musician we got ear musician we got drunk guy
we got gremlin from gremlins 2 is a pretty good movie but don't really want to play as a gremlin
we got the drunk goblin i don't like the drunk goblin to listen i like lizard people undead i
don't think i want to play fucking frog people we're playing as a fucking frog man i'm not even
going to go any further on the characters so what you do in minecraft is it's pretty simple
you go around or you collect resources and you fight months what the hell is it what the
fuck is this what is going on here what is this a ninja turtles what the fuck are the ninja turtles
doing in this game look it's leonardo let's turn it tell him behind him what are you doing this game
i don't i have no what am i supposed to even be doing does anybody know what you do in this game
i have not figured out all i've done is was it a b it's a fucking b come on still true
the real awesome part about this game is the fact that i'm battling right now as a frog there's
never been a game in existence where you could fight people as frogs it just never existed
and that's why i like it and that's the f5 experience points right there ladies and
gentlemen i just figured out how to play cube world i'm concerned about the people who made
this game because they're gonna get fucking sued first this is ninja turtles and then look
it's the seven dwarfs disney is gonna have a field day with these guys i look at a snuffy
that's gruffy that's poopy and snoopy see that's the seven dwarfs how are they not gonna get
sued by this there's funny i i really am concerned i'm gonna let me go get a closer look here
all right fluffy you need to go back to disney world because i said so what what
actually that was actually pretty surprising the seven dwarfs didn't have those fucking powers
oh would you look who it is everybody it's donatello by himself without his boys hey donnie
how are you how are the rest of the ninja turtles yeah without them you aren't so fucking tough now
are you got something to say i have my own house um donatello i think you might have a brain injury
somebody help me somebody please help me i got a bunch of animals following me
i got like two animal pug birds what what are they what are you doing this is the same thing
happened three times in a row i must have just run out of shit to do because there was what do
what do you even do in cube world i think i committed to make a cube world video and then
i was like fuck um i did you just run away from enemies okay doing what do you do leave him alone
what'd he do why why did they do that to him you bullies you savages you beasts no leave him
alone all he wanted was some bird seed i have it in my pocket what about this bird this bird's like
fuck dad i want nothing to do with this he has absolutely nothing to do with it well it looks
like all your friends are dead you're gonna hate he's like fuck that dude all right i guess i'll
what am i talking about what am i talking about oh yeah fuck that dude
okay i kind of feel bad about what just happened how did i end up in a tree what hello mr peacock
how are you how are you doing today yes i want to skip it's almost done um got some trouble here
that's oh my god kick his ass kick his fucking ass look at this animation look at this awesome
animation he's skiing at him look at this oh my goodness you are oh he died now i'm sad
i keep killing birds in this game i feel terrible i'm a bird killer but i still got it i keep killing
birds in this game i just i feel awful about it i feel absolutely fucking terrible about all this
it shouldn't be a thing we should have out yeah i still got it this video is like this video is
seven years old by the way to be fair here guys he did do that on his own i didn't ask him to
he just flipped the fuck out and started skiing at the guy and you know what that's what we shoot
the clouds i like this game some kind of encampment over here looks like there could be some food and
some supplies there is nothing special well there is some stuff here is this yours hey what if i
just re-uploaded this come on up here i want to talk to you every week camp every Saturday how did
you build this come on up here you want to make you make some food and stuff we could be friends
would even remember this video okay don't want to be friends you just dug your own grave because
i don't remember this video being uploaded i made this video and i just was telling that person i
never made a cube world video see you later get fucking rapid fired that's how you do it ladies
gentlemen you take his money and then you go back oh here it is this is old enough to have blue
pineapple is mine you had your chance to be friendly like the video just wanted to share
if you liked this video it tastes real good baby yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum what's it
the only good part about this video i think is this part here like the first like minute the
pot roast part is pretty funny look all right so give me a break guys let me tell you a little
bit of a youtuber secret okay well not even secret you all know this by now i put at the end of the
video it was only at the end of the video it was just like hey if you like the video then give me
a like right i didn't know i don't have a set it it was just in the very end you could even have
clicked off the video by the people used to do like hide content behind likes do you remember
that shit i will upload part five if this video gets 50 000 like dude shut up what are you talking
about you made 10 of these already they're already uploaded they're already ready to go you just have
to hit public on them guys i really don't know if you want to see more of my minecraft uh my my
gameplay here i don't know i wish this is episode three let me know in the car by the way i already
have 15 of these done and they're already uploaded i'm going to upload them regardless of what happens
in this video do people still do that they don't still do that do they they do i thought that if
not time would have gone by are people still giving away xboxes but now you go to ring a bell too
they give away iphones now i remember doing a giveaway before i remember i gave away like a mouse
i wonder if this person is still around in the community because i i got a mouse and i remember
given it was like a razor it was one of the razor mice it had nothing to do there was no like
sponsorship it was just like i had this mouse and i was like oh fuck i got i i think i didn't
want it or i didn't like it or something i think maybe i bought i had two of them i don't remember
what it did it was like 10 years ago but i i mailed somebody a mouse i wonder if that person's still
around i wonder what if the way that if they still have that mouse do you ever miss the old early
days yeah sometimes but it's i mean it's like a different mindset though sometimes you know i
miss like making these old the little youtube videos you know i like the ones from like 2012
i think it was it was a lot simpler back then in regards to like grandpa's gonna just
do a cube world video and if i'm gonna get like chased around by monsters for two minutes you
know what i mean it was just like yeah it was just like kind of simple but if we're talking like
2011 2012 i mean that that's just the kind of videos people were making it's videos i thought
were fun and interesting 20 like 14 15 16 is when i really started to try to make a bunch of shit
that i really wanted to put time and effort into and yeah i do miss the it's just it's never gonna
come back though that that's not gonna happen anymore like 2013 to like 2016 2017 really
is like i spent i mean i stream like this streams almost eight hours long right i streamed yesterday
for a few hours i mean that typically it would be longer than that but because we would test on the
server but it's not like i'm spending less time or more time sometimes i would spend
four three four five days straight on a video you know like i i'm live three or four times a week
with what i don't know what like i average for hours a week on stream like actually turned on
it's probably i mean if i my average stream is six and a half to seven hours six to seven hours
seven like 14 21 to like maybe maybe like 20 to 25 to 35 hours a week on stream like on broadcast
if i was going to make a youtube video on a game it would probably be like
30 hours in one session to do like one video so that makes like that makes sense do i have
an alternate path in case twitch doesn't work out well here's the thing about that question twitch
already has worked out a lot so it's not like oh i i have i have plans when i don't know whenever
this starts to people start to lose interest i i have like little contingency plans of what i want
to do but i don't i wouldn't look back and be like oh man this didn't work out i'm doing something
that i've wanted to do my whole life i've already i've already achieved my dreams
of just doing stuff like this so i would never look back and be like oh damn like let's say this
over the next few years let's say viewership drops or you know it's okay well that's
whatever you know i i i did everything i wanted to do in regards to like audience level and
engagement with people and but i don't even i don't even look at it like that seriously like
whatever happens tomorrow i have to see what happens tomorrow two or three weeks from now
we'll see i don't know i'm just riding the wave and just doing it for fun and just trying to stay
on the i'm just trying to stay on the surfboard and we'll see where the where the water goes i
have no idea you're the number one jump king streamer on twitch i don't think that's true i
think a lot of uh big streamers have played jump king i don't i think i'd be pretty far down on
that list so i don't know about that probably not even now right but it's always nice to reminisce
and i do forget some things what is this germa sandler oh can anybody i before i we have like
bits to do but what's that uh can i can i get to somebody leave you some fucked up clips from
tonight so i can know what i said
that's adam sam to speak okay how that one was weird any other like any other anything let me
ask let me just say this anything else i should know about i mean like anything else i should
know about goblin and chicken noises chicken and teeth goblin nails
when you got to come like i just get go grab a chicken in the woods and like go on all fours
yeah that's not that bad
that's all right actual meltdown no when you put actual meltdown in the title you know it's gonna
be bad to get this jump okay can i please just get this jump before i start to have a little bit
of a problem i'm gonna have a okay okay okay okay
okay
video games suck video games suck video games suck video games suck all video games none of them
will fun all of them suck all video games suck i've i've never played a video game ever again
uh we'll do one more jesus in my brain it's somebody behind me playing a piano
i'm wrong i'm just crusted to cloud there's a lot of these how many things that i do
no no ladies and gentlemen via satellite let's see how he's doing to discuss all politics
larry steven
okay all right i don't want to see you anymore i don't need to see you anymore
i don't need to see you anymore i don't need to see you anymore the toronto
okay all right i just need to make sure there was any i need to make sure that i needed to you know
be aware of them okay let's let's do the bits right how does that sound oh it's late finally
oh no dark soul 250 from dark soul thank you dark soul was this a cube world uh i was okay
you had a cube world video years ago a friend told me this guy's hilarious and proceeded to show me
only grandpa plays videos so it turns out i did see your content years prior and thought you were a
psycho who just pretended to be an old man in all your videos keep up the great work and keep the
peasant children off the grass like that's just what i did every video gnarly thanks in 250
i had fun playing for five minutes until you died in the lake for real though the best part of the
stream in my opinion was seeing what the community build i would love a community server that you
visit every month or so that's maybe we'll see maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe i don't know
maybe hold on to that idea sigmatic thanks for a thousand bits
i'm gonna say a line and i want you to determine which stream it was from it was from today or
from yesterday this was the worst stream since the surge which which day are they talking about
they're talking about today or yesterday uh with some tweaking of the guards and fixing
hardcore this will be sick as hell yes i know no stream is as bad as the surge was the surge is
it was the that was one of the worst just that that really was the worst stream i probably ever
did i don't remember it that's because it was so awful that you you just refused to acknowledge
it existed the surge wasn't funny even in like a pity way no i know it was horrible it was awful
it was evil within two is close to that was just awful just awful awful just i was in bad mood and
shit by like i hated the games it was just really was not good i remember the evil within two i
hated the game i was i hated that game and i was just like was it a bad i was in one of those
moods and ideas a bad mood well i remember it oh surge what is this how do you have this ready
this game doesn't suck i'm sorry for saying that if you're like a developer and you're watching
this game try fucking harder next time jesus christ oh my god that's like so bad i'm sorry
i'm like retroactively sorry i'm sorry that was i told you that was a bad stream that's the worst
stream i've ever done that was from the surge god damn it oh i got up okay let's um yeah but
thank you sigmatic for the thousand bits i appreciate do the surge too that title of that
stream would be the it's an obvious was meant as a joke i yeah i know but like i didn't know
uh that if i play the surge too the title of that stream will just be titled the second worst
stream i've ever done what if i love the surge too what if it's so good what if i love it like
love it it's possible all right let's fire through these what's with the spam
spamming derma's mad good job nicolas good job nicolas good luck in the first grade next week
damn it man that stream was scary all right but all right listen to me this is important
we're gonna go over this real quick does anyone know how many times i've broadcasted
like how many times has the stream turned on does anybody know it's been like hundreds and
hundreds of times like 700 sick 857 all right so in 850 broadcasts all right so i so i said the
surge sucked and i told a first grader that i didn't like him or something i mean that's that's
two instances of like almost 900 streams right like that's not bad that's not a bad ratio of
being like annoyed i bullied fortnight jimmy no i was i was bullied by fortnight jimmy don't get
that twisted all right let's do the bits bits bits bits bits bits bits bits uh yes is on the
fifty dollars from yes is online 5000 bits good job getting past chapter one thank you for the
50 dollars i think we caught it thank you that stream was i played if i fished right i'm just
this is all coming back to me i think i have a distinct memory of looking over at chat
and people are just just spamming please do something else everyone was spamming it and
i just didn't even listen to him i just kept fishing right i remember that i actually really
liked that stream that was like that was like a lot of fun for me that was nancy drew i i don't
i think there's a lot of nancy drew supporters in this community i mean i'm yeah nancy drew right
telling you all right let's keep going uh yes also gave 250 he'll get my name right one day
yves yves is online is that correct i think i got it we had a shitload of community subs today
some from atmosphere fish five adventure mf dan five fitty three a three drop fitty gave five
dolls as well right after that remember the just farming channel points and emotes ignore that
please that's right i ignored it but i didn't because you gave a lot of money thank you
thank you zake for the 250 um they have they linked an image of a guy screaming and crying
behind a smiling face i think this is supposed to be me today is that me i don't understand
what is that that's me hiding behind like a smile well i i i don't think so uh desoid j capcha
thanks for the thousand bits ten dolls are you finished with that book yet never finished it
never even really started it i got like 10 pages in or something and it was like now the same for
me i'm not smart enough to do this but thank you for the thousand bits just so i appreciate it
what do you use the name five community subs acidic vengeance five community subs
morcus borcus five desoid kajad for five community subs thank you all of you
davy davy gave some subs too thank you for those community subs davy that's the thing
that who watches you for the game the game doesn't matter if it's it's you that makes it worth it
you're hilarious and you make trash games funny that's why they're on nancy drew supporters
that's a really thank you that's a really nice thing to say
i yeah i just i hope you have fun regardless of what game is being played what we're doing
i hope that you take at least some form of entertainment away from it whatever that is
right uh bible thanks for the five subs non-descript civilian gave a bunch of subs
to his 10 here a lot of community subs tonight flood boy gave 250 germ i hope you're doing well
hope you get to make it into the next fuck the king stream was wondering are you aware of your
meme that has suddenly blown up it sounds similar to the defiant frenemy strider i know yes i've
been i've been made aware of the giant enemy spider and then that's a pog moment no way that's
he's the spider guy that's right
why did i just pretend to do that that was weird hey swiggity swanky thanks for the 250 bits
appreciate it this a uh ah malding memories oh my god please bomb listen jump king i was way more
i was aware jump king was like times 10 of just absolutely all over the place like
psycho it was like times 50 they was getting we were getting close to hit and run yep uh at
its very peak we're probably but we're probably seven out of hit and run i'm not sure i'll ever
get there ever again though you gotta remember guys hit and run was like 13 hours long at hour
number 12 if you're a 10 out of 10 10 out of simpsons simpsons out of simpsons it was like
hour number 13 i was i was out of control this stream was like i played for like seven hours
which is still a lot of for like a hard kind of focused crazy game like that yeah you were in such
pain towards the end i felt bad by proxy yeah i know i know that's the bad i will never get
there again i don't think it'd be hard to get there again adorable cockroach thanks for the
thousand bits channel points are forever thanks for the 10 bucks cockroach and i'll figure out
something fun to do with channel points i'll tweak some of the numbers uh pif flavor thanks
for the 500 bits derma sir you okay your mental health is slipping also pronounce my name right
or i will lose it it's pronounced pie flavor not pea flavor well i said it wrong both i didn't say
either one of those ways like you have said you see it's pie like the math number but maybe you
just don't know what that is do i it's hard to get it to like the 40th decimal but i mean i can do
it uh i did call you pea flavor i just called you pif flavor so it's pie flavor got it thanks
to the 500 bits appreciate basic feral thanks for the 900 bits 30 out of 30 germa snort what is the
oh the title of the stream is wicked fucked up isn't it what is this title right now time's upset
today 50 out of 40 with two in bracket stream turns off at 30 okay well that didn't happen
we had some type of system we were counting uh thank you basic feral for the nearly 10
dollars in bits appreciate that abomination zero thanks for 250 we love a good melt downstream
i i it was close it was i i this was like mario maker level of losing my mind right
yeah this is mario maker 2 yeah this is not simpson's hit and run there's more than that a
little more mario make was less than that more i mean okay maybe you did say you hated all video
games yeah but we say things when we're angry we don't mean you know we say things when we're
angry like i don't i didn't mean that i don't even know what that means it's called it's called
opening up all your windows and just venting out the toxic air surrounding your body
yelling out the window i'm not yelling out the window using my points for something
fun before you fuck them up balls balls balls that's pretty good pretty good use
but thank you abomination zero thank you uh ff12 pen elo for the 250 bits here
some coke brand coke gaming coke because you're epic no sorry it's because you're epic
here have some of this because you're epic uh lord reptile thanks for the 1500 bits 15
dollars in bits from lord reptile they just say love you germ germ thank you thanks for the 1500
bits i really hope that that never happens to me because if this stream ever gets like 100
community subs subs from coke gaming i'm just gonna like talk a bunch of shit and laugh at them
and stuff and like i'm not even think i don't think it's real that's not good right i hope
that never happens to me is that shit set up do we know anybody know is that shit just like set up
is that just like an ad was that an ad did i get added i think i might have been i think i got
baited by the ad is that is that really happening is coke gaming like giving community subs to
people like subway was i don't know you have to be partnered oh you have to get partnered
oh so it's like a coke gaming partners you on twitch sort of thing oh i see okay for i i don't
know why but i thought it was just coke gaming was going into random streams and just dropping
subs and stuff with like a message like this you can always tell when a brand doesn't give a shit
if they literally get your name wrong in what they're doing or if they just pick a random
video or a random stream that you've ever done dude germa we here at brand so so much loved
grandpa plays cube world we really think you'd be great in our brand hey germa rock on it's us here
from brand can we just say oh we are such big fans of the rats how many do you own anyways
we hear we think that rats are cool too don't i don't own any right you didn't you haven't
even seen the video no you don't you don't you don't get it you don't get it you i'm not if i
don't like i have i'm not like a fan of rats that's a reference to a video i made in a shitty
animation program you didn't see it though you think i actually have rats in my house
and that i have my pets i don't have any delete the email dude jeremy we love your worst stream
ever stream please sponsor us oh that is like the mixer thing hey jerma this is mad from mixer
we're reaching out to you and your rat pack we're big fans to offer you a deal
i oh look i have to say this because when will we ever evolve advertising and like pr
shit why does it have to be the same way that it's just been forever like that shit nobody
that doesn't work nobody gives a shit about that like that it doesn't do anything for anybody
we need to change the way that we advertise because the current system is just annoying
don't you want your brand to not be associated with i'm fucking irritating you sound like a
ted x talker they're literally all out of touch it's just gonna get worse do your own advertising
and get paid for it are the advertising needs to be i don't i just feel like random video ads just
don't do it anymore modern advertising is just dude relatable yeah but it's dude relatable with
like a 30 year old medium that they're trying to still do it's dude relatable but with tactics
that we've been doing since the 60s you can't be dude relatable when you're not at all and you're
using marketing strategies from 1965 what's something that i recently bought from an ad
um i don't know not nothing on the internet because it seems like all internet ads
are for like jokey food companies that i'm not going to eat you know what i mean most of the
online ads are weird shitty mobile games that nobody wants to play and 600 calorie per serving
like garbage can fucking food i don't i don't that doesn't appeal to me at all and cars
yeah and cars you should do a stream where we watch ads and then rate them well found the
fucking account found found the like the hidden advertising account here oh dude yeah it's so
fucked up you should watch a bunch of ads on money stream that would be like crazy right epic
yeah because you're epic but may i recommend some coke ads uh maybe if you think that would be cool
i they made a few good ones i think recently there are some very cool racing coke ads you
should check them out all right let's go let's go i i could sit here all day and talk about brands
and advertising even i don't i never ran ads on this stream ever unless it was like a joke
because like i don't what i don't care if i'm gonna something good if someone's gonna advertise to you
it's gonna be me you know what i mean i want you to hear it from my mouth i want you to hear it from
me anybody getting ad uh i don't think i get ad i i don't think my ads work on this channel
i don't think they do i've tried to run ads no they don't i don't i i have tried to run an ad
from my dashboard it's running right now it says 28 seconds remaining did they remove my ads can
i no longer send ads to anybody if i said this too many times it's saying this is 15 seconds
remaining all right okay 12 seconds why did i lose the ability to run ads on my channel
three two one complete okay welcome back um did anybody see an ad no no no okay so
hey twitch i just i just want to make sure that you have twitch like twitch listen to me um
if i run an ad this is good data for you if i run an advertisement and nobody sees it
what in the ever-living fuck is the reason for running ads what's the point of running ads if
like 75 percent of all people are not going to see them because they have like ad block
they're subbed what's why they what is this for it's more like 95 percent i i
the last few times that i've ran ads i have thought they have not worked because you guys
tell me you don't get them isn't this something else that we could do here why do we we're still
doing ads old school video ads that everyone's gonna skip anyways that anyone everyone is going
to just not see because they block them i don't get it i don't get it hey guys let's do another
one why are we talking about ads it's important stuff i want you to i want you to be aware of it
no i know there's it like this for like the for like the 10 percent of you that actually get
these i'm not going to put you through that again jerma is deprogramming his audience what
he's deprogramming his audience what are you talking about you're unplugging
i just don't see the point of running ads and twitch is like oh give us feedback on our ad
program here it is uh if there's 2,600 people here let's say there was there was 6,000 people
here six to what 7,000 people here at the peak of the stream if like 300 of them get ads
what's the point twitch there you go this is my feedback there you go feedback anyways oh
where are we okay somebody's name is funny it's jerma sandler 985 they subscribed thanks thanks
for the uh subscription jerma sandler 985 pretty good espada escalada thanks for the 250 uh not
gonna lie that imbecile achievement joke made it hard for me to not to breathe from laughing
i don't i don't i don't even know i don't even know what that is
oh no i do right talking about achievement stuff right i don't remember that is this it
that's pretty good i've done that once or twice before that's pretty good
mostly lost thanks to the 250 this streamer is sponsored and didn't announce it don't give
them any of your bits thanks jeff for the five community subs chunky baloney thanks to the 250
i just want to know if this is still your official stance on video games thanks to the 250 chunky
baloney i think i know what this clip may be already this is still what i think about video
games let's find out can i please just get this jump before i start to have a little bit of a
problem i'm gonna have a okay okay okay okay video games suck video games suck video games suck
video games suck all video games none of them are fun oh jeez i heard that like three times already
by the way you you motherfuckers every time a raid comes in every time a raid comes in
you there's a wall of the slap we can't get we people are gonna hate me we don't
don't don't do that anymore oh a new raid oh community we don't even know oh watch
spansman slap slap slap slap slap slap i'm just sitting there going like god damn it
do they want me to have any friends oh you want to fight you want to fuck fight don't fuck come
at me don't it's fucking ridiculous i can't even believe it sometimes don't fuck come at me don't
it's so loud too it's so loud and that's what that's the first thing people see
oh i'm just kidding i love it i love that clip as embarrassing as it is it's just so funny to me
every time somebody comes in that if you still hear from uh lidwigs community i believe it was
thanks for sticking around uh yeah we talk ads here and i stream for like nine hours what the
hell am i doing still live they're all gone i don't know all right one in the chat if you're
from uh lidwigs channel one of the chat i okay i know at least two of the people are lying
uh all right that's a lot of people i don't think i don't think that's that many people
all right i don't i can't i have no idea maybe some of them most of them are just subbed to you
yeah i know hey horace too thanks for the 300 bits i've been waiting days to pog i'm not sure
how long i can hold out good thing i got up to the snow otherwise we would have had some pog
problems there you go it was like three people well hey three people thanks for coming thanks
for staying maybe we'll see you tomorrow if not then maybe we'll see you another time enjoy your
stay on twitch it's a what it's a crazy website thanks for even coming in the first place uh
gnarly thanks for the 250 don't chase the money says the guy with a six percent tax on his viewers
income just take your filthy bits you greedy grinner ice cut digital thanks for 250 germa
you mentioned uncut gems after watching the trailer for it i went and checked out another
movie by the same studio called good time i and watched it the entire movie it was incredible
when i reopened the stream he was still in the same spot yeah i did get up though i did get up
there i got like 60 percent of the way through the game that's what everyone told me pretty cool
uh amnestic ow gave 50 i forgot about the 50 community subs that's a that's a lot
that's a huge amount of money thank you amnestic again for your crazy contribution watch good time
yes by the same yeah i'll check it out i'll check it out martin had a meme we're getting to the end
here martin had a meme thanks for the 2000 bits 20 dollars from martin had a meme jeremy you know
you can't jump on an empty stomach how about fixing that with the new crispy chicken pretzel
fries at burger king are those real they're crunchy pretzel on the outside tender white meat
chicken on the inside only available is that is this a real product because those sound absolutely
incredible don't lie to me here is that real i'm going to get them when was the last time an ad
worked um right now when a viewer pretended to be a burger king employee a fake advertisement
for a real product is making me want to buy the actual product so there you go there's the last
time it's right now i'm going to go get those as soon as possible thank you martin had a meme for
the uh 2000 bits and the great uh great tip there thank you mr dask for the 1500 bits
hey jeremy it was my birthday today i just want to thank you for giving me and everyone that's been
following you these moments to share even if jex clocks out for the night sometimes jerma jex
jerma moon b wl seriously though thanks for the incredible amount of hearty laughter and actual
even moments over the years wasn't even here's to an awesome and positive holiday season and new
year for everyone jerma heart ps can you say cheeky breeky l u l there you go um first of all
happy birthday happy birthday don't know how old you are hope it's a good one thanks for watching
thanks for sticking around have a great birthday it probably isn't your birthday anymore depends
on where you live if you live in the united states uh it's the next day but happy birthday
regardless thank you let's get the credits to roll uh there was a lot of community subs here
tonight so i feel like this is going to go very quickly and it is yeah that's a lot that's a lot
of stuff all today clap roll the credits that's someone zooming thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you do you have a pet rat you should get one i was thinking about it i also want a lizard
i wish i could just have a huge zoo you know i mean if i had the re if i had like the money the
resources and have like just a huge house i would want to have a bunch of animals to have like a
farm have like a bunch of lizards like a bunch of rats and ferrets and dogs and cats and shit
i think you know what that's probably my calling i'll tell you for real people saying what are
you gonna do after this what are you gonna do after this what would you do if twitch doesn't
work out anymore what have you done i'm just i'm just gonna go be a zoo i don't know i'll go work
for some pet store or go work for like a some a clinic or something like that i volunteered already
at an animal shelter and i loved it that's what i'll do that's what i'm gonna do probably what
will happen weird flex what what being a zoo to let someone else build it i forgot about the
gull of that that was so funny but thank you seriously everybody for something there's a
shitload of you thank you uh snoozing coffer thanks for the 250 hey first of all thanks for
looking at my f-tier sour tower in the ftk stream looking forward to next time it was really fun
so can i get an audience with the king from my founder privileges so next time you see me take
a look at my skin from all sides also can't wait for more jump king at the end when everyone starts
rooting for you it's great i do think you can make it to the top it's more up your alley than
getting over it in my opinion also apparently there's a surge too now you guys did get behind
me you did that's why i didn't stop i was like yeah talking a bunch of shit and it was a little
angry and i was like what the but then you then you guys got behind me and you were just like
cheering me on and i'm like i can't stop and then i had to pretend to be normal for a raid
so and then we had we just kept going that was a push that we needed and then you talked to
yourself immediately after very normal you pretend to be normal every raid do i he does
what do you mean what is that but what does that mean you go into tuber mode
you have a raid personality you act like you're in front of your parents
yeah but think about it okay listen this is important if a bunch of new people that have
never heard my voice before they come to the stream boom they put right in the middle of it
do you think this is the first thing that they're going to want to hear
hey okay okay okay
you know i don't know if that's the first thing you so i could be like hey
i'm just trying to like introduce myself video games suck video games i'm just trying to give
you a game suck video games suck i'm just trying to give them a like a like a very normal hey this
is what i'm doing introduction you're too formal i can't help it and we'll play the surge too soon
i want to just make sure that i hate it why am i why would i why would i do that we're going to
do it bro luck thanks for the 550 you said it was simpler making 2012 youtube videos i couldn't
think of something more simple than taking five hours to push a sleeping dog's character into an
ocean i did that though that's the thing that a lot of people i don't i'm not sure how many
people realize a lot of the stuff that's in some of these old videos like the 2012 13 14 15 kind
of era of me making youtube videos i did that i sat in a grenade room for like three or four
hours that was not a joke that was real i thought i wasn't just saying that in the video i couldn't
i was in there for a long time i did that stuff off stream and recorded it and edited it down
joel says he's gonna punish you joel don't joel don't do it joel don't do it don't do it joel
i'm telling you listen to somebody that just like walked out i just got out you're gonna all right
wait wait wait wait wait joel if you do it listen to me i want to hear you i need my
bias to be confirmed you're gonna get to the basketball hoop there's a jump that's a basketball
hoop that's all i need to tell you and when you do it and you see it and you do it and you're
gonna miss it a few times and you're gonna go what's this was dumbass basketball hoop oh no
that's what germa was talking about that's what he was saying and you're not gonna say it on stream
you're going to just internally be like oh fuck that fuck that i should have listened to germa
he's smart race race him right i'm not racing you jump no no you can't you can't race somebody
and jump king it's too hard it's too fast it's no i can't do it i'm not doing that i'm not doing
it i'm not doing it i don't want to get embarrassed and i don't want them i don't want joel to get
embarrassed i don't want to get embarrassed it's too no no no no no let's do let's do like a who
can click the mouse fastest i got that one because he was he's live right now did he just
turn him did he just turn his stream on he just turned his stream he's been streaming he's he's
on your stream right now get out of here okay this is get out of my bedroom get out of here mom i
why are you coming in here close the door i need to lock this door i'm playing my i'm joel if you
play jump king and hi everybody on joel's stream hope you're having a great night
um good to see you again first of all i want to say thank you for uh jumping on the stream
and checking me out for a little bit um how are you i hope you're doing good if you're gonna play
jump king let me just give you a quick little tip about jump king you're gonna get to a couple
of parts where you're gonna really really really be mad and all right okay okay okay okay all right
all right all right all right all right all right what's he saying i need to don't
hey did you do you have all your channel points activated do you have anything cool for it what
what hey what if you if you're gonna do something cool for your channel points what would it be so i
didn't fucking steal it if you got something something cool for your channel points would you
like i don't know like do something cool and i can maybe take it from you what are you doing
for your channel points uh he's not even he's not he's on a black screen anyway
back to the game back to the game you see you see
what it wasn't so funny what is even happening he i don't understand he he he doesn't know he
doesn't he doesn't know that that like i i made that game all right he he doesn't know you know
i mean um he's watching you now no he's not now he's listening oh yeah check it out check it out
so yeah so thanks for uh thanks for the subs appreciate that snusikopter thanks for the 250
um no that's an interesting that's a really cool conversation to have though about um just
advertising advertising is really strange and the way that we advertise to each other i think it's
a human thing you know we got to be more human way more human than we are than we already are
so we can move on from that really really good deep uh intelligent conversation that's happening
on my live stream that's what we do we have and that's why a ton of people if you're like
into that kind of thing you like we have a lot of interesting conversations on this stream um
yeah that's true we need yeah we oh what is what's going on somebody's somebody's here i don't
understand what would it mean um here's what we're gonna do i'm gonna i'm gonna take his offer and
say yes i'll play jumping with them i'll school a minute you know um that's right that's right
germ i know you're let's school a minute i'll say yes to it i'll say yes we have about uh on
my stream we do we have a uh once a month we do this thing we read a book on stream on my stream
we do um we read a book on stream and we go over it with each other we each person in chat does it
does one page uh and then we say it out loud kind of like you guys remember how much fun that was
when we would uh you'd go around the classroom and everyone would read like two paragraphs and
it was the dumbest fucking thing on earth and for some reason the teacher thought that that was a
good idea to have everybody not be able to do any reading comprehension and have like 25 to 30
people all read out loud in different voices for different characters i loved it when it got to my
part because i would just i was always hoping there would be a quote you know what i mean
because it was like oh and then that person said i would just put on voice on i'd be like
get out of here you you bastard and everyone would go whoa that was such a good what easy to do voices
and i'm like yeah i gotta bow and i gotta bow and then i get up and i teach the class
and the teacher sits down starts listening to me see germa has lost the germa germa's having a
crank ego maniac i see what happened to somebody said what happened to jump king i beat it it was
easy wait wait wait joe it was easy quiet quiet this is important i'm gonna show something on
play play jump king with me just watch i need you to look at something
play jump king with me listen listen i need you to watch
you know what i could just shut the stream off now and what do you think about this what
is what do you what do you think about what is the first thing you think about a little grumpy dumpy
germ the old the old germa germa is the first grumpy dumpy all right what is the first thing
a little grumpy dumpy germ the old what do you think
looser looser i see what i see right now uh there we go what i see right now
all right he didn't say what i see right now you guys are crazy this stream sucks all right
he didn't say which one mine or yours they're talking about you they're talking about you
my stream's over my stream is over i know yours i'm done you my stream ain't been on
for like an hour yeah your stream is fucking over when you come around you pigeon shit
you pigeon poop all over my stream and you give you give me these challenges
well i got the end of my stream be fucking more loud on stream all right okay that's it well
thank you thank thank you for it's like this i'm getting deja vu this just reminds me of
the taze on day hey little reach yeah when are you gonna play halo again dick is he listening
when are you gonna play halo again oh oh dick oh let me tell you something let me tell you something
we're not gonna go down that road let me tell you something let me tell you something we're not
gonna go down that road what's with your echo what's going on with your echo what's with your
echo you have me open on like five tabs what the fuck are you doing dude what's
going on relax what's with your echo you have me open on like five tabs what the
fuck are you doing dude what's going on relax what's with your echo you have me
open on like five tabs what the fuck are you doing dude all right see you tomorrow
good night guy good luck on jump king the game sucks wait is he still watching
Joel you still streaming me like yeah yeah but I don't know is he actually is
turn on the stream on the web and violence stream is he is he going like to bed or is he doing
something else all right well we'll go rate him after see you guys tomorrow we did have a couple
more bits come in during that nonsense there we had a wince ryan thanks for the springing of bits
sliding it at the end sorry don't be apologize for giving me money thank you despite all the
obstacles you guys faced I'm so happy you're able to stream FTK for a bit I was part of the
farmers guild and spent the entire time just planting wheat and corralling chickens while
hearing chaos in the background it was fantastic that's my favorite part that's my favorite part
is that people could just do whatever they want and not have to even be participating at all
in like the ridiculous nonsense brawler thanks for the 500 bits have you heard of dc dc
1032 v 150 watt boost adjust mod module mobile what is this it's a really interesting thing from
just thought they'll let you know what the hell is what is this laptop car from bang I don't want
to say the rest of that that's a website that's banging it I'm not gonna raise the rest of that
and that's it we'll see you tomorrow see you tomorrow we don't know what we're playing we're
either gonna play jump king again or we'll do Nancy Drew I don't know we'll figure it out
have a great rest of the night have a good sleep we went very late tonight I know
and uh go tell uh go tell Jill hello let's go ahead and queue that up right now why don't we
see you tomorrow take care guys