Thank you for your patience. I have returned and it looks like, wow, there is pretty unanimous.
The secret PlayStation 2 game is actually a, apparently it's a, I've never played it,
but it's a really, really, really great game from what I've been told. The secret PlayStation 2
video game that we're going to play right now for a little bit is Shadow of Rome, question marks.
I didn't even know what it was. We blew it. Shadow of Rome. It's a, a game.
Good job. All right, all right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Now that you, now that you've opened
the box, do you want to revote with Shadow of Rome? Because I didn't know what this was until
I went into the closet and looked at it. No, I'm playing it. I'm playing it. You guys picked the
mystery box. You, you can't up 70% of you opened up the fucking crate and sorry. Sorry. You didn't
get, you didn't get a knife this time or whatever it is people look for now. That was guitar, man.
That was very, very fun. A little like two plus hour, a little fun game. We're going to try Shadow
of Rome now. Apparently people are already talking shit, but I don't know if you should be. We're
going to play I'm Jammer Lambie regardless. We're going to play I'm Jammer Lambie regardless of if
that shows up now. We're also going to play both the Parappa games, but who knows this?
This could be a very, very, very big deal game. I feel like a lot of people might actually really
like this. I don't know. Uh, this is not the original Guitar-O-Man anymore. This is that
create a save file. Okay. We'll see if in the first, we'll give it 30 minutes. If in 30 minutes,
we can reliably say this, this game sucks. Okay. Then this game contains scenes of violence.
Okay. Um, what do I? Not Guitar-O-Man. This is a strategy game. This is a top-down RTS game.
This guy's still interested? It's not. Okay. I don't want people to take off because of this
setback. This game is going to be fucked up.
Continually defending her from hostile neighboring states.
As the power struggle ensued in the political arena, the quality of Roman life declined.
It was then that a great man appeared and changed the fate of Rome.
A most celebrated hero, Rome, Julius Caesar, super villain.
Disturbances were squelched and discontent alleviated under his competent dominion.
With the rule of Julius Caesar, all who inhabited Rome waited hopefully. I spelled Colosseum so
incorrectly years that it can't even, it's not, there's no auto-correct to help me. Colosseum,
Colosseum. But it was not to last. Despite her citizen's wishes,
Rome was once again sucked into the vortex of violence and destruction.
Yeah, it's Colosseum. Colosseum War. What a shitty title. Colosseum War. That's a great iPad,
like iPhone game. All right, I'm keeping it okay. Imagine you have to keep the analog in a thing
and it's a rhythm game. Did I get killed? Now, wait a minute. Spoilers, by the way,
if you don't know about, this is a huge spoiler. I just, I know you, if you're looking at this
history class, Caesar gets stabbed. It's a huge part of like the last season. He's, that's the
line, yeah. I'm sorry if you've, I just spoiled like history 101 for you. Now you're gonna be
pissed because now you know how it ends. We got four options. Violence. Violence on. What do you
mean? Violence off. Player cannot cut enemies into pieces. Green blood? Why green blood?
Like I don't want to keep green blood on. They're all like aliens. Okay, I want to keep that up.
Uh, subtitles on the screen. That's fine. I thought about it, but this is like 2001 hard.
It's different. It's not like 2020 hard. This game is insanely hard. What was I thinking?
Do I get to choose my weapon? Which one of these guys is me? Opening, opening, opening.
What's this really long intro? What's my, what's this guy's name?
Kratos? Something like that, right? You're on. I'll explain today's event. First mess. Three
potentially lethal rooms await you. The first room is set up battle royale style. You must defeat
all your opponents to proceed to the next room. There are a few weapons. Fight it out for them.
In the second room is a guard. He's carrying a weapon, so don't let your guard down.
In the last room, you'll just have to find out what awaits you there.
Okay, so you move with left analog, move camera right analog. Press R3 to center the camera. Good
to know. Press circle button when the talk icon is displayed. You can also listen to the conversations
of others this way. So circles talk and listen. Did I just, was there a down three rooms? Hey,
this won't be easy. What a salvo list. Memo. Defeat the enemies. All right, well, let's just go.
Go to the first room. How do I leave? Can I leave? Did you catch all that? No, explain it again.
Yep, three rooms. Yes, yes. I wanted to see if I could go down. I understand. Let's let me out.
Talk to the masked man by the gate. Can you buy stuff? New recruits enter the arena unarmed.
Pick up weapons to defend yourself. If you want to enter with weapons, prove your worth by
finishing by winning a few times, okay? Are you ready to enter the arena? Yes. Give the audience
a match to remember. Please upgrade the resolution. I can't do that. That doesn't exist. This is,
you're, this is 20 years ago. Press the circle button near the desired weapon to pick it up.
Okay, why is that guy so huge? Hold R1 to lock onto an enemy and main attack is X,
sub attack is circle, is square. Get the big guy first. He's got green blood. He's a fucking
science experiment. No, work together. Your weapon will break once its durability reaches zero.
Be sure to watch your durability gauge to make sure you aren't left fighting without a weapon.
Okay, where's the durability gauge? Oh, there it is. Ow. Is there a dodge? Is there like a dodge roll?
Shoulder ram. When unarmed, press the X button while stepping forward to ram the enemy. If you're
lucky, he may just lose his grip on his weapon. Shoulder ram. Okay, that's a shoulder ram.
No, give me that weapon. Get the, why would you bounce off of somebody? Step on his head. Threat
from above. What? What do you mean threat from above? Yeah, I want the weapon. Give me the guy
with the weapon. Give me the, give me the weapon. Oh, that guy has it. Steal the enemy's weapon.
Sometimes you will end up grabbing hold of the enemy's weapon after you shoulder ram.
At that time, repeatedly press X or square to pry the weapon from their hands.
I'll get it every time. All right, that guy's dead. Okay, got him. Now, is there any of the weapons?
Oh, domino effect. Is this thing already broken? Okay, get attention from the audience.
Appeal to the spectators by pressing square and X buttons at the same time. Time it right,
and you may just get your hands on a weapon that won't please the audiences with your performance
the better your chance of having to throw out a powerful weapon. Give me something. Holy shit,
that's big. Anything else? I'll take the grand halberd. What did I do? He's using his arm.
That's a guy's arm. Holy shit. Give me another weapon. Cheese. While holding meat, cheese, bread,
et cetera, press the square button to eat and restore some health. Tap square to eat faster.
Looks like fucking Minecraft. All right, let's go. Who's left? All right, next room. How long do I
get to keep the halberd for? Now, this, this, this is a garden here, right? It's not a land mine,
is it? Hold L1 to guard. No, give me, are you serious? No, I'm gonna cut this guy in half.
End him. Yeah, we're just gonna throw a bow. Give me a bow. Oh, fuck, there's people here.
How do you fire the bow? Um, what else dropped? Can I pick this guy up and like throw him? I need
a dodge roll. Bad. I got a ram. All right, come here. No, no, no, no, no. What's dodge? What's
dodge roll? I know it exists. Kill him. Stab him. What? You have a knife in your hand. Stab him.
Fuck. Can you throw? Give me something. What'd he break? Oh shit. I have no weapon. No. This guy
back here. He's like having trouble. What do I do? Give me that. No, this guy over. Are you serious?
I'm gonna get fucking embarrassed by this tired guy with the shield. Really?
Don't even think about it. No, no, no, no. Pick up that. I need that shield. Oh, give me a fucking
break. How did that not hit you? Pick it up. Oh my god. Kill him. What's wrong with my head?
Kill him. Why? Kill him. He's dead. Geez. Give me the new mace. Crawl through a hole?
Where's the last door? What happens if I lose here? It's more than one of the common criminals. Cowards
who haven't resolved to fight. I hereby order the execution of these dogs. Let the crowds be
pleased by their grisly demise. Hold the X button down for a short while and you'll perform a powerful
attack. There's no cheese. No, I don't want to kill these guys. Where's my choice? He's dodged.
And actually, where are you guys getting these from? How do you throw that from there? How do
you- this thing has to be like 200 pounds. Oh, you have another mall.
All right, give me something faster than this. I- they- hold on.
Give me this thing. You're in trouble? Hold on. I cut that guy's head off and he peed out of his head?
Uh oh. Cheese. Give me it. I want more cheese. Watch out. Okay. Just little hits. Small ones.
Oh, fuck. Stab him. Stab him through the face. Stab him. Really? Stab him. It wouldn't break.
Anybody got another one of those? Uh oh. Get him down. Shit. Oh, fuck. He almost- why does
this keep breaking? Everybody loves me. The crowd loves me. Wait, don't I have to like execute that
doesn't- doesn't see- oh. Yeah. I was gonna say doesn't Caesar put his hand up or hand- thumbs
down, thumbs up? Not like this. It's Chris Redfield? No. It's- I don't know. Chapter one,
the wickedness of men. Marvelous madness has invaded not only the wicked but even those who
are held to be good. Change blood. Red blood. Why would I do that? We want violence. You're getting
violence. I thought this was a Colosseum game. This better not be a sneak around game. Don't do
the few days earlier thing and have me sneak around. And here as well. Centurion Agrippa.
There is no doubt of it. It is certain that it belonged to a Roman messenger, sir.
Guitar Man was fun, wasn't it? They have been captured. It has not been long since they left.
We shall separate and look for them. Do I play as the wolf? Rome has embarked on a campaign to the
Germanic territories in the north, endeavoring to fully secure its realm. During the battle,
a group of Roman messengers disappeared suddenly while in enemy territory. In order to prevent
the spread of confidential information, reconnaissance troops have been dispatched
to the forest of Germania. Wait, this is- press select button to bring up the map screen.
Player. Enemy. Ally. Target. Item. Weapon. Okay, well, I'm- no, there's no friendly fire.
I've been to many land and weathered my share of harsh climbs, but I must say that this place
may well be the worst. All right, well, I'm gonna go over here in this tent because there's a weapon
in here. I don't know what was in there, but it's not there anymore. He's having a tantrum. Okay,
well, what's this item then? Change blood. Change blood. I'm not gonna change the blood.
No, this is a PG-13 stream. Something in there. All right, let's just- I just gotta go this way.
No, I don't want to get in- I don't want to get in trouble. If my mom comes in in this red blood,
she's gonna be very concerned, and I'm gonna have to explain. Please call me if you need anything.
What is it? Tell the men it's time to mobilize. Should I have done that? That is enough. Let us
move forth. All right, here we go. All right, what happens if I turn into red and then turn
into green after one hit? Supra attack. Press the X button while holding R1 and pressing the
left analog stick forward. Press X while holding R1 and pressing the left analog backwards.
My mom's gonna fucking kill me. How did I do that dodge roll? Supra! Give me that kick. Does
kick get rid of the shield? That guy's gonna get destroyed.
That guy went pretty high. Red blood is uninspired. It's the enemy's fort. They must be close.
I want to go back to the arena. Thank you.
I was gonna say, that would have been terrible. We must hurry. The cremation of the assassinated
Julius Caesar took place in the Foro Romano as the raging flames reduced Rome's former ruler
to ashes. All who looked on were struck by the poignancy of his own too early demise.
Sugar, spice, and everything. And here comes Cicero, champion of the Senate.
We, the members of the Senate, have found the man responsible for the grotesque
betrayal of Julius Caesar. It is the traitor of Rome, Lipsonius. Lipsonius?
That is Zagreba's father. It cannot be. It is not true. Did not kill Caesar. I would never do such
a thing. Kill him. Kill him. I shall now announce the successor to the hero Julius Caesar,
the man who shall ascend as the just ruler of the nation. It's going to be me.
This does the Maggie. Oh, is that him? People of Rome, as Caesar has expressed in his will,
Tonius shall step up as his rightful successor. How much money does that,
how much money does that skin cost? 600 gems? To dedicate my life to the glory of Rome.
I just, I don't get the cape. It's bullshit. It's not fair. I cannot believe that Lipsonius
would do such a thing. That really divided chat. Constant fucking conflict. I didn't,
somebody read it. I didn't. Vipsanius, a murderer. There's got to be more to this story.
Rome will never know a hero like Caesar. What's that? You're concerned about that wretched criminal.
Are you a friend of that traitor? Here comes the lore. Caesar may have charmed with his elegance,
but no one can ignore Antonius's youthful grace. Antonius is the most capable of Caesar's advisors.
Surely no one will find. All right, well, what do we do? He loves Caesar. He held him in the highest
regard. Could he have faked his admiration and loyalty? The Senate house is but a stone
throw away. It's only a moment's journey by foot. That said, I fear the real challenge will be
found in gaining entry. The Senate house. Yes, leave. This game is not what I thought it was
going to be. This actually is like a strategy game. I don't know who the fuck I am. Man,
this is bullshit. I get to play the first 22 minutes as Snake and now I get to be
riding for the rest of the game. Don't do this shit. Apparently Caesar hated having security
guards think it would end like this. It's been successful. I mean, pretty cool. Interesting
lore here, but I mean, I got to get in the Senate house. Yes. Hi. Here we go. What?
That's a quick way to die. This is not a child's playground.
He's got a Rolex? What is on his arm? He's got like a fucking nice watch.
Octavianus.
Senate meeting. Go home now. Please watch Rome on HBO. It's very good.
All right. Add. What do you mean add? I just read that. I would have gripped his father,
slay Caesar. I must speak to the Senate. This must be a misunderstanding. What troubles you,
young man? Give me like a spear. It's all we want. Who are you? Have you forgotten old Pansa,
good Octavianus? People still name like Octavianus and like Asperinius or whatever.
No. How did we get from there to like Dan? Oh, Octavianus. Steve. Hold L2. Oh, it is. What is
this? L2 is sneak. Oh, fuck sneaking. I missed the stab. Holy shit. He just did the back stab to me.
He got behind me. Oh, listen to that. Right there. Got it. Give me that. Can't fall off. There's no
joke there. Sorry, guys. Steve is short for Stevius. No, it is not. We've got a long way to go.
I think we just started taking off the Eus off of our names. Like, you know, like Jeremiah Eus.
Then it went to Jeremiah and then it went to Jeremy. That is true. You can throw in this game
one full letter grid. Press triangle while holding weapon to throw it straight ahead.
Did I get him? I don't even see what happened. Did I? What? I hit him. Cut this tree down.
You actually do cut the tree down. That's pretty cool, actually. That doesn't go. He just,
guys, there's a guy here, you know. Nice work.
Give me, I want that. I want his torch. What just happened? He just spit in our face.
There we go. Give me the torch. Get sand. All right, we're reaching about the 30 minute mark.
It's almost there. Ow. It's fun. It's fun. But it's just not, I don't think it's 2019 fun.
Like back like 20 years ago, this is probably the best game that ever came out like for the year.
What's my favorite game of all time? That's too, that's too much of a loaded question.
I looked at chat, I looked over here and I thought there was an arrow in my head.
How is it loaded? Because this is that I can't answer it. First person view. Look at this. It's
got first person mode. Press R to FPV mode. FPV. Just look at how old this is. They couldn't even,
FPS. First person FPV. You can zoom in and zoom out. All right, so throw. Uh, can you see me?
Is he shooting arrows? I don't think so. Well, what was that? Throw it back. Quick,
do something funny. I don't, I'm just kind of, I'm trying to throw a rock at this guy.
Was that like funny? The rocks are all broken now. Just get out of the, why are you standing in the
way? These guys, these NPCs don't do anything but just get in the way. No, this way. There you go.
Fuck off. All right, now burn him. I can't, I can't even see. The sequel to this game became
Dead Rising halfway through development. Are you serious? That's kind of awesome. That's ridiculous.
Yeah, the way you throw shit too is to just play Dead Rising. Because this game did so poorly,
they changed the game mid-development. Are you kidding me? No way. Okay, I, maybe I will play
Dead Rising. I've, I played Dead Rising like three. Um, there's like 15 people here. I was
supposed to sneak, I think. Just go in the door. The door is locked. Well, that's fucking horrible.
I'm dead. Didn't I have two friends? Are they dead? This is it. Don't lock on. Just hit.
Oh fuck, he's going around me. Give me that. Give me, give me, give me, give me. Don't die.
All right, I was trying to, wait, can, somebody gonna throw me cheese? From where? All the way
back? Like in three years? Hold on, so someone's in three years in the future is gonna throw me
cheese from behind the rock. Die. Die. Die before I play Unjammer Lammy. Secret PlayStation 2 game
that I forgot I had. It's pretty good. It's, it's pretty good. Nice Resident Evil death screen.
Time to bring in Lammy. I think it's time to bring in Lammy. I think so. And well, here's the,
hold on a minute here. This is important. Oh, this, this like sucked. No, no, no, because this
confirmed that I was going to play Dead Rising 1. If I didn't do this, we would not have come to
the conclusion that I was going to play Dead Rising 1 on stream. You understand? Like how things,
there's like cause and effect. It was worth doing this. Imagine, yeah, imagine the timeline
that would have, I wouldn't have, never would have probably played Dead Rising 1 on stream.
It was worth doing. Absolutely. Now let's play Unjammer Lammy. Pretty good secret stream.
I don't even know, where is Unjammer Lammy? Oh, fuck, that's right. It's not here yet. It's
being delivered like tomorrow. Just kidding. Relax. See, hold on. So the, are you telling me
the PlayStation 2 can do this? Are you sure? I have like the PlayStation 2 baby. I don't
have like the big one. Can the little baby PlayStation 2 do it?