Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary like you know it, ladies and gentlemen.
But tonight, I'm not going to talk about the gameplay really at all. I've got something very, very important.
Something I really want to talk about. And I'll give you a brief little synopsis of what happens in the gameplays.
First, it's going to be a soldier on, I believe, Gold Rush on Gold Rush. Then it's going to be a spy on Lakeside and then a pyro on Lakeside.
I do pretty well as the soldier, and the spy gameplay and the pyro is okay. I mean, it's not spectacular or anything, but I do alright. I get the job done, let's say that.
But what is this video about? What do I want to talk about? And before I get into this, I do apologize. My voice is kind of a little bit raspy today.
I'm coming down with, I think, a head cold, so please bear with me. I apologize if it's annoying or anything.
But what I want to talk about today is death. And not so much death in regards of a human being, but death, let me just try and rewind for a second.
My dog just died. My dog that I had of 17 years just passed away. And now that might not seem like a big deal to many people, but to me, it is a huge deal.
And I'll try to explain why and I'll try to get some of your guys' opinions on these things, but that is going to be the topic of this video, topic of discussion, I guess.
And let me start from the beginning. So when I was 11 years old, I got a birthday present for my 11th birthday, obviously, and it was a dachshund.
It was a mini dachshund, and we named him Simon. He was a really lovable dog. He was one of the most lovable, caring dogs I've ever come across.
I mean, I've come across a lot of dogs, and he was definitely up in the top five of incredibly friendly, just awesome dogs.
And it's very saddening because obviously you fast forward a little bit, and it's been 17 years. I know he was old. He was really old.
And a lot of you guys know this, but some of you don't. I mean, I'm 26 years old, and that dog has been in my life since I've been able to really form memories.
I mean, you really think about it. When you get to be about 9 or 10 years old is when you start to store information into your brain.
So I've had this dog in my life for almost two decades, ever since I was able to formulate theories and ideas and memories and thoughts, and now he's gone.
And all the memories I've formed of him, all the things that I knew, all the times I've seen him, he's gone forever.
And it's very strange to think about that, guys, because it doesn't really hit you until it really happens.
And I mean, we've talked about Ami, my mother, my father, my brother, my sister. We've all been talking about this.
He's been kind of on the lower end of health issues recently. He had Cushing's disease. He had diabetes, I think.
He had a bunch of diseases, and we all knew it was going to happen. We all knew he was going to die.
One day we were going to wake up, and he was going to be gone, and it happened.
It's just really crazy to think about that, because no matter how much you prepare yourself for something, you don't really look into the future.
You kind of keep yourself into the present. You say, oh, he's going to pass one of these days. It's going to be sad.
But then you don't think about the future. You don't say, well, I'm never going to see him ever again, for real.
You can say that as much as you want when it's about to happen or when it's coming soon, but once it really does happen, shit, man.
I've gone upstairs to go see this dog, and he's just not there.
And I really want to get your guys' opinions on this, and I want to get you guys involved, because whenever I tell these little personal stories,
I like to hear your guys' input. I like to hear your stories, your experiences.
So if you've had a pet that's been put down or has been passed away for a while, or even if it's a family member,
somebody actually a living human being that has died, then definitely let us know about it if you're comfortable,
because it really is interesting to see the different viewpoints and the different experiences.
It's something I like to see, even if I cannot respond to all these comments or all the PMs I get.
I read them all. I read every single comment, guys, all of them.
So again, if you are comfortable doing this, then definitely leave a comment, because the comment really is not just for me.
It's for everybody that's coming to watch this video. Everybody can really relate to each other.
It's crazy how much we really all can actually relate to each other.
You'd be surprised, but I just wanted to share this story of my dog passing.
And for one little follow-up thing, just before the video is over, I think I only have like maybe two minutes left,
but this is sort of a transition period for me, guys, because that was the last thing that was around as part of my childhood.
I mean, that dog was really the last thing that I had when I was younger.
So now my brother's married, my sister's married, everyone's all moved out of the house and everything.
So now it's almost like I have to grow up. There's nothing holding me back now.
I don't have something from when I was a kid to fall back on.
And I mean, I've done a lot of growing up in the recent years.
It's getting to that point where you're almost 30 and life has to kind of be on lockdown.
You have to really have yourself in check.
It's almost like your life is a giant jigsaw puzzle, right?
And you have almost all the pieces plugged in, except you're missing one piece and you can't find it anywhere.
And then once you find that one piece, and in this case happens to be my childhood dog,
and when that piece is finally in the puzzle, you have no excuses anymore.
You have nothing holding you back. You are starting your life for real.
And that's beginning to happen to me.
And it's very, very scary, but at the same time, it's very accepting because you're becoming an actual real adult.
I would say that when you're in your 20s, this is that transition period.
If some of you guys are in your early 20s, you'll know what I'm talking about.
You guys that are in your 20, 21, 22, you're starting to get there already where you're like,
Okay, what am I doing? What's happening in my life right now?
And you'll start to see these little key chains from your childhood just start to get removed.
And when they're all gone, just like the puzzle I was talking about, when it's all put into place, time to go.
Time to be an adult.
So this is going to be the end of the video here, guys.
Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
I'm glad I could express this and get this off my chest a little bit because it has been bothering me quite a bit the last few days.
So I will see you guys all soon. Take care, everybody.