Does anybody think I lost my mind? I don't know, there's a lot of question, but I'll
explain. So, is it weird that I've made a coffee, like I've got a coffee, and I drank
half of it. And I said, damn it, I really wish I had more coffee. So I have a water
here. And I said, you know, I could just turn that water into coffee. Like Jesus. I could,
I just poured it in to the coffee that's here, and just made another coffee. It's just a
coffee here now. So when I get to 50% again, I'm gonna add more and fill it up again. It's
gonna be it's gonna be infinite coffee. Let me see how it tastes. Pretty good. That's
the third time I've done it. So you can drink. Like I love coffee. But I could just make
a coffee and just dilute the fuck out of it. Over and over again. And it's like I drank
eight coffees, but I only drank one. This is actually a really good idea. And then it
would just become Dunkin Donuts. That's all the time I got here, folks. I'll see you next
week. We're gonna keep going with Dead Rising 2. If you didn't know. Off the record, I'm
having a lot of fun with it. We are at just about the halfway point. So gonna see what
happens gonna see if we can do it all in one stream. We'll see. I think we can do it. Hey
failing kidneys. Thanks for the five community subs. Appreciate that. So we'll we'll take
a little assessment of where we are at like the six to seven hour period. Right? Maybe
I'll just power through it. I've eaten. I came prepared. I ate a full salad with this
delicious Gorgonzola Gorgonzola dressing. Oh boy was it tasty. Oh, he ate a salad. Do
I want an award? No, I'm just saying like I ate a shitload of greens. So I'm gonna be
full for a while. I ate 1900 calories worth of grains. I'm done till tomorrow, right?
The you mad diet. I'm actually I'm liking the you mad diet. I get to eat once and eat
like 1900 calories worth of kale. You're just eating grass. Not true. All right, let's get
Let's move over to the game. It's not called you mad. Yes, it is. It's it. Yes, it's oh,
yes, it's oh mad. But I changed my opinion. You mad chats mad. All right, let's go. It's
just paused. Time doesn't go when it's paused, right? Shouldn't. All right. Oh, let's refresh
some memories here. It does not. This is what I look like. This is what I sound like. Cool.
All right. So we have four to run for the money. I have one Zombricks slave to fashion.
This is right here. So let's get it done. Locate the woman in distress at the Fortune
City Hotel. We get time for how many how many cases are in four to just so we don't mess
it all up. Okay, for two, I got a long time to do for two. Once we do case five, though,
I got to get on that because I don't want to burn time. Let's move. It's saved. I got
my drink. I don't know why I have it. Can I give this to him? No, not going to get time
management today. Not going to be like last night. I meditated right before this stream started.
So I'm going to be way better than I was yesterday. Why am I seeing a million cappers?
Is that a meditation joke? Well, those men. Okay. He ate greens. Andy Frank is lying on
the test. How many? This is a lot of shit going on here. How many cases are here?
How many? Look at all these scoops. There's too many. This is this is right in my level
range. It's yellow. You know, I feel like these are going to turn blue and I don't really want
to do them. Come on. Come on. I'm waiting for it. Give it to me. Nothing. I'm surprised.
Holy shit. Some of you Wow. I was waiting for like a wave of hatred. Not really that much.
And true. That's really interesting. Actually, I got to write that one down.
Like that reaction. That was a World of Warcraft reference. And that's always a guaranteed like
German shut the fuck up minus two. That's interesting. Bargaining. Yeah, I know what
magazines do. I should have picked this up beforehand. Hey, hey, hey, get away. I'm looking
at stuff. Just leave this thing here. I don't need it right now. Just put it down. No, no,
don't put the break down. All right. My meditation like fuck me all up. I'm like still
meditating right now. No. That's why meditation doesn't work when you play Dead Rising. I've got
to be like lit up like a Christmas tree. You know what I mean? I can't be slow and calm. I have to
be like freaking out. Wait, can you not break an ATM with a rake? Local man tries to break ATM with
a rake. Why can I not get into these? Can you? I don't know. Probably. I got lots of money. I
want that car though. I expect that's the longest I've ever gone without getting bit.
All right. Slave to fashion. What do I have for weapons? They're terrible. I have a shitty rake.
Just get rid of it. I need gems. Wait, gems, gems, gems, gems. Where's the jewelry store?
Where's our jewelry store? Charms. Here we go. Right across the way. To the right straight.
Off of me. Where is it? Charms. Right here. All right. So now I'm going to combine this with the
head. Should I? I'm going to grab like two or three of these. These are like, I feel like these are
like a great ingredient. Just like stock. Can I do gems and like most shit? What is this hat? I don't
know. It was available so I picked it up. Okay. So gems and the alien head. Maintenance room is right
across the way, right? Yeah. There's one right there. It's me. Can you start streaming? What the hell are
you talking about? All right. Gems and then alien head. The face cam. Let's see. The laser eyes?
What the fuck? Okay. I don't want to use this. Is it? I got to make sure I have that on during
cut scenes because that's like really funny. All right. Machete and power drill. Power drill and
gems. Gems and machete. Power drill and gems. Gems and flashlight. Right, right. All right. I'm
going to get a flashlight. I want like two lightsabers. Where can I get a flashlight?
Use the broom? Yeah. I want to hold on. It's going to be such a pain in the ass to keep these gems
though. All right. Give me that broom. There you go. The drill sucks, but it's a panic weapon.
All right. I think I'm all right. I got some decent stuff. Drill in the bucket. Yeah. Isn't that a
one-time use though? Let's try it. Blossom PP. Oh, that's good to know. All right. There we go.
Drill in bucket. I'm just gonna... I'll just use it on this guy. Can I pick it up again?
Oh, holy shit. That's actually a lot of PP. You're right. All right. This is just a PP farming.
Put it on a boss? Does that actually work on a boss? No. Wow. Oh, well. Well, then we'll just
use it on random people. Let's just use it on like, I don't know, this guy. This person over here.
What are you doing? What are you doing? All right. Give it to me. Let's go. Okay. Slay to fashion. I
gotta do this now. That is a lot of fucking points. Is this part of your time management skill?
Uh, yes. All right. Slay to fashion. Let's go. Do the wilted flower? I should... I think I'll have
time. How far away are they from each other? I got time to do it. I'm gonna do this one first.
I'm gonna save it right in the middle just in case there's a nightmare scenario where I can't.
Why do I hear machine guns? Who has a machine gun here? Is this pre-recorded stream Tuesday? Yes.
Welcome everybody to pre-recorded Tuesday where, you know, every stream I stay up after last night's
stream for seven hours and I stream to myself for until eight o'clock this morning and then I render
it and upload it to Twitch and let it play as a rerun. That's what I do. I'm gonna keep this one
here because this is a, this is the complete total rewind save zone. Quick accuse him. All right,
that's saved. Now this thing lasts a really long fucking time. I can't believe I can still use it.
This is not good time management. I know. I know. All right, one more time.
I can do it again. Okay, it's done. It's done. It's done. Okay, we're gonna keep it because I
don't want to stand still and get hurt. Who's firing a machine gun? These guys are in the game
now? Why is the viscera cleanup detail guy going fucking crazy? Now I need healing. I need health.
There's some stuff over here. Can't rewound too many times. What do you mean they rewound too many
times? French fries. Nice. All right, I'm good. Wait, coffee creamer is a, take coffee creamer
and get rid of the french fries for the other coffee creamer. No, the french fries. That's,
okay, I'm good. Somebody's yelling to me. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm
coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. Eat shit. This is unbelievable. I'm not going to use
that. Holy fuck. This thing's incredible. What? Hello? Are you, you all right? Oh my god. Don't
look at me. Sorry. I'm trying to help. Oh my god. This is totally embarrassing. This is like a total
tragedy. Okay. I'll have to turn around and talk to you. What happened? Like I was in my hotel room.
I went to get some ice and then stupid door locked behind me. I came down and this place was totally,
a zombie outbreak started, but come with me. I can get you to safety. Are you drunk? I can't go out
here like this. Give her your onesie. A hunky prize fighter, a hot movie star come down here.
What? Maybe if I wasn't the only one doing it, I'll tell you. I'll go if you're just wearing
your underwear. What? How do I take off my clothes? A men's store at the other side of the mall.
Oh god. There's a men's store by the statue at the other end of the mall. Oh, you got to be shitting
me. Can I make it back here? Time management. Let's go. Almost there. He's so fast. I know.
Okay. It's right over here. There's the statue. Okay. I'm in. Underwear. Look for men's underwear.
Let's go. All right. Where's my wheelchair? What is it? Too hot? What? I don't understand.
And she's going to get in the wheelchair and we should be good to go.
No, I don't want you in this thing. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. No. Stop. Don't forget to
take a picture. How do you do a selfie? I can't seem to get it to work. There's a magazine right
there. You need to be unarmed for the selfie. Okay. So wait. Unarmed and it's right bumper and
right trigger. It's not working. That's spit. No. How do I? I don't have time for this. Let's go.
It has to be next to a zombie. Okay. Let's go. Slave to fashion. Good. All right. Get in the
chair. In the chair. Get in the chair. What do you mean? No. The floor is cold. Carry me. No.
God damn it. I don't have any weapons besides the laser. Hold on. All right. Let's go.
Yeah. Okay. All right. We're going to do wilted flower now. Do I have time for that? Do I have
time to deliver her and then do wilted flower? Don't think so. We have to go right for it. I'm
going to save it right here. Let me see. Yeah. I got to bang a left. Save it and then we'll see.
All right. Out. No, no, no, no, no, no. I want to bring the wheelchair so I can go quickly.
Stop banging directions. I'll handle this. Okay. There's people shooting machine guns at us.
Just go. Just run. I got french fries for it. Don't worry. Car. Car. Get in the car.
Flashlight. So you're going to eat the french fries and then we'll save the game.
Why? What the fuck was that? Why did the car accelerate to a million miles per hour?
That's fucking crazy. Okay. Just a quick save point. French fries. Eat them. Just a quick.
I got to do one something real quick. Lightsaber. Done. Board. I'm just going to take two boards.
Board and knife. Right? No. Just take the knife. Take the board. Let's go. Ball of yarn and knife.
Okay. So this is the safe one. Let's do number one. Give her a weapon. Here. Take a board.
I can't give her a weapon. I can just carry her. Just get in the car. She just took damage.
Unbelievable. All right. Let's go do wilted flower. Wait. And go. Just move. Just run.
I got a coffee creamer. Oh my god. Oh my god. That was fucking funny. All right. Don't look.
Just go. But first. In here. Take one of these. Full heal. Close the door. That guy just got
fucking destroyed. What? That was insane. That's the best thing I've ever done in a video game.
Take this too. Okay. Give me the gun. Okay. I don't need a 2x4. And what else we got?
Ketchup. Beer. I'm gonna drink this. Okay. Can you take a gun? No. Follow me. I'm gonna bring a
cocktail too just in case I need it. Okay. Let's go. I don't want to waste this too much.
Gun. Money. Money. Gun. This is just one of those streams where I just say verbs and like nouns.
Go. Gun. Money. Casino. Go. Run. Gun. This is every stream. No it's not.
Gun. Money. Money. This is kind of far away. Is there a save point?
Here it is over here. I'm gonna go up for this. We don't have time for the save point. No we don't.
Let's hustle it up. Europa. Right outside the door. Are you serious? Anger. Anger. Gun. Mad.
All right. I got a lightsaber for what am I even looking for here? Cook. Wait. Is food in here?
This pineapple's in here and shit. Hold on. Here. Eat a couple pineapples.
Orange juice. Eat a pineapple. They work good for you. Orange juices. Oh shit. Come up here.
Run this way. Don't get stuck. All right. Chug contest. Oh I just totally. All right. Don't
fuck around. Just get full health. I'm going to take one of these. I'm going to. Where's my
lightsaber? What happened to the lightsaber? No. I don't want a fucking pineapple. Oh that shot.
It's just a t-post. I'm trying to pick up the lightsaber on the ground. Oh my fucking god.
All right. Let's go. All right. Here we are. You're in. Where is this person? What? Look at
the women in distress. Why is the. Why is the GPS having me do. Why did the GPS make me go
down the stairs? It's the spa. Here we go. I'm in. That just scared the shit out of me.
What is it? Was somebody in the tanning bed? Oh all right. Here we are.
Can I help? Please. Please help me. I was stuck in the tanning bed. The staff ran away or something.
I'm so parched. I can barely move. Do I need to give you orange juice?
You're baked. Literally. I was lying on my front for way too long. This can't be good for my tan
lines. You didn't know how the zombie outbreak happened? Listen. I can take you somewhere safe.
Zombie outbreak. I just thought the service here was bad. I can't move. I need something to drink.
Orange juice solves every problem. Here you go. Some good old-fashioned orange juice. Okay.
Let's go to the safe house. I've got two people. All right. Let's get a picture.
I work at brand new you on the second floor. Take me there and I'll show you the shortcut.
I have to carry. Oh no. This is gonna be bad. All right. Everybody filled? Everybody. Everybody
got snacks and everything, right? Here. Take a snack. What did I just pick up?
No. Don't give her the lightsaber. I'm not taking that. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
I need to bring you up where upstairs to what was a brand new you brand new you clothing.
Let's move. Take it. I'm not taking it. Combine that with a leaf blower. No, I'm not taking like
the fucking she actually won't move. I have to give you the you have to take the lightsaber.
Oh, this is really bad actually. All right. You're gonna have to stay with me.
Let's go. Come on. So far so good. Gotta go upstairs. All right. Where's the best place?
Can I go up there? That doesn't look like a place I can go. There we go. Up these stairs here.
Quarter circle to forward. All right. I'm gonna start for two here in a minute.
Is she smart enough to go up there? She's all right. Brand new you. All right. We're here.
Where is it? Where's the shortcut? Where's the shortcut? Brand new you upstairs.
She says she's going to show it to me. Who's talking? Hurry up. Hurry up. Quit like lurching
and get over here. Go. Oh my god. Is it this room? What the fuck? Okay. Here we are. The
shortcut is through the changing room in the back and it will take us to the royal flush
plot of safe houses right next door. Oh shit. All right. Save it. Put it down so I can finally
I get a shortcut. That's unbelievable to me. Okay. 430. We're gonna do this is the complete
oh shit moment safe. Let me drink some more of this coffee and then dilute it again.
Let's go. All right. I'm gonna start for two so I don't run into a problem.
I have to take a picture of both of the girls. Whatever. All right. And then we're right. Oh
we're right there. Nice. What do you mean? You have plenty of time. Don't get me started on this one
today. Why is it telling me to go there? What's with the arrow? What's this arrow pointing at me?
Oh it's all the way up there. Oh no. What's going on? What's happening? Are you okay?
Everybody. It just came out of nowhere. It just appeared in front of her.
And he wonders why he's soft locking. I don't wonder. I look I'm gonna get like a hundred
thousand points. Thank you. Thanks for sharing the embarrassment with me. Have a bit of my
shopping money. Whoa. Wait a minute. What do you mean shopping money? Twenty thousand dollars is
shopping money. It's a lot of money to just go shopping with. Got the combo card for this one.
Good. All right. Let me save it real quick. Only eighteen thousand two hundred two million bits.
Such a gentleman. He didn't take a picture of them. I mean I did but I was very very I'm look I
ain't gonna take like a picture like of them. Everybody wants me to get the erotic points
but I'm not gonna do it. I'm only gonna take pictures of my own ass and my own like penis
and then those photos are gonna get like leaked and all right now I gotta go I have to go I have
to go I have to go all right let's move I have plenty of uh shit to have okay all right I don't
have time to get these two you can't save them all everyone knows slappy locate the mascot where's
this one no locate there's a mascot look I just have to complete four two and then the new case
starts no I'm gonna stick with it wait I gotta I'm gonna stick with it take this shortcut yeah so
the shortcut is where's that I gotta I have to burn that into my brain the shortcut is over here
right what's that what is this thing no which one is it it was like this way where is it I forget
where it is it's a bathroom next to the safe room it's this one right so it's in here or is it in
here okay I need to burn this into my brain that this is then I need to see where it takes me
but for now uh well I need to see I got the game saved it's okay these bottom two missions are
psychopaths so well yeah I'm not sure I have time to do them because four two I don't want
to soft lock myself out of not doing four two and I want to see what this ends up though where is it
other side other one is it like a vent on the other side soft lock I don't think so
right here here it is that's the toilet there so now where am I from here I need to burn this
into my brain so now I am on the second floor above uh palisades I mean shit it is like right
there let me see if it's possible right like you got it we have to at least see if it's possible
I got the game saved royal flush plans I have a zombrex still I also have enough money to buy
another zombrex what was in there I don't whatever I don't know 7 p.m. time to no it's not
slappy's right next to me there's so many things to do there's too many things to do investigate
the chef or locate the mascot there's a lot of shit to do fuck ah that's so this is far away
I'm already on the way slappy has time we can find him later just don't let me forget that
slappy's slappy's literally right here he's right here is that slappy that's slappy right here
oh it's one of the soda the soda pop pee brothers
we asked for chicken but it was in my direct line of sight
you need something help you I have a lightsaber though
but what is it is it just need batteries just do a full swing below the knee take both the legs
so he can't run around then pick up body throw over the balcony into the zombies
yeah
that's pretty good all right he's on skates let's do a dodge go fuck what oh shit oh shit
oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit okay hold on what can I oh we can play this game man
I'm gonna be baby alien let's go motherfucker it's recess I feel like this is just what happens
this is what's inside of the minds of toddlers when they're just like plant
it's empty okay time for here we go I gotta go in oh okay right when he stops stop why is he
not stopping oh you prick dude I can't hit him what all right so I can't you can't swing at him
where's the checkpoint is it right there there all right
it watch out orange juice quick come on Jedi fall in order looks really good
oh fuck you slappy out out all right now we're gonna do lasers got you pepe hands
be really funny if you took off the mask and he looked just like that under the mask too
flamethrower water gun and gasoline canister that's pretty awesome okay hold on oh I can just take
yours all right I don't have time for this gotta get a good photo okay um now I've gotta go this
way the chicken one uh I'm gonna get soft locked if I don't do it we're up wait I need to I need
that kid's like jumpsuit onesie thing I need it and um is it like fun superhero boots yep okay
I'm ready it's just Christopher Robin as an adult but not Ewan McGregor this is what it
should have been like how do you save the game right fucking now okay so this is casino vaults
there's a save point over here and drop this I don't need it I just want this one all right
where's that save point it's right here hopefully I have enough time to do both of these now can I
even get in here shit I don't know ATM don't I can't Jeremy you're fucked this story mission
is so long but it's okay we're going then now I'm doing it right now it's too I can't even do this
if it's like yellow can I get into this bathroom this is fucking bathroom but the bathroom's the
elevator the bathroom's in the elevator huh oh all right I can make it where even is this one
is it this one here is that where I'm going yeah there's a woman in the underground
it's what it's all of these locations it's all of them oh no that's not good we may have to go
back in time and a dude's four two before when it's halfway to like when I'm in one of my safe
zones climb over dude just do the cases as soon as you can well some of them you can
all right I have a checkpoint which is right here how the fuck am I going to be able to do all this
all the casino vaults all of them um how how am I going to do that I need the car the car is
like all the way over there wheelchair and it's gonna have to redo it we'll see how far I get
I got I've got some decent save points just reset now there's no way I'm doing this hold on of course
you're laying down fire across everything and I'm still gonna grab him no there's no way this is
happening oh man this is no way I have to come here first look at all this shit this is this is
like gonna take all day just kill me just kill me I gotta come here prepared with like weapons and
shit I mean oh it's it might be possible though don't give up yet did this motherfucker just eat
a whole pie yes I had to all right they're over here shit this is really long
I thought I had time I thought I had time to do all this okay well here they are where are you
they just didn't hear okay are you shitting me are you shitting me
I have to do this in three separate places dude what is it with zombie games forever there always
has to be assault rifle military people in these games I just want to play the zombie game it's
almost like they second guessed if the game was any fun fuck we're gonna add like segments where
they shoot at people with guns this happens in almost every zombie game so uh this is tricky
because the one 620 I think maybe it's gonna have to be the 621 this is
rare this is very far away how much time is in this one let's take a look I want oh this still
it's it's you two are here shit god damn it really and it's yellow all right I have to
dump these two and then go so I'm gonna that's not that far away I could I think it's possible
now here we go there should be enough time I'm gonna have to abandon all the other missions
we just have to dump them and go unlock the shortcut I didn't didn't I I did yeah I did
this is after the shortcut yeah I'm good shit and then I'm gonna have to go to the furthest one
away up and just try to not die fuck and here's the 20 grand and then I think this I think that
this is where I saved it I sort of gone to the first one because I remember I was like oh let
me make sure I have a timeline back here yeah so the other save point is this one's 10 minutes
faster because see watch this ready this one is the same exact timeline but I was like five
minutes faster so we're gonna do this one and remember the absolute like fuck face scenario
if this is impossible I've got take a look at this I've got two two is four hours ago look at
that that's why you never save over that keep that there that's why I did this I saved three
minutes so I need to go to this one this one here no all right so I'm gonna take the take the
shortcut and then go to this one and then try to make it all the way back I think that's correct
that's right I have such shitty weapons though I need to be able to kill two of them why not left
middle right because I think that's shorter I think if I go to the shortcut first do the one
right next to me yeah and then go in the shortcut and then okay so left shortcut middle right no left
shortcut right middle or left right middle I don't know I'm just gonna go for it so in that case
just do this one which is in here okay let's go do I have enough time to do this shit
I really hope so otherwise we have to rewind three hours here we go take your time take the time take
the time I have to get an assault rifle quick how many times do I have to shoot you before you die
get too much body armor just give me a break
I wanted to pick up the handbag creamer I want the creamer what is that a drill how do I stop
the drill okay there's one okay uh it's a lot of money right here good job on that frank but
there's still 75 000 dollars all right I need assault rifles uh drink this coffee drink this
other one too 27 and get rid of the handbag let's go good money it's not that much okay so now we're
gonna go just straight up just straight up or should I take the shortcut and go right help me
hold on let me refill my coffee there's a second money case key and case key and case key and case
key and security uh key key and case another case I didn't see it I don't see it I didn't see it
give me the assault rifle where's that case where's that case
hell no these are suitcases guys stop baiting me oh here it is that's it 10 grand that's all
I came back for okay go all right did we decide on what was the better idea just go straight through
he hates bits what are you talking about I have to save it though all right did we decide
I can save it in there and take the shortcut and then come down that's what that's the play
that's the play no no but I have to save the game what if I get caught and die
what if I die I might die and then you're gonna hear loud noises I'm gonna be like I should have
saved it back here and I should have done this and I should have replaced the handbag with that
orange juice and I'm gonna be like I should have listened to my own intuition I should have listened
to myself you've already heard it before somebody's in trouble I don't have time
for whatever who is it I don't have time to do it where are they they close follow the sound of my
voice can you hear me can anybody hear me just making sure good luck meat melon oh you're screwed
like fire the gun in the air I'm not gonna do it because okay this is where I have to start
what who shot me fire the gun in the air just make sure that they know that you have a weapon
place where is he where is he big slot machine big slot machine taking a lot of effort to not
play that show your fucking million times mate what nice bouncy bullets what's in there get that
money all right and more stuff more thugs okay um what's in here no time there's no time there's
no time there's a woman in the underground handgun what's this thing electric prod uh
pizza take the pizza full heel probably okay magazine combat three 10 boost to pp when from
weapon kills keep it almost done anything else I need to grab some people are gonna freak out if
I leave something whatever too late I gotta get this done okay go go go no no no no put down the
uh whatever almost done who the hell is Janice Janice uh hold on let me uh no let me clear um
they put too many things in front of you there's too many things
there's something is Jasper fuck hold on wait wait wait wait uh how close am I I'm far away
I'll be back does everybody stay alive ah who else needs help there's too many people need help
I'm overstimulated okay I have should have enough time to turn these all off Jasper is dead
I thought you guys said I was gonna have time to come back and save them that was not true
all right where is this other box oh
it's straight ahead the gps is freaking out does it just get bumped fuck all right there it is
why are you even why are you even here wait eat eat eat eat no don't drink don't eat just
don't fucking slow down what is that one bullet oh shit no no drink drink the orange god damn it
this is outrageous how the fuck am I supposed to go over here
shoot it where the fuck is this guy oh my god give me a fucking break capcom what is this
you gotta be fucking shitting me I need to eat something is anybody left in here
this tk's goons are still going you're talking about
stop picking up I wanted to pick up the fucking I need another gun wow give me a break man
forget doing the story but you need like the whole day to do this shit this whole mission
takes like the whole bar get away from me motherfucker is this the right they're everywhere
I don't think I'm gonna do this I fucking god give me your gun give me your gun give me your gun
I don't have any food is it beer on the ground there was so much food I thought I was done
oh it's gonna be really really goddamn close oh come on why is it military it's case four
what's the military doing here that's over yeah forget about the zombies that was fun for the
first three cases watch out for the fucking guys in the yellow clothes that just have assault
rifles now I'm dead I'm dead where's this checkpoint is it close enough I wonder if
it's still possible maybe can I sneak around this military dickheads or goons whatever they goons
watch out for the goons take the bike that's not that's not gonna do anything that bike is
fucking tiny that bike is not hey I would like some food do you have food in here
food you don't have you don't sell food do you sell food you don't sell food in here
I thought they had food in here I'm so dead this is like I'm fucking locked the motorbike
fuck me I'll get it after this next attempt which is going to be over in about 12 seconds
you go to the pawn shop for lunch I don't know they might have something there
move move move all right where is it any food on the ground give me that bike give me this thing
give it to me give it to me give it to me get any food in here he's covered wars you know
taping guns to a bike shouldn't be a problem but bring a bike to the combo bay
experiment with different that's really cool I can't wait to figure out what that means
I've got to go now where am I going straight ahead to the left okay it's actually right here
please get away from me please get away from me okay I know where it is now I'm gonna fail
I'm gonna fail it I'm gonna fail it's okay but I know where it is give me the bike give me the
bike okay I have to destroy this okay I have to destroy that just destroy the van and I'm out
god damn it man oh this is so uh do gun and bike you mean like right here how do I do it how do I
do it a different gun I'm still just being lied to great no no god give me the gun how many
bullets were there I can't even take out the fucking van oh come on there's so many people
over here okay so let me not waste time do I have enough time to eat anything like that let me
that probably is like a sandwich or something lying around somewhere a beer anything nothing
at all I'm driving into the restaurant kidding me give me this what I can't get it's locked
okay give me a fucking break man so uh here's the strategy strategy is um I need to look for food
so get bike grab something to eat I think I should have enough time to do this so where's
there's a restaurant right here somewhere where's the restaurant I mean this thing is a restaurant
here we are okay I should have enough time to like get some health I don't want to use any
guns give me the lightsaber okay let's heal yeah of course it only heals one let me pies back here
there's just beers everywhere just drink just drink all the beers okay well I'm done oh why did
I drink three in a row okay so look at how many zombies there are and shit here's the plan I'm
gonna I have to kill these guys I can't just like I'm just gonna run straight and shoot the van
I have a gun I meant get away from me get away from me get away from me get away from me
get away from me would I do it would the time run out
so time ran out yeah well we got one of the endings that's good it's possible
spent too much time in the restaurant um so I have a question those of you that have played
this game like 30 times in a row and I know everything when I blow up this van is at the
end I just look at it fucking chat kill me just kill me kill me kill me is this still a drill that
I have to undo there are more trucks god damn man so I I'm gonna have to go back just restart the
whole game I know that's what you're supposed to do but and when it's if it's possible I want to
try to do it in one go okay right here get off the bike whatever I get I where are these guys
shooting what are you doing out here why are they here what are you doing here I'd say I had the
same amount of help that I started with and I have no more guns no so I have to have to back
uh I don't think I can go in the restaurant there's nothing wrong with starting the whole
game over yeah but I feel like I don't want to do I don't want to do like the whole game again
you know what I mean it's definitely possible if I have to oh absolutely yeah get three guns and
shoot the van let's try this side yeah but I need three guns okay this is actually not a bad spot
seriously like the glue that these zombies have in these games holy shit all right let's see if I
can do it I gotta do I gotta go to the same spot I was before down here wrap around otherwise
it's gonna die okay let's try it I just need to get a gun I need a fucking break just give me the
gun give me a gun give me a gun give me a gun give me a gun Jesus Christ all right I'm just
gonna go in and swing in the truck with the lightsaber kill the people it's not that simple
it's not that simple just go in and kill them huh
it's possible to do it like this if I had okay if I have full health it's possible it was that
simple I refuse to believe it was that simple I refuse to believe it oh I have to believe it
give me a break no Jesus why is it that simple to drive the bike into the van and just spam x
mod that guy you do that fuck it I'm going in
I gotta kill people I have to kill people I have to kill them I have to kill people you have to
kill them they have to die okay you gotta kill them you gotta kill the guys hey who's winning
shoot the prophet Jesus Christ uh no don't unmod that guy he didn't even get modded in the first
place I would I wish I could come in here with like have food right now you can't hit the back
of the truck somebody fucking of rules no I thought that was a beer there's a knife doing
over here I didn't what what just healed me to full put it down I did a snack just healed me
to full health as you should know it's one bar all right here we go I'm going for it when
shoot propane tank get it and swing violently just like what fire the gun what is happening
oh fuck no no die die die please die die you motherfucker please give me this give me this
thing this way this is heavier this thing's way heavier explode I did it now what did I win
I'm going mad oh I'm going mad not like angry mad like mad like the hatter like the guy from
Alice in Wonderland I'm so happy that I have the dealer hat on
though first story I'm meeting with my source tonight I think maybe it's time you met oh yeah
guess I'm not such a burden anymore I think this is kind of a special case I can't believe it I'll
meet you at Benny Jack's thought I had so much time and it happens this next case I'm not going
to let run into the ground the next case will occur at 12 a.m. okay I know it happens every case
but there's so much interesting shit to see in this game that like I get so stuck okay this one
which is a safe one this one okay five one let's go just get to five one wait a minute I have no
health um all right where do I go don't die it starts I have time I actually do have time
because it just starts I just have to be in the right spot for this I could probably do this one
because it is yeah a woman with a golf club is fending off zombies she has a good she has good
form see what I can do I do want to go back to the bar though where's the bike and there are
people shooting machine guns at me still there are people that have guns still this is just
my life now this is my life now for the rest of the game German throw the trash can for food
holy shit there's food everywhere in here what okay you can eat food out of the that's why you
don't eat food out of the trash okay I'm going this way I need to get guns stop dropping that
I'm already sick so might as well just go all the way soda doesn't go bad it's got like a
shitload of chemicals in it uh all right what is this gonna make freezer bomb all right you
dickheads out here I'm so done with you zombies and no I'm not even done with the zombies I'm
done with the machine gun guys I got just tripped on my throw up that's just just use it now
holy shit that was way more ridiculous than I thought it was gonna be all right all right all
right all right just hug this wall I don't have any guns okay food is it drink no it's a hamburger
don't eat it you left your lightsaber at the bar well don't worry it's so did Luke knife
he's right actually I know yes I know I don't people just don't have they guys never seen the
Star Wars before all right I've got the Wolverine hands this is the best weapon in the game really
I'm gonna save it then all right more importantly let me get back to normal okay there's some vodka
let's just drink it dress shoes okay here we go let me look decent again good I'll take the
tuxedo I'll be the dealer gems I'll take gems I already have gems but I'll get rid of them I
don't want them I'm not gonna drop these don't worry now I've got 500 grand when did that happen
all right uh there is the thing I'm doing is over here and then I just have to get back let me make
sure I know what this is this is just a safe house no no this is I have to meet Rebecca and
her source later is that the safe house I think it is right that's what that means package I need a
I'm gonna go save it go do slappy let me save the game before I do anything stupid this is
the right way right no one's behind me stupid all right this is 9 p.m. I'm gonna keep the one
yeah this is fine slow down any food in here yeah this chips I'm looking for a drink
all right I'll take it uh drop this I don't even I don't want the gems
fuck it okay let's go over here and actually do this before the time runs out maybe I'll be able
to save you maybe there's laws coming all right get up what do you want what's happening good
thing I got a strong swing no problem it's not safe out here come with me if you follow me I
can take you to the safe house I used I'm used to crowds on the pro tour but the fans aren't you
well plus uh swinging is good for my form I just hope my favorite club can handle the extra
punishment okay you need to eat these right now can I not give you these I found them in the trash
I'm not giving up my favorite club well then I actually do not care if you die so that just
tells me that I should not care if you live or die I don't I don't get out you can do it
take this she's not gonna take the orange juice no I wanted I saw the orange juice go
case I'm going back to case the cases I'm gonna be this is where I'm bringing her
you're like a shark you can detect orange juice like blood
talk of comedy here this thing has lasted pretty long but it's sort of annoying to use
get those shoes off nah thanks to you I can still make the pro tour thanks for helping me out have
a slice of what I got from the last leg of my pro tour that sounds like a lot of money there's a
girl in here that's shopping with more money than you just gave me for your pro tour dynamite hunk
of meat and dynamite that's cool so where's this case quick meat on bone case is not in the safe
house ah okay did you just hear the gulp I just did an audible gulp which one do I it's probably
gonna have to be this one is safe it's possible to complete it from here this one uh probably two
can you not tell which save is latest no I know what save is latest I'm just trying to not save
over one that puts me in a good spot to not get locked out there's nothing to do with when I when
I saved it it has to do with where is it what part of the game yeah okay boomer okay zombrex
yeah okay boomer yeah yeah see in like another three months when you guys come up with some other
insult to tell people the season age I'm trying so hard I'm trying so hard right now to do this
but I couldn't do it gamble the 500 000 I don't have time to gamble you have to be so
you can't be tardy at all what is this doing okay gotta go up the upstairs is there a staircase
I know I know I know I'm worried for Rebecca but is there a where's the stairwell to get up there
is it in the back with the stairs in the back or do I have to actually go up like some other
escalator or something I don't think there we go but I'm gonna eat a hamburger we're good
a million dollars what is going on in this game man I have to dump my million
I'm only halfway there I got how much time to come up with a million dollars
let's see that's actually a pretty long time that's enough time oh a steak steak and a sphere
I'm gonna take the spear I'm gonna replace the uh hamburger with with the steak uh
okay money I've got to make money we're gonna get to a million dollars first we have everybody
knows slappy which I'm gonna try to make money on the way to slappy oh fuck slappy who cares
this is right here mail order zombricks get book on table book on table book on table gambling
too significant increase when playing gambling games oh shit all right let's go gamble where's
that big machine there's lots of food in here all right where's the big one okay let's try it 100
bucks nothing come on I gotta play more than one machine at a time that's 2400 bucks going to the
money machine yeah I'll do this like another two minutes money hackers not a bad idea oops uh
whatever gambling too come on where's that thousand dollar machine let's go where's the big one
money machine let's go okay let's try it I don't want to break it 50 dollars that's it
okay it's only 4000 it's not that much to do this 98 more times don't make me laugh
this should be like 20 grand all right one more and that's it wrong button all right let's go I
need to eat after that one sick okay where's the uh any other thing like blackjack or any poker or
oh here's a big one all right everyone get out of the fucking way this is my machine
Wild West draw all right we got a we got a jack queen keep the jack and the queen
draw there it is jack's bread I'll take 500 dollars let's do it again we got uh hold the fours
nothing uh this sucks because it doesn't have enough uh payout uh we got it go for a spray
or just hold sometimes you just hold the ace there it is jack's bread it's okay
six seven eight nine ten just need to nine uh we got just hold the ace and the jack
hold seven pray to god it's only 20 I could do that I could mash my fingers into the ground
and make more money prepare six uh hold the queen dump just dump the whole fucking thing
there it is we got two three ace tab what is it we got two ace ace two three now let's hold
no what about slappy oh fuck what slap who cares it was shit about slappy oh
damn this is pretty good I mean you got to go for it come on free of kind what are you
gonna spin it grab the two gambling magazines blah blah blah blah blah this I can't read that
that's all I see where sports it what I'm not gonna like exploit defeat this
hold the aces aces in the tens looking for a full house full house 10 grand
third time germa this is slow all right one more this is it all right yeah I got kings here man
great time all right what I can't read this it's just mess mega man I can see it's mega man
okay he's everyone's about to break wait can I go in the cage I'm going to the cage hello not a
lot of money all right somebody just simplify this because I the chat is going so fast I cannot
read what you're writing just give me like two sentences play the giant slot okay go to a big
machine that that's I could that's much easier for me to see go to the mega man slot you guys
got this like huge fucking paragraph of how to change and close go to slot ranch see look at
that simplified and ready to go just give me the sword fuck the gems all right slot ranch
go get the gambling books well I already got I got one of them I've got gambling too
all right slot ranch I want to do that the one with the zombrex I still need 450 000 yeah but
I got a long time to do it break all the small machines he rolled its dark souls ha ha ha
okay all right slot ranch down there I need to go get there fast eat a brownie eat both the
brownies personally I blame the gifted subs for this I'm trying to even think of what that means
I'm having trouble anything on the way oh would you look at that it's right here
magazine gambling blades three times durability for edged weapons all right I've had enough of
the laser face this thing okay I got the book so this thing's three times more durable um where's
this thing that I need to oh it's right here what is it does it got zombrex it's slappy it's human
slappy god damn the ghostbusters references for dan ackroyd dan ackroyd in ghostbusters is wearing
the same hat and doing like taxes and shit he's got like a cigarette hanging out of his mouth
and it's a bomb oh it's messed up the truck
well there's a gun I don't have one of those
by the way uh I saved like 110 000 check watch it it's not that bad oh it's a bomb
he's done throwing bombs where'd he go bow and arrow bow and arrow where is he what the
fuck is he this is gonna be impossible with a bow and arrow I may just oh what are you doing
here fight him carl what a pain in the ass I well this thing sucks asshole I need that orange juice
oh am I gonna fight this dude shotgun from that that far away that's it the food in here
where's the food there's no food in here good to know
what is it where why you gotta be shitting me from from that far away I need to heal
is it food line up this coffee cream right here take it all right can I cheeseball this guy
from this far away he's doing it to me range weapons are not gonna help with this
this dude is going fucking nuts just go in there and end him he's got a shotgun aimed at me
okay ready and I'm going in carl no why I gotta heal you shoot me through the fucking wall oh
eat my ass eat my fucking ass that's dumb there's food right there but it's covered in zombies
not like this not like this not like this not like this not like this not like this not like this not
like this not like this he's dead this dude's toast though it's gotta close the gap on him in
oh fuck fuck off with this oh I got you mate I'm saying mate a lot so the mailman clothes are
available I need this this one's a special delivery the dud no it's not
it's a wicked witch of the west I had to get it and a shotgun on the ground here
yeah I'll take it all right money money is important right now so let's go get some
where the hell was I going save the game right behind me turn around bang a left turn around
left see no I'm glad I have to do that again and then get the money hacker that's correct
this is I'm in a good position right now let's put this at one I think was back here right
where did I get surrounded was it over here other side I wonder other side yeah
there it is should I use this on the slot machine oh I'm just only on atms oh god
oh fuck oh god there's a security guard 20,000 cookies just the knife gloves are almost done
anyways all right time to go win slots slots slots slots slots I'm gonna play the Willy Wonka
machine and then I'm gonna play the Betty White machine and then I'm gonna play the Ellen machine
and then I'm gonna play I don't know that's it that's all I care about
all right big one where is it on the edge somewhere there it is clear it up this is
a thousand dollars a pull but I'm I'm hoping I can win the money here
remind me never to take this blade book off thousand that's it now these are in every single
casino but I don't I don't have a played this machine you know why because if you ever win
money on this thing let's say you put in like let's say you put in like five dollars right and you
pulled it it's five dollar bet it's gonna be a huge deal let's say you win five hundred thousand
dollars on this machine every single fucking person in the whole casino knows you're like you
just made a shitload of money holy fuck it's got a hundred grand see look at how everybody knows
everybody knows you can't just be like yeah I won like a hundred it was I won 50 bucks whoa
no if you ever win money on this thing you need to like hire a detail to take you out
I want the 777 I'm not gonna leave here I'm gonna try to get like five million dollars
I can't even see what's happening the casino will ask if you want someone to walk you out
uh-oh I think my luck has run out come on give me all the money signs all right oh
that would have been great money oh money it's my machine get up wait for it
get off of me it's my machine you bit me you bit me you bit me
zombie apocalypse get the fuck out of here oh what was fun even though it's oh no I did the
thing that people do in the casino when you just spam the button and you don't even care how much
money you want you just go keep going that's another 50k you lost a hundred viewers oh I'm
I need a million dollars what do you want me to do I need to make I need a million dollars guys
I'm not doing this for fun what's the highest amount you can get for a payout from here
can you win like a million dollars just give me the two million dollar hit so I can just
never worry about money go buy a call that's 100k wait that's a big deal I gotta put that on my
Instagram story the payouts are at the top okay so yeah the hearts are wild so it's the money
symbols you need three money symbols or three uh diamonds looking for the money symbol three
diamonds come on just do the money machine my my whole body hurts from the money machine
and it's only four thousand I have almost doubled my money I'm not stopping at a million by the
way I'm gonna sit at this I'm just gonna sit in this machine until tomorrow at morning
I I want to buy the car never enough 50 grand yeah 50 grand I'm over I'm almost there
but we're going for two million you'd rather watch me playing numbers go up
million I need more than a million dollars though I know that I'm already at the million but
I'll be I'll have zero dollars all right not bad not bad these are insanely generous slots yes they
are there please give us content fine here happy you don't even need to see it I just want 25
thousand dollars I don't even know how much money I'm winning I'm just winning when you're
hot you don't get up uh-oh someone's calling me oh well uh Rebecca call the police okay if I go
under 1.8 I'm gonna stop if I go under 1.8 million I mean no no no no no I mean 1.18 1.18 million
you know what I was trying to say you guys told me to come here if I remember reading that
huge paragraph that people were spamming it was to get the gambling book and come over here
you did this I didn't I was gonna just walk around and try to like
rob people and like smash stuff uh-oh all right under 1.2 million about uh-oh uh-oh oh
miss that's it one more for good luck and one more after that for good luck too
and one more for like all my friends yeah okay three more see that's it I got 200,000
dollars but what about the car okay let's go um let's go do uh I have a lot of time for this one
barn burner that's way too far away bank run is right here what would germa do
what would what would is this what would jesus do what would john wick do
ego maniac so you're jesus now I mean I did just make I did just win 700,000 dollars on slot
machines I think there's something going on here that don't happen unless you're the son of god
I'm kidding everybody relax jesus jesus criminy all right we're gonna do uh I can't do this one
we'll do bank run because that's right here let's go I was trying to change the camera angle
oh if only you could see the face I just made it was wild you have no idea turn on the face cam
fuck's sake settle down oh no we got a chance to be real patriots
I have to turn right the fucker down and go to the door I haven't saved since like 400,000 dollars
are they on the roof
it's hard again that's right because we love our country
apple pie was invented in the UK
okay um I need a save point so I'm gonna go over here oh johnny is right there
johnny where's my save point where's the save point should I go up and just kill johnny
no I don't want to go that way save point like one that I can actually reliably get to
I do have to go that way have to turn right that's it am I gonna get sniped
am I gonna get sniped right now this is I'm gonna get sniped just hug the wall
hug the wall and then there's a save point right in the middle the waterfall
oh my god that was so much damage oh my god no no no no my fucking god it's insanity drink
all right I'm going up with I'm going up there with a shotgun this is gonna be a
checkpoint when I go up here what if I go this way I'm just looking for a safe point that's over
there I can't even go in the bed okay can I go across and then do the bathroom you already
I'm gonna have a checkpoint yeah but I don't want to get another checkpoint if I accidentally
if I go up that's what I'm saying if I go up and I get an auto checkpoint and I die up there then
it's over is there a bathroom down here bathroom give me a bathroom no not toilet paper for the
bathroom this is bathroom they're up there you can just go back down uh where are they wrong
roof but where's the bathroom there was supposed to be a bathroom over here on the roof where's
this bathroom that's an elevator that's not a bathroom I thought these were bathrooms
until right now in the game okay so oh that's very bad okay the bathroom is in the middle how
the fuck am I gonna get there how about espress yeah but I thought I know I know but like it just
there's the elevator thing oh okay that's all right we're good everything's good
I can get rid of the gambling book now I just have to make it to the middle just go up there
and fucking kill him all right listen listen Rambo what if they what if they keep killing
me up there and I got stuck up there forever money it just sucked over to him what it was
connected to his body explain it huh what happened I put I pressed it on the thing and like
over to the left onto the guy's body okay well go watch a peep show you're trying to get me banned
all right where's the way to go up is it right up there over here right actually I'm kind of just
I'm safe right now I don't even want to it's right the thing is here I have to pee I actually really
do what is gonna happen in here though I don't know this guy's gonna get sniped and shit when
we're running back this way no I've got it I got him I've got him I have to get to that safe point
first give me that cart you have a checkpoint yeah but the checkpoint is gonna keep getting
overwritten every time I like leave a door leave a building I wonder if I can just is this fast
enough to not get sniped what do you think maybe no all right well time to kill them I'm not
sticking around anymore I got a shotgun let's go I just did it it's over okay Johnny I have to time
this so it's bang shoot now what these bricks over there oh fuck he's to reload but wait wait
hold on dodge it he's gonna reload fuck okay oh I've just been still for that I hate this I hate
so he's just rush him no I know here we go that's it what do you mean that's it he was spamming no
I wasn't spamming I was merely trying to dodge his attacks are there other people up here
there's three more on separate buildings so that sucks what do you got any suitcase full of money
bacon okay I have a sniper rifle now though so I can the bricks were key I think in that whole
scenario in fact I'm gonna take a couple just because they didn't they did not fail me wait
I'm gonna take a cheeseburger um handgun I'm gonna drop the gambling book which book is this that's
blades keep that one gambling book cares I don't want it and give me a hamburger now I can go
save the game drop the brick for the gun take the gun okay now I can save drop the brick for the
book no no more books save the damn game why do I hear noises that are shooting sounds
Derek you can't aim straight down like that he's gonna shoot through the building
all right I gotta get up there or not maybe I can I get in there and save I gotta climb up this
shit and get him wait can I bastard sniper duel do a snipe off I actually do it do I actually have
to do a snipe off with this guy I can't get up on that roof can I okay like I gotta clear this shit
out that does not know that's not gonna happen I have to headshot him that's not real all right
how do I get on the roof from here so onto the roof okay so through here obviously right
I go find a clam person if only I had a map yeah I'm looking at it I'm trying to see where I have to
go who the fuck are all these people um no I don't have to I don't I don't have time to do this
where's the fire friend have you looked outside there are zombies everywhere we need to get you
all the safety wait just a second here let's not jump to conclusions hey if we walk out there and
you have that American flag on that we we don't we don't get shot at anymore right is that how
that works can't you see we're trying to have a game of poker here big stakes pal we could use
another player hold on now the only way I leave a game is if I'm out of chips beat us all and we'll
go with you my pappy used to say money talks I'm sure you could use some extra cash more gambling
just sit down and play some poker time's wasting it's a hundred thousand dollars okay I don't know
how to play poker I don't know how I don't know how to play poker what do I have a two and an eight
that sucks right yeah this thing sucks yeah I don't know like I don't play poker
I'm a blackjack and backer rat guy six and four that's terrible too
they're six and four off suit dog shit fold it say she's right now I would have lost
six four off suit I suck yeah I would have gotten destroyed six four off suit queen eight two
what do you got sure let me see can we see the cards do we just never know what you have
all right now that's what I'm talking about all right now I don't understand the whole raising
thing and like the call check did you just put forty four thousand dollars on here wait you put
everything there all in or I'm going all in oh all right here we go oh shit I hope there's a bunch
of kings there's a lot of kings here uh-oh wait ten king jack uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh that was bad
what I won I got a pair of tens a pair of tens wins this hand
holy shit the guy had nines I just wiped everybody clean completely it's just me and you Jessica
okay I got ten not going all in okay ten same suit king ten let's raise the I got all the money in
the damn world I'll raise you a fucking eight thousand dollars you don't can't even afford it
all in all in
I just got a flush get out of here that's fucking ridiculous why would you ever do something that's
stupid all right everybody stick around we need to get some I'm not fucking around who cares about
this mission because I got three turn ins two flushes in a row we gotta go we gotta go to the
safe house look at my money I'm a millionaire okay this is important how do we get the hell
out of here without getting everybody sniped is the question because I don't I don't know how is
this how to get out of this I could wrap back around this way and get in the shortcut right
let's go save the game first shit where I can't go out here the sniper they just have to stay
alive but the sniper spend some of my winnings mermaid self mermaid self mermaid at shortcut
mermaid shortcut wait wait what do you mean rescue the mermaid and then I guess we could
hold on a second give me a second let's take me a minute so go get mermaid go through here
through the hotel through this way out around all the way back around get mermaid and then just go
the long way save the game here all right that's the plan that's what I'm going to try absolute
journey yes we need weapons for you guys let's see you take this gun take a brick
you this is about to break so you take the sword I'm trusting you with that so no give me that back
take this gun I want that okay we have two guns a brick what else is in here everyone's at full
health all right let's do it can't fuck it up so let's go out this door just go get the mermaid
follow me don't get grabbed don't get grabbed don't get grabbed don't get grabbed
Tammy you all right clear him out everybody just do what you can we're doing our best
good brickwork Jessica excellent brickwork everybody get up here are you all right I can't
move around in this costume this is bad can't you just take it I forgot my bathing suit at home
Jacob take this Jake Jacob Jacob all right where's your gun take the gun
Tammy's joint take that gun you I have to carry you all right everybody hustle we gotta go this
way fish wait let me get the let me get the lobster it's a full hill and a fish and shit
like and a spear okay fish and shit my favorite fucking meal all right no wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait there's too many people to okay put down the uh fish it's not
necessary straight through here into the safe point right is that a bad idea I'm gonna piss
my pants if I don't go to the bathroom or this one this is the shortcut right no it's up so I
have to go to this one that's so far no it's the green one green one where's the green one
second floor oh I'm gonna pee I have to pee is that dressing room in that second floor it's this
is it this one right here this one right here there it is okay I gotta go up the stairs
so from here so we gotta go out this way and then upstairs here all right see in a minute
time does not count in this menu doesn't 10 25 no it doesn't okay let us continue so we're going
up so let me I'm gonna have the waypoint for here because that's where the stairs are let's move you
guys have got you have to keep up that's fine just don't get grabbed don't get grabbed this
is gonna be tough because they all have to be over here it's gonna be tricky I have to do a
couple spins one two three go upstairs made it what is it you it's you you you you and me
me and you what's it called oh what and I'm I am on the second floor brand there it is okay brand
new you yes yes are we good get in you can do it Jessica make it through and we're off
fantastic and I got a save point right here can you believe it nice hot take zombies suck
yeah they do they're incredibly annoying they just cause a bunch of problems and shit
it shouldn't be too hot it should not be too hard to get over here no it's not hot
as Frank would say yeah fantastic oh sorry hard yeah I gotta use my broadcaster voice
it's really hard to do that sorry guys you just got insulted I got this is a four turn in
always go all in and every anything you do in life give a hundred percent or don't give any
I'll bet on you any day gathered up some change from that fountain while I was stuck
right that's it five thousand dollars that's a lot of escort she was just standing level up again
double level up the fire spitter toy spitball gun and tiki torch 30,000 pp bonus 30,000 pp
bonus 30,000 bonus 44,000 bonus judo throw okay I gotta look at that I gotta look at these new
moves come uh status skills snapshot yeah face cry I haven't done this yet rtb quickly escape
from a front grapple to deliver this devastating suplex I've been doing that this is the jump press
right trigger and x in the air it's the knee drop thing okay so it's not just jumping x it's
jump rt and x walk like a zombie great way to go unnoticed that's pretty good and then quickly
escape a rear grapple to give the zombie a toss just a taste of Frank's judo skills so we can do
is hold both triggers and then hold b for three seconds I got 2.1 million clothing locker okay
we're all four pieces of the psychopath alpha to gain added abilities okay good now I have
money to spend I've saved the game where are we going this I still got lots of time to do five
two I need to bring one million dollars to the shawl nightclub at seven p.m. to pay Rebecca's
ransom so I've got a lot of time for this this is at seven p.m. bank run I'm gonna go back in the
get the car now buy car get car okay well hold on a second there where's the car is it right here
it's closed it's like right here I need the key to the car all right let's go to the pawn shop
this pawn shop right here is the keys right key is a million dollars I got it
save first I just I just saved it right there didn't the game glitch out last time I tried
to buy something yeah it did all right I'm gonna go up and then into the pawn shop
do the zombie walk hold left trigger and right trigger and B for three seconds one two three
well this is not a great way to get around it's incredibly slow it's really really slow
it's pretty funny though yeah humor and comedy sometimes is more important all right what do you
got ding dong we got a laser sword gem blower zombrex salt rifle tenderizers no car key sports
car key a million give me a fucking break what did you take why does it have to happen every time
like it happens every single time you think you're getting away with my shit
did he walk in the store spawn three psychos okay cool give me the car give me the zombrex
and give me why can I buy this twice buy the sword laser sword that doesn't count as a sword
this does drop the fish get the mask no all right where's that car down below right there it is I
see a woman in hot sports car key used all right nice oh what happened why can he not die all
right bank run I can't take this with me can I pick up the car so um that kind of sucks but I
have it now it's too hippie that's a waste of a million dollars that actually really sucks
it can only go through that one thing what is going on oh the snipers the snipers
well thanks Derek okay well the key is a one time use item is that a why key is not a one time use
okay all right I'm just gonna load checkpoint now how the hell am I supposed to get I have to
I went the wrong way I gotta wrap back new uniform oh okay so to get to there instead of I'm gonna
go let's let's go this way so I gotta go this way I get to keep it in here right yeah I was
gonna say that would be so stupid now I have to go fuck I have to go we're gonna do bank
run uh bank I'm just gonna drive around okay bank run let's do it and bring the thing that I
what winning looks like I did it on this machine you scumbags and I'm gonna do it again queen there
it is 10 grand let's go have any limbs left need to be over a million just go to like one point like
one book oh shit you're right don't even need the book oh they said it couldn't be done they said
it couldn't be done they said it couldn't be done they said it couldn't be done what's that
this is how you make real money so long suckers I don't even look at you I don't even need to look
at you I don't even need to look at you throw the car all right turn left I'm gonna go through here
Shit, I can't bring this out here. I got how much money I have. I'll just get another one. Oh
So just I have to wrap to the okay. I can go this way. Let me in now
Oh, I need a tiki torch for something. Don't I nothing over here?
Right ATM
I'm so fucking mad right now fucking dumb stupid fucking game. It's a fucking angry fucking idiot fucking dumb idiot game
Wait
It's a stupid game
dumb dumb fucking game
How many of you guys do that I
Bet you a shitload of you guys do that you just in your room by yourself and every time something happens to you in
The game you just like fucking stupid game sucks. Just you just under your breath
wait a minute snipers and
If somebody's like in the house and they hear you doing that it's like what's going on in there. What's wrong?
Yeah, I did this bit already. Just pretend I said it already
Okay, go bank run run out of time on this one the shamrock casino
Where you at?
Woodrow
Trying to like make a deposit
Hey
Hey, buddy, what the hell you think you're doing?
Prudency young man and just over one day's time the military would rescue us from all this perfectly good money
I am Woodrow Wutherford CEO and owner of one of the largest banks in state
We can't let the cash in these ATMs go to waste so you're gonna pocket it before anything happens
Well, no one else is and the yard is a bit small. I could really use another boat
Money is gonna be the least of your problems if a zombie gets you. Let me take you to the safe house
I will not let all this money go for nothing. That will be letting those zombies win
If you want to help follow me and keep those zombies off my back. That's right
I
Will you run it directly into him you're not trying to get away from them he's gonna get sniped
Oops, I caught you
Stop coming over here. Do your thing
Dude, do you a thing?
What is he doing?
What keep?
Is he running from me? No, I don't know what's happening. I'm not sure if he's running away from me or not
Hurry up son times wasting
Alright, keep those off of me
All right, open it open it do what you need to do. I
Keep hitting with my backswing
Okay, go on do go go go go do it
This one's done. Let's make a way to the next one. I don't have a weapon
I need weapon right now hungry son times away. So we're gonna fill our duty. This is the last one. We're almost done
He's gonna get sniped. He's gonna get sniped. No, we can't
Woodrow we can't go that way
Woodrow
wait
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die quick
What is gonna fire it I need they give me the briefcase
briefcase quick eat the lobster here fridge I
Have the briefcase go
Holy shit. Holy shit
This motherfuckers dead long legs of the law a woman in a police uniform is shacking up in hot
exciteramo
But if we have to go through the snipers, then they're just gonna get sniped kill the sniper. I mean if there's like four of them
Counter-snipe, that's not I was that's not gonna work. Oh
Don't nobody look at the screen. You're alright. I just play one in the peephole
Why do you get a bowling pin? I like to use props when I'm I like to go bowling
I'm really good at it. And that's why I always keep a bowling pin with me
Because I'm really good at getting strikes and stuff. Okay, can we have to keep having that? Can we talk?
Can we have another conversation? There's a book over there
Wait, what's this book? This isn't a rock. I meant to pick up the book get a 10% boost from
female survivor related activities, I
Guess we're doing that say no more. All right, I got you
Okay, I need
weapons and stuff
What the fuck is in here?
Good. All right. What about what's this bathroom? This is a secret way to go. Oh
Shit, okay. I need to go back over here. We have to deposit this person
either that or
All right, I'm wrong. I'm gonna start to run out of time. I need some weapons
How you doing on health? I'll just keep this in case you need it still let we say there's a maintenance room
But let's just check and see what they want us to do
What's in here?
Sheddy, okay, I can make the spear. I'm gonna do that. This counts as a
Weapon, right? This counts as a knife. How does this not count for the book?
I mean, that's on the way, but I yeah. Yeah, let's try it and
There's a point right there. All right
We're gonna go there
I'm gonna rescue those people. We're gonna go and then deposit
They're actually it
They're still alive
There really is plenty of time there is and I don't mean that in like a funny laugh out loud. Look plenty of time reference
Yeah, it's we just have to go this way
Debbie Debbie
No
Debbie
Go do I have to come here? You need this heal?
Stop. She's fucking out of her mind. She's gonna die. I
Have to give you a heal
Get over here and like there's a spot right here. Come here drink it. Let's go
You can do it. Let's move
What the fuck was that? I thought that was my I thought that was my machete
I was like my machete to shoot
Does she still I think I just got saved by the cutscene
This is why I was coming here the dumb look on my face
Shoot the detonator out of her hand
Games too quiet. Well, I turned it down because the cutscenes was so loud
Okay, don't move don't move
Aaron's sure
What do you need
Oh, no, I just get it what she needs that's funny, okay
uh
So what the hell is going on? What do you want?
Darling, my incompetent crew doesn't understand how exhausting it is to be a star
Uh bring me something to refresh me for the show
I'm parched
What are you waiting for? Okay. I've got
I'll get you a drink just stay there
All right. Stay here you stay here, too
A drink how do I know? Okay. I need a beer just a beer or something. There's a beer just probably lying on the ground
alcohol drink flashlight beer
Just a beer a beer
Does she fight back?
beer beer
They're just they're lying around fucking everywhere. I can't find one now
I'm just gonna have to go to like the bar. Where's the food thing?
She's not being attacked is she?
All right bar
Okay beer
Eat this pizza
Give me back my pole
Whiskey, uh smoke smoke. This is one. Maybe she wants pizza and shit, too
Oh, I hate this
Yeah
Get the fuck out of here
What is this? What is this? Not the erotic magazine. No
I have a give me the pizza
Put down one of these whiskies. Give me the magazine back. Give me my pole back
And get me the fuck out of here
I will say though. Let me tell you
The zombies in dead rising
Are the most unbearable to deal with in any zombie game and it's by design and it's actually pretty great
People are too scared
To like have the zombies actually hurt you
Here
Now what i'm not dressed for the this show. I cannot work under these conditions
Go spiff yourself up or this show is gonna end with a bang
What i'm dressed for the occasion. I look just like you
Go spiff yourself up. Oh, no, don't throw that. I want you to go here
I need to get a tuxedo
Come on, man. Where's the tuxedo when you need one?
a tuxedo
Is that one backstage?
There's no
Talk to alison
She went for shadow for anything with less than a tuxedo. Yeah
I think they carry them in the modern businessman in the royal flush plaza
I can't just
Throw this into her head
modern businessman modern businessman
modern businessman
Modern businessman modern businessman modern businessman modern businessman
It's actually pretty close
All right. So is deidre gonna stay? Well, just go backstage deidre. I don't want to put you in harm's way
She'll stay here, right?
She's gonna die
Will she just I have to take her
They only take damage if you leave them alone. God damn it, but hey eat a pizza to just
Come over here and eat this pizza
Eat it and i'm gonna give you a wrench
here
Let's go
Give me a fucking break
It's like honest to god
What a total fucking joke
And it's all gone
Uh
It's funny
It's kind of funny
Yeah, it's funny
Now i'm gonna take you back
Case five two needs to be done. You know what?
Fuck it. I don't care. I'm not gonna sit here you dumbass ai gonna walk into a zombie and die
Am I your man? Mr. Dumbass
Dumbass the name
is
Dumbass
That's pretty thick-headed
Same thing like an ice cold a and w root beer
She wouldn't even fucking she was not even fucking here with me was not even here. How is that possible?
It's not even possible
imbecile
I'm trying to feed her
You get grabbed more than anybody in the whole game
She's been grabbed like six times
It's like you're the only person that gets grabbed
heaven of the pineapple
All right, I need a tuxedo
Is that all I need?
Do I need like special shoes?
Take off the hat. How do I lose the hat?
I don't know how to lose the hat. Can I lose the hat?
No, I just got into college clothes
I can't take that off
I can do it backstage. Okay, good
Speed it up
Follow me
Oh, man, it's taken a lot to not do that to you
Okay
now
We just got to go right here
Let's go
Get grabbed get grabbed
Hi
You are mighty tasty. Can you feel it handsome?
It's almost time for the show
But where's my audience? Won't you round up some fans for the show?
fans
There's like five people here. That's all you're gonna get how many more?
Come on, let's go
Come on. Oh my adoring fans a few more and the show will begin. I know you can barely wait
Is that enough? Is there all here? Come on
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 3 I need like three more somebody's I need 15
Get a pic of her ass
You would want you would like that wouldn't you?
I did the thing. I did the thing you wanted. Okay
jeez christ
Get backstage
Start the show
All right
So drop the stage light on her head
The comeback tour everyone's waiting for the big number get a little angry if that happens listen lady
I love the voice of reason
I like that guy
Thing will give you instructions
Prepare yourself. Let's just chat
Come on man, just do it
so
What where am I?
What do I have to do?
Press a button circle
Oh, fuck. It's a rhythm game
The interest just danger don't get too close to the pyrotechnics. How was that wrong?
Is why how was that wrong?
What this did that?
Does not work correctly, but what the hell was going on there?
Why she
How did she just fly?
I pressed it. What the fuck?
Something not right here
Something's not right here
Is the frame right now? I don't think so
So then she gets eaten by her fans
Yep
This is how it ends
They start eating her and killing her and that's how it works and we get a really good picture
Wait, she's
Um, I need a better weapon than I don't want to accidentally kill her
Okay, so
Don't hit her
Wait darling you almost as incredible as moi. You are a true fan
I guess
Oh shit
Okay. Okay, she's joined the party
Everybody join the party everybody get up here. Get up here. Get up here, please
Oh
Okay, there's a lot of people we need to have a plan
Okay, I need a plan
Wait, this is important come backstage
We need to have everybody decked out and stuff. There's weapons and armor and shit here. Come here
You are you have a wrench here
Want to take this?
uh
I need any other weapons
Who wants the the toy set?
Give them all instruments
Okay, um
BB
You won't take it. Will anybody take this?
Into the uh into the room
Okay. Wait, can anybody take?
a
Uh, you need to have a whiskey uh, Deidre take the whiskey
Newspaper isn't it's it's something. Okay. No, give me that
It's something it's it's something it's at least something
Fuck. Okay. I need the leaf blower. Wee
Okay. All right. Are you guys ready?
Okay, we got it. Cameron is not doing so well off her shoulder
No
No, I can't
Oh
Let's go
Okay, there's a save point right here. We're gonna use it
Everyone's gonna fucking chill
Follow me
Let's go. Wait, what about food? What about food? No, there's no type of food. Yes. There is. There's nobody here
Shit food who needs some snacks
Okay, who needs a snack bb come take this snack
There's so many people there is managing a lot of fucking people
Okay. Now take the wrench back
Take this wrench take the wrench
Okay, Cameron
Let's go, let's go we gotta go come on
Okay, let's move
There's a lot of people here
a lot of people here
Uh case five two is gonna start
I
I have a million dollars, right?
It's gonna happen all over again calm down everybody make it
We are we're all here. I have the car though. Does that help me?
Shoulder, where are you?
No, we've just we don't have to go that far it's not far
It's here car
And then fuck it's gonna happen again
What are you holding a briefcase? Did we get everybody?
The car can only hold two. No, i'm talking i'm talking about after
Let's go
And then I got a hustle if anybody gets
And there are psychos now
please
Just are there snipers in here too?
Everyone's fine. Everyone's fine. We're almost there
Not much farther
You dickhead
Juan Juan, come on shake it off Juan
Shake it off Juan
No
Shake it off
Shake it off. Shake it off. Shake it off
You can do it. Shake it off. Come on Juan
Come on
Can't leave Juan behind
Oh
They run into my gun, why would you do that everybody's so stupid I killed him at the door
Oh my stomach
Okay, everyone's fine
Reset i'm not gonna reset
Oh, my throat is like fucking killing me right now
I don't I gotta go
I didn't fuck it up Deidre fucked it up because I
I didn't tell them to stay so she just
Ran in front of my gun and fell down when I shot her in the head and then
I closed the door and killed Juan with the door. It's
That's the way it falls
I'm not going back
I got hold on
Jesus that's fucking that was so funny
All right, I have to go now
But to be fair a psycho one of those guys had like a grenade in his hand
He was running straight for Juan. So I had to try to save him. Let's do I don't know
day three at
This one at 11 a.m. Oh, no, this one at yeah this one here
running into guns
You guys are so stupid
Why would you run into my gun? All right. Do I have enough to go up and get some healing?
I need to go to the uh, hold on
What's a cafeteria? What's the cafe?
right there
I have a headache
Shit
That was like two that was like too funny too quickly
Okay, let's move
I gotta go from here
Excuse me
I got the million dollars
Did you hear that burp? That was like a stress burp. All right
Uh, so I can do the shortcut
Right. The shortcut will bring me up there closer
Yeah, it will
So I should have time
So the shortcut is right here. Correct me if i'm wrong. Am I wrong the shortcut not right there?
It's wrong, which one is it?
I know it's right here somewhere right here
Just go the long way. Why would I go the long way? There's no time
It's the other bathroom
It's in royal flush
Oh, so it is in royal flush. Oh, so I had it right. Yeah, it's the men's room. Not the women's
Yeah, it's the right spot
My like my eyes hurt right now
Uh right at the very end
Yeah
I'm so disappointed
But it was too funny
Okay
We're good
Just have to give a million dollars
Tall guy
Well, will he be how long will he be around for
snow job
investigate the clown car
Well, that's right in front of me
um
I need to go there
Uh, it's just gonna automatically start
Just don't go to the clown car
Yeah, I gotta I have to do the case
This is not a plenty of time scenario. It's not
It's gonna move this way
Just get it done
I actually was full of actually was what I needed to do
okay
now this is not a case where the
the person's gonna be like
two fire axes
This is gonna be a scenario where the person's like, oh you brought the money, but it wasn't enough. It's 1.2 million
I wanted to pick up the beer
She's not my girlfriend stop
Idiot leave me alone. Not my girlfriend knife. Where's rebecca? It's a sword
Appreciate all your interference
You really need to learn some business you secure them talk that idiot protester. I'm too dumb to know you're behind me
Yeah, actually i'm i'm smart
Too bad. She couldn't just take our tape and leave it at that
Do I have to fight two people at the same time?
How many shots do I have my sniper rifle? This is not going to be fun
I always saw you more as a strong silent type. I have a fire axe
A coffee pot and a sniper rifle. I don't know how to use this is gonna go very well
Wait, I have the I have the
No, they tag out. What was that move? I wish I had a sword
Where's the other one?
fuck
What a terrible heal
Holy crap. Why do you guys get to do this shit at the city to get butt picks?
Uh, I think something's way more
Important than that and that's not dying
Is it like guns back here? There's a lot of beers. I don't read like dirty magazines right now. Where's she?
Holy shit
I can't stop throwing up, but I need to heal
What's wrong with my run? Am I right? Am I stuck on like an invisible thing?
No, not next to the how do I stop on her?
How do I step on her head?
No, i'm in trouble
Am I
I need my fire axe
You're the fire axe back
Okay, just do some dodging as long as I get rid of one of them. Oh, that was bad. Fuck you
I don't know what i'm trying to say. I'm trying to say i'm okay for now
Almost one down. Come on. Where are you going? That was terrible. They didn't do anything one more get out of my way
One down is what is that it this is not like an ornstein smog scenario, right?
Like she's not gonna get huge and start lightning abilities
It really is that scenario, isn't it here comes phase two well that was easy
We got a story to cover
I don't think she did the power up, right? I don't think so either
Wrong sword
We need to catch them chopper
Are you kidding me?
Take take pick
The next case will occur at 7 pm
Save it. It's for points
Oh, look at all this time I got and we have
not one
but two katana swords
and
we're gonna get a
I'm gonna get
All right, can I take the sword out? That looks like a good sword. Can I take it out of her chest?
I don't think so
Let me make sure I have everything that I need
We're good. What is that? Whip cream battery money
What do I have the heels pretty much nothing I need some more heels, uh replace the machete with the vodka
and
What's this?
edge weapons, right?
This is always good
Uh erotic magazine. Um
Just leave it. What am I here?
All right
Now we have fetching females
Investigate the grotto. That's kind of like right here, isn't it? And then snow job is down there
Kind of annoying that I lose the money and they still tried to fucking kill me
Let's go sword no stand
Dude this is my favorite music for every recent
top-down spaceship galaga type shooter
the waves of enemies
And by the way, it's every level. Hope you like that song. I can't slide down
Okay, save point. Hmm. Ah, there's one behind me. Ah, I did just save it though, didn't I?
Confirm with me, please that I just saved the game like 15 seconds ago
I did right?
Yep. Thank you
This way that's a pretty cool move for that weapon
And I have the book with it. So it'll last a long time
Okay sports town
Huh? Am I gonna beat this tonight? I'm gonna try
What's the deal? Is it upstairs?
Okay, there's nina kora and summer
Wow, you're a lot cuter than those zombies
Honey, don't mind if i'm a little forward, but are you single?
I'd love to get to know you a little more intimately. What's going on?
I is am I sure this is not like I opened up like a like a vr pornography video game
Thank you guys are always coming after me. They're not like this
You had better come with me back to the safe house
We'd like to sugar but we aren't just any girls
Our time is money and we don't go any with anyone without settling the bill first
Everyone wants money
Ten thousand dollars and we're all yours. We won't move for a dime less baby. You know, you want to
Are you all are you capable?
I don't want to give somebody a katana. This is all very very good stuff here
Here you take the you take the axe
I don't want to give you like one of these something else like a super sucker or something
Oh, there's a slide
Use the slide
Ready?
Whoa, that was really fun
All right, let's get them back
So I need to go upstairs into the short cut
Yeah, huh? Yeah, that sounds like a plan. We're gonna go up to the shortcut
That's his real voice maybe take pick take pick a bump
Make it make it make it make it just walk forward and make it move
Break it off. Break it off. Break it off. Break it off. Break it off. Break it off
Break it off
They're not breaking it off
The bolt is dead
I like seriously
That strategy sucks like 30 to 40 percent of the time
And they they need weapons. No, they don't I've had so happy people run forward before and not have to have a weapon to get out
Excuses excuses and come down here and get a weapon. I can't promise it'll be a good weapon, but it'll be something here
um, i'll give
I'll give you a
um
Okay, how about
Who wants a?
um chainsaw
Here you go. Nina. This this has got your name all over it. She won't take the chainsaw
I'll take the chainsaw and i'm gonna get rid of
Painkiller any more vodkas I can use melon and uh something else
melon and cocktail
Stay over there give her some whipped cream
maybe I need another drink a beer and
This cocktail just sitting on the table right there
I can make another one
That's actually all I can take
randomizer
Okay
Listen up go over there
So go, um, I hate to do this but seriously
It's a it's a weapon
And the whipped cream container come here. You won't take it. I think it's kind of fun to use
All right. Well, whatever. I don't want to get you take the super soaker
Will you take this?
Okay, good now we're ready
Not that hard to go now
We just have to go upstairs
Follow me the chainsaw boomer get the chainsaw boomer
This way up
Up
In verb noun verb verb adjective the mad live streamer
Just fill in a random fucking word every four minutes
Now now as an adverb not an adjective ready
Yeah, get mad get mad
Okay, let's go
Just have to deposit you guys into the you know, where to go
All right, yeah
I went the wrong way. It's okay. Just saved it in case something bad happens
Mad because bald mad because bald
Mad because bald mad because bald bald bald bald bald
Hey, if you guys are bald
So a recent movie came bald
I just got a new pair of sneakers. Anyone have reckoned bald
I I got hit by a bus this morning. It was really bald
Oh, you ever need protection again, look us up. We're the book under guardian angel's personal security
Well, you don't didn't do a very good job
the defiler
sledgehammer and fire axe
I kind of need that
a sledgehammer and a fire axe
I'm thinking that's a good one
Does that count as a blunt or a sharp weapon? Well, I got a pretty good setup here
so the getaway
Stop tk's escape in the fortune city hotel rooftop. I have to stop him. How many cases are in this?
only one
so
I this probably takes a while
But there's only one case here
Do I have enough time to do this snow job? Let's find out. I need a fire axe and a sledgehammer
But I ain't gonna get it
He's not that far I could get in the car and just drive down
Where's that car? I always forget. I always forget where the car is
Dumb brain of mine
We want face cam
No, that's all right. All right now. I think you guys will be all right. You'll manage
It was an hour face cam
Okay, I will turn the face cam on
for
15 minutes
if
It's a big if
Uh, all right, so i'm gonna get in the car
if
You guys are all really really nice
I'm talking
You guys need to
Just realize that this car sucks. Well, there's a reason to take the car because I don't want to get sniped
I could have just walked to the left and opened the door. I know i'm realizing that now. Don't worry
Wait, don't just I don't need to go that fast. This is tons of time
I can't read like
I can't even read some of these comments
Okay, no sniping
Bang, right
And wait, I could get in the
motorcycle
right
Where is that motorcycle? It's over here somewhere
Where's the clown car? There's a bike right here. There's a clown car on a bike
Okay. Well, it's gonna just start. I would like some ice cream
There's a little clown clown family
She's in the third game
Okay
Motorcycle I had an opportunity for a cool pp bonus
See if I can get it now, let's see if I can get it I want to get a good picture
I got time for a good photo
Is that not gonna even hurt me?
Drive into him. He's too tall. He's actually too tall. I gotta throw shit at him
Can I knock him over?
What's this one do?
I think I just have to bash him
rocket
I'm taking 50 less damage. That's pretty great
All right. Let me try one of the other weapons fountain firework eat this
I bounced off of that stupid zombie's head
It was ice cream on the ground though. I kind of want to eat it. Oh, no, does this is this a
Yeah, I just got humiliated
Get out of the fucking way get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way
Oh
Fuck. Oh my god
I wonder if something up here I can use
Have you tried a gun? I don't have any guns. I have a power drill. What about the car? I can't get in the car
Throw shit at him
And he freezes you like this
Annoying
Do anything
I guess I could just run into him and then run away
Nope, that's not gonna work. I'm dead get on your own stilts. That would be great
Dude, if I could like activate a fucking city wide fucking zombie detonation
These motherfuckers just are in the way always
Like I wish I could just delete the zombies from the boss fights
You have it but no i'm talking about the entire thing like all game whole game every game
I'm just throwing benches at this guy
This is so stupid
Jumping and swinging the sword was good
Well until until all these zombies surrounded me
No
Randomizer. All right. Well, it's a puke
If I had the rifle I'd shoot in the head
Okay, if I keep throwing up man, yeah, it doesn't stop. It doesn't stop. It doesn't stop
I can't it's always puking. I'm always throwing up
What?
It hasn't done the full animation yet. So I I keep getting stuck
Oh my goodness
I fucking hate this fight. I hate this fight
I hate this fight
die
Revenant too cold too cold. I leaned down just stuck going
I'll save you
Let's go. I need to save this game before it gets too late straight ahead
My katana that's right ahead, too
car has a butt
Yeah kind of goes
You drove back for a sword but not for one
The sword was useful
All right, we're just turning around and going straight get a pick up the ass. All right
I'll take a pick up but I will take a pick up the flounder
I promise
I missed the turn god damn it
Wait, it's just in there
Just in here
Wait, where the fuck does this want me to go?
I can't get in this for here. I don't know. Whatever. That's not erotica. No time until the military arrives
Who is this people firing guns?
Oh god, what the fuck is happening?
Is this clown going to do anything?
Mid-dive is there
Ah
What a pain in the ass watch out for the guy in the elevator ding dong. Here he is. I couldn't even aim
Get the fuck away from me
Somebody else threw him
She just gets like
No, it's just like blood. I'm sorry. I gotta settle down. I'm like it you sound stressed
It's very stressful
Now reel it in we're just sitting here. Oh you why don't you go somebody unhook it?
Just pull back a little and somebody lift it up. Shoot the pilot shoot my god
Spotlight
Shining in his face
No, uh pull it
In the blades. Oh, come on
Wow. All right, I don't have any heels
military
Military cases that's not a checkpoint. I have to do this again. I hate this part
It's just guaranteed to lose if you get in the middle here like it's a guarantee
Eat food from the trash. No, then I throw up and then I get obliterated
They're all dying up there you gotta die down here man, is there any food here?
All right, we're gonna get our puke and over with this way behind the counter trash
All right. There's lots of food back here. Actually, I can keep a soda
And now it's right. Okay. There's a coffee creamer
I don't even need the guns because they're just a kind of a waste of time at this point
Because i'm just gonna throw shit at them
so
Let's move. All right. What if I walk in and walk out of here?
Will that reset the the if I walk in and walk out?
That doesn't work. All right, let's go
It just fails the mission damn
Military case comes back
Oh my god, he's a lightning gun. These are just lasers
Fuck I gotta bring these things over
Oh my god
Please don't lightning gun be the military case. It takes too long to pick those up
I'm just
Fucking god
I was gonna say how dare you?
The snowball gun's not gonna do anything
Here comes the lightning gun
Oh, my eyes are itchy
Okay, so military cases bait. There's no reason to pick those up
Just pick up the stupid cones
And spotlights that's it the military cases of bait
That's death that's death
How are you alive from that you're alive from that the military cases have rocket launchers in them
I am I being lied to
Nice invincibility frames. That's dog shit
I can't swing the sword. I was just unlocked
Oh my goodness
I'm just gonna throw plants at you
Give me a break
And he's alive
You got hit twice with a katana and you don't even have armor on
Hit him right in the fucking head
Let's use the snowball gun. Okay, i'm gonna do that just so you can see how wrong it is
Oh man
Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man
How did the second swing not hit him?
You die so fast with the bullets. I know it sucks. I'm just gonna stand here
Stuck in the fucking wall
It's a wash it's a wash
How did it work the other times? I got lucky
It's five guys with assault rifles versus the dickhead with the crown on and a katana in his hand
I'm not gonna kill him with a fucking coffee. What are you thinking?
It's another one
You even know i'm there before you shoot fuck you
Get out of here. That's such bullshit
Use this if next person says use the snowball gun ban him for life
Uh, okay. I got one shot at this
I'm just gonna eat the fries get full health
Uh, i'm i'm gonna bring some items with me, you know, like fuck it drop the snowball gun
It works on zombies put the coffee down bring a computer
Computer case i'm just gonna bring a bunch of keyboards
Get grab the scissors
Grab the computer
Okay, can't bring the computer. What what can I store like what can I store like in my ass wherever it is?
And i'm just gonna throw this shit on. All right. What about the briefcase? Okay, take keep the briefcase
What is this domestic magazine?
Furniture items have much more durability that don't matter. Give me the briefcase
Okay, i've got a bunch of fucking household items that are gonna throw out this guy
flying around in a plane
Pick up this other suitcase too. Fuck it. I don't care. I can make that dumb thing
All right, I got only household items. Here we go. I thought he's gonna do the laser
Oh my god
Fuck you
Ah, I missed the computer
He's gonna fire
You've got to be kidding me. That was stupid. It slowed down to hit me. It slowed down to hit me
It was aiming slowed down to hit me
All right, here comes the fire
He's held the button down longer that time god, where is he give me a fucking gun
Yeah, yeah, that's what you get. That's what you get. Somebody told me to walk out and walk back in
It's gonna fail the mission
If this fails the mission i'm gonna be very very bad
Don't you dare
Why did you guys lie to me? Why would you lie to me?
This part is so stressful. And why would you lie to me?
I have to don't have to do this anymore. What's with the lies? What's with the lies?
All right household item
suitcases
Forget about guns
Who cares about guns?
Small stands and and briefcases and computers
What else can I grab? Like how many would have got two briefcases? I need this. There's another uh,
Where's the other keyboard?
And bring one soda. Now, where's the other keyboard?
No, one coffee creamer
Okay, get rid of one of the katanas. No, keep the katana get rid of the yep. Okay
The keyboard is right here
I have to drop a katana
Which one's the one that's gonna break?
No, this would be all right. This is fine
And a soda that i gotta get a soda from here. No, not a handgun
No, no, no, I got a coffee creamer. I'm good. Okay, let's try this again
I'm just gonna run but if I run too far away when the lightning gun happens
I get hit by the blades from the rotor
Oh, no
Who knows the katanas not the katanas
Not the katanas
Not anything with the katanas, man
Don't do them all
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay
What why am I running in the line of fire to try to run backwards though the it takes a turn down in the
It'll get hit i'll get hit in the face by the helicopter
No, that that sucked
And you know what made that suck?
the fact
That I was baited and lied to I was beating and bruised and brought down to my last second
Everyone told me I was gonna fail the mission. He would be beating me down and bruising me, but I came back and I persevered
What's he doing here isn't he the host of that show
Tk paid some pathetic protester to start this whole thing
Ratings were down on his show
He needed the cash
We've got enough to run with the story. I love this game. Oh, really?
Well, i'm still keeping an eye on your friend until the rescue just to make sure
I love
This game and I hate this game at the same time. It's award material. Oh, yeah
He's out cold
We ought to make sure he stays that way don't hit him too hard. So
Why capital punishment was made for a guy like this?
That's true love
That's the natural feeling chief yeah, I do really like it though I like both these games listen i'll be back for the rescue
They're fantastic. I'm gonna go see if I can find a high vantage point and some pictures of them
There's more to this case now. Okay, the hail mary is a football and a grenade
case number seven
9 a.m
And I got my money back
Yeah, okay
so
Uh, I need I have I have two zombricks. So i'm good in that department
Here's a computer keyboard. I'm gonna get rid of it axe
And I need to find a sledgehammer
sledgehammer
Wait, there are slots down here
That's like a family guy slot machine
Are these rigged to lose? I don't think these can win. I think they're unwinnable. That's fine. All right
uh
I don't know who just said that but um
relax
All right, I can do bent wood family feud
I also need to deal with the snipers
Wait listen to lose his proposition
The golf the golf pro that I saved
um
Yeah, let's do that
That sounds interesting. I mean that's just a continuation of her quest line
Let's check it out. I'm actually in the cafeteria
All right, what's going on here?
How you doing?
I lost my favorite club. How can I practice for the tour? I feel practically naked without it
Sorry to hear that
Could you fetch a new golf club? I spotted some real nice ones in the sports shops
I'm, not sure. I want to risk my neck for a golf club. No
Fuck
I've got some cash tucked away in a surprising in surprising places. You could get that club. I'll give you a real nice reward
uh golf club
Where's there a good sporting goods store?
clothing
travel sport goods
All right, let's do it. Have you tried rolling a seven to craps?
Uh, I have no i've tried rolling the dice
Uh, I feel so happy right now
And I don't have to do
the fucking
Machine gun corridor again
Sledgehammer? Sledgehammer? Sledgehammer?
No
Sledgehammer?
I know there's one lying around somewhere
Oh, I thought that I thought that was it was a big green one. I was like nice
Why are your face cam commands not working? Oh the bot must be like messed up or something. Sorry
Where's the hammer? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
There it is
Okay
Let's go. What are these magazines?
It's time for the defiler
Sludge and axe. Yes
Okay, this thing's pretty cool
This is pretty cool. All right, don't
I can store it too. That's it makes it even better
Cool. All right, let's get the
Uh
The thing we need to get
Into the sporting good shot
The weapon is insane
I'm gonna hold on. I have the combo card for it, right? So that means it's better
It's not just shitty
Get more. Yeah, I get more pp for it. Yeah, that's cool
All right, let's get a golf club
Foot wait football
and what was
Yes
All right football and I need a golf club golf club
No golf club
Golf there is golf
Casino cup, what is wait?
What is this?
Okay, so just
I got it. That's not good enough
All in one
I just want ten thousand dollars and I get to keep the club
No, I don't get to keep the club. Hold on do it again
Just steal it
And when he's gambling we can use golf
10 grand
And a pp bonus let's do whole this is going to be very very hard
Hard that's in there you bet your ass it is
Just barely short. I just need one more
Oh
Too early. I got one
Oh, I did it. I actually just I
Leave me alone. There's a golf club right here
golf club
All right bent wood
Bring it back
cool
Don't break it. He was only watching. Well, leave me alone
How would you just be standing breathing on me? Your breath stinks
Run with the football
Go long
All right. Now pick it up and pretend that you catch it
Why am I getting minus twos for this? I'm just i'm fulfilling a chat request
He did it for the fans. I did it for the fans
Now what's what's going on here here? I brought you something
Thanks frank. Now I can get the practice. I need to make those other girls on the tour feel my wrath
Okay, um easy
What do I get for this?
Five thousand and a new skill
60 000 p that's a lot
Now, what do you need?
Between zombies in the military. There's like a terrible danger. Have we not found clothes for you?
We have to like save the fortuna aspid
It's a small plant that only grows in the fortune city. But do you don't you know anything?
I know a local artist that used it in his pieces
I'm sure it's at the clero collection in the palisades mall
I came here to get it and plant it to make sure that this is the wonderful piece of flora lives on
Not sure if I would risk my life for a plant maybe I will
You wouldn't risk our ecosystem
Okay, green plant used in peace art. I saw some in the clero collection
All right
I won't be doing that one world's most dangerous trick
Investigate the stage. It looks like someone's performing tricks by the stage in the atlantica casino
This is the
botany thing
Help the girl on the roof family feud
Uh, we'll do this trick one first
Let me save it. We want tricks. We want tricks. I'm gonna give it to you
Don't worry. You want tricks? I'm gonna give it to you
Good answer. Good answer. Good answer
15 minutes of face cam rage 15 minutes of face cam rage face
Where's my 15 minutes of face cam?
rage
Where is my face cam?
I'm only here for one reason and one reason only
It's to see
your face
on camera
And that's it. There's no other reason why i'm here
Now get it on there
Okay, god damn it
Just don't just slow down
There we go. That's what I like
I like the feet. Okay. I'm not gonna keep going with that one. That's not a good one to do. All right way
Most dangerous trick me save the game. Uh snipers are out here
Fuck
That would hurt way more I think than a a knife. I don't know why I just think like the keyboard to the head is like
worse somehow
Where are the snipers?
There's they're like right here somewhere. Okay, hold on
Can I get in there without dying?
Plastic keyboard. Well, some of these keyboards weigh like fucking 25 pounds
What do you mean? No, what do you mean? No?
What do you mean? No
Go chat
chat
We're gonna have a little fight here chat chat. Do you guys like being referred to as chat?
Now listen chat chat chat. Hey chat
Do you?
What did I drop for this?
Uh, the rake is the best weapon in the game. Why did I not have this?
Term i'm laughing too loudly. It's 3 a.m. Stop being so funny
I'm gonna get you in trouble
It's my job for the rest of the stream to get you in trouble
I still haven't even picked up a treasure chest. What am I thinking?
Okay, that person's dead. So you try to tell me that's not as bad as getting stabbed
That was like a that was like a corsair vengeance
I want to get I want to open the chest
What's in it?
a hundred dollars what a waste
All right. Did I save the game like I was trying to?
chat
As I deserve
Don't you see this is finally my chance. I mean our chance
Go you imbecile get ready for the next trick. This guy gets it
Just surrounded by idiots imbeciles all around me
I'm rep I said this before during like this is a callback
Are you just paying attention?
chat
I don't have a chance to stop that
I do actually, uh, so there's two there's two people that are in either side one of them is contorting their body
Lying down flat where the feet come out the bottom part. I'm gonna ruin this for you guys
What you don't want me to tell you?
It does the feet are lying down on a lower platform
So when it pulls apart, they're actually underneath lying down curled up and they stick their feet out and then it's two people
got it
What is this music this guy's hiding
Watch the back. He's coming around the back. Damn it. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh my god
Oh my god
I need food
Food something food something to eat anything to eat anybody got some food around here on the boat
There's gonna be beer on the boat, right? It's like
Can I eat this?
I can't eat the swordfish
In here, where is it? Where's the beer? Where's the beer? Is it coffee creamers and a gun?
Get that cocktail
Okay
This top this shit loads of beer in here
Say i'm gonna replace the
Uh the rake
I'm gonna replace the that's good. No, that's good. That's good. That's good. That's good for now
I can come back in here take the gun out here
Where'd they go? I'm part of the song roger shot. Wow. This is ultimate. I'm so glad I didn't get hit by that
Pick up the gun. What are you doing, man?
All right, that's fine
Ammo guns, where's uh, where's what's his name roger? There he is. Let's go
bye
Tunk just the ranged one. Where is he now?
Everybody see him. Where'd he go?
Uh, is he in here?
Behind there he is
All right
Don't get shot point blank
Drink don't fire that gun
Oh fuck
Okay, i'm gonna have to go back here and drink
Fire over here. Shit. He just dodged that by doing a bow
Wait for the puke wait for the puke. It's gonna happen again
Okay, let's get in
No, he just cast a spell on me. That does a lot of damage. Don't get cocky. Oh my god. Just get another drink
One more just hit him one more time just hit him one more time. I can't take the photo that was intense
I don't know why that made me laugh so hard
So he said you're gonna be shitting blood why because i'm drinking like a bunch of cocktails
It was four beers
Okay, I can make a rocket launcher now
Pretty decent pp. Let's see if we can get a should we get like a photo of this?
Magician sword cool and a rocket launcher
Oh boy
This looks like it's gonna be fun
Okay, now I can pick up the stuff on the table that I want to pick up
All right. Where's the feud? Oh shit. Oh, no, he's shitting blood
Uh, I can take one more heal
No, I can't
Let's go. All right. Where's the feud?
family feud is
Is that family feud? Where's the actual case back at the?
Rescue should be arriving soon when the time comes the royal flush rooftop should be great to capture all the military action
so i've got
Not that long to get into there, but that's when it starts
Let's see if I can get into family feud
Okay, and let's go
See if I can get there. Yeah, you need to be there for that when the time goes down
I need to save point. Uh, actually this is a point right here
Although the snipers are still up there, right?
Can I get across?
I wonder if I can get across
Blast him with the rockets
Where do I end up here? I think
I should as long as I stay
I
Okay, i'm gonna hug the wall here
If I get shot once when he takes on bricks
It's all right as long as I don't get in the open
Oh my god, there's a I didn't know that was gonna happen a lot of pp
Oh, yeah, let that go to waste
Okay, I made it just unload not with 85 of this thing
I'm not gonna unload
If I die because of this shit
It's it's it's gonna stick into the same motherfucker
Family feud ding no
It hits the first zombie it touches and it explodes
There is no what just spam it. It'll explode in front of me. Don't you understand?
Don't you know you can't aim this fucking thing. It's gonna hit the first person in front of you
And then it goes
Okay, so family feud just don't get hit. I know seriously
Just just don't take damage
If this is hard that is all going off the roof
Why didn't I listen to her don't shoot me? I can help you. I'm looking for my mother
All right, we're gonna find the mother
Did you see where she went?
food court
All right. Well, we gotta go
Stay here and take your finger off the trigger if she's alive. I'll find her
Okay. Goodbye
Headed to the food court
I gotta get up to that roof
That's when it starts. I wonder if I can get up. Can I do this?
I hope so
Man, I love this game. I know
It's very good. All right food court
That's pretty damn far away
I'm gonna have to lose the rocket launcher and get in the car
I gotta get my use out of this thing. I'm almost a little 27
Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it
Get a blow. Help me
Let's go
This thing's really slow
Okay, but I can wear the snipers if I just get her in the car
Wait, what's going on? She's in here. The snipers are gone. Okay. Thank you for telling me
I don't have time. I have to go to the k7. I'm sorry grandma. You're dead
That's just the way it is
9 a.m. That's I mean that's the way it is
Sorry
But I I have to get over there and I have to bring her all the way back and that's just not gonna fucking happen
It's been a while since I've saved the damn game evil. It's a zombie
See
She's in another plane now
I'm in time
I'm not gonna let this go to shit again. What?
Oh the it's the roof right?
Free soda. I'll take it and a hot dog
Okay, I don't need it yet
But oh
Hold on just a second here
Where's my football?
Shit
Wait, can I do wait?
No, what is it? It's a lead pipe and what is it?
Fireworks, right? Stay right there. I'm gonna go get fireworks. I think this is the other some right here
I got my weapon back only 75 though
Is it the same weapon? I think it is
All right
rooftop
Let's go
I am ready
I have dynamite
I have one bottle of whiskey
Any food is bacon here, but the bacon sucks. It heals like one or two
Just testing it pick it up so I don't lose it in the cutscene
Follow the arrows
Uh, what are you doing there? What's here?
Follow the arrows dude. What are you doing?
Wasting time. I have like 12. I have like less than 15 17 16, whatever minutes. I ain't going anywhere
Make the machete copper. I'm going anywhere
Could have saved mom
No, because I would have had to put mom in the wheelchair
And here's what would have happened
Come on, please, please
Wait, no, no, get in get in get in. No, no, no, no, no, no how much time?
I would have brought her back. I would have happened like 12 times in a row
I'm relaxing right now
Just chilling and then I would have got her back
Completed. Oh, thank god. Wait, look at seven one. Oh, no, no, no, no. No, I got it wrong. Give me back
Wait, no, what the fuck was I thinking? Why did I do this?
I'm secure and I ain't going anywhere think of all that stress that yeah, that's not here right now
It's just me
and you
And case seven point one just think of the amount of oh my fucking gods that you're not gonna hear
I'm doing this for you. They're actually called goons
Well, this is now military. So now we have do we have goons and military or no?
This is the guy from the first game that I spit on
Are you sure?
You didn't take the lens cap off rebecca how are we ever gonna prove this all in court and wait, there's a gas now
Oh, no, it's gonna get like special infected now
This is bad this is not gonna be good
Look out this is the gremlin that drank the vegetable potion in gremlins 2
Otherwise, he not
Do you feel like a hero?
Okay
Case seven two case seven two engaged
Let's go military rescue backfired now rebecca's in danger out there
Save it
Oh here comes in. Oh my fucking god
jesus
Uh, do you think so?
I don't think so
time until fire bomb
I actually have a lot of time to do this
Family feud, let's go
Oh fuck. Uh
Where's where is rebecca? I could do it, but barely. Um
Not even hard just carry around this thing
Where am I going back in here?
Is the whole thing gas everything is gassed
Nothing happens if I touch it. I missed the
Why would you dodge roll? I lost my fire. I lost my crutch
No, I didn't
Is the fucking thing gonna detonate?
Um, excuse me
Excuse me game
Excuse me. It's spinning like crazy
Oh my fucking god
You have to wiggle the stick
Yes
Just run
Have I been spinning it this whole time? No, I was wiggling it all over the place
I was going left right left right left right left left left left left left left left left left left left right
You can like hear it
You guys been over here like the clanging
All right grandma. Let's go
It's not even grandma
Thank god you found me. I had an argument with my daughter and
Actually, I saw your daughter on the hotel rooftop and she's got a gun i'm worried she might do something
But I can't I can take you there
She was always such a tomboy. I never did play with dolls, please. Okay, sure
Sounds like a plan. Let's go level up
If I have to carry you just be aware
That i'm not doing that
You've got a weapon
Do I have to carry you?
What is going on?
Are you gonna leave the store?
Okay, good. Let's move
I'm scared
We have to go down this one. We just do
There's a queen there, but fuck it
and
Come on. What the fuck?
Uh, she's too far away. Oh my oh my god
That's like did I really have to be right? Like can they just can you open the fucking door?
Sir, this is about to fail
Uh
Scream
Give me my toy
Come on
Where are you going?
You are so slow
You're killing me
Oh, i'm so glad you're safe
Okay, hurry up and make up and then hug
game do a hug
Hug good
We're hugged where everyone is fine. Everyone's having a good time good
Thank you so much for saving my mom. I'm very you're very welcome skip. We're not that we need to go back to the safe house skip
epic
That was really close
It was also made closer by the fact that when I was about to take the photo
I've right triggered and uh left triggered and almost shot them with the rocket launcher
It was that almost happened. I'm very glad it didn't
Let's hustle it up
Heal them
I don't have anything to heal them with is there whiskey lying around?
Isn't there whiskey over here somewhere?
Wait, what's in the military cases?
It was a lie
Trying to get rid of dynamite
Heal them with dynamite. Wait
Here we go. No, not the fucking patio table
magic tricks
It's it's always funny
You need a weapon. Okay, take this take the pipe
You have a gun you have a shotgun. So you're all right
All right, let's bring you guys back
There is a short sighted talk to the confused lady
Let's go for it
That's not far
straight left save
I want to make this fucking impossible
To have us lose
Sorry, just leave it leave it. Leave it. I don't need it. Leave it. I don't even
Trying to clear it i'm trying to do my best into the bathroom
Oh, I heard a scream
Don't save over this one. I need level. Which one is it?
9 a.m
4 a.m on day four. I think I want to keep safe
I panicked
Let's go. Oh, no
Good hold the attack. I am I don't have whatever it is you're describing holding attack see
Oh, I do have it. I'm an idiot liar stupid
He's broken. Lillian white. What's wrong with Lillian? What's Lillian doing Lillian? Is she all right? I just don't move
Nobody touch anything
Lady, don't be scared. Oh finally a clerk. I came here to get my grandbaby a present but on my way
All these young hooligans kept fighting me
Then when I enter here, no one comes to help me for shame
Don't think I won't tell your manager young man
Uh lady, there are zombies everywhere. I have to get you out of here now
It's a real boomer. That's right. I need to I i'm gonna die
I have one hit and i'm dead
catch more flies with this
lady we
Tut tut young man. What did I just say about flies and honey? The zombies are not toys. They're real zombies
There's been an accident
Camille is like, oh, there's somebody over here
nice
You young people constantly dilly-dallying when something important is going on
Mm-hmm. I'm a little too old to hurry my bunions keep
Ah, you're killing me here lady. You really are and I have to carry her
And no health either
Zero my god, there's orange juice in the back
Serious any more are any more food?
Lillian's screaming downstairs
onion rings
Mask on the shelves
Here we go
Move it or lose it. I gotta get down
The stairs meet up with lillian. We're going for it. We're going for it
I can't I can't go for it. I can't go for it. I have to I was gonna jump down the stairs
Wait, I I I I I we're already are we're already there
carrying people
Down. All right. Everything's good
Oh my god, I just ate so much damage
What happened to my head?
Didn't I have a cool helmet on?
Lillian's gonna die. Maybe she'll shake it off. She has a weapon
Come on lillian. You can do it lillian breakout lillian. You can do it
You gotta be kidding me
This fucking old bitch just ruined everything
and you weren't even
I'm so disappointed
I don't even I don't even think I have a checkpoint
Just 98 years old. No, you're not
When was it's too late?
It's like
What am I gonna reload it?
You reload it and just leave her
Should I just reload it? How far away was it? Does anybody remember?
Did I have them all together? It's not that far
Let me see
It was pretty close. It's not far
Let's do it
Which one of these was it?
it was
8 11
10 40 a.m
I think it was yeah, this one. That's the has to be this one
He sounds so defeated. He sounds very german pluto. All right, so I have
Okay
I don't give a shit about the old lady
We're bringing the original tube back
Is it a waste of time?
But what about the orange juice? Well here it's the way that they're in range
What about the orange juice?
I'll just clear a path you hear stay with me. Lillian stay with me
She's really far away. Oh, come on. I'm trying to look and see where she is
They don't give you a moment's rest. There's not a moment's time
I can't even look over my shoulder
All right, I had the checkpoint because I came in this door. Whatever. I'm not gonna take a hit writer
Okay. Now I got a good checkpoint. If they both make it in if not, then that's very very very good
Let's try this again
Get in
All right, come this way. I'm just gonna make sure she gets over here. I mean, this is not a bad strategy
Am I going the wrong way?
No, it's good. I didn't change this. Okay
I am going the wrong way
No, i'm not the gps sucks
Stay with me, Lillian
Stay with me
All right
The same fucking person. It's like it's it's it's bullshit
Lillian you good?
All right, two is better than one. I don't care about grandma. It's like a carrying people around
What is it now?
Now I don't want to care like if I wish you know what I wish you could do in this game
I wish if I brought somebody up there that was able bodied that they could carry them. You deserve a reward
combo card
Go carry granny to the car right now and then drive
I'm gonna save it. What's the card?
defib in medical tray
Go get granny
All right. I will attempt it once
Thank god for the inventory increase. Yeah, that's really good
Short-sighted let's go get her my good weapons almost done
Nice dodge comes to grab here comes to grab
All right, get the car. I'm gonna bring the car
Uh go get the car
I'm losing my mind. Okay, get the car car and then put grammy grammy in the car
98 is not a boomer
No, 98. What is what was before boomer?
that's like
red dead redemption
It's like
Those aren't boomers
Those are wild west
All right granny, let's go
I'm here for you
this thing
How do you drive this car?
Seriously, the thing is on ice skates
Hello
Don't be scared. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Skip skip skip skip skip skip skip
Hurry up ester you hundred year old
dust bag
Orange juice let's get in the car. Let's get the hell out of here. Oh don't die. There's a lot of people on there
I gotta go the other way
fuck
They're too fast. They're too fast. They're too fast
All right granny, let's go
I feel like i'm not driving the car
What is this driving?
Thank you kind man. Yes, you're very welcome granny
30,000p that leaves me with nothing else to do
Except to go get to level 29
Enjoy the next two days of your 98 year long life. Yeah, go right to the next case. I what about zombrex?
I feel like I need more
Next case like just immediately let's go
That was a good one. Some of you guys are funny
Very funny. Yeah, because case seven. This is gonna last a long time. I still have some decent weapons. I wish I had uh, yeah
Uh, I guess I could make another one of these
Not creative. I'm not trying to be creative trying to win
Let's let's hammer in here
Yeah, but I know there's a sludge hammer in here, but yeah, I know and i'm gonna get another axe
I'll grab an axe
And i'll make another one of these once I find another axe
What is this?
Okay
Doesn't look bad. Yell if you see an axe because I need it. I have a lot of money, too
I could buy zombrex if I needed to
I got one in my hand. I got one in my hand, but
I'm talking about a regular axe
way
Well, it's gonna be this all over again
Here's the maintenance tunnel
Maybe an axe
There's a spear
machete and
oh
Ah
I got a little bit of time
handgun
drill and spear
Does it work?
Oh damn
the driller
That's actually kind of cool. Okay
Uh, i'm gonna drop i'm gonna leave the defiler because it's done. It's toast anyways
broom and gun
That's right
You're holding a brick
Yeah
What's the point?
That's important now that didn't work. All right, uh
Fine fine, let's go fine
broom machete
I I i'm running out of time
I'm gonna get inside of this this bow
Kind of cool, but who cares?
I got the zombrex that was over here already
I kind of wish I had the motorcycle. This is pretty slow
Jump, let's do it. Are you kidding me? I thought it was over
Nope, now it is
Come on, that sucks
That sucks give me this other one move doing well lost a little bit of health, but
What can you do?
It might be food right here
Tires what is that?
That's a shotgun
Have I I don't think i've been in this maintenance room
Another shotgun you can combine the shotgun with something
What can I combine with the shotgun?
shotgun and
I don't know. I gotta look at my cards shotgun and shotgun. Does that work?
shotgun and battery
No way
No, that doesn't do anything
shotgun and shotgun
Why did I come in here
This is never gonna stop coming in. All right, give me my goodness. All right, so
Forget it. Just goodbye
No reason to do any of this shotgun and the lawnmower. Let's see pole weapon air horn
wheat tenderizer ripper
Pegasus sticky bomb i'm gonna get that hell blade and get the filer. I know that
battery and sledgehammer
Okay, I can do that
Money hacker is a flashlight and a computer
knife gloves, right
That's a laser sword snowball cannon spike bat, right?
All right. Well, i'll make the shotgun a battery battery and lawnmower. I want to let me try this
It looks pretty good. This is can I hold it and I have to okay I can have it in my inventory
That's pretty huge
How does it work? I mean as slow as shit
Holy fuck
Well, i'm dead. I lost that much health just went into the maintenance room
And the whole game flooded in it's just you have a magnet. They just want to eat you you just
Fresh meat or whatever and now I have to do that again
Because I didn't close the door I was surrounded by people coughing in my face
They were just sneezing on me and stunning me
Just like in real life
And that happened remember when that happened. We're just gonna redo the same scenario
I don't play games differently the second time through we just do it the same way every time
That's just the way it happens
But wait a second
There's a tennis ball launcher
Tennis ball launcher and the blades is I mean obviously
The tennis ball launcher. How do I use it?
Fuck I thought it was
Can I pick it up?
No, there's no point with this. There's no point
There's no point. I can't even bring it with me
That would have been really useful. Yeah
Okay, do not have the same scenario play out twice
I know they call me Jeremy
Do it again
elbertson
Nothing changes. They call me german. Nothing fucking changes elbertson because I do the same mistakes every time
Okay battery sledgehammer done rock now. We've got that's pretty much what I still had before. I'm gonna pick the other shotgun
remember this
I went real far
I saw the hot dogs
No, I need that crusher
Snack it's only one bar. Anyways, let's go
Axe I I used the sledgehammer already
accents let
You know what just get rid of this
It's it doesn't do anything for me. It takes so long to detonate
the axe
And where's the sledgehammer over here?
battery
Where's the sledgehammer?
deeper in
That's not it, right? No, there it is
And there's orange juice and shit
Just let me take a second to look
Okay
I want
The what the fuck do I even put down this random blade?
Give me the other orange juice. I'm gonna put down a shotgun for the orange juice. It's more important. It is
All right, two heals
Drink one not yet. I don't need it a little soon
If there's if I see another orange juice, oh i'll i'll be drinking it eight ball
Oh, he's losing his mind. Okay
I see that walking out
You know that kills people
They always show people waking up like four hours later
You're dead if someone does that to you and you hit you in the temple. You're gonna you're dead. You're going to die
and if you don't wake up and
Your your your whole life is changed
All right, so uh don't I have a shotgun?
Hmm interesting interesting i've got to kill this guy pretty quickly, too
Is he did he just what's he what why can he do this?
That's a long fuse that takes a long time
Do that again. I dare you
Where's it? I knew it was gonna happen. He shot me
I wonder if I should just run up there and just start fucking stabbing him. I'm going for it
Well, there are guns everywhere so maybe that
All right. That's a good it works
Is there any healing my health is there healing or anyone healing?
Don't do the thing
Toddler
All right. I get it. The spirit did a lot of damage it did
Checkpoint is not where there's no checkpoint
Oh
No way
It's i'm all the way back here
Oh, no
so
There was a save at the boss entrance
Oh, that's me being this is my face right now
When I can't believe it
Forget about the hammer battery. Yeah, it's pointless
Just throw grenades back and shoot them with the guns stab them with your spear
Bring the century. I have to walk it the whole way. I'm not doing that
Video games suck. I hate video games at the worst
Oh, no, no, I forgot this one up there
Video games are having fun
He finally admits it
I just killed like 50 people
Now we're good
We're good. All right. This is I can't believe I missed the save point. I'm so embarrassed
I'm gonna get the shotgun though
I'm embarrassed
Somebody just spit in my face. I swear
Something just hit me in the mouth that was liquid based and I didn't do anything
I got somebody spit right in my face
I need that double oj
Like i'm seriously coughing from the
All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
I have to get the sludge hammer shit. I know I know guys
Thank you
Do I have two shotguns if I don't I thank god I do
All right, i'm gonna drop this
Where they are, I forgot this is like the orange juice bullshit over here
Where's that orange juice? What's over there the safe point?
Uh, wait, this is 28
Let's do one of these ones like 26
All right orange juice
What I there is no orange juice. I blew up the orange juice
I have to settle for these fucking stupid jelly beans
There's no oj in these boxes. Nothing
Well, just gonna have to kill him
Get a beer hat beer head
No, I should have brought grandma
No, as long as I play this correctly, I just need to use the stabber
When he gets in close stab him shoot him with the guns
Dodge
Just checking for orange juice
I thought that was a huge jug of orange juice. I was like that's two or three of them in one container
That's disappointing
I can throw them back
I'm gonna do shotgun first
Because it's easy, uh tick damage
I ain't moving. Jesus christ
Throw it
Grenade out
done
Don't lose it
If he throws a grenade, it's gonna be too far
Too far that's too far, but I have to do it. I gotta go for it
Throw one. I got a club. I'm losing time here
This is way too long to be spending on this
Jesus
I have a new plan
It's grenade stabbed like three times. I'm gonna throw it after he throws a grenade. Here we go. Ready? Watch this
Didn't work
Oh, don't shoot me, please
There's a rifle. Give me the rifle throw me over there. That's where I want to be
Why did I do that? I'm gonna die. Oh fucking bounced
Bad bounce really bad bounce
I've got to get over there
Change places with me
Wait my turn. Oh fuck
That's been a great
The orange juices are destroyed
The orange juices are destroyed. I can't even oh i'm so
Just slash him. I'm okay. I'm going for the technique called
Who cares just go try to stab him in the face over and over again and then dodge his kick
Wait, do we ever go over this?
Wait, they they wait. Oh, wait. Wait, they respond they respond don't they?
Joe juices
I gotta get this guy off
Get off
He's coming
They respawn
I can get the juices so that we're gonna get rid of
The shotguns are useless
It's not gonna work
I gotta get in there. I gotta throw grenades
Assault rifle will work shotguns not gonna do it. I can't fucking believe it. Thank god. You interrupted me
Just pick it up man, they're so fast
They just run up and you
Save it again
Just get away from me
No redo it
Just redo it for the love of
I need these two heals for this fight
Imagine killing the zombies imagine going over to kill the zombies
But they've upgraded their characters
And if they sneeze on you
It stuns you okay. Just pick them up
Get the fuck out of my way
Oh
Why are you so hard?
It's like running into a wall
You know get rid of this fucking thing too. What a waste of space
I'm making a new one. Anyways
I'm ready. You know the plan. You know, the drill drill is very simple
So
Where's the assault rifle? I know there's one over there. I'm gonna wait till he
Just let it run. That's all right
Okay, here he comes
one stab
Dodge
Why is he chasing me? He's not supposed to do this
He's not supposed to do this
Assault rifles over here. Don't shoot him
That didn't do very much damage considering. He just got hit by two
So I didn't get it
Oh my god, this is horrible
Aim for his head. It doesn't do anything and they also have like when you shoot them
There's like a one or two second period where they have invincibility frames
Yeah
Am I dead? I'm dead. Where is it? Just drink the oil
Is that I wonder if there's anything else around here I could do
Oh fuck it's over. He's gonna kick me
god
I missed
So if I try to stab him more than once
He just hits you it's tough
I'll get it
I'm not i'm not even gonna use a gun. The guns don't do they're not that good
What's the most damaging thing that I have?
Just pick it up
Fuck
I think the stab takes too long switch items during a roll
Eat the trash can food
Uh and and i'll puke. Yeah
There was nothing in that one. That's kind of stupid
Any more trash bags on a drill?
That was like a I thought that was a cantaloupe magazine bikes
Bike durability will last three times longer
Somebody else can read that
How's the toughest boss treating you?
um
I mean he's kind of annoying
It is hard. Yeah, it's this guy sucks
See if I can do with melee
I wanted to take a photo
Left trigger right bumper and right trigger
Why does that not hurt him?
like
Why did he not get hurt by that?
I'm so confused
Fuck
I clearly hit him right in the fucking chest
I mean I can do two hits
I'm gonna cheese this right here. He's gonna go for a kick idiot
Who's the dumb one now sergeant?
I can't even I don't know his name is
Hit me with that
Now everyone's gonna laugh and go like he missed lol he missed. Yeah, did he did he?
I don't think he did
Where the fuck did he go?
He baited me
Tell me i'm wrong. Tell me
Rest again, you know, well, he missed again easy idiot. No, don't i'm okay. Just stay with the plan stay with the plan
I have to wait till he's done swinging
I'm gonna go get it
Yeah
Yeah, what would you like for dinner, son?
Huh?
Oh
Oh, I have to get this one my life
No
He's he's what are you doing? What did you do?
Don't blow it here. I could just get
What no way
Like six arm lengths six arm lengths away
Swinging through this motherfucker
Oh, come on. Like what the fuck?
Should I hit him twice? I don't know if he's gonna tell
I i'm swinging through the guy
He's got like
Eight free no, no, no, no. No, he has like 16 invincibility frames when he swings more than that
It's like 30. It's like two. It's like three. It's like it's like it's like
It's like five seconds
Just get the juice again
I'll handle this
I'm gonna fucking lose my mind relax get the
He's truly malding
That sucks, man. Come on
That sucks
Put the shotgun i'm saving it with the juice
All right out of my way
What's with the ticking clock that I hear now? What is wrong with these guys?
Okay
Yay
Yay. Hooray. We get to do it again this time. I know what to do and this time hopefully I can hit him
50 percent of the time that I swing
I can't believe he did this elbow strike
If he hits you with any of his melees you get to see a fun taunt kill every time
Let's go
Wait till he gets ammo get to that same spot that I was in or even no, it's gotta be it's gonna be far enough away
This one is all right
I didn't like that setup
You guys think i'm cheating this guy when he attacks has game genie turned up with every fucking code
He just doesn't exist
Truly truly about to fucking go next level mad. I'm gonna try this weapon
It's broken
It was the weapon the weapon just is broken against this boss
What a catastrophe
Stop talking
In the right direction oh i'm just breaking this whole counter
I honestly feel like i'm drinking estus
That's what it actually feels like
This is not the run. This is not the run
You can only do it once
It's gonna happen I will beat this guy
Okay
Everybody just relax
And there is extra juice on the ground
We can just scum this
Um, hold on a minute here
I'm gonna be a piece of scum
Like truly dogshit
What am I magazine? No, I need this
No, I don't need that much
I really don't need that much
I just need my spear. Okay, i'm gonna drink
No
It's it's unlimited juice it is
Okay, well I worked
Imagine dying to a guy named boiken
stop
What it's
Okay
Shit
Whatever who it's a person's name. That's not a big deal. All right. I'm like sweating. Let's go
This slow watch out for the ball. Should I have plenty? Uh, I can't think the word healing
But when he if he accidentally hits me through three walls
Somebody wrote munkah s question mark like i'm is munkah s
I have three estus
Bring him this way
Okay, begin the carousel
Greedy, fuck you. He's not dead. I need that fire axe. Where'd it go?
Yay
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we did it. It was easy
Don't make me laugh. I'm not gonna let you bite me
That's it i'll handle the field reporting for
There's another there's a seven four
No, there's seven how much time?
Okay. Well now we have a problem
Get me to the safe house
We have a problem
How am I gonna do this in time? There's another case after this
Just go fast
Who the hell are these guys?
My private what's going on?
Guys, excuse me. Let's go. Let's go come with me
We've been wiped out safe for me and us. Okay. Yep. Good. We intend to follow that last track down 10
I need to start right. No, this is just us follow me
Let's go
They got guns good
That's a long way to go
faster a little bit further
Did I lose somebody clean it up?
Don't worry. I got
Pressed x instead of triangle whatever different control the same idea
Bingo
Got them all come on all three of them. Hurry up. Don't breathe in the gas
one two three
This doesn't look right
It's almost like the actor was so bad that they just superimposed a mask on and redubbed all of his lines
He was just the name they gave me
they
Talking about somebody had to take the fall
And ain't you cute trying to figure it all out?
FA
Frankie west
World famous
This doctor vader one last try to make it to the lime. Yes again, frankie
You all that does have some relevance. You're right
He's not going anywhere that mask has to weigh a ton
One standard operating procedure means there'll be another rescue operation it fails again
That thing's probably
They had 10 to 15 pounds at least
That's like a eight pound nine pound ten pound
Boy smells really bad, too
He's been in it for a long time
But he's nose blind
You can't he has no idea what it smells like in there when he takes that off and somebody's around him
It'll be like holy. This is horrible
So wouldn't you love to see like the thermal camera when he takes that helmet off just like to
All right
save
Okay
Yeah, so funny
Hey, thanks
Which one do I do?
Dave this one probably the one that's yeah this one here
Find the generator gas barrel in school of wire
Take each item to the gate panel at the safe house entrance to hack the gate
Love with the gate and secure the safe house generator gas barrel spool of wire
Uh, well
Well, i'm gonna go this way
Oh everyone's people can die here
People are dying here
Bring to the broken panel
Okay, this one generator. Oh, man
Oh the fuck
This is not okay
An in is dead
Who's an in?
Where's this thing? What am I looking for?
Spool of wire gas barrel spool of wire
Where's this wire?
vacuum
wrong room
Who's wait?
Kirby is dead
Oh, no kirby
Poor kirby
Excuse me
Reset kirby died spool of wire and now a gas barrel which is
Um apparently like very close to right here. I think I don't know
Chris
Gas barrel that's a propane barrel
Lulu, these are all made up people. So this is not canon people who cares about these people?
Oh, no, not chris
I had such a connection with that character
These people just accidentally found their way in here
Crystal's the only real person and she's doing just fine
Okay now
Is that it?
Hack the panel
How does one hack a panel?
Uh
Where's the panel?
Wait, wait, no, you guys are gonna back up the zombie part
You're getting a little too close too quickly
Reset to one wait for the actor to come through
Did I do it?
I did it hack the I think I did it. I win. I did actually do it. I think forever loading screen. That's a problem
That's not good. I think we're gonna have to reset the game. Just wait. What if it corrupt my save?
Just wait
No, that's it. I'll give it 10 more seconds. It's loading a really great cinematic
Yeah, it's this it's loading
Like 30 000 people on screen at once
They're all dressed as blanca. Well, you're gonna know when to fold
This is a fold scenario. Let's try it again
Uh, where's the last checkpoint?
Now that's a great question
It's right before that I think
Let's try it again. Oh, that's not that's a sound. I haven't heard before when opening the game
Uh, the game's not opening but it's playing sound
I don't even have it on my task manager
There's just a weird window here
Uh, that's weird. Let's try that again
Okay
Starting to get a little concerned here
I think we're good. There we go
Start game
Uh, yeah, we're okay
It's right here, right? Yep
I just have to do all that bullshit again
I think this whole thing again. All right. How do I prevent that from happening though?
I'm kind of scared of this mission
Where am I going?
Oh cool a nectar
Anything else back here?
Use it watch this
This is gonna be crazy
Give me the queen
All right, we're back. We're back. We're back. We're back. We're back. We're back. We're back
It's a pc gaming wiki article about this. There's no way to progress
Uh, I can't click this. It'll crash the game. Uh, give me a give me a tldr of what that says
Use your phone. It's okay. All right. Well, whatever
Wait, is it the other room? No, it's down here, isn't it?
No, it's in the other room
I have to what open user profile documents my game's dead rising off the record render settings. I ni
Change the use multi-core entry to false after getting past this loading screen. You're free to charge
Let me just see if I can get it to work once let's get that last one
Changing one value all right
Yeah, this is not we're gonna have to change ini files
Like 90 of the way through the game
Come on, what do you want to build here?
It's the gas barrel. I'm looking i'm looking at chat
All right. So let me i'm gonna hit i'm gonna pause it and then unpause it and pause it really fast and see what happens
Hurry before crystal dies
All right, what's the file user? Okay. I've given the link where is it rising the rising link? There it is
Okay, so go to my user profile settings
Yeah, edit the ini, okay. Yeah, I just gotta get it
uh
Open user. Yeah the user profile
Documents my game's dead rising off the record. Okay, bronc cam
Don't tell him where it is. He's deleting the game
all right, uh
It's documents, right? What the hell documents? No, it's you have to do like the percent percent percent thing
What's it called percent user profile percent or is that just?
Okay
Uh documents my games
Dead rising 2 off the record. There's the render settings
Change the use multi-core to false
false save
After getting past this loading screen, you are free to change it back. What if I just keep it i'm gonna be on one core
suit up
You get a poodle face when you're pissed. I don't i'm not even sure what you mean by that
Your macbook is heating up I know
I'm working on it. Oh, this is horrible
Okay, I have to get through this
This is 10 frames a second
It's a hard mode
I am not gonna leave this if we're saving it right when this is done
You know, I used to play games like this guys
It sucked. I played games like this
And the resolution was even lower. Give me it back. Give me this pull
This is you know, it's the sound it's doing too
I think button pro. I think button presses are not registering at some point wrong way. I know I don't know going the wrong way
It's hard to pay attention buffering inputs. I yeah it is it's like using fraps
I think I actually played
all
of
soldier of fortune like this
How I don't know I did
I'm specifically remembering this insane slowdown with my computer. My computer was a piece of crap
Okay moment of truth. Did it work?
It worked
Nice
Yeah
And
ladies and gentlemen
we've reached the eight hour mark we have
Probably because there's
There's definitely something after this as well
You said dude I said I was gonna try to finish it I said I was gonna try to finish it
so
Hmm. I have I have doctor shit to do over the next couple days
I'm trying to think of anyone how much time is actually left
Like probably four five six hours something like that. I could probably have another stream on this
There's another maybe six hours or so four hours six hours
Then that's a whole that's another stream then
four hours
Because is there an overtime in this game? I'll be doing that too
Okay
Yeah. All right guys. Yeah
It was a ton of fucking fun. I love this game
but
We are going this is probably not going to be the only thing we do on friday
Because if I can if I blow through this in like two or three hours, then we'll just move on to the next thing
So we're gonna open with
Dead rising 2 off the record. I'm gonna beat it
The kind of doctor stuff I have I have a couple of appointments that I need to go to
And one of them is long
So we'll see you on friday
We'll conclude this
Let me say let me like save it and make sure everything is good to go
Oh, I like
I love this game though. I love these both dead rising dead rising 2
It's just
It's equal parts frustrating
hilarious
Stressful and I I love this game
Now we're gonna go with save slot one. That's the best kind of game. I know it really is
But we'll see you friday
I'm just gonna let this play out and make sure I have a good spot
Yeah, i'll change the config back. Wait, did he just die?
I'll do that right before i'll do actually while we're just hanging out with you
Zombrex frankey, and you gotta move no, he needs zombrex
Looks like you got yourself bit pretty bad there tk. He's not turning yet
why
Some people are just more resistant to the infection than others. I'm just story man
You gotta help me
so
Won't know until he turns
How much money do I have?
It's 150 000 for an extra zombrex in the store
I have two
There's a weird shitty x-men
You know what would make this game so much better if frank west had intermittent
Rick burps
It's too late for that kind of
Retrack that no it stays
Uh, you still got a sprained ankle sit down
Shrek
Um, i'm getting a little uh, i'm getting a little sleep. I'm not even that tired
I kind of am but not really go for the kiss do it
I thought she was gonna go for a kiss
All right, save it
All right. We got lots of time
So now we're good to go game is saved
I'll see you guys on friday
Hell yeah, no change the file. Yeah, i'll do it right now
Restart story
I wanted to get it done tonight, but
It's all right. I i'd rather not push it
into like early this morning and
Already starting to lose my mind
And I mean, I don't want to reach simpson's hit and run levels of insanity
So we'll see you friday
Have a good midweek. We'll finish this up. We'll start. Um
You know what I might do on friday after dead rising
Because that would be a pretty good spot to do it. I think
uh katamari
for xbox 360
That sounds like a pretty good place to do it
Start with dead rising and who knows dead rising 2 might just take the whole stream
Depends on how long overtime takes depends on how many times I fail
Uh over and over again at a certain part. I'm not sure we'll see
Am I gonna do dead rising 3?
Yes
But that will be the last one that I do
I'm not gonna play dead rising 4
I already did
And I did not like it at all
Ban him for life
So but i'm not gonna do dead rising 3 immediately. I actually didn't even plan to do dead rising
Two immediately just kind of was like you know what I let's do it. Thanks for sticking around as always
These are some of my favorite types of games to play
Because I feel like there's a lot of fun
Interactions to have there's a lot of ways the game can be played
So i'm having a blast
But that is the end I will see you friday. Let's do the bits
going back
To abomination zero. Thanks for the 250
I mailed you a cooking an envelope full of milk. It's up to you to eat it or turn it down
And give up your point. You have 72 hours to decide
Well at that point it'll be rotten and I don't think it'd be very edible
Thank you, though
Well fade thanks to the 300 bits. Hey jerm, I was wondering if you could stream rainbow 6 vegas 2
it's a fun tactical shooter and
The terrorists in game call you swear words
I feel like I would be way way too adhd to play that game
Doesn't that require real strategy and tactics? You can't just run in there and just start throwing grenades
Put it on the list
rainbow 6 vegas 2
That might be a disaster
But at it. Yeah. Well, i'm all right. Let's do it. Whatever
Uh germa ass stinky feet. Thanks for the 250 bits. Hey germa. I know you hate my username
I don't think it's that funny anymore either
The serious question
I got diagnosed with adhd a few months ago and was wondering if you had any tips for doing schoolwork without taking adderall
I don't want to become dependent on it and you've been living with adhd for longer than I have
I used to actually take adderall
20 years ago
It suppressed my appetite that and ritalin is what I was on. I switched
Uh, it suppressed my appetite
I didn't like it. So I stopped taking it and
I you kind of just have to try
You just have to let it take over if i'm honest
because
If you when you have adhd you have scatter brain all over the place
But when you scatter in each individual piece
Should be something that you can focus on enough to make something work
You kind of just have to
Unless you want to take medicine for it because there really is no other way
You either take some medication to like kind of even you out a little bit or
You just kind of play it out
And this is what i'm focusing on right now. This is what I care about right now. Okay, well
Do it very well for the time that you're going to focus on it
how people with adhd get in trouble and i've been i've done it in the past
is
You you get scattered but you don't focus on any of the things you're scattering around and you
You spread out so much and you're just so
So distractible that you don't you need to at least have one of those things be something that you can pay attention to for a while
Some people have it way worse than others
But there's no
I mean not that i've been able to even think if there's no oh, yeah, just
Do this and your adhd will go away. It's not I guess if you want like actual advice
Uh, turn off your phone. That's number one
If you're doing something important don't have your phone in your room with you or an ipad or or
You don't want to have any distractions like that because it's so easy to pick up a phone
What happened? Let me check my twitter. Let me check this. Let me do this quiet the room down
Even stuff like listening to music can distract the part of your brain that needs to be distracted while you do something else
So your mind gets to play with the songs that are being played while you do the work that helps
Even background noise doesn't even need to be
Um music put on a podcast put on something just to have something to pay attention to while you're doing something
That's what I use twitch for
Yeah, and if it works it works as I watch your streams also moving around
Somebody just said pace around
It that actually helps too moving around while you're doing something
Oh, yeah
Just don't move around away from like your desk too long
But go over something in your head sit down write it down do whatever you're gonna do get up move around a little bit
Have something in your hand
Rubik's cubes are great, but you have to know how to do them
Otherwise, you're just gonna continue to be just gonna be you'll never get it right
But also don't if you don't want to take
If you've never taken something like adderall before request to see if you can get put on a low dose
Sometimes you don't need that much. You just need like enough
to start to correct you
at least up there if you have
Chemicals kind of in balance and all flying around sometimes a low dose
The doctor might just be like, yeah, you know, we can start you off on this and see how you do
Instead of just going just balls to the wall. Give me a full dose and then you feel like shit
It's doesn't and you don't you didn't get scared of it because you don't want to take it anymore
And it ain't just adderall
There's a lot of different medications out there now
Some of them might be better for you than others
There yeah, they're very there are a lot of options
Do I still take no I have not taken it in a long time
But I've
Contrary to what you guys might actually believe i've slowed down a lot
I used to be
like
Uncontrollable I was all over the place
20 years ago 15 years ago
I had so much just energy that had to be expelled
If you think that i'm all over the place now
You should have seemed like 15 year old me
That was off the walls
Did it calm down on its own it sort of did but it's always there it doesn't matter guys i'll put my keys down
on the counter
And i'll something will how i'll walk in another room
And then the keys don't exist anymore and I walk around the whole fucking house
searching for them
And they're just right in front of me
I lose things so easily. That's why I have to keep everything in my pocket
Everything that I need stays with me
And that's why I got those tiles
To be able to ping my stuff
When I inevitably lose it every single day
And you I've like complained about those things, too. Is there any product that I like?
Have you guys ever heard me talk about like a product that I own that I actually enjoyed does that happen?
McChickens, okay, dr. Roker's pizza. All right hash house a go go at the link. Okay
Banana milk. Yeah. All right bananas jet blue. That's right
Cheez-its. Okay, you got me. Yeah, jet blue is the best airline like without a doubt
No, no questions asked
If you can fly on jet blue, do not ever take another airplane for the rest of your life. Just don't there's no reason to
Alaska airlines is better
I'm not maybe but that's a smaller airline. I don't know jet blue is pretty good
Their seats are really comfortable. They did free snacks
Wi-fi on every plane
They got a ton of direct flights you listen to this you want to fly a shitload of the other airlines
Oh, wait, we're stopping first
Jet blue's got a bunch of great direct flights
Use code germa, that would never happen. These airlines make so much money
They don't need me to like sign up
A handful of people to buy up to have airplane ticket
They make like a hundred million dollars a week
Here's the code germa get 10% off. They don't need me
Use code. Look at me and get 5% off
But they do
but I to kind of end that
tangent there is
Sometimes you just have to let it
work out
If you start getting distracted take a break
Get up move around
The reason why I can sit here for so long is because the stuff that i'm doing is so
Rapid fire that I can't get distracted. I get oh I get distracted in the game
But not enough for me to have to stand up and go do something else
You see it happen in the video game. I mean i've been here for eight hours and 15 minutes
I got up once to pee and grab a water and shake my legs a little bit and
Like i'm able to do that
there's enough stimulation going on with the stream with people talking and
Chad and game stuff and yeah, I could get distracted really easily but it's in it's in it's contained here
but I wish you luck on your
ADHD adventure the best part about ADHD is
it is very very very manageable and
Sometimes I attribute it to some of the things that I come up with
So it's not a complete curse
ADHD adventures
ADHD comedy
Why do I feel like that would be a great youtube channel name? It probably already is
And it's like quick 10 second videos that are all in a playlist
Like 10 to 15 second comedy videos, that's vine, right? But that doesn't exist anymore. It was taken over by tik tok
tik tok is vine
But people just lip sync their favorite songs
But anyway, uh, thank you c4g for the 300 bits. I haven't been able to watch in this stream
But my girlfriend is and they say I get the allure of the face cards jerma
Really? I really do but if you have at least three of a suit
My best bet is to hold those instead you absolute fucking fool
But i'm the bits giver in this relationship
We're playing jacks are better the face cards jacks are better you get your bet back
Hold it's free of a suit. But if you get queen
And king you get queen jack jacks are better gives you bet back
That's the machine we were playing not every machine is jacks are better all in every time. What's the worst that could happen?
Thank you dark soul for the 250
Can you explain to us why you have that massive i can has cheeseburger tattoo on your back?
I don't have an explanation for that
Swiggity-swanky. Thanks the 250. I'm no doctor, but i'm guessing a majority of your mysterious health problems might be caused from your laughing
I know that when I strain too much I get lightheaded and weird could be from that
No, it's not
uh
It's something else
It's something else. I'm sure it doesn't help
He hates to laugh
is not
We we don't think it is like
Bowel and irritable bowel disease like colitis related
Something else is going on
I don't know. We're gonna figure out what the hell's going on
I've had a lot of random just doctor's appointments and I know we kind of know what's going on
I don't think it's anything serious
I've had a ton of tests and a ton of
stuff poking and prodding
But if we're getting we're narrowing down and it's just kind of annoying
If it is the thing that it's might be it's
There's no reason for me to talk about it because I don't want to concern anybody there's no don't worry. There's no there's no concern
It's just an annoying thing
I have to figure out so don't worry
It's nothing serious, but annoying. Yeah
I will know much more very very soon. We'll put it that way
but the reason I don't really talk that much about medical stuff just because I
Sometimes i'll talk about in like pre-stream or oh, I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow. Oh, don't worry
I don't want to concern anybody about anything. I'm that everything's gonna be i'm fine. Don't worry
I don't want people to start like wait, wait, hold on. What's wrong with him? What's something wrong with him?
Something's wrong with him
So don't worry. We'll be good to go. But spaghetti swanky. I appreciate the 250. Thank you
Stinky beaver. Thanks for the 250 soft lock. I don't think so
Not today
Uh piff flavor. Thanks for the three dollars. Hey, dude
I just want to make sure you love auto because I recently lost my dog
And it sucks to be sure so be sure to love auto and also this is your six percent germ attacks
I'm really sorry to hear that
Sure. It was a wonderful dog
It's a family member. It is
Plain and simple. Thank you for your 300 bits
Sorry to hear about your awesome dog
It's tough. It is. Yeah, they're a lot there. Sometimes they're around for a very long time
We're gonna sneak
Into this portion of the stream here. Let's get that there
Thanks for watching everybody see you friday
We got the credits to do
All the subs that rolled in
Uh a little odd error unable to detect stream start on your platform
Stream labs error for some reason
Let me go in here and see why that's doing that stream was never started in the first place
Weird
See if I can run it from the website itself
Stream labs is not even connected to my twitch anymore. They do like an update
Learn how to stream like a pro
Okay, i'll try
All right. Let me see if I can do through here live events
We need the actual
widget
What's wrong with this thing? Okay
Let's try it again. Here we go
roll the credits
Uh unable to detect stream
This is not cool
Something's wrong with stream labs
We may not be able to see the sub credits today
I think it's broken. Let me try it one more time
credit settings
Sorry, i'm taking so long
Test i'm gonna test it not doing anything unable to detect stream start on your platforms
Yeah, something's wrong here
Sorry guys. Sorry that this uh, usually this the subscribers all fly by here
Maybe it's on twitch's end maybe
But anyways, thank you so much for subbing in the first place
We do have the final couple of bits here
From flug boy. Thanks for the 250 jerma. I had some bits lying around on my couch seats
While I was cleaning from my move. Hope you're doing well friend. Also, did you see the joker?
And what did you think? I've not seen it
I've not had very much time
Wait, what is going on here?
Well, that ain't right
Hey here come tonight's uh, subscriber one subscriber two and subscriber three
You guys continue to support this free stream and I really appreciate it
Thanks a lot you three
Really interesting usernames, too
All right
Uh, i've not seen the joker. I plan on seeing it soon
Thank you bg
Fkj for the thousand bits
I had a dream of you
You chased me through my room and put a knife against me saying something about saints row two
Uh, you were you appeared to be sporting an 80s wall street businessman getup
As this was happening the chat was watching all this they were collectively agreeing with each other that you weren't that you went too far
And that you truly were a psycho
I managed to escape and had a talk with your dad
He said he always knew this day would come and that you were a problem child the chat spammed lore
That's
Just strange enough to be real
That's a this is a copy pasta
You your dream created an actual new coffee pasta
Especially the end
That's the perfect copy pasta ending
Hey, keith king crimson. Thanks the 250
Hey, if you're gonna play beautiful katamari for 360, you should grab all the dlc levels too. The game's a bit short
Yeah, I was gonna get everything as much as I could paste it. Let me paste the copy pasta
I've reached the character limit
You cannot cheer in your own channel. Well, i'm not trying to
All right, guys
see you friday
for the finale of dead rising 2
and
Possibly depending how long that takes
Katamari for the 360
Get some sleep. Thanks for staying up
Take care guys
See you soon