Don't head out to sea understock. No one beats my prices. Friend, come and see for yourself.
Got some coin to spend? What? Up!
Shut up! Keep that.
Have a look. No matter what you pick, I guarantee you'll love it.
Shut up!
Shit! Where's your eyes?
Friends, come see what I've got in stock today.
Swab the deck!
Sweep the floors!
Sweep the cannon!
Be a lookout!
What the fuck are you doing?
You're gonna come on my boat!
And not do work?
You're the one limey bastard that's gonna get a knife straight into your skull!
You know what? You can stay.
You can stay.
Go bird.
Go, do it again. Steal from this guy too.
Good job. Good job. You picked up a couple of his hairs.
Nice. Two of his hairs.
How do you do?
Oh, fine. How do you do?
God be with you.
Good day. Good day to you.
How is it? How do you do?
Oh, fine. How do you do?
Something wrong with my bird.
Stupid pig. Get out of here.
What the fuck is that? Is that a gorilla? Is that a monkey?
What are these animals doing? Why are they just all hostile?
If you're this close to the town, get out of here.
Alright, pig. Get him.
Get him, pig.
He just threw a rock at me.
You're gonna throw rocks? That's what you do?
You little shit.
I'm glad I get to see the pitching machine monkey.
It's rapidly throwing rocks.
I just like the batting cages.
Holy Jesus!
What the fuck?
Why is it like mountain lions?
Help me.
Help me, guys. Quick.
God be with you.
Good day. Good day.
Indeed. Oh, please.
For some ale.
Good day to you.
That Spanish commander, what's his name?
His fleet's been restless these days.
That's another guy. It comes from the same guy.
That guy just...
Oh, let me just be in mid-conversation.
Eating an apple while I walk by eating an apple.
No, this fucking alligator is so stupid.
There's no reason for this to be in the game.
There's just one alligator.
Okay, now the alligator doesn't go in the water?
It's just a sand alligator.
He's afraid of the water. That doesn't make any sense.
You think you're a big man, don't you?
Yeah, you really do. You stare at you.
Stare at my eyes.
Yeah, you ain't nothing.
I'm not gonna look away.
You're gonna look away first.
Are you really all just afraid of the water?
Except for the pitching monkey. He's not afraid.
Well, he kind of is afraid.
I tricked him.
You see, I'm the smart one. I'm the man.
I am the human.
You're scared of the water, so I put you in the water.
So you're afraid to come out.
Stupid animals.
That's why we will always reign as humans.
God, right now we are standing in the temple of Osiris.
And I can tell you right now, guys, I'm a little excited as an anthropologist and an archaeologist.
I have been waiting for this day for a long time.
I'm a little nervous. I can't wait. My whole life has been dedicated to this.
I can't wait to give it a try.
Getting a little too excited.
I don't want this to be a puzzle game. I don't want to do puzzles.
I don't want to do a puzzle.
All right. Is this where I'm supposed to go?
I think so. I've got to drop down.
This is one of those games where you have to find the place to drop down.
This is it. Right here.
Specific amount of damage.
Hold on. How much damage is that?
One, two, three.
One hundred and seven million damage.
That's a fucking shitload.
Hold on a second.
I've got to make sure there's no traps in here.
Okay. I've been fooled before.
You know, I've been fooled before.
Nothing on the walls.
Nothing on the ground.
Nothing on the ceiling.
I'm pretty sure that that's normal. Nothing.
So we're free. I think we're going to be all right.
Step on the button and let's go continue our quest.
The button kills you.
You put in some crocodiles. You put in some pigs.
What, a dragon?
A dragon is in the game.
You're going to put a dragon in the game?
A real one?
How? Can I?
I guess we're going to just slide down this.
I wonder how long this is going to take.
Is this ever going to end?
There probably has to be something at the bottom.
I'm using my sword. See, I'm cutting down.
What you guys don't understand is I'm cutting down right now.
Like this is a cool action movie.
I stuck the sword in and it's sliding down like puss in boots.
Didn't he do that in that movie?
What are some other things we can talk about?
This is in fact...
No, we're going to pass it.
Going right by. I believe that is the last level I was just in.
I think. I could be wrong though.
I've been wrong before.
I see water.
Or is that water or is that just terrain texture?
I believe that's just terrain texture.
At least we're going to land.
We've landed.
So I'm in no man's land right now.
Shit's getting a little weird.
I wonder if there's anywhere...
Can I go anywhere?
Have I unlocked the secrets of humanity by falling down the giant dragon pillar?
I believe I have.
What's this?
What's with this random tree?
Who put this random tree here?
Alright, Ted.
You put a tree in this spot down the lower left.
Delete that.
Control Z.
What the fuck am I?
I'm lost.
This just got so scary.
This really just got scary.
There's nothing out here?
I should turn back?
They have actual text in the game to tell me to turn around.
Because I got to the end of the developer's map.
There's nothing out here.
I should probably turn back.
Yeah, turn back to where is the question.
If I get the sun, I will get superpowers.
I can't imagine anything else what this could be besides the sun.
It's the sun.
Or is that God?
I'm not sure.
Entertaining to say the least.
You know what this looks like?
I'm in a movie theater.
I found the secret.
Game crashed.
It was a big projector.