Hello. Hi. How are you doing? What's going on? Explain yourself. Okay, fine. Guess I'll explain
myself. Uh, so I woke up today and I had a bad headache. Is it- I did the thing where you just
pop two Tylenol, go lie down in bed, and just like sit there and pray with your eyes closed.
Go in. Go away, go away, go away, go away, go away, go away, go away, go away. Well, you don't do-
that'll make your headache worse, but, um, yeah, I'm okay. It seems to have, uh, subsided a little,
but don't be too loud. I would like if everybody could please lower your volume a little bit.
I've got a headache today. Can you imagine going to a concert or going to a live event
and the person you're going to see comes out on stage and you're like cheering.
This person goes, hold on. Wait, wait, guys, guys, excuse me. I have a headache today.
If you could just kind of lower your volume and not be so excited.
And they do their whole routine. And every time that somebody, the crowd laughs,
like that big crowd laugh, it's just like, stop, stop. I told you guys, please get it together.
This is ridiculous. I'm going to leave. Hangover, Andy. I don't, I don't have a hangover. I didn't,
didn't drink anything. That would actually be pretty funny. Oh, I just get headaches.
I'm just a headache, Andy. I, uh, I've had an MRI of my brain, so there's nothing immediately
concerning. Apparently that this is ongoing for like a decade plus. So don't worry. I'm okay.
But today we've got some stuff going on. I'm going to play GeoGuessr on cam. That's right.
I'm going to be on camera today. And then we're going to play Dying Light 2 again with stir.
So play, play GeoGuessr for like, maybe like an hour or two. Maybe we'll see somewhere around like
four, four 30. We're going to ping stir and be like, Hey, ready to get back into the world
of Dying Light. He's going to go, yeah, dude. So let's go. I think we've spent enough time here.
Let me clear my throat. Let me take a sip of water. No cheating. How do you cheat at GeoGuessr?
I don't get it. Don't you have to just kind of guess where you are?
Would you guys progress in Dying Light at all? Well, um, kind of kind of, uh,
well, do I, we're not playing Dying Light yet. So we'll tell you about it after we didn't play
anymore. We may have progressed. We might have. You can't look up companies or addresses. Oh,
that's fine. I didn't do that anyways. No, we're just going to see if I can know where I am.
Let's go ahead and get it on the screen right now. Hold on. Let me click this. Wait, hold on.
GeoGuessr is a premium service now. Yeah. I already, I already bought it.
I saw the five minute thing and I was like, that's not going to work.
So we're, we're not limited to the five minutes and then 15 minutes.
Where's our a hundred community subs. I still can't figure out what's going on. So like I,
I am the process of trying to figure out why that's happening. So there's real debt on this
channel now that I have not paid yet. The jokey two billion debt thing is, was a funny joke,
but now it's real. I owe a hundred community subs that I haven't paid yet. I actually have,
uh, actually have a real debt that I have to pay. So I have not found a solution yet. I'm going to
figure that out very soon. I promise. Just keep it, add it to the tab. All right, here we go. You
ready? Oh, I had a crazy dream too. I'll tell you that it's fucked up. Can you see me? Okay. So
we're going to play GeoGuessr. It's going to be fun. Uh, I don't, this is all like a new menu.
I don't know what any of this is. What, what is all this stuff? Beard? Yeah. I have to shave.
It's getting bad. It's getting too long. Don't ask us. We're no, but yeah, look, this is like
a completely new website. I don't know. I don't get it. Explore mode, daily challenge, world famous
places. Should I just do world? What's like the regular one? Just do world. That's what I'm going
to do. This, this sound effects too. I'm going to hold on. Single player. Yeah. All right. Default
setting. No time limit moving around. Yeah. Start. You ready? I want to full screen this like this.
Yes. Okay. All right. Where the heck are we? That's my new series on Twitch. If you check it out,
you check out the title. The title of the stream is where the heck even are we guys? Let's go ahead
and start. Okay. Looks a little, looks a little industrial. I don't think, I don't think this is
North America. I want to take a guess right off the bat immediately. I would say it's somewhere
in Europe, either Europe or, I don't know, the default answer for everywhere. If you don't think
it's America is Russia, right? No, this doesn't look like a somewhere in Kentucky. It's Russia.
Like that's not, it's not, it's never is. I mean, it could be, wait, what was that sign?
I don't, wait, go back. How do I zoom in? It's just mouse scroll, right? What's that? What's that
say? Uh, I don't know what that says. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to say Italy. I think it's
somewhere in Italy. I think that was Italian. No, that's not, that's not Italian. Wait a minute.
Russia. This is Russia. That's Russia. That's Russian. I don't know. I don't know what language
that is. All right. It's, okay. It's not here. So let's go over here. I've been doing the thing
where I'm just holding the mug. Okay. Here. Let's keep going. All right. There's no time limit,
but I feel like that kind of should be. Maybe I should turn it on because eventually I'll figure
it out. Right. Okay. What does this say? I, I N A. Wait, what's that? Ineos. Wait, what? This is Japan.
This is, we're in Japan. What? No, that's, this can't, no, what? This is not Japan. What flag is
this? This is not, is that the Jap? That's not the Japanese flag. What is that? I don't know what
flag that is. Okay. Wait, it's probably like here. Of course this isn't fucking Japan. Am I stupid?
All right. I'm, I'm going to say, wait, they got the state puff marshmallow man over here.
What happened? What? I thought my screen got, why is there a bullet hole in my screen? I honestly
thought there was something wrong with my monitor for one second. I was like, why is there a fucking
bullet hole? What is that? It's a tree. All right. I get it. I, I'm going, I'm going, we're going
right here in Lida. I'm guessing. Let's go. It's not bad. Where was it? Slovenia. Okay. That wasn't
that bad or no Croatia. Okay. I mean, it was across the entire continent, but whatever. Okay.
Now this, this is a, this is the United States of America. Orange, Orange road. Keep left.
I feel like that sign needs to be a little bigger because it looks like it's been run over like
a hundred times. I feel like they need to make this a little more elaborate. I'm, hold on. I'm
thinking, I'm thinking we need to see some business or something here at Hearst golf range.
It's somewhere in the South, but is it though? I don't know. I don't know. I don't think so. Now
that we're looking at it for another minute, am I going to take a sip of this fucking coffee
already? I've been holding, how long has the streaming been live? I've been holding this
right here for 13 minutes and I haven't sipped out of it yet. What's that school zone? Eight to
nine, two, 30 to four, 40. Wait, does this say you can go 40 in a school zone? Isn't that too, way too
fast? 40? That's zooming in a school zone. Oh, I thought it was like 60 in a school zone. Holy shit.
All right. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's this bus stop? This is,
it's probably, I think it's in the South. 40 miles per hour school zone. Where's the school?
Where's the school? N school zone was on this side of the road. Where is it? Is that a school?
Is that a school? Remember, you're pretending. I am not pretending. There's a flag right here,
but it's like folded over. I can't, I don't know what that says. That's Australia. I mean, yeah,
you don't know that. Wait, closing day and boarding college, pre-kindergarten to year 12.
Oh shit. SU. And I don't know why I thought that was not safe for work. What? I was like,
what are you talking about? Scott Saints, NS, like what the fuck? All right, that's the AU.
We're in Australia. But where in Australia? Australia is fucking huge. I know absolutely
nothing about Australia. Nothing. I would say, let me keep going. Wait, N. Oh shit. That's right.
NSW. Stop cheating. I wouldn't have gotten that. Oh, I think it's pretty close to Sydney, Mike.
All right. Got it. Stop cheating. Stop. All right. Now I'm not going to look at chat for
the rest of the, I'm not going to look at chat. All right. This is leaves are turning, which could
mean many things. Is that a ALFL? I can't tell. I can't read it. Anything's like a state or
something in there. I'm not going to look over a chat. I swear to God. I've seen leaves turn,
which that only happens in New England. The leaves only turn in fucking Boston. They don't
turn anywhere else. You guys ever been to Maine? Don't look at chat. Wait, what's this? Birch Harbor
estates. Okay. Birch Harbor. This is definitely, this is definitely either all the way up or all
the way down, all the way up or all the way down. I don't, I don't think, hold on. Let's keep moving.
What does that say? Only, only, all right, nothing. Wait, we got a, we got a business up here. Alaska.
It was AL. Okay. This is Alaska. I told you either all the way up or all the way down. We're in Alaska.
Free bears Alaska. Is that the name of the, did they just put that there to make it so people that
play GeoGuess or know what town it is? Is there a three bears Alaska? Delta Junction. I, this is
definitely not on a coast. I don't think, I think it's pretty much in, but Alaska is fucking huge
too. It's so, wait, my face cam is in a bad spot. Isn't it? I put my face cam top, like middle right.
Hey, look at this. Let me, let me move the face cam. Top right, but then you can't see that.
No, I didn't want to turn the face cam off. No, wrong fucking button again. Wrong button again.
Wrong button again. What the fuck am I, what's, what's my OBS doing? Oh, okay. That's better.
That's good. All right. So we're in three bears Alaska, which who knows where the hell that is.
Stop looking at chat. All right. Well, we know we're in Alaska. Let's see if we can get a town.
Oh, nope. Anything else here that would give us a, give it away? Liquor, grocery, pharmacy,
fresh meat, fresh produce, sporting goods. It's got everything. This is like, this is an everything
store. Sporting goods too? Well, there's produce there. What does that mean? I'm giving it like
another minute. Fresh produce. I, I said the word wrong for a second. Like please. Auto care.
Nope. Nothing there. It's definitely in the middle. I see mountains in the distance though.
Almost all of Alaska is a mountain. That doesn't help me at all. Wait, or does it?
Look at this over here. This is pretty mountainous up here and it's pretty mountainous down here.
See that in the distance over there? I think this is the clue. My voice is such junk because
that's a mountain. We're either really far away here or, okay, here we go. Ready?
Oh my God. What's wrong with me? Grizzly group. Grizzly group cafe. Quilt Alaska.
I'm going with the mountain technique. He's old. I know. I know. Shut up. What's that say?
Or even ribs. That place is probably like 10 out of 10. Oh my God. Why are there, why is it
like a Canadian geese congregation of mailboxes over here? This feels like, this feels like too
many. Okay. We're in Quilt Alaska? I don't know. I'm going for it. Here we go. We got the mountain
range here, mountain range here. I'm going to go, I think it's a little bit closer to Anchorage.
I'm going to say it's like right here. Right between McGrath and uh, and Nikolai. That was
actually pretty good. That's not bad. I really should have just said Anchorage. It's probably
these mountains right here. This is like beautiful. Oh my God. This is like incredibly
lush and gorgeous. Okay. Where are we? Hump. I think we call it bump in America. I don't,
I don't think we call it hump. It's a, we call it bump. Who would say hump? This is a nice place.
I see uh, I see industry over here. Okay. All right. Okay. We are in, where are we?
We, I saw a flag and my brain is trying to figure out what flag that was and I have a pretty good
idea, but I'm not going to say it because I don't want to sound stupid. Oh, Chatsworth Road. That's
where you guys live. Okay. It's over here. But where? Where? Chatsworth Ave. This is Chatsworth
Road. Chatsworth Ave. All right. What's going on over here? We've got buildings. This is like
we're in like a city area. It's that T. Chatsworth Road. All right. I think I got an idea. Danger.
High voltage. I'm not going to look at chat. Chatsworth Road again. What's that? Hold on.
This is like a park. Taxi. What's that say? Max height limit. Three meters. Okay. Hold on.
What's that say? Passenger pickup. I want to get over to that building. I think I get a better idea.
Okay. It's somewhere over here. I think. What's with Chatsworth? Is every road Chatsworth?
Watch this be like somewhere like Louisiana or something, right? Like what if I'm just
completely wrong? But wait, it's all in English. Wait, what? Every road is Chatsworth. Where are we?
Hold on. Times are changing. Times are changing. Hyundai. We build tomorrow. Okay. So Hyundai.
Hold on. They are building tomorrow? No. That's not what it means. That means like Hyundai. We build
tomorrow. Like they're like a technology company. That's not what that means. Like that's not like
announcing that they're going to be starting building tomorrow. That's them saying that we
build tomorrow because they're a tech company. What flag is that? Road works. Whoa. That's...
I love that little thing. That's so cool. Is it animated? Does it go like... Oh, that's so cool.
Land Transport Authority. All right. I think I know where this is. I know where this is. But I'm like
too stupid to remember where it is. I just know that it exists in the world. I just need to figure
out where it exists in the world. And I'm not going to say where it is because I don't want
people to think I'm stupid because I don't know where it is. And I now know where it is.
Okay. I now know where it is. I've narrowed it down to here. Ministry of Education Headquarters.
But what country? Ahead. Humps. I don't... Hold on. I'm not leaving yet. What's that? Escape?
I got it. I told you it was right here somewhere. And everyone thought I was stupid. All right.
Where? Wait. Wait a minute. Wait. Is this an ad saying to come visit Malaysia? What if that's
an ad saying like, hey, leave Escape where you are right now and go to Malaysia for a vacation?
Right? Uh-oh. I don't know. I don't know. That could be... That could just be like an ad to like
go visit Malaysia. Oh, shit. Uh-oh. I don't know. All right. I think we're going to get a big reveal
coming up here. I'm not looking at you. I'm making... What does that say? SG. What's SG?
What's SG around here? Singapore would be SP. SG? Wait. No, it wouldn't. S... Sing... This is
Singapore. Where? Wait. Singapore is in Malaysia. Wait. No, it's not. What? Oh, shit. No, it's not.
It's not. It's not. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, it said visit Malaysia. Singapore is Singapore.
It's different. No, they confused me with a huge text on the screen. They confused me. It's here
somewhere. Where is it? I'm going to keep going. SG. That's Singapore. Somebody I caught in chat
earlier said South Africa. No. SG. That would be South Gaffrica. No, that's not what this is.
This is Singapore. Mandarin Hotel. Going to meeting... Getting meetings is faster.
Is that... It's Singapore. All right. I'm going to get... I'm going... I'm going for it. We're done.
No. Is it... Or is it like Malaysia? Because it's like, hey, visit... I don't know.
Wait. What was that? That truck had something on it. Who's that truck?
Where's that truck? Where's the truck? What happened? Oh, God. It disappeared.
I missed my, like, quest opportunity. All right. I'm going for it. I'm going to say
we're, like, probably in, like, a downtown area. Wait. One last little check here. What's this say?
Land Transport Authority. Okay. I'm going to say that means it's probably, like, a land transport.
It's probably, like, down here. I'm going to say it's, like, here. Let's go for it. Bingo. Done.
And that was very, very close. They almost got me with the Malaysia ad. I was like, oh, shit.
But does it mean go? Does it mean... I don't know. All right. Let's go. Snow. Snow. Right off the bat.
This actually could be... This could be New England. I thought they were going to fucking
get us with that one. Oh, yeah. You forgot to clean up the snow, GeoGuessr. Oh, I forgot to clean the
snow up. Yeah. Sorry. I caught it. They could hide it. They could, like, melt all of it everywhere
else. No, you didn't catch that part. I think that's, like, a... Is that, like, a state flag or
something? I don't know. Is it a bird or is it a moose? It looks like a bird. All right. Who has a
state bird? Every state has a state bird. Who has a state bird that looks like that? Who has a state
bird? This is... Yeah. Look at these homes. This is definitely... This is, like... This is, like, New
Hampshire or something. Oh, absolutely. This is, like, New Hampshire. Or, like, Vermont or something.
Let's go out this way. Gotta get to a main road here. And this is how I know it's... This is how I
know it's probably New England. Because, like, good luck finding the main road. Because, like,
there's a shitload of these neighborhoods that just lead into each other. This is New England. Yep.
Absolutely. I'm convinced. Yeah. This is definitely New England. I thought a driveway was a road.
This is New England. Oh, yeah. I'm convinced. Get me to a main road and I'll confirm it. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Without a doubt in my mind. You know why I... You know why I know this is New England?
Easy fucking answer. This snow was probably here. Let's say that this photo was taken in, like,
March. That snow probably snowed in February. Or, like, January. And it's just still there.
I'm going for it. I don't think I need to see anything else. And I'm gonna go... I'm gonna go,
like, right on the border here. I'm gonna say, like, I'm gonna say, like, Western Mass up into,
like, kind of the, like, the New Hampshire potential, like, Vermont area. I'm gonna go
right here. Fuck out of here. You don't think I know my own place? You don't think I know my
own country? Are you shitting me? You don't think I know what I'm doing? It was closer to Boston,
but still. That's up in Newton. That was an absolute giveaway. That was a giveaway. Let's
do it again. This is fun. I could have said closer to Boston, but I figured it was a little bit
further out. Closer to New Hampshire. Uh, let's do it again. Are there sound effects? How come
I don't hear anything? All right. This is... Razor King. Where even are we? I have no idea.
Pharmacy? Butchery? Fast foods? It's like a little... This is a market. All right. I think,
I think I've got an idea. Get out to a main road here. What's that say? Otimo Saco. Wait! What's
this? Otimo... Otimo Saco. It's definitely not over here. It's definitely down here.
But where? Forward Travelers. Otimo Saco. Otimo Saco. What is this? Good times. Good times.
Jackpot! Jackpot on the top of the truck. Wait! There's a chemist! Pharmaceuticals
chemistry. I love, I love the word chemist, by the way. Where are we though? Breakthrough Summit
2018. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! What's that say? In 21 days. I can't read that.
Rwanda. I don't know where that is. Are you sure it's Rwanda? Hold on. Oh, I gotta go back to the
chemist. You're reading chat. I don't know! I'm not! I have to read chat sometimes. I don't know where
Rwanda is. Where is... I don't know where that is. You're an ignorant streamer. I don't know where
Rwanda is. I don't know. Central... I don't... I know it's like... Oh, shit! There it is! Thanks, chat,
for shit. Right here. Let's go. You didn't even have it correct! You guys got it wrong!
I love chemist. Billy Hills. Oh, that's not... I thought that was like a sign of where we were.
Vote for Billy Hillis. But where? What state or county? That's Billy Hillis. Okay. That's either
somewhere in the UK or a GTA NPC character that you do missions for that like has a tractor.
And like at some point during the story, like drives the tractor through like a store to save
you. And you have to get in the tractor and like drive the tractor and like avoid the police and
stuff. So we're... It could be either one. Classic tractor NPC joke. All right. Where are we? This is
a... This is definitely... Is it one house? How do you get your trash out here? This is like a hundred
miles away from the... Your driveway. Can you imagine how... Imagine lying on the couch with
no pants on? Just being like, ah, I gotta take the trash out. You gotta go for a fucking walk.
That sucks. That's so... That's too much. That kind of house, you just have a maid. I don't know.
You have to get a golf cart, a trash golf cart. Somebody said that's not that far? This is far.
This is a far way to go. To bring a bag of trash here. That's far. Yeah. I don't know about that.
That's like you look out this window and even get in the barrel too, right? Like when you know you
gotta go get the barrel, you just look out this window staring, just going, I'll get it tomorrow.
And then tomorrow you look out there again and you go, I'll get it tomorrow. You will drive by this
barrel. You will pull into your driveway and you'll look out the window and you'll go, fuck.
And you'll just keep going. Barrel? I mean barrel. Barrel. Barrel. Trash bar... I call it a barrel.
Trash can. I call it a barrel. I'm from a different part of the world than you. Sorry.
Sorry, I'm from a different part of like the country than you. I'm not in the same country
that you're in. I call it a barrel. It's a barrel. Well, sorry, we have different ways of talking.
Donkey Kong trash can. It's a barrel. Whatever. I'm not... I'm not gonna take a sip out of this
just because you said that. A barrel. Okay, you wanna... Okay, what do you call the thing that
changes the channel on your television? We have to talk about this every six months.
Changer. I call it a changer. A remote. When I was younger, we called it a changer beeper.
It was just the... It was the changer beeper. And that was cute and fun and whatever. Sorry,
we talk differently. Clicker. No, sorry, you don't say it right. It's the remote control.
TM. You say clicker. You say changer. Sorry, you got it wrong. I don't know why you did that.
All right, this is definitely... This is def... I don't know. I'm gonna go like up here. Like here.
It's probably like the Netherlands or something. Or like UK. I don't know.
We need to live in more information. This is... Wait. Oh, I went backwards. I was like,
why is every house the same house? This cow is just here. All right. Wow. That's cool.
I think I'm narrowing down my decision here. Not yet. This is so beautiful. It's so great.
Okay, I've never been to the UK before. Never been to Ireland. Never been to Scotland.
But does anybody else feel like it just smells nice here? It's probably the air is probably so
clean. It's probably so fresh. What's that say? Einstein. Einstein rugs. I don't know. Wait a
minute. That's rugby. I'm fucking around. I'm kidding. All right. Where are we?
Oh, we're gonna get it right off the bat. It's gonna be right here. Dude, is that a fresh wild
apple? Are you serious? Where is this? That's a fresh wild orange. Or is that a wild tomato?
That's a wild tomato. A wild onion? Holy shit. That's awesome. This is wild fruits and vegetables.
Oh shit. All right. Where are we? We're in Asia somewhere. I can't get over that wild like
orange. Are they more like wild fruits? Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't know. I don't know where,
but we're here somewhere. Holy shit. I hope you didn't hear that. That was so gross. That's worse
noise there. If it picked up on the mic, it was like a bullfrog. It was like, all right. Oh my
God. Can you imagine the amount of wild berries and fruits that are out here? Oh my God. This is
so... I feel like you live longer if you're in a place like this. Like you're surrounded by
like agriculture and oxygen and not like Starbucks and tar. Don't you think you probably live longer
when you live in a place like this? Surrounded by wild onion trees. It's like a lot of us are
just like surrounded by like concrete and lights. I imagine if like you were surrounded by like
oxygen and wild berry trees. Okay. Wait, we got something here. Shit. I don't know how to read
that. What's that? That's something dot dot. Is that dot K U? Dot K U. Something dot K U.
Is that a website? No, that's not a website. I thought it was like something dot like dot
com or something. I thought that was a website. I thought that was a website. All right. That's
not a fucking website. It's a website. Fucking goddamn idiot. All right. It's... I'm gonna...
We're gonna go here. I've narrowed... It's somewhere in this square. I'm not pretending. I'm really just
like... I don't know. My brain's a little deluded. All right. I'm... Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Uh-huh. Oh, yep. Oh, yeah. Yep. Hold on. Let me
get it closer. Let me get it closer. Yep. It's close. Ah! Oh, it's an animal! What is that? It's
like a bat flying into the camera. What is that? What is happening? What is this animal? There's
like an animal stuck. Why is it like flattened on this windshield? It's following you. Okay. Where
are we? What the hell is happening? Is it... Wait. Is it a leaf? Or is it actually like an animal or
like a bug on the camera? It's changing. Whatever it is. It's growing. Is it a bag? I don't know.
All right. Where are we? This looks like, um... I'm seeing sand here. It looks sandy.
The sand. Okay. We got a UPS shirt on? This dude is fucking jacked! Holy shit! What a Chad!
This is like a Giga Chad! I see the American flag. So, we're in the United States. It's
deserty. That could be a few places though. This guy. All right. This is... This might actually be
somewhere down here. This is... This is potentially like the kind of Nevada, Arizona,
potentially like New Mexico. Like, I'm thinking New Mexico. New Mexico, Arizona. I'm thinking.
Like, somewhere over here. I don't think this is Vegas. I don't think this is Nevada. Although,
no. No. I don't know. It's close. It could be. It actually could be. It could be right here.
I'm gonna say, like, it could be here. But we're not done yet because it seems like we're getting
to a road here. Texas is a lot more green. Texas is a lot more green, but there is a lot of green
here. I'm thinking Arizona or New Mexico. What's that? Welcome to Highland Ranch. Wait, why did
it just turn into a different fucking season? Wait, what? What happened? What? It just turned
into a different state. It ain't down here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No chance in hell.
It's up here. Where? Maybe it is Texas. I don't... I don't know. This is not Colorado. No way.
This is, like, somewhere over here. I don't think it's this far up. No, it's not that. It's not
north Utah. It's southern Utah. In fact, it could be Utah and Nevada border here. Something like
down here. I don't know. It's close. Let me keep going. Whatever that animal is, it's still here.
School. Hold on. Wait. Something up here. Whatever that is, we're gonna get a look at it.
What is this? School? It's a school. Does it have a name? What's the name of the school?
Ah, Virginia. No, that's... no, Virginia's the name. Virginia Palmer. Go Palmer. Good luck on your
tests. This is not... this is not... this is not Virginia. No way. No, this is... it's impossible
for it to be Virginia. All right, I'm gonna make my guess here. There's snow, so I'm leaning more
towards it not... I'm leaning more towards it being, like, here. Salt Lake gets snow. This area,
I don't know. But when you go up here, you get into, like, Wyoming and Idaho, and it's not
like that. I'm gonna... I'm going right here. Right here, kind of near the Nevada border, but not
quite Nevada. I'm going here. Right here. Fuck! It was Reno! Oh, shit! That makes sense, because
right here, a border of California. I gotta stop thinking about Vegas. That right on the border,
that's right. Yeah, Reno does get snow. That's all right. Italy. Italy, France, and Italy. This is
Italy. Where in Italy? Italy. Done. That's speedrun right here. Wait, that was the... I thought that
was the Italian flag. Does this mean don't... is that a no entry, or is that a flag? Does this
mean you can't go in here? This looks like a, like, don't enter. Wait, what is that? That's not...
what flag is... that's a flag, but for what country? I thought it was, like, boats don't go this way.
Is that... that's not French. Italian. This is... okay, we're in Europe, and we're somewhere over here.
We're somewhere here, I would say. Not that far down. Somewhere, like... I'm gonna sit right here
for just a minute, because I'm not 100% sure. What? They got Dippin' Dots! They got Dippin' Dots! I
know where we are now. Whoa, these are fucking crazy. How come we don't have these? What is that?
I want that one. Nouvelle. Nouvelle. Solero. Mojito. Extreme. I don't think this is Italy.
I don't think this... I don't think this would be in Italy. What is this? Wait. Switzerland.
Rado Switzerland. This is... this is Switzerland. Or maybe it's not. It's probably... it's close to
Switzerland, though. It actually could be, like, one of these, like, here. I know we're... hold on,
I know where Switzerland is. Just give me a sec. Where the fuck... where is... where is it?
Where is... where is Switzerland? They don't have it listed on this one. All right. It's... it's... they
have a... they have a Switzerland ad and a French flag that leads me to believe, with a little bit
of deduction, that we are potentially really close to Switzerland in France. I'm gonna say
we're somewhere here. I want a little bit more info. Cars can drive down here? Wait, what?
Why are there just cars here? I thought that person crashed into the wall for a second. I was
like, what... why are they crashed? You can drive down here? I feel like this would be, like, a...
I would be terrified to drive a car here. There's, like, a lot of people.
You're gonna go up this? I don't know. That would, like, freak me out. What's that sign say?
I don't know. All right, so we're in France slash Switzerland. What's that say?
Okay, so tout du futur stationnaire. I gotta... wait, there's a... there's, like, a lake here. All right,
this... look, there was water, so I'm gonna say right here. Paris. Okay, really? Where's the Eiffel
Tower then? NA education? I feel like I'm, like, about to start, like, mission one of an RPG,
like, a Far Cry game. I'm, like, following the NPC somewhere. Where are... where... what... where did
put me? Where is this? What is... what's going on? Where are we? Where the fuck are we? It's...
it's the beginning of, like, a Hitman level. Is this, like, a... like, a bridge club for,
like, old people? What is this? No, this is a tour guide. There... this is a tour somewhere.
So this is... this must be a landmark. I don't know what it is, though. Let's keep going this
way. See if we get any more data. There's a lot of people here. I see camera. I see camera. Tour guide
camera. I see brochures on the ground. Damn. Is this a line? Okay, there's a tour guide here
giving a speech. Why did the Google car drive down here? Can you imagine just sitting there
getting, like, a tour? And, like, the... the Google car just scans all of your faces?
Virginia! Virginia. I see a Virginia t-shirt. What's on the hat? Oh, I can't read... lightning?
I can't read it. Is a tour... yeah, this is a tourist area in Virginia or somewhere in that area.
Okay, wherever this is, this is like a... why, the trees have names? Markings? Where is this? Hold on,
that's... oh, shit. Is this, like, an old, like... hold on. Where is this? This is, like, an old,
an old fucking, like, plantation or something? What the fuck? Okay, where are... where is... where
are we? Monte... Montecello. Montecello. Where's that? Where is that? Where is that? Okay, I'm
looking for it. Monte... I don't know. I don't know where it is. I'm just looking... I'm just looking
for the town. Oh, nope. All right, here's Maryland. Like, right here? Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah. Come on, I can't get this exact. I'm gonna say right here. Ooh, okay, it was... it was right
outside of Charlottesville. What the fuck? All right, well, we got... okay, we got that one.
Wait, what time is it? It was on the screen? Fuck, whatever. All right, so I... Ster and I got a...
I'm having too much fun, but Ster and I are... have a scheduled date for Dying Light 2. So,
maybe, like, one more. Maybe one or two more. Ster, if you're watching right now, then, like,
just, um, maybe, like, another 20, 30 minutes. All right, this is absolutely, absolutely
somewhere with a lot of green. A lot of green. Birds. He said birds! This is not in the United
States. This is somewhere else. Where? This is... I'm thinking, like, is this, like, Greek? No, not
Greek. It's, like, Spain? Is this South America? This could be, like, hmm. I need more intel. I
need a little bit more intel. Does that say? I can't read it. I don't know. I need a little
bit more intel. You think it's Greek? I'm not reading chat right now. I don't know. I just
think... I thought, like, Greek. I don't know. What is that? That's just, like, a picture of something.
A sign with a picture? Is that a picture of this road? Is it a mirror? Whoa! I changed my... I
changed... I think it's South America somewhere, I think. Like, here. I need way more intel. Ah!
Wait a minute.
French. No, it's not French. That's like a shitty dressing that somebody made up.
It's French dressing and ranch. Can I get some French dressing? That's... No, we're here. We're
somewhere here. We're somewhere here. I'm going for it. Right here. Oh, that was French! That was
French. Ah, I should have just known. I was speaking... I was saying, like, the French words
too. 28 fucking points. My god. Why did you think Brazil... I don't know, because Brazil is, like...
Brazil's got, like, so much, like, lush, like, beautiful green, and I don't know. I saw, like,
the... I thought it was, like, I don't know. I'm just... I'm not very well traveled, okay?
Not at all. Am I kind of stuck in this parking lot? Ooh. Estrella de Luz. Okay. Hold on. Hold on
here. Fashion store. Saldos. Vestuario, lingerie, digitaria, ten... All right. Okay, okay, okay,
okay. Okay, okay, okay. This is not France. Oh, hold on. All right. I don't know where this is.
Serras do Porto. I think it's in this area. Bem-vindo seja bem-vindo. Gondomar parades
velongo. Como alto, patrón sinio de sua excelencia. Something is excellent. I need to find out what
it is. President of the Republic. Preacher. I need more intel. This could be... this could go
either way here. I... this could go... it could be either one. This is either. I don't like Mondays.
Oh, Pedro. Yeah, yeah. Property. Come on, come on, come on, come on. Pedro. Es Pedro. Escola de...
I don't... this could go... it could be either way. This is either Europe or
like Central America or something maybe? I don't know. It's either North America, South America,
Europe, Asia. 999 euros. What is that? That's euro. So now where? It's got wi-fi.
Sondo P.T. Okay. I don't think we're on a coast though. Not a coast. Yeah, this is... this is...
I see a lot of green. A lot of green. Wait. Porto? Why does Porto ring a bell for me? I swear to
God, Porto was somewhere. Going right here. Oh, man. That was close. Okay, cool. All right.
I got it. Let's automatically get this set over here. Would be anywhere in this vicinity. Tamaya.
Okay. Tamaya. Parking a hundred something. Right? We got... no, never mind. I don't know. I really
don't know. This could... I mean the easy answer here is... what does that mean? What's that?
What is that? Is that... I don't know. And... wait. No. Is it Japan? Osaka. This is... yeah. This is
Japan. But where? In Japan. I'm just putting the names into memory so like if I see them.
Here we are. Let's go. Toyama. Anything that can get me closer though because this is pretty big
place. I'm not seeing a lot of green. I think we're somewhere down like in this area. I'm gonna
go right here. What? Wait. That was Nintendo? What do you mean? I didn't see Nintendo. Where?
Nintendo HQ? What? All the signs said Toyama. I didn't know I was next to Nintendo. I'm pissed
now. I saw all the signs. Toyama. Toyama. Toyama. I saw like three of them. Okay. This is... what are
these? These are very individually placed. Very deliberately spaced out trees. This is a farm of
some sort. What are they growing? This is very deliberate. These are berries. Wine. Wine land.
If it's wine then it's either somewhere in Italy, South America, or California. This is okay. I think
we've... or it could be Spain, Soviet, and Venta. Everything is just Italy. Every place is Italy for
I don't know why. It just is. Yeah. These are... these are wine trees. What's that? Yeah. Okay. So
this is... these are grapes. This is wine. What's a part of wine? I see a city in the distance. That's...
that's not Los Angeles. Is it LA? No. This is down here somewhere. Where's all the wine made?
Let's just go there. I... no. Where is that? Okay. I'm gonna go this way until I can figure out.
All right. We got somebody here on the road. What flag is that? Relax. It was a joke.
I've seen like motorcycles and that stop sign looks a little sus, doesn't it? I'm getting a lot
of minus twos. I'm just saying that stop sign does not look like a stop sign that... I don't think
this is America. I think we're in South America and we're about to get over to this city and we're
gonna see what it says. Wine country in South America or wine country in North America,
Central America. I don't know. This could be somewhere here. You know what? I'm... I'm going...
I'm going probably Argentina. That's what I'm thinking. I think this is potentially Argentina.
In fact, yeah. We're going right here in Argentina. All right. One more. One more. One more. One more.
Last one. One more. Maybe one more after that. Defensive stir like starts yelling at me.
All right. Where are we? The tow zone. Art, art. Art, art. Art for art. Object 19.
Burgtheater. The Burgtheater is over here. This is... is this like... it's Sweden maybe? Denmark,
Sweden. I don't want to look at chat. I don't want to give it away. Panzerhalle.
Wait. Is this Germany? Is this... no. Austria? Hungary? Slovenia? It's not Texas.
This is... I think this is Texas. This is absolutely Germany. But where? Object 12.
Let me get out to like a big street.
This is... this is definitely Germany. We got to find the city though.
Mobilix? No. Oh, it's... there was Burgtheater. The Burgtheater. Hamburg. Austria. Okay. All right.
I think I've got an idea. I'm thinking... I'm thinking Greek. I'm thinking Greece. See?
Greek lettering. Well, we're back. We're over here again. Okay. Well, we're... I know where we are.
I just don't know what... I need specific names. This is Japan. No, it's not. This is not Japan.
I don't know what are these... these things. It's like a weird... it's like... is that so you can see
like over here while you're driving this way? Where in Japan? This looks a little more country
to me because we're out here with the big mountains. The big... I don't know. This feels
a little more country. I don't think this is in a major city. This is not like Tokyo or like
Kyoto or, you know, I... this is... this feels kind of like country. What is going on here?
What is this? That... is that water? This is crazy. This is... okay. That's cool. It's making...
they're making rice? Really? You just like make your own rice? I feel... they all live... I feel
like you... I feel like... like if you live in a place like this, you'd live like a fucking
hundred plus years. Like I don't have like rice behind me. I've got like rocks and like dirt and
concrete. Like imagine if I had like a fucking whole thing behind me. They're like... I could
just get my own shit. I can't do that though. I would ruin everything. It takes a lot to do that.
You make your own rice. You make your own like fucking tomato. People... I mean people do that.
People like make their own tomatoes. I don't know. I feel like it's different. It's different than
you taking a picture of like the tomato vine you bought. Like on Instagram. Like this is one of
them. Like maybe if you live in like the farmland or something, right? I'm not talking about like
the... like the fresh tomatoes. And there's like three. Like that's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about like you literally live and eat off of like your land. Grow your own tomatoes.
Don't you live in the U.S.? I live in the fucking desert, man. All right. I'm saying Japan,
grow some agave. Yeah. I mean I could grow... I could grow agave. But what's that gonna do? Like
I'm gonna squeeze that in my coffee. All right. I'm going here. Right here. Done. It's close. I knew
it was like kind of in the country. Grow your own weed. Okay. This is weird. I never... Okay.
I might... This might be weird. Oh! I didn't tell you about my dream. Okay. But this is more
important. So it's gonna be kind of messy because I don't really... It's hard to piece it together
because I woke up and I like fell back asleep and woke up. I think this is why I have a headache.
So I had a dream... Remember the dream that I had a while back where I was naked on stream
and like I went up like this and like my like my you know genital area showed like a little bit
right here and I freaked out and nobody said anything in the chat and I deleted the vlog and
shit. This was... That evolved. This was... This was 2.0 that dream. So let me see if I can like
piece this together. I need to take a second. In this dream, it was a big event stream and it was
like there's a ton of people watching and it was a big event, right? Whatever it was. And I don't
know why. I have no idea why. My brain just decided to do this. At some point like in the
middle of this stream, we had to go BRB and like I had to change like costume. I gotta get in my
new... I gotta get in a costume. Okay. Costume change. And I don't know why but like when I came
back like from the BRB like at five minutes, I was naked. Like naked with a towel like in like
with me. Like walking around like I had just got out of the shower and like maybe I didn't like
expect that like the camera was... I don't know why this was happening. Like I was changing like
in like an area or something and like the camera came back and I was like on stream and I was like
what the fuck is going on? Why am I on... What's happening? And like I freaked out and like the
stream ended, right? Here's the... Here's the fucking crazy part. Apparently... This is like
three hours of the stream had been going at this point. Apparently, the stream was not pushed to
the Twitch servers. So we were... This was just broadcasted to nothing. So I was like no way.
Wait, what? So we haven't even been streaming? Oh my fucking god. This... That's so... Oh my god.
Thank god. Like there was a camera problem. I don't know what fucking happened. Whatever, right?
So I was like wait a minute. So we have like the studio recording version of that whole stream
and it was like Community Jake was like yeah yeah we got the whole thing recorded man it's all good
and I'm like fucking Jesus. I don't know how I like walked into frame. I don't know what happened
but like wait a minute. That whole stream was like a bunch of money, a bunch of time.
Why don't we just like censor that part and I'll just like... We'll just do a rebroadcast,
right? Instead of removing the scene entirely. I was like why don't we just like rebroadcast,
like play the video and like just because I didn't like push the Twitch servers or something.
What the fuck? So instead of removing the whole thing, just cut that part. We had like a black
censor bar over me during that part and the worst part about it is when it got to that point like
I don't know if it was I edited it I guess but like when it got to that part and like one frame
was not moved correctly and you still saw me naked and I'm being like what the fuck man what
I'm still naked you what happened we're supposed to censor that part did I miss it
and like everybody freaked out in chat. Like I don't know why our brains do this shit. Why
wouldn't I have just taken that part out of the stream? Why wouldn't I have just taken that part
out? Why did it have to be there with a censor bar? The fact that like it was streamed and like it
got caught like holy shit oh my god thank god I caught that oh we can just re-upload we can
just do like another broadcast but make sure make sure we censor that part so stupid that was the
dream because please keep your dream journal if you don't I know I always say I'm going to but I
every time I have a dream I wake up I kind of feel like shit and I go I gotta go back to bed I feel
terrible and I put my head down and I fall back asleep you go over the dream like 30 plus times
in your brain and then you fall back asleep you wake up an hour or two later and it's gone
and maybe a little bit is still there all right where are we and now I have like a really bad
migraine today so it's kind of annoying if you have a lucid dream yes and the thing about a
lucid dream is when you start to become aware that you're lucid dreaming you have to like use
magical superpowers to concentrate to keep yourself from trying to get out so you sit there and you go
wait don't move you kind of have to not move you have to sit there and just go don't move don't
just don't think and just let yourself become lucid without becoming completely lucid because
if you're like here we go I'm in the lucid dream you're out once you are aware of lucid dreaming
stop and just don't do anything don't think don't move let yourself just solidify into the lucid
dream if you want to because once you're aware of it it starts to pull you out it's really hard to do
your lucid dream just look at your hands no I mean no no here's the thing if you flick lights
they don't work if you look at a clock it won't work you can't here's things about dreams that
are interesting if you use a light switch in a dream it will not turn on it won't work that's
how you'll be like wait what the fuck's happening if you try to read in a dream you cannot read
that part of your brain is not turned on so if you look at a clock or a or a like a piece of
text or a book you're going to be it's going to be just mess you did I don't know what that says I
can't read that it's nothing it's like this alien language if you look in a mirror be careful
because when you look in a mirror your brain decides to fill in those blanks because a
mirror does not work in a dream so you will see horrifying twisted shit if you look in a mirror
I'm serious like don't be careful when you look in a mirror uh because your brain has to pretend
that you're actually looking into a mirror and your your mouth your eyes might get like big and
like black and like your chin might be like shaking it's seriously like a horror movie
oh yeah it's weird I saw that I saw that in a reddit post too you see the thing is I learned
all this from I watched a movie called waking life okay and that movie came out in like 2002
so I did not read the reddit post that you're talking about oh I read reddit too Jeremy well
not everybody reads their computer screen why is he so mad because I wanted to be the one that gave
you that info not a reddit post I wanted to be the smart one that you guys go oh oh oh oh wow really
I go yeah yeah I found out how you didn't yeah you know let me tell you something else you guys
tell me shit all the time that you've like read it in game informer okay like oh yeah you didn't
know this about this video game yeah because you fucking read about it on like the IGN review
I didn't we everybody gets info from somewhere else yeah when you get really mad at me in a week
and a half when I don't know where the item is an elden ring you wikipedia'd it you looked up where
the item was you had that info I was close hmm all right I actually got a ping stir because it's
been almost two hours and I told him he was gonna be like probably like 4 30 liar why Andy don't
ever listen to Jeremy when he ever says anything always add at least an hour to everything he ever
says um but hey come on come on hey valve time that's how I can hide behind that yeah valve time
sooner or later I'll come up with a Wii U brick that plays Call of Duty in the bathroom all right
where are we it's not Canada bicycles expected so like okay it is but Canada is so huge Canada
is enormous like how can you even know where you even are I see uh some activity up here though
uh real fruit protein smoothies three dollars at the McCafe is that I'm gonna sneeze I think
Saint Paul yeah get that out of the way I can't see Saint Paul all right where's eh where's Saint
Paul good luck I'm not even gonna look because it's like Canada is like as big as Russia so like I
don't I'm not gonna even guess Saint Paul Canada alpha food whoa what's that Watson's pharmacy
pharmacy and wellness center chiropractic personal training center no no no no no no no no no no
guardian overseas shipping packing moving crating shipping shipping LTD there's another
little intersection here what is this oh come on that was a real estate sign come on what's
this teleporting bullshit what's it say uh Ottawa where's Ottawa I have no idea Ottawa
where's Ottawa Ottawa Ottawa Ottawa Ottawa it's Ontario Ottawa where's Ottawa oh yep thank you
thank you that was within 1.6 miles folks got it thank you that was 1.6 miles thank you don't tell
me you think that Greenland is huge uh I mean it is kind of huge how can you tell me that this is
not huge this is enormous on maps they make Greenland like bigger than the entire like
North America it's because it's distorted well where is it then it's distorted look at how big
that is this shit's like Northrend okay where are we so how big is um is Greenland okay if I
were to take Greenland and move it over here on top of Texas would it be bigger than Texas
or higher bigger or lower than Texas yes actually yes so Texas is huge what are you talking about
Spain Greece oh nothing there okay wait wait what's over this way okay I see a big
a big vista here I want to see it all right there we are okay okay all right all right all right
I'm thinking somewhere around here or stir I know I know we're done we're done stir we're done we're
done all right I got it I got it right here that was really good really close I mean not really
but okay all right it's time I get the camera off I fucking hate this uh I'm gonna ping stir I'm
gonna take a quick pee break when I come back we're gonna be playing Dying Light 2 again with stir
for a couple hours two three hours something like that I don't know and uh I'm gonna get the first
I'm gonna get this first try before I go one more let's do one more here we go I'm gonna take
literally 10 seconds one two three four five six seven eight nine ten what's that say okay I got
it right here here we are in Missouri thank you it's fucking Greenland whatever it was all right
I'm out I'm out I'm out we're back I'll see you guys in two minutes or so and we're gonna get set
up with Dying Light 2 I gotta play more GeoGuessr this is a lot of fun I'll be right back oh one more
round of GeoGuessr so are you uh how are you doing how am I doing did we get to the do you want to
keep playing uh do you want to keep playing do you want to keep playing it sounds like you're
bringing up a lot of times like oh we're just talking about like uh sandwiches too much and
I'm like don't want to I have like too much fun when I'm with you and I owe my game crashed
do you want to play GeoGuessr or like a round or two uh you want to co-op some GeoGuessr I mean I
think there's a co-op mode but I think um you have to like pay for it though I could just look at
your screen you could just look at the screen and like yeah like let's do that how I mean I'm not
going to help because I've only left the U.S. like once no it's don't worry let me open this up
let's play some GeoGuessr so this is let me explain how this works
so GeoGuessr is a game yeah I know how it works okay so you tell the people someone here doesn't
know no no no they know that no no this is a policy that I have it's called no chatter left
behind I feel like a lot of streamers will you know they won't will leave someone behind and
they'll just be there like I don't understand what is he looking at okay and so you have to
explicitly every 10 minutes whenever someone asks what's going on is make sure you in detail
re-explain what's going on so can we get one good explanation from you no no no everyone
everybody knows how to play this I just unlocked a razor cannon a two-handed bike razor cannon
wait you got a cannon yeah and now it's gone wait what oh I was looking at something else
I'm gonna not capture my screen I didn't play GeoGuessr it's a game where hold on
can you please explain it why can't I capture it it's annoying so I have to I might have to
like restart my obs this is annoying don't do that it obs crash uh it actually may have hold on
black screen andy I know I know I know I know I don't know what happened hold on let me try this
what the fuck what the fuck did I get it ah I got it that was weird I had to restart this like
three times all right I'm gonna change my stream title because this is wrong so as you see let's
go and get that face cam turned on so as you see wait I'm gonna have to see your face you don't
have to but okay so can one and can one of the mods please change it to GeoGuessr you don't
change your own stream titles I have to like get I don't I do but if somebody can do it it's easy
all right so as you see on the screen here you have to decide where we currently are where are
we where it could be anywhere in the entire world it's just any place that has been captured by a
google device right so google um like street view google uh cars google taxis google bicycles
whatever it is I'm gonna do one and then you can do one okay well we're not gonna do it together
oh wait that would be like I so I want to know how well how much you know I don't know anything
okay well then I'm not then just watch the street just turn the stream on and watch
okay just watch your stream that's what I'm doing now I'm watching Jerma stream all right I think
this is I'm seeing some text up here koditar koditar.fi I think that might be Finland I think
we're in a Finland area here yeah I'm just watching would you say sir that this is fi
Finland makes a lot of sense doesn't it um I mean that makes sense okay if we keep going down
we're looking for something that would be give us an idea of exactly where we could be
we're in Finland somewhere but can we narrow down the city well how how far do you get to
travel down the road before the thing is like hey come on man you can as long as you want
there's no time limit unless you set a time limit so there is none okay I feel like you should be
setting a time limit then because couldn't you just drive around and just ask for directions
I mean yeah but the whole point is that you don't spend too much time you just wait zoom
in on that license plate license there are here yeah they're all blurred out you got to find a
non-blurred one and I'll track it they all license plates are blurred out like can we get some can
we get some facial recognition no those are blurred out too have you ever used google street view
before I have but sometimes they might miss one all right I'm gonna say this is pretty this is
pretty the green uh lush environment how close of a guess like how close to the city do you
consider yourself a winner I would say within five miles you've won within five to ten miles I say
that that's a win that's pretty tight but within like 50 miles I think that you did a good job
okay all right we got a bus station here what is it to blur it out can't read it 4 000 is a good
score yeah that'll get you within probably like what 50 plus miles uh there's a lot of bikes
100 miles maybe a lot of motorbikes over to your left there is that's kind of cool okay I'm going
you know where I'm going I'm going Finland seeing a lot of rain I'm thinking of going I think we're
in uh Kivola just based on nothing that was that was all right that was all right that's not 130
miles that's not even good you said within 50 miles was good job yeah 131 miles that's okay
that's not bad that's more than double what would what a good job would be and you're patting
yourself on the back by your own definition lane control all right we get this is english
lane control on main road ahead lane open lane closed gizzards gazzards for decorating wait we're
I don't know we're driving on the left side of the road though so I think this is somewhere in
Europe it's always Europe goals fabrics okay this to me this looks like England look at this like
uh Big Ben clock thing that's England do you know what I mean hell any bank on the windows
under the clock tower and the windows oh okay so this is helenny antique center all right so
where's helenny that's what we're gonna figure out I'm gonna go to England helenny I'm saying
maybe the London area what do you think maybe somewhere in London um let's keep going somewhere
like in America like I've heard of America hearing care this is the driving on the right side of the
we're on the other side of the road it's not America dolphin hand car wash we need to find
helenny there's so many little towns here though it could be any of these orly new romney is it
cheating if you just google helenny yes that is 100 cheating city center all right barnsley is
that way at some point we have helenny we have barnsley and we would barnsley be I need a big
town like I need a sign that says like london freeway that way or something I feel like you
have the city name and the note the next most adjacent city like what what more do you need
you need to get it right you have to get it on the map yes so like shouldn't you be looking on
the map rather than around the city because we already have everything we need but we but we
don't though because we're looking for something that can tell us where a major city might be
located like a road sign or like oh over here okay low fields park sheffield city council
stir excuse me look at where we are sheffield and that's why you spend a little extra time
now we've got sheffield the next step is to look for it's there it's right south of it right here
helenny if you zoom in heli that's heli not helenny we probably read it wrong do it do it
just no no that's not right this is god please please please it's not gonna be right this is
heli you click please please I'm not gonna click it because we could get we're co-opping we could
get like 10 000 points if you get it right you did the first one this one's mine I noticed the
first sign I'm in charge click it literally if we spent literally if we spent like five more
minutes we would have found it 900 yards and you're complaining but you opened up a google map
what what are you talking about didn't you just say why don't you just type in the location and
I heard I saw the the name we thought it was wasn't even the name so even if I googled it I'd be
looking for helenny not heli all right do you see what's on the screen now I see what's on the
screen you're just mad because I got like within a like a mile okay so this is either this is
potentially United States somewhere like in middle America this could be somewhere in like Japan or
I need to find a main road I feel like that's cheating cheating is typing in helenny into google
it wasn't helenny and pretending you know where it is click it click it yeah I just tried to
wink and both of my eyes bugged out there's a freeze frame in there somewhere that is terrifying
all right here we go we got a road where we going okay okay this is potentially somewhere
somewhere in Asia and get some signs here okay I think this is let's get over here closer I don't
think this is not Japan is it Japan no it's not this can't be Japan is it Japan I've gotten Japan
so many times in like the five times that I did this in a row well everyone everyone loves Japan
but it's a random place in the world mm-hmm okay it is Japan yeah ask that guy you pass the guy on
a bike ask him okay no I don't think so so what sign are you looking for when you can't read the
language I'm looking for you in there's a lot of times this the town name will be in English
or at least written out so you just do this forever I mean it's kind of the point of the game
in Japan yeah hmm big solar field out here this is the countryside they're not going to do that
they might they might yeah they might I mean we're just you're on a nice drive right now you guys
got to enjoy the journey I guess is what I'm learning yeah it's cool you should play this on
stream tomorrow so I can watch I I would be playing with like 30 second timers I hear German likes to
go fast I just I'm just I just want to know man make sure everybody's aware that like literally
this is in English and everyone was think said I was an idiot wildlife protection area shows
Shaozong prefecture wildlife protection area whatever it says I don't know you told them
your mic is still compressed no it's not I think mine is mine sound like I reset mine it still
sounds like it's messed up which is why I didn't want to do this joke in the first place because
now we're all the way down here and we're just going to keep doing the joke the whole time
I don't want to turn that on right now but I'm going to so what I think we're going to do here
I think we need to go a little bit further down I think what you need to do to prove that you are
a good geoguessor is just open up the map and we're both going to guess the spot and whoever's
closer wins fine we've been driving around for a while now okay all right all right where are you
going I have to go first if I go first you'll just see what it is and well uh down there by
shikoku that's where I was going to go to oh well then let's zoom in let's see let's see who gets
closer if we're really going to do that okay that's as far as you can zoom in I mean I can keep going
you want do you want southern coast you want northern coast what do you want I'm going I'm
going right here that's that's a good spot I think you I think you might have it not even close
all right so you get it you get the idea I get the idea rumble fish what's that oh I thought it
was going to be literally right there I thought it was going to be right there I'm calling that
number wait what's that seafood unified seafood company import and export holding nothing there
stanford ab that's very that's kind of that's kind of a name ah yama yamasa enterprises oh no
fish cake importer of hawaiian foods okay wait wait yeah this looks like la ocean choice seafood
we're like hold on like the quality of living looks like it went way down so we must actually
you know we're 100 in america yeah what's that skyline that's not la manu baptist okay uh what's
with this what what's with this picture there's like street sign right here I can't read it
well keep driving grandpa I can't read any of the signs all right hold on definitely not la
that's the one thing that we know for sure right now okay hold on hey wait wait wait operation no
it's dot org that's a dot org ah made in no downtown women's center downtown somewhere
we're downtown somewhere remember yeah no shit brand opening and Pedro wholesale center all right
we've got a name dude 80 dude just zoom into la on the map this is not los angeles do it
do it or you're a coward I'm I'm doing it right now san jose up top left go up the coast there's a
san jose what that's what was on the thing right now that was san Pedro san Pedro okay then just
click la dude we're in hollywood where's hollywood where's how downtown la hollywood's where up I
don't know where hollywood is I know it's like right here somewhere isn't it it's not la hmm
where's hollywood I don't know never heard of it there it is okay but hollywood we might be able
to get this exact yeah but that that's a bus and that bus drives around and that bus isn't
representative of hollywood that's right this is bait California silk yeah they have wheels this
is los angeles oh wow really san Pedro is right there at san Pedro road fourth street san Pedro
the corner of fourth street and san Pedro wait waiting come on it's like right here somewhere
seriously what what about those emails you're saying it as a joke I don't take kindly to that
you make that joke every time we hang I'm not joking you say that every single time we've ever
been in a call so I'm just no I'm making fun of you okay all right I'm just gonna go right here
it's like it's not even hollywood it was downtown LA yeah I was gonna say that should look like skid
row whatever jerma's never been to that part of LA forgive him I've been to calif I've been to LA
like he's only seen it from the top floor of one of the skyscrapers I've been to LA maybe five
times my entire life okay where are we one of the skyscrapers I I've seen a lot of I'm gonna say
I think I think we're in South America somewhere like in here that's my gut reaction wait google
maps is I guess they you said they have google bikes they're driving around like yeah this is
this is not a car yeah that would be weird this is either South America or somewhere in Asia
a lot of terrain looks a lot like what's the name of that place I don't know it could be like
Central America could be wait I got a sign what does the sign say uh yeah you're right there
what is that I don't know what language that is um okay that removes South America for me
but then it has to be over here Antarctica no it's not uh I can't go any further oh he's got a
guess he's got a geo guesser uh wait okay I'll go down this road is it something here uh
on that little note what's this I can't wait until the future when you can play this game and
on like a drone and a drone just goes around and annoys people and you can like put money into the
the game client to like annoy people and be like hey where where is this and you can like ask
questions and everyone in the world knows the game you're kind of describing like tourism in
general like people go and to travel to different places and they like walk around like the books
and the maps and shit and like ask people stuff yeah this is gonna be a thing they're gonna sell
like a drone you activate the geo guesser drone and you have to pay money to ask questions to
people all right I'm going for a guess starting the business I'm gonna say it's somewhere in here
uh let's go with put it uh I'm I would put my guess right in the middle
it's right here of the ocean there just so that I can get all of those islands
and equal distance I'm gonna say hey hey hey hey hey is that the same that's that's the same
writing isn't it oh bingo right here let's go right here island that was cheating how was it
cheating all right so that was cool uh 65 miles you're 15 miles off of being good all right I'm
gonna do the challenge to play today's daily do you have what it takes to become a geo guesser
master navigator start let's start the game maybe you can get your I'm gonna make a multiplayer room
with you since he has geo guesser pro oh give me what I got your pro I'm peeing just entertain the
audience for a minute I'm just supposed to sit here and entertain the audience when I have no
control over the mouse the keyboard uh he's the one with the geo guesser pro and apparently I can
play with him and generally speaking oh I'm actually shocked he didn't mute and deafen
because he's usually so scared of what I'm going to say while he's gone but the truth is that I'm
a nice guy I don't say anything weird I mean like sometimes I talk about like like weirder stuff
like Hillary's emails and like all the comment in it and those are just like it's just life
it's all exists yeah I don't know everyone's obsessed with cum these days talk about furries
well I don't know does your most chat know about I feel like I talk about my furry policy so often
I'm spreading the word at this point you gotta gotta be a furry now to get the tax credits
for when it's uh it's a thing in the future and you can check the box for furry but if you don't
have evidence now that you were always a furry and you're just gonna look like you were playing
along everyone has to know that by now I've told pretty much everyone what's he saying is he saying
something bad did he say something bad what do you say I'm giving them like uh legal tax advice
don't do that please all right we have three minutes here we go Northwestern University
that's that's California right there California uh okay where probably in the northwest wait what
the fuck dude but that's California no it's not I just looked like California it was shaped like
California okay all right I got two and a half minutes all right uh I'm gonna go over here I
think it's in that same kind of area that we were before like down here maybe I'm gonna say I'm just
gonna go for it we only have two minutes I'm gonna say like the Philippines or our timing this is
the challenge the challenge no no no no no no it's not no it's not this is over here this is like
somewhere over here don't look I'm not looking all right I'm gonna say like uh Bangladesh right
here oh my fucking god I've nailed it next round okay good one yeah you know pretty good the time
do you get you get more points this one's gonna be hard Oklahoma it could be we gotta go kind of
fast down this road though there's no way you don't have time you need to guess these long roads
you're never gonna see anything oh my god you're just losing time shit uh this is not Oklahoma man
this is way Oklahoma's not like this what is this like side of the road are we on we are on the
right side of the road is driving you can see the car behind you okay so we okay so where is this
though this is anywhere it could be uh I'm gonna say damn it's like a cloudy day too so it's like
it's hard to tell um hmm I think this would be further north more like a Montana maybe I could
see a Montana Wyoming Dakota kind of area let's uh let's go with Wyoming I'm gonna say right in
this kind of area here like here Wyoming let's go yo I was not even close I was gonna say some
of the trees looked a little yeah for us but the right side of the road and this is uh I think this
is European I don't see these signs in America looks like California yeah I think it's California
look at these little green things what are these little green containers these are like tiny little
recyclings and to Nova are these really small or am I crazy these are tiny well Americans have a
lot of garbage that's all we have look at how little these are okay yeah this is like normal
size like rubbish for a family it's a Nova Antenna Nova I there's something going on up here this is
somewhere in South America probably shit we're right in the middle of nowhere again
this could be this that was like a dead animal or something this could be the same exact spot
this looks pretty much uh it's either okay I'm saying down in that same exact area or
somewhere in like Europe like here any input I have never left my home all right well I'm going
with like Russia I'm going with like I did hear earlier that you always go with Russia a good
reason you think everywhere in Europe is Russia it's like ratio okay we're this is Asia but where
in Asia let's go which way look what looks more populated down here I don't know it's not Japan
again is it Japan again again I mean it's been this is like so how rare would this be to have
it in like anywhere in the world and I've gotten Japan like seven times okay here we are that's a
nice hill that's what I really I'm liking this this tree hill Japan's fucking beautifully okay
oh yeah you got names Naroshi and and Suzu and Naroshi Suzu's closer 15 kilometers yeah
Suzu is closer oh no was it Naroshi I got one minute and 52 seconds to find it this could be
big points here Naroshi or Suzu Naroshi or Suzu come on
hmm no come on one minute you need this man Naroshi or Suzu
um I need this 40 seconds hmm shit yeah also you could look for 249 highway 249 25 seconds
there's so many numbers on the screen good luck 15 seconds yeah this is a fake image
from uh this place isn't real Africa wait this is where I clicked
you must not have clicked in time or something because that's I'm pretty sure that's like zero
zero longitude latitude yeah fuck god damn it you just scared my cat I'm sorry I didn't know
man you you all right this is we got what side of the road are we on
precaution radar in operate okay so this is probably this is South America
or it could be like Central America too where let's go okay something up here what is on top
of this car it's like a dog chasing his tail what is that hey I all right I'm gonna say
I'm gonna try to get this quick what's that sign uh come to Brazil further come on yeah we got it
we got an L that explains the whole thing I'm going for it well okay it was it was Mexico all
right there it is did it I did my daily challenge I got that way how many 7 000 points what do you
do with these points just nothing only one person has to pay for two player you can stop the awkward
co-op well I think the stream is probably over oh you don't want to do just like one more Geo
guesser where we're co-op you don't want to like learn how to do this right now I mean do you do
you want to do this I want to beat you right now you want to throw down I want to destroy you okay
I think you have to like make an account yeah you have to like go to you're gonna make an account
yeah okay they're getting I'm giving them my social security this website uses cookies they
have all my data I'll play for free now this does this does be what just I don't I would just like
block your screen for a minute are you streaming uh yeah I'm streaming I'm going through my email
right now yeah I would just make just block your screen do a screen blocker okay this is
my password guys anyone wants to join start a party complete our quick tutorial to understand
the basics of the game I'm clicking the map invite friends hold on it's giving me a three step
tutorial this is why I click I'm just clicking I was thinking about maybe giving you some time
to do it hey I don't want to hear it from you all right so we do uh distance duel battle royale
what should we do battle royale distance should we do distance I don't know what we should do
so I have okay so guys I have an invite link should I just like send him that link and he
clicks it yeah give it to me on discord make sure you're hiding your screen you know I'm not I'm
not showing my screen yeah my password is on screen actually be careful because I don't know
I've never used this website before I signed up with an email yeah I so are you ready to click
this so do battle royale countries do no do distance distance is our distance time do you
giving me a link yes I am so there's a friends menu I haven't added any friends yet don't show
your screen I gave you a link don't keep your screen private so what should I do just a duel
I just want to we just want to 1v1 duel fucker duel okay duel okay and I added you to my friends
list okay so now if I did if I click duel I should have okay duels the world or hold on
round time 15 seconds holy shit no holy let's go let's fucking go no 15 seconds is not
at least 30 seconds all right here we go you ready okay here we go 30 seconds three two one
good luck punk oh my god it's got sound effects it does have sounds all right where are we don't
you by the way if you give me if you give me a hints you fucked up if you give me hints you
fucked up there's the timer easy is there a timer uh it shows a five minute timer at the top five
minutes I thought it was 30 seconds yeah I don't see a timer anywhere is there no timer who knows
you're the one that did this I put it to 30 seconds oh it might start counting with oh
yeah you guessed and then it sets the time on me so I'm the one that needs to panic where you
gonna go where you gonna go where you gonna go where you gonna go uh I'm thinking I'm thinking
I wasn't ready I didn't know how the game worked 10 seconds no one explained it to me
am I gonna pull a germa oh sorry I just lose that's closer okay go go go go go
I don't know the controls yet you're a master at this you just just click on the screen okay
there's a lot of trash this is the US I it might not be actually okay don't go down my road get
out here leave what I'm going with the make you have to guess within 30 seconds try that
now I was hit with I might be way off oh I was in the right continent
South Africa yeah I've seen a lot of offenses like that in South Africa
it was a rambunctious guess okay very very green oh this is repeat I've actually did
this one it's Greece how do they have repeats when it's the whole world it's a fucking repeats
it on sometimes it does it are you fucking with me are we clicking Greece
no I'm just I'm just saying what do you mean you're just saying I'm just messing around
sometimes it happens he's trying to throw me off where is it I know what I'm gonna I just don't
know where it is okay fine I didn't even notice that you got it's okay how did I beat you on that
because I clicked Greece because you said Greece thought it was Sweden I don't know why
this is like really dramatic wait that's
hit him with the timer I'm thinking of hitting you with a timer I thought that I'm so stupid
I'm gonna hit you with a timer in a minute here oh you want to do it to me that's fine yeah um
who's closer by a tiny bit you were a little bit you know I thought it was Munich because
I saw a sign wait what the fuck is what did that say I thought that said it was healing me less
really really we just got the full health double damage on this one okay oh shit
I should have taken an extra 30 seconds tripled yeah you could win I could win with this triple
damage of these bushes and seconds dude come on how did you how did you even know that how did
you even know that because I see I had previous knowledge from hump ahead how did you know that
just looking around there's a lot of clues in the environment also how many of these have you done
before that feels kind of fucked up I've done this like five times total yeah but if you keep
getting the same ones you like twice you said you've already gotten these I mean it's it's
likely you're gonna get similar the same country more there is a whole world what do you mean there
before I was actually fucking with you when the grease thing came up I made it up
I don't think you're making it up yeah I don't yeah he's reading chat
I'm not reading chat you're gonna go back and look at your eyes I'm gonna get over here man
uh I'm going for it I'm just gonna go for it I'm going for it yeah I feel like I just need
to click something I don't know I don't know I don't know no no no no no no I don't know
god damn it are you seriously that much closer than me got them triple damage
five times you want to come back you cheater fuck out of the way
five times damage got a sniper dive on your head one shot one kill
got a bullet with your name on it
I do do I get your one more one more one more one more one more one more one more last one okay
15 seconds sure Russian roulette last one in the barrel why California because it's the first
place I could click into a half a second I don't know man what the fuck um I I don't I actually I
don't I have no idea how would you put that pressure on me because I'm trying I'm trying
to do the pressure I'm trying to put the heat on really I'm just trying I'm just you know
um um um um I don't know I'm kind of banking on you not clicking anything
or apparently just like accidentally consistently like getting a little bit closer I knew that was
like somewhere up in kind of the European area yeah 15 seconds is too much I'm giving them too
much time okay thought I knew but now I don't clicking you could any moment yeah I don't think
you're prepared I don't think you are either I don't think you're ready for this
I don't think you can handle this I know exactly where we are I don't think you know I've been
down this dirt path many times so how come you haven't clicked if you know where we are
you're so confident I'm definitely more certain now
can I change my answer I would have beat you honestly if I could have changed my answer I
would have beat you in one turn but what would have made you what what made you change your mind
after you clicked just get the language oh this is Greece okay might as well just want to stop
now this is Greece yeah that's Greece right there so I would so click Greece if you're so confident
if you're so confident it's so residential it's so hard to tell
oh so you heal from this one you don't like damage the other person this is just a healing
room I am understanding I get it give me something to fucking work with it not like
city skyline signs what is that supposed to mean I don't know I don't know man I don't know I
I saw that sign I don't I can't do flags you know kind of nice houses here a little
little techie little a little modern I like that design there I got a little bit of information
right there like when there's pressure I can't do anything like when I'm up against like somebody
else I'm just going to sit here with my fingers up my nose yeah just guess what do you just like
just 10 seconds like all it matters is whether you do that I don't know I'm gonna say like here
somewhere oh it's CA not California Canada but if I had a few seconds to think that through I
wouldn't have clicked that but it's not always you know in life you don't always have as much
time as you want I know but like if I had if my brain was not in like dreamland and like the music
it's like who wants to be a millionaire like hurry up music yeah this one's definitely
Greece I know that for sure whoa oh please come on Spain now what do you mean Spain
oh dude I've been here before yeah this is Greece stop saying Greece you started it yeah I started
and you just won't let it end I gotta get up to a road this one is I'm brain dead where the fuck is
that oh I unplugged my thing it looks like that at all you're gonna guess this I feel like I have a
slowing down I'm trying to figure it out slowing it down a little I don't know where it is this is
totally just for four times damage dude oh I'm gonna kill you it's all gonna be over if you
you might where the fuck is that dude yeah I don't actually know where it is
I could just I could get you right now oh fuck come on dude really I don't know I don't know
you're looking a little dead here
California I was looking at every I saw the Mariana Islands and I was looking at every I
checked the islands over there and I fast and I just like there's so many islands off of California
it starts it's not like this passport center and these trees are so not I know but it's like
office of the secretary like commonwealth of the northern but that sounds like that sounds
American to me yeah it is I think it's like it's a US territory somewhere in the fucking ocean out
there so I just clicked in the ocean all right actual last one one more okay actual last one
it is American I know but like I thought it was gonna be like right there yeah we don't we don't
let anyone be independent just play all of our independence all right let's do it fuck that
I'm one let's go you're gonna get three zeroed so bad I've been here before yeah but like okay so
stir has never played this before but you never know when you unlock a new game that you're
actually really good at and you never knew it I'm not very good at GeoGuessr so he could be
actually pretty good at it and he's like finding a new thing that he's actually really good at and
he could like just play and stream it and stuff I always have problems with languages I think as
as an artiste I pick up on a lot of like tiny little artistic like architecture details
that I've seen before but I have no fucking clue where this one will be
real it didn't count my click did it where were you clicking it didn't count my click I was so
close to that why was there Russian and English oh man I saw a sign it was English Russian and then
um like um Malaysian whoever was I saw a lot of weird shit I was thinking Madagascar for a
second I was way too zoomed out to take tourists I thought was the safer guess
there's a lot of places like uh only one place I've been where did me and Ashley go
Cayman Island there remind me a lot of that where everything is made for Americans to tourism there
uh wow we were both waiting why was there a French flag it was like a French flag right there
uh street names are French I just like I was like I'm okay French but it's even the name of this
language there's so many different languages it's so hard to oh I have no idea
it looks like the one
yeah the ring was engraved with the elvish it's elvish oh my god give me a break
give me a break you're the one that guessed but they were they were two how did you know I
guessed because it gave me 15 seconds but how do you know that how do you know that yeah I didn't
know that that was a literal guess I mean we're it's geoguessr is what I'm saying here so you
didn't look at my camera and see my hands go up and do that I don't know I'm looking at your camera
dude they have the fucking longitude here oh it's just I think I saw somebody's dick what was that
what was that that was weird what's going on what was that I couldn't even click I was dumbfounded
what do you mean it said like peep show and there was a guy sitting on a chair it freaked me out
okay well you can heal up this round you don't have to see any dicks that I was literally like
oh here comes the peep show and there was a guy like sitting down like this it could be any of
these it's crazy how like how many we've done in a row and they've all been greased we had the same
idea but whatever I mean you healed I did a little bit of double damage
that is actually almost exactly where I was clicking I saw this thing that was like an ad
for like the Mediterranean I can't lose like that that's fucking lame yeah really I was seriously
was almost exactly where that was and then you lose the whole thing oh yeah that was bad I just
had been holding a two-handed sword over my head just queuing it up charging it I let it go and
killed you I'm like an hour growing you for that this is the most powerful I've ever been
fucking slimy little dirt bag where are you where are you wait that's not friends oh shit
wrong flag yeah I there were Russian butters I wear that's the wrong flag yeah I know I say
this often but as a well-traveled man I'm pretty sure I've been here before
I stayed in this house Coca-Cola that's actually a big
to me again oh I was closer what's it Aloha like Guam again I keep doing this exaggerated like
annoying hog face I'm probably pissing off so many people they don't know it's exaggerated
I don't know where it is there is I think I fucked up damn that was not bad for like
guessing within five seconds I must go to on Norway how did you guess that close goddamn
because I saw nl and I saw the point I didn't see anything I saw like one word and I was like
ah somewhere around here why did I go this way what was wrong with me I was distracted by my own
my own talk this could be a lot of different places unfortunately
I have a feeling you actually I don't know I don't know how I feel like you are not going
to be able to I actually feel like I have a weird kind of wild guess here it's not that wild so I
think I'm just going to go for it and see if I can screw you over right okay it's always grease
healing round oh dude wild onion trees really are you serious
guys you did what you just clicked random place in the middle of Russia well I'm not I'm not going
to get like a bigger clue by spending more time I know my limits it's gonna be hard I feel like
it shouldn't be yeah with uh I don't want to say it serious oh shit um um um okay yep
so I had a little bit more time I might have been able to do it
it's always grease it's actually really not a bad place to click because it could be right
in the middle the uh the rooftop very grease I feel like I'm gonna die you're right I just
felt like you were gonna like see something in this city and instantly destroy them like that
yep oh this is so far down into South America are you kidding me really you got there closer
than I did how is uh a football bus I could totally go to school here and then play demons
on my off time such a small road really fucking cool looking actually I was gonna stay Tokyo but
I was like there's no way it's like it's Tokyo like every time I mean they must have a higher
density of you know you know cars driving around it fuck
Jesus you're fucking dead I went too fast I saw Slovenia Slovakia I went too fast I that was
based off the last name on a grave state like I looked over immediately I would have killed
you immediately I just I thought it was blurred out a little it was like it was Slovia god damn
you're dead how does it feel last one okay truly the final one for real it was actually a lot of
fun to do like I I don't think I would enjoy this so much uh single player it is really fun yeah
this is the true final one see this game is fun see I told you I got food on the way to okay well
it's like the competitive aspect you're trying to do it in a hurry like the whole just sit there
for 30 minutes and pause and be a streamer kind of situation it's not doing it for me he has
streamer yeah we're gonna like pause and tell oh wait you know you don't know what you're talking
about wait wait wait there's big this this thing you grew up with I grew up with you didn't grow
up with that like that's weird for you so everybody didn't do this one thing that I always did as a
child what you gotta I feel like this is gonna annihilate you main yeah why would they say
Quebec city on it and it's in Montreal uh I don't know I'm surprised that I got so like was was so
competitive with that guess that was like 100 like I have no fucking clue these houses look
look expensive
what I'm learning is that I need to like educate myself and stop being so dumb about
any country that uses this language that's what I've learned today literally only one country
don't tell me that you're making it up
that's great
I was over there too I was right there but like I can't tell
I've got a huge hunch just from what I've seen
where that fucking sign just go no dude really there's no like it's it's something like that
wait yeah shit I gotta I have to guess what were you doing Florida you thought that was Florida
yeah left side cars I don't have a driver's license that does that's not the first thing I
look at Florida it might as well have been Florida all right uh too blurry yeah this one's kind of
looking like Florida too that's too blurry I can't read it's too blurry too I too blurry
it's too blurry I can't read it um um uh I'm just gonna I'm literally just gonna pick I'm
gonna just take it I'm gonna take a guess I'm just guessing yeah I don't think it was that far south
all the signs were all I couldn't read them you don't even know you really don't I really
don't you literally just did that and like now I have to like do this
yeah of course it is of course it's a heal round fucking where did I see this before
oh you are you're fucked really
it's 26 damage to you okay how come the ones that I beat you in I you like are right next to me
they're the easy ones and you can only do the easy ones music is very tense really you really
like light the fire under you I like the hunt for trying to quickly figure out like where the
most information would be I know right desperately desperately searching I don't think I have it
right I thought I did immediately but I don't think so now of course it's your oh look it's
next to Paris it's right next to London right next to Paris I got it I saw a road map that was
kind of going that angle and I just tried to pick one I saw a road map you fuck they're always like
right next to Paris right next to London right next to like all the major cities who has any idea
vague idea I have a vague idea too but how would you in some architectural
but also yeah
you're fucking dead dude honestly you just you and his one isn't happening we're like really really
close like the first four or five rounds so far away and then the quadruple damage rolls around
and you're like equally as fucking wrong but you're still you still do quadruple and I'd lose
so just get a little bit closer again yeah winner takes all winner takes all four million community
subs all right this is it final one this is for all the marbles let's go yeah I feel like I went
down the wrong road and I'm never going to see a sign anywhere down here and you're going to
figure something out soon that I'm not going to know I knew it had to be somewhere like down here
yeah I was going to put it in Glasgow honestly and then I was like I'm going to put it close to
the middle in case I'm wrong most improved one turn around turn around turn around turn around
what I can't read this yeah that's the clue that's how I know where we are shit there's a flag
right there what is it oh my god it's switzerland what yeah so unlike the fourth round where the
quad damages what did you even click on where was that Singapore why was there a switzerland flag
there was a swift there was a flag it seemed like it was near an airport or something
it was the swiss embassy that's so fucking annoying all right I gotta get it together
I see the one flag it's like the swiss flag and it's the embassy in Singapore where is this
why don't I know where this is it was somewhere in here I don't fucking remember dude you can't
be serious you're gonna I'm as over I lose I have absolutely no idea what this is I was gonna put
it right in the middle of China I'm on the screen yeah I hi what are you doing I I had no I didn't
even have a chance that one didn't count that one sucked I turned the corner to a giant mall of
Montenegro yeah but okay so I turned around and I see like the swiss flag on a building and all
of a sudden no sorry that's the embassy dickhead okay so you want one more one more okay my food's
at the door I just want to make it so it's not in the cold okay well speed run we have literally
10 seconds my food is literally at the door I'll be right back in 10 seconds go go go go try USA
oh okay famous places USA let's do USA that sounds good this is a lot this is so much fun
okay well I just not even there let's go all right we're doing United States okay play again
play again United States this is only in the United States okay how much you know I already
have an idea yeah here it feels like if I just guess I'm pretty close but you can't fuck up a
guest here as humanly possible yeah I think I think I'm gonna be pretty close I mean it could
it I don't it could be anything though hold on if I could click in any faster than this oh come on
it was Florida it was god it was Georgia and you know it it was not Georgia palm trees I'm a hobbit
man I just have my comfortable little sofa and my little spot and I wanted to have my books and I
don't care I'm like why are you so mad because I got it I thought I had it right he doesn't know
he doesn't fucking know I'm guessing you just guessed dude really I can guess you're way better
than you can guess really I don't have any idea I have no idea I actually have absolutely no clue
oh and apparently I was supposed to see it apparently I was thinking I don't know like
one of the Carolinas I can't guess good this one has to be Greece imagine you clicked Greece
I got an idea oh I absolutely have an idea oh you better believe that I have an idea
fucking sub work from somewhere in NA literally all of these are in NA you're gonna have to narrow
it down a little bit more than that I think I think it needs a little more narrowing down
because it could be there's a few places this could be I have yeah but I don't have a lock on
I pretty much have to just click now
what the dude the car that we started next to pointing out the red truck that we started next
to had Pennsylvania on it but there was a church across from a church across from a church
that's very like up in that area too like all of the east coast is all of the churches
hey slow down slow down dude come on and if you're not from us like how political all this shit
honestly is where every single lawn has like vote for this person vote for this person we're not
seeing that anywhere else this guy had an Obama shirt on what did you get what what do you what
what kind of genre of food do you have I got this place called Austin Burger Company I never heard
of it but Boston Burger Company is the best burger I'm hoping I think me and Holly are
gonna get McDonald's okay that's fantastic there's no there's nothing giving me any information here
is that a guess or did you see a sign or something we'll see how much of a guess
it was when we see how close I am I don't know right okay I mean it was the poverty
I gotta get you right here this is the next round after this I gotta get you
it's always on the fucking healing rounds okay I always like clean it up on the healing
seriously like this I would have wiped them out like five times yeah I bet
you didn't even click on Santa Monica Boulevard by the way I couldn't find the street I like
didn't even move once I didn't see what cross street was there's no way I lose
is
St. Petersburg it was on one of the trash cans oh I don't even know what that is
okay we're walling in we're walling in citizens by the way how do I click on the like like within
like five miles of the city and it's triple damage and you still like because I wasn't
not that far off I think St. Petersburg is in Russia what how do you oh every time it's
times four damage you you immediately know where to go you're gonna die it's times three by the way
how the fuck is three how is it even possible you're dead you're gonna have to hold that
every time or this motherfucker just guesses immediately and gets it right immediately you
just must know where this stuff is I saw a sign said Louisiana on a mini mart you're just getting
lucky every fourth round every fifth round oh I guess I just keep getting luckier than you
it was sucked to be so unlucky it's I know it sucks man I'd stop my totally five times one more
oh I gotta grab my food actually this time yeah all right you run it you look back and you see
every fifth round every fifth round it's like five seconds to go by and then it's
do famous places okay that's fun oh we're making this 20 seconds I feel like I have a I feel like
I have a better chance of beating you if we're in America because Ashley keeps telling me she's
gonna go on the run and I really practice how to locate her this is famous places in the world
apparently which good luck I don't think I'm gonna be able to get any of these uh the more famous it
is the more likely I have no idea I know I know this one right off the bat too bad it's not round
fucking five here's the problem though I don't actually know where the fuck this place is
well take your time I got some soggy fries
where is it where is this place I don't I actually don't fucking know where it is I know what I know
this exact monument thing but I don't know where it is on a map yeah I don't know either I think
that's it oh my god I don't know where it is I don't know it's I don't know where it is
fucking god damn it's the tallest building in the world yeah I the wrong like bay for Dubai
it's the I knew that I was wrong I zoomed in I didn't see it I was like that's weird
oh you gotta get like the street I know seriously
oh fuck you you don't know oh nice good job I didn't bother to look for the specifics
I just said fuck you for no reason that was like rude
nope um you actually know what this is no I see you in guest land I know it's somewhere
please stop throwing
what come on guys is a burger is it good is food good yeah it's pretty good it's whatever this is
this thing here my connection sucks so I can't even see it's all blurred out how do we both
get zero I was closer I don't like this one I'm too stupid I don't know anything is that like
famous um it's a famous uh there's bridge this is not easy is this the London bridge
let's give it away it is why don't I say that out loud I don't know neither like we're either
gonna need no one's gonna score points I want a real game okay well um the real question is
where where are these oh I fucking okay did you get it wrong yeah I put it in Las Vegas
I don't know where they are though okay yeah it's Cairo did I just kill you yeah so not
the famous pyramids of Egypt are not in Libya no they aren't
I want to do another real one what you don't want to do a real one not monuments I don't I
don't like famous places famous places are lame okay I like to support local business
United States again um oh let's see if you want to yeah all right this is actually the last one
because I'm starving plus it's getting really late it's been a lot of fun though
maybe this is United States yo no shit it is is it how's that one place the other place
the lamer place no no I just I need an extra minute
that's like we're still doing famous places I that was in my brain for some reason
I clicked central New Jersey oops the first two rounds don't even matter it's round eight that
is the only one that matters why are you so mad about that getting a tree this could be
I know I understand that you're like taking a bite and just guessing randomly
but yeah but I'm still gonna beat yourself like does it really matter all right we both
making the same thing I was thinking like Portland
Linda area you just said you don't even think that these rounds matter yeah but I mean whatever
yeah that's one degrees
I know you can't look at license plates that's kind of um cannot that's some NSA level stuff
so I this actually might be I don't want to say it why does the sun have to be so
bright every sign I've looked at when you zoom in it's like a pure white sign
yeah I gotta get I'm getting away from the sun he's using the sun evasion technique
okay I'm dead end this is such a average place an average city yeah but with like no commercial
areas so you can't actually see like business addresses or anything like that everything's
just blown up by the sun I'm going off this way I don't know
I mean I could I'm just gonna go for it here I mean this round doesn't matter right
not necessarily none of the rounds matter not until it's four times damage and I win
okay I was thinking like all right yeah San Diego or whatever I was thinking like
Paso or El Paso said La Mesa I don't know what that is I'm I like can't move down this road
yeah it's hard to drive in either direction oh I'm ready to guess this is yeah this is bad
trying to eat over here oh I see something get closer I'm going for it I just want to get to
this one building I'm going for it I'm going for it I'm going for it I'm going for it I'm just
gonna say somewhere like around here this is a lot of trees wow I mean Vermont New Hampshire
look I mean that's what it looks like during like the spring and summer is that snow or
solar ash I don't know sir I think it might be solar ash okay then I think I know where we are
still a shitload of people and it's late I'm surprised I don't know where this would be but
I'll say like somewhere around here really you thought you saw a sign for St. Louis didn't you
I did it was a healing room whatever none of the rounds matter easy I got really lucky with that
St. Louis I had no idea where I was America it's very America it's a little bit too America
the thing is I don't know where that is I think it's here I'm pretty sure it's like up here
I think it's like up here I'm like 99.9 percent certain that's like here I'm about to get
destroyed is it right here or is it like up here yeah Kentucky oh what really yeah that's a lot
man no I mean on two times damage that was all my life because I pretty much was I literally got
like almost the exact place yeah I really thought it was up there too but I wanted to
put somewhere more middle yeah I was very unsure that's crazy we're gonna play one more right
I gotta call it man I gotta go get your you're eating I haven't eaten all day yeah that's why
we can do one more all right this is the last one real everybody's betting all the doubters
right you mean you're just so confident and you lose all your points this photo brother lives here
where can you drive that fast on the highway the speed limit on the highway is that's
fucking crazy you know where this is I don't know where this is I know the general area
I'm gonna be closer than you and it's only the first round and you're gonna heal this and like
my you gotta go so the speed limit in Idaho on highways is 75 so I just said that out loud
what an idiot I don't know what you said
wait what they usually say what like first like town or county or whatever
where is that I don't know
I don't know I don't know I don't know I don't know
no
it looks like Philadelphia like Pennsylvania or something yeah I found out I would have never
guessed California until I saw the sign I was originally thinking like Georgia it's
burger something oh this is a hiking trail or whatever that how are we supposed to know what
this is that's part of the fun noticing some birch looking pretty close to Montenegro again
I almost want to say it's a dead end at the edge I mean what
you actually might win right now you find something that I don't
I mean there's nothing out here I don't think you have to worry about that
yeah actually I'm at another dead end
yeah what was sold over here I'm just going for what I would
I mean I'm just gonna go for it like somewhere like up here
oh shit I didn't really put Alaska on here I forgot it was a thing what is that
whoa I've got you too bad it's just a shitty healing round
it's too bad it's just a stupid shitty healing round
is it do I just kill you I'm closer than you you're closer than me
bullshit how did you find that out a couple buildings had Hawaiian on it and I picked the
biggest Hawaiian city because it was a big city which I had no idea Honolulu was that big of a
city be serious let me break I mean I'm full health you better guess well
81 double damage it begins you ready this is where it actually matters yeah a lot of cars
here a lot of endless roads a lot of cars Home Depot here this could be anywhere I mean it could
be it could be anywhere in this entire country yeah wait you actually got it no you do not
two times damage are you about to win oh it's Seattle god damn it what Houston
this space needle was just on there
that's the space needle right there that's the space needle in Seattle
does Houston have a space needle too Houston's a pretty big city look at that is the god look
at this this right here that you can't see it that well but that is the space needle
that's not a pen that is a needle do you see this thing right here that's the space needle
that's an like an it is actually I see what are you talking about am I crazy that's literally
like the space needle or like the stratosphere in Vegas it's one of those like spaceship things
with the needle on top oh come on that's not a pen I think it's an arrow pointing upwards dude
no it's not that is the space needle okay we'll go back to Houston and find that street and zoom
in and prove it why would you have the space needle or the stratosphere in Houston as your
logo uh I don't know how come every single pizza place in New Jersey is a New York pizza
it is the space needle that's what I'm saying all right that's it call those guys up and ask
all right that's it that's it maybe the company's from Seattle but like I thought it was like oh
space needle whatever yeah yeah maybe I'll see you around kid no it was a lot of fun
thanks for playing dude yeah no for sure yeah it's been seven hours we're gonna go
that's uh he's already gone he didn't even say bye what the fuck that's don't ever bet for me
ever again I won like five of those uh that was twitch.tv slash stir thanks for staying up with
us everybody and I will see you guys on Sunday Sunday the 20th not sure what we're gonna do we'll
do something though that was a lot of fun I was so confident that was like bang we're right in the
middle this is Seattle yeah I'll see you guys on Sunday we'll figure out what we're gonna do
good night goodbye thanks for watching everybody as always you want my final thoughts on dying
light 2 it's okay I mean we spent like an hour and 25 minutes talking shit about like the entire
video game industry you know I guess that's the way it is what about the hundred subs I still can't
pay for anything on twitch so I need to contact somebody whether it's my bank doing it or it's
twitch doing it I don't know but I'll see you guys on Sunday probably starting around the same time
so remember probably two or three let's just say three and I'll see you again there's background
noise on my mic yes there is because uh I have a fan turned on uh pretty because it's so hot in
here I don't know what it is lately it's been heating up to like I gotta figure out what to do
about like the AC or something yeah that's the urinal moving back and forth all right guys take
care of yourselves I'll see you soon thanks for staying up good night goodbye get some sleep see
you Sunday afternoon