Ah yes, Super Frog. Hi guys. We're a little early, yeah. I want to start early because
this stream, I'm not going to have very much time today. If you don't know, this stream is the last
stream you're going to get for a small but significant amount of time. After today's stream,
you will not see me again until Friday of next week. I'm not going to be here for about five or
six straight days. Part of the reason why I wanted to do five plus days in a row here.
I'm supposed to start in 30 minutes. Yeah, I was starting early because I don't have,
um, I have until about four to five hours from right now. So I wanted to really start and get
going. What are we supposed to do for that time? I recommend read the entire Lord of the Rings trilogy.
It'll take you a week and then you can come back to me and say, hey, I've read it all.
Actually, that'd probably take longer. That actually would probably take a couple months.
So I'm not, I'm not leaving for a couple months. I'm leaving for about a week.
Less, a little less than a week. What a waste of time. Oh man, you guys really don't like reading.
But, uh, the plan today is to try and continue our hardcore Diablo 2 adventure.
If you've missed the last two or two or three times we've done this, we are standing outside
of Diablo's area. So Diablo is within 20 minutes of where we are right now.
And we have the skeleton crew trying to fight Diablo. So, uh, if this stream turns out to be
40 minutes long because I die to Diablo because I'm not prepared for it, we'll do something else.
But the plan is to try to stay alive and to get into act five and keep going. We'll see.
Don't flatter yourself. I feel like it'll take, it'll take 40 minutes to even get to him
because of how our character is currently built. The plan is simple. Yeah, if, if I die
in Diablo, the Asura's Wrath DLC is the plan. But I don't plan on dying in Diablo. I plan on playing
for at least a few hours. Here comes the flush force. For the love of God, please do not die.
We have an interesting chat today, I think, because a bunch of people in chat might want me to die
because they want to see Asura's Wrath really bad. They get the DLC there, but there are also
a bunch of people that don't want to see the Asura's Wrath DLC and they're like, no, I don't,
I don't want that. I will. I please stay alive in Diablo. It's going to be an interesting day.
There's a civil war here. All right, let's, uh, we've waited long enough. It's been about five
minutes. Let's get into it. Hope you're having a good day. If you missed yesterday's stream.
Well, yeah, technically yesterday. Tony Hawk's Underground was a lot of fun.
Let's try to kill Diablo. I'm almost level 30. So I got to get a refresher here. Oh, that's right.
We did Raal Raal. Probably the worst thing ever. I made stealth. I don't really have very good
items, do I? My items are kind of terrible. All right. I'm going to die in the first five minutes.
I know. Hey, get, get, get your Asura's, Asura's Wrath DLC hype ready in the chat, boys and girls,
because I'm probably dead in 10 minutes. I need a skeleton crew to refresh your memory. Here is
where chat has decided to put the points. We have a lot in Iron Golem. I'm going to make sure you
just give a quick little refresher course. It's been about a week and a half since you've seen
this. Ray skeleton, skeleton mastery. You've gone down into the, you've gone down into the Golems.
Iron Golem members. Iron Golem gives synergy, 20 attack rating per level to all Golems.
You put points into skeleton mage. We are about to unlock in, if I'm to stay alive, that is we're
about to unlock fireman or revive. All of these are very good. Fire Golem or revive. Revive just
lets you bring any character back to life. That's not a boss. So if one of those big demon guys dies,
I can bring them back to life and I can do this. Um, like you can have like 20, I think monsters
out at once. I feel like there's going to be a fight here. Uh, thanks for the two teeth. It was
a waste of a point. People thought it was funny. I mean, I laughed. It was pretty funny and then
amplify damage. Obviously if you don't put a one point and amplify damage as a necromancer, I mean,
what the hell are you doing? So that about does it. We have this guy here. We have, uh, Vic is
still with us. Vic, uh, by the way, Vic has better gear than I do because the, uh, the real hero here.
So let's do river of flame. I'm, I think I'm ready. I didn't even get it. I didn't wait. Did I not
step on the waypoint? Did I not step on the waypoint last time? No, I did. Didn't I? Didn't we
get to the river of flame and I like stepped on the waypoint? Did I? That's a big oops. Oh shit.
That's actually really bad. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Now I got here.
Yep. Right. Right. Right. Right. Okay. We're good. They were, I didn't get to the waypoint. I did the,
uh, the gems. All right. I gotta be careful. This is probably going to be a quick one. So what
happened to Sir's wrath so far? The story, uh, you're one of the eight deities or you were until
you were cast away from all, from there's seven of them now. Nah, we'll be fine. Let me get my
skeleton crew up and we'll be good to go. My man, I have such shit, man. All right. We're going to
have five regular skeletons and we can add three majors. I believe I've got the whole crew. Uh,
we need to amplify damage. All right. I'm, I feel a little safer. What is my fire resistance? Not
good. I don't think we should fight Diablo without proper fire resistance, but you know,
we'll see if we can get some. I'm going to take it very slow because I really don't want to play
Diablo for 12 minutes. I would, I would like to actually kill Diablo. All right. Let's go this
way. Right. Any majors, like for instance, up here, Diablo is a discount sun joke.
You could say that, but today is going to be fairly chill. It's not going to be that long.
It'll be probably about four, three, four, five hour long stream. I want to relax a little bit.
Last night was a little all over the place. I, uh, I got some good sleep though. I'm feeling
refreshed. You are so fucked laughing my ass off. I know. I know. I see the end of the tunnel
and I know what the outcome is. What's really going to end up happening
is this guy is going to have to kill Diablo. Not me. I'm going to have nothing to do with it.
That guy. Yeah, Vic. He's the one that killed Duriel. He's the one that killed Mephisto and
he'll be the one to kill Diablo. I'm just a bard that follows him around with my skeleton band.
We just sing while he fucking does work. All these skeletons all have different
fucking instruments. What a real pain in the ass that would be too. Imagine you had like a full
eight person band following you around. Three of them are singing. Two of them have little drums
be like, get the fuck away from me. They're all getting in the way.
That would suck because that's what we're doing to this guy.
How are we going? I really do want the way point though.
One of them's playing their rib cage like a xylophone. Uh, it's so stupid. I love it.
I love it. I really do wonder what you guys are going to do because revive is so good.
It's so good. But you know, there is, there is a channel community character.
I feel like that's going to win out over everything else. How's everybody doing? Everyone
good? Everyone feel safe? Everybody's dead. So that's a good sign. When I open the seals,
though, that's what it's going to be really painful. That was a lot of damage with one hit.
I think I really would, I think I'm going to get a pole going or maybe one of the mods can do it
well because I don't really want to die. Do you think I will beat Diablo? You think I will kill
Diablo? I got a wink. Did I? I'll do the pole. Let me see. Did I get a wink? No, I didn't. I didn't.
Nice try though. Uh, let me get a, let me get a pole. I'm actually curious as to what people
think about this because I have my answer, but I want to know your answer. I'm curious
what your answer is. Let's see. Vote on this. I'm going to check it later. Okay. Let's go.
Those are three very real scenarios. I do. I don't just die or I give up because I have to
run back and forth to the blood war. There's a no option for you both dying. Um, I'm not going to,
no, this, this isn't like a boxing game. We're not going to do a double knockout.
One of us is dead or I take 10% HP off of his bar every eight minutes and it gets to about
40% of the way there and it's been 40 minutes and I'm just done. And I'm like, no, nevermind
any of those are possible. I can get it. Once we get to the actual, that like sanctuary place,
not sanctuary, you know what I mean? What's the place before Diablo called? It has a specific
name. It's probably not the rip. What is it? It's like, it's like his castle.
Why do I not know this? You like, do you actually like this game, Jeremy? Do you enjoy playing this?
I feel like you really want to play goat simulator. There it is. Okay. Good. Here we go.
You know, I'm really just hiding the fact that I want to play goat simulator. Here it comes.
Why do these angels help? Proceed hero. You're the Nephilim. That's why you can do this.
Did I mention I can shoot lightning out of my hand? No, you do it. I gotta be careful.
I understand like the whole, no, no, no, I can't interfere. I can't interfere.
Terrial could just do a cleave and kill every enemy on this fucking map.
Like, could you at least just do that for me? Fine. Don't fight Diablo, but can you just drop
like a fucking angel nuke on this spot so we can just walk to him? And look, you can ghost ride it.
I'll just say I did it in the history books. And it'll just be like, and then the brave
skeleton necromancer conjured up a gigantic ball of lightning and dropped it onto the river of
flame. Like, why can't you just say that? Does it matter? And I'll just, in all the interviews
that I do afterwards, I'll just be like, yeah, no, it was, I don't know. I just kind of did.
I used all my strength. I tried as hard as I could. And I, yeah, I don't, I can never do
it again though. I used all my energy. Yeah, the CCTV installed. Wait, would you like, like,
they're monitoring what's going on right now? Okay, but you wouldn't like the game.
Okay, but we're talking, we're talking strictly lore here. We're not talking about game, video
gameplay. Don't die. I got a full crew, right? Once those super uniques come out of the seals
is where I'm really going to have to shift my pants. I got to have portals ready. Can you
imagine a guy named Tommy Lee Bones in the history books? Use teeth. Teeth does three damage. What
I'm doing right now does 36 to 104. Teeth does three. All right, gollum's gonna die. Hey, come
on. A little bit higher. Oh, I have to kill Diablo with teeth. But you want to last hit Diablo with
teeth? That make you guys happy? Would you guys be happy satisfied if I did that? I'm not even
sure it's possible. All right, here it is. Oh, boy. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Just back it up. I need fire resistance. Bad. Still have these stamina potions for some reason.
Dude, that was an auto tube. What am I going to do with this shit? Does anything have fire
resistance? Oh, this does. I lose 41 health. That's a lot of health, but I gained 25%.
Me taking, let's say I take 100 points of damage from fire and like somebody does a 100 damage
spell is having 41 more health better than taking 75% of that. The health is better, right? Or is
the percentage better? I don't know. I need to do some math. I'm going to wear it. Any other
fire resist shields? You know, I need like a socket shield because with the socketed shield,
I could just dump rupees into it and get fire resist. There was ruining chat's character. What?
I'm just trying to, I'm trying to survive, man. His inventory is a mess. I should just sell this
thing. All right. I'm selling this. I'm at 33% fire resist. It's not very good. Resist is way
better than 40 health. I'm under 300 though. I'm going to get fucking double tapped and die
instantly. Okay. What do I have? I can't do anything. All right. Somebody's trash can
ruins have got to go here eventually. I think how many portals do I have? Let's go. It's still
alive, right? All right. Everybody get up here. There's the chaos sanctuary here. Oh fuck.
What do they have for resistance right now? Oh, oh, I'm going down. Vic, you got to stay alive,
man. We dropped Ruby puke cloud. Good. Nice work. I'm going to turn. I got to turn that into
a friend Gothic shield. Wait, I don't have anything. I need to find like a weapon there.
There let's go. Dodge the missiles. We're good. All right. Into the sanctuary. Let's go. I'm
actually nervous right now. I've never played a character on hardcore. I was just run in and
just don't give a shit is if I die, who cares, right? But even on normal, I'm kind of scared.
I really don't want to die, but this is a place where I can die because the boss here is scary
and he's hard because if you just, I don't know, we'll see. I'm scared. The one thing I am very
thankful of is besides the mages, the majors kind of suck. Everyone's staying alive in here,
which is encouraging. What do I do if I die? Oh, that's it. I close Diablo. What else can I do?
Make a new character. I'm like, I'm not doing it. I'm not going to do that. Be very, be sad for five
to 10 minutes and then move on to something else. All right. We've got to do the seals.
If you'd like to see where we're going to end up, Diablo spawns in here. Hey,
me. Army versus army. I got to get to level 30. We need an equalizer here. Oops. Oops.
All right. This is weakened. Careful. Vic, you good? All right. What does Vic have for fire
resistance? 58. Just keep Vic alive. Keep Vic alive. What you got to do is you got to get the
ball, the tuck. Arnold, I want you to pass over here to Helga. Helga, I want you to drive to the
hoop and then I want you to get the ball, the tuck. You guys don't like Hey Arnold? Nobody likes that
show. How old are you guys? Hey Arnold was like 20. If you guys are like 20, you didn't see Hey
Arnold? That was the thing in Hey Arnold. Oh shit, we got stuff. I loved Hey Arnold. My character
wasn't in the show for very long, but it was like a big episode. All right. I'll keep my references
to Garfield and SpongeBob. Garfield's older than Hey Arnold. He's just still relevant though. He's
been around for a long time. Thank you. Thank you. That's better. When was the last time you guys
actually read a Garfield comedy? I'm not talking about online. I'm talking about in a newspaper.
Never? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. For the amount of stuff you guys did. For the amount of talk.
For the amount that everyone talks about Garfield. I was assuming you guys were all big fans.
I get requests to play Garfield's card. Maybe like once every four days. All right. I have to be
careful up here. This beer sucks. This sucks too. I don't even want it. He said it. See you. Let's go.
This is Lord de Sace. I remember. Diablo does time seven damage to summons.
That's going to end very well for us. I'm so fucked. I'm so fucked. You have no idea guys.
I'm so fucked. I have to fight Diablo alone. I'm so, I'm going to die. It's going to be really,
really bad. I need to get more fire resist if I stand a chance. We'll probably get to
level 30 though. So that'd be good. Don't get in the middle of a firestorm.
Come on. Level up. I need it. This is a huge amount of money just came in. Hold on. Actually
huge, huge money. Oh, I was supposed to, let me see the, will he, let me check this first.
Will he kill Diablo? Most of you think yes. Besides the people that think I'm going to
run around in circles for 30 minutes and they give up. I appreciate the enthusiasm though. Thank you.
Thanks guys. I just mentioned it and now more votes are coming in. All right. All right. Not
very many people don't think I'm going to do it. That's, that really is encouraging. Okay. Let's
get my, let's get my bits up here. Somebody gave a hundred bucks. Rentaburger gave 10,000 bits
thanks to the hundred fucking dollars Rentaburger. I can't believe I get to become a sub baby in a
Diablo 2 stream. Come a long way from the first of your videos I ever saw. I watched Germania in
2014 for almost an entire minute before I realized it was funny on purpose. I'm confused. What does
that mean? I watched Germania for almost an entire minute before I really, oh, you thought it was,
you thought it was somebody making like a real league or something? Funny by accident. That's so
funny. Yeah, we got a wink too. Got my backpack. I'm ready for school. Hey, is that a different
Germa? He looks different today. I'm not wearing overalls. It's imposter Jeremy. No, it's because
my pupils are small because the sun's in my eyes. That's what people don't, that's what it is.
I'm not wearing a backpack. No, I've got, I'm wearing my boomer brace for my costochondritis.
You have small pupils. I do look like I'm going to school though. Just waiting for the bus mom.
No, it's, I got a costochondritis. I got a fucking back brace on
as you wink. Uh, but rent a burger. Thank you so much for the fucking ridiculous amount of money.
A hundred dollars. I never expect anyone to give one dollar, let alone a hundred of them.
Seriously. Thanks. Am I wearing beads on my wrist? Shit, shit that you saw it. God damn it. No,
I forgot this was on. It's, it's a, it's, it's black tourmaline. It's like a crystal bracelet.
I, I, I'm just wearing it because I, it's a crystal bracelet. It's black tourmaline
and it's supposed to help with your energy. It's not, it's made up. Like it's literally all made up.
I just thought it was cute that I put it on. It's literally the whole, the whole thing's made up.
Uh, somebody made it up and sold bracelets to people. I just thought it was cool. It's like
cool. That's an interesting idea. Like, oh, it's like crystals and it's like power crystals.
It's, I know it's like, could be just bullshit. Whatever. It's fun. It was like 12 bucks. Add a
couple zeros. It's cool. There's like different crystals. This is like, look, okay, hold on. Let
me, why is my game crashing? I am not going to lose in act. I'm going to, I'll save and exit.
Okay. Um, look, see, isn't this cool? It's like a gem. It's like a stone. It's a crystal. It's
like kind of interesting. I don't, I don't like think it's going to like heal my ailments because
I think it would look cool. And it's like interesting concept and it's like cool like history.
And I always take this off before streams. I know someone's going to be like, what the fuck is he
wearing? And then I have to do a baby food explanation and I wanted to avoid the baby food
explanation, but I had, all right. Everybody's dead. Everybody's dead. Everybody's dead. I have
to hold on. I leveled up. Why is everybody getting smoked? Somebody said it's just a bracelet, dude.
It's all right. I know, but it's a, it's like a black tourmaline crystal stone bracelet.
Holy fuck. This guy is eating me alive. I think it's neat. Yeah. I think it's cool. It's all right.
We good. Who is it? Just Lord they say. All right. Get in there and holy fuck. I'm in trouble.
I'm just going to keep putting people in there. Dude, they're dying before they can even come out
of, they die before they can even like get out of the womb or whatever this is. Get in there.
Goodbye. We're going to fall back and we have a point to put in. That's priority. Number one
right now. We've got a point. Uh, click maps are going to be enabled here. If you'd like to vote
for something, you just have to click the screen. You will see it on the screen in just a moment.
Okay. So here's what the points are so far. We have unlocked the bottom row on the summoning side.
And again, this is fire Golem and this is revive. Revive can bring anything back to life for a
significant portion of time. Fire Golem is fireman. We also have the other points here.
Summon resist Golem mastery. You don't have to be embarrassed about owning crystals for their
properties. I know where it gives me power. How do you guys think I can like fucking, how do you
think, where do you think my comedy comes from? It comes from this fucking bracelet. I don't wear
this. I've can't, I'm not funny. This is where it comes from. It's a comedy bracelet. When I take this
off, I like, I like decrepify. I've got somewhere I got like boomer brace on like power crystals.
All right. Where do you guys want to go? What are you thinking? We may have to zoom in for this one.
We might have to zoom in. We'll see if it splits. Do I have a Zen garden? No, it would die.
I wouldn't, I would, I can't be, I wouldn't be, I would, it would die. I wouldn't be able to take
care of it. I would be like, dude, Zen garden. Oh, I can't wait. And I would, the first day I would
strip, strip, strip, trim, trim, trim, place the rocks, put the trees. Ooh, this is so cool. And
I'd put it out in the sun. Wow. And I'd forget it was there. And then three weeks later, everything
would be dead and I would find it. I'm going to zoom in. Oh, wait, that, wait, that, that's,
that's one of those trees. That's one of those little trees. Wrong. Zen garden is not, what's
it called? Uh, the, the little tree, the bonsai tree. Yeah. Whoops. Zen garden is just sand with
rocks. I'd fucking spill it. Not a bonsai tree, not a bonsai. No, it's a bonsai tree, bonsai,
bonsi tree, bonsai tree, bonsi buddy tree. All right. Let me zoom this shit in because you guys,
you guys are, you're split at the bottom. You're not supposed to see that.
Did you guys know that when a graphic is on screen, it's like magic?
All right. Choose wisely. Decrepify for fuck's sake. Gray, I can't, I cannot influence anything.
They've chosen to be down here. I, uh, I can't click poison over guys. That's, we don't have
enough points. All right. Spreading ourselves out. We're going to make our own Diablo.
We have, he's exactly like you in every way, except he's one eighth your size.
Here we go. Fire golem, mini Diablo. There he is. How strong is he? 400 health, 165 attack, 40,
410 defense, absorbs 36% of fire damage, fire damage, 44 to 90. Holy fire. 46. It's actually
going to come down to can my mini me Diablo beat actual Diablo? You think that's a joke? It's not.
Where are the stats going? Oh, wait, before I do that, just so you can get a clear indicator,
here's what the stats look like right now. Revive Vic? Oh, I absolutely will. I, when we open this
last seal, I am not going to get any more skeletons because they're all going to instantly explode.
The presence of Diablo is going to kill every single skeleton. So it's Vic and fireman versus
Diablo. We're not going to get them anymore. All right. You see what the stats are. We have 5%
We're not going to get them anymore. All right. You see what the stats are. We have 5 points.
All 5 points are going into what you pick. Choose wisely. Choose wisely. And a wink showed up. Yeah,
it did. All in on vitality. Yeah, this is not, this is not even a contest.
You're all right. You look like you're in pain. I do? I look, oh, I think I look okay. Do I look
like I'm in pain? Great hair today. It was styled by a professional. A shower head and then a comb.
Vitality. Thanks for voting. Lego hair of the year. New category 2020 awards.
Best Lego hair of the year. Back over 300. All right. Here we go. Let's get a Vic back.
$6,300. I am going to get a full group though for this. So I'm just going to, I'm only doing
this so I can revive some people and then we're going back through the portal. Yeah, I know,
I know. I'm just getting a full skeleton crew. Your skin is really clear. Just drink more water.
Make sure you get adequate rest. You want to be, you want to get some good sleep.
Make sure you're sleeping well and also make a blood contract with the devil.
Whatever. It's not, it's not that far. I know where it is. Everything's dead.
Everything's dead. Whatever. Just drink one of these and run. I got a full group.
Mormu. 13 community subs from Mormu. Thank you, Mormu. Congratulations to those that all got them.
No, no, no, no, no. Don't even fight. Don't even fight. Just go. How do I do, how do we,
how do you do a blood contract with the devil? Look up into the, down to the ground and go,
oh, devil of mine, I'd like to open a contract and then a pop-up window will show up
and you are, you have to go into a queue. Usually about 16 to 17 years long and then you have your
appointment. Okay, what a portal here. Guys, you, you, you gotta remember you, you're going,
you, you're, you're behind people that like sold their soul to the devil for like a pack of gum.
You know, people say this shit all the time. Like, oh, I'd sell my soul for a fucking hamburger
right now that you, you now 17 years later, you need to pop up. You will sell this soul for all
kinds of fucking crazy shit. How do you think the guy from fucking that pot, how do you think the
guy from Popeye died? Burger guy. He sold his soul to the devil for a fucking hamburger. What was
his name? Tootie? What was that guy's name? Wimpy. Wimpy. His name was shitty. By the way, I,
I feel like I stole that joke. Anybody else get, feel that? Like, I feel like they've made,
somebody's made that joke somewhere. You know what I mean? Like, oh, he's like wimpy, sold his soul
to the devil for a hamburger. That's like an easy joke to do. That's probably something. I'm sure it
happened. All right. Uh, once I opened these seals, this is it. Clown anxiety. Oh God. Okay.
Let's, I gotta get a portal all the way back here. He's going to say the line. Here we go.
Let's open this one first because we're going to get ported on. Okay. You ready?
Here we go. Oh, it's this motherfucker. I forgot. Get in there fireman.
No way. Vic. All right. This is my Vic fund. At least I have money in the Vic fund.
Please keep bringing him back. Oh boy. We're going to, we're going to walk there again
from here because I need another, I need another army. I knew this was going to happen.
I can't go back in that portal as the portal will be surrounded. What's my opinion on
Warcraft reforged? Um, it would have been nice if it was actually reforged. Warcraft refunded.
For some reason, I don't know why Blizzard thinks this, but when you open up the oven
to check on your pizza, it's not the same as making a video game. What the fuck does that mean?
You know, I was going somewhere. If you reheat. No, I fucked it up. Uh, sorry. Fuck is this not
doing on? Uh, I meant to say is, uh, reheating your leftovers is not the same thing as making
a new pizza. And why did I take it off? All right. Wait, no, no, don't go over there yet.
$1,200 bracelet joke. It's not that much money. It was like, it was probably like $9.
$9. Okay, let's go get in there and start fighting. Go overwhelm them one at a time.
They can't, they can't kill us all. Okay. Hold on. Get in overwhelmed. Forget, forget about the big
blue guy. He will instantly kill me if he touches me though. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. We're going. We're
going. We're going. Get ready. Where's the portal? All right, guys, we've been a, we've been a good
crew for a long time. I'm going to need you to step up. Go for it.
Get him. He killed everybody. Wait, wait, run away. He, okay. He's got like the 3% of his health is
gone. All right. Where's, where's my fire? Wait, iron golem is 397. Fire golem. You and me. I'll
just recast you over and over again. Fight him. Get in there and fight him. Get him. How, why is
he, why is he freezing him? I don't have enough mana for this shit. All right. You want another
strategy? It's got to be Vic. It's got to be Vic with rejuvenation potions. I just have to spam
rejuvenation potions on him. Super, super, super, greater, greater, greater. God, I need a gem.
I need chip gems. Oh, let me just try here. You take this helmet. You take this. He's got 75%
fire resist. Okay. I'm going to just, let's see how long he lives. This is a test. All right, Vic.
He needs lightning. He's got 58% lightning. All right, come on, Vic. Let's go. I'm just going to
try to keep you alive. Give Vic the controller. Vic, turn on your blessing, please. You're really
going to be the guy in the raid that doesn't have his blessings on and shit. Come on. Do I have to
remind everybody? Why do I have, as the raid leader have to constantly tell people how to use their
own moves? I have an idea. Iron Golem. Iron Golem returns 225% damage back to the attacker.
We're just going to have Diablo kill this guy and hurt himself over and over again.
Let's test the theory. Is it working? Holy shit, it kind of worked. Holy shit, it kind of worked.
Leave, run. Oh, that was a ton of damage. Get me out. Get me out. Should I port? He's going to
chase me down here. Port here. This is fine. Do you see the damage? That took like, all right.
That's the plan. I'm just going to buy like 10 swords. What's the cheapest sword I can possibly
buy? All right. Just buy all the cheap shit. Get your helmet back. All right. I'm going to get the
helmet back. I need a socket. Give me this. Okay. I got the helmet back and I'm going to get a
socket shield and just put rubies in it. You sell those? Fire defense on any of these? I don't care.
I will wear like my big brother's clothes. Look at this. 30%. I don't care about that. Just put it
on and give this back. Act one. Good call. But Diablo is going to start. It doesn't matter if
he regens. We're just going to sacrifice like 30 iron golems. We're just going to, okay. We're
just going to, we're going to riddle trash all over the arena so I can always revive an iron
golem no matter where I am. I'm going to just back up a dump truck and dump the whole thing
into the arena. This is so stupid. What a joke. This is 60. I don't have enough money.
Oh no, rub. Just sell this. Use daggers? Well, I, I bought them all.
I already have. Okay. Let's go. Move the potions. So we need a distraction for a minute.
That should be enough for a little while. You're triggering me with your inventory management.
You know what a seller spider is? If you don't know, look it up. That's how I roll. Holy fuck,
doesn't leave. So we need to do one of these right now. Here's one. All right. I need to do this.
Let's start riddling this area. Like I'm going to say this is the trash zone right here.
Let's go. He heard himself. Get in there. It's kind of working. I just have to stay alive.
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh, he's almost at the O. Oh, that's it. I have nothing left.
What's he at? He's past the O. Get me out of here. It's too big. Too big. Whatever. Impossible. Any
more little ones. That's good. Let's go. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Your potions suck. Fuck.
Oh my God. I need mana. What's going on? Oh my God. This is where it ends. He put me in a cage.
Oh no. Just get up here. Get him. Oh fuck. He's down to the L. Get in there. Get in there. Go get him.
Why? It's starting to get expensive. God damn it, man. These shitty hand axes. Move these potions
out of the way. That's not even metal. Wait, no. Come here. Bait it, bait it, bait it, bait it.
He's almost at half health. This is going to work. He can't hit him. Oh, don't run down here. He's
dead. Oh fuck. Wrap around. Where's my pile? Where's my trash? Hit him. Come on. Get in there.
Come on. Get in there. Watch out. I shouldn't be going down that hall anymore. We're going to move
our trash. We're going to move our trash over here. This is really the only safe place for it. It's
like up here. Ready? Just don't kill me. Get out of the way, please. He trapped him in a cage.
Actually working up for us. He's coming for me. Why? God damn it. Look at his health. All right. I
got to back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Look at this. He's almost... This motherfucker is dead.
This motherfucker is dead. Ain't no way he wins. Look at his health. Back to act three, act two.
Do you trade? You do. What do you got? Do you have any junk? You do. Let's go. Potions. Trash pile.
Going up here. Oh my God. He's right there. Wait. Don't do anything stupid. Right here. Trash pile.
Right here. This is a bad spot. He's already dead. Fuck. I got to get him away. That's a bad spot.
Oh my God. Not a good run. Not a good one so far. We got to wrap around the other way. No.
He's... We got this tiny fucking hallway. We have to pull him. Don't go in yet. Pull him down here.
Pull him down here, please. He done... All right. New strategy. Come with me. We're putting a portal
up here. We're going this way. We're doing another trash zone up here. Right here. Up the trash. Good.
Okay. Let's go. He'll chase us over here and we have an open space now.
Follow me. Chase me. Look. He's a piece behind the D right now. Get over here. Find me. Follow me.
Good. I'll bait it.
Come on. Come on. We can do it. It's so close. My stamina. Watch that stamina.
That was almost a killer. We instantly probably killed him. It's okay. Oh my God. Where's he running?
We're out of trash. He's blocked the entrance. Okay. We have to do another trash run. I'm going
right in that portal after I cast this. Okay. Go. There's more trash here? Where? I don't see.
Oh, I wish that counted. Who sells stuff here? No, no, no. I don't know who sells stuff here.
I forget. New act. Act two. Again. Down here. Just... I don't care. Whatever. I have plenty of money.
Okay. No, don't go in. Are you stupid? Come on. Look at how close I am. All right. Trash pile set.
Good run. That was a really good run. Excellent work. Excellent work. Trash. Trash heap number 60.
Good job. 61. Not so good. I think he's found. He found the trash. He's spotted. He's spotted. Hold
on. Wait a minute. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is a bad idea. This is a really bad.
That's three damage, guys. Nope. Don't care. I'm living. My heart just exploded. I thought I was
dead. He still has too much health. Oh my God. No, no, no. Who cares about jokes? Give me up.
Help me. Trash monster number... That was the loudest I think I've... That was the most actual
real scream I've done in a long time. That was like I was about to get into a car accident.
I got him. No uniques. Game sucks. I said... Somebody said that was the stupidest fucking way I've
ever seen somebody kill Diablo. I worked for it. He's dead. Wow. My title can change now.
Oh. Hey, look guys. You see how it saved the run? You guys put six points into iron golem for some
reason. And here he is. He was returning. 225% damage done, returned. That's pretty good.
That's pretty good. Dude, trash pile 69 for the rumble. All right. Well, we did it. We can move
on to act five and we get to watch my favorite cut scene. Did anything else? Let me... I know
canes here, but we did it. First cane. This is a great day indeed. Oh no. Holy shit. I'm gonna
just get 50 subs. 50 community subs from Zyxia. Jesus.
Yes. Thanks so much. Seriously. That's a lot of fucking money. That's so much money.
I am honored that you would give it to me.
Best act, by the way, incoming. Act five D2 is awesome.
This place now. Thank you hero. Praise be to the light. Diablo and Mephisto have been
and big bits into the black abyss that spawned them and the corrupted soul stones are no more
bailing an army of hellish minions. Now this army is searching for the world stone ancient
source of all the soul stones and their power while leaving behind a wake destruction.
Yes. We're going to the barbarian homeland. Ben Eleanor gave the bits, by the way. I just wanted
to wait till that was done talking. Ben Eleanor gave 5,000 bits. Thanks Ben. Seriously. It's
never, never necessary to ever give this channel these amounts of huge dollar signs. Thanks.
I hope you can afford it and I'm glad that you think it's worth paying for.
Thank you. They say, hey, I hope you're doing well. It's been a while since I caught one of
your streams. Thanks for being amazing. Thanks. I appreciate it. Scam Wink. It's already been paid
for like five times. Backpack. Talking about my backpack. Let's identify these because it might
be anything. It might be good. No. Yes. Not an assassin. Well, we did it. Oops. All it took was
just buying up everybody's trash. Let's repair and let's watch. Let's watch one of my favorite
cutscenes. Here we go. The gates of Cessaron have stood for eons beyond remembrance
and you shall not reach them now. Remove your foul demons from our lands. We stand on the side of
light and you shall not be allowed to reach Mount Ariat and that which you seek will not be yours.
Enough! Enough! Enough! I shall take your position into consideration.
Well, it seems your terms are not acceptable.
Bail. Best act. Best act. Best boss. Best villain. My voice is low because that was it. The audio
is incredibly loud. Best laugh. Best enough. We're in act five. Hooray. Currently under siege.
Best salad. Worst build. I have to say that was like a nine out of ten. Enough. It was.
I've been helpless to stop them. Bail is still out on the mountain looking for something.
Bail is looking for something. The world's stolen. Look, it's Otto. Best music. So first things first.
Let's, we're gonna say goodbye to our iron golem who's very, very good, but it's time to replace
with our fire golem. Fire golem just does more damage. Rest easy. Trash number 69.
He's ready to be swept up into the great dumpster out behind the chilies. Goodbye. Farewell.
Shank the Overseer. This is coming up here. Wait, is this Diablo or Warcraft? What's the
difference? What is this? So let me help you out here.
Diablo one and two way better than Warcraft. Here it is. Diablo one and two better for me than
Warcraft three. Warcraft one and two way worse to me than Diablo one and two. Diablo three way worse
than Warcraft one and two. They kind of switch. They swap. It's wrong. I mean, I have to disagree.
Diablo two is better than Warcraft three. I'm just gonna say it head to head, pound for pound. I think
Diablo two is a better game. Although I'm biased because this is like, I love this game. I love
this franchise. So I'm pretty biased. Why is there just a shield in here? All right. Stop the siege
by killing Shank the Overseer in the bloody foothills. We're going to have an army. This
should be pretty easy. I use that term pretty loosely. I do want to get Vic back. Oh, well,
I remember this guy. This guy. Spoiler alert. This guy.
We're both necromancers, man. Come on. A lot of lore here. I really do implore you to buy this.
No, I don't. It takes more than a siege to stop me. All right, get him.
I need Vic. I need Vic. The reason why I say is because the game doesn't really run that well.
You got to do a bunch of bullshit to get it to run. Blizzard does this really great thing where
they sell a game for $20 on their official website. And like the game can barely run on
like Windows 7 computers. It's cool. It's really cool. Like you have to download fucking third
party apps to get it to run the way it was supposed to run. $20, by the way,
on the official Blizzard shop. You need, uh, where is it? There it gets Qualkeck. There is
Qualkeck. There you are. I am Qualkeck. We, all right, this is where we have to, no, no, no,
this is very important. Do we trade Vic's combat aura for a super strong, heavy melee damage
barbarian? Yeah, Vic just makes all the skeletons stronger. Barbarians are cool though.
Just fun to watch him use two hands and swing and shit. I love it. All right, let's get the army back.
They're not going to instantaneously die now. Also, I'm thinking of, uh,
thinking of doing a couple of Mephisto runs. Thinking about it. We need better gear.
I need it. All right, after shank the overseer, we're going to do, uh, at least one,
at least one Mephisto run. We're going to go, we're going to go open up the treasure box that
is Mephisto's body. I need all the help I can get. This is true. I got rid of my keys, right?
And we'll get in there, guys. Come on. I don't, don't go up too far. I get overwhelmed if I go
too far. I want a better spear for him. Everybody needs better stuff. He's got a unique, but it's an
old, unique level 17, 11 to 27 life steal. I mean, it's, it's just old. We're like level,
how old is, how, not how old, what level is he? 29. We've got to get her something better than that.
Life still is really good for tanking. Yeah, it is. It is very good. What do you, what do you
get for doing this? I forget. I think you actually get a rune word. Yeah. It gives like
Rao or Tao. You get Kim the gifted prize. We have not gone to McDonald's. I've not given 10
community fries to, uh, Kim yet. We have to go to McDonald's. The next time we go, I will.
He hates Kim. Everything they have, everything has to be hated.
We're good. Terrible. Skeleton friends are starting to die faster now. I don't like it.
We need better stuff. I'm definitely going on at least one. We need at least one more unique,
one more set. Pretty good. What free full set do you get when you hit max level?
Well, that's very interesting. You don't. I'm affording Goblin.
Ooh, a wand. You know what? That's the problem with Diablo 3 now and Diablo 3 in general
is it was never about the journey. It was about the grind. It was just get max level
fast as possible. Get set to do max level riffs and just grind riffs until you have
your gem is max the fuck out. It was just, and you could, I guess you could argue that during
this game's heyday at the cow level was the same thing. But even when I first played through Diablo
3 and Reaper, it just felt, it just felt like a get to the grind, not necessarily like kill Diablo,
especially considering what they did with the Nephilim riffs. Like it was just log on and just
watch white and yellow numbers explode on your screen. And that's it. Here comes a three hour
video essay. Oh no, it's, hey, there's Decrepify. It's a lot of cold resist. I should hold on to
this. Ooh, magic find. You're going to have a video essay with a YouTube video essay that's three
hours that has 14,000 views. Why is that so specific? That's so specific. That's all video
essays. Don't want to die. Grand charm. Come on. Have it be a good one. Shit dog shit.
Just dog shit. Oh my God. How bad one to maximum damage. That's this is little brother levels of
bad. Your little brother would have this on and he'd be like level 60 and he'd still have it on.
That's what I forgot. I had jewelry slots. I picked that up already identified
or it went immediately into the slot. I didn't even put it there.
This way, this way, this way. I think I'm almost at the top. Get in there. All right, slow down.
All right, I'm going to get in the middle. We leveled up, level 30.
It's not in my inventory. Why? Where is it? Where'd it go? I think it also
video essay incoming. The reason why I had so much fun with this game was
just miserably failing characters like trying to do a vengeance paladin.
It was just you could mess up. You could screw the fuck up in Diablo 2 and maybe you could still
try to make it work. D3. It's just you made a barbarian and then I don't like this switch
switch switch. I can just use this one who cares. There were no stakes to your character.
It was just here's everything. Use whatever you want. All right, here we go.
Video essay 2. All right, hold on. Shanks up here.
Every time I played this game when I was younger, I always had to say that out loud.
Every time I got here, no matter how many times I've been here, I would go,
shank the ol' bustier every time I just did it again. God, I remember when I was younger.
Fireman's gonna die. This is a traffic jam. I need you up here, Fireman. I think these
people can explode. I don't want to end it here. Speaking of careful, nothing. All right, kill them.
Yep, they can explode. This could end real fast. One wrong explosion. All right, let's get in.
Kill them. Shank. Burn. Ah, stupid gank. Larzok has the reward.
Oh yeah, if we're doing this, he will put a socket. This is one of the best rewards in the game.
First playthrough. First playthrough, Larry. First playthrough, Andy, whatever.
Oh cool, add sockets. I could use another one in here.
Can you just waste it completely? I'm not going to use this. Even with the cold resist,
it's not very good. Maybe I'll hold on to it. All right, we've got some management to do.
We've got some management to do here. A lot of management. Oh boy, I have to sell this.
It's just, it's worthless to me. I was keeping this to, why was I keeping this?
I was making a rune word, right? Am something thul? Holy fuck, that's a lot of resist.
Rid of the extra tier. If. Eld. F. F. Get rid of it. F. These things drop all the time.
Rowl. Rowl. Rowl. Get rid of it. These flawed diamonds. Get rid of them. I just don't, I'm not,
get rid of them. They're taking up too much space. Anything flawed is out at this stage.
We're keeping complete or higher only. All right, let's dump all this shit.
Okay, if I organize this, I can make a flawless. I must have enough to make it perfect.
Flawless amethyst. Always good. Still have the leg. Thul? If I have more than one thul,
I do. Get rid of it. Hey. All right, that's a lot of light and resist. That's why I'm keeping it.
I need a rune word. What was the word? What was the rune word for this? Fire alarm? In all my years
playing Diablo II. Decades of time. I have never once thought that it was a smoke detector.
Now I do, and now I can never un-hear that. But what was the word? What was it? It was am
something thul. Anyone remember? Am-ral-thul. I have it, right? Am-ral-thul. Oh, right,
because I was waiting to see if I could find something better than a war sword.
If we just say fuck it and do it, who cares? I mean, war sword's pretty good. Am-ral-thul.
I'm doing it. It's am-ral-thul, right? Let me just look. I want to make sure I got this right.
I would hate to have this completely wrong. Okay, it's called King's Grace, right?
Am-ral-thul. Yep. All right, you ready? I don't have enough strength to use this,
but I probably will eventually. Am-ral-thul. Boom. King's Grace. 16 to 40. A huge amount of
attack rating. Tons of damage to demons. Tons of damage to undead. Adds 5 to 30 fire. Adds 3 to
14 cold. Tons of health stolen for a hit. Pretty good. Pretty good. Some of you may have joined
the stream very recently and are probably thinking to yourself, is this guy crazy?
He's- why are you- why are you doing this on a necromancer? Well, it's because I, um,
I have- I don't have any moves. I have teeth too. I don't have any abilities. Quick, do a flush.
That's stupid. All right, back up. I have- all right, let's move. The hard wall. I'm glad I beat
Diablo. The actual wall. The true wall is going to be the Ancients. If you don't know what the
Ancients are, the Ancients are- it's a boss encounter that you cannot leave. If you leave,
it resets. You have to do it in one shot. You cannot lose. So, and that's, unfortunately,
right at the end of the act. So, we're not going to know for certain. Oh wait, I was going to do
Mephisto. Yeah, let's do that. Let's go kill Mephisto. Not that good. And also jump. All right,
let's go do Mephisto. Let's pull this crew. Durance of Hate level two. Let's go. I already
know where it is. Glorious. It's up here. I wonder if this would be any easier now that I'm
10 levels higher. What, 10? 15? Am I 30? 30? Yeah, what was I? I was like level 22 when I was here.
24 maybe. It's still probably going to be hard. Somebody's blocking the door.
All right. Are you getting out of the fucking doorway? Get out of the doorway. I have Fireman
here to protect me. Yes, I do. I'm going to die to Mephisto. I'm only level 30. It's not like,
it's very possible. I have to be careful. You can drop shit. This desk is falling over here.
There we go. These guys are still pretty dangerous. That just fucking hurt a lot.
Don't run and pull. What are you guys thinking? You're just going to go pull Mephisto? You're
going to get us all killed. All right. Come here, Mephisto. Get in there. Yeah, that's just going
fine. Burn them. Come on, Fire Golem. Stay alive. Make it clean. And something good.
I think I already have those boots. Oh, no, I don't. Seagulls. Sabot. Holders is 40.
Not enough strength. Do I have anything else for Seagulls? It's very fast. Plated belt. Don't I
have? Do I have something else for Seagulls? I don't think so. Now you can finally go kill
Duriel. Yeah. All right. That was fun. Good again. No, I have, I have Catan's. These normal little
early game sets, though, if you get two or three pieces, it actually is really good.
They have a lot of good bonuses. Let's start from the beginning.
Impossible. Let's try to sell the cube. I'm glad you can't do that.
Barrens of Hate level two. Again. No, don't pick up blood. My army. We're back. Back in business.
Let's go. Get hit right in the head. Do I have potions?
Get caught up here. I gotta get potions. That hurts. Yeah, I need.
Even if they're shitty, I don't care. Yes. No, just get the good ones. Just get the good ones.
The best part of this game is that it is not Warcraft remastered.
Uh, I guess, I guess I follow you. I think I, I pick up what you're putting down here.
Reforged. Reforged. It's not, hey, it wasn't, it's not a remaster.
That's where you guys got it all wrong. It was reforged. That means that's a made-up term
that it could mean anything. It's not Warcraft remade or remake remastered. No, it's reforged.
I thought you guys got that when we announced it. Oh, by the way,
you can never play the original ever again. We had to, we reforged the damn thing.
We didn't teleport, did we? Fireman died. Poor Fireman. Gave up. Again, here let's go.
Hey, Mephisto, remember us? We're here. We're here for the diamonds. We're here for the jewels.
I just get to watch. It's not even worth picking up. We're gonna do it five times.
This'll be number three. And then we'll go, we'll do the next quest in Act 5. We'll do this five
times. Man, the times that I wish I was a sorceress. One of them is right now. It's boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. Exit game. Enter game. Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Exit game. Enter game. All righty, people. Careful.
Easy. The mages just died so quickly. These mages are getting beat up. You guys dead? Come on,
guys. Clean it up a little bit here. This is embarrassing. The same hardcore run it is.
It is still hardcore. I've not died yet on this character. All that could change in an instant.
Okay, let's go. Look, I'm helping this time. Okay, so I just dropped a meteor.
Hold on here. Hold on here. It's getting a little hairy. Not clean. Not clean. Heavy boots. Boots
again? Sanders. 40%. These are actually kind of good. Sanders riprap. These are really good
actually. Do I have anything else from Sanders? I'm gonna put these on. 40% faster run. Bunch of
strength in decks. Oh my god, I fucking vroom. Don't I already have? Yeah, I have stealth too.
Well, I can do this faster now. Yeah. Why am I not opening the chest back here? Why has nobody
corrected me? Where are all the Diablo 2 veterans in here that should be correcting me to get the
chest back here? Because it could be unique. I remember being like a Sunday afternoon and I
was on my like 40th Mephisto run. I had a fresh Mountain Dew Code Red. I was just in my element.
It was just so much fun. It was in my element. Somebody would come into the room,
spam a Diablo 2 item scam website 10 times, and then instantly leave.
Ugh, those are the days. Oh my god, don't die. Reminiscing is gonna kill me. I do, I remember.
I remember having to have a password protected private game or every 10 seconds a new account
that was a keyboard smash name would come in and talk about how much percent off their wind forces
were. I remember also, God bless my mother. God bless my mother because I remember being like
15 and wanting to buy a wind force and I was trying to explain to my mother why I had to
have this thing. And she just shook her head and said, that is absurd. You don't need that.
And I was like, no, but I do, but my character, come on. And she refused to do it. It didn't
matter how much I was like, no, but mom, by the way, I was 15, not like six. So I don't know why
I'm doing like a come on mommy voice. I was like fucking a teenager. I was like 15. I was, I was,
I had to have been fucking like, oh no, stop, stop, stop, stop. Where's my fire friend?
Hold on. I just need to never talk ever again. Um, my mom, I was a teenager at the time.
She told me it wasn't worth it and it was a stupid thing to do. To buy this item from the
Diablo 2 scam website. Your mom had a big brain. I think a wind force, wind force was like,
don't die. I think a wind force was like 200 bucks. It's crazy. Oh, wait, that's actually a head.
They were expensive. They were like more than a hundred bucks or something. They had to have
been. I remember freedom life tap. Oh, hooray. One more. You were a pretty stupid 15 year old.
Um, no, just the wind force was one of the hardest things to get in the whole game.
Wind force was just the unobtainable. It was that one bow that was the best bow.
All it would have done would be to let me to use strafe and kill cows faster.
That's all I was doing. So in 2020 hindsight, no, it definitely was not worth it. I just wanted
to be able to farm because I wanted to find the runes. Yep. It was to be able to farm cows.
All right, this is the last one. It's 55 cents now. I would not put my credit card into a website
still selling Diablo 2 items for 50 cents. I don't think that would be a good idea for me.
Come on, man. It's a steel. It's a wind force.
Oh, fuck. I can't let this be on the tombstone.
I'd rather die to the ancients than die farming Mephisto. That's embarrassing on the tombstone.
Yo, they're gonna be a pain in the ass still. All right, let's get council number two.
Your mom probably bought the wind forces and got you banned. My account wasn't banned until recently.
Played Diablo 2 a year ago. Just installed it to check it out for the first time in a while.
What you think? You think my mother now did this? My mother in 2020? That would be sort of strange.
Mom trying to get my account banned. Mom got my account banned. That's like a YouTube video.
Guys, my mom sold gold on my Warcraft account banned.
Come on, give us a unique. This is five times. I've spun the slot machine five times. I want something.
Give me something. Ouch. One more. That one didn't count. All blues doesn't count.
Jesus, that was stupid.
Where are my friends? I'm about to exit the game. It's because there's a champion in here.
Wait, were there two champions? What the fuck? You guys didn't kill it? All right, well look, come on.
Let's go. Big co-op juke. Nice. Nice. That's what I like to see. Follow me.
All right, let's go. I can run faster than them. I can run faster than them. Just run.
I have super speed. Use it. All right, now slow down. Do I have any healing potions?
I think I have to go back to town. All right, let's see if I can just do this without getting hit.
Just don't get hit. Just don't get hit. All there is to it. Let me adjust the boomer belt. Adjust it.
Just. Also terrible. Let's go. Last one. No matter what happens is it. Who cares. It'll be it. No more.
Everybody in attacking me. Don't do that. Ow. And unique. Ah, no. I can't do it again. No, I can't.
I'm just gonna get there very quickly. Hold on.
Maybe I should change it up. Should I do Undariel or something? Player count?
Yeah, but that's dangerous though. I'll do players. Players four. You can call me a
coward or you won. I mean, there's eight. Let's see if players four. If I can do players four, then I'll
keep going. Dude, and this is gonna be. No, no, no, no. Bad idea. That's a really, really bad idea right
now. No, no, that's so bad. Players 200. Let's go. I'm just gonna try it around there. I have a no
shit button. Almost there. Good. No, uh, no little guys to screw it all up. Here we are. Now we're
gonna take this slow. I can't hurt these guys. I'm gonna be solely reliant on the companions,
which has to be like that anyways. Footstep sounds kill me. I can't even hear footsteps on.
Oh, no, I do. Yeah, I do. It's like, damn, I don't appreciate your passive aggressive tone, Jerma.
What the fuck are you talking about? Players four. Where is it? Jerma's weird. I mean, yeah,
kind of am. Whatever. I don't think I'm that weird. I don't think I'd do anything that out
of the ordinary that a normal person wouldn't wouldn't do. That's what they all say. Yeah.
So what? That's true. Just in case I die. I can't, I, I, I, I, I'm dead if I die. There is no coming
back. I got to heal the, uh, I got to heal Vic. Come back here. Vic is healed. Stay the fuck out
of the way. He's going to one by one take out every skeleton. He's going to kill. It's gonna
take a while. Why are you killing this guy in one hit? Vic, you good? Just Vic, you just do it.
You'll be fine. I think he's healing himself. Use it now. He's got that pole. He goes down.
There it is. Heal him. Oh my God. He's fucking gonna die.
Kill him. I can press shift. Yeah, that's right. Come on, Vic. All right. Unique.
Get some bad luck here. Usually you get like one. Usually you get one unique. I just had to
stretch for that one. That's it. I'm not doing another one. I'm not doing another Mephisto run.
That's it. No more Mephisto runs. Didn't say anything about not doing an Andariel run.
That runs so fast.
Okay, minor mana potions. All right, get in here. Uh, Andariel is going to be pretty easy.
Should be. Do I not have any magic find? I, I do not really, but it's hard to get at this stage.
I could make a moonward maybe with that magic find on it. I think I have like
20-30%. You need like, you need to have more than 100% to really do runs efficiently.
But I don't have any. I'm just trying to do it straight up. Shit. Thought it was a different
rune. Oh well. All right, let's go get her. Hello. Killer. He's like already almost dead.
All right, Andariel. Drop a unique. You dropped so much shit and none of it's a unique.
It's all like level eight. Level four. Player count, player counts at four. I could do eight.
I could do player count eight with Andariel. You know what? Let's do that. Let's just do that.
Let's do that right now. Player's eight. Definitely can do eight plays with Andariel.
That shouldn't be a problem. Just to hope it's not. Easy. Okay. Oh, we're fine. Can I get it?
Good. I'm fast. Best part about a unique, it doesn't matter what act or where in the game
you find it. Well, not entirely true. But for all the normal uniques, they could drop anywhere.
There are a lot of uniques that only drop in Nightmare in Hell difficulty, but
it's not like I'm going to get like a level two unique. That sucks. All uniques are pretty good
for the most part. Open the door. I mean, in normal, like if you're like level 20, level 30,
level 40, a lot of normal uniques can carry you. I mean, take a look. I've had this on the whole
time. I've had this on since level 10. I haven't taken it off. I haven't needed to. All right.
Eight players. I'm about scared. I was when I first came in here. What did I have? Three
skeletons. That's not even a challenge. Not even a challenge. Unique. If everybody in the chat says
it at the same time, it might happen. Everybody in the chat say unique. Nobody. You guys didn't say
it. Not enough people said it. Oh no. We failed you. Hello. Do a Diablo run. Impossible. Let's go.
Mephisto. Done. Coming back to act five. Last one. Truly, truly the final one. Truly with certainty.
And then we'll do the next part of act five.
Make me laugh, E-clown.
No, you have to do a joke now. No, I don't want to. I don't want to. No, I'm okay.
Let's play a game. I gotta level up from doing this. That should be good. Gotta power up the
funny crystal. My funny crystal. Pull up from this. Whoa. That's bad. That's lower resist all.
No, he killed everybody. That's one you don't want to see. That's not a good one. You don't
want to see that pop up. Weaken. Resist lower. It sucks. Still not anything here though. Let's go
this way. It's locked. When he said Diablo resident sleeper. Opening up the box is the most
interesting thing you've ever seen. And you mean to tell me that killing Mephisto seven times in
a row is not the most exciting thing in the world. Oh, you get to see like yellow text hit the ground.
What are you talking about? All right. Just keep a big alive. Amateur hour. Only seven.
This should level up. You finally get to pick something because you picked the least entertaining
play style. I didn't pick. Probably should have put that in the title. This is not going to do
with me. No, don't die. Stay alive. Oh, well. Level nine. Get the fuck out of here with this shit.
Level nine? Level three? This is act three. All right. Take a look. That's not correct. That's
the runeword website. Those are the cheats. Okay. That's better. Wait. No, it's not because I remember
we had to zoom in. I didn't even click this either. What the hell am I thinking?
Let me fix this. All right, guys. Pick the next point, please. Make it a good one.
What do you want to do? Please choose wisely. Okay. Revive. I didn't. I'm surprised. I thought,
okay. Somebody said, I want the one that looks like a big poop. None of the three of these that
have been clicked remotely resemble that. Not even close. Which one of these are you looking at?
Okay. We're doing revive. Pretty good choice. Thanks for voting. Now, what about this?
Bunny Poo Poo streamer. Omega Low. No, it's Bunny Poo Poo chat members. How much do I actually have
strength? Okay. Strength it is. Strength it is. I can now use that sword and I can use the
something else too with 70, right? What else is 70? Something else is 70. Is revive.
I need to put that on the bar. Let's do, let's see. F1, F2, F3, F4, F5, F6 can be revived.
So revive does this. You'll see in just a second. See these guys? He's Blood Lord.
When he dies, I have Blood Lord. They have the same moves. They do everything the exact same,
except they're yours. Very, very useful. All right. It's time to continue to play the game
after a pee break and go for about three hours. Let's, let's take a break. I'll be back in like
two minutes, three minutes. Let us continue. Oh, the last thing we did was the Virgin of
Island. We have a revive. Where is he? There he is. See? Isn't he cool? He just like floats around
and it could be anybody. It could be anyone. Oh, my sword. I'll get it in a second. Oh, he's dead?
Oh my God. They're getting stomped. We have strength in numbers, not individual strength.
Come on, guys. Somebody kill somebody. Oh, damn it. I thought it was going to be good.
Doesn't look very good. Oh, for the love of God, it's on players eight.
It's like, why are we getting our asses kicked? This shouldn't be happening.
What? Did it get this much harder? All right. Now we got the whole crew. Let's go. All right.
Two players. I too live in an evil demon hut. We'll get, we'll get the heck out of there.
We got a big guy now. Let that guy out. Why? Oh, find the soldiers in the Virgin of Highland.
So there are soldiers locked up that we have to find and help and rescue.
Need to rescue them. A battle going on. Oh, man. I can't even tell who's friend or foe right now.
All right. Time to go back. Do you think he realizes how dumb he is? What? By doing what?
I normally might agree with you, but what are we talking about? Can I do the cow level?
Cause I'm winning because I've beaten Diablo. Wait, I don't think he would. What do you mean?
He doesn't realize. What do you mean? What did I do? What happened? It needs to be Bill.
Do you, is it Diablo or Bill? He just doesn't get it. Oh, I guess not. I need to have potions.
Potions please. Potions please. Thank you. He just doesn't get it. I wish we could make him see.
Oh, 46 to 121 versus 37 to 106. A shitload of everything else. This can now go away. I can
use this, but why would I? He's a much better. We could make him understand.
If only we could just make him understand. See? Right there.
I'm just going to pretend like you guys are just making a joke and you're trying to get me to go,
what are you talking about? Which is what already happened. So you already did it.
You've already done it. You did a good job.
Saved one. I need two more. Two more soldier
prisons. Two more. Difficulty. I mean, I have it on players too. I mean, it's extra experience
and we can handle it. We can handle it. You haven't changed the difficulty. I changed it twice.
What? Yes, I did. I forgot the slash the first time. Didn't I put it on two
after four? I fixed it. At least I thought I did. You never set it to four.
I still like it. Another camp right here. Let's get it. Breathe. Oh shit. Hold on. That's death.
I want the big guy. Hey, Vic leveled up. Good. My mana is so bad. It's just bad. All right. That's
a unique. That's a... One more. All right. Kill this champion, please. I have 100% more damage
to demons. Look at how much I'm melting this guy. Did you see that? I have 100% more damage to demons
and undead. I may as well be unkillable. I may as well have put it on players
50 because there's no way I'm going to lose ever again. I mean, like, geez, it's just not fair.
I just uninstall the game. I'm looking for another prison. Looking for another prison.
Yell if you see one. I don't think it would be that much further down than this.
I thought it could be. How am I this powerful? You struggle with the necro on normal?
I'm not sure I am. I mean, I'm pretty weak, to be honest. Abaddon. Just a random dungeon.
I'm not looking for Abaddon, though. We're looking for another... We're looking for another
barbarian camp, which for some reason we can't find.
I'm so fast. I can just ski around at, like, 75% extra speed. No, it's definitely down.
It's definitely not this far up. What's my favorite PS2 game?
Uh, I don't know. That's a pretty good question. I have no idea. I don't have any idea.
Tony Hawk's Underground? No. I don't know. That's what you get in, like, an hour.
Maybe I'll be able to come up with something then. All right. Barbarian camp. Barbarian camp.
I thought I would have bet all my chips that it was right there. I would have lost all my chips.
And then I would have fucking slowly been like, okay, cool. Thanks for the game. Thanks for the
game, guys. And I'd just slowly get up from the chair and go to my car. Yep. Bye-bye. See you later.
Fun night. And the door closed in the car. And I'd be like, haha, let's go home.
Just fucking, just bullsh- scream. What's my favorite chip? Fake Blaze.
You're doing the YouTuber voice at the poker table. You deserve to lose your chips.
I didn't go into the poker table or like the blackjack table and be like, okay, sounds good.
So what's that, 11? I think what I'm going to do is I'm going to double down on that one.
It would be like, shut the fuck up. I'm sorry? Oh, so I can't hear you. The YouTuber voice.
Where is this other barbarian camp? Or should I say, where is this other barbarian camp?
Let me try, I'll translate it. I'll translate everything into YouTube for you guys.
Just in case anyone didn't know. Where is anybody? Bring back the voice actor frog.
I don't think I could do that. I'm not sure we'll see him again. He didn't, he did not like,
he was not happy on that stream. He was very angry with me. I apparently, I quote, put him on the
spot. And he said, it would be as if I called you to come over my house to stream from my house
on my channel as you. And I laughed in his face. Don't call me ever again. Retell the joke,
I missed it. Yeah. But that frog actor is not going to come back. Weirdly enough,
when's Bugleberry coming back? When he makes his album called Scare and Through the 70s.
10 hits sung by Bugleberry himself of his own writing based on original characters he wrote
and drew. He drew these characters on his paper like he like artists that draw and drew them.
I need to find these barbarians before I lose my mind.
No, I want this guy. I don't want you. Come on. Barbarians. Barbarians. I need one more.
Where are they? Bugleberry. Bugleberry. Give me this way. Bugleberry sucks. No, he doesn't.
I can't believe you guys didn't like him. He was so sad. Hey, hey, hey. He made his $40.
Okay. And when I handed him the money, I gave him two 20s. He was like, two 20s. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. He was like really fucking VIP. Excited about it. It was like he'd
never seen that much money before in his life. It was really weird. I mean, I can't do the impression
well, but you know. And he called me from his car and he asked me if I still had one of the 20s.
I said no. He said, I'll do my best here. Well, I only have one. Are you sure?
Somewhere along the way, he lost one of the 20s. I don't know how. We put them both in the same
pocket. I don't understand. It was within five minutes of me handing it to him. And I'm like,
dude, I paid you. I can't. I'm not going to give you another 20. And then he called again
that night and he asked, he had, he just real quick wanted me to ask me what kind of dog I had.
What was the breed? I don't think he was under the assumption that he was going to buy a dog with
$40 for 20. He's a weird guy. All right. Got them all. That's good.
He just wanted a puppy. We've been hating on him.
You're so mean. Bugleberry is a good person. I cannot speak to Bugleberry's character.
The guy carries around urns of demons and shit. You know how long it took after the Halloween
stream to get that fucking thing back inside of its dwelling. An hour? No.
Probably three weeks. This motherfucker put on like costumes and was running around,
was going to the bank and shit. We had to tail him in his Bugleberry's fucking shitty old car.
Fucking stupid. Maybe you should check in with him sometimes. Oh, don't worry. He checks in with me
all the time actually. And I answer the phone every time and we talk because we're fucking
old friends. I love Bugleberry. He's the best. You know, I've got this great, great plan for Bugleberry.
I can't wait. It's going to be awesome. I cannot wait. If only I could tell you.
If only I could tell you what the plan is for Bugleberry. A lot of you would actually probably
really have. Because I am. We lack critical information.
I have big bits. Oh, freak out. Freak. How many times did you do this? One, two, three,
four. Did you just give two, what, a hundred dollars? All right. Freak out just gave
a hundred dollars worth of bits. There's a lot of information here. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is, this is confusing me. First of all, thanks for the hundred dollars.
Jeremy, I've been watching you for a few years. Have you ever seen a professional RC car race?
I have not. Here you go. Speaking of cars, when was the last time you worked on your car? I don't.
I know it might seem like a steep hill to climb, but I've been working for a Honda as a technician
for a few months now. Why do I feel like this is not real? I don't think this is, I don't know,
I don't think this is real. I think this is made up. I can guide you along the way. The
following is a list of things anybody can check without having to buy any, any expensive tools.
Wiper blades, washer fluid, engine filter and cabin AC filter, battery terminals, drive belt,
front rear brake pads, tire tread, transmission fluid. I'm not going to do any of this. No,
I just drop it off and I say, please fix my car, sir. And then they charge me $1,500 for like,
that's what I do. Anti-freeze power steering fluid, tire pressure. If you find any of these
are in need of any attention or replacement, you should bring it to a local dealership or
certified mechanic. Or if you want, you can try to replace it yourself. Hey, that would be a great
idea for a stream. Or if you do decide to do it yourself, you should take any and all precautions,
even after working on cars for almost a year. The smell of these fluids will make me gag.
You motherfucker, you motherfucker. I don't think I'm going to be, I don't think I'm going to be
uh, reading any more messages from Mr. Freakout. I think, uh, I think we've, I think we've hit the
wall here talking about the codes. Uh, I'm not, I'm not going to give any more codes.
This is the porn guy, by the way, for those of you that are curious, the porn guy. I will answer
this one question though. I will give this to you. Uh, they want to ask how many towels I use on a
weekly basis. One. Showering. I mean, that's a weird question, but I mean, one. I think, uh,
God damn it, man. What the flying fuck. Who uses one towel? One for every, no, one for like,
showering. I don't know. What does that mean? How many towels do you use on a weekly basis? Like,
what, if I go to a pool, I'll use an extra towel. If I, like, yeah, I don't know. I use one towel
a week every like three or four days, replace a towel. That's normal. You use a towel to wash
your dishes and a shower. No, we, we're not, we, we have not, you're playing semantics now.
Like, I'm thinking of how many towels I use in the bath, like tub. I use one towel to like
shower, get out, dry off. Three, four days will go by, use another one. You got to conserve water.
You're going to just, you're going to wash a towel every day? You made the second part up.
What do you mean? What? That's two. He doesn't wash dishes. No, you use a different towel. Okay,
there's a dish towel. There's a bath towel. These are two, they're two separate entities
that they're used for different things. Okay, I use a dish towel. One. You know, who, why are we
even talking about this? Uh, thank you, freak out for the hunt, for like the $500 in porn messages
and the tips on cars. But I'm sad to say I'm not, I'm not going, I will not be reading
one of your messages again. That's, that, that you, you popped out to the pitcher on this last
message. You popped out to the pitcher and he caught it. You swung it right in the air and it
was caught. You're out. You're out. That's it. I really appreciate it though, but you're out.
No, all right. You, you, you can, you link a bunch of porn codes twice, two different times.
And the third time you reference explicitly the porn codes that strike three men.
At some point you got to strike out. That's why he's naked. Um, oh yeah. This is on hardcore. I
can't do that. What kind of weirdo would wear a backpack and a t-shirt?
Some of you new viewers don't get it. No. All right. I have to stand up guys. I'm wearing a
boomer brace. See, I'm wearing a backpack and a fanny cap, a fanny pack. And you know, and you
know it. You know it. It's right there. Oh, oh, oh, oh, the bionic boomer. Another one? Really?
That was just like a bug. I can't even do it. Yeah. I've done it. Okay. I have to wink too
many times. I can't, I don't know how to do it anymore. These are scam winks. Whatever. I want
to do, I want to turn this in. I think the wink experience has been a, has been a failure.
Has it? Oh, I got a ring. Oh no, he gave me Raal-Ort-Tal. Raal-Ort-Tal. If only I had a
shock and a shield. That's what he says. Uh, look for Anya under the crystalline passage by the
frozen river. Anya is one of the townspeople here. She's trapped in ice. 100,000 points to show Otto.
No, I'm not gonna like drag my dog in here. I'm not gonna like channel point my dog into the room
and like pick him up. And no, that's like not, I don't want to do that to him. That's not nice.
Hey Otto, somebody gave a 10,000, 100,000 points. Come here. You look at the camera.
You know, he's not, he's not a toy. I don't want to do that to him. All right, crystalline.
Where's my, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. He's a dog. He's not going to get mad
if you pick him up. All right. You see how many winks happen a stream? It's at least like six or
seven. I don't want to like pick him up and put him down, pick him up, put him down, pick him up.
Plus I got, guys, I have a back brace on now. I can't do that anymore. I can't even move. Stuck
in the chair forever. Forever. How about a nose cam? All right, we need to go to the crystalline
passage by the frozen river. It's, I believe it's just to keep going up. Boys, up to the right.
Once, once you start to see frozen stuff. Hey, you know, we're there. Somebody just asked us,
does Otto know any tricks? Yeah. You know, sit, he knows, lie down, he knows, roll over.
He can do a lot of stuff. Kim actually taught Otto a lot of stuff. I think it's up here. He's very
smart. Well, he's very motivated, to put it that way. If you have a little treat in your hand,
he will do whatever you want. He'll be like, let's go. I know every trick now.
Without a treat, he's just like, nah. You're like, hey, Otto, roll over. He's like, no, why?
Like, roll over, Otto. No, I don't have anything I want. Why would I? He's smart.
He's like, I only do that with shit that I want. It's like his streamer dad.
Quest reward. What's Otto's alignment? Um, dog. I think dog is its own alignment, don't you think?
I need more. I feel like I have people, but not a lot of people. How? I'm being overwhelmed.
German is only funny when you give him money. That's not true.
All right, let's keep moving. Almost level 30. What? 32? Cool. All right. First align passage.
We need to go in. It's not this way. A little bit further up, I think.
Tip of Archeron. Nope. There it is. Streamer, be mad for me. Um, I can do that. Yeah. Uh,
just open up twitch.tv slash German nine eight five. Go to the videos tab.
Uh, click. Oh yeah. Click on, uh, click on the Tony Hawk underground stream
and fast forward to about nine hours into the stream and then let go and watch this thing sucks.
The poison's all right, but just go watch the jump king stream. I'm glad I caught that live.
I'm glad he caught it live too. I thought it was fun. I did. All right, here we go.
Crystal line passage. Now we're fucking, this is no longer a joke now.
Once we get through here, this is where we're going to see if I have what it takes to win.
It's only muted for like 20 minutes. That's really good actually. It's only muted for 20 minutes,
about 10 and a half hours. What songs got grabbed? What did anybody know? We've got, uh,
they killed all the skill ups. Level up. Can't revive champions, unfortunately. That'd be nice.
Oh shit. I forgot that's the, that spawns a champion. All right. Let's, uh, do the skill
point. Take a look. This is what we have so far. We're at the bottom here. Give me a better
picture here in a second. Here we go. Take us somewhere. Take us somewhere. I'm going to
sneeze. So if you hate sneezing, I would, I would just leave the stream open. Walk away from your
computer. No, it's not going to happen. Ah, the worst. Torn. This might be a zoom in.
I think this is a zoom in. What does more revive do? More revives. So you can have two,
three, four, five, six. I think we have to zoom in. Sorry teeth. That's never going to happen.
Sorry teeth. Try again. Okay. Cancel crew. We're going to do a second point and revive. Thanks
for voting. Don't go anywhere yet. Oh, he needs mana. He needs vitality. He needs more strength.
Imagine helping the streamer. It's up to you. Vitality it is. This will get us a second revive.
By the way, in case anyone is curious, revive. It just, every point you put in just lets me have
more revives. That life and damage only comes from skeleton mastery and summon resist. So it pulls
from skeleton mastery. This does not do anything else, but it gives me more revives. I want to
make sure that's clear and whatever is yes, whatever is summoned, but let's get a,
we have a harpy. I'll take both of these guys. They don't explode.
He did. They both exploded. Great. These moonlords are really powerful. I'll take both of them.
Can't explode though. I don't need them to revive anybody. All right. The skeleton mages that are
freezing people. Could you hold off on doing that? My mana is such shit. If I revive one person,
I have to drink a potion after doing one spell. Where are you going moonlord? Get over here.
We're starting to get a very large amount of people. Five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11. There are 12 summons taking up lots of space. You have a whole community. It's just
going to get bigger. Especially with the revives. You can have like 20 revives, 12 skeletons,
eight skeletal mages. You can have a stupid amount of people.
These people have their own discord. Can I just say, they're all watching right now,
I didn't think that I was going to be playing Diablo two into act five.
I'm actually pleasantly surprised by this. I think this is really cool.
I thought I was going to make it to like act one. I didn't think I was going to go much
further than that. But here we are. I left a decent resist charm on the ground. It was like
five resist. I apologize. I forgot it. Will I be able to enjoy Diablo non-hardcore after this?
Yeah. Because as interesting as this is to do, I just like kind of running around and
dying doesn't matter. And I prefer a non-hardcore character for sure.
We need the crystalline frozen river for the frozen river. It's one of these places here.
How did the moon lord die already? That'd be possible.
The river is frozen because it's still a river. Yeah. There's the waypoint. Yeah, it is.
Because it's just, it's a river, a river. All right. Let's find this passage down here.
It really can only be this way. So it has to be over here and watch out for the champions.
I wish I could revive these guys. Surprise me with a unique, unique frozen river. Anya
is out here somewhere. There's also, I remember there's a champion here that can be a pain in
the ass. Oh, I'm going to be careful. These vomitables are a little boy. I'm going to stay
back here. I'm going to go over there. Revive. See that ship. My man is so bad. It's just a brawl.
I don't even know who's winning. I hope it's us. Burrito turns into pure carbon. It's still a burrito.
No, I don't think so.
No, it's carbon. Yeah, because if a river freezes, it's still water.
Burrito turns into carbon, then it's carbon. It's not still a burrito. Quantum burrito. The game was,
oh, by the way, I, I know the story now. I know I, I knew it already, but I, I know, I know the whole
story. I was kind of on the right track. The shit I was saying to you guys was a joke. I didn't
really believe that. Um, but yeah, that's pretty cool. That's a pretty cool story.
That's a pretty cool story. Story of the quantum burrito. No, the story of the story of
Outer Wilds. Playing like I'm five, the Outer Wilds. No, I've read a couple of timelines.
There were some good timelines to really piece the whole thing together. Like a whole chronological
events. Easy to see that way. And I don't want to talk about anything about it because
people probably hear them might not have played it, but it's pretty good. It's pretty good.
Reenus synopsis? Yeah, kind of. Isn't that what you do? All right. Anya, where are you?
Usually right in the middle, right? Oh, that wasn't smart. It's still alive. I have way too
many healing potions. It's just like, just throw them away. I love that sound. That paladin
charge sound. It's got a good ring to it. All right, Anya, come on. What the hell? Not down here.
Pain in the ass. Fine. Outer Wilds is supposed to come to Steam this year.
Well, sooner the better. Don't get overwhelmed. A little too late. Yeah, they did kind of release
that game on Epic Games Store right when Epic Games Store was kind of becoming that
exclusivity thing, right? How long? When did it come out? Like six months ago? Seven months ago?
Is it on the Windows Store? I don't know. I don't know very many people that use the Windows Store.
It was early last year. Yeah. Games for Windows. Pog. Or what? All right. Hey,
what's the anti-pog? What is anti-pog? Is there one? I feel like the market could be super,
what's anti-pog? Resident, but no, I don't know. Resident Sleeper is like, I'm like,
this is boring. I'm falling asleep. Anti-pog would be like, what you did was not as cool
as you thought it was. Like you did something that was supposed to be exciting, but it wasn't.
Ha ha. Yeah, but I guess.
Balefish? Yeah, never mind. Balefish fills that completely. Not like this. Yeah. Yeah, they're
there. They're there. Have I played Temtem? No, I have not played Temtem. I probably will not
play Temtem. I probably will avoid Temtem. I don't have a plan to play it. Not, well,
avoid was probably the wrong word to use. I'm going to use a better one. I'm not into collecting
and fighting monsters unless they come from a seedy stone. Pretty much it. I think we're close.
Can we get a price check on Chibi Robo, please? 200. It's 200. Still, it's 200. Wait, you can
buy it on the GameStop website? Remember when Jerma used to play TF2? Pepe Hands.
Oh, no. I played it every single day. What are you talking about? TF2 waiting room. Well,
you're going to be waiting. They're there. Your appointment's not for a very long time. You'll
be waiting a very long time. I think you should probably bring some snacks and maybe a few dinners
to that waiting room. Not only dinners, like rations. And when by waiting room,
I hope you mean bunker because you're going to be there for a while. So many potions, but no
mana potions. No, I have no plan to play it on stream or anything. It's a great game. One of the
best. Do I enjoy variety too much to play what play that message, but I think it's got the gist
of it. Do I like variety too much to stick with something, pick something that I played or liked
or stay with one game? I'm not even sure it's about variety as much as it's I can't stay with
the same thing. Like I just, for example, I'm not playing Diablo two right now to like make sure my
stream has variety. This is just what I want to do. Everything you see, I mean, sure there's a lot
of recommendations on the channel and you do a lot of them, but it's not, this is not like variety
for the sake of me doing, oh, I'm going to do variety for the channel. My brain needs to be
constantly stimulated and I get bored really easily. So that's why it was a shock that I was
able to really stay with TF2 for that long. That just speaks to how good that game actually is.
Are we boring you? No, I'm talking about video games, not like talking to people.
We're getting kind of creamed here. I need mana. Where are you going? That guy just
fucked off somewhere. Hey, get back here. You're supposed to be helping this frozen Stein.
This is going to get bad. Kill frozen Stein first. Oh, the thing I wasn't standing there.
This mission is really awesome. You get a very, very special,
you get a very special item for doing this. And.
Son. That bastard.
Do I ever get a desire to go back to TF2? Um, not, not in the way that you think.
Not in the way that you think. I do miss Team Fortress 2 because a lot of people have tried
to do this too and I think have not done it as well or have failed trying. It's very specific.
It's making your characters in your game, the character classes, the people that you play as,
such interesting personality types and such truly engaging characters
that you want to play as them and you want to hear more of their stories.
People have tried to do, like, remember those shorts? I remember when the only ones that were
out were, there were three of them. And when Meet the Medic was in development for like
four years, Meet the Medic was supposed to come out in like 2009 or something. It was
a huge fucking deal when it came out. I think a lot of game companies have tried to do that
and it's just not as interesting. Like the character, the demo man character
was fucking awesome. The spy was awesome. They all had these insanely different personalities.
I mean, they're all crazy, but in different ways. I don't think there'll ever be another TF2 demo
man. I really don't. I don't think that people will try, but I don't know if it'll ever happen.
The heavy, the heavy weapons guy, just think of that. Oh, by the way, big deal. Big deal.
Oh no, not yet. Toilet. Heavy weapons guys, just characterization wise, voice acting wise,
they all had these crazy personalities. We forgot about the princess. And the thing about
the TF2 voices guys and the actors that play them, they're not big famous names in the industry.
The guy that's the demo man and the heavy weapons guy is not some heavyweight in the voice acting
world. The medic is really the only one that has an actor that was at the times. I mean,
still Robin Atkins Downs at the time in like 2007, that was a long time ago.
Thank you so much for bringing Anya back to us. This spell to increase your resistances
as a token of my thanks. It isn't much, but I hope you find it helpful.
Nathan was streaming a little while ago. Yeah, he, he streams and he's, he's around. The
characterization that he gave to that scout. I mean, when you first played as the scout,
it was just like, this guy, I love this. This is awesome. We've actually streamed together before.
Some of you guys that might, the last couple of years or the last year or two, you may not have
watched the streams, but he's been on stream like three or four times. We played Dark Souls
together one time. Yeah, we played Dark Souls three. I get permanent resistance for taking this.
Take a look. Pretty awesome. It's always there. Permanent. Let's talk to Anya. Remember when
Jeremy used to play Dark Souls? Well, remember the future where I play Elden Ring and like
collaboration streams. You should collab, you should collab. Yeah, we've talked about
collabs before. We've talked about streaming with other streamers and stuff before. It's,
I don't really do it. Very rarely is there a multiplayer stream here. It's just kind of,
I just kind of do my own thing. Organically, something might come along where it's like,
yeah, that sounds like fun. Let's do that. Bomb streams with Joel were great. Yeah,
they were a lot of fun. Nelufak has escaped to his temple where he's being a real piece of shit.
I mean, I talked, I talked to a lot of people and stuff, but I have that sort of philosophy,
that sort of philosophy of, hold on, this is actually kind of good. Ray's Skeletal Mage.
Can I finally just get rid of this fucking thing? This thing is bad. Two to Ray's Skeleton.
38, 20. Look at how bad this is. It's just because it has the two in Ray's Skeleton.
A part of the reasons why I do mostly solo stuff is because I talk a lot. I'm like, oh,
it's like, oh, look at me. I got to say this and I got to say this and I got to say, and I,
anytime there's like more than two, three, four people in a stream call or something, it's always
like, especially when you get to be about three, four plus kind of people, it's almost like you
take turns talking and you don't want to talk over somebody and somebody has something to say,
but then you don't, you have something to say, but you don't want to talk over them. And
it almost becomes like, cause, and especially if everybody's streaming at the same time,
if you have like three streamers who are all streaming at the same time, they all want to
talk. They all want to talk to their audience and engage with people and talk and try to make it
fun. And you want to, you almost become like, it's my turn to entertain my audience. No, now
it's my turn to entertain my audience. No, it's my turn to entertain my audience. It's like,
you're going a weird circle. And then when people start muting each other and muting themselves and
somebody like is talking to their chat and then it's like, Hey, you still here? Yep. I'm here.
What? Yep. And the sounds of other people talking, let's say, let's say I am mute,
I mute the stream, you know, it's just something I don't really like to do.
I love playing multiple, when it works, it works. Right. And some people love
doing content in groups and it works very, very well for them. There's like, there are at least
three or four streaming groups that stream together almost every time on this site.
And they do a great fucking job and they really connect together and they work together perfectly.
I, I kind of just like doing me, you know, I'm just me here. And that's not to say this is
the right or wrong way to do that. But, you know, you, you do the things that you know,
that you'd like to do. That's pretty much it. I can't remove this because it has two
to raise skeleton in it. I can't let this be, I can't hold this over my own head. It's only one
point. If we're losing, how many points, what would we lose? One skeleton. All right. The
skeletons suck anyways. They're dying. One to confuse, one to raise. We lose one point.
That's going on. Look at how much other stuff we get. Fire block,
mana, lightning resist. And I actually get to have poison dagger. Hey Jarvis, this is Diablo. Please
stop cheating at my game. You think the tricks or glitches are so cool, but you're going to ruin the
immersion game that I make for you. You think duping is cool. You think cheating is cool.
If not, it's not. Please stop. I'm crying. That comment just get removed. I think it just got
purged. I got to get rid of some of this stuff. What time is it? I'm going to check the time.
Okay. I still got a little bit. Still got a little bit of time. Rip that dev. Okay. Ort.
This is Tao. Oh, how many spells do I have? Can I make anything? Yes, I can. I can make this.
Diamonds like not very good. I never was a fan of the diamonds in this game.
Is all res- no, all resist eight is better. I have to sell the rest of this shit. Okay.
Still have this lightning resist jewel. I have nowhere to put it. Oh, what's my favorite PS2 game?
Sure thing. Uh, the bouncer that looks clean. You're good to go now. Okay. No, no, no. I got
to go back in. I got to go to, uh, Alice. You were about to see the thing that Blizzard had to patch
because it was so easy to farm. Did you see where I just went in? Right? See this guy right here?
Endel skin. You could just pour it in here and okay. This is like a thousand people. Hold on.
They, uh, nerfed his loot table because it was too easy just to come in here and just
kill him instantly and leave. And he dropped really, really good shit. Stop hitting me.
Damn. Killed him. I would laugh my ass off if he dropped like a Zod rune right now.
I would. I would, I would laugh my ass off. Where is he? Endel skin.
Is he already dead? I think he's already dead. These guys come back to life. Did I- wait, did
he come out? Yeah, he's dead. Uh, we're going to level up though. Take a look. At this point,
do I even give you guys choice? All right. Make sure if when you click, yes, yes, yes. Uh-huh.
I will. All right. Make sure when you click, if you're clicking down here,
if you want fire golem, make sure you click like over here. If you want revive, make sure you're
clicking like here so the bubbles can spread out. We don't have to zoom in. If you want teeth,
well, then you're just out of your mind and you're deliberately trying to ruin my video
game playthrough and I don't appreciate it. Okay. I'm going to let this play out for a little bit
because it's okay. So I have to, I have to ask for help here. There are 4,500 people watching
right now and there are 560 votes. For the love of God, please, some of you, fix this.
But third point is just throwing it in the trash. He's influencing. Well, I directly asked.
I don't know where the bubbles are going to separate here. It looks like a majority want
to go down there. 55, 55. That's 20, 20. Zoom in. I have to zoom in. Do it again.
I'm going to squish it. I have to like really squish this. Get it so you can see both. Okay.
Again, germamandering. Nobody clicked on the curse menu. If even one person had clicked,
on amplified damage, nobody clicked over there. I did. Oh, looks like we're doing another point
into fire golem. Oh, this game is so lame. Can't we have some fun? Whoa. Calling Diablo 2 lame.
What the heck? What the fuck? I'm upset about that comment. All right, let's go.
Fire golem. Another point. And pick these two. The dreamcast sucks. Laughing my ass off.
The dreamcast fucking sucks. Laughing my ass off. That's one of my favorite moments ever on stream.
Hey guys, I'm showing you this cool dreamcast. Look at all these games. This one sucks. This
one's not very good. This one's really, really crusty and really not very like kind of bad game.
Somebody just random dude in chat. The dreamcast fucking sucks. L-M-A-L. In the middle of like one
of those kind of bad games that I was trying to show. Like that person may have never even seen
the dreamcast before. It's just like, dude, this console sucks. Like, no, it doesn't. I promise.
All right, vitality. Did I get like banned from single player? What the hell was that? Here's
what's going to happen. Fire golem. That's way more damage. That's a lot of damage. Did I get
timed out? You can't even, you can't get timed out in single player. You know, it'll probably
happen. I had game paused. When I clicked back into the window, it probably clicked right here
and just, it's all right. I wasn't that far. All right, we're going to, our guy is good. 124 mana.
What a joke. Speaking of which, I'm just going to fill my sack with mana. Just
to the brim. One spell requires a full potion, so that sucks. I need a better belt too. Look at all
this bad shit that I have on. Why is the cube in your inventory? Or extra space in my inventory?
I usually put the cube here, but people were not happy about that. So I'm doing the thing that
people were saying to try. Okay, let's go. Hey, we get to kill Pindleskin again.
The scent of death. How's the fire go? I'm doing better than last time.
It's got like an AOE effect. It's all right. Um, guys, we've got, we're getting close in.
I got some friends now. We're good. Oh, I heard the ding and I was like, no way. Oh, I only have
four skeletons, but I took up the fuck. That's right. I'm sitting there going, why can I get a
fifth skeleton? I was thinking about getting a fireman tattoo. Shale. That's a pretty rare one.
That's actually not, that's pretty good. This is not, this is rare. It's not super rare. It's like
second or third tier. That's pretty good. That's like a two, uh, tier two. That's pretty good. Nice.
I'm happy about that. Okay, let's move. Neelifax temple. What the fuck do I have this? Oh yeah,
cause I have a million potions. Oh, let's store these junk. So we're trying to go down all the
way to go fight Neelifax guy that imprisoned Anya in the ice. Get a bigger belt. Oh my God.
I would, but I mean the cold resistant, the defense is just, it's really good. It's really
good. I just realized my title doesn't make any sense anymore. I thought I was going to spend way
longer on Diablo. I beat Diablo in like 45 minutes. I thought it was going to be the whole stream.
Be trying desperately to get them to die. I'm like having them refill his health for like two
hours. Well, it's still the name of the game. Yeah, that's true. It is the name of the game.
You're right. All right. Don't go too far. These nightlords demons. I want both of them.
It's not over here. See if I can quickly find this. Then we have to go to Mount Ariat and that's when
the stream turns off. I don't think I'll be able to do it, but hey, I will try. I'll give it a solid
attempt. I'd say I'd be ready. The halls of want, halls of not, whatever it's called. What is it?
What am I looking for? Halls of something. All right guys. Dead. Leveled up. Let's see. Level
33. Good. Nice. Good job. Let's get the skeleton through back. Hi. Follow me.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I forgot how big this place actually was. It's kind of huge.
New champions? No. Oh, am I getting cocky? Oh, I think I got cocky. All right. Okay. I'm okay.
Ooh, I just can run so fast. It's like almost a shame if I don't run. That champion. All right.
Pause here so we can rebuild the, uh, the team here. Okay. Let's keep going. I'm surprised I
haven't found it. I can just zoom around. I think it's up here and when it's, if I take a look.
Okay. This is a stupid idea. Really bad idea. No, I have potions. Nevermind. Pause it. Freeze it here.
Well, we're in trouble. I may have flown too close to the sun here. It's possible.
No, we're good. Am I talking about it? Fine. Yeah. Shit. I thought it was for sure it was
gonna be right here. Come on. Don't make me run all over the place. I just want to find the next
level. Yeah. I'm right. Show auto. I can't show auto. He's not here. Flying around looking for
the place to go down. I'm so glad I can run this fast. Um, maybe I should rethink my strategy
because that was pretty close. Damn. All right. Hold up here.
I need some revives. Holy shit. Angelic sickle. Three to eight. Oh, yippee. I wonder if it,
I think I have the angelic blood. Interrupt whatever your dog is doing and bring him here
for our entertainment, Jeremy. I'm not gonna do that. Jesus. I can't. There it is. All right.
Halls of Ayn. One more level. Hopefully I find it quick. Wait for me. Keep moving.
Stop. Lucky. Good. Finally. Took me long enough. Let's go kill Neelathak.
It's a lot of sapphire. That's pretty good. What if he's going to die? Yes. I love the love
that was that through. Oh, I forgot about this quest. For doing this, you get to name an item.
You get to take any item that you own. Okay. Here he is. Where is he?
It's like right here somewhere. There he is. Okay. They're all his minions. It's necromancer
versus necromancer. They're his summoned ogres. Just playing auto chess. Get in. He has corpse
explosion though. That can kill me in probably one hit. I'm not going anywhere. I'm not even
stepping over there. See? Holy fuck. He has a lot of corpses to work with. All right. He's just a
necromancer like me. Just go up there and punch him in the face. All right. Will you guys get
out of here? Stop. Fight this thing. Whoa. Kill him. All right. Let's go. Teleports are wrong.
All right. He ain't getting away now. We got this in the bag. Wait till something dies and then just
bring it back to life. He's... Come on, Vic. I know you're capable. What's happening to fireman?
Mike, get on him. Where'd he go? Get him. Get him. He's right here. Get over there, fireman. Come on.
Hill. Go get him. Just don't step on any landmines. I'll be all right. Um, there's no potions?
How are there no potions? He's gonna corpse explode dead. All right. Aye. You dick. He was an evil
man. Yes he was. I got these cool things. So now it's time to see if this stream is going to continue.
This is where we figure it out. Speaking of figuring it out. Do I have any angelic stuff?
No. So I... I just was gonna sneeze and it went into my body. That was... That sucked.
Ugh. I was like... It went backwards down into my... Into my stomach and shit. That was weird.
I was trying to. I don't have any angelic stuff, no. Sanders. Arctic. Not angelic.
Bands. Rathras. No. No. Just a little shitty normal one. Just a shitty normal one.
I do have a shield. That's good. So talk to Anya before you continue through the crystalline
passage past the glacial trail to proceed up to Mount Ariat. Is this the sword angelic? Wait.
No, no, no. Oh no. You guys confused me for a second. All right. Let's go.
Back to the glacial trail. Do I have the waypoint? I'm an idiot and didn't get it.
I bet he can't play with facecam on. Oh yeah?
You're right. Travel through the ancients way to find the ancients at the Ariat summit.
I did not get... No, I did. Thank goodness. We went the glacial trail and then we need to go to
Mount Ariat. And I'll be in the process of probably saying my goodbyes.
It was a good run. I'm gonna try. It's a good run. You look like a cop. That's the first I've ever
heard that. Glacial trail. I think I've walked by it, didn't I? We are going to put this on players
one because the ancients are going to be the thing that's going to be nearly impossible for
me to do, I think. It is very necessary. Call me lame all you want. I'm still going... I'm going to
survive. Glacial trail. Is that not it? Speed walking. Holy fuck. Now, this is the crystal.
Where is this? Ariat plateau. Nope. We need the glacial trail. You guys good in there?
You guys all right? All right. Everybody's all right. Look, we're fine. It might get lucky.
It might just be right here. Oh my fuck. Okay, guys. Help. Friends. Skeletal mages keep just
dying instantly. Warhammer. Eh, okay. How we doing? We still have a full team, right?
Glacial trail. Glacial trail. Not over here. Aw, too bad. Where is it? Down lower left?
Wait, Ariat plateau leads to glacial trail. Does it? I thought it was crystalline to glacial.
Oh. Is that true? I don't remember. I remember it being crystalline to crystal.
Because here's the frozen. Frozen river. Maybe, yeah, you're right. Fuck. Ariat plateau. But
wasn't Ariat plateau behind the glacial trail and the waypoint? I always thought that was. Diablo
to poser. Not a real wink. I know a real wink when I see one and that's not a real one. Oh my god.
I can't just run through that. Oh my god. Where's Vic? I think he's just fighting down there by
himself. Oh my. Look at this. He's just getting. Alright, I have to go. That's not happening. I'm
gonna get my team to go in there. That's not happening. Okay. There's that. Let's get fire
back and let's get mages and then go back in. Follow me. 15k away from a wink here?
Well, use those points wisely. Use them very wisely. Here we go. One, two, three, in. Can
you wink anything other than your eye? Okay. I don't. How did I read that? I don't know. I
didn't understand until after reading it. Whoa. They were just sitting here. Sestus. Alright.
Ancient's Way. Look at the glacial trail. I think I know where it is. I think it's on this side.
Wait. Is it up here? I feel like it's not up here. I really don't remember. I thought it
was glacial trail to. Hmm. Glacial trail is up top right. You mean like this way? Or you mean in
that in the. It's been a while. I don't remember. I think I can run fast. It's inside the frozen
cave there, right? Go to the ancient. Yeah. I'm trying to remember where to go.
I kind of forget. I've done this a million times, but I just don't really remember.
It's crystalline and then into glacial way, right? Crystalline to glacial and glacial to
the summit. No, it definitely is. Hold on. Yeah. I had it right the first time, didn't I? I
definitely had it right the first time. At least I thought I did. Yeah, I had it right. Alright.
Let's go. Slowly making our way to the ancients. I got the shoes. Might as well use them.
Although I want to level up one more time. So let's not run through this.
Saber. Don't die. I definitely will not die before the ancients. I do want to be level 30. I want
to be level 34 though. If you beat the ancients, you get three to five levels. So 30 pog. You get
three full levels or four full levels by doing the ancients. It's pretty pog. Look, I'm using
twitch speak. I'm using it correctly too. So at 34, this final point is really going to matter.
These final points, but we're going to potentially determine the end of this whole thing.
We can't even pog. What the fuck are we supposed to do? You can pog. It just doesn't show up. I like
reading it. I prefer to read it than to see it. I like pog. I like it. This pog champ exists,
but pog is you saying it. When you do pog champ, that's your face. That's your,
you're not saying anything. You're saying pog. A little different. Come on. Let me get to 34
before I go to the ancients. Come on. Come on. This is my face. This is not your face.
I know what your face looks like. Not that Dave. You guys remember when, um, I wanted to do that
joke where in the title of the stream, I titled the stream like Anthony Roberts, come to this stream
or like this street. I wanted to do that so bad. Dave Smith, we're waiting for you.
And imagine scrolling down that and being like, what the fuck is going on?
Oh, a unique name that it's not necessarily like gone or like Dave Smith or anything.
Omega Lol Dave. Why is the name Dave funny? Name. Probably should do it. Omega Lol Dave.
We're going. Uh huh. Drifter Cavern. No, that means it's on the other side. I really wonder
if I'm going to be able to do this. This is the last real roadblock before bail. That's not true.
List of the tormentor is the last roadblock.
There's a chest right there. I'll take it. I need revives. Good chest.
What? Ooh, I heard a skull. Why don't I hear a skull? Oh, it's down here.
Okay, don't worry. We will level up before I do the ancients. I just want to because
if you, when you go into the ancients, you get one shot. If you try to portal out,
the whole encounter resets. So you pick up, you put a portal. Although you otherwise have to run
the whole thing. Yeah. This is going to suck. It has to be down here. Remember, we'll literally
never say penis. He's too pure for this world. I've said that, like I've said that word. It's
anatomy. What? Who cares? Like guys, it's all right to say vagina. That's anatomy too, right?
Yeah. That's what doesn't matter. I don't get it. Wink already. You want to see where my gamer
face is? Like this is where I have to pay attention. Right there. Just pretend I'm on face cam.
Wait, where the hell is this? Wait, what the fuck? I need the ancients way. Wait, is it frozen
Tundra? Did I miss one? Is it frozen Tundra? Then to, I don't remember. Frozen Tundra?
And then ancients way. Yeah. Damn it. Yeah. Ancient's way. All right. Ancient's way. Let's
find it. I actually cannot just go through this. I might be able to just run to get it.
It's like right around here. Look at me. Look at how fast I am. No one will catch me. I have
65% increased speed. Good luck. Ain't nobody catching me. I could run a mile. Iron Man's
going to protect you. It's going to be all right. Although I have to be careful that I'm running a
stamina. I will not get hurt until, unless I have no stamina. Here we go. It should be right here.
Here it is right here. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Do this right. Do this right.
Do this right. Do this smart. This is where I die. This is smart. Like anyone's going to click on
curses. Where do you want to go? You've had stretching. You've had 34 opportunities to
click a curse and you haven't done it once. So trying to get me killed. It's all right.
A little late for teeth, isn't it? Apparently not to, uh, 48% of everybody watching the channel
right now. It seems like the perfect time. Vitality. Four to six damage. Four teeth.
These potions. Okay, let's go get an army. Dude, that's like 24 damage.
That's pretty, it's pretty sick. That should be enough. Actually. Yeah, that should be okay.
As long as I have like five people, it should be all right. Okay. Where we at?
Where we at guys? We good? We're good. Kill these champions. They might drop good shit.
Come on here. I'm overburnt. Ancient's Way. We are the spirits of the Nephalem.
Cool. I'm gonna have to use it again. Amulet. Should I fill the whole Ancient's Way area with
trash and do iron golem again? Because you have to activate it. What if I just drop like a hundred
weapons on the ground? I think that's the only way this is doable. Unless, I mean, Vic might be able
to handle it. Vic actually probably can do it. As long as I keep him healed. Level up too. Good.
Ow. Big Vic energy. That's right. Who is killing fire golems so hard? Who is destroying them?
This is kind of ass kicked. Icy cellar. That's not correct. That means it's over here.
Harriet Summit. I forgot. That's, okay, let me explain something very quickly.
You put that there on, if you're not playing hardcore, because portals are not allowed here,
but you can come back through the portal and walk in again. I can do this, but if this has started,
I can't use it. You have to do it in one shot. Oh my god. I didn't get any waypoints.
I didn't get any waypoints. I'd have to run the whole thing. Fuck. How did that, that was just,
that, like, two unfortunate things in a row. I could leave and just come back. Why did I use,
I was just showing people, I don't know. I thought I had like a thousand. Okay. Um, I, I know,
salutations. It ain't gonna end like that. It's a big Vic energy. I mean, at the end of the day,
at the end of the day, I have to just go for it. And I'm, okay, let me ask a question.
Am I allowed to port out? Because if I use a portal, everything resets. Am I allowed to do that?
No. I'm seeing a lot of nos. Open the fucking door. We'll do a proper poll. You see, if I'm
allowed to portal out of the Ancients, you're supposed to do it in one go. Ancients way. Watch
that stamina. All right. I just have to get up there. Just get up there. Fucking god. These
skeletons are getting beat so badly. These skeletons aren't good anymore. They used to be good.
What happened to them? They used to be so good. They can't take any punches anymore. Oh shit.
All right. This is blocked off. Chad Barbarian Ancients versus the Virgin Bone Boys.
Not that way. It's the other side. Is it? Yep. Here it is. The summit. Let's hang out right here.
Put a portal. Let's go for it. Let's get a full team. I might, I might just be overthinking this.
We might be able to do this. We might just be able to do this with a full team. It's possible.
I'll give it a try. I want a full team and I want two moon, uh, moon lords. Okay. How many we got?
Four. We got everybody. We got two moon lords. We have two something. Let's go. Let's do it.
I'm ready. You ready? Let's go. First try. Oh no, it's Bugleberry.
Focus one. Focus one. Get a moon lord. Come on. He said E3 gameplay.
Kill this one. Somebody's dead. Who's dead? They're both dead. Oh, we did it. We definitely did it.
It's over. I just did it. How many level? What level am I? 34? 35. Oh, that was a bogus. I did it.
I was not even, but yeah, I was overthinking that. Kill Bale. Let's do it. No one's going to
click on curses. You know it. Respec skills before Bale. Please. I, I can't do that. That
defeats the whole purpose of these streams. Could I just go delete everything or you guys have picked
and do a real build and kill Bale? But no, this is hardcore. Chat picks every skill and stat.
Can I beat the game on hardcore? It's important. All right, it's revive. That's three revives.
Very cool. These might be one of the, this probably only give you probably about five,
four or five more levels left in the remainder of the whole game. Chat, get bone mastery you zoomers.
Thankfully vitality is still on the brains. That's good. Okay, let's go.
Three summons. Next one is four. The world stone keep. Bale. The gates of sesharon have been close
for Eon. You will not open them now. Come on Vic. I need you down here. Well, that was easy.
World stone keep level two. We need the, we need, very important, we need the waypoint. It's going
to be a normal enemy that kills you. No, it's not. I've gotten this far. This is what hours,
it's been five hours. This is, is this the third or fourth Diablo two hardcore stream? Third,
right? The fourth is the third. So in like 14 hours, 15, 16 hours of gameplay, you think that
at this point, a greater hell spawn is going to kill me. I mean, that's field play is awesome.
More summons. Three. Good. We need the waypoint. These guys do explode, so I can't see your
concern. You're going to get too full of yourself and you're going to get cornered.
I don't know if I will. I'd like to level up once or twice though before Bale, which the
throne room should. The throne room is a EXP heaven and we get to hear the laugh. The best part of all
of act five. I thought you were one of my friends. Get out of here. I thought that guy was on my team.
Need to do a potion run here in a minute. Hey, listen, it's a login screen.
Full team. I need a mage. I don't think there's anything over here.
Bastard sword. Nope. We angry. We want teeth. Your rage is going to consume you.
Waypoint or level three? Waypoint. All right. We are now good to go. The final waypoint of the game.
Very useful if I ever want to do this again and come back and kill Bale for any reason.
So it's down bottom right. Like this way. I'm scared of list of the tormentor.
Like kill Bale music. Why? Oh, it's kill Bale music. What do you want me to play?
Oh, here we go. All right. One more level and we're at the throne room. You want to
play like the theme song and hold on. You want me to play the kill Bale theme song and have me get
muted. The apex of this whole stream series. I don't think that's a good idea.
We're going to have Diablo music. Throne room. We've probably going to level up two or three
times in the throne room. At least once. It's not this way. So what the hell am I even doing down
here? Does Mike just vibrate or am I imagining it? It probably didn't. Why fucking not? Hey,
don't pay attention to run down a hallway. What am I thinking? What are you doing?
There it is. I can see it. Ball hacks. We just need a good portal and we need to pray.
Throne of destruction. Kill Bale's minions and then kill Bale.
This is going to be fun. Win or lose. No matter. Win or lose. We made it.
10 community subs from FurtBernandes. Thank you Bert or Furt. FurtBernandes. Thanks a lot Bert.
Appreciate the subs. Thanks for the 10. All right. I need potions for this. Good potions.
Not these shitty ones. Okay. This part is uh you fight waves of enemies.
Just clear it out first. It's kind of a pain in the ass. Adventures of flying Jack like Kevin
McCloud. Let's do it. You're going to see him. He's scary looking. I have to warn you. He's
scary looking. Open my eyes. All right. I'll tell you when to open your eyes so you won't see the
scary monster. Open him now. All right. Everybody get in there. He spawns people right here. Hit it.
This is the exp heaven. Although there's only one person in the game. Me. We're good. I feel much
stronger. Good. Are you outpacing me? Am I being outleveled by my apprentice? Boys it sucks. That
was act two. Here comes act three. Counsel. Hey. Why don't we go out the back door and make some new
friends? Okay. A couple of mages. Let's go. Hey. We have a full team of friends. Remember somebody
said that fireman was bad. Um, what are they? What are they? Nuts? Back into it. Focus one.
Revive a council member. No, don't blow them up. They've made it ice. Oh God.
There's nobody to revive. How? Revive a council member. Finally. Here comes act four. I don't have
the skeletons are worthless, but they take, they take one hit of damage each. That means that seven
swings that I don't have to see or the other actually good companions don't have to see.
Okay. Let's go. I need mana. All right. See if I can get through act. So fucking dead.
Hey, at least you got to see veil. Have a good night. Everybody still have a council member. So
one, two, three. All right. Everybody's stuff in the middle. Get the council member in there.
He's the most, he's the strongest one. Get in there. Oh, kill somebody. I can revive someone.
Good. There we go. Look at these revives doing work. Okay. This is it. This is the last wave
and it's the worst one. I have three. Stay in there. Come on. Vic's dead. Vic's dead. I still
have my three, my three. Come on, kill one so I can bring one back to life. Anyone.
Nobody even has any health taken away. Get away from me. He tried your best. Um, he tried your
best. You couldn't hurt him. And now I'm going in there with no beefy minions. I said you
shouldn't be giving blizzard any, uh, was there any what? Any advertisement? Um, I've kind of
been talking shit about blizzard from five streams. I think, I think every time we've talked about
anything to do with blizzard, I've, I've made a comment about how bad of a company they are.
Blizzard north made this game. That's like a totally different company.
I'm not, I'm going to get fucking wrecked in here. Yeah. Go to river of flame. That's,
that's a good idea. I really want to kill this thing. Blizzard north. Yeah. That's a sad tale.
Blizzard north made Diablo and Diablo two. And then the entire company was liquidated
for some reason. Let me, do I have anything? Blizzard just got rid of blizzard north.
They were just like, yeah, we don't want blizzard north anymore. What is it going to get rid of them?
They used to be called condor before blizzard bought them. Yeah. And we got hell gate London.
Yeah. But what they were responsible for torchlight, weren't they? Wasn't one of them,
didn't one of them go on to one of the two or three people that made, uh,
Diablo go on to do torchlight. They just, the, the D it's like, we talked about this before.
It's like Chrono trigger. You had this perfect team and they all, from the artists, the designers
to the programmers, to the people making the engine, like that you had this group and they
all were really good. And then you split them all up and they all do their own version of the same
thing. And it's not as good as the, when you were all together doing the same thing together,
unfortunately. That's why we'll never get another Chrono trigger or a sequel because they're all
split up and they're all completely different companies in different places. So we will, you'll,
we will never get a true sequel to any of these games. Unfortunately. God, I hate video games.
That was funny. All right. I need to go to act four and revive. This is a fucking, this is a joke.
All right. Wait, I need Vic. I'm nothing without Vic. So let's revive a few people here. I think
I can actually go try to fight bail without fighting these things. See if I can get a couple
of this nights. I'm pretty sure I can just run into the gate. This nights are really good.
Oh, I got a bug. I'm on another wrist night. I'll take these three. Okay. One more this night and
I'll be good to go. Should be all right. And it didn't ogre. No, I want all ogres blowing them up.
Three ogres. Don't blow them up. I need him. My God. You fucking idiots. All right. Let's go.
I'm just going to, I got an ogre, an ogre. I have two bugs, two small bugs.
God damn it. Fuck it. Let's go. Who cares? Let's go. Whatever. I'm going in.
I'm going in. Wait, why was the portal in the middle? Why was the portal in the center
of everybody? Look at all the money I dropped. All right. Am I insane or wasn't the portal down
here? The portal was down here. When did it come up here? Oh, okay. Three. It was, wasn't it? Three
Winx redeemed. Check the VOD. You moved it. Did I? But why would I? Okay. I don't know. Would I have
been this dumb to put them? I wouldn't have put it like right in the middle. At least like,
that wouldn't have done that. You were rushing. It's because I got two maggots and I just wanted
to go in and ugh. Your deeds of valor will be remembered. You have died. Call me Lee Bones. Dead.
You cannot create or join with a dead hardcore character. That was a good run. All right. That
was, at least you got to see Vale. Take a pee break. We'll be right back. See what I'm going to do.
I, what time is it? No, actually I have to leave. Wait, it's been five and a half hours. Holy shit.
Okay. I have to go. Not immediately, but I have to leave like soonish. Uh, let's go pee. I'll be
right back. We will, we will settle. We can hang up for like another 45 minutes or so. Just about.
See what we can do in that time. I'll be right back. Let me just go pee.
Bro, I'm so late. Did he beat the huge red guy yet? I did actually. Uh, that's the last one.
I'm going in. My theory. Okay. Here's my theory with what happened right there.
I was going to try to pull them out because you don't have to kill them.
And I figured if I pull them out, I can get into the chamber where Bale was,
make a portal in the chamber, and then figure out what the hell I was going to do.
I guess, I guess I made a portal in the middle of everybody somehow. Did I like panic or something
halfway through that? I don't know. All right. Let's uh, Tommy Lee bones is level 35. He's gone.
That was a lot of fun though. I did not think I was going to get that far.
Not a chance in hell. It sounded like you were getting murdered in real life too.
Yeah. And I'm going to call it here. I might as well. Just because this stream was only going
to be about four to six hours because I have to go meet. I have to go meet friends. Some of you
guys don't know, but this is the stream where I have to say goodbye for a little while.
I will be back next week. It's probably on Friday afternoon. You will not see me for about six days.
I have a group of friends that are coming up from Boston. First time any of them have,
some of them at least have been out here. Um, first time anyone of any of them have come to visit
me in particular, except for one of them has come out once, but the most part, no.
So we're going to have some enjoyable friend time. So you will not see me again. They are here.
They knew I, you know, obviously that I wasn't going to be available till a little bit later,
but it is now later. So at 8 PM Pacific is when I need to essentially meet them.
I'm just snort cocaine. No, I do not do drugs. I do not do them. I thought we were your friends.
Yeah. But, uh, we'll do the bits. We'll hang out for a little bit. If you're taking off,
thanks for joining me these last five days. These streams have been very fun.
I've had a blast on all of them. For those of you Assura's Wrath fans that thought maybe today,
if we had time, we were going to do DLC, I was under the impression that if I didn't kill Diablo
and I just couldn't do it and I died within like two hours that we would have done it,
but there's still a lot of Xbox stuff to do. Assura's Wrath DLC will be tacked onto one of
the Xbox 360 games when we go back to it. When am I going to stream next? I'll be back on Friday.
So Friday the 7th is when I will return. Don't forget about me. Don't forget about me.
And that's going to call it tonight. Time to rewatch the Sorcery VODs. Oh, that was
some of my first streams. It was a lot of fun. As always, thanks for joining me, everybody. Let's
do the bits. Thanks for joining me. Again, a lot of people watched these Diablo 2 streams.
I'm happy about that. I'm happy that people are still interested.
This is like one of my favorite games ever. It's nice to share that with people.
Play Diablo 3? I'm not going to play Diablo 3 on stream. But thank you. I will see you all next
week. But Isaac, thanks for the 500 bits. Hey, Jeremy, I wanted to thank you again for the
laughs from last night's stream. I haven't laughed like that in a long time. Yeah. All right. Last
night's stream was very funny. When I got to the point where we were 10 hours in, 10 and a half
hours, and Iron Man did the royal flush and hit his face on the bar, I was gone. I literally was
in outer space. I was gone. It was just so stupid. I loved every second of it. Yeah. I had a lot of
fun. It's a great game. It's one of the best skating games. Glad you enjoyed it. Esquilo,
thanks for the 300 bits. Jeremy, I had a dream last night where you were my brother and I came
to visit you and Kim. It was an hour before TwitchCon and I was ready, except I had to pee.
When I got to the bathroom and zipped my pants to pee, you came in naked to take a shower.
I asked you what the fuck you were doing and why it was all see-through glass. You answered it was
Kim's idea of having a bathroom like this. And you had a massive, I had very large hands.
Weird. Thank you. Thank you for thanking people for their dreams. Hey, thanks. Thank you for your
dream. Thanks for the dream. Thanks for the 300 bits. Appreciate it. Don't eat macaroni and cheese
after 11 o'clock. Silent Serenity, thanks for 250. I once sold my soul to a guy on TF2 for a couple
of reclaimed. He emailed me a contract to sign and everything. Bulbaswag Desu, thanks for 500 bits.
I heard you looked hot today. Read about it in a Discord chat. I hope it's true, but I can't stay.
Have a good stream. Well, I don't know. You may never know if that was true or not.
50 community subs. Let's talk about it one more time. Zyxia dropped 50. Monster sub dropped
earlier. Thank you so much, Zyxia. Say it right. Say the name right. I always say people's names
wrong. I'm sorry. Say my name right. I can't. Hikikomoris Sunday. Zyxia, I can't do it. People
in chat keep calling me Morris. Wait, Hikikomoris Sunday. It's not Morris. Dude, people keep calling
me fucking Morris, man. Like, get it right. Sorry. But regardless, it was a shitload of subs. A ton.
No one's ever expected to even sub to this channel, let alone give 50 other subscriptions
to other people. Thank you. We had the shroom gave 370. Thank you, the shroom.
Oh, I thought you said now I'm developing. Now I'm getting deployed
to the Middle East. I'm just getting rid of the last few bits I have.
You all deserve so much more. I hope you see this message and understand all you've done for me and
countless others that have been here for so long. Even ones just starting to watch. I wish you the
best of luck. Take care of yourself. Thank you so much for being part of this community. If anybody
gets anything from these streams, I say it a lot, but it's true. If you get anything from it, good.
Very good. Very, very, very good. Take care of yourself. I wish you the best. I missed this.
I missed this message here. It was $50 earlier. I don't know. I must have been in the middle of
something weird. 5,000 bits from butt sniffing George. He said, Jeremy, I've been watching you
since you uploaded the TF2 video to Lepto1's channel in 2011 when I was 12. I want to say
thank you for all the content. I also wanted to embarrass you. Lepto1. We actually talked about
Lepto1 recently. Lepto1, I mean, to be completely honest, that was a pretty big reason why anybody
watched my channel when I had 200, 300 subs. I was getting maybe 500 to 1,000 views of video,
and he was getting 5,000 to 10,000 views of video. Maybe a little bit more, and it was like,
holy shit. That did a lot of good early on for the channel, which is the most important thing.
Going from one sub to 100 subs is way harder than going from 10,000 to 50,000. That initial
first thousand subs on YouTube is very, very hard to get, so it did a lot. It helped a lot.
No shit. All right, ban that guy. Hey, we got a wink. I wonder how long it's going to take
before I get really sick and tired of doing that. You know what I mean? At what point is this going
to be like, when am I going to not want to do this anymore? Like, oh, let me turn on my webcam
and wink into the camera. I wonder. I'm going to give it like 30 days and see how I feel.
But yeah, you linked my Combat Engineer Lakeside video from Lepto1's channel. I mean, it's not
really, it's not going to embarrass me. It's not because this is just like 10 years ago now.
This is almost a decade old, 10 years, a 10 year old video. Here's the link for it. I mean,
I don't really want to watch it because it's, I mean, it's 10 years old and we've watched 10
year old videos before and I'm just like, ugh, it's all right, it's good. It was okay. Another
wink? What is going on? I'm sorry, I'm already sick of doing it. How long? Took like two weeks?
It's staying though. It's not going anywhere. The worst part about this is somebody is always
going to be saving channel points for the wink. So if I ever get rid of the wink,
it's going to be really bad because somebody's going to be mad because like there's always
going to be a cycling saver for saving wink points. Anyways, thank you butt sniffing George.
Thanks for being around for a decade. Let us get the subs rolling. I'm going to bump you again.
I'm just, I'm just bumping you all day, huh? I just keep bumping you in the face.
Please don't stop the wink. I'm almost there. You almost add enough points.
How did I read that? What the fuck am I doing? Thanks all the subs. We had a lot of community
subs tonight. Appreciate it. All of you. The community subs from New Year's Eve have turned
over as you can imagine. But surprisingly enough, a ton of people that were gifted subs on that
night stayed. Thank you guys. Over 10k, not anymore. We, the channel sits at 80, 8,300 subs,
which is an absolute huge amount because you got to remember before, before New Year's Eve, it was
like 6,000. So New Year's Eve had thousands of community subs and for that many people after to
stay on. It's crazy. That's a huge retention rate for somebody staying subscribed. So I wanted to
give you an update on that because I know we've talked about a few times. Hey, we're almost at
like a, we're at like, we like, I've got 10,000 subs. I've got, I'm at 11,000 subs, but you know,
I want to make sure everyone's, I don't want you guys to think that I'm like, hey, we're almost
at 12,000. Pretty good, huh? Let's go, go, go. This was kind of an interesting piece of data.
I thought you guys might want to know. Numbers go up hyper. A thousand of your subs of mine,
give them back. I kind of can't, but no, seriously. Thanks guys. 5,000 subs was a huge milestone. I
didn't think that it would be more than that ever. And here we are. Thank you. Scam train.
Yeah, I don't have scam trains turned on. Hyper train, whatever. Potion dweller, thanks for the
250. Attention chat, save up your winks. I would like to have an ultimate wink where we all cash in
our winks one after the other in two months. Start saving your points. Let's organize and make him
wink endlessly. That would be such a, that would be such a bad stream. But if you spend your points
the way you want to spend them, if you want to spend your points, if you want to spend
your currency wherever you want, you absolutely can. Do blinks so it's two winks at once.
What do you mean, oh God. What are you talking about? I said you can use your currency for
whatever you want on, you can use your winks however. Why is everybody monkey-essing? Sorry
about that. Hey RTM, thanks for the 300 bits. Watching you play Thug yesterday, maybe remember
an old skating group me and my dad watched years ago. I ended up spending the night watching them
and some of the morning too. The group is called Fancy Lad Skateboards. When I went to look up what
they were doing now, I saw that they are now based in the Boston area. Small world, huh?
Anyways, here's a link to a member showing off some of their flatland tricks.
It says this guy's on bath salts, apparently. Hold on, let me turn this music off. It's not
like a joke video, just that's the title of the video. Matt Tomasello aka Rodney Mullen on bath
salts. This is just here. What the fuck? Okay, the cow... Jesus. The cow throwing the rock
at the crowd of people was saved here. That was when Murius was like throwing shit and breaking
stuff. All right, let's take a look. Oh, free tax, pay zero dollars to file. Pretty good trick.
Actually, this is on ice. Does it have no... There's no wheels. That board is broken in half.
What? Is this board broken or is that separated? Hold on. Is this guy a skateboarder or is he a
magician? Is this like a magic guy? These are magic tricks. He has two boards in one. He has
like a fake tear away board that turns into a real board, but all of a sudden he just does a royal
flush. What? How do you even do that? That's not even possible. Humans can't do that. Gravity
doesn't even work that way. I'll break it. Did a smaller skateboard come out of his skateboard?
What the fuck? That's so funny. Live birth. Yeah, awesome. Four heads. Nice. Nice. Oh, I could just
sit here and just eat potato chips and watch this for like the next four hours. Good commentary.
Guys, huge crunching sound. Sick. That was pretty good. Yeah, it's blowing my mind. Me and my dad
would blast through hours of these guys. I mean, this video has a million views, so it's not
surprising. It's really, really cool shit. It's surprising that people watch this stuff. Crunch joke
incoming. Link this one? Yeah, here. Wait, the original PogChamp right there is what that is.
Oh no, this video was uploaded in 2018. Never mind. Never mind. For some reason I thought this
video was from like 2005. I don't know why. That was awesome. Here, I'll link it here.
That's really cool shit. That was Matt Tomasello. Matt Tomasello. Thanks for sharing that though.
I'm probably gonna like watch those. Not tonight because I don't know. I'm not gonna have time
tonight, but music was really good. That was Artyom. Thank you, Artyom. Catboy Kubey. Thanks
for the 250. Jerma, I love the stream and I'm looking forward to that shower stream you promised
us. I don't remember doing that, but hey, Sinz. Thank you Sinz for the 300 bits. Hi, Jerma. Thank
you so much for all the kind things you said about my art during the last community content night
stream. I love to have your streams up while I work. Shout out to the lovely Discord community,
what is your favorite kind of fan art? I don't really have a favorite, but if I had to pick,
if you were like, pick now, go. No, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to influence any community
content. I like it all. I think it's all good stuff. I don't want to influence anybody's work.
I'd like to see what you come up with. There you go. But no, I love that shit. I'm glad that
that's something to do because before it was, I don't want to say the word sweeping it under the
rug, but images would come in and it would be right now the end of the stream. The stream's over.
Half the audience that was here for the stream has left and I just kind of open it and go,
oh, that's pretty, that's really good stuff. Good work. And then I close it. So having a place
where I can actually, that's the whole point. Everybody knows that's what's going to happen
and that's why they're all here. People are just, that's what we're doing today.
It's a much better idea. It's crazy how half the viewers leave and miss so much. Yeah, but
if you have, I mean, I'm not going to say you always stay, you have to stay and stay at the
post stream kind of chill discussion talk session. Some people want to watch the stream. They want to
see, oh, you're playing this or you're doing this and then you're done. All right. I'm leaving.
That's all right. Not for everybody. You know, you don't have to sit here and just watch a screen
like this and listen to me talk for like 30, 40 minutes while we go over messages and stuff.
That's fine. More than 3000, more than 3000 people still here. It's a lot of people just
are hanging out and just talking about nothing. Like I do a lot of times. I will just go off
and just start talking about anything or nothing during these things. And then of course we have
the people's donations and sub messages coming too. So it's all good. You don't, you don't have
to stay. You do, you do. And if you don't, you don't scream about nothing. Seinfeld,
swiggity swanky. Thanks to the two 50. I know you're a big guy on Twitch and very busy
because you are popular, but have you ever seen this clip of the, of the scout,
of, uh, what Nathan doing something? Would you and Jerma stream together again? I would. Absolutely.
Jerma is way bigger than me. So he's way hard to get away. Harder to get a hold of you guys.
I'm available. Jerma to get a hold of me and that you want to see a stream. I am happy to do it.
There you go. I think of a co-op is like,
got to find like the right co-op thing to do. Hey fellas, he's available. That clip is over a year
old. Oh, that hurt. That clip is a year old. He didn't wait. He didn't say this like last weekend.
This clip, wait, this clip didn't happen at like four o'clock today. I am available a year later.
He's been emailing you for years. Uh, no, I mean, if something comes up to do, uh,
I just need some co-op thing to do. Look, italics is right here over there and all the time we're
just like, you want to, we have everything we can, you have any co-op stuff we could do? And it's
just like, no, not really. SWAT4. They just think about SWAT4. Actually, I talked to Star today
about this. Star and I have been trying to play SWAT4 for five years. We actually talked about
it today that you can actually do it now. We have been trying to play this game somehow for five
years. Is there a stream that's been five years in the making? Uh, it wasn't going to be a stream.
It was going to be a video. Whether it was, uh, Star was going to be the one making it or I was,
we were going to make a video on SWAT4. Guys, this is like 2013 or 2014. First upload on the
main channel in three years now. I can't believe it. Hey, man, German, German Nathan. Oh yeah. Hey,
here's a clip. I thought this was from like a week ago or something, but co-op games are fun. But
like I said before, we already went over it, but we'll go over it one more time.
I just mainly do my own thing. Maybe like once every couple months there is a multiplayer kind
of co-op stream. Just kind of do my own thing. But that doesn't mean I'm not going to do them,
right? Me and Joel played, keep talking, nobody explodes, you know, and whatever,
whatever happens happens. We just keep going. Music is gone. We don't even need it right now.
I'm talking to you personally right now. Just once I want the rat to get the popcorn.
Not good for rats, but you're not supposed to eat it. It's supposed to eat berries and celery
or whatever rats eat. Yeah. I will use the same streamer blanket statement. Like I said before,
I love playing with people. I love streaming. For the most part, I do streams alone, unless of
course there's some big event going on where multiple people are going to be involved.
Eat an onion, eat an onion on stream. I don't think I can even eat a raw onion. It'd probably
be bad for me. That's very edgy, dude. Just me alone. Let's do my own thing. I'm alone loner.
Hey, gnarly. Thanks for the 250. I love these streams where you play a game you loved when
you were younger. They're still, they're very chill. Nice to watch you not suck at something.
Hope you do more in the future. Have a good week. Hey, thanks. Appreciate that.
Kiari, thanks for the 500 bits. A shame to see you lose right at the end, Jerma.
It was a good run. Just want to thank you. You help us all out so much by making us smile.
My grandfather passed away tonight and it helps having you stream around to ease pains like that.
Thank you for the great stream as always. I'm sorry for your loss. May he rest in peace.
Losing a family member is always very hard. I wish you the best. Thanks for hanging out.
Stick around. Stick around. What's the matter? What? You want to get out of here?
You want to get out of here? Yeah. I'm gonna get out. He wanted to come in. Now he wants to get out.
He's like, let me in. And he's like, let me out. He's like, let me in. He's like, let me out.
He must have. What? You want to leave now? He's like, just. All right. Hold on. One sec.
He wanted to go see Kim. He heard Kim. He's like, I want to be out there. Like, you're boring.
Let's go. But let's keep going. Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 500 bits. Enjoy your time off.
See you Friday. See you Friday. I will be back. We have a lot of stuff to play. I will return.
You will see me next week. You died to Bale. Well, I didn't die to Bale. I died to Bale's minions.
We didn't even get to see one move from Bale, but that's okay.
Further than I thought I was going to get. Merry GR. Thanks for the 250. Jerma, I had a
dream the other day where you were doing some Little Mermaid parody. Nothing really to the
dream, but I woke up crying in a weird fit of feeling the love from you and this whole
community. Thanks for all the joy. Feeling the love from you in this community and this community.
Why would I be doing a Little Mermaid parody? Do I have just like phantoms that just go around
at night and just cause mischief? Isn't this some folklore monster or creature or something that
does that? What is that called? It's called something. This is these little like phantom
goblins that mess with you and fuck with your dreams and stuff. What are they called? Your
sleep paralysis demon. Well, no, I don't think. Okay. If your sleep paralysis demon is a parody
of the Little Mermaid playing out in your room, that would be a very strange sleep paralysis
demon. It's just lying back on your bed, just not being able to move. It's just like
get me the fuck out of here. Peaceful Haley. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jeremy. Hope you have
fun with your friends this week. Thank you. I just want to say the other day during community
content night when you asked how I built your name in Minecraft, all he did was build up one
block at a time, made a bridge up top and just built the letters on that, then went back and
removed the bridge one block at a time. It took me a while and I wonder if there was an easy way
to have done that. That's pretty pog. That's 200 IQ, you know. Have a good night to you as well.
Thank you. That's coming back probably sometime in the middle of March, I would think. We'll see.
Still being worked on. Got something special for it. That's why. It's not just going to be what you
think it is. Whole of one zombie thanks to the 250. I've had two dreams that you were in.
The first, I was your security at some red carpet event. That's pretty cool. The other,
I met Italics Kim and yourself, had an awkward dinner. Italics was super friendly, but you were
not. Then you drove me to the airport. Why does everyone dream of you? I don't know. I don't know.
You're a dick. Why are you a dick in dreams? I don't know. That's not me. Quantum Jerma, yeah.
Nothing like that. Keith King Crimson thanks to the 250. What if that guy who kept spamming
Jerma just like backpack a few months ago could see the future? I was trying to talk about the
straps of your boomer harness. We, I haven't said that out loud in a long time. Was that actually
just somebody from this community just writing a sentence that made no sense or is that an actual
meme that somebody, it just was, I'm going to write a nonsense statement. It means nothing.
It's not a meme from anything. It's not a reference to anything. It's just somebody wrote that.
That was it. I'm here. It was just one guy. He did it for like three streams. Hey, look at that.
A wink. Could you believe it? People have been saving up. All right, we only have a few more
bits to do. He smiled at me. He smiled at me. A poop killer thanks to the 500 bits.
Freezy burns thanks to the 300 bits. Jerma gonna miss you for the next week. Always a pleasure
staying up late to watch your streams. Don't forget about me. Don't worry. I won't forget about
you guys. I hope you don't forget about me. Come back. It's going to be empty. It's going to be an
empty town here. I've been away for much longer than this. You guys are still here. So
we'll see you when I get back. X war two. Thanks for the 250. I forgot you. I forgot you had to
use at least 250 bits and that is a newish rule over the last probably six, seven months or so,
just about just about maybe a little bit longer than that. But still, it's still a fairly new
rule in the grand scheme of things. Just want to say that I'm sad I missed all the streams this week
but this new blood has been getting caught up on VODs. There's just too many old games you had
gone through almost caught up. Expect to see more of me in the future. This new blood's here to stay.
I've only been falling for two weeks. Just finished black and white. Hopefully you'll
play the sequel soon. Well, welcome. Welcome to the stream. Welcome to the channel.
If you want to really catch up totally, you've got seven and a half years of YouTube videos
and streams to watch. It'll take you, I mean it might take you maybe two or three straight months
every day, 24 hours straight to watch them all. Maybe like four months straight. You just got to
catch up. Skip season three. So I would skip season two. Season three was really good.
Start with the Shwee videos. This used to be a Maynay stream and that's an old one.
Now welcome. Thanks for joining. Thanks for following. Especially thanks for giving me money
because that's not necessary but people do all the fucking time. So thank you.
Jay Bum Bum. Jay Bum Bum 7723. You got to get it right.
Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey Jerma, you know when you're watching a horror movie and start
screaming at the screen because the protagonist is doing something dumb and you know exactly
what's going to happen. That's what watching the outer wild stream was like. Watching you try to
find the entrance to the vessel was like watching a fly in your house try to get out through the
window. All jokes aside, I love your streams and the outer wild streams was amazing. Keep up the
good work. Somebody wrote, that's called backseat gaming. Now that game was really fun. It was very
interesting too. It wasn't that bad. I, all right. I feel like I figured out a lot of the stuff in
that game. I, I was putting the, I took my time. I was trying to do stuff. I figured out the last
puzzle on my own. Right? I did okay. I didn't do fantastic. It did all right. Not the worst Tony
Hawk player that's ever by the way. I'm still on that. We're going to YouTube the end of the game.
Yeah, but we don't talk about that. That was, I was just, I was cranky. I didn't have my fucking
go-go applesauce. Sun joke got old. It's the new, it's the new bear trap thing from Darkwood. I can't
tell you it was fake because nobody would believe me anyways. It doesn't matter.
I can't like tell you that it was real because it was like, no, there's no way it was. Yeah,
whatever. And finally, silent serenity. Thanks for the 250. You should upload another update
video to the main channel just as a joke. No, that's just like, and that's just like,
it's like antagonizing somebody. I don't want to do that. Did you buy Super Frog 2? I don't even,
I didn't, no, I didn't. I'll have to get it. Somebody said, why, why does italics not want
to do co-op streams? No, no, that's not, that's not what I meant. I just said there's not a whole
lot of co-op games to play that we really want to do. There's really only like two.
Swat's one of them. We'll probably all just play it. I think it's like, you can have like up to
three or four players in one of those games, can't you? Try to get all the boys together.
Yeah, you can squat four, you can have like four players. The boys. Let's get the boys
to get, let's get the boys back. Hot Dog Chokeslam just gave 300 bits at the very end.
Uh, they don't say it, just Jerma Hart. Thank you Hot Dog Chokeslam. And that is it. I will see you
all in a week. I've got to get going. I have to meet up with friends. Have a wonderful rest
of your night. Have a wonderful week. See you guys soon. Much love to you. Take care of yourselves.
Good night.