We're in Sunnydale, California.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the first ever
Germa Rumble Live Action.
You know how it works.
20 contestants enter the ring.
Every 60 seconds, another competitor is going to come in.
And if you get thrown out of the ring,
you're out.
Last man standing wins, getting all the glory.
My name is Germa985.
I will be the host of the festivities tonight.
Thank you for joining us.
The whole event, by the way, is sponsored by Fruit.
Eat it up.
So let's begin the rumble.
Thank you again to our sponsor, Fruit,
for making this all possible, and for giving us that wonderful
Fruit table for our contestants to snack on.
And speaking of contestants, here comes the
first contestant.
The Disco Diaper.
Making his first ever appearance in a Germa
Wrestling event, as he does his patented
Definitely Not Disco.
Point to the left and point to the right dance.
And wow, listen to that crowd.
They are really behind him right now, and can you really
blame them? This guy bleeds charisma.
Former tap dance artist, former dance
instructor, so he's got it all.
He's got everything you could possibly want in a
competitor.
As he finishes up his entrance, we have the
second competitor coming in, number two.
This is Jay Buffay.
AKA The Wine Guy.
Germa's Grand Theft Auto character.
And look, just smashing a glass.
This is somebody I don't want to be in the ring with.
He is dangerous, he's unpredictable,
and he is incredibly strong.
And with that, we're going to get started here.
Get ready to ring that bell.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the first
Hey! He didn't even ring the bell.
That was disgusting.
That was absolutely deplorable behavior.
Inexcusable. What's he have to say for himself?
He's a shit character.
He's calling him a shit character.
And you know, I will have to agree with Jay Buffay here.
He is a shit character.
But that is no excuse for that type of behavior.
We haven't even started the rumble.
And it pains me that our first
fruit, eaten up on the replay, is gonna
have to be of this situation.
Let's break it down here.
Jay Buffay gets into the ring and sneakily comes
behind the Disco Diaper, who is just trying
to have some fun with the crowd and clocks him
right in the back of the skull, hitting him so hard
that he punched all the blood out of the
front of his face, something that I didn't think
was even possible until tonight.
As Jay Buffay is
just taunting and gloating, causing
and he just kicked the Disco Diaper while he was down.
What a disgusting, pathetic person.
And he's doing a butt sumo drop on him now.
As the next contestant is coming.
What is this music? This music is terrible.
Did I pick this music?
Backstage
might potentially be on fire.
I just want to make that very clear. Jerma seems to be pretty
upset about something. And he's here
the three time Jerma Wrestling Federation
Champion is coming in at number three.
We are so excited to have him here. He is a
top seed. Staring down
Jay Buffay. This is an interesting
composition. You have master and
creator. And I think we're finally
going to get to see some wrestling here in the
first ever Jerma Rumble live action.
Jerma? Jerma's
looking to maybe do a test of strength here with Jay
Buffay. They're going to do it. He's got his
right hand here. Jerma is grasping
with his left hand now, showing some
strength. He did mention
Jerma made multiple tweets talking about how
he was going back to the gym. He was getting
stronger. He was going to get back into shape.
And it looks like that is absolutely
not the case. Because at this point
he looks like a Pelican Jerry Seinfeld.
As wow he gets pushed back by Jay
Buffay. The strength of Jay. Just tossing
him into those ropes into the corner.
Jerma is yelling into the
audience. I'm not sure what that was for.
I think he saw something he didn't like while he just
barrels himself out of the corner. And they're back
in the center of the ring.
Really wish somebody would win this.
As Jay Buffay goes down
on his back. It seems Jerma has the upper hand
now. Can he potentially?
Nope. No. He's going to go on his back.
You know, you could let go of each other's hands.
What a jumping jack there by Jerma. As he gets
back on his feet. And you heard the
buzzer. That means someone else is going to be coming
in here to crowd the ring up. At number
four. The most acclaimed
Demon Slayer of all time.
Carl Griffinstein.
From Castle Griffinstein.
Looking very regal.
Wearing his knightly drape.
And jeans.
And blue, regular blue sneakers.
He comes into the ring and gets right
in there. He's going right to the disco
diaper. I'm not sure what he's doing. He still has
his giant spectral long blade.
Saying some type of prayer.
While Jerma gets punched. Two punches. Three punches.
Wow. He goes right to the gut. Right in Jerma's
big fat stomach. That's a big target for him.
Jesus. He just
stabbed him. He just mercy killed
the disco diaper. He's still unconscious.
Who's coming out?
It's Burger Boy. Why is Burger Boy
out here right now? He's supposed to wait another 30 seconds
before he can come in. I didn't see a countdown.
But big double clothesline off the top
rope. Nonetheless, Burger Boy
currently in retirement
has come out of retirement to be part of
Germarubble live. Big elbow drop
onto Jerma. He is fired up
and so is this crowd. Following it up
with a drop kick. And let's take another look
at that. The fruit eat it up on the replay.
Burger Boy on the top ropes. Jerma and Jay
still holding hands. One of them could
have let go. But neither decided
to. And it led to a vicious
double clothesline off the top rope. Speaking of clothesline
Jerma gets Carl Griffinstein with one.
And not very much real estate
in this ring for anyone
to move around.
And it's gonna get much, much
worse. Five competitors
in the ring were about to add a
sixth. And here
we go.
Waiting in the wings backstage at number six
is Glueman.
Gabe the Glueman
Degrosie. The fourth
appearance in Germarubble history.
The original shit character.
And the original superhero.
He's here to prove once and for all
that he can take on any piece of shit
in this ring. And we're gonna see it right now.
Everyone's scared of him. Carl Griffinstein's gonna take
a punch. Jay Buffay's gonna take a punch.
Jerma's gonna get knocked down. Burger Boy's gonna get knocked down.
Glueman has cleared this
ring. Just simply untouchable.
Jerma gets another one. Jay Buffay another
one. And Jerma's back up immediately.
I think he bounced off the ropes. He's getting
really close. One punch. They're trading back
and forth. Glueman and Jerma. Glueman
and Jerma. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. He's got Jerma by the
neck. Getting really close to those ropes.
Jerma's gonna.
Through the table. Over the
top ropes. Through the table. Jerma
has been eliminated. The first
elimination of Germarubble live.
Being taunted.
A very, very
strong appearance. Gabe the Glueman
Degrosie. And
not sure.
Not sure what we're watching right now but that was terrible wrestling.
Anyways Jay Buffay seems
to be sweating through his shirt. Look at him.
It's almost like he's wearing a different colored
suit. Wait a minute. Dangerous place to be.
He's gone. That's
a second elimination from Gabe the Glueman.
Capitalizing on an
extremely costly mistake.
And now we've only got four people
in the ring. We've got two or three
exhausted wrestlers while Glueman
has plenty of vitality just coming in.
Burger Boy going off the ropes.
Into a rock bottom. Beautiful rock
bottom. That looked like it actually
hurt. And that was
a terrible snap there. But here comes number
seven. The most iconic video
game character of all time. You've
heard me gush about him. You've heard me talk about him.
It's Pac-Man. The most
beloved person in all of
gaming history. And as I
watch his entrance I'm reminded of all the wonderful
times I had playing Pac-Mania.
I don't think he knows where
he's going. I think he's having
somebody had to come out here and try to tell him where to go. I don't think he knows where
to go. He needs to get
in the ring. He's not getting
in the ring. Pac-Man has decided
not to get in the ring. I have no idea
where he's going.
I think it looks like he's leaving the arena.
As we come back to the ring, big sweet
chin music by Glueman who is just
dominating the opponents right now.
Oh, he's doing his patented move. That's called
a sword slash. And
just want to bring up real quick. Jerma
is still on the ground out here.
He's just gonna leave me out there?
That's pretty messed up. Somebody should probably
come and get me. But Bergeboy now
on the back of Glueman doing a reverse
choke. Glueman has seemed to lost
a little bit of steam here. Bergeboy
taking the advantage doing some submission moves
and really working that leg
into the knee area on
Glueman who now seems to be in a little
bit of trouble. Can't seem to get his bearings
up while Carl Griffenstein now going for a right hand
onto Bergeboy gets thrown
back into the corner
where he has spent a lot of time
in this rumble while Glueman really connecting those
sword slashes. You can just feel the impact
when he connects with those sword slashes.
And Bergeboy now trying to go for a close line
no one gets rock bottomed again.
And here comes number eight.
The ultimate bag of shit.
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand
for some...
He just threw a bottle into the crowd. He was trying
to hit somebody with a fucking bottle.
By the way, that's not our belt.
I have no idea where he got that. It's not ours.
But anyways, here's Sonic the Hedgehog
coming into the ring for the fourth time
in German rumble history. Really going real fast.
You see how fast he's going. Just
blazing up those stairs at Sonic's speed
as the character's title suggests
that he's getting in the ring. Welcome Sonic
the Hedgehog as Glueman is
choking Bergeboy with his cape
in the corner while Carl Griffenstein...what is he doing?
Sonic the Hedgehog's charging up a move.
Oh, a devastating
Sonic dash. His signature
move. And it's a remarkable
feat that he didn't lose the cigarette
hanging out of his mouth. I can't believe
he did that. What a true
testament to his ability to do
things like that. And I don't even know what the fuck
I was just saying. But ladies and gentlemen, now Carl
Griffenstein is coming over and punching
Bergeboy with Sonic.
You'd think that they would want to team up on Sonic as he just
got in, but apparently not. They're both
working on Bergeboy as...and no, no,
Sonic the Hedgehog now throwing Carl Griffenstein
in the corner and is
going to do absolutely nothing to him.
Well, I think this is a good enough time to do one of our
two legally required advertisements.
So let's check out some fruit. Fruit.
Not just a healthy snack,
but also very cheap and affordable.
Go to your local grocery store and buy it by
weight. You can do it with apples, you can
do it with bananas, or you can even juice some oranges
with your son. Fruit.
Eat it up. As we get
back to the action here and Bergeboy is in trouble. Bergeboy gets
dumped over the top ropes. No! Just
barely does not get eliminated. He held
on for dear life. Thank God we got back
in time, as now he's trying to get himself
over the ropes where Glooman now gets a right punch
allowing Bergeboy an opportunity to
gracefully get over the top ropes again
and find his way back into the ring.
Almost eliminated as Glooman
big right hand into Bergeboy's face.
That really happened.
Let's get a replay. That's not a
joke. That actually happened. He really punched
him right in his nose. Take a look at the fruit.
Eat it up in the replay.
Punched him right in the face in real life.
I don't think I've mentioned this yet, but
don't fucking do this at home. Don't try this.
Fuck. This knocked over my fucking drink.
Anyways, we got Glooman
has got Bergeboy in a
pedigree, it seems. He's got him
lifting him up in the air. No, he can't seem
to lift him. He pushes him into the corner.
Bergeboy now is trying to get him under the top ropes.
We're gonna see a big move here.
Potentially a huge slam.
Well, at number nine, we got a new contestant coming in.
This is a fan favorite.
This is none other than Dick Dastardly
Richard from the rat movies.
He is a criminal. He is an
outlaw. And he's also a master
of taekwondo. As you see him
showing off his moves there for the
cameras getting into the ring for the second time
in German Rumble history. Getting up behind Sonic the Hedgehog
throwing him down to the ground.
Sonic the Hedgehog wasn't really prepared for that
while we have him. What are
these two doing? This is just
awful. This is the worst wrestling
I've ever seen in my life. And you got Carl
unconscious in the corner
doing nothing, just sitting there, while
Dick Richards is kicking the shit out of Sonic the Hedgehog.
I don't know what to look at. I'm not sure what's
worse to talk about. We are getting
a maybe three percent
effort performance from these two.
I would appreciate like five percent
effort. And they're dancing now.
They're dancing. That's fantastic.
Well, we cut to Dick Richards adjusting his mask
and kicking Sonic, while Glooman now
getting punches in the back and he's going over the top
ropes. Are you serious?
Well, Sonic is on the other side as well
and Dick Richards is gonna be going for a
slide tackle, knocking Sonic
the Hedgehog out. He is eliminated.
That is it. See you later, Sonic the Hedgehog.
You are
gone. As we cut
back into the ring and we see Glooman now is in trouble.
Burger Boy does the same slide tackle
and eliminates Glooman.
Glooman is out. He is eliminated.
He was dicking around too much
and got too gassed and exhausted
and he is gone. It's too
bad. Maybe next year, Glooman,
when you don't look like such a fucking ripped up
sock as we get back to the ring.
Burger Boy riling the crowd up a little bit
here, trying to get some energy
into the arena.
Getting the
boo, Dick Dastardly Richard.
Wow, it seems to
go and he gets a knee in his stomach for his troubles.
Got under Dick Richards skin there.
You don't want to do that. He'll get you with that
clothesline, a devastating one. I'm sure
he can see real fine through that mask.
As we have the next contestant.
If I could please have your
attention. For the
first time ever.
Someone in the audience
will be the next contestant
in the Dremel Rumble. So
if you could please look under your
seat and if you have number A14
you are the next
contestant in the Dremel
Rumble. What a true
honor that is. Wow.
What lucky audience member
is going to be the next
contestant in our sold out
crowd.
There he is ladies and gentlemen.
The audience member.
Rounding us out at number 10.
We are at the halfway point of Dremel Rumble
live. As he gets into the ring
rips off his shirt. He's going up against
two top seeded competitors.
How can a regular fucking guy
deal with these two?
That's a question we need to get answered.
While the Burger Boy gets an opportunity here. Gets a left handed
swing slapper onto Dick Dastardly
Richard. And no he gets reversed.
Going into the ropes and Burger Boy is
That was the worst elimination
in the whole rumble. So he's out. Burger Boy
is eliminated. Which leaves us with
Carl Griffinstein, Dick Dastardly Richard and the
audience member who went for
a sneak attack but forgot to do the attack
part of the sneak. And now they're doing a test
of strength. This is the second test of strength
we've seen so far in this rumble.
Remember guys. The test of strength
is also defined as extreme
filler for untrained
unprofessional losers.
What's going on? More bullshit?
Really? There's no competitor
that's coming out right now. There's no new contestant.
Wait a minute.
Oh Jesus. No, no, no, no,
no, no. What's he doing here?
That's
Demon Lord Zaraxas.
He's not supposed to be here.
He's very upset.
I'm not sure what to say.
Oh shit, he's looking for me.
Oh no, he's not.
Whoa! He just threw it!
He just threw a shitty CG
fireball at Jerma and he's burning.
Jerma is burning alive right now.
This is insanity.
What's he doing?
No, no, no, no.
He's...oh God!
He's casting a giant spell.
We're in deep shit.
Oh God. I can't even...
It's hard for me to even talk. Dick Richard
just went over the top rope.
No, no, no. This is it.
He's gonna kill us all. This is the end.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
That's the apple.
Ladies and gentlemen, the apple has come to
rescue the rumble. Thank
goodness for the apple.
And speaking of apples, cool and crisp
with a refreshing crunch. It's no
wonder it's the doctor's favorite. At just
95 calories, it's the guilt-free
party fruit. Invite some friends
over or just enjoy one in your
home. Apples, nature's
candy. And that's gonna
bring us to a...
Okay, alright.
Look, there's another competitor coming in right now.
You can stop booing.
Did someone ask for an egg?
Because it's the egg.
Fun trivia for you here. This is
only the second video the egg has ever
been in. You've got to go back five
years for the last one.
So thank you for the dedication here, egg,
making your appearance after five years
missing in action. As he gets
up to the ring, the crowd really loves him. People
in the ring not so much. He's sort of getting
laughed at by the audience member. I wouldn't
do that if I were you, as Carl Gryffenstein
is standing up and...
He's
leaving the ring. He just bumped into
the egg. The egg didn't even try to get out of the way.
The egg has been eliminated.
And Carl Gryffenstein has been eliminated.
What the fuck is going on?
I don't know.
But nonetheless, we have a
wrestling event to get back to. That's right, this is still
a wrestling event.
I would like to get back to doing that.
As the EMT, our medical
professional on staff, is going to try
to use his skills to
salvage what he can of the egg.
And hopefully we see a swift full recovery
of the egg. But
it looks pretty dire. It also looks pretty
dire for Jerma as well.
Looks like he may have at least one broken bone
here, as the EMT is
going to pick him up and get him on that gurney.
If we could get a small round of applause for these
two, they put their heart and soul into
this event. Both of them will be in our
prayers tonight for sure.
So we are at an impasse.
Because there's currently only one person in the
ring. Number 12 was supposed to be
the apple, but we know what happened there.
So number 12 is going to have to be this guy.
Or technically 13.
Backstage, somebody's going to have to push him in the right direction.
I know this is very short notice, but we do
appreciate it. You're probably not prepared for this.
You are. You are very prepared
for this. Wearing a bunsy under your EMT
uniform. That's a little strange.
I'm not going to lie. But that allows us
to put a real countdown on the screen.
He filled the spot. Thank you
for filling it. Well, we do a quick
sort of cut over here to see our new custodian
here. That's Custodio Daniel.
Doing a great job cleaning up the mess
of that catastrophe of situations that
just happened. While number 14 is
on its way, this is going to be a popular
one. From Overwatch,
please welcome
Winston.
A real hero. An accomplished
scientist. And currently Jerma's
favorite character in the game.
As he gets in the ring here, not going to waste any time here.
Big right hand onto the audience member.
And another right hand onto the EMT.
Listen to this crowd as he goes back to the
audience member. Back and forth between the two
with more right hands. Absolutely
stunning work by Winston.
We are just graced by his presence
here. Currently trying to get a new
Overwatch team together. I'm not sure
what he's doing here. He may, in fact,
be looking at this roster
of 20 to see if anybody in the JWF
can qualify to be on Overwatch.
Ooh, as he takes a left-handed
swiveling elbow by the audience member.
And he dazed him a little bit. He gets a right hand
by the EMT into
another right hand.
Wow, and what's he going to do here? Ooh, a right
hand. Hmm.
You know, I wonder if anybody in this ring can do
something else besides a right-handed punch.
As they are now
squaring up against each other. What's going to happen here?
Right hand. Oh, I wonder.
Right hand into another big
right hand. Wow.
Really exciting stuff. Another exciting
right hand. Are we potentially going to see
an- Ooh, a right kick!
A right kick, ladies and gentlemen. Did you
see that? I can't believe it. He actually
kicked him with his right leg into-
Wait a minute. I think he's got his ultimate!
Jesus!
Ooh! Ooh!
That did not sound good.
That's a noise that I don't want to hear
again. Oh, boy.
Can we get a look at him? Make sure he's alright.
Is that- Oh, God!
Oh!
Okay. Well, we have a new contestant
coming, and hopefully the EMT is going to be alright.
But we do have a show to do, so we're going to have
to move on. Hailing from
Deadwood, South Dakota.
A real rootin' tootin' cowboy.
The two-person horse joke.
Currently seated at 19
of 20. For
pretty obvious reasons. As they get into
the ring here. If they even can
get into the ring. I'm not sure.
No?
They got it. They're doing it. They're doing it.
They got it. The two-person horse
joke is now in the ring. A very,
very strange competitor indeed.
And it looks like- A big front
kick there! And a big back kick!
Big back kick as well, by the
two-person horse. They seem to have
this flawless strategy of defense
and offense at the same time.
What are you supposed to do against this?
They're just going to trample around the ring like this. There's no
approach. And I'm actually getting word
we're going to be going backstage to see the EMT
is doing some type of self
procedure to himself. I'm not sure
if that's some type of saline solution, or if
that's something else entirely, but hopefully he's going to be alright.
He's okay.
Okay, good. We got the confirmation
from the EMT. He's going to be just fine.
So no worrying about that.
While the two-person horse is just trampling
the audience member and making his way over to Winston.
Trampling Winston as well. Double trample!
Both the front and the back are involved
with that. Digging those hooves down
deep into the chest of both these
two in the ground.
As we introduce number sixteen.
It just wouldn't
be a rumble without at least one, right?
We have to have at least one.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's 788 to be exact.
Flexing for the cameras. Showing off his strength.
That he's ready to get in the rumble.
And ready to win the rumble.
Which is definitely not going to happen. I can guarantee a
Bjerg will never win a gerber rumble.
A Bjerg can barely get up in the morning and brush his teeth.
Let alone win a fight.
Wait a minute. He's having some trouble
here.
He's yelling to somebody backstage. He's not even in the ring yet.
That's another Bjerg.
Guys, you can't
tag in mid rumble.
I don't think they understand that.
As the two person horse is now doing
his finishing move. The rootin tootin
tornado. Getting Winston
multiple times with the same move.
Absolutely devastating.
All these guys did is just change clothes.
Like I wasn't going to notice.
But you know what? I don't even give a shit at this point.
Get the ass 788 in here. Get him in the ring.
And he instantly gets kicked by the two person horse.
Who is just circling the
ring. Kicking everybody.
And look at him now. Just taunting and reveling in the fact
that nobody can touch him. He's so confident.
He knows him. Wait a minute.
Looks like the three of them are going to get together and
potentially work something out here.
The two person horse is not even paying attention.
And here we go. They're going to get behind him.
And really slowly and badly actingly
push him over to those ropes.
Really shoving him through there. They're wedging
his head in between those ropes. But will it be
enough force to push him all the way
through? And it looks like they got him.
Wait.
Hold on a second. They think they eliminated
him. No. The bottom half is still
in the ring. They need to turn around.
Triple clothesline.
And listen to that.
A completely revitalized
two person horse. Let's take a look at that again.
He slips out of the back while
they're eliminating the front half. They didn't
even know. And they got a triple clothesline
for their efforts. That's what
you get for not paying attention.
So very interesting development
here. As it looks like the bia
is going to be going for
a big suplex onto Winston.
Ladies and gentlemen, that
is the first wrestling move in
almost nine minutes.
While the bottom half of the two person horse
is currently choking in a sleeper
hold, the audience member
who just barely broke out of that
as number 17 is going to make their entrance
I was promised a show with this
one. Please welcome
all the way from the whimsical world
of Wimbledon, the magician.
Me and him actually talked
backstage before the event.
Ooh, that was flashy.
He promised me we were going to see a lot
of great magic tricks. And he was going to quote
dazzle the entire audience.
So I have no idea what that
means. But hopefully we get to see some great
family friendly magic tricks from the magician.
Welcome. As he
is kind of just sitting on the turnbuckle.
No one's really paying attention to him.
What are those? Are those gloves?
Why is he putting on gloves?
I have no idea why did the hat
comes off though. And that was kind
of cool looking. I'm not going to lie.
Wow.
That was awesome.
What is that?
What did he just do?
He pulled his brain off. That's what he did.
Oh Jesus. Okay.
Whose heart is that?
I didn't know he was going to do this.
I thought he told me he was going to do magic tricks.
Organs out of a hat. Oh boy.
What's he doing? I don't know. And why are these
two just missing clotheslines?
Was that Pacman?
Whose is that?
I have no idea. But Pacman is
now getting into the ring. And a very large
portion of our audience is rioting.
He thinks this is hilarious.
Well Pacman is just looking around the ring.
I'm not sure what he's doing. But now he's got his
eyes set on the magician. He's on the ropes.
Easily the magician
is out. And
Pacman I believe just
wanted his seat. That was the only
motivation behind it. As we get back into
the ring and Pacman now is going to get picked up
on a powerbomb. No. Hurricane Rana.
What a beautifully
crafted Hurricane Rana that was. I forget
sometimes Pacman just accidentally
does things right.
As you see he's missing punches at
no one now. And now he
lost his shoe. As
Winston is going to grab the bottom half of the two person horse
and drag him into the middle of the ring.
Potentially go for a submission away
from Pacman. Getting underneath
no it's going to be a DDT.
Also
by the way I'm getting word right now that
we have some unfortunate news to report.
Backstage the EMT has died.
So the bottom half of the two person
horse gets thrown into the corner and Pacman
is kind of doing his own thing. As
number eighteen is on the
way. And I've just got
to say it's time to get in the
spirit. It's time to get into
the mood. Merry
Christmas and welcome
the Christmas tree.
I kind of want this video to be watchable
year round. So
you know you can come back and watch this on
Christmas. You know what I mean?
But anyways the Christmas tree
making his rumble debut. Dolan
literally falls into the ring.
May have just been able to see his dick.
I truly hope not. I'm
not sure why he's not wearing pants. But
he's in the ring nonetheless the Christmas tree.
As he's going to grab Pacman here.
He's got Pacman in the air. He's going to do deck the halls.
That's deck the halls. The devastating
move. He does it to Pacman. The first
move he does is his finisher. That is
impressive from the Christmas tree.
As he takes off one of his presents. Throws the present at Pacman.
Pacman's a little bit shooken up still from
that devastating deck the halls. And a right handed
punch right in his mouth. While
Winston is being pummeled away in the corner
by the bottom half of the two person horse. And now
Pacman they're doing a punch train. This is
ridiculous. Pacman just got behind him.
And wait a second. Oh speaking
of finishing moves. Here comes Pacman's signature
move. The push. There he goes.
He's got two. He's going for three.
No he gets caught. He's going to get thrown over the ropes.
Oh he just barely hangs on.
Pacman is still in this
rumble. And can you hear that crowd? They
want him to win. And you know what?
So do I.
Shit.
So coming in number
19 after that tragic
self elimination
is going to be
Well we were just in a pizza box.
So I have no idea.
I think we're outside.
This looks like a junkyard.
So I mean we're going to cut back to the ring.
The two person horse now is getting its tail pulled.
Seems to be a working strategy.
Now the Christmas tree is going to help Winston.
I think they finally found a weakness.
As he rolls
onto the ground. Pulling that
tail must have been extremely painful
while Winston and the Christmas tree.
Oh big left hand there by the Christmas tree.
Not sure who's going to make a move here. They're both kind
of reluctant. Oh a little right handed jab.
Must have. Oh!
A low blow.
Wow. That was resorting to some
terrible terrible things. As we are back
on this camera now. Whatever this happens to be
is in the arena now.
Climbing up on the steps.
Currently in the ring. This
is number 19 by the way.
Still unsure of what it is.
I can't really see from over here. But I
do know that whatever it is, is causing
some type of problem in the ring. Everyone's
kind of walking around scared of it.
Nobody in the ring seems to know what to do
with whatever this thing is. The Christmas tree
now kind of peering at it. Looks like
he's going to potentially stomp on it. Oh!
It caught his foot!
It's a giant rat! That's a giant rat!
I'm not sure how I didn't see that before.
I must be having vision problems. Because
I'm pretty close. But the Christmas tree now
everyone's running away from it. That's not a good
place to be on the other side of the ropes. Wait
the giant rat is biting his leg. Just gnawing
at him. And the Christmas tree
is re- Shit! I just bit my tongue!
You just made me bite my tongue!
Ow! Here's the giant
rat. Christmas tree has been eliminated
cut down by the giant
rat who seems to be wanting to
make friends with the bottom half of the two-person
horse. What the hell was that?
Why would you try to shake his hand?
Oh! They're both animals.
Okay, I get it. And Winston
is also an animal. Did you
guys think that there'd be three animals in the
ring in the final four?
Yeah, I probably actually could have guessed that.
As the giant rat doing multiple punches
into Winston who has been in
the ring the longest.
A very long time as the giant rat
is going to go for a hug. Trying to hug his
friend. Is he going to get it while the last competitor
is coming down into the ring?
I don't think he got it. No! He's getting punched.
But who is number 20?
He always comes back
and he always gets what he fucking wants.
And that's the titan
demon grandpa, ladies and gentlemen.
If you don't understand
I will try to explain as best as I can.
But, wait a minute, grandpa
Grandpa's grabbing the giant rat
by the face.
He's holding him in the air.
He's yelling something. I can't tell.
We're at the rat cam right now.
We can't really determine what he's saying.
He just dropped him in the trash!
That's it!
He's been eliminated.
My god.
Let's try to describe what's happening here.
Ladies and gentlemen, grandpa
was chokeslammed into hell
in Jerma Rumble 3.
Grandpa is not a character.
He doesn't get extra lives.
He doesn't get to come back to life.
He goes right to fucking hell where he belongs.
A few different skills.
I guarantee you he came in the same portal
that Xeraxos came in. And he probably
taught him a few things. Let's see what's
going to happen here.
Just lightning-like reflexes.
Goodness. He just hit him with
the three stooges. I think that's
his finishing move. I have no idea
what to say here, guys. All I
know is that he is probably
going to win. And now he's just
taunting Winston, who's been in here for so
long he's probably exhausted.
What a grab. He definitely has
eyes in the back of his head and twists and turns
and throws the bottom half of the two-person horse
down on the ground.
I wish there was something I could do.
There are no rules in the Jerma Arena.
Shit like this is completely legal and totally fine
and accepted.
What's going on?
He's having a heart attack?
No, no, no. Don't listen to him. Don't fall for this.
He's done this shit before.
No! Winston's been eliminated.
And just like that
we are down to two.
The bottom half of the two-person horse
and Demon Grandpa. And the bottom half
of the two-person horse not only has been
in the ring for a long time, he was up
on the horse's ass for like 25 minutes before
even getting in the ring. So this is just
terrible. He needs to find some type of strength
to take on Grandpa.
He needs to do something. Anything!
What can he...
No, not this again. Don't fall for this shit
again.
Oh, heart attack. Okay, yeah. Go after
him now. Fight him! Any second now
he's gonna...he's gonna jump
up and he's gonna slash you with like a demon blade.
Any second he's gonna
he's gonna bite you and he's gonna stop biting you.
He's out!
That's it!
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner
of the first ever live action Jerma
Rumble is the bottom half
of the two-person horse.
What happened to
what the fuck was that?
That was a real heart attack?
I don't believe it. And the top
half is out here to congratulate his friend
for winning. They both are
winners.
Wait, what the? What's he talking about?
They're having some type of argument here about who actually
wins. They were one character. You have to remember.
I don't agree with that. I think you need
to be a collective unit.
He just tripped over and fell over
the ropes trying to attack his
friend. Oh my
fucking god.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the real winner
of the first ever Jerma Rumble
live action
is the Disco Diaper.
And here come the fruits to congratulate
him. He never was eliminated.
Everyone just forgot about him. I even
forgot about him. He died like
fucking two hours ago.
Whatever the fuck it was.
And they're celebrating.
I am speechless right now.
But congratulations
to the Disco Diaper.
And thank you all so much for joining
us for the first ever Jerma
Rumble live action.
It was a fucking train wreck.
And like seven people died.
But thank you nonetheless for watching.
We'll see you next time on
the next Rumble. I've been Jerma.
Thank you to everybody that
participated in this event. Have a
great rest of your day. A great rest of your evening.
The fruits are out. Everybody's
out. Have a good night.