Good afternoon. How are you? Good. Welcome. Welcome to the third stream. One, two, three. This is number three
for the weekend, ending on April 19th, 2020. If this is correct, press one. If this is incorrect,
press two. To erase and re-record, press three. At the beep, please re-record your message.
When you're finished recording, you may hang up or press pound for more options.
What's going on, guys? Welcome to the stream. It's me, Germo. Just getting you, hitting you up.
See if you're ready to go. If you're ready to go, then give me a call back whenever you get the
chance. Although I'm live right now, so you ain't gonna get the chance because this is it. Today
we're gonna play... Well, we had a little bit of a pre-stream issue, and what I mean by that is today
we're gonna potentially play Toontown Reloaded, but it turns out it was... Not that it was hard
to set up, but I wanted to see if it was possible to do a different server or set it up in a way
where I could actually play Toontown, and it turns out no, I can't. So we're gonna do, instead of
Toontown today, we're... I'm not gonna eat a ghost pepper. What the fuck are you talking about?
Eat a ghost pepper. No, not that I couldn't be bothered to. Listen, all right, you're distracting
me. So I'm gonna do MMO Grab Bag 2, because I've seen a lot of people write stuff like,
dude, you should play City of Heroes. Dude, you're champions online. Let's all dump into Roblox.
Let's all play RuneScape. And I'm just like, eh, eh, eh, eh. Toontown. So we're gonna do
a MMO Grab Bag 2. Did one before. Toontown will be part of that. It's just not gonna be today.
Because every one of these is all gonna go the same way. I'm gonna get in the game, and there's
gonna be like 500 people. All of you are gonna try to push me into the ocean. And, you know, after
about 20, 30 minutes of that, how many times can we get me pushed into the ocean? Or too many names
on the screen so I can't attack or tag the enemy or touch the quest giver? You know, how many times
can we do that in Toontown before? It's always funny though. Yeah, I know it. But we have to...
When will I do this? When am I gonna play Toontown? All right, so here's the deal.
Okay, the guy that plans nothing is about to give you a plan. Okay. Wednesday is public domain movie
night. Thursday is community content night. Friday is mystery game night. Saturday is the
Easy Bay government stream. After that, somewhere probably around Tuesday or Wednesday, Wednesday
the 29th, we will try to do MMO Grab Bag 2. I'm still waiting for Doom. Me too. It keeps getting...
I'm never gonna play it. It's not gonna happen. I'm just gonna be completely real with myself.
I don't think I'm ever gonna play Doom Eternal. Anyways, today we're gonna do drugs.
Fake drugs? Because after it turned out the Toontown was not gonna really work out,
we were like, hey, but what about like a stocks simulator? That'd be fun. So we looked up a bunch
of stocks games and some of them for DOS, some of them for like regular Nintendo, and they were
kind of all ass. And I was like, wait a minute. Isn't this drug game is stocks, right? It's just
stocks but drugs. Like, okay. Drug dealing stock simulator. But I did find a good stocks game.
We're gonna play it. It's not today. And here we go. I only gave $50. I got it loaded and ready.
You can hear it though. The chef's corner just gave 5,000 bits. Thank you. Chef's corner.
Hello there, Mr. Elverton. Thank you so much for the entertainment you provided me in the last
few years. But a long few years for me, for sure, mid-20s are apparently always hard.
Anyway, love you and hope auto gets well soon. Also, please peek your microphone. I can't. I
have a compressor on. See, I'm, you guys didn't even know that I had one now. New office, new
compressor. I can't even peek it. It's not possible. It'll, if I, when I go, it's just gonna go,
try it. No, I don't want to, you can break a fucking microphone that way. I know a lot of
you guys think it's like funny when people like scream into their microphones. I do too. Everybody
does. But if you have a microphone, if you have like a nice microphone, you can damage the insides.
It's got the, it's like a light bulb in there. You get to, it can break. Loud is funny. Child
humor. It's not even that funny. Okay. But it is. It's not. But that means screaming is kind of
funny. You can't tell me that like a scream isn't funny in some places. Screaming at a light bulb
will break it. That don't, I'm saying that just be careful with your shit. Okay. This is drug
dealer simulator. We're going to play the stock market except it's drugs. Thank you chef's corner
for the fucking insane 5,000 bit drop. Thanks for the $50. And Otto is doing very well. He's,
I think he's pretty much better, but he has an appointment to make sure of it. Can you hear this?
And I hear this and I hear this. Why can I not hear this? Why is it silent? Um, hold on.
Just don't set that too low. Why can I not hear this though? I'm kind of important. You know,
I mean, my voice is for, you know, I could make this not happen. I don't know how to do that.
Wait, this is, this is a setting on the go XLR. I don't know how to fix.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I don't know. Hold on.
Um, hold on. Yeah, that's better. No, just leave it. Nope. Didn't work. Hold on. What's this do?
Oh my God. You're one of those guys. I don't know how to do this.
That's why is it coming through my mic? Why is my desktop audio coming through my mic?
Why did it be this one? Wait a minute. Hold on. Let me see. What does that do?
Oh, for fuck's sake. Okay. Now you're just fooling around. Um, how do, what, what's, does that work?
You're fooling around. How does this work? I don't understand how this works. Blah, blah.
Why is it coming through? Why is this coming through? I'm not, this is not me making a fucking
joke. Why is this coming through? Why is this bleeding through? My microphone is a mic. Is this
my mic? Desktop audio system. Blah, blah, blah. Now I can't hear it because it's muting my microphone.
Can I not just capture the mic from the GoXLR? Why is this happening now? This didn't happen
yesterday. What the fuck? Stop this. I'm not joking. I'm telling you. Thanks for the money,
by the way. Hey, thanks for the $50, $10, $5. Um, I have to like unplug this and plug it into
something else. This is fucking stupid. If I turn this louder, uh, blah, blah, blah. This is fucking
annoying. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got it. I
got it. Nobody. Why can nobody hear me now? This motherfucker. I swear to God. All right. I think
it's done. Why can you not hear this now? You now cannot hear the audio. What the fuck? Okay. It's
just going to have to stay like that. Can you hear both at the same time?
Okay. It's coming through. That's apparently coming through my microphone, by the way,
just in case anybody was aware. I was curious. Those sounds are coming through the microphone
input. What a dumb fucking hardware. I have no idea why the fuck that would ever be happening.
All right. Anyways, uh, we can turn it up a little though.
Just don't set that too low. Okay. Uh, I've, I don't know why I go XLR. I'm not going to say
anything fucking. I'm not going to say anything. I'm not going to die. I'm, I'm, I'm angry at the
stupid fucking. All right. I'm done. Let's go. All right. Where's my, uh, where's, where's the
fucking, I don't even know. Let's go. Why is the door locked? The ancient enemies of short term
memory. Yesterday, you got so fucked up that even I forgot where the keys are.
Wait, is this me talking to me? Why is it motion blur? This shit should be off.
Search the apartment. You gotta be here somewhere. Dude, fucking weed. I know it's unbelievable.
I can't use the workstation. All right. Where are the keys? Is there a flashlight
or in the game up? It's all right. Streams not on yet. Streams not on yet. I'll be right back.
All right. It worked. All right. I fixed it. Starting the stream again. All right. We're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Dumbest fucking thing I've ever done in my life.
All right. Let's find the keys. That's a real crack stream now. Okay. So I have to find my
keys. Tasks available. Let's see. I have a quest log. Q just like nods my head. Okay. That was,
that was a great comedy bit called drop, kick the go XLR out the window. Fuck. No, it's a good
pro. It's okay. I like it. It works. I just, for some reason it was stupid today. God damn it.
No one will ever fucking like me. I'll never have any friends. All right. Let's go. Let's go. How do
I leave? Where are the keys? There it is. I found it. Why is this like pub G? All right. I just got
money. Why do I have like a pub G backpack? I thought 50 more dollars came in during my fucking
like temper tantrum. Uh, Toby, Toby four two seven. Thanks for the fucking $50. That's 50 exp
and $50 at the same time. Thanks a lot for the 50 fucking bucks. They say,
Jeremiah, I live in the UK. So it's hardly very, I can't get the chance to catch a stream.
I've been a huge fan for nearly seven years. I feel like donating was long overdue. Don't worry
about that. You don't ever have to feel obligated to give me a scent of your hard earned cash
train coming through the fucking house. Wait, what? Uh, thank you for the many years of laughs
you've given me. Thank you for the many dollars you just gave me. Thanks for being around for
seven years, dude. Really appreciate it. Thanks to both you chef corner and Toby. Enjoy the crew
review. I can leave now. All right, let's go. Is there a car? Is this automatic one letter grid?
Where are we? Okay. I have to go in there. The tires of the smell of tires in the morning.
Why is this game postal to but a different game? Okay. Um, I need to go to meet Eddie.
There's a jump. He's just a parkour button. Why is there parkour? I thought it was like a stocks
game. Is Eddie sit down? I'll brief you up. Okay. Eddie, how do I want to do? So I'm gonna just
stocks and I heard drugs are like stocks. Um, no, thank you. You know what? Sometimes when I get
these so called second thought kind of thing, he's a square. What?
How was the party? Um, I was crazy. Yeah, you young motherfuckers tend to do nowadays. I'd be
fucked up big time for a week if I party that on one evening. Well, okay. Anyway,
I thought that was a cloud. It's like, it's like poison. Listen up. I'm your main. I was like,
Oh, nice clouds in the cartel. Anything and everything. Considering the business in and
out dialogue up by little from now on. I'm your daddy, your boss, your fucking wife,
all in one person. Okay. You need dope. You write to me. You got the cash for the cartel.
I take it. You shit your pants. I need to know before you change your underwear straight forward.
Why? Well, Eddie, um, just want to let you know, grab them, go home and get your laptop.
There'll be clients writing you soon. You make them sales and I'll get back to you soon after
questions. Uh, I do drug sales through a laptop, encrypted app cartels in the 21st century. Now,
baby, totally safe. Uh, excuse me. Are we using any protection and security? Eddie,
you're going to smoke that or you're going to let it just burn? All right. Um, was it,
what's a dead drop? What a police, what a police officer I am. Eddie, what's the, uh, dead drop?
What do the kids call that these days? Like a new tick tock dance or something. What is that?
Eddie, a dead drop. I know what it is. Uh, do you know what it is? How do I get off the bench? Oh,
yo, you're going to explain to me what the fuck just
frack. There's a bird stuck on the wire. How do I get up there and release him?
No, he's stuck. Let me turn the volume up. Just don't set that too low. Okay. I don't like having
loud music. It hurts my ears. Okay. So the task now is go to get the first pack. All right. Let's
get our first package. Where is it? There's already, there's already police here. There it is.
Three gram pack of marijuana, popular and light smoked drug. Okay. Items held too long in public
containers may end up stolen. How do I pick it up? I've G pack of amphetamines. How do I get them?
Oh, like that. Okay. I've got them. All right. Now go back home and get to the computer.
Your first client should be messaging you any moment now. You'll get notifications on new
messages on your phone, but to read them, you'll need the encrypted app on the laptop.
What is going on? Okay. You need to, it's from Eddie. Eddie, how do I answer your phone call?
Read messages, left mouse button, Q and E is swipe. All right. Miss call from Eddie. Can I call Eddie
back? Why can I call Eddie back? All right. I'm going to go back home and use the laptop.
That's not a missed call. Wait, am I on call? Am I on the call right now? What is this stuff?
But where, how did this get in the road? It's a monolith. All right. This is my house, right?
Okay. I go over and use the laptop and then sell the drugs. Well, that's not my house.
Where's my house? There it is. Okay. Now use the laptop. Can I cook food? Okay. That's a,
that's a, that's not a laptop. That's a microwave. Where's the laptop? Or clean that window. Oh,
that's a mirror. That mirror is destroyed. I have a nice house tour. This is a new house tour.
Where's my laptop? Do I even have a laptop? Where's my laptop? Wait, hold, check. That's
not a laptop. That's a laptop. Okay. This is Shadycon, a special, fancy, dark web
communicator. Stocks, stocks, stocks, stocks. This is where you order the merchandise from Eddie.
And this is where your clients will contact you. Okay. It also has other options, but
we'll get to that in time. Why are there, why are there three dogs? Why are there animals buying
drugs? Okay. So we have Leon. Yo, you have three grams of weed. Would like to buy some.
You expect high quality. How much, what do I have for drugs? I have five grams of marijuana. I can
sell it for $10. I have seven grams of amphetamines. All right. What does Donald want? I need three
grams of weed. You have some. Hey, yo, you still got stock. 5G would be awesome. All right. 5G of
what? What about what? Sale price. That's $10 a gram. That's correct. What do you mean? All right.
You have three grams of weed? Yeah, sure. All right. Yeah. I got it. On the way. Have cash ready.
Hey there. You still got speed and stock. Oh, that's right. Okay. Yeah. I got that.
All right. I'll deliver to you soon. I don't have any more weed though. How much weed do I have?
I don't have enough. Do I? What do I see how much I have? Yeah. What do you mean? I don't have speed.
That's amphetamine. What do you mean? I have amphetamines. That's what speed is.
What are you guys talking about? Speed is amphetamine. You guys, you guys don't know
anything about drugs? What are you doing here? I took, I've taken drug classes to find out like
how to determine. I've, you know, there was a programs to tell us about how dangerous this
shit was. I know what this stuff is. Are you going to order? Oh, I can order drugs on Shady
comp as well. Communicate with your clients. Choose a person on the contact list and click
the chat input field for options. Clients will show on the map, find them and deliver the packages.
Okay. All right. So let's see, where are they? All right. Emma, deliver five grams of amphetamine.
Let's go right there. That's right here. That's the bathroom. Close the door though.
Let's deliver. Oh, why is the door? I'm on drugs apparently. Oh wait, no, that's the bathroom.
How do I leave? No, that's not the exit. That's another tenant. Okay. Uh, Emma's over here. Do I
need to be able to have protection? Like should I have, should I pick up like a wrench or something?
Like what if they, what if I get attacked? All right. Where's Emma? Why climb the barbed wire
fence? Okay. Emma, finally here. Got the stuff. Yeah, here it is. Um, five pack of amphetamine is
what she wanted, right? Okay. Drugs expected it. Drugs got, okay. I got a hundred respect and $50.
Did I tell you backpacks have downsides as well? The bigger the backpack, the slower you run
and more suspicious you may appear to the police. This is going to turn into death stranding. Now
that's your problem. Imagine having like 50 different suitcases all over me. Okay. So now
I have 50. Oh, I have, I actually hold the money. What if I just like throw it in the air?
Okay. Marijuana. Where's uh, Leon's over here. Drugs stranding. Yeah. Hey, what's up Leon?
You finally got the stuff. Yup. Here it is. What does he want? Three grams. Okay. I want to give
him one. No, no, no, no, no. You're not getting, you're not getting two for one. How do I, I only
want to give you one of these. That's a three. I almost gave him six grams. $36. Thanks a lot.
Okay. More respect. Meth stranding. Okay. I did it. The night, the drug store, the sewage treatment.
This looks like a lot of stuff going on in this game. All right. Let's keep going. I'm going to
go get another order, which I checked. Hold on. New message from what do you mean? There's no new
message here. Why is it lying to me? There's no message on my laptop. What? Fucking pizza.
Free pizza. All right. Do I eventually buy a new apartment or something?
And there is a flashlight. That's cool. And you have to actually hold the phone out.
Fucking Zoopers. Don't even have like a mag light in your car. Okay. Let's go to the laptop.
All right. So I can, here's, here we go. Eddie, Eddie, I got to deliver. Okay. I, where's my money?
Average delivery time. Awesome. Average satisfaction. Not great. Not terrible.
I'm pretty fast. Any three grams. Oh, I did have three grams of weed. Shit. Yep. Okay. Confirmed
that I thought I didn't think I had it. All right. Donald, you might need that sexy red backpack on
the cupboard. I know you're probably used to those sissy casual games where money stored in
a magic cloud under God's fucking pillow, but it ain't the case for us here. You need space
to carry cash. So take that into consideration before you run those first clients. Thanks for
the personal attack. I've been personally attacked. All right, let's go. All right. It's 10. I can't,
you can disable or re-enable the product from sales. Let me just go deliver this shit first.
There's the, the red, the red sack, old beef row backpack. Um, wait, how do I, I have $86.
Is it in there? Backpack contents. Okay. Now I shouldn't take this, right? That one has money
in it. Okay. That backpack has $86 in it. I'm not taking that with me. What if somebody tries to get
it from me to deliver this, to throw it at them? Oh yeah. If you ever have like a thousand dollars
in your pocket, always make sure you have a like $20 bill wrapped in fake paper in your other
pocket. So then somebody's like, give me all your money. You take like the wad of fucking fake paper
with the 20 rolled around it and you go take it. Okay. And then throw it and then run. That's how
you get killed. That's how, that's how they get you. Then you're in fucking a lot of trouble.
Oh, make sure you throw it real far. Then they'll be like, why'd you do that? Why'd you just throw
that motherfucker? It's like, I don't know. I was scared. Just check his pockets. No, no,
I just threw the money over that way. Don't you see what I did? Where is he? Oh, I have dummy money.
That's how you get, that's how you get killed. Hey Donald, thanks for the 36 bucks.
The client should be ordering more. Get to the computer and order more dope from Eddie at a
resupply. Oh, text. Check the gas station shop. Oh yeah. Let's do that. No friends.
Check the gas station for powdered additives. What? What do you mean from, where's that fucking
train? Holy shit. It actually is there. Can I ride it? No. Oh, there's a furniture shop too. Cool.
I thought I could start parkouring over shit. All right, let's go. Now that's an interesting
place. Look up the two towers. They call it creme de la creme of the native pathology.
But there sure is a lot of magic going on. If you know what I mean. Should I go in?
Is it a big party in there? Should I go in there? Can I come in?
How do you knock on the door? Why? I want to go in the party. Okay. Are they having fun in there or
is the inside of this building burning? Like the doors are all locked. Both. Both. I get it.
Oh god damn it. That was sneaky. That was a sneaky one. The doors are sealed with bricks.
Are we sure there's not like some fucking horror movie going on in there? Are you sure like saw
eight is not going on inside of that building? Okay. So here we are. Microwave. Cool. All right.
Where's my? There it is. All right. Let me get open up my backpack. Let's put more money in there.
$122 is in this. Do not lose that. In fact, hide it under the bed. I don't want this in my
doors are unlocked. Look at that. Put this that people wouldn't care. I don't know. Like right
there. All right. Now let's go to the computer. Shady calm. We got Eddie's got something for me.
All right. I heard that you made them sales. Well done. Now if you need more drugs, write to me.
I'll get in contact with you by text and let you know where and when the package will be dropped.
All right. Hold on. Let me go lay on one some more. Yo, you able to deliver two grams of gonjo
would really need some man. I don't have any right now. Uh, I need two G's of FET. Have some FET.
Um, that's five FET. FET and all. Eddie, what do we want? I need an order. Let's go.
Now let's get how much is marijuana. All right. This is 10 grams of marijuana.
That's 50 bucks. I mean people, people smoke weed, right? I get 20, five dollars. I'll get 10.
Give me 10. And then we'll do 10 and 10. Okay. 120 dollars. Order it. Here we go. How are you?
I got a new order. Gotcha. 10 speed. Cool. It'll be ready in about 30 minutes. What? Give me 30
minutes. Sometimes order delivery may take some time. It depends mostly on how large the package
is. Remember to always plan this ahead. Eddie will inform you when the package is ready to
retrieve. In the meantime, you can either find some other tasks to do or wait, hit T while in
hideout to open the wait dialogue. I go. Oh, wait, wait, wait. I'm going to go to the, um,
wait, I'm going to bring, I bring like five dollars with me. How much money is my backpack?
Wait, how do I pay for the drugs? That's their skill points? What? General risk factor.
Raises with every risky trade, chase, and high risk action. This increases the chance of being
robbed, attacked, or ambushed by the DEA. You want to keep this low. Every time criminal activity
includes sales, police chases and arrests. This affects the general visibility of your actions.
Higher exposition means your more police patrols are on the streets and you'll draw DEA.
I'm going to keep this low. All right. What about skills? Illusionist? I don't care what it is.
I want to be an illusionist. Okay. I'm going to be an illusionist. How much more? Do it again.
That's a slight percent chance that police won't find drugs in your inventory when searched. Good.
All right. I have, how many points do I have? That's it. I should have done pockets.
Probably should have increased pocket size rather than be like a street magician. Okay. Hold on.
Let me just let Otto out of the room. Watch out. He sensed, he sensed Kim. All right. So there we
go. Organizer. Earn your debt to Eddie when you make some money on sales. Check the gas station.
All right. Let's check the, I'm not going to skip time. I want to check the gas station.
Sounds like fun. Wait, I need to bring like $5 with me, right? How much is stuff? How much is,
how much is stuff at the gas station? Okay. Pick it up and take, um, is that one dollar?
Go buy like a pack of gum. Okay. I'll bring like package, retrieve the package.
I'll bring $10 with me. I have a $10 bill. All right. Now get rid of this.
You have three clients so far. That's cute, but it won't get you far to grow your business. You
need to unlock more areas and keep your respect high. Get to the computer to learn more about
gaining new sales. Deliveries left in dead drops for a long time may be stolen. Oh fuck. Wait,
I have to buy it? I have to bring the backpack? Oh shit. Okay. I gotta go. Do I have to buy them
here at the drop? Oh shit. How much money do I have? $122. All right. Where's the drop?
It's right here. It's close. Hurry, hurry. I'm going. I'm going as fast as I can.
Where is it? Are they dogs? What's that? Quick, use my zoomer light. Where is it? Oh,
there it is. Okay. I got it. All right. So now take this, take this. I didn't even need to bring
the money. Do I put the money over here on the wall? I have, why am I had this cash on me?
Why did you guys tell me to do this? Oh, it's Eddie. What? Oh no, I have to fuck it. Wait,
good thing I'm a master illusionist. Excuse me, sir. And I'm going to fucking like put crumple up
like a piece of paper and like throw it behind his head and I'm going to find the paper behind
his ear. Just like that Chris angel episode. Okay. I gotta go back to my house. All right.
Bring the drugs into my house. Okay. Now. Okay. So I'm put the cash in the cupboard.
Is that in the cupboard? It is. Okay. I'm going to take, let's take half. I want it to keep half on
me. Oh, I'm holding control. Control is supposed to be quantity, right? How come that's not working?
I want to take, Oh, it's one 10. What? It's one 10 gram pack. No throwing rocks at my window.
Oh, well, can I give somebody? Can I like dump it in his hands? I unlocked East old town. Okay.
Eddie. All right. Packages waiting for you. You can pick it up. Okay. Here. Deliver cash.
I have cash for you. Can we meet? All right. Waiting for you at my place. You owe $120.
Fuck. Choose a spray symbol to mark your territory. Um, gas mask, nuclear, one guy, a dead,
dead one guy, Satan, bullet, uh, the letter F but backwards. I wrote from team fortress
and the funny number. Hmm. Hmm. It's tricky. I'm gonna have to go one dead guy.
You can buy spray paint in shops like the gas station or find some leftover cans in the ghetto.
Look around. All right. So I have to meet him with $120. All right. Where's my cupboard? Okay.
$120. All right. Just keep, drop $2. All right. I have $2. Let's bring. All right. 120 bucks.
You have a $2 profit. I know that's not good. $2. All right. Where's Eddie? Deliver a free sample.
I don't have any. I don't have a sample. There's money in times. Just what I don't have. All right.
But look at this. Eddie, is that a cop? Is that a cop? This is not a cop. But who is this? Why
did the question mark? Talk to stranger. What's the problem? Attention. Attention.
Attention. Attention. What? To all guest citizens. Police hours are to start in 60 minutes.
Wait. Why is there like a dystopian half-life? For their own safety,
citizens are to proceed to their quarters. What? Individuals caught in public areas during police
hours may face consequences. Attention. Attention. Attention. We're gonna do the whole thing.
We're gonna do the whole thing. Hi. Yeah, here it is.
Police hours are to start in 60 minutes. For their own safety, citizens are to proceed to their
quarters. Individuals caught in public areas during police hours may face consequences.
Attention. Attention. He does it again? Does it do it in every language?
It will start in 60 minutes. I repeat. Police hours will start in 60 minutes.
All right. I guess I have to go back home.
That's not my house. Fuck. Where's my house?
That's not my house. No more? Are we not going to get that in any other languages?
Okay. Here we go. Activate workstation. Workstations are furniture-based equipment.
Here you can customize your drug lab. Store drugs and substances meant for mixing and
processing. This is also the place where you pack the product to its final weight portions
prepared for sale. There we go. Okay. So you're in workstation mode now.
You can arrange your lab to mix and produce whatever you desire. Remember chemistry classes
back in school? No? Yeah, me neither. Fuck it. Who cares, right? You'll find more info in
the workstation manual. Okay. Hit tab and cycle to the drug replacement mode. Here you can put
drugs and additives on the table to pick them back up. Don't mix bleach and ammonia. You'll die.
Right? I don't want to do that. Equipment mode. Medium jar. All right. Hold on. I need my drugs
first. Somebody's knocking the door. All right. I want to break this up into three, three, three.
Right? What do people want? Okay. I want three G's of weed, three, five, two G's. Okay. We need two G,
three G. Okay. Two G of speed, three G of weed. No, two G of grass, three G. Can we just have the
same code word? Just call it W. Why are you changing the code word? I just gave it to you. Okay.
You want two G's of speed and then two G's of... Who the fuck are you? Heard that you sell weed.
I need two G's. Urgent. All right. Well, hold on. I need two, two, two. Two, two, two. All right. I want
pick up 10... Okay. So now it's on the hit tab to cycle equipment mode. Okay. Put some containers
around so we can store the drugs in them. How much is a small jar? We need just little jars, right?
Okay. Yeah. We need two little jars. One, two. We need... Okay. We need weed. Urgent.
Now we'll put the substance into the container. There are two ways to do that. Select the source
with left mouse and then choose add substance. Or simply drag and drop the substance on the
container. Okay. All right. So I want handle objects with options such as lab mode. Oh, okay.
Oh shit. Okay. I get it. Put that on here. Go to lab mode.
Okay. Two G's. That's too many. That's two G's too many. Two point O G's.
Edit the container label. What? Ding dong, motherfucker. Bedtime. During police hours,
you should remain home. But we, the bad guys, we don't give a fuck. The police do though. So
you keep an eye on them and better stick to the shadows. Working at night reduces exposition and
boosts respect and experience gain from sales. All right. Well, okay. So that's two of those.
Give me this back. How do I pick that back up? Okay. Now I need weed. Okay. Lab mode was two
two G's. Okay. This is mirror. That's not how you spell it. We're going to, this is, um,
okay. That's in there. That's two. I need one more small. Um, I need one more small one.
I can, can I just grab two? I can't have, I guess I can't, um, I got to buy more.
Really? Okay. Well, let me get off this. How do I get out of here? Give me this. How do I pick it up?
Oh, select add dump contents. No, no, no. I want to pay. How do I just put
everybody equivalent on every equipment type has its options. One of them is somebody just shot a
gun package product where you can choose and what quantities and grams has to pack the dope. If you
need more details, but isn't it already packed? Hold on. What? Hold on. I think the dog is outside.
Hold on. I thought, I thought that was a dog in the game for a second. Give me one second.
How do I pick this up? So not throw backpack package product. Okay. So that was a package
product. Total source, new package, add new package package size two grams. Wait, what should I make
a, I can't just put this in my backpack. Can't see. Oh, so why I can't just pick up the jar and put
it in my backpack. Like I have to package the product package product, total source mass,
two grams. Okay. Add new package package size two grams. Or as I used to store, you sell with bags.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm still, I'm not, I, I'm, I did this wrong. I'm supposed
to sell with the bag. Package product. I'm just going to do a new package package size two grams,
two grams of amphetamine. I got it. Okay. So now this is empty. The jars just sit on the table.
Okay. Package product. This is two grams. I need two of these, don't I? Right. So I need two of
these because I'm doing two, because I need two of them. Will it just make two? That will work,
right? Two. Yeah, it will. You can only have two in there. Total source mass two grams. So it can
only be two grams. There's only two in here. Should I put four in there? Okay. So there's four in
there. So now if I go to package product, new package, I want two, two gram packages. There it
is. Okay. Good. Store drugs in jar. Make drugs to sell. Yeah. All right. I thought I was trying to
give you to sell them. Add substance. Put it all in the jar. This will just keep us labeled as
correctly as amphetamine. Put these in here and add it all to the jar. This is marijuana. Make it
green. Okay. Now I know what these are. Oh, wait. I need weed urgent. Well, I didn't reply yet.
Okay. So there's my drugs. I get it. Now I have, I have, what do I have? I have two, two, two,
two dollars. All right. I'm ready. Where is he? I need two grams urgent. I'll do you last to make
sure I get you in delivery. Two grams of weed. You got it. Two grams of that. You got it.
And two grams of weed urgently. Got it. Okay. This guy right here. Save the game. Fuck. Well,
it's urgent. It was urgent. It was urgent. It was urgent, but it was urgent. Okay. Please wait one
minute. What? Did it save? Oh, okay. I'm ready. I need my zoomer power. All right. There's that
guy that needs it urgently. Is that somebody that I need to talk to? Oh shit. It is. Hey, come here.
You got it. Yep. I got it. What did you want? Two G's. Thank you. $44. All right. Have a nice day.
Next is Donald. Donald, you're right here and put him right next to each other. Good.
I do have it. You wanted two G's. Oh, excuse me. One. Thank you. Okay. Last one was the urgent one.
I did it to the cops. Is this guy? Right. I'm going urgently. Don't worry.
Hey, you're finally here. Yeah. Well, you just ordered. Thank you. $40. Done. All right. I got
to get the hell out of here. I got to get out of here and go to sleep. I got to mark my territory
there. I have to piss on the wall like a dog. Mark my territory? Why isn't it tag? Why is it
mark? Where do I do it? Oh, I don't have a spray paint. Right. Oh, fuck. Police. This guy's like
on the phone. I'm going to break in his house. I feel like this is a trap. Is the ground going
to fall underneath me now? What was the point of this? Okay. I'll get paint. I will tomorrow
morning. I got to go back to the house first. I'll get paint. Good. I got money. Let's store it.
I got $126 in cash. I have no money. Only $126. What the hell? I have $4 in profit. How much do
I know? I still have drugs in there. Okay. It was pressed T. Waiting time. Does this go any faster?
Nobody fucking calls me. All right. Donald wants four grams of amphetamines. I have that.
Got it. Get him a new package for you. All right. I need a workstation. Go ahead and pack that up.
One package of four. What do I mean? How am I supposed to do this? Oh, well, okay. I got it.
Yeah. I didn't know if I had to do it in one. What? Why are they getting closer? Where's my
backpack? Okay. Where's the delivery going to go? Over there. How much stuff is happening right now?
A lot, apparently. All right. I'm heading down. Possibly robbed armor on Old Town. What? Did I
just eat? I don't even know the words. I just. Hey, come over here, pal. Run, motherfucker, run.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm sleeping. Your door is open. What? They can't see me now.
Oh, damn, man. I almost shit my pants. I suppose you've gone all the way though.
Did I call Eddie? All right. I got it. You're a fugitive now. What do you mean I'm a fugitive?
The policeman that chased you will probably recognize you, so watch out. What? Others will be
more alerted for naughty looking assholes like you running around the area. God damn it. Better
keep a low profile. I have to change clothes now? Change faces. I have to deliver these drugs. He's
right there. I got to go out and bang a left. All right. The train is going to give me cover.
God damn it. What? Oh, don't get me. Wait. Oh, wait. Where's my secret area? Where's my secret
door? The one that I opened? Where's the one that I opened? Which one is it? Where is he? Oh,
fuck. I just, I found him. He's literally right here. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, buddy. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it. I got it. I got it. Give me the money, please.
Thank you. Bye. Bye. Hey, by the way, take this fucking backpack. It's free, dickhead.
No, I need the money. All right. I'm good. See, officer, I didn't have any money. I just had drugs.
No, the other way around. So I wanted to say that the other way. Hey, hey, hey, Jeffrey,
Jeffrey, Jeffrey, Jeffrey, Jeffrey. How are you? Hey, you want any more? I got some free samples
for you, Jeffrey. Here it is. This is my secret house. I got to remember this. Where is this?
Okay. I mean, I need to remember that's the secret house. Suspicious individual. Nope. Not me.
What? Oh, that's not even my fucking house. It's got a house symbol on it. Nope. All right.
I'm going to sleep. How do you go to bed? Tea? If a tea doesn't go to sleep, it just makes time
go a little faster. How much money do I have? I've got a hundred and I got a hundred and ninety four
dollars. Tea. Tea again? I'm going to wait till like what? Where I am? Toop. Toop. What's that?
Hello? How am I still a fugitive? Well, it's only been like four hours, of course.
All right, Donald. I want four grams. Emma wants four grams. What do I have left?
Buy some more. I've got, I need more amphetamine. Amphetamine selling pretty well. I got to buy
more amphetamine. Hey, just cut the drugs. Okay. Eddie, I need to make an order, Eddie. I need
four, eight. Yeah, I need eight grams. I want twelve. No, we'll just do, do twelve grams.
Twelve grams of amphetamine and yeah, let's spend some money. Total value. I can only buy
$130 worth. Why? Well, then fine. I'll buy, I'll buy like, I don't know, four? What? Why? It's eighty
four bucks. It's only fifty dollars. What are they talking about? Five, ten, fifteen, fine, two.
Can I only buy one of these? What the fuck is going on? Fifty dollars for a bag. That makes
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve. I still, I fucking goddamn mathematics. Minimum ten grams purchase.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Cash is in there. You ready? You got it? It's minimum. You have
to buy a minimum ten grams. All right. Thirty minutes. You, uh, four grams to be specific.
Four grams and four grams. Everyone's good. You guys have, I've already delivered to you.
You too. Wait, I did. Two grams urgent. Got it. Two grams urgent. Yeah, I got it. All right. I need
eight. I can't do these yet. I have to get the drugs first. I can take one because that's all I
have. Okay. I can do you and then I can pick up the package. Let's go. Oh, you're right out the
fucking door. This is perfect. Why is it still police hours? I was right here. Emma? Emma? Sixty
eight bucks. Good. It's always police hours. I want to go to the gas station. Okay. Well,
now I get away for the drug. Can I just stand still here? Now, why would I stand still here?
That would be the stupidest fucking thing ever. Watch out for the police patrol. I know. Don't
worry. They're not going to get me. I got some decent amount of money though that I can spend
on whatever the who knows something. Something fucking good. I buy supplies, food, or a
figurine of the green Teletubby. Which one? What do you think? He's a Funko Pop addict.
I need four grams. I can't do that yet. This one is now empty. How much how much man one is in there?
How much is in there? Ed, drop package ready for the trash bin. It's still police hours. What the
fuck? Why? How much drugs are in there? Yeah, they're in there. I don't know why I decided to
do that. Twelve grams in there? No, that's an electrical box. It's right here. It's police
right over here though. Get out of the way. Move police. Oops. I don't have anything on me, right?
No, I have $68 on me. Why is that such a concern? Where is it? In the trash? Okay, now I'm illegal.
Now I'm against the law. Get the fuck out of here. All right, I made it. It's still police hours.
Why is it still police hours? I want to get invited to the party. Why am I not allowed at the party?
Whose fucking house is this? I thought this was like a hotel door leading to the other room,
but it's the bathroom. I've seen this like five times. This is not a hotel. Okay, I got the drugs.
Let's go ahead and do some placement here. Okay, let's pick this up. Cost that shit in there.
N. So there is now 10 grams in there. Put this marijuana in there. Fill it up. The rest of this
shit. Uh oh. Just get a medium jar. How much are these? Do I just own them? I just own these.
This doesn't cost any money. I just own them. Oh, what's the point of having the small ones?
Okay, good. Mixing tray. Wait, how do I mix? Can I mix like, can I mix marijuana and like
coconut oil or something to make it look stickier and better? That's to cut it. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
So hold on. Wait, show options. Okay. Mix details. Mix details. Amphetamine. Total mix mass. Add
substance. Need to buy powder. So wait, I have to. Okay, I can't do this yet.
The worst mix is not ready. What? No, take it out. Dump. How do I take it? Apply the mix? There is
no mix. Deselect. Package this. Apply mix. There is no mix. New amphetamine. All right, if I take
the amphetamine, put it in another box and write new amphetamine on it. Look at that. All right.
All right. So I need to do, let's see, still police hours. I'm fucking just going to wait till
five in the morning. What color do you think the Hulk's? Of all the things that somebody writes
in chat, why would I pick that one out? I just decided to pick that up. Press T again. I think
this is as fast as it goes. And to answer your really, really stupid fucking question, it's green.
The Hulk is green. He's green. What are you talking about? It's still police hours. 5 a.m.? 6 a.m.?
How can you be sure? What? Because it has to be. All right. I'm taking these orders. All right.
The package is waiting for you. How much do I owe you? I own like a hundred and 120 bucks. All right.
We'll do it all. Four grams of that. Confirm it. You want two grams of that. Confirm it. You want
two grams of... Oh, nobody wants any weed today. Shit. Okay. What was it? 442? I can handle that.
New package. Two. One. Quantity of two. And then we need... We actually need a lot of those.
So we need four of these. All right. Let's go. That gives us... All right. You want to do...
Four. Two. Four. Two. Right. We're good. All right. Let's go. Let's go give him some money.
Still fucking police hours for some reason. I need to put $120 in here. Take this shit out.
Take out... I don't know math. Who cares? Let's take out seven. All right. I got the
222. Wait. I already had one. That's two, four, six, eight, ten grams. Okay. Who cares? What? No,
that's right. Okay. All right. Let's go. Still police hours for some reason. Six a.m. No more
police. What? I have to deliver this shit. I took all these orders. Fuck. Orders are going to be
late. All right. Let's do top to bottom or bottom to top. Still police out. Why did I not take the
sneak ability? What's wrong with me? Hey, Donald. You wanted four grams. So you take two of these.
Okay. Thank you. $68. I thought that was the police. I thought it was like... Let's go to Emma.
Hey, no police. Emma, I've got two grams for you. All right. I've got to give... After this,
I've got to give some money. One. Okay. Thank you. And then we got to go across to
Raphael. Shit. Still police hours. I don't know how. Can you stop by my place and sell me some
crack? I don't know. Do you live here? I got what you need. Here we go. You wanted... Oh, and no,
you don't get anything for free. Not here. Not now. All right. Good. All right. Eddie.
Where's Eddie? Right there. Let's square up, Eddie. 120 bucks. Good. All right. Let's go. Let's give
a free drug sample to somebody. It was somebody standing around here, right? Just give free drugs
sample. Find a stranger and just give them drugs. No, those are cops. Don't give cops drugs. Hey,
officer. I got it. Something you might like. Police hours is gone. Good. All right. Deliver
a free sample. Somebody should be right here. I saw them earlier. Where the hell did they go?
In the house? No, he was walking around. Well, I can't do that right now. All right. I want to
go to the gas station. You should buy a gun. Well, I need money to buy a gun, don't I? All right. Gas
station. Let's see what they have here. That's a cop. Stop. Police checkpoint. Well, I'm not going
through that. Is that me? Okay. Talk to Amy Schrader. What do you need? I want to buy something.
Washing powder, baking soda, and a spray paint. 25 of them. All right. I want one of these. How
much is that? It's $57. All right. Medium backpack, acetone, salt, sugar. All right. Give me some
sugar. I'll give me some salt. Oh, I can't fit it. Baking soda. Okay. I'll take some baking soda.
Okay. I guess ibuprofen pills. Can I take those? All right. Well, I got what I want. Okay. All
right. Beat it. Baking soda. Baking soda. All right. Beat it. Yeah. You too. Can I buy beer? You need
to look away. You guys need to fucking relax. All right. Let's go. I got spray paint. I want to spray
paint. I want to spray the territory. I want to get invited to the party. When do I get invited
to the cool party? Not invited. I will be. I'm going to become the best drug dealer in the city.
Now I'll get tons of drug points. You got to start selling in bulk. Well, I'm not there yet.
Let me just spray paint my face. Excuse me. Here. I have a present for you. I can't just give him
$10. Okay. Here. You want some drugs? No fucking messages ever. What? No one's talking to me.
Who's that? Another drug client? All right. Wait. I got a spray paint. Okay. Hold F.
Holy shit. That's awful. Keep in mind. Gaining respect is one thing. Keeping it is another.
Respect in neighborhoods slowly drops in time. I couldn't forget to keep those sales flowing.
Low respect is less sales. Less sales is less money. Where is this person talking to me from?
Well, it just sucks. Okay. All right. So unlock East Old Town Old Marketplace. Buy spray paint
and place four wall markings. All right. Don't lie. Don't lie. You all had to fucking done that
with a can. You've all turned the can of whipped cream upside down and ate like fucking way too
much whipped cream. Not right side up. Upside down. Not right side up. Upside. No. I'm talking
about like the joke that's in every fucking comedy movie from like the 90s. I don't even
joke. You take the whipped cream out of the fridge and you turn it upside down and go
and then you turn to whoever you're talking to in the room and you go.
Every single fucking person has done that. I don't believe you. Let me get this straight.
A bunch of you guys have never turned a whipped cream can upside down and like into your mouth.
That's impossible. There's no fucking way any of you are telling the truth. What? Not ever in your
whole life ever. There's no way. I don't believe any of you. Unbelievable. I've never done anything
like that. It's disgusting. How dare you do something like that. No. I sit down at a table
with a fork and knife and I get a plate and I take the can of whipped cream and I turn it up. First
I wipe the nozzle down and then I turn it upside down and I do onto the plate and then I take the
fork and knife and I cut into it and eat it like a fucking steak. No, you've done that. And if you
haven't, I just don't believe you. Okay. Where are we going? No, I got a lot of storage. I got to
store some stuff. I got money. Do you eat rubber cement? Rubber cement is not whipped cream out of
a can. Rubber cement is an adhesive. And no, I'm not talking about like breathing in the gas. Okay.
I'm talking about, no, some of you guys. Oh, fuck. I'm talking about just, no, this is
eating a tub of whipped cream ASMR. No, you guys know what I'm saying. This is like you eat it.
This just crashed my computer. Okay. I'm not going to listen to that. No. You go here. I'll do it on
camera. I'm talking about when you go like this, you go and then you, and then it turns the liquid
in your mouth. So you go and it's gone. Don't do that on cam. Oh, all right. Don't call me Lego
hair. Okay. Donald, how much do I have? Let me check my inventory. All right. Let's put, wait.
Hey, people are trying to sleep out here. But I don't, I don't know. Trying to find the window.
All right. Well, I was going to put baking soda in drugs, right? This is bad. This is bad. Sugar in
okay. So let's do placement mode. Just baking soda. And am I going to like, am I going to hurt
people? Oh, nothing in there. I need more. Um, I need more drugs. Shit. Okay. I got to buy,
I need more amphetamine. God damn it. Okay. Hold on. Let me put this away. Uh, let's put the money
away. Let's do, we'll keep the, this can of spray paint. I'll do one more tag and we'll have that in
the, you know, he's a drug dealer with a conscience. I mean, what do you want me to do?
All right. I need more. Everyone wants amphetamine. Eddie, Eddie, I need a new order and it's, it's all,
it's going to be all amphetamine. I'm going to get 20 G's of amphetamine. Okay. Anybody call me?
What the fuck? Throw the backpack. Chop Antonopoulos. I'm looking for ganja. I need two
grams. All right. Don't have any amphetamine. Okay. I need, uh, that's amphetamine.
All right. I can sell to you. I got weed. What? Two grams? I got it. Don't worry. What if I just
brought the box of sugar? New package, two grams. All right, let's go. And then I can pick up the
delivery. Sounds good to me. Cut the weed with sugar. Oh, you're literally right there.
Where are all these dogs? Every time I come over here, there's dogs, dogs, dogs, but I don't,
I never see them. All right. What's up? I have it. 20 bucks. That's it. I was about to say who the
fuck did that? It was me. I was like, who's stealing my stuff? I have to go to the other place. I have
to go to the other town. It's not even my house. Wait, I'm normal. I'm normal. I have spray painting
cash. I could be working. I'm doing a DIY project outside in front of my house. I'm spray painting
a table. This table. Okay. We're good. This is a new customer, but I don't know. I don't have any
drugs. All right. Where's my uh, is this like whipped cream? I can't believe none of you guys
do the whipped cream thing. There's so many things that are normal that I have done in my life that
you guys think is just like, I may as well be like screaming somewhere, like on the sidewalk,
like with like, like naked or something. Like, oh, what are you talking about?
All right. I got my, where's the package? All right. Package is right there in East old town.
I, that's, that's, those are my drugs. I need them. This guy breathes regularly. No, actually,
I kind of don't. I kind of, when I'm like sleeping and like lying down, I do like a,
and then I kind of, sometimes I do that and I like, hold on. I think I,
did I have another backpack? Geez, please tell me you're giving free drug samples.
No, you're under arrest. Oh geez. All right. Let's just go get the package. Wait, that person was
running over to the package. These things get stolen. Can't they get the fuck out of here?
Need to level up illusion. Where is it? There it is. It's the tires. Thank you. Got it. All right.
Let's go do these orders. That's not my house. I think it's my house every time.
So can I eventually unlock any door I want? This is like a lockpicking skill.
Why don't I just do that? Illusionist. Pockets. Quick learner. Increases experience points.
Increases the price you're able to demand for your product. Oh, but illusionist.
Decreases the probability you'll be spotted by the police. That's so important.
Increases running speed. Stamina. Number of pockets, making you able to carry more
items without a backpack. I think I want salesman. Yeah. I want to be able to sell my stuff for more
money. I got the drugs. Now who wants them? I could just waiting at the playgrounds. Okay. Cool.
I need two G's. So we need two, three, two. Two, three, two. Two, three, two. Oh, here. And we're
going to change this up a little bit. Okay. Two, three, two. So let's put these drugs over here
and we're going to add what? Five grams of five grams and then I'm going to put five grams of
baking soda. Okay. And then we're going to apply. Okay. So this is, all right. I did it.
The mix has been applied. All right. So store it in here. 9.96. Okay. Cool. This is 90% baking soda.
No, it's not. Okay. So now I'm going to sell this. So we need two, three, two. So now I'm going to
package one package of three and then two packages of two. Okay. Let's try it. Remember you're out
here curing heartburn, but don't you guys know? You think I'm like such a bad guy, right? You know,
every Hershey bar can have up to like six bug legs in each bar. You know that, right? They can,
the FDA allows up to like three insect legs per Hershey bar. This is true. This is not me making
this up. This is a real actual fact. So I can put two or three bug legs in my cocaine or 50% baking
soda as an urban legend. No, it's not. That's a Facebook headline. It's not a Facebook headline.
It's been proven by, you know, you know, I don't know. I don't know. I've never looked into it.
I, it's just, that's what I've been told. I've never done the research to determine if that was
real. I think that's just what was something that was told to me over like the decade or so that
I've been what? Whatever, you know, 20 of them, whatever, however long it's been. It's just, hey,
this is a, there's like 10 bug legs in every Hershey bar. And it's like, oh yeah. Everyone
just says that. I never fucking looked up like, are there insect legs in a Hershey bar? I don't
fucking care. I don't care. If I'll leave them, maybe I don't give a shit. If this bug legs in
them was zero bug legs, who cares? Bug legs are fine. It's not going to hurt you. All right.
Goodbye. Oh, people have orders waiting. All right. So we got two grams. You got it. Two grams.
You got it. Three grams. You got it. Okay. Two, three, two. Let's go save the game.
Why not 10? What? Okay. There's Donald. Here you go, Donald. So you, how many want two? I'm
not sure I would take something with the label that says filler test. It worked.
Mayor Raphael. Do you want three? You want, no, you wanted two.
Four bucks. Thank you. You can keep some of your money on a bank account. There are a few
ATMs in the ghetto where you can withdraw deposit cash. You'll need bank account money for furniture
shopping. Oh, I can put money in a bank. All right. That's good. Really good to know. Emma.
I do. Here it is. Three grams. It's a lot. Check out one of the ATM. Okay. Where's the ATM?
ATM. You are allowed up to 60 insect parts in a hundred grams of chocolate. This is real. Good.
So I was right. All right. I got a hundred. Let's put a hundred dollars in the ATM.
All right. So, okay. If they stay alive and theoretically, shouldn't I just do
like 98% baking soda at some point, I guess you're going to get it caught doing that.
This is ATM. Oh, I can't, I'm not allowed over there.
98% bug and phetamines. Okay. Here we go. ATM. There it is. All right. Activate the ATM.
Okay. Now listen up carefully. The bank account is the place to keep your legal money.
You can use ATMs to withdraw or deposit cash, but be careful. Huh? And keep in mind that you're an
immigrant ghetto low life too much unregistered money flowing through that account interest of
the state. Let's put, let's put in $10 and watch while the bank gives us fees every month for
$30 and our bank account becomes negative, like 250 over the course of the next three months.
Bastards. Oh yeah. At an ATM, you can withdraw or deposit cash. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Keep in mind that too much unregistered cashflow draws authorities attention.
You need to check your account balance. You can do so the Shadycom computer.
Also getting into debt. First of all, you'll need that account for some payments. And second of all,
the state dislikes criminals, but it sure hates debtors. Okay. Well, I got my money safe.
Who are you? Can I come in? Furniture shop. Oh, that has money in it. All right. Cool. What are my
tasks? Unlock East old town in the old marketplace. Nobody fucking calls me. Nobody cares. All right.
Back to the house. I think that's like a shadow of somebody running behind me.
Wrong house. No, no, it's not the wrong house. Not yet. Almost wrong house. He thought I was
going to do it. Fuck. Okay. Save game. Now let's keep going with this drug stuff. Take a look at
the computer. Chop. You have two grams of speed. I would like to buy some. Your bank account is now
available. Check the bank app to see your expenses and account balance. Okay. I have nine. Wait,
I have $950 in here. Your last salary. Fuck you. You lazy piece of shit. Wait, I have a thousand
dollars in here. Alcohol store. Sex shop. ATM. My $50. Money for the rent. Oh, phone payment.
Subscription to film flicks. Horn master's account. I get my celtra security and then $63
at the grocery store. I got $950 here. Yep. Cryptocurrency Bitcoin wallet for the good stuff
here. Illegal stuff. You can buy cryptocurrency from certain shady vendors. In theory, it's been
de-legalized by the U.S. a few years back, but yeah. $18 for one PTC. Would have been great to
buy at those levels. God, if only I could grab a time machine. I would buy 10,000 million of those
things. Okay. So I have speed. It's bad, but I still have it. Emma, what is this filler test shit?
This is not what I expected. Bring me something better next time. What is this filler test shit?
Bring me something better. This is filler shit. Okay. I'll get you something fine. I got you.
Don't worry. I got you guys. I'll give you something better. I have to powder this.
I don't have a mill. Here we go. 3.98 grams. Shit. I have to add. Okay. Add 0.2 grams to this.
No! No, this is 4.9 grams of unregulated shit. New! Made with real amphetamine.
Um, okay. They both want two, right? Two, two. There's a little bit extra there. Who cares?
Try this new recipe. It was what? Two? Two grams? What do you want? What does Chop want? Two grams?
Two grams? Two grams of marijuana. Oh, fuck. I need, I need marijuana. Oh shit. This has to be real
too. Great. All right. Let's go. I guess I've been waiting for a long time. All right. Try my new
recipe. Emma, look. I promise this one's better. I got it. Here it is. Two gram pack of new made
with real amphetamine. Try it. Tell me what you think. Except it's only made with one.
Donald, how are you? Uh, you want marijuana? I got it for you. Level four. Who buys two grams of weed?
That guy. Here. Wait. Damn it. I need to abandon farm. Can I like search this place?
Will there be supplies? How'd you have a boat in here? All right. Well, this place is dumb. All
right. Back to the house. And then I'm going to try to unlock that new thing. What? Oh, behavior
looks carried backpack or the intensity of crime in the area may affect the decision. Try to stay
nice and calm around police. Don't run from them. I'm good. I just have $70 in my pocket.
I am running. Money is illegal. Book it. Money's against the law. Where's your credit card?
I need to. Okay. Let's see. I need two grams of speed. They did not just give it to you.
All right. Let's take a look at the desktop. I need the old marketplace. I need,
I need 700 respect. You'd be level four. I need more respect.
All right. So we set a new price. Right. Is that charge?
Did I drop the, should I make the price higher? All right. It's now $15. Prices might be too high.
12.5. How many of your sale prices exceed your reputation? Oh, fuck. How about 11?
How about cheaper? No. Give it a 12. 11 for weed. That's too high. 10. Prices are still too low.
How about 10.0.1? All right. No, 10.2. Okay. It has to be in. All right. Nevermind. Look,
my prices are considered low. All right. I'll get you speed. How much actual drugs do I have?
What is even on here? Like, what is this? One, it's one gram. This is the, someone's going to
hate this. All right. I'm going to give this to somebody for free. Package product. Package
mass extends source mass. What? No, stop. What am I supposed to do about this?
Add flour. This is for me. Like, how do I package it? I can't even take it.
Source is different substance. All right. Put it in here. I'm going to make this red. So I know
like this is just junk. Make a meth cake. Stop. Okay. I have six grams of marijuana.
I have 12 grams of marijuana and then two almost. Okay. We'll take this one.
I need a two grams. So that guy wants it. Heard you sell amphetamine. I need three. Urgent.
I don't have any more. I don't have any more. I have like, I have the junk.
He doesn't want the filler test. That's what you're going to get. I don't, I urgent. It's
not going to work. Here's the only way this works with urgent. Okay. No, I have a lot.
Actually, it's just sitting on the table. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
remove, remove, remove, remove, dump it. No, no, no, no, no. Um, all right. Well, let's,
I have to do this now. So there's how much is on there? Two grams of baking soda. Add this.
And then we're going to add it to this three there. Seven grams to the mixing tray. Done. Apply mix.
New baking soda mix. All right. Let's go. Who wants this shit? What do I have? I have,
what do I have in my inventory? Two grand pack of filler test and three grand pack of a new
baking soda mix. This is bad. All right. Ah, the master revolutions. All right. How about, um,
click learner sales. That's an, that's irreversible. I can't reverse that. Thanks.
Okay. Let's go. We have, uh, wait, how many, wait, what happened to the element? Three grams.
I'm not even accepted. Three grams of amphetamine. Yes. You got it. I want three grams. You got it.
Okay. We can do more. Okay. I need more than that though. I need another three grand bag
of the new baking soda mix. Okay. We're good. Let's go make some money. All right. You two
are right next to each other. I got to put some money in the bank too. How much money should I
put in the bank? What do you want? A three grand bag. You got it. 36 bucks. Nice. All right. Now
you both of you are standing right next to each other down here. Armed robber.
Should I be concerned? Okay. You wanted the two grams, right? No, you want three grand. Then you
or you, you're over the other side. Stop. I had more respect.
Almost there. All right. Back to the, I'm, I gotta go to the, I gotta go to the ATM.
I got too much money. Remember, what's your only fans? Uh, twitch.tv slash German nine eight five.
There's a little button underneath it that says subscribe to, to, to German nine eight five. You
can click that and then that's a look at you. You're a, a, a, what a fan, right? Let's do that one.
What is this ATM? I keep fucking forgetting. Alexa install fart button. Come on, hurry up and get
your strength back. Wait, where? I'm on the other side of town. How did I do this? I should get the
stamina increase. This is annoying. I can't get that ATM. Are you getting high on your own supply?
Get a bike. What do you mean get a bike? I want to deposit money. Deposit. That was my account
balance. All right. Back. Deposit money. Deposit another a hundred bucks. I don't have a hundred.
Seventy five. Let's just do 96. Okay. I'm going to go buy some stuff now from the online marketplace.
Love Bellina's mansion. All right. And at some point I'm going to start dropping bags of cocaine.
I'm going to buy eventually like 500 grams of cocaine and put them in individual one gram bags
and make a, like a Hansel and Gretel trail to my house from like Eddie's house.
I don't have anything on me. I have no, I've just, I'm just, just me.
Yeah, look, they planted drugs on you. Imagine they did that and they forgot to take me.
I just had like a thousand dollars worth of cocaine or something. All right. Let's go back and do
what I want to do. Free crack. All right. I'm almost, it's almost time. Okay. I need,
with my respect and let's see my bank account with 1041 Bitcoin wallet. How do I buy stuff?
How do I buy Bitcoin? I need more respect. All right. I can start taking
drugs with me places. This is one. This is, this is 3.9 grams. Let's just like give free drugs away.
Package product, new package, one, one gram. We'll just, it's just free. We're going to give
it to people on the street. So that's free. The marijuana is going to be free. We're going to do
two packages of marijuana. All right. So I've got five free samples. I've got a hit.
Any chance for weed? Two grams. Yep. Let's go. Nobody's, nobody calls me. You know what I'm
saying? That's kind of, that's kind of sucks. This is new message, new message, new message,
new message. There are no new messages. All right. Let's start giving drugs away free on street.
We're looking for people that are walking around and we can give drugs to like you. Hey,
I have a present for you. I have this new thing that people, everyone's into it now. Everyone's
doing this. It's a baking soda. You're putting it, you're using it to clean your fridge. You're
using it to, uh, using it to freshen their refrigerator and the orders and the, and uh,
yeah. Give me a call if you want anymore. Okay. We're good. All right. Where's Chad? Chop. All
right. I got it here. You wanted the marijuana. I've got one of those packs of marijuana for you.
Oh, thanks for saving me there. This is the free sample. Sorry. Sorry about that. Oh,
thanks. Do a business with you. Oops. Oopsie. I'm a dummy. Yeah. Sorry about that. All right.
More free samples. I threw the backpack on the ground. I was trying to throw the backpack over
the fence before they searched me. Where did, where did I throw the backpack? There was money
in that backpack. Does it show on the ground where I threw it? Do I have to buy a new backpack?
Oh, but what about all those free samples? Wait, I walk in and like, and be my own lawyer.
Reload to save. That's cheating. Isn't it?
Did I get respect for getting arrested or anything? Why would you get illusionist
if you'd want him to use it? I mean, that's a great question. I forgot I, that existed.
I forgot that existed in the game. It's all right. I got some samples out there.
Yeah. Respect. Oh, this is fucking break. I close it. How much was my money? I got 290 bucks.
I didn't take any money from my bank account. All I did is they took some
marijuana and some shitty baking soda samples. All right. So I need four grams of speed.
I need three grams of amphetamine. Okay. Now hold on just a minute here.
There's 0.96 a filler test. I'm going to, we're going to get that over here.
Add it. Just mix it all fucking together. Who cares? Who gives a shit? Just mix it all together
and then drag this over here and add it all. Okay. So now, so this is, uh, my mix.
Yeah. New baking soda, new, new, new, new baking soda mix of the mix. Telling you,
you're going to love this one. Two grams of FET. This is fill as shit. Shut up. Three grams,
four grams, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. I need nine grams. What's here? This is five.
I need more. There's two grams in there. Are we going to, I got to
shit. I have eight grams of marijuana. I need more, um, white stuff. Eddie, the red jar. Oh,
wait. Okay. There is some in there. This is one is new made with real amphetamine mix.
Okay. And that's going to go into the new, new baking soda mix mix trying to snipe me through
my window. Okay. So now mix that. So this is the new made with real new baking soda mix mix.
Okay. And I need a little bit more. What else can I get? Okay. That's six grams. How much do I need?
Four, five, six, seven. I need nine. I need, I need to just buy drugs. Do I owe him money?
Everyone's buying this shit. Just get me like 30. Limit 80 bucks. What? I mean $80 limit. What
are you talking about? They lowered your credit. Oh, well, I need this now.
Then I'll pay you here for cash. I have any $210.
I don't know. Where's my backpack? Oh, it's on the ground somewhere. $210.
Okay. I'm holding $210 in my hand. Okay. Fine. What else? What's this in the works? Okay. 25
minutes. All right. All right. All right. Let's go. Let's go. I got it. I got to live this money.
I have nothing on me, right? Just three, just $200 in cash. Let's go and I'll get the drugs.
Come back, put it into the new, new baking soda, real baking soda mix of old baking soda into new,
real, made with real American cheese. So stupid, by the way. Can you believe that?
Can you believe that they have that companies actually write that on a box?
By the way, this is made with made with real cheese. It fucking better be.
There you go. All right. I don't have anything for you. Get out of here. It's a comedy club joke.
Well, welcome. This is a comedy club. Welcome to the show. All right. I need that drop
38 minutes until 38 minutes until I press the T and go to the bathroom. Remember the
Russian radio said to stay in your house. I'm gonna get messages. LMB left mouse button to read.
They don't, there are no messages. It tells me I have messages. It's lying to me.
Backpack idiot. But where's the backpack? Where is it? It's not on the map or anything.
Abandoned item. That's abandoned farm. No, I never get, I'm not getting that back ever again.
Hey, where is this thing? Under the slide. Eddie, did you bury the shit in the ground?
I don't understand. No, it's in the trash. Shit. I don't have. Okay. I have to hold it in my hand.
Oh, this is very bad. I gotta get the hell out of here. I gotta turn this house is right here. Go
on that one. All right. We're good. Let's cut this shit. If you turn the lights off,
they won't think anybody's in here. I'm this fucking thing. Okay. So workstation. Let's add
rug placement. It's 10. What do I need? A nine, right? So this is six, seven, eight, nine. We're
gonna have to do, uh, so put four, put four real in here. Okay. So now there's, now there we go.
Mix that up for real. Real for real. All right. Pack this up. What do they want? Got it. Okay.
We need, we need four. There's only one three. Okay. So we need six and then a three. Okay.
All right. What do they want? It was six, two, two, four, six, right? All right. I got it.
This is dangerous to go out there with just holding it in my hands.
It's police hours, but I can't, I have to, I'll go for it. This is, I get extra respect if I do this,
right? Three, four, two. Wait, that guy wanted weed. Wait, let me look at the map. Three of
amphetamine, two of amphetamine, four of amphetamine. All right. They're close. They're
close. They're close. I'm just going to go for it. Fuck it. Let's go. Emma's literally right here.
There.
Three grams of Noonoo made with real baking soda mix mix. And then Donald's over there.
There's no messages. Oh shit. She's going to rest. Don't, don't tell them it was me.
Run by and say that. Emma, don't tell them it was me that sold those to you.
Okay. Thanks. See you tomorrow. Same time, same place, same amount. Yes, I have it. He wants four.
Go dude. All right. What happened? Where's my respect meter? I did it. I can, I unlock,
I can unlock the other town, right? I almost have a thousand respect. All right. Now I gotta
get the hell out of here. I'm going to unlock East Old Town. Wait, this is East Old Town.
What about your backpack? I know. I'll have to wait till tomorrow. I've got to go to an ATM.
Find backpack. I can't, what do you mean find the backpack? I don't know where it is. I'm just
looking for my backpack. Sir, what are you doing out after hours? I'm just looking for my backpack
filled with drugs that I've cut with baking soda. Oh, and there's like 80 bucks in there too. If
you find it, let me know. Should I file a report for that? And then the cop looks at you like,
what the fuck? And then you go, just kidding. I'm out here. I'm out here trying to find my dog shit.
I didn't have a bag on me. So I, I was like, ah, fuck, I gotta get back out here and find the
dog's shit, which is a pain in the ass. Got to come back with a bag. You know what I'm talking
about, man. And then he's like, oh, okay. Well, it's not funny. I know it wasn't funny. Hey,
can we meet? You available? I need two grams of that weed stuff. Yup. I got that weed stuff.
How much is left in the, in the, okay. That's going to dwindle. Okay. Here's the thing.
I'm going to keep mixing shit in here until it dwindles down to zero. See how it's 0.87?
I'm going to, it's going to dwindle down to, it'll be, finally it'll be diluted enough.
Yeah. Finally it'll be diluted enough to be like, uh, homeopathy, right? I'm making homeopathic
amphetamine. You guys think this is a cop? I've been selling to this guy for like the last two
or three weeks. The less of the drug, the more that it works. Yeah. Eventually I was going to
put this cocaine, this amphetamine into a water, one grain and then shake it up and then sell it
to people. Okay. I need to go give the guy the weed, but I need to sleep. I have $108 in my hand.
Where does he live? He's right there. All right. Then after this, I'm turning it off. I'm not,
no, not turning the game off. I'm turning off my eyes. I'm going to close my eyes and turn it off
and like go to sleep and then wake up tomorrow and do it again. Like I'm going to just turn,
I'm going to go to sleep is what I'm saying. What I'm telling you.
Chuff run. Oh, all right. Have a nice night. How many times have I been arrested?
I didn't have anything on me, man. Ah, it's all right. I made it back. Oh, that's a lot of money.
I guess I can't do that anymore. I can't get caught. Hey, at least it's daytime now. Yeah,
that's true. Um, Hey, you wait. Oh, fuck you. I just got out. You just let me out. I just got
out of jail. You just let me out of jail. Stand still, please. You guys. It's all the two of you
guys from yesterday. By the way, when you booked me, I didn't have anything on me. All right.
That's what I thought. Oh, leave me alone. But you ran. I wasn't running. Let me ran. Did you see
inside of my shoes after that? It was there were hornets in my shoes, like a dozen hornets in each
shoe. And I was freaking out trying to get them out of here. I'm trying to run, crush them on them.
I was trying to crush them running. Please. Hi, how are we doing? I was trying to make mashed
potatoes. Yeah, I was trying this new socks technique where instead of socks, I smear
mashed potatoes all over my bare feet and then put them in shoes. But then, sir, wouldn't they already
be mashed potatoes then? Yeah, they would be. He's running. Old marketplace unlocked. Unlock.
Okay, old marketplace has been unlocked. Emma, I heard that you sell amphetamine.
I need it urgently. All right. Well, how many? I need ganja. Okay. Where it's starting to spread
that I got the best shit in town. I need to reorganize. This looks ugly and I hate it.
This looks this looks ugly and I don't like it. Small jars are going to go up here.
Oh, there's something in that. Okay. Media. There's a medium amphetamine bake. Well,
I got to put baking soda in one of these is important. Okay, draw. Let's put this.
I need to put you in here. Yeah, this is the baking soda jar. Take it white. All right,
the sugar is just going to go up here. How do I move it? I just want to move it.
Why can I not move this? Am I stupid or something? It's too heavy. Lab mode.
Isn't it drug placement mode? Pick up sugar. F. Handle objects switch to lab mode. Okay.
Pick up drug placement. Pick up sugar. Pick up amphetamine.
I'm going to put this in here. It is amphetamine in there. Let's put the mixed stuff in here.
It's 0.87 of the mixture. I can't move this. Yeah, I guess if I press F on an object,
but I can't press F on the sugar. Sugar is too powerful to move. Okay. What do people need?
No messages. Nobody cares. All right, we need three grams of marijuana and then,
hey there, I got an idea. Would love to work for you and help you sell more of your great stuff.
How about that? Oh, this guy wants to hire as a dealer. Yeah. How much is here? You've just
hired your first dealer. Congrats. Dealers order the dope just like any other clients,
but a lot more progressively. Okay. The thing is that they pay up after they distribute,
so take that into consideration. All right. So go get some orders for me, man. All right,
so three grams of ganja and four grams of amphetamine. What do we got? This is amphetamine.
What's in there? Do we have any amphetamines in there? Okay. So what have I got in my mixture?
Okay. Let's go ahead and put this in here. Let's do, yeah, put the six. No, put two, three here.
Now four. Mix that up. That's all mixed up. Now we have our 4.8. Okay, so that's all. That's now
we can mix that. Put that away and let's package that up. We'll put the trash that comes up from
underneath it back into the trash box. There we go. So here's like the leftover fucking gross mix.
We're going to do this until it's gone. Okay. So I've got my amphetamine. Now I need my weed.
It's three grams, right? I can't fit an inventory. Why not? Oh, I need to buy a backpack.
All right. I need to buy a backpack first. Put this in the cabinet. I need money. Let's take out
like, I don't know, a hundred bucks, $142, whatever. I need back. Where do I buy a backpack?
Supermarket, furniture store, drug store. Where do I buy a backpack? Can I like buy,
can I use my bank? I was going to say, what happened to my money? Go to the market. Yeah.
Where was that little, where was that shop? The gas station. I can't go up here. Can I?
See what I can do. Oh, go to the feet lady. All right. And I know like who you're talking
about now. Like I know who you're referring to. Go to backpack store. Yeah. Where was that lady?
He was at the gas station, right? Don't, don't call her that. Listen, I'm not, I've don't,
I'm not trying to. Okay. I need a medium size backpack. 80 bucks. I'll take it. And washing
powder. Ooh, a new recipe. Acetone and salt and ibuprofen. Okay. All right. I don't have that
much money. I can't do that. I don't have any money. Okay. I'm not going to buy that much.
Don't buy the whole store worth. One bottle of ibuprofen, a one bottle of acetone, uh, and then
one of washing powder, and then a bag of salt. I'm going to make a Coke cake. I'm going to try
Oh, I can't take the salt or get rid of the acetone. So new social security payment. Hey,
it was great to see you again. See you later. Social security. I don't have any drugs in here,
right? No. All right. I problem washing powder and salt. All right. What if I make,
can I just buy pepper? Can I just make a dry rub? Why can I just sell that? I'm going to get salt,
sugar, pepper, and like cumin. I'm going to mix it together with no, with no drugs in it.
And it was going to call it like a germ is famous barbecue rub. And I'm going to sell that to
people. And that's what it's going to say in the label. Ooh, me. Who are you talking about? Wait,
I don't know. I have, don't move or we tase you, buddy. Okay. Clean. Go home. Yeah. I got salt
washing powder pills and cash. I just took a random grocery trip. All right. Let's get back
to the house. All right. It's time for a, I'm going to take a pee and I'm going to get some water
and then we'll get back to it. I'm going to make my world famous fucking barbecue cumin rub.
And that's right. Barbecue cumin, BQ cumin, barbecue cumin. It's famous. I used to put it
on everything when I used to grill all the fucking time. Hey man, new order, five grams of speed.
Can you bring it to me? Hold on. No, I can't. Not yet. I have to make my fucking famous world
famous recipe. I bear back eight long shit. I just got like a one of those like oatmeal chewy bars
and I took a bite of it and the rest of it fell down on the ground. I got to get another one.
Hold on. I bit the top of the thing and wasn't holding it hard enough on the edges. Just landed
on the ground around. All right. Let's continue selling drugs. Why can I pick this up now? Okay.
I'm ready. Any chance for speed? Two speed, two weed, four speed, three weed, five speed.
Fuck. Guys, relax. They're talking about bikes. Talking about mountain bikes. I need a lot of
amphetamine. Well, let me scratch that. I need a lot of fake amphetamine. How much weed do I need?
Three? I need five weed. Five weed, nine, eleven. Nine and then eleven speed. Okay. Wait, how much
do I need? I'm so stupid. Five. This is five. Four. This is two. This is five. God damn it. Hold on.
Five speed. Five. Two. Oh my god. I'm gonna lose my fucking mind. Five speed. Four. So that's nine.
Okay. Nine, ten, eleven. I need eleven speed. Shut up. Stop. Rumors. I swear to god. I need
eleven speed and then five weed. Okay. First grade. No. It's just like they're weirdly...
I wish I could have them be in order of what drug they want. All right. Here we go. So this is...
Where's my actual amphetamine? Can I buy some? Okay. Custom drug mix. Okay. Go back over here.
So in here is two grams of amphetamine. Four grams of baking soda. So that's five. I've got
these in such weird places. Okay. Four. Put the baking soda on here. Put the strange mixture on
here. Put the amphetamine on here. This is six. And then put the actual amphetamine on here.
Okay. Wait. This is an amphetamine mix. Didn't I buy... Okay. There's ten here. Didn't I buy
a bunch of amphetamine or did I not do that yet? I didn't buy the amphetamine. No. Right. Because
I couldn't because I didn't have enough credit. Right? Right. Okay. That's what it was. Give me
20. I don't need any more marijuana. All right. That's fine. I don't need to do that in real life.
Let me just drink some water. Two speed, three weed, one baking soda, two eggs. This is a mess
right there. But we're going to use it. We need 11 grams. I don't have that yet. But I'm going to
package it anyways. No. Actually it's three, two, three. Three, two, three, three, three, three, three.
Wait. What actually? What? What actually is it though? It's about five. So that's three,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. What's the actual denominations here? Five.
It's three, six, five, and then... All right. I got it. So five. Somebody wants a pack of five.
And then we need... I almost had it. Fuck. And we need 11s. Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven. So was it three and three or was it two and then three? I don't remember. And I don't want
to go back and look at the fucking laptop again. It was four. Okay. So five, six, seven, eight,
nine, and one more too, right? Drug dealing is fucking hard, man. Hold on. Why can't you
guys just order in one? Okay. You want the bag of five. You want the bag of four. Okay. I have that.
You want the bag of two. So I had it right. Why can't you just fucking order it? I only
sell in bags of five. Okay. Can I just... Can I make that clear? I don't have enough. All right.
Whatever. All right. Let's accept all these on my way. Emma, you wanted the fucking amphetamine.
Okay. You wanted the two grams. That's fine. You wanted... Who wanted four? Who wanted the four grams?
Package is ready. Ganja. Two grams of MJ. Who had the... Okay. You wanted it. All right. Let's
fucking go. I got it in my backpack. Five, two, two. Just make all the bags one gram and dull it out
when you deal. I'm coming. I'm coming with the drugs. I swear. What do you want? What are you
doing? Why are you here? Okay. Go. Let me alone. Fuck. It's a hit man. Wait. I got to go. What's
his name? Jerry? He needs me. Jerry. Jerry. Don't tell anybody. I cut it with baking soda.
What are you talking about, George? It's the biggest scheme. I just realized it. Okay. Hold on.
What do you want? Five? Take it. Go deal. And you. My backpack. My backpack. I found my backpack.
It's there. I got it back. I'm so happy. Yes. Okay. How does it go into my inventory? I got my...
Wait. I have to go. I have to get my package first. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Hey. Stay right there. I
can give you something. You want something? Here. Wait. I've got a present for you. Here. All right.
See you later. No drug dealers ever acted like this. What? Being excited that you found a lost
package? A dig? Oh. What do you want? You want two grams of amphetamine. I have it in this bag.
There's amphetamine in this bag. Why can't I... How do I open... How do I use this backpack?
There's amphetamine in here. Can't put a backpack in items with a backpack.
Swap the bag. All right. Yeah. I'll have to carry this. Wait. I've just seen this shit. Okay. Hold
on. One gram. How much money is in here? I can't consolidate? Put the cash in my hands. Okay. All
right. This backpack... This backpack is empty. Wait. I need to empty this one. What? No. I don't
want to put the backpack in the backpack. How do you fit a medium backpack inside of a small backpack?
Whatever. What does this guy want? He's going to get two different types of products. Wait. I think
this is the cool kids area. Hey, you. Medium backpack. All right. I have one pack of this
gross shit here for free. How can I help you? I want to buy something. Oh. Give me one of these.
Yeah. I'll take two of them. No. I'll take some small jars. Nice. Okay. Cool. Yeah. And then I'll
take a... I'll take one of those medium jars. Okay. Send it to my apartment. Thanks a lot.
Oh, wow. I didn't know you existed. Hi. You the dealer? I am. You were looking for two grams of
amphetamine. Uh-oh. I gave one of those away. And here. Here's the going value of one bag.
Take it. Something wrong? I forgot something. What did you forget? The drugs.
Hey, man. I see that you're selling a... You're selling a TV? Yeah. I'm selling a TV. Cool.
$100 for the TV, right? Yep. That's me. I'm selling $100 for the TV.
Okay. What do you want to meet? Bob's Grocery Store. It's close to me.
Oh, that's close to me, too. It's only a couple of miles away. Yeah, sure.
All right. I'll see you there at 2 o'clock. 2 o'clock. That's perfect for me.
2.05. 2.02. I'm a little late getting up to Bob's Grocery Store. Not here. He's probably
just like at a light or something. And now it's 2.28. Still not here.
Hey, Dan. Are you here? Are you coming? Are you on your way? Yeah, yeah. I'm coming. Okay.
You're still doing this, right? You have a TV? Yeah. 3.45. A pickup truck pulls in. That must
be him. Get out of the car and see who it is. Hey. Hey, you've got the TV? Yeah. Where is it?
It's out of the house. I figured we were going to meet here and then you could drive back to the
house and get it. It's kind of hard to put in a truck, so I figured we could just meet and you
could come back. I don't want to do that. What are you talking about? You don't want to do that.
Fucking asshole. You're an asshole. No, you're a fucking asshole. I told you the TV's too big
to put in my truck. It's a 30-inch TV and I have a small four-door like Chevy Malibu.
Yeah, but just come back to my house. This is a really good joke. I know. I'm aware of that.
Is this a joke or a movie? Is this a joke or a movie? It's just like a podcast, like a play,
like an old radio play. And then the aliens pulled up in the war of the worlds and a nuke
started to fall. This is a movie. I don't know. I was still going. I still had it.
I was still having fun with it. All right, back to... What was that noise? That was like an explosion
in my... What was that? Oh, that was this. Okay, let's go. I have some clients here that are waiting
for stuff. Here we go. Let's put the sugar back here. The baking soda marijuana. Here we go. We've
got 20 grams. Let's put the marijuana up here for fun, just because we want to look at it,
look at our stash. Okay. What is on here already? Some junk. Let's do... Oh, I got my... Didn't I
get my new things? Oh, nice. There it is. I put this. Okay. And then we'll put the jars up here.
Give me a moment. I'm working. Stop. Shut up. I'm working. All right, let's take the salt.
Okay, lab mode. Salt in here. The sauce is already powdered. Oh, well, okay. Let's just add it then.
Now, I want to make a new mixture. Get this out of here. Move this. Okay, salt. 30 grams. That's a
lot. I did like the restaurant dumb prank bullshit joke. Okay. The stupidest... Okay, salt. Sugar.
Crush it up. Can't add any more substance. Why? Oh, because it can only hold 30. All right,
put it back in the box. Put it in here. Just salt. Salt. I want sugar, salt.
But how do you make the Powerpuff Girls? I got to be careful. Otherwise, there's going to be three
extremely powerful mutant teenage girls that are going to fucking be able to... I got to be careful
here. Sugar, spice, and everything. Nice. All right. What are you talking about? That's in the
mill. All right, mill it. It takes a long time. I just like knotted up. 14 grams of salt and then
14 grams of sugar. Salt, sugar, and one gram of cocaine. These were the secret ingredients that
Professor X put into his pot of stuff and he created the Crack Girls. Oh, wow. Did they fight
crime? Nope. Not at all. In fact, just now, they've robbed and killed Professor X.
And the credits just fucking screamed by and there was like 12,000 people that worked on it.
All right, here we go. Let's mix this up. Sugar, salt. This is just fucking... This seriously is
just like a drug rub. Sugar, salt, amphetamine, baking, so should I put some washing detergent in there?
That was a good adult swim robot chicken joke. Whatever. Who cares? This can't be empty. What do
you mean this can't be empty? Oh, there you go. Here is my dry rub. This is 30 grams. Someone's
going to kill me. I'm going to get attacked over this. People are going to kill me. I need to give
weapons. I'm going to be like in trouble. I have 29 grams of the dry rub. Okay, hold on. Wait, wait.
What if I just crush up the ibuprofen and just sell ibuprofen? Oh, what's this? Oh, the sugar.
Right. Put the sugar over here. I don't know. There's only 20. Put this in here. All right,
ibuprofen pills. All right, I'll crush them up. Oh, what? Okay, here, over here. Okay,
ibuprofen and... Okay, ibuprofen. Package it. Oh, okay, fine. Just mix it. All right, ibuprofen.
All right, guys, I can just tell this is a headache cure. You know what I mean? God,
I got a headache. Hey, I've got a headache cure. You do? Yep. Oh, you can cure my headache? Yes,
I can. Okay, well, now I have a lot of product. Let's go get ourselves attacked by a bunch of
people. Ready with the money in delivery. Let me know. Yeah, let's meet. I want that cash.
All right, we need weed. Oh, I'd like to... I got some contacts that could help you distribute.
Yeah, let's go. On it. All right, so we need marijuana. We need five grams of marijuana,
three, and then two. Three, two, two. How much marijuana do I have? Perfect. Not perfect. I need
one more. Ah, what do I? What do you mean, wet substance? Just run it under the sink.
Just hold it under the sink for a second. What do you mean, dry? Do I have to put like...
Well, I have to put it like... Why? Do I have to put it like a soda? All right, whatever. I'll do that
guy later. All right, we're going to be delivering soon. I can do you, and I can do you. You on the
other hand, I'm sorry, but I cannot get it for you. Let's take a look at the inventory here.
Look at all this stuff I got, and I got skill points. You've got it. Okay, I want to do...
We need something better than just illusionist. All right, I'm a pretty good illusionist. Okay,
addict at least five clients to your product. Oh, okay. Dr. Germa. Just got ibuprofen.
All right, first one is we got to go meet the dealer. No police, right? We're good.
How you doing? Are you a stranger? No police. We're good. All right, here we go. You're the dealer.
I do have the dope. You're looking for two grams of marijuana. I'll give it to you. This is actually
real. I promise. Now, if your dealer says, I guarantee you, I promise you, this is real.
Find a new dealer. Or just in fact, don't do drugs at all. Because drugs, you know, why do I
don't do drugs? There's an electric box in here. All right, but you picked the worst possible spot
to meet, man. All right, give me my money. Give it to me. 60 bucks. You can do better than that.
When I was out here fucking dropping, I was making $150 a day. $60. You can do way better than that.
And then change that tie too. And now we got to go to over here to Donald. Here's Donald. No police.
All right, here you go, Donald. One of the three grams. You got it. It's back for me. All right.
So, the question now is, I have to go back to the house. Put this money into my money safe.
Ronald Duck is a quack dealer. Not bad. That wasn't bad. Okay. So, what do we got? What's the
what's up? What's the goal here? 800 respect and you get level six on it. All right. Cool.
You want two grams of marijuana, but I don't have it. I need more marijuana. I need. Yeah,
we'll just do 10 grams. That's fine. Also, how much do I owe you? $190. Do I have that?
Holy shit. What do I have? I have ibuprofen. All right. I got to get the. Wait, how do I take the
backpack out of here? I have to do this. All right. Now I can put this shit away. Put this one on.
There we go. Take the spray paint. Money in here. Take out 190 bucks. Close enough.
Dry rub, cash, ibuprofen. All right. Let's take some ibuprofen out. Why? There's no reason to do
that. Okay. No, let's take it. I'm going to, if I get stopped, I'm going to be in big trouble.
No. I'll spray some paint. By the way, for the delivery. What about the free sell the small
backpack? How? But I can sell the small backpack? Like, can I sell the ibuprofen? But it's ibuprofen.
Yeah. But it's, it's crushed up. I'm probably going to tell somebody. That'd be something. I
know. But that's not illegal to have ibuprofen, but to have it crushed up in a mill? In a baggie?
You don't think there's something wrong with that? All right. There's Eddie. Let's pay him.
What is this one? Good. I've had one new available message. I think for the whole game.
Oh fuck. This has to be a bug. All right, Eddie. All right. Package is there. It's the marijuana.
Where is it? Far away. You're not cool enough. Yes, I am. Hey, come over here,
pal. Oh, I have ibuprofen. I have bad headaches. Are you carrying any drugs or weapons? Yes,
it's ibuprofen. It's a drug, technically. Okay. Now you're fucked, buddy. It's ibuprofen. It's
Tylenol. What did they take? They took the, they took the ibuprofen and they took the money.
Fucking dicks. Do you have anything new? Wait. Okay. Here. This is, I need one of these.
I gotta take money out of the fucking ATM. Where's this shitty ATM? There's not even an ATM over here.
Of course not. All right. Let's go get the package and then go home. I'm waiting for the train.
Oh, what are you one of those hunters? Get out of here, you bastard. That was funny. That actually
was funny. That's the Yarnham. That was funny. That was funny. I know it was. And you can tell
me it wasn't. I don't believe you. It was funny. That was funny. It was very, very funny. I mean,
like I thought it was, I thought it was really good. I thought it was really funny.
All right. Where the hell did I? What? Can I not go in the furniture shop? Why?
I don't have enough respect to go to the furniture shopping. Now take out, take out 500. No,
take out 250. All right. This is the package. You gotta go. No shit. They took it. Right. I was
going to give him ibuprofen. No. Fuck off. Where are they? All right. I'm out. Now this guy wants
the, I think we lost that customer. So here's back home. Shit. You gonna get a bad Yelp review?
I don't care. More spray painting. Please laugh. In quotes. Jerma 2020. I didn't say please laugh.
I said, I thought that was funny. I didn't say please laugh. I said, I thought that was funny.
So how do you know if a door is unlockable? Is there anyone to tell? All right. And now I have
drugs. I'm ready to start selling drugs again. Go with the cops. I've never seen any of these
robbers, violent people, drinking people. Where are they? I haven't come across any of them.
All right. Give me my computer. Package is waiting. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Emma,
I need 16 grams of marijuana. What the fuck? 10. There's one in there. I have 11.
Getting me. Do I seriously need to buy another one? This guy wants two. You want 16. Well,
I need to do another order. I'll just, let's give me, give me 20 so I can have it.
No, you know what? Fucking give me more than that. Give me, give me like 30 so I can always have it.
What? 10. Oh, I have two. 12. What the hell is in all this? There's sugar in here. There's salt in
here. Sugar in here. I need to move these things. It's occupied. I can't move it. Sugar, salt,
sugar, nothing, dry rub, and then 0.84 of the baking soda cocaine crack mix thing.
And then there's one gram of marijuana in here. All right. Get it out here. Take it out in lab
mode. Just give it to me. All right. So we've got 10, 11, 12, 13, and then we have 19 amphetamine.
We have a bunch of our dry rubs in the, where's our dryer? Back here. Yeah. Uh, we need two grams
of grass, two grams of grass, 16 grams. Uh, your drops coming in 45 minutes. I know what to do
about that. Okay. What is this new baking soda mix shit? This is not what I expected.
That's the last text. All right. Two, two. Everyone wants, uh, okay. You want just speed.
You want marijuana. So the plan here is I'm going to bring,
I'm going to get the, this is going to be very, very, I'm going to be, this is going to be bad.
This is going to be very bad. Two grams. So we need four grams of marijuana, three grams of speed,
which we're going to bring our, you know, what we're going to bring. I'm going to bring like
six. Okay. So let's bring, uh, there's three. Activate this workstation. Let's put, um,
it's that bag, the big one, bring this over here. It's just about, I can't cut this. I need
to, I want to, I only, I want to cut this up. Come here. Put it in here. Okay. Now give it to me.
All right. Let's let's like the orders. 16 grams of marijuana. It's in that box. I'm going to bring
it to her. This guy still hasn't done anything. Two grams, three grams of speed. So I need two,
two, and then 16. What do I have now? Two, two, and then I need 16. Okay. I'm ready. Let's go.
Please for the love of God, don't stop me. I'm going to get that fucking package.
This is going to be a disaster if I get stopped. I need two more grams. Do I? Well, I'm going to
get them from, uh, the package. All right. You wanted amphetamine. So here's your drive rub.
He's going to hate this. I'm going to get after a little while. I don't know how much longer this
is going to take for me to get hurt. Okay. The package is right there. Let's do that.
All right. What's that package? Give me the package. Give me, give me, give me, give me,
give me, give me, give me. There it is. That's 30 grams of marijuana. All right. Don't fucking
get stopped. The deal is right there. Holy shit. People are giving subs. I'm sorry. I've been locked
in. Bull myth gave 10 community subs and then tipped over. Just gave five. Thanks for the subs
guys. Also, uh, Fez. Thank you Fez for the five community subs. Thanks all of you for those big
fucking sub drops. Seriously. You need 16 grams. So here's a pack of 10, a pack of two. So that's
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15. Fuck. Can I over give? I'm just taking both. Take two of them. This is not
what they expect. The product must have the expected quantity. Shit. Really? I can't just
give it back to me. Two, three, wait, two, three, four, five, 15. You want 16. No. Oh, something's
wrong. Oh, I'll be right back. Just add one dry rub. She's not going to take it. I'm just going
to do the ones that are already here. They both take over here. Just put some barbecue sauce on it.
Where the hell is this person? What the fuck are you? Wait, what? And where is this? Where are you?
Oh, you weird spot, man. I do have the dope. Here it is. Two grams of marijuana. Oh, all right.
Now I need to go back to the house and cut this shit. This guy's got massive hands. Kind of.
Magically, I have not, no one's attempted to rob me somehow. How has nobody tried to kill me yet?
Okay, here we go. Activate the station. Currently holding eight grams of marijuana.
Please, if you could package up six of those, that would be wonderful. Thank you very much.
Okay. Have a great day. Goodbye. Now I have 10, 16. Very cool. I'm going to store these. I don't
want to bring them all. Wait, anybody else want marijuana? Who else wants a marijuana?
Five grams of, oh, I need five. Yeah, I got it. And I need a five, four grams. So yeah,
I got that dry rub for you. Got it. Bring a bunch. Okay. I'm ready. Let's go. Make them all one gram.
Yeah, but it's fun to do the math that I can't do. All right, Emma, let's go. Take this huge
amount of marijuana and make me some money. Get rid of the extra weed. What if I want to give
it to somebody for free? You know, what if I want to give it a free sample? Is you 16. Oh,
make me some money. You're definitely not a drug dealer. What do you mean? Hey, partner, you got it.
Yep, I do. You want five grams of amphetamine. Here you go. Let me know how the customers like
the dry rub. See what they have to say. Another door that's here for no reason. How many no reason
doors exist? Eventually, there's going to be something in one of these, right? Somebody in
this one though? What I'm doing is technically illegal because it's, but it's only like an
abandoned warehouse. There's nothing even in this. It's all empty. All right, Chop, come here.
Here's your four grams of amphetamine. Take that dry rub. All right, good to go. Back to house.
I'm making some good money at this point. It's technically illegal. Well, yeah, but it's an
abandoned warehouse. What if nobody owns that property? Dry rub only gets you high if you
watch. What do you mean if you watch? All right, let's check our emails. I need some respect.
My average delivery time has been really good. I need to get a level six. I'm gonna wait. Okay,
got some. Let's put the marijuana back in. Let's actually use one of these for not a moron purpose.
Take the salt out. Put the salt in one of these little jars. We'll have salt over here.
Salt. Can I get mustard? Can I get mustard and ketchup? Sugar is right here. Okay, we have
salt. Nothing. We'll move the sugar out of here. Actually, I'm gonna keep the sugar in there. That's
fine. This one's empty. This is gonna be weed. Oh, please. My dealer's trying to sell me ketchup.
Okay. I mean, it's true, but what? Marijuana. We're gonna move marijuana into this jar.
All marijuana goes in here. Dry rub is okay. Marijuana. In. All of it. We can put this in the
bags that we need later. How much does this hold? This holds 40 grams. I have 23 grams of marijuana.
What's in this one? Sugar. Look at all this stupid-ass sugar I have. How many things this
holds? Why did I buy this much sugar? What's fucking wrong with me? Amphetamine going in here. This
is gonna be like pink. Real amphetamine is in the pink jar. Okay, that's important.
I'm just gonna hold the dry rub. Okay, what do we need? Who's got something for me to do?
What is this dry rub shit? You got any more speed? Six grams, dude. What? You don't like my dry rub?
That's bullshit. All right, I'll give him something. I'll give him a real one.
Fine. You'll get three, four real ones and then a dry rub. And I got- how much dry rub do I have
in my inventory right now? So you wanted six. Two, three, four, five. All right, we'll have one more
dry rub. Okay, I'm waiting for another- I'm gonna go sleep after this. Give him dry rub and mustard
sauce. Where is this dude? He's right there. Why is everybody saying end of the stream?
Isn't that the end of the fucking stream? What? Okay, here you go. It's four amphetamines.
And then, look, I'd like you to try it again. Just give it one more try. And then you tell me
if you think it's gross. Did you put it on correctly? Did you put it on before you put it
in the oven or after? Don't tell me you're a fucking idiot and put it on after it came out
of the oven. Is that what you did? Because you must have used it wrong. But I can't give him- this is
two, four, five, six. He doesn't want it. Two, four, five, six. What? Two plus two equals six.
That's two plus two equals four and then five, six. I'll be right back. You don't like this shit,
huh? Fine. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't like it. I don't like it. Oh, that's gross. I don't like it.
Give me something better. Oh, really? Okay. We'll see. We'll see.
Ah, I've got something for you. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the level up as well.
New drug available. Ecstasy. Oh, we check your drug offer. How do I get it? How much is it? New
unlock. Like 10 bucks. I'm never buying from you. You used it. Wait, wasn't that my dealer?
Wait, that was my dealer. Hey, cash delivery. Ah, yeah. Let's take it. I'll get it. New stuff
is available. Ecstasy. Check it out. Oh, yeah. I'll make an order of ecstasy. I'm going to mix
ecstasy, amphetamine, salt, sugar, um, boogers, baking soda, salt, garlic powder, onion powder.
This is going to be my ultimate display. Give me some more amphetamines. All right. We got our
mix. I don't have any drug. Okay. Well, that's $400. Wow. That's a lot of money. I got 500 bucks
and skill points too. Salesman, runner, more illusion. Oh, wait a minute. My character sucks.
I'm too risky. All right. Let's go. I don't have anything on me. Yeah. Let's go get the money.
I'm going to have like six or 700 bucks. Illusionist hasn't worked once.
Sir, stop. Stand still, please. An illusion. What are you hiding?
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money. Excuse me. Do you have any money?
Hey, I got cash. Let me see it. $260. Nice. All right. Let's get the fuck out of here.
Let's get out of here and go. I haven't slept in like three days. All right. I'm going to get back
here and put my money in my safe and I'm going to sleep for like a day. This is a farmer game.
No one's tried to rob me. I feel like my security is not that high. I mean, at this point I have
that I don't like that number. Um, switch that. All right. Eddie in the works. I shouldn't be
more than 45 minutes for the new drug deals. Okay. Yeah. I did these already. It's waiting
for the ecstasy and then we're going to take a nap. Open up your mind. All right. Let's go get it
that far. I don't have any drugs on me. Just have $1 on me. Imagine getting arrested for having a
dollar. I got to pay him to under a rock. I'm not even close. Oh shit. I don't have anything.
I give him some ecstasy. The hell do I get over there? I guess this way. Where is it? Where the
hell is this thing? You don't have to hide it this well, man. I still have to be able to find it.
Open your mind. Yeah. Where? Stop. Leave me alone. Who? I can't even answer your texts.
It's got spray paint on the ground in the vent. Where's there a vent over here? Reception zero.
No perception. Like where's what? Where's a vent on? Open your mind of this vent. It's not even
under open your mind. Liar. Open your mind. Except it's the building next to open your mind. You're
fucking fired. Fire that guy. What is happening? My phone is broken. So I can't tell people spamming
me with messages. Why? You're E fired. E fired. Are these dry rub death threats? Are they?
I mean, it was, I was getting spammed. So let's see. What is this? What is this dry rub shit?
Are you the dry rub guy? Oh, I heard that you sell candy. Hey, they still got amp in stock.
Still got MDMA in stock. Hey, can we meet? I need ecstasy. Heard you sell candy.
Why would you ever come back? I must be the only drug dealer in the state because what is this new
new baking soda mix mix shit? Oh, fuck. Do I really got to hit up the baking soda guy for ecstasy?
I don't know if I want to do that. He's going to give me something that's.
Oh, all right. It's all ecstasy. So this is six grams. How much ecstasy did I even buy?
Oh, we can, we can make it. We can make it last. Don't worry. I got plenty of amphetamine.
All right. What's on here? 1.8 grams of new, new baking soda. Baking soda is shit.
All right. Get this out of here. Put it in this jar. Who cares? All right. Put, we'll do dry rub.
How much dry rub do I have? Can I mix dry rub and ecstasy? Is that going to kill somebody?
Oh, the guy that keeps everybody hates dry rub. Well, it's because it's just sugar and salt.
That's a really bad dry rub, by the way. That was, that's bad. That's not even good.
That's gross. Okay. Let's work this out. Uh, placement. I've got 20 grams of ecstasy
and I've got 10 grams of amphetamine. So, and by the way, I also have, uh, quite a few.
I have dry rubs. Put them over here. Work this out. Oh, look at this. Everybody wants them.
Don't worry. They'll, they'll, they'll have them. All right. For every week, we got to do,
we got to dilute this correctly. So for every, every five grams of ecstasy, there's going to be
one gram of dry rub. So we need two grams of dry rub here. I just got to get rid of this shit.
I got to get rid of it. That's two grams of dry rub. This is, I want five grams of, uh,
Oh, I got to crush it up. Okay. Five. Smash it up.
This item management. Sorry. I have a bad item management. I'm dealing with some shit here.
What do you mean? Stop, stop. Urgent, urgent. Stop, stop. What? What's the matter? This is
eight grams of unnamed mix. This is dry rub and ecstasy. And, okay. This is nine. Let's do,
oh, how much do I need? Six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. They want this 12 grams.
Inted rock. What's here? This is nine and 11. Was that all the gross shit that was over here?
This one. Okay. Now let's mix this up. No, don't say dry rub. Um, no, um, ecstasy. Yeah. It's not
ecstasy. It's ecstasy. That's way, that way I can sell it. Okay. There's my, that's my ecstasy.
Now we got to package it up. Package it just as one grams. I'll figure it out later.
Need 13 of these. Okay. 16 grams of ecstasy. I got ecstasy. I got it. Here we go. And I'll figure
that out later. Uh, God, I hope mom don't come over. How about 20 grams of ecstasy? Emma, you're
an absolute legend. I need six grams urgent. I need ecstasy, ecstasy. What do you mean need
pill press? What are you talking about? I need a pill press. Where do I get a pill press? How
much money do I have? Okay. Put that, put my, all right. I'm going to take, I'm taking $666
at the grocery store and it's all in ones. I need a pill maker. People don't want powdered ecstasy.
Oh, all right. I got to go to the gas station, right? It's not illegal to have $666. It's just,
you, it just makes, it solidifies your act with the devil. Let's go here. Hi, I'm here or you
don't have this stuff. Um, who does have this? Wait, it's the, the drugs. Should I go to the
drug store? No. Wasn't there like a market or something that was right here? Where was it?
At the sewage treatment furniture store. No, not the furniture store. Drug store has it. Yeah,
but I can't get over there. I'm not allowed out. I, we want, why would they locked us in?
Wait, what do you mean they locked us in? All right. Well, there was like somebody that sold
stuff down somewhere in here, right? Some market or something. The old market. Yeah. Yeah. All right.
So I, I got to go that way. There we are. Okay. All right. Where's that lady?
And she right there. She's usually right here, right? All right. Other side, the other side of
the market. What's, where? Oh, you see, she's standing right here, right? Yeah. She's like right
here. Shit. Where is she? I'm just going to stand over here. Oh, I can't. Well, I have to just go
home. She's dead. No, she's not. Both of the checkpoint, both of the checkpoint was $666.
Why would I do that? Do it. Let me, let me deposit my money. I'm depositing $500.
All right. Do you want me to go through the checkpoint? It's not going to give me a,
I can't, how? I don't think I can even do that. Okay. So how do I let them, how do I go through it?
Police checkpoint. Stop. Police checkpoint. Hello? No, I can't do it yet. All right. Well, let me go.
Should I just wait it out till tomorrow? Pick up that can. Sorry.
It's not his house. All right. Staying still for 12 hours. Just go make Half-Life 3. I can't,
I don't have the, I don't have the tools for that. From plus two to minus two in a second.
Is that right? It happens. Sometimes that happens. DMC 2 waiting room. That's an interesting waiting
room. Somebody said, Jerma, I love this Half-Life 2 multiplayer dark RP. I said, oh my God, you're so
boring. What? Cause I'm sitting here? Cause I'm, I have, I have to do this. I have to sit here
during the fucking, what do you want? I gotta wait till tomorrow. Oh my God. You're boring me.
I have to sit here and do this until 7 a.m. tomorrow. Why don't just go get, it's worth me
paying a hundred dollars to just go get arrested. I'm going to bring one bag of dry rub outside
and just put my hands in the air and pay a hundred dollars for it to be tomorrow. I mean, is that,
is that's worth a hundred dollars to me? But no, it's not because then I'm going to get my
bars are going to be fucked up. DEA is going to come get you. That's what I mean. I don't want
to have to get arrested that many times because that bar will fill and then I'll be, I can't sell
my drugs anymore. It's now Wednesday. You just say like the one gunshots. When do I get a gun?
In fact, actually I'm kind of happy I don't have a gun. Respect on the way. What? T. Respect on sale
area is very low. Low respect, negative fixed sales. Make more sales, rent hideouts or mark
territory to regain respect. Who doesn't respect me? Old marketplace. Oh wow. We're losing respect
because I have to sell drugs, but I can't until I get the pill smasher thing.
Maybe it's because you're selling salt in a bag. Yeah. All right. I'm going to start selling real
stuff. All right. No more funny stuff. No more like jokey stuff. Get this out of here. No, we're
going to, okay. I'm going to make real drugs. I mean, I'm going to get rid of them. I'm still
going to sell them, but you know, all right, I'll get my respect back tomorrow. Sell insect shavings.
Stop. I have to do this. FDA approved. I think there's a bug in my hair in real life
and it's freaking me out. I'm about to pull it out. What is this? I think, I actually think this is,
this is a piece of small chocolate from the Reese's that I ate earlier. Oh, that's just gross.
I have to, now I have to clean my head. I think it's an insect head. I think it's an
insect leg. Maybe. Yeah. All right. One in the chat. If you say Reese's pieces, two in the chat.
If you say Reese's pieces, like an idiot, pretty split. Okay. I have to do this. I gotta go. I gotta
go. Nobody likes me. I'm about to get run out of town. Okay. We need respect. A lot of it.
How do I get respect? How do you get respect? How do I get respect? It's sell stuff people want.
All right. I'm going to get you the cleanest shit ever. All right. You still do an MDMA.
I'm not, but you are. Okay. Who wants candy? No, I need the pill crusher. Ecstasy. I need the pill
thing. No, do I actually need that? Can I just bring her, can I just bring it to her and she can
do it? Yes, I do. Respect me. Just give it to them. It comes in pills, but it doesn't matter.
Just get the pill thing. Well, I just tried to, but I have to wait till tomorrow.
Nobody else wants anything else besides ecstasy. MDMA, candy. All right. Let's just, I gotta get
my respect up. Don't bring him dry rub. Bring him real stuff. I just need, where's amphetamine?
Okay. Put this amphetamine into a fucking jar. Where's the amphetamine? Here's the real one.
Package. He just wants two. All right. This is the real stuff. This is what he wants. Okay. James,
two grams of the real stuff. You got it. Put this money away. Just give them the real ecstasy.
You have so much ecstasy in pills. I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna give him the ecstasy.
What, what did I, where, where's the, uh, where is it? All right. Ecstasy. Gonna crush up the,
we gotta just give him, just give him the ecstasy. Wait, if, wait, wait, it already was pills.
It already is pills. I broke it. It already is pills. It's already pills. I think, you guys,
somebody had to get a pill crusher. What? Six. Oh my God. Six. Yes. Urgent. Urgent. Six grams.
Two. Six. Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten. Eleven. Twelve. And then you want 20. You're gonna have to wait.
I'm ready. Let's go. I've got, I got enough. Wait, I have to, do I have to wait? Hold on.
I need to put it in the jar and take it out of the jar. Here we go. Which one of these is empty?
There's sugar in this one. Dump it. No, just deselect it. Um, where's an empty jar? This is
one empty? There's nothing in there. Okay. Put it in the ecstasy. All right. All right. All right.
Okay. Put this in here. Lab mode. No. Lab. Labo. Nintendo lab mode. Nintendo make drugs mode.
Okay. Get it in there. Add it. Package it. Take it out. All in ones. Thank you. Put this in here.
All in ones. Take it out. Let's go. I'm out. Yeah, I have too much amphetamine in my bag. No,
I have enough. Let's go. All right. We got a lot of customers. We got everybody. We're just gonna
run. If the cops try to catch me, I'm just gonna run. I don't care. I have super running.
Number one. We're gonna go right first. Wendy and Chop. Okay. Hey Chop. How you doing? I have
drugs. Um, I have ecstasy for you. And remember, we're under new management now. So, um, if you
could tell everybody, maybe give us a Yelp review. Maybe give us a, uh, thank you. I appreciate you
and appreciate your business. Thank you. Oh, at least even four stars helped. Bye Chop.
Chop. Hi Wendy. Hey, yeah, you want ecstasy. Sure thing. I got it for you. There you go. Okay,
Wendy, you're gonna get a survey emailed to you. Um, if you could take that survey.
Fives across the board will help. Um, make sure you do it. If you don't, it's all right, but do it.
All right. Okay. Thank you. Have a great day. I laugh for both of us, sir. Uh, but we're both
going this way. I both have to go the same way. Fuck. No, I made a joke. No, no, no, no. It took
too long. Get in your house. That's not my house. Where's my house? Throw it. Throw it back.
Fuck. Standing right. I don't have anything. I don't have anything. I don't have anything.
Okay. I think we're good. Throw the bag of drugs. Go hide in the corner next to all the drugs on
the table, which is way more than what was in the fucking bag. Oh my God. My brain is so,
so small. Okay. We good. What the, what do I have? Ecstasy. Put it away. Let's go back to do this.
Two grams. I need another. I need the real stuff. The fake stuff is already in there. Okay. Cash.
Store it. Go back out. Donald, I'm coming for you. What? No, no, no, no. This is not. That's
ecstasy. That's the real one. That's not the fake one. You have a ton of dry rub on you. I don't.
What are you talking about? Oh shit. They're right there.
They're in every corner. No, I'm not going to go home because I have the, it's 30 minutes or it's
free. I got to make it to Donald. Where's Donald? Donald. What do you need? Ecstasy. Six. You want
a lot. Here you go. Six. This is going to be a lot of money. There you are. Have a nice day. Thank
you. Thanks for the 80 bucks. Have a nice night. Now we got to go over this way. Get some sleep.
What do you want? Two ecstasy? Got you. Thank you. Give me that respect. Appreciate it.
And that's the real stuff, by the way. That stuff's real. Just in case you didn't know,
it's not, I'm not, it's not like a just stupid stream joke. That's real ecstasy.
Just want to make sure you know that. What are the ATM? Why? Hey James. Two grams of amphetamine. Hey,
that's mid strong. Oh, here. Have a nice day. Goodbye. More respect, please. There we go. Now
I'm doing a little bit. No, it's not so bad. Okay. I've got cat. I still have ecstasy on me.
Fuck. Have your pockets. Officer, don't worry. What do you got in your hand? Just dry rub.
Look, see. What's in the other hand? It's dry. No, that's amphetamine. I'm going to jail.
Oh my God. Throw the backpack? No, just put it in the backpack so I can just, I can throw the
backpack. Back to the house, which is over there. What? All right. Red car. Red car. Red car. It's
by the red car. Am I in jail? Oh no, I thought this was a prison cell. It's in my house. Red car.
All right. Red car. Any more deals? 20 grams of ecstasy. I don't have that. And I never will.
I gotta get it before somebody finds it. Red car. What's that red car? All right. What's in here?
Drugs saved. Yep. We're good. Store them. And then I need to come up with, I need to get 20 more.
Oh, I want, I want to get the pill thing that you guys are telling me to get.
20 grams of ecstasy. I did, I traded everything. All right. We got, how much money do I have?
410 bucks. One package of dry rub. Blood echoes recovered. Yep. I have a lot of actual amphetamine,
just okay. Don't sell this to anybody until I have enough respect. And get the dry rub out of here
too. Store this, get this, get rid of this. Just keep it in the closet forever until people like
you again. So now I need to come up with, I need to get one of those shipment of ecstasy.
I need money to give you money too. How much do I owe you? 360 bucks. Fuck off.
All right. I just have money on me. Let's go. Yo, house flipper got wild. All right. I'll be
honest with you. Okay. Let's give you the real opinion. It's been about four and a half hours.
It's pretty fun. It's pretty, it's pretty good. It's good. It's kind of fun. Money. Now I get to
buy more ecstasy. Local streamer loves selling crack to kids. None of these people here are kids.
These are all, all of them have been adults and I'm virtually selling drugs to virtual adults.
So sorry. You have, have it wrong actually. He adults give me as much ecstasy as I can possibly
buy from you. Sorry. Fake ecstasy. 50. Give me 50 of them. 50 grams. Yep. This is virtually illegal.
You need 20. I'm coming. I'll give it to you. Can I get this guy to come back?
If I promise him an hour and 15 minutes, that was just a bugleberry.
Okay. B11 and B12. Those are important vitamins. Whatever that means. All right. We'll just go to
the, I'm going to go to that old market, bring some money. I'm going to bring any, well, I say
it takes from my bank account, doesn't it? Take my laptop first. Omega lull. But I do have that.
Okay. I do have that. What? What's going on? Omega lull, omega lull, omega lull place. What?
What's going on? Tell the shit stain story. Wait, what? What happened? Wait, what did, what did,
what did Kim say something? What did she say? Tell the shit stain story. Kim is asking if you want
McChickens. Oh my God. Are you kidding me? If you're still listening, Kim. Honey. Yeah. Oh yeah.
You know exactly what I like. What happened? Yeah. Okay. You ready? Yeah. Oh, the stream is
going to have to end. Oh no. No, it won't. Maybe it will. We'll see how long it takes. All right.
You already got them? Are you here? Are you here right now? Wait a minute. I hear, hold on a second.
I hear rustling of bags and I hear a person. I hear a person over here. Wait a minute. Oh my God.
I just got a legit McChicken delivery service. Holy shit. This is the best day of my whole life.
Oh my God. That's a lot of food in there. I'll be right back everybody. Give me five seconds.
Okay. We're going to go on a quick McChicken break. I'm going to eat these McChickens and
then I'm going to be back in like five minutes. I'm dying dead serious. I'll be back in like three
or four minutes. I'm, I'm very serious. Wait, hold on. Put it up. I'll prove it. I, this is
fucking ridiculous. Unbelievable. I'm so happy. Yeah. I'll prove it. I'll, I'll eat a couple of
fucking classic McDonald's french fries. And you can tell that that crunch was more like a chew
through. Um, that was not crunchy at all. All right. Okay everybody. Don't ever hit the fucking
jackpot. See you guys in an hour. I'll see you in an hour. I'll be back in five minutes. I promise.
Time it. Yeah. I know. Oh, I cracked. Whatever. This is a crack stream. So it's fine. I'll be right back.
Yeah. That's what I'm talking about. You're a little late. It's all right. It's all right.
It was worth it. It was worth. I was getting hungry. You know, when you, you know, when you're
really just starting to get fucking hungry, I was thinking, all right, I'd probably stream for like
another hour or two. See what, maybe I'll see how it goes. Maybe another hour or so. And then what
am I going to, I got to do something for food. I'm going to make some food downstairs because
obviously there's, you can't, we can't really go very many places and somebody walks in like,
like a magic trick. Somebody walks in the door with a bag of everything that you love.
It's like, what the fuck? That was insane. Oh, and it had to be good old fashioned classic
McDonald's. The best, the best restaurant in America without a doubt. I love McDonald's.
It's the best. All right, let's go. Wrong. I don't care. You can think I'm wrong. That's fine.
You're a McDonald's shill. Yeah, sure. Call me that. That's fine. That's the,
you can't beat a McChicken. I don't care. The Big Mac is one of the most classic
fast food staples. You can't be beaten. Sure. But what about the fucking Whopper?
Get that shit out of here. No, they're, they're, they're single from Wendy's. Now get it out of
here. Delete it. Oh, my package is, oh shit. Wait, how long is it? All right, let's go. I have a
package. I'm slowing down. Okay, I have to, I ate a lot of food and now I'm slowing down. Okay.
I have to, we're going this way. The McMagician, the McChicken Magician. He's, I'm slow. I have
to eat a lot of, I have to eat like three McChickens in a Big Mac. You got to slow down. That's what
happens. And I'm slowing down, but I'm good. Okay. What was I doing? Oh yeah, right. Ronald,
right. Ronald McDonald. I love that guy. No, Donald, Donald Rick Model. All right, Donald
McDonald. Let's go. Excuse me. Wait, can I give you something? No. The chicken was laced. You want,
what do you want? What does this guy want? I don't know. Where's that package? Don't look over here.
Okay, there's a lot. There's 50 grams in here. What does that guy want? He wants like five.
Fuck off. For now. This person wants 20. Here you go. How's it going? Here. I got for you
huh? No, break it up. I, no, I don't want to, I wanted five tens. Why'd you give me a 50? 50.
Oh, you gave me a 50. Only want to work in fives. Did I check my upgrade points last? It was pretty
long ago. I'm actually, you know, I'm actually surprised that this many people stayed on the
stream. I was going for like 10 minutes more than that. Oh, you guys stayed. Thanks. Hopefully you're
having fun. All right. Let's get it out on the table. It's a huge bag. Can I anything even hold
50? What's in there? Marijuana. What's in there? Sugar. Okay. It's time just to make like a sugar
syrup. What's in there? Dry rub. Put it in there. Okay. There's nothing, nothing. Salt. Put it in
there. Okay. Cool. Now mix it. I'm just consolidating. Sugar. Okay. Now I need to do
is nothing in there. Please put 20 in there. An ecstasy. So we get blue. In fact, I mean is
pink. What's in there? Nothing. Also put this in here. 10. It's blue. It's ecstasy. Pure
ecstasy. Nothing in there either. You know what to do. I don't have to be the one to tell you. You
know what to do. Nothing. Put it in. Blue is ecstasy. There we go. And then this is the,
can I just like slide this off the table on the rug? Won't pass meat inspection. What does it say?
Yeah. I'll take it in ones. Somebody's trying to talk to me. All right. I'll take it in ones
and then throw the rest of this shit away. Just dump this. I don't even want it. Goodbye. Throw it
to the dump. It's, it's a one gram of sugar. Just put it in the trash. Okay. So now I have,
let's do, let's get the ecstasy out in small doses. I want it. Blue 10s. That's 20. And then
I want the rest in ones and ones. It's too many. I can remove it then. Okay. How much is in here?
10 grams. I want it in ones. Thank you. I want it in ones. I want it in ones and I want it in
writing. I have a lot of, I have a lot of ecstasy now. It's almost there. It's close. I have,
it's close. I almost had it. If I get there, I'm going to talk like that for the rest of the
stream if I can. All right. Let's go. And two grams of marijuana, two grams. I need four grams
of marijuana and then a bunch of ecstasy. You want 20 grams of ecstasy. You want, so 20, we need four
and then, okay. Where's the marijuana? Right here. Take it out. Hey, hey, what about clinks? Thank you
clinks for the five community subs. Appreciate it. Thanks for the subs. Five drop right there.
Yep. Get it out of your system when you have a chance. Get it out now. Okay. How much do I have?
A lot. New sugar mix. I don't need this much ecstasy. I need 20, I need fucking like
more subs. Just came in. Ten community subs from non-descript civilian. Five from putrefashioned
groat clown. Thank you both of you for your insane sub drops and community subs from non-descript.
Thanks a lot, dude. Dude, that's a huge pog moment there. Fucking massive pog moment. What are you
talking about? All right. Let's go. Get rid of them. Go. Don't stop me. Another five from clinks.
Please, please. All right. Do illusion. Is this your card? Is this your card? Oh, it's the king
of diamonds. Oh, I bet you didn't see that one. Yes. And then poof, poof. Be gone with you.
All right. Emma. Emma. 20. Here you go. Have fun with it. That's a lot of respect and it's gonna
be a lot of money. We now have to do Donald who Donald wants the four grams. We'll do the rest on
the way out. More subs came in. Five more from fritz in the house. Thanks a lot, fritz. Thanks
for the five subs. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Those mick chickens were mick edibles. I don't know
the name. They were not. They were very good though. It was perfect. I know people say this shit
and they pretend to mean it, but I really do mean this. I could probably eat a two mick chickens for
lunch every single day of the rest of my life. I'm serious. I'm just telling you the truth.
You want to, um, I don't have any extra. Nevermind. Fuck off. Wait, it's the lady. Functional.
It doesn't have anything. It's a short lifespan. I'm just saying like I could.
What the mick chickens aren't even that, what do you mean lifespan? It's one little chicken
patty with like a little bit of mayo and lettuce on it. It's not like a big deal.
Come here. Here you go. You want the marijuana? You got the marijuana.
What? Oh, that's too much. Sorry about, sorry about almost giving you double.
Why didn't you take it? How are we doing? What does this guy want? What's this guy want?
Two grams of marijuana. Oh, I have that. I can give it to you. Hey,
10 community subs from the chef's corner. Thanks for the more subs.
10 more subs. That's that more hog subs. Thanks a lot guys. All of you got to remember that's
that 10 community subs. That's that's somebody paid $50 to put those through. So that's a lot.
Thank you. There's another 10. Another 10 community subs from non-descript civilian.
Thanks for the 10 fucking subs. And I'm out of drugs, but I have more money. Well, that too.
That too. Also, yes. 10 more from chef's corner. Another 10. Stack them up. Here's another 10
from chef's corner. Thank you. All of you. That's a lot. Here's more five subs. Five more stack
from Royal Dawi. Thanks for the fucking ridiculous amounts of money guys. That's a lot of money.
Thanks a lot. Rack stream. Rack stream. How we doing? You want? I got weed. You got? You want
weed? I got it. Two grams of ecstasy. I got it. See you in a minute. We're gonna do a very quick
delivery here. And I'm gonna take a little bit more. I'm gonna take like, wait, do I not have
any more ecstasy? Am I out of ecstasy already? Oh no. What the fuck am I doing? I'm gonna take
like, I'm gonna take like eight with me because I want to give free samples. He doesn't enjoy
streaming. All right. Eddie. Uh, do I have money for you? 350 bucks. I think I have to take a
withdrawal. No, I, what are you talking about? All right. I got marijuana. I got ecstasy. I got cash.
I'm gonna pay. I'm gonna pay Eddie. Let's go. Is he getting burned out? What are you guys talking
about? He hates it when people sub. What? He hates him. Hate who? What are you referring to?
What are you describing? He must be burned out. If I was burnt out right now, guys,
when the McChicken delivery came to the door, I would have left. I would have been like,
I'm fucking out of here. I got more drugs to sell. Uh, you want two grams of ecstasy. I'll give it
to you. And then who has the marijuana? You do. Is there an ATM right here? No, there's not.
Five more subs on the sub train. This one's from Ratamibo. Thank you Ratamibo for the five subs.
That's another five. Fucking crazy. Thank you so much. Lizard95, not to be outdone,
decides to get $50 right now. 5,000 bits. And they say,
Jerma finally gets a new sponsor and it's McDonald's. That hasn't happened. That's not
real. Sounds like you need these bits more than me. What? That didn't happen. It didn't happen.
But I will just tell you that I don't need to get paid any money just to tell you
that McDonald's is my favorite fast food restaurant out of the big three. Out of the big three. How?
What was that? He just stabbed me with a voodoo doll. What the fuck?
All right. So Burger King's good. I like it. I need to make some. I need to get, uh,
go take money out of the ATM. But thank you Lizard95 for the huge amount of money. That's
$50 you just gave. You just gave me. You just gave it to me. Thank you. I'll take it. Thank you.
All right. I need the ATM. There's only one ATM I can even use and it's by the furniture shop.
Dumb. The big three, McDonald's, Wendy's, and Burger King. The big three fast food restaurants.
What do you think I was talking about? KFC? KFC doesn't do hamburgers. I'm talking about like
the three, like the three big three hamburger restaurants. Uh, oh, okay. No, no, five guys.
There's all this. We already went over the tier system. Five guys does not have like
28,000 restaurants. The big three, the big ones, the big ones, the ones that are everywhere and
every city and every town one mile apart from each other. Burger King, Wendy's, McDonald's.
Another five subs came in from Westeel. Thank you. Thank you Westeel for the five community subs.
Take out 250. Five one guys. No, five guys is on a different level. It's like on a different tier.
Of course, obviously five guys is better than McDonald's, but it's on a different playing field.
It's more, it's like, it's not even in the same, it's not the same thing. They're not the same
restaurants. It's, it's a better restaurant, but it's not in the same tier of restaurants.
It's more, yeah, it's it, but that you can't compare, you can't compare like Shake Shack to
McDonald's. That doesn't make any sense. Just hold on while I give this guy some free ecstasy
because Shake Shack, because Shake Shack sucks. I say that five times fast. Shake Shack sucks.
Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack, Shake Shack sucks. I gotta take my headphones off. Shake Shack sucks.
Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Hold on, I'll get it. I feel like close my
eyes and close my ears and shit. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack
sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack. Shake, I have to, this is what I have, this is what I have to do
to get this to work. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. Shake
Shack sucks. Shake Shack sucks. I got it, didn't I? I got it, right? Um, no, no, no, no. I, I, I love
Shake Shack. I love Shake Shack. I actually really do. I think it's fantastic. Shake Shack's great.
Shake Shack slaps? Shake Shack slaps, right? Does that work? Does that work for you guys? Shake
Shack slaps. Shake Shack slaps. Shake Shack's great. I love, I actually really like Shake Shack a lot.
Uh, so don't, I'm just trying to tell you that was a hard thing to do. Hard thing to say.
I, I really like it. I love Shake Shack. It's like, I, it's probably, I, it's probably the top five of
fucking medium-sized. Not super-sized. Like McDonald's, Burger King, Wendy's, and KFC.
KFC's just fried chicken. What are you, insane? All right. Whoa! What? Oh no. Wait. Throw the
fucking bag. I'm right here. Oh, it's because I dipped around the corner. Uh, 100 bucks. Where's,
where, where the, where was that? Where the, I need to know where that was. There was like
$400 in that bag. Where was that? Who knows? Somebody has to. Where was I? I don't, I don't
remember. He hates bits. Oh shit. 6,900 bits came in. $69. Where did it go? Right behind the house?
So, so, Solaris gave $69. That's fucking crazy. Wait, it was like right here, right? Yes. There's
$420 in there. Good. Okay. Hold on. Let me, come on, Eddie. Here, take some free stuff. Hold on. One
second. Let me pay Eddie. Here we go. Good. All right. I'm in the clear now. Let me get the hell
back to the house. I got a bunch of new clients probably. But Solaris, thanks for the fucking
$69. I say, hey, Jerma, happy holidays. Happy holidays to you too. Holidays? What? Happy
holidays? Happy holidays to you. Have a good 420. Wait, what? What's today? Today is 419. I, I, wait,
I didn't play this game on the right day. It's 419. Oh shit. I didn't even do that on purpose.
If it was on purpose, I would have done it today, tomorrow. Yeah, well, happy, happy, have a, if you
smoke weed, it's recreationally legal and medically legal in the state that you're currently in and
the jurisdiction you're in. By all means, if you enjoy it, do it responsibly and do it privately
and do it in a place where you're legally allowed to do it and hope you like it. Take care of yourself
if it's legal where you are. Have fun. Anyways, I spent, I just want to say thank you for being
the best antidepressant I've ever had. I spent most of my adult life as an isolated shut-in.
Seeing everyone else going insane under quarantine is kind of fucking hilarious.
Like they just can't watch Twitch forehead. I live in Michigan and no one here is taking it seriously,
so I guess we'll, we'll just die. No joke. After I bought these bits, it left me with $69 in my
account. Nice. I'll hope I get away from the train to go by. Will you? Okay. First of all,
thanks for the $69. I mean, yeah, everyone's gonna say nice, nice, right? But it's the whole
lockdown thing and the quarantine thing. It's a, it's hard for people. It really is because
at least for, I mean, I'm talking to just be personally, I like to go do things. I like to
go places. And for people that are very, very, their normal lives are to just be out of their
houses. It is a pretty huge major change in their lives. So, I mean, it's difficult just to say,
well, just continue to stay home. You can do it. It's like, we are describing things that people
have never really ever had to do before. And some people really, really like to be out of their
houses. So it is hard. It's tough for pretty much everybody, but it's necessary. That's the thing.
That's the next part of that. Normally it's shuttered and even I'm going crazy. I think it's
not just, it's not about going crazy in quotes. I think where I get kind of annoyed and sad and
irritated by this whole thing is just knowing that there's a bunch of people that are just,
they can't go to work and they can't do anything. And it's like, you're almost in like this, this
state of complete limbo. And I feel so terrible for those people that have to go through this
shit. Essential workers that have to be at their job every day. They have to be there because they
know how important what they're doing is. It's tricky all around. I really hope we get over this.
I really hope it is something that can realistically in the next few months, hopefully
we can seriously just try to get back to somewhere where we can even leave our houses without just
being in our cars or being able to get out of your car and go somewhere and do something.
Go to work without a problem. But people aren't used to this shit. We've never had to do this
before. This is something we've never had to do before ever. And it's just like, hey, you got to
do it now. And it's like, oh, fuck. Okay. Well, we got to do that now. And people are doing it.
There are, yeah, there are some cases obviously in a lot of, you've seen the pictures. I've seen them
too of like, oh, who cares? We're at stay at home orders, but let's just go to the fucking beach.
Right. And it's just like, okay, what the fuck are you doing? Right. People going out to buy
shoe cakes. Hold on a second there. Wait a minute. Already actively assuming that I,
well, you don't understand. That was made by my mother. My mother made that and shipped it to me.
That's where that came from. What a great mother this guy's got, by the way.
Okay. Mom, I need a shoe. Oh, I got you. Okay. That's it. Mod your mom. Oh, fuck. Time's going
by. I got to pause. But, so Laris, I know that this, depending on what state you're in, I know,
especially if you live in a place like New York, New York is all over the place right now. It's
difficult to know exactly what's going to happen because they have almost, what, 30, 40% of all the
cases are in New York. That's just, that's fucked. We're in a really kind of fucking weird time
right now for everybody, especially if you're in one of these hot zones. So it's realistically just
about trying to just follow the guidelines and hopefully we can get over this and vaccines can
get produced. Everybody wants the same thing. Thanks for the $69. Really appreciate it. Thanks
for hanging out. I know we're talking about some serious, I probably should have paused the game
and put like the music and dialogue on zero. I'm sitting here talking about like, oh, let me tell
you something. Let's talk about this. It's very important stuff. And it's like trains going by,
people screaming at us. All right. Let's go back to what we were doing. And what were we doing
exactly? Oh yeah. We were fucking cutting up ecstasy and putting fillers in it and selling it to
people. All right. Can I clean my office? This is not an office. Yes, it is. Of course it is.
All right. What are my orders look like? Okay. Thanks. Your total debt was $350. I did it.
I got cash. Okay. We're going to need to collect the money from that. We need six grams of marijuana
urgent, eight grams of marijuana, N grams of marijuana. Damn. Do I have that? I do, right?
Yeah, I do. Of course I do. I'm prepared. And we got our money. Make sure I don't have any
bullshit here. Uh, put the cash away. The ecstasy. I'll keep the ecstasy. Give us people free.
Should you take a break soon? Yeah, I'll probably, I'll probably be done streaming the next
like 30, 40 minutes, something like that. I think I like this game though. I kind of want to keep
playing it, but I've got stuff to do tomorrow and Tuesday. Why do I have to have responsibilities
to do? I, that's not, I don't want to do that. I want to sell, I want to sell virtual drugs to
people. Let's go get the money first. Postmates. Um, I can't postmates. I can't postmates my dog
to the vet. That's not, I can't do that. 200 bucks. Nice. Please play this. Wait, finally.
Somebody's calling me. Finally. Eddie, what's up? Hey, expand your apartments in the ghetto.
Expansion like the Roman Empire. Awesome. I just give you stat boosts.
Rent a new hideout. Not yet. Oh, there's a guy. This game is cringe.
Is that a police? Why is there so many police officers here? Oh, there's a hideout here.
Wait, let me sell this stuff. I need to keep my operation going. What did he want? Six grams of
marijuana. That's a lot, dude. All right. Well, what are the, what are the fucking people over
here want some stuff? You're a popular drug dealer. Am I? Hey, what's up, man? Like you can tell that
guy's on drugs. If your dealer jumps the fence like that, yeah, you can probably be aware that
they're probably doing something. Hey, do you want something for free? Hey, how about a package of
good ecstasy for you? Respect is going up. That's good. Hey, James, would you like some marijuana?
Uh huh. Very cool. Let's go back and see what I can do. Yes, please. You didn't say it like that,
but I did. And I'm annoyed that I did. Wrong house again. Oh, fuck. Stupid fucking. I am,
I seriously am the dumbest fucking. I'm a fucking more back in here. All right. Buy a new house.
Mike Byers. Hey, Eddie was supposed to let you know I'll be contacting you. I'll make things short.
I have some apartments to rent in the ghetto. They're all owned by my various companies,
so police can't directly connect you to them. The prices include all the creativity behind it
in my fee. It ain't cheap as worth it. Oh yeah, I'll be acquiring some more of them in time.
I'll let you know if any places are available. Hey, I've got some new places in my offer.
Check them out when you have time. I know it's work not only to storage and lab locations,
but they also constantly boost your respect in their neighborhood. You can use hideouts for
waiting, refuge, and most of them save stations, which can be crucial for your progress. To rent
a hideout, you need to use a bank amount, preferably legal. Ooh, small talks warehouse.
Ooh, this is fine. What about this one? Stink. Small storage building, it's stink. Plus 5%
stink. 6% stink. 3% stink. Okay, cool. Got it. All right. I got a stink. I got a stink house.
Thanks a lot, dude. Nice doing... Okay, bye. Ooh, okay. Unlock new sale areas. Stink. Wait,
I can't even go there. Go test out furniture mode from your new hideout. Oh yeah. How do I get there?
Okay, I need 800 respect. Oh, I'm respected now. All right, let's go to that stink house.
Where is it? All right, let's go to the... Can I even make it to the stink house?
Is there a way to get there? Let's find out. Don't bring a whole lot of money. Wait,
should I bring money for the... All right, I'm going to deposit this money into an ATM.
Sell more fake drugs. I will. Don't worry. I'm going to make it... I'm going to make the best
fake drugs. Why haven't you smoked any rivals? You mean like roll them up and smoke them like a joint
or kill them? All right, hold on. Can I go in here now? Oh, how can I help you? Show me your
products. Wait, I can get beds? Dude, look at this. How much money do I... I don't have any money.
Do I get a bed? Just a couch? No. No, don't. What? What? Show functional only. What are you
talking about? Can be used to place... Oh, this is a drugs thing. All right, I need a cabinet.
I need a cabinet. Order and pay. I need a bed too. Am I not going to have a bed there? 150.
Buy it. Take it. Put it in the stink hole. Whatever it's called. Put it in the stink hole. Okay, then
that's it. Is it there? 300, right? Why is the drug dealer stream set up?
There's not going to be one. Oh, skills. More pockets? Or more stamina? More quick learning?
Stealth? Salesman? Yeah. Would you like some free drugs? Sure. No, I don't have any. Just kidding.
Good day. All right, let's go check out the stink hole. This is it? Did I do this? Where's the...
Do I have a... Do I not have a door? In a hideout, you can launch the furniture by beholding space.
Okay, well, it's a big shithole. Maybe not exactly what I expected, but... Cool. It's important that
you like it, right? Because you like it, don't you? How do I put this down? Anyway, a bit of
furniture and decorations should solve the problem, I hope. Oh, shit. These are stackable.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Nice. Okay. Cool. I haven't... What is this? Oh, the sink.
Hold on a second. Wait, can I actually... Wait, this is the wet thing. Why is there no sink in
my other house? Wait, there is. I have a bathroom. I couldn't... I can wet the marijuana in the
bathroom sink. Who is it? Okay, cool. So now what are my tasks? I have to unlock the new sale areas and
I have to addict five people. Oh, I already went into the furniture shop. I checked out the furniture
shop here. Yeah, yeah. Cool. Nice. All right. I checked it out. How do I leave? That count
is checking it out. Earthquake. All right. Well, there's no save point in there, though.
Imagine buying soaking wet weed. Is that the game? Yeah. All right. I am going to call it here.
I'm going to try to adhere to the rules that I set for myself a couple weeks ago. The rule,
doctor's orders, rules. I have to adhere to them. I have to. If I want to actually beg my body better.
Defunco pop quitter. Fuck the rules. You streamed for eight hours yesterday. Yeah,
I know. I'm not supposed to be doing that. Don't eat McDonald's. You ate McDonald's,
though. McDonald's has nothing to do with my bones. But I want to play this game more.
I want to play this game more. How do I do that? How do I play this game more?
You might have to take a look at it. We might have to do some schedule changing here.
I can't play it tomorrow. I can't stream tomorrow. And then Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, Saturday. OK, hold on. I figured out what the mystery game is. It's 420. I did play it on
420 Eastern time. Listen to me. This is important. OK, you ready? So, I'm going to change the
schedule a little. We're going to play. This is the mystery game because I want to play this more.
The mystery game was supposed to be on Friday. But, excuse me, the mystery game is moving to
Wednesday. So mystery game is going to happen on Wednesday. Thursday is going to be the movie
night. Friday, no. Thursday is going to be... How am I going to do this? Thursday will be
community content night. Friday will be movie night. Saturday will be Easy Bake Oven. I think
that works. Movie night makes sense on Friday night. That's a good time to do it. And then
Saturday is Easy Bake Oven. Yeah, that works. What about Saw the Game? Yeah, I want to play
this again, though. I'll have a couple glasses of wine on movie night. Do Saw on the next mystery
game. I have it. I just can't find a reason to play it. All right, so that's the plan. We're
going to come back with this in a couple days on Wednesday. And then we're going to do it on
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday. And there's a lot of shit to do this week coming up. That's
the plan. That's what we're going to do. See you on Wednesday. Thanks for watching, as always.
Had a lot of fun. That's why I want to play it again. Take care of yourselves. We'll see you soon.
Save the game. Yes, I will. I'm not going to play even one second without you, I promise.
So we'll see you tomorrow. No, not tomorrow. I'm so dumb. We'll see you on Wednesday.
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday. Hey, the chef's corner. 10 more community subs.
That was that make like 50, 60 tonight from the chef. 10, 20, 30. That's 35 community subs.
You have to do force 20. No, I did on 420. I played it for 30 minutes on 420. See you
guys in a couple of days. Thanks for watching. Much love to you. Get some sleep. Fix your
Reddit room. Don't worry. I'll rearrange it and make it look even better. See you guys soon.
Thank you to the chef's corner. Not only for your insane monetary contributions
through the course of the night with your huge bits and your huge community subs,
but you also gave $10 earlier as well. Find your webcam mic and peek it right now.
No, I can't do that. Okay, I promise. There you go. I peeked it. I peeked it by smacking into
you. All right, listen. Unlike the 30 webcam stream, I'm going to try to break one of the
webcam mics as hard as I can. I will put my mouth... I'm going to just scream in the room
and there'll be 30 different webcams screaming all at different delays. I promise I will do
that at least once. Plus, we got to plan that one out because I'm soon here. I'm going to start to
try to do the process when they come back in stock to buy them. Remember, we're talking about
I'm going to do... I'm going to fight... I'm going to have a brawl in the room. I'm going to fight
myself with 30 different people. I'm going to chop myself up into at least 20 different pieces
to do a puzzle. Put myself back together again. I'm going to try to have a conversation, a full
conversation with 30 people. It's going to fail. Oh no, it will not. It's going to work out very
well. Do a concert. Yeah. Do a full singing concert. You did the webcam delay joke. Yeah,
I know, with the top rope. I was with two. What happens when you add like 15 more combatants?
All delayed at different times because you can delay a webcam on OBS by like a full,
almost a full minute, two minutes. Maybe more than that. It's going to be crazy. Yeah, I will.
Jeff, I will peak it. I promise. Sticks Renegade, thanks for the 250. Hey, Jerma, thank you playing
Jackie Chan Adventures as the mystery game later this week. Oh, mystery game is going to be not a
mystery anymore because it's going to be crack crew. What's the, what's this called? Drug dealer.
I don't know what the game's called. Thank you. Sticks Renegade for the 250 and another 250.
Sorry. I mean stunt master, sir. Canine. Thanks for the 250. Toon town is a dystopian future
where the tunes are in a constant struggle with the humans for their civil rights.
The humans created the cogs as a means to gather tunes to work in slave camps on the surface
that the humans used to proliferate their existence. The actual lore kind of fucked up.
LM man, thanks for the $5. Jerma, I'm only giving you these bits so I can call you out.
You were an inspiration to us all and now you are nothing more than a greed infused drug dealer.
No, it's fake. It's all, it's all, it's all, it's make believe. It's like when you used to go
hang out when you were a little kid and make Play-Doh food. That's what this is. This is my
Play-Doh food. It's just Play-Doh food. There's nothing else. Big Mama, thanks for the $15.
1500 bits from Big Mama. This is great. I love drugs and crime. Well, I hope that's not true.
Thanks for the $15. Real doll, thanks for the $5. Two things, Jerma. Okay. One, marijuana was
originally spelled with an H, but it was replaced to a J so it will be more associated with Mexican
immigrants. Two, how do you feel about the lack of proper bots in modern games, particularly
shooters? What do you mean the lack of bots? Like when you play CSGO versus like Bot Bill,
Bot Frank, bot, as you mean? I think it's because so many people play them now.
Why program bots when you have a shooter but people are just going to play it anyways?
I think too many people play online shooters now. Where would you put bots in like a Battlegrounds
game? Unless it's like PUBG mobile. I mean, you could do like an offline mode, I guess, maybe.
Perfect Dark had awesome bots. Perfect Dark also had the best weapon in any game.
The one where you could shoot and see through walls. That was the worst thing ever. And it
was an instant kill. I remember getting so angry and being so happy when I had that,
but when I got killed by that, it was horrible. Yes, in the original Perfect Dark for Nintendo 64,
the weapon was called Farsight. And what it did is it let you see through every wall
and thermo outlined every other player. And you could shoot through every single wall.
You just had to target them and kill them instantly. And it was in the game. Yes.
Anyways, thanks for the $5. Hey, Omni Cash. Thanks for the 300 bits. The first time I
catch your stream and this is what I see. We're just making Play Doh hamburgers.
And I ate a couple of Play Doh hamburgers earlier, so it's all good.
Omni Cash again, $5. This should be enough to buy some whipped cream.
Still though, I can't believe none of you guys got, like did that.
That's like, I can't, that's bonkers to me. Not even one time when you were like a kid or anything.
Mr. Lester. Thank you, Mr. Lester for the $5. German never been able to catch a stream till today.
Nice to hear your voice live. We are live. But hey, welcome. Thanks for checking out the stream.
Hope you liked it. Thanks for the $5. Dark Soul. Thanks for the 250. Hey,
made a really great stream and hope to see you return to VR one day.
You will. And the VR is going to be way better. Because I'm going to have a better space for it.
I'm going to have probably two, probably two times more space when I set it up.
So instead of being in a small little office cube, I'm going to make sure I'm in a bigger room.
Not a Reddit room, but actually the Reddit, you know, this is, this is accurate. The Reddit
room is bigger. I have a much bigger Reddit room now. I'm able to do it. So there'll be more. I'll
be able to actually, remember how, how many times I'd be like, what the fuck is, I can't even,
why is it not tracking me? Oh, fuck. Is that the wall? That will not happen. I will be able to
full stride, walk around like a dickhead, looking forward to it. But yeah, we will return. If you
ever do go back though, if you ever set up Skyrim VR properly, you can get porn mods and make
everyone think you're playing Skyrim, but no, it's porn. I'm not going to get porn mods. I would get
suspended from Twitch. They would remove me from the platform. Vimthral, thanks for the 300 bits.
This one's going to be hard to read. This one's going to be very hard to read. In fact, I'm not
going to read it. It's just fucking weird. It's, uh, it says, no drug man. Don't put your feet in
the mash. Ha ha ha. Your feet will get so sticky and gross. Ha ha. The mash will, yeah, it'll grow
on the, at least on the, on their face. What? Okay. Thanks for the three bucks. Anonymous
Cheerer, thanks for the 250. Just anonymous. Mitchell, thanks for the five dollars. And once
again, this shit is fucked. Thanks to the drug grub girls, the drug grub, the drug, the drug of
girls. Oh, the Powerpuff Girls thing. Right. Right, right, right. Hey, S10, double the update, slow
update. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jeremiah, I love this Half-Life multiplayer dark RP. I read this
earlier because I thought it was funny. Anyways, glad to see you again. Not sure if I'm stepping
out of line here, but I would, I'd love to see you play Bioshock 2 on stream. The personal
favorite of mine. I'm just glad to watch you again. Peace and love. Uh, I've played through
Bioshock Infinite. I watched somebody play through all of Bioshock and Bioshock 2 did not exist in
my brain. So that's the one that I had not actually done or seen. People say that's the good one,
right? Although people say Bioshock 1 is more storyline wise is actually more interesting
versus Bioshock 2's gameplay improvements. Am I correct here? Just making sure I got it right.
Uh, but yeah, I mean, I'm not, I can't say I wouldn't. It's a fantastic series. The series is
great. Eventually. Yeah. Still have to play Doom, but I probably never will. Mitchell, thanks to the
$5. I figured this game out. You're a synthetic human made specifically for the purpose of being
an expert drug dealer. That's why the only dealer and why the cops are only interested in you
and why the inventory screen doesn't show your face. You become good enough and are released
and they move on to the next sin. That's an interesting theory. LM man. Thanks for the
250. German. Have you ever played Heavy Rain? Um, we've gone over Heavy Rain a few times.
I know everything about the whole game. I know the whole story. I know the spoilers.
I know how it ends. I know how it begins. So I only really like to play games on this stream
that I don't know anything about unless it's one of those games that I love so much that I
want to show you guys because I like it so much. So I won't be playing Heavy Rain. There's a lot
of games that I won't play just because I already know the whole thing. I've already played it before.
I like this stream to be, uh, genuinely things I've never done before because it makes it more
interesting for me. Like Beautiful Joe. Yeah, but that's, I, but that falls into the category
of things that I really love and wanted to show you and that backfired. So that falls in that
category. Binding of Isaac? Binding of Isaac is a game that it's different every time. You won't see
the same thing every time when you play Binding of Isaac. It's a different game every time. That's
the nature of the game. Next question, please. I mean, false. How is that not true? No two Binding
of Isaac games are the same. They can have very, very close similarities, but you're not going to
get the same exact experience every single time. That's one of my favorite games. Don't you dare
make fun of it? Uh, let's show the credits. I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to bump you
right in the face here. I'm just warning you. Here it comes. Just watch out. Play No More Heroes 2
already. Jesus Christ. A lot of twos that I have to just be happy that we actually played Black and
White 2. You know what I mean? Like that's another two that we did at least. I need to play Mario
Galaxy. I don't know. Why am I going to do anything? I want No More Heroes 2. Who's the artist
that made this for you? That would be Blordow. Very, very funny. Very, very, very, very talented
person. Got a great style. He's got a really, really unique way he does everything. I mean,
I've known each other for a very long time. It's great. He promised Patapon. Yeah, I almost
promised. I, I, I, I promised I was going to eat a shoe and that happened in like three months
after I said it. A promise is still a promise if it does happen. He promised Toontown. And you're
going to get Toontown. Just not right this second. He's an eternal liar. Fine. Just keep it like that.
I'm eternal lying. Hey, thanks. Dark Soul for the 250. Cheesecake Factory Smokehouse Barbecue
Burger is great. Also, Five Guys sucks. It's like $13 for a bacon cheeseburger and you may as well
get a diner burger or restaurant takeout burger at that price. I, I, listen, regardless of how you
feel about Five Guys, the restaurant's quality is better than McDonald's. It just is. The restaurant's
quality is higher than McDonald's. That doesn't mean that, but they're, they're completely
different restaurants. Cannot compare. Five Guys and McDonald's, they're doing completely different
things. One of those restaurants has an incredible huge menu of tons of different things. McChickens,
cheap. It's, you know, is it like the greatest quality? I mean, not, probably not. No.
But it's good. It's food. It's hearty. It makes you feel good. You feel, well, after maybe six or
seven hours, maybe you feel a little bloated, but if you eat too much of it, don't eat too much of
it and you'll be fine. Versus the other place, which is expensive, great. The hamburger quality
is very good, but the points get knocked off a little bit when they give you the bag of,
of just ground, essentially julienned up potatoes in a bag that weighs like six and a half pounds.
I'm not a fan of the Five Guys fries at all. It's, they're just like, they're just,
just sliced up potato pieces that they just stuff in a bag and it just weighs the bag down in the
bag. It's all heavy and like oily on the bottom. And it's just a potato-y, I don't know, they don't
like them. They're very potato-y. I like my French fries to be shoestring. I like them uniform. I
like them to be able to be pushed in, folded and crunched in my mouth. I don't like thick,
I hate potato wedges. Let's make that clear. I don't like thick potato wedges or thick cut
potato-y fries. Potato wedges don't do it for me. It's too much starch, too like mushy and
starchy in your mouth. No, not for me. Maybe for you, not for me. But what about waffle fries?
They're incredible. The skin, the skin of potato wedges is like Reese's paper. I didn't say that.
I did not say that. Somebody else did. So you can be mad at that person, not me.
That's fucking hilarious. I'm going to use that from now on. It's very good. That was like a solid
like 8.8 out of 10 comment. It's like Reese's paper. Oh, potatoes are gross. Yuck. Anyways,
8.7, 8.9. I don't know. What did the Hulk get? 8.9. I thought Hulk got 8.8. Now that I think about
it, I don't really like potatoes. I really kind of just don't. I remember. This is a real story.
Are you ready to get the truth here? I remember ordering HelloFresh. HelloFresh is a subscription
service for food. It seemed like, oh, this is interesting. Let me, let me, let's try this.
Yeah, that sounds good. And it was Kim, I, it's Alex. It was like, this sounds like a good idea.
This makes sense. You know, we can just have food here. We can cook it and it just gets sense.
Whatever. We tried it like other people have tried in the past. And every meal, almost every
single one, at least seven out of 10 of these meals all just had fucking potato chunks
for their side. It was like, oh, hamburger and potato chunks.
How about this green bean casserole with potato chunks on the side?
Steak with potato chunks. Salmon with potato chunks. And it was like, this is fucking stupid.
I want, I don't want to eat like, I don't want to eat like home fries with every single meal.
Why are you not eating rice? What are you talking about? What? I don't want, I don't want to eat like
potato cubes every meal. Does that make me weird or crazy? No. What?
It was like five or six out of 10 meals were just potato cubes or potato wedges, potato cubes,
potato wedges, home fries, potato cubes, potato wedges, potato fries, potato, potato, potato.
And that's not even why I canceled it. You know why I actually decided that we, that we weren't
going to get that service anymore. And this is real. This is, this is, this is like a review.
This is a review of that service, although this is like a year and a half ago. So don't take this
review that seriously, I guess, because maybe they've changed it. Packages would be fucking open.
Like we'd get meat sent to us and like one of the packages of meat would just be
fucking open and like leaking. Like, okay, great. I throw this in the trash now. Thanks a lot.
What's the best restaurant in Vegas? That's Hash House. I'll go with the link
or Carson kitchen downtown and a fucking refund. I just was like,
look, you know, okay, let me just tell you, let me be very, very clear. It only happened
maybe like three or four times, but on the third or fourth time that happening, it's like, all right.
No, thanks. Don't want to do this anymore. So, you know, you get like three strikes in my opinion
with something like that. Goodbye. This is my opinion. These are my opinions about real opinion
of some of these food services. This has really happened. I've really made a phone call and really
talked about this and really said, Hey, please cancel. Cause I don't want you to send me food.
That's just fucking open. And they were like, okay. I was like, okay, bye. Thank you. Remember
your opinions are as consistent as your schedule. I don't have a schedule. So that's fine. What
schedule are you talking about? The one that doesn't exist. So it doesn't matter. All my opinions
are my own, right? By the way, um, why do people say that? Like if you, okay, if you work for a
company and it's like, by the way, it's one of the, you guys know my opinions are my own.
Like, what are you, what did, did, did, did BNB realty not sanction you talking about how, um,
like you shit your pants today. They like tell you to say that they can say shit and not get fired.
All my opinions are my own opinions. All right. But isn't that, isn't that just true anyways?
I thought you were ending. It's also pertinent to if you serve in the military. That makes sense.
They're saying that their opinions are theirs and not their companies. What if their companies
are not in their biographies? Okay. What if you, what if you're just like, Jake Stevenson is my
Twitter profile. I don't, I don't tell you who I work for. Just that's my, that's just my profile.
Just Jake Stevenson. People are going to find out who you work for and then
tell Ashley employer if that's what they covering the trail. Do you not know this? No, I like,
I know. I understand like why, but like at the same time, I was always thinking like, wait, isn't,
if your opinions aren't your, you have to say that a company, a company is really that annoying.
Jake, German, nine, eight, five Stevenson. Hey, don't talk about the perfume you bought.
It's me from B and B realty. What did you say? Let me look. You better tell people that I wasn't
me that said that. No, it's not because it's not you. It's me saying it. Are you sure?
But people, people say that I said that. No, it's my, it's my, it's my profile and my,
I'm typing it. I have my eyes on you. Jake, by the way, you're working on Sunday.
Fucking asshole. That was a state farm joke. Wait, they, what? Hey, wait, that happened.
This happens in a state farm commercial. Anyways, thanks. Who, I don't know. Who even said that?
Who told me that? Somebody said that. Who said that? Why don't we just talk? Why are we talking
about that? Who said that? Oh yeah. Potato, which is a gross. That's it. There you go.
Opinions are my own. Opinions are my own and not representative of the German nine,
eight, five enterprises. But guess what? They are. They are. Cause that's, it's me too.
I like potato wedges. You little fuck. Delete that tweet. Hey Art Vanderlay. Thanks for the
$5. I'm watching this stream from work right now. I work in a first responders station.
I've been pulling 60 plus hour weeks and your stream is helping keep me sane and less stressed.
Thanks for that. Thanks for doing what you're doing. What you're doing is exponentially more
important. Thank you for the $5 and thanks for continuing to do that shit because it can be a
lot. No, it's not for Tony. Thanks for the $5. Hopefully, hopefully you can get a break soon
from all this. Take care of yourself. Crypto. Thanks for the thousand bits. Hi,
Jerma. A friend told me about you a year ago. I've been watching your VODs ever since.
Sorry, I ate two or three McChickens and a Big Mac in like fucking eight minutes.
Give me a minute. Wait a minute. Did it happen? Is it there or no? It almost happened.
Jerma, a friend told me about you a year ago and I've been watching your VODs ever since.
Haven't, God, haven't been able to watch you live because of the time zone difference.
Been meaning to donate for a long time. So here, feed your love for McChickens. Funny you bring
that up. Well, that's funny you say that. Um, I will. I will. Chef's Corner, thanks for
10 more dollars on top of the hundreds today. Thanks a lot. Love you all. Hope you all survive
this crazy quarantine shit. Have a good night. Right back at you. Thank you so much, Chef's
Corner. Appreciate it. Let's show the subs. Show them. Did they come? Roll them. These are all the
community subs, all the regular subs, all the long-term, new-term, everybody. Thanks a lot,
guys. This ungrateful streamer hates donations. Why does everybody capitalize hates? Why can't
you lowercase it? Makes me sound bad. No, but thank you guys, seriously. All of you. All of
your subscriptions. You don't have to do it. You're never obligated to. But a lot of you still do,
so all I can say is thanks. AppleShift, thanks for 250. Hey, yo, have you ever played The Last of Us?
It's pretty dialogue and cutscene heavy, but I just played it for the first time last week.
It was so good. I'm bummed that the second game is delayed indefinitely, though. I have played
The Last of Us, although I've never finished The Last of Us. The Last of Us sits in that same category
of thought of war, where I put more than probably 10 to 15 hours into it, maybe got to about the
40, 50, 60 percent of the way through the game, and then stopped. It happens twice now. Three
times or so. I did that, and that happens more than that. I do that a lot. But yes, I have played
The Last of Us. Very good. God of War was awesome. It was hard to just sit down and play it. Not
because the game was any bad, but because, I mean, it was the first hour of God of War for PS4.
That's one of the best hours of any single game I've ever played.
There's no question. The first hour and 30 minutes of God of War has to be up there in the top five
or like best first tutorial plus zones, areas ever. Only the one hour and 30. No, I played for like
15, 20 hours. I got to like the halfway point or something. Dr. Clay, thanks for five dollars.
You mentioned Perfect Dark. I really do miss playing that game. The frame rate was terrible,
but that game was so ahead of its time. I remember playing Combat Simulator all the time with my
bro and friends. Good times. Fist Sim was the worst. Always punching and making you dizzy.
Sorry you got the frog tonight. Yeah, no, Perfect Dark. GoldenEye and Perfect Dark. I used to play
with three other friends on a probably 19-inch CRT TV, and each person had a fourth of the screen.
Those were the real days, weren't they? Those were the days. Okay, Grandpa. That's fine. That's fine.
Call me Grandpa. Call me Mr. Boomer Man. Whatever you want to say. That sucked. It was horrendous
sharing a fourth of a screen in a game that ran at 12 FPS. Barely when we can have our
own goddamn screens now and have fidelity of like 4k and have the internet and have a thousand
thousand fiber connection. God, the old days were terrible. These new days are so much fucking better.
Holy shit. Usability, accessibility. My god, how bad was it back in like the fucking early 90s?
But I still loved it. It still was the most fun thing at the time. It was amazing. I loved all
my time. And those are some of the times when games, the pavement of the gaming roads that you
drive on today were paved back then. Every game system that you think is cool, everything that
you like, the road was paved. You're driving on that road now, and that road was paved
15, 20 years ago, 30 years ago. It's a great road. And that road, by the way, has no,
there's no potholes. There's a few potholes on that road. You can avoid them though. Just like
slowly, you know, go slow and don't run them over. It's still a pretty good road.
Fucking fantastic analogy. God, you're fucking so good. Dungeonist, thanks for the thousand bits.
Remember, the lockdown in New Zealand is extremely strict, so I haven't had takeout for over a month.
McDonald's McChickens with extra mayo is my favorite food, so fuck you for getting my
favorite food when I'm starving. But seriously, thanks for being my source of vitamin J over the
lockdown. Love you, Jerry. I'm really sorry to hear that. I'm sorry that everybody around the
world, especially in some of the places that have really, really, really heavy lockdowns, because
yeah, around here, the orders are in place, but takeout and delivery is still, without contact,
you know, is still available. So I can't even imagine locking down even more than that.
It's probably so fucking hard. Stay with it. Hang in there. I hope the best for you
and everybody in New Zealand. Hopefully it's over soon. Take care of yourself. Thanks for the 10
bucks. Peaceful Haley, thanks for the 250. Stop talking about Hash House or GoGo. I'm sick of it.
But what if you found something that was the best thing you've ever had? What if you had to tell
people? You need people to know of this thing that's the best thing ever and people need to
be told. They need to know. No, that's not to do with sponsorships. That's to do with the truth.
The truth. No money exchanged. No rules or guidelines of what can you say about this or that.
No, just the truth. Hash House or GoGo at the link. Just the truth. Best. Best ever. Best in the world.
Best in the world. You need to spread the word of it. I do because I sat there for the first time
and I took one bite and I said, oh my god, this is the best food I've ever had in my whole life.
I have to tell everybody. People have to know if they come here, they can do this too.
Truth. When you go to Hash House or GoGo and you get that blue cheeseburger,
tell them that you came there on your own because they're not going to give a shit that I said to
go there. Hey, I want the blue cheeseburger. Okay. And by the way, German985 sent me.
I don't know who the fuck that is. Oh. The blue cheeseburger? Yeah, yeah, that's what
they are. All right. See you in a minute. You've made this joke. My cover. I'll blow my cover.
There are people here weeks ago or three years ago. There are a lot of new viewers.
Lots of them. Do not blow my cover. About that, he's trying to make people aware.
Thank you. Fucking weird Bernie Sanders, Larry David thing in my head that came out of there.
I appreciate that. And they need to know that people do need to be told. What happened? Oh,
Holly. Holly, thanks for the three dollars. The best restaurant in Vegas is the Omelette House.
Fight me. Omelette House. Don't get angry. I know you're going to get angry. Just slow down.
Hi. So, Omelette House. Yeah, you think that is? Don't do anything quick, but slowly. Back away
from your computer. Back away. It's Omelette House word. I need you to recite these words coming out
here for the next two seconds. I need you to say, I respect. I respect. Your opinion. Your opinion.
But. But. I happen to think. I happen to think. Hash House of Gogo at the link. Hash House of
Gogo at the link. Sucks. Because the restaurant sucks. Sucks. Because, wait. Wait, what happened?
No. Bring the prompting back down. Hash House of Gogo is a good restaurant. Omelette House is
all right, I guess. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. The best restaurant in Vegas is Hash
House of Gogo. Easy Measy, thanks for the $5. Yo, Jerma, missed the stream, but I've been watching
you since TF2. Hey, welcome back. A funniest, weirdest, and most humble streamer I've ever seen.
Never change, big man. Oh, man. I had no plan on it. Thanks for being around since TF2.
A long fucking time ago. Hey, Jerma's left foot, thanks for $3. Will one of those 30 cameras be
pointed at your feet? No. And if they do, I'm going to wear three pairs of shoes.
Thanks for the $3. Hey, an anonymous gifter, thanks for the five community subs. And Jizu,
five community subs as well. Thank you, both of you. And then finally,
I didn't even run the fucking credits. Yes, I did. You did. I was there. I did? Yeah, I did.
But you did? Yeah, because you didn't do it. You're too busy talking about, whatever, drugs.
Oh, well, thanks for doing that. Appreciate it. Anytime. We're going to bed now.
All right. Good night. Good night. See you tomorrow? I'm not going to be here tomorrow.
Okay. See you when you come back. Probably next week. Okay. Good night. Who am I talking to?
My mom was texting me, so I had to call her back. Saying good night to my mom.
Jerma lied about Morrowind, thanks for $2.50. Hi again. Jerma lied about Morrowind multiplayer.
Yes, I did. That was a lie. That was a full lie. Not even a jokey lie. That was just a lie.
See you on Wednesday. Have a great rest of your night. I would say have a great rest of your
weekend, but it's over. Have a good start to your week. We'll see you midweek for more drugs.
Sounds weird to say that, but then that rest of that week is going to be weird.
Good night. Goodbye. See you real soon. Take care.