I have returned. I'm back. Hi, how are you? Good day to you. Safe track. Hey, I'm the Warcraft guy.
You remember me? I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. NPR Andy. Yeah, that's really cool. And I did not
ever think I was going to be on NPR, but here we are. Crazy. Disney. Oh yeah, I've been all over
the place. And I'm not done either. There's a few things coming up here this, I want to say next
couple weeks, that there will be, you'll be able to see. Also, official planning of the Battle
Act stream is officially underway. I'm going to prove that once and for all. You'll see that
sooner rather than later. And today we are going to play Scorn. I've heard things about this game.
I've heard this game is not what everybody thought it was. I've heard this game is amazing.
I've heard it's like, it's an incredible experience. I've heard it's not what they,
somebody was expecting. I don't know. You're going to rage at this. I mean, I don't know.
It looks creepy. It looks cool. I'm into it. I'm ready to see like how cool it's going to be,
how scary. I saw the same trailer you did. Raid someone? I just turned my stream off at the first
time for like two weeks. But I also got something to talk about too. So you guys are going to get
something here on this channel. This kind of end of the week here. You are going to get three
streams in a row. It is Omega Gaming Weekend 2. But the only difference this time is it is a
contractually obligated Omega Gaming Weekend. So I can't delay it. I can't move it. And I can't
just do it one 14 hour stream. So I'm going to be contractual. You're going to get three streams in
a row because I'm contractually obligated to be here. I'm going to be playing Gotham Knights.
It's going to be sponsored by WP with three days in a row. And what that means
is not only am I going to be playing Gotham Knights for three days, I'm also going to be playing
other shit for three straight days. So we're going to do another Omega Gaming Weekend.
Maybe some Splatoon. Probably some Breath of the Wild. Maybe we'll sprinkle in some Sorcery. I know
people have been waiting for that. More Turmoil. No, yeah, I can't play Turmoil for eight hours.
It's not going to happen. And look, scary stuff too. I want to play the new Puppet Combo game.
We'll do that this weekend. It's not just going to be Gotham Knights, but Gotham Knights will be a
part of each one of these streams. And it's not and it's not like, oh, yeah, guys, I got up today
and like, I gotta have a headache and my back kind of hurts. I'll stream four days from now.
Nope. You should play Guitar Hero. I mean, it's been a long time. Oh, you bet. You better believe
I'm going to wear the Nightwing shirt. Yes, I am. 100%. 100%. Is it going to be Saturday,
Sunday, Monday? It's going to be Thursday, Friday, Saturday. So it's Omega, I don't know, Omega end
of the week. End. Kind of. You should play PS1 games. Maybe. I did that a while though. Yes,
I will confirm today. The most important announcement you'll hear on this channel
over the next six months. I will be playing Among Us VR as the sus guy, the day it launches.
I told everybody I promised him I would do it. And I'm going to. I promised. Now that means I
could literally play it for 10 minutes. But I was kind of thinking of really just cashing in on that
meme. And look, people are going to come to this channel when I stream that and just be like,
wait, this is the sus guy. So I'm going to brand the entire channel that way.
All the branding you see here right now will not be here that day. It's going to be the sus face
everywhere. The stream title is going to be the sus guy finally plays Among Us. All the emotes,
all the badges, they're going to be the sus face just for one day only. I'm leaning into this. I'm
cashing out on this meme. I get to. When does it come out? What day does it come out? Is it when?
Like, I don't know. I need to prepare for this. November 10th. You should keep you should have a
sus filter on. Wait, have the sus face on my face. But I talked about this, right? I was concerned
about this. Because if I do this, I'm going to break the dollhouse viewer record. You don't
understand what I'm saying? I will break the dollhouse viewer record. And I'll never be able
to do anything else. I'll have to be the sus guy forever. Okay, let me ask you this. This is what
an inflated ego. No, I'm just saying I'm just I'm preparing for the worst here. So if I do the sus
guy, and I rebrand the whole channel to be the sus guy, and I play Among Us, and there's like
80,000 people watching. And the next day, like 50,000 people are watching. And they're like, dude,
where's more Among Us sus guy? I mean, what am I? Should I just cash in for like a month?
But then all the long term people that have been watching this channel will just leave
and I'll go back to the normal viewership numbers that I've been seeing. And it'll all only be
Among Us sus guy viewers. I'm going to be in trouble here. Maybe I shouldn't do this. Well,
we'll see. It's gonna be a new community. That's so stupid. All right, let me tweet this. I'll be
right back. Good thing I got that one off. I had 1% battery. I think I got that on. Oh, RT game
with the raid. Hey, what's up? Spent some time with RT over the last few days here.
Good to see him again. Trying to actually go do things with friends and family. I've been
kind of just kind of in work mode essentially for a long time. So it's really nice to see a lot of
people. I'm so aloof you guys would not even know. You don't even understand. But hey, thanks to the
thanks for the raid. Saw Taleks hung out with Taleks again, too. That's cool. Good to see
everybody. Are you you played Overwatch 2 for 80 hours? I didn't. All right, you guys ready? No,
we're done stalling. It's time to play some scorn. That's what I imagine when I click on
when I click a new game here. It's gonna go scorn. Does it do that? And we're live. Does it do it?
When I click new game, is it gonna go scorn? Is that me? Scorn. Oh, Jesus loud. Hold on.
Oh, this game doesn't have any hints. Good luck. Well, that's what you guys are for.
I'll get them. I'll get them. So I asked this in pre stream. Is this a gug at a game?
Does it actually do we are we going to get some of that or no, it's not. What is it? It's a this is
a okay. No, it's not. Well, I'm not even going to explain that because the people that it's the
people that know, you know what I mean? The sensitivity is way too high. And by the way,
this FOV is controls sensitivity, right? Camera settings. All right, here we go. Way down. FOV.
What was this? This is a numerical value. What is what would this be? So what's 90? Am I at
90 right here? I wonder. I don't know. I feel like this I needed a numerical value here.
All right, let's try that. It's better. A little too low. I have to do my settings. Just wait.
That's way too high. That's still a little high, but it's better. All right. That's good. That's
fine. How's it look? Turn off mouse smoothing. Oh, smoothing. Okay. All right. So let's go.
I got to press this button. I got to figure out the puzzle. All right. So what I have to do is
I just woke up in a distant land that I'm not familiar with. Do I have a map? I mean,
the game looks really nice. Should I be not should I be walking? Right. I feel like I shouldn't just
be spinning around. This is getting scary. I turn it up. This is scary. It's crazy. How can I tell
if I can open these doors? Is it fall damage? Okay, I can't. I'm just gonna go down there.
Everything looks cool. I heard some move because it's just left click to interact.
Why does it look good? But also like a PS2 game. I think that's why I like it.
Let's think that. Is it filter? What do you mean filter? TOS? What do you mean TOS? What are you
talking about? Keep it on. I don't care. All right. Um, ignore it. All right. So I can't touch this.
I need to have. Whoa. That sounded fake. That was a fake. Whoa. It was. I have to admit to that.
That was actually fake. It's been like two weeks since I've been live guys. I got to remember how
to like actually stream normally. That was genuinely. I made that up. Me saying, whoa,
I got caught. I actually made that up. So like I gotta, I gotta get back into this.
I forgot how to like pretend to have fun. What's this thing? Oh, whoa. That was real. It just
sounded a little deflated. Okay. So I have a thing on my arm now. What the hell? That's weird.
Is this toilet? This looks like a toilet of some kind. Like what is this? Is it an alien toilet?
All right. Well, it's definitely right here. Use direction. Wait, I don't get it. Okay. Wait,
I can switch between them. Okay. Just turn them both on. How do I get out? How do I get out of
the blood pressure reading machine? How? Oh, exit. Right. Okay. All right. There we go.
130 over fucking 70, dude. I'm fine. Yo, I didn't make it. Oh, come on. I have to keep it there
until. Okay. I need to stay in here. It's not just activate and walk away. It's activate. Stay in
here. Now we exit and we sprint. There we are. Okay. I get it. Give me an extra second or two.
So can I attack with this thing? I definitely have to climb up this thing. All right.
Get to the top of that and activate it. He's never going to complete this game.
That's what everybody says about every puzzle game that I've ever played. Okay. I'm going to
beat this. I will complete it. Everybody says that every time I play a puzzle game. Oh, hey,
dude. He's never going to beat this ever. And then I beat it. Like it takes me an extra four to six
hours than a normal human, but I still do. What is this? I don't know. I don't exactly know what
I'm doing here, but okay. I can, I don't know. All right. Whatever. Is it fall damage? Remember
you're an alien. What does this do? Okay. I don't get it. This game sucks. I'm done. I can push this,
right? Why does it tell me I can touch this? This thing's on a track. So how do I get it to move on
the track? It goes like this over here. And then what the hell is this thing? All right. So I am
on the track track moves like this. I've got this is correct because this, I want this to go down
here. Otherwise it would just spin around in a circle around this whole environment. So I've
already got it in the right place. I just have to move it and trying to figure that out. It's going
to be the challenge. Can I pick it up? What if I just leave it here? How do I activate this? How
do I get this move? Like go and take you forever? No, it's not. It's the first. I'm fine. I just
don't, I didn't know how to turn the thing on. Is this it? What is all this wacky shit in this
cathedral wherever we are? Do I have to get it here? All right, hold on. What is this thing?
How do I get the chair to move? Because this is, I did this correct. I just need to move the chair.
It's a two player puzzle. What? No, it's not. There's a lie. What can I do with this thing?
I am not going to be one of the people that said they quit this game in 10 minutes.
Because they thought it was going to be like, I'm not one of those people. I'm not quitting
the game in 10 minutes. No, I'm not doing it. Wait, what's this? Oh, I know what this is.
Okay, so can I move it? That's to get it to go up that way. Very obviously, I need to, I need to
figure out how to move the chair. I need to get that thing to fucking move that way. Is there like
a power thing I have to turn on? There's more places to explore. Oh, okay. I don't even know
where, I don't know what direction I came from. I'm just going to go this way. I need a map. Oh,
shit. Okay. I thought that was a concentrated puzzle. That's my bad. Okay, so what is this?
Okay, that's that scoops up whatever's in there. So what I need to put something in there to scoop
it up in here. All right. So how do I scoop some stuff in there? What should I scoop? Okay,
dude, what are you doing? Why? No, pick up one of these cubes. Pick up one of these. Scoop this
stuff. Okay, I can't do this. So they're both scoopers. Both are scoopers. And I can't use
them right now. So I'm gonna leave. I'm actually, I'm very interested in this game. I'm very
interested. I'll tell you right now. I'm not very good at puzzles, but I'm very interested in this
game. I want to know who the fuck I am. Why am I here? What am I doing here? Right? That to me is
worth me doing puzzles. I'm I want to know what I'm doing here. Who am I? Why am I here? Okay,
let me go this way. Can't activate these. All right, give me something. Give me like a bat,
a thing of meat or something to scoop, right? I've got nothing to scoop. I actually don't
have anything to scoop. There's all these scoopers and I can't scoop anything. You'll see. No help.
No help. No help. That's fine. I'll figure it out. I'll figure it out. When is he going to start
scorn? Scorning? What's this thing? I feel like get in this thing. It's like sod. This shit's so
weird. It's like this organic shit. You know what I'm saying? It's creepy. Organic tech. Weird.
Should I pick up like a like a skeleton or something and grind it up? I can hear something.
What's the point of this? Yo, what do I do? You beat Elden Ring yet? I got to the one of that
horse bosses the very beginning and I just puzzle games are like more my thing. So I quit it because
I just thought I'm not really into it. I'm more into like puzzle stuff. My game's just too fucking
hard. Like it's just, you know what I mean? I like stuff like this. Okay. Wait, what about here? I
already went down here. Okay. So very obviously I have to grind up something, put it into one of
the scoop machines and then the scoop machine will scoop out a, I don't know, something to use. I
don't know what to do. How come there's not every 15 seconds the game pauses and freezes and tells
me how to walk and like what interact button does. Okay. Try using your brain. I didn't think to do
that. All the rails. I just did that. Didn't I? There's the grind thing. All right. I'm going to
follow this one. Yeah. I, I, but how do I turn the cart on? I understand the concept of moving the
rails and changing the directions and everything, but how do I turn this? I'm just stupid. It's at
this game. I almost said stupid. I that's, I that one. That's not what I was going to say. How do
I turn the machine on? Explore more. Where have I not gone? I can't do this. It's gotta be something
to do. Maybe over here. Cause did I, did I go down here yet? I don't think so. No, I did.
I can hear a sound. Oh wait, what's this? What? Why can't I use this? What is this? You have to
pay attention to every possible path. I'm going to, I'm going to get a whiteboard in here. I'm
going to have to map this out. There's no map. There's no map. Somebody said you went down every
single path except for the correct one. That's not possible. You've literally did. There's an
elevator. What elevator? You keep missing controls. It's where the scoop is. It's,
it's the concrete level all over again. I just don't understand what I'm supposed to do.
Look, you guys are going to make me part of like a video essay on, look at how spoiled we've become
with all these developers giving us every hint we've ever needed. StreamerGerman985 couldn't
fucking find his way around scorn because there's no map and there's no fabled two breadcrumbs.
You guys are going to make me part of a video essay on how gamers need all this shit nowadays.
I could dodge a fucking axe on stream and I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna dodge a battle axe
on stream and you're not going to be able to say shit for months. You just ignored it again? What?
What? Where? What did I ignore? I don't get it. Everything is, everything is made of meat and
bones and shit. What am I missing? I missed something? Where? It's in here? Is this it?
It's in the snow. It's in the scoop room. No, it's in the scoop room. I don't, I don't. Guys,
if you paid me a million dollars to find the scoop room right now in 10 seconds,
I wouldn't be able to do it. Let's try. Let's see if I can get a million dollars. 10, 9, 8, 7, 6,
5, 4, 3, 2. Well, that's not fair because it would have taken more than 10 seconds to get here.
What? Okay. Did I, did I get, did I make a million dollars? If I go straight from here,
did I get a million? Nope. I don't get a million dollars. That would have been such an easy million.
It's the same room. Okay. You're talking about the room that has the scoop machine in it. No,
I don't owe you a million. I just said if I got there in 10 seconds, I would get a million. It's
over here. It's not over there. Okay. All right. Where? Where? Oh my fucking God. I couldn't even
see this. I didn't even see this. This like just didn't exist in my brain. Everything's made of
fucking bones. I walked in here. Everything's bones and like sinew. Okay. I, it's hard to know
where I need to go. Nobody talk from the elevator. Straight ahead is the big room. Okay. Lock it in
straight ahead from the elevator. Big room, big room with a bunch of big shit in it.
Left from the elevator. Left is dinosaur rib cage machine. Left from left is dinosaur rib cage
machine. Got it. Locked in dinosaur rib cage machine. Big room on the right side over here.
On the right side, left is dinosaur rib cage area. Straight ahead is big room over on the right side.
We have hallway leading to a wires and then here we are leading to a um I don't know. I don't know.
Where does it go? This is on the right side. Remember. I don't remember this. It's alarming
how many message deleted there are. Okay. What does that mean though? How do I get into that room?
Where's my little fucking robot that's flying around that can be like oh of course go that way.
Now I think that if you go one meter to the left. Where's my inventory? Where's my a million ammo?
This is still on the right side by the way. You still have the first puzzle in your 40 minutes
into the game. No. No. The stream has been live for 40 minutes. I've only been playing the game
for about 20. Don't lie. Don't lie. Don't lie. It's been about 16 minutes or so. Okay so it's
just a big circle and there's nothing here. There's just this I don't know where I don't
actually don't know where I am. Did I do a few? Okay I did a big circle. There's the big room.
So it's a gigantic circle that goes around the whole thing. So what does this do?
What's this? God damn it. What is this? I don't even know what the what the object is.
Oh my god this is gonna be horrible. What do I need to do? I need to move this?
What? Shit. Okay do I have to get this all the way around the other side? I don't get it. Okay but
what's the goal? Is the goal to get the lit up light to move? Okay which ones can even move?
Okay they can only move into the holes. So then all right so can I go like this? I can't move this
down. Move this up? Okay wait now what if I do this? Can I pick it up with the other one? What
happens if I pick it up? Does this do anything? Okay so I have to get what about the other eggs?
The ones with the lights on them maybe? I'm imagining that this has to come up like the
ones with the lights. Is that what it looks like I guess? I don't know. I'm gonna try it.
Okay does that matter? Because that one has lights on it. I can't hear how that sounded.
It probably sounded really fucking bad. All right whoa whoa whoa what was that? I just I didn't even
I missed the in- who cares what my voice sounded like? What did I just do? What happened? It broke
and fell down. So that was not- it shattered and fell down there. It's a- all right well let me get
the other one. Oh that's really annoying. Okay um yeah out of the fucking way.
Shit! All right I have to get- this is- this is gonna move this one here. Where am I bringing it?
These are locked in place but can I move these? I can move these over here.
I don't think it's that complicated. Bring this all the way down. Bring this all the way up. Right?
Because this has- I have to get this out of the way. Let's go like this for now. I don't. So what
if I do this? Can I at least get this up here? I can. All right. There's that. But I have a new
problem. Problem solved? Kind of. This better be it. Did I do it? I mean not- it's close.
Uh okay I gotta go- we're gonna be able to go that way. Can I move this all the way down?
Fuck! All right what about- hold on. I think I got it. Yeah that's it. I got it. I hope this is right
otherwise I screwed this whole- no shit! I gotta- can I zoom in? This sucks. I think I- I think I
screwed the whole thing up because I can go over here but I can't go down. There's no scenario
where I can get this up here. I have to move everything. What needs to be moved? Somebody
said I hate this game. It's- it's- I'm playing it. Let me move this because I- there's an area where
I can get this down. Can I- can I move this? I can't move this up. I can't go across here.
I need to get that single one down here. Hold on. All this shit has to be out of the way completely.
Right? Like it has to be. There's no other way to do this. No no no don't move this yet.
So this now comes over here and comes down right? Then this comes over all the way over here.
Then I should be able to- no because this has to- wait I got it. Oh I got it. We're good. Oh thank
god. Okay. I hope this is right. Average thinker. I'm- I got it. I'm fine. What are you doing? What
do you mean? I'm gonna have to grind this thing up. I'm gonna have to grind that up. Yeah okay I get
it. It's a wild puzzle. Oh man puzzles. What I'm known for here. So back down into that room
where the um kind of the saw is. Doritos. No it's not gonna work this time. It's not gonna work.
Okay I'm imagining I have to take- it probably came down this side right? Burn this into my
brain. This image right here. Okay I got it. So that means that this is where the scooper is.
If I see this exact image with like the thing hanging in over there. Okay stop saying Doritos.
It doesn't mean anything. What is going on? What is that sound? Where is it? Oh shit it's above me.
All right wait where's this going? This is gonna go over here. So where do I want this to end up?
So if it stays on this track which it could it could it's gonna go in here into the scoop room
which I don't think I'm ready for that yet right? I think I need to to put the I need to um use the
blade. I think that's what I have to do. So let me see where that is because where is it over here?
I gotta get into memory. All right so I need to move that- where is this one going? I gotta close
that up and see where this is. What's this over here? Track will go over here, through here,
around the corner, into- here it is. All right so uh okay let's- I'm gonna go move the tracks.
How's it- why is everybody saying yay and nay? All right so I gotta close up that one back here
because you know what I mean I have to move this. So this one is already correct but I have to close
this one. So this one has to come back over this way. So close up that one and that's the only one
that needs to be closed. Yes all right that's good. So it's where- where is- where am I?
It's this one over here. Where's it going? Okay so that's what I need. That's correct. We good?
Let's go. Let's go. All right begin. Move. What are you doing? He's reaching. What's going on? Wait
what? No no I want to keep going on this track. Can I do this? Let me see what this does.
What did I do? What did I just do? I don't know. I- this feels like I shouldn't be doing this.
Okay well we're going this way and then this wraps all the way around and then it's the-
the- should I- I don't know should I put him in this thing? Okay.
Okay now what? Now I- I- do I have to pick it up? Dude what the fuck? No no no no stop go back.
Wait a second. Okay now I can click. What the fuck? Wait they go in- what's the point of doing this
though? What is the point of this? What- what's the point of this? Why would I do this? What's the point?
What the hell? Hey wait he's getting up. Should I run? I feel like I've been- the game has given me
an opportunity to run away before this guy Michael Myers is me for like the next six hours. Help him.
I- I- how? What am I supposed to- why is that sound effect happening? Why is that sound effect
happening right now? Help him please. How? Can I like- standing? Yeah. Am I supposed to do something?
Oh wait no no no no no no. Walking? Walking? Wait you're just- are you following me? Okay um so now
we're gonna go sit you in the- in the scoop machine and get- get you scooped up. Careful. Can he use
this? This would make sense right considering that this two- this is the- yeah this is co-op partner.
Yep. What do I do? How do I help him? Wait what? Jesus dude. Oh my god.
Ah you're gonna need a gun. Let me give you the- let me just take a look go into my menu and find
the thing with zero ammo and the gun that I never upgraded and it's a pistol with maybe one bullet
in it. Here take it. So let's try- let's get- let's get that big door open right here. Come on. You
didn't even give you a new friend a name? I- we just met. I got a- I don't know. After a little
while I'll come up with a good name. All right come over here and touch it. Go come and put your hand
over here. All right come on come over here we'll get this open.
Dude this sucks. This is like fucking horrible. So this is open. All right so stay right there
for a sec. Did you just lock me in here? I was just about to give uh I was about to give you a
name too. No you locked him in there. It's gonna be some like AI took control and has been killing
us. I don't know. It's some- it's gonna be some alien alien tech. You know what I mean? Yeah humanity
is being like harvested by the aliens and they're using a- they're using us for their alien tech.
What was that? That's creepy. Ace in there? He's gonna break open. All right room with all these
pods. Can I do anything with this? Looks like a quake map. Wait what am I doing with this mine?
Okay uh all right up there. I knew it. Fucking alien tech. I don't know why I think that's funny.
It's just- I don't know it's just a word. Am I inside of a thing that's just alive or something?
This thing's alive. What does this do for me? What does this do for me? I don't know. I don't get it.
Um I guess I can turn this a different way or- no I can't. What else is in here? Can I move this?
Okay I can move this again to there? I don't know. I'm gonna try it. You're- oh I'm so sorry
that probably hurt your ears. Have you ever seen alien? Yeah um let me- do I just get another one
and put it somewhere else? Do I have access to any more of those? I saw those things sticking out.
I definitely have access to more of those things. Right? I gotta place them here. I think I know
what I have to do. Let me get out of here. All right. There's more of those um uh uh the alien
tech globes. Do I have to pick one up and put it over here? Or do I have to pick that? I would
put it in here. I don't know. That's what I'm going with. That's what I think I have to do. So
I'm gonna try it. What is it back here right? Yeah okay. So can I just pull one of these off?
I gotta be- this is gonna be a way to get that off right? Something to do with this
but I don't have whatever that uh attachment is or something yet.
Huh okay. So that's not what I have to do. Uh oh. Seeing a lot of not like this. Go back. Go back.
So do I just pull it out of there and then put it in one of the other slots?
That's what I'm thinking. It looks like I couldn't do that though. All right I'm gonna look over here.
Is there anything else? Is this a big circle? Oh oh found one! How do I get that? How do I pick
this up? I can't pick this up. I need more- you need more alien tech. Okay there's another one.
All right it's a big circle so I've obviously this is not done here yet. I need to go somewhere else.
I guess. I feel like it's that's the thing that's powering that stuff. I'm just gonna go back.
Is this here? All right I need to lock this into memory. That's that way. When are you gonna get a
rocket launcher? I don't think I'm gonna get one of those. All right this is where I came from.
So what- is there anything over here? Now this is where I was.
Did I miss something else? I guess I could go over here back with this.
God I'm so sorry. Holy shit that was that was like the worst thing that ever happened to me.
That was actually the worst thing that ever happened to me like my whole life.
It was- it was just a- it was like a weapons case appeared. So much shit has not happened
that I did not think that the weapons- whatever. Oh I got- oh we're ready to rock and roll. It's
time. Start playing the Guggernaut. Does this have ammo? This is the shittiest jump scare I've ever
had. Whatever. Does this have infinite ammo? This thing sucks. It's like a party horn.
Oh I'm out of ammo. So what do I do with this? So I take this back to there and I start- I can
put this- okay I know what to do. This is gonna go right here. Oh cool. There we go. Okay so now
I go over here and I- they're all gonna be over here now. What? Did I supposed to do that? Oops.
Hey!
Too high. Okay. Did one of them fly over here? Oh look at that. Okay cool. I know what to do now.
Let's get it. We pick that one up. Stick it over there. Go! There we go. So where should I put it?
Spaces open up there. This is space right here. I'm just gonna put it here. I think. No I'm not.
I'm gonna put it where the thing opened. All right. And there's one more. Taking my blood
something. That's definitely using my blood to power. Well I got it. Aliens are using human
blood as oil to power their machines and shit. Like our blood is oil to the aliens right? It
has to be. Okay so this is here. There's another one. I gotta get- I have to crack down another
one of those lobe things. Where am I gonna get this last one? Oh the French champagne.
There we go. All right. I should be able to open them all now. Get to it. See you later. See you later.
They're not gonna fucking harvest us. Dude those are just air conditioners.
Relax. You bastards aren't gonna harvest us anymore! Because you know he's talking to a
fucking like air conditioning tube. Yeah you bastards! They were literally just cleaning stuff.
Dude you're speaking to a Roomba. Overloaded it with blood. I overloaded it with too much blood.
What the hell is going on? What the heck? I'm in a different like world. One sec. Otto is chilling
in here. I'm gonna let him out. Wait hold on. Why am I like being born or something? This is weird.
Wait it actually is the birth canal. Wait what? What the hell is going on in this game? All right
give me one sec. I have returned. All right so I've been born. Did I rip that out? That was
the worst time to leave. You- did I- whatever. It's fine. I don't care. You missed it. I don't-
whatever. I don't- I didn't miss anything! You missed lore. Vital lore. It was a graphic umbilical
cord removal. Oh whatever. All right well this is different. This is- I came out of the wall.
There's other uh scorns here or whatever is going on. Let's go this way. Yeah we'll be- we're being
harvested and it's like- anybody seen the matrix? What a dumb question. I bet you're like everybody
probably has seen that. That's what it kind of feels like. Anybody- hey anybody seen the matrix?
No dude. You're the only one. You're the only one. Like a ship? This is a different planet. Did we
land on this planet in search of something or contact and we ended up- we woke up this-
what is that? Is this backwards? This is backwards. This is backwards. Is that backwards?
This is- I'm wrapping back around here. This is where I came from. Did I go all the way back?
That- I just wanted to circle. What about this way? Can I go this way?
It didn't look. No. Hey Jerma it's Dave from Mensa. I want to know that we've rejected your-
oh it's like a I'm dumb thing. Okay this is really cool though. The atmosphere is definitely on point.
Atmosphere? Nine. Weird. One of these is gonna get up. What's my goal here? I'm just walking
around aimlessly. Okay I could go down over here. It's a cute game. All right let's go.
I'm ready. It's like ships. Are these gravestones or like alien pods? Alien tech. Oh that's right.
That does what it is but that looks like. I don't- I don't think this- I don't think this one made it.
I think I gotta go in here. Is there a door? Like a front door? Oh something over there.
Is that something glowing? All right hold on. This is the Futurama house.
That was- yeah that's- that's really good. That's like how did you- how would you even-
It's right though. Like you- you're completely accurate. It just is. All right I think I found
a way in. This is one of those games where the graphics are so pretty. It's so- it's such a
beautiful game in regards to uh human tech. I'm not talking about alien tech. I'm a graphics of
humanity. Uh the human tech on this is great which makes it way more unsettling. It's like
too real. It's like just all the graphics are good. Like really good so it just makes it worse.
All right so I don't know what this is. This thing is gonna start moving. It's gonna be all
the organic shit. This is alive. Oh god it's a lizard person. All right do I have to fight that
or hide from it? This is so weird. Oh god okay um honestly this is what I would do in real life.
That's what I would do in real life. I would get freaked out and fucking run away. I did it
and all the time all the while I'd be running and like clapping very very loudly. New uh my hand.
It's saying I can touch it. Can I now put my arm in this? I guess I can't touch this right now.
All right let me get this into memory here. Oh my god wait where's the thing? Where's the monster?
All right that's glowing red room. Remember that. Glowing red room is that area. I don't have
whatever this is. Interesting. I can't do anything over here. What do you think this smells like?
Um okay you know that basement smell? That really heavy basement smell. I'm gonna say like that
and cheese. Okay so where am I supposed to go? The shadow I thought was the monster. Um could I have
done something with that? I just don't didn't see it. Or is there another way to go? It didn't look
like I could interact with anything in the red room. Oh you know what? No no basement and like
something that has been something burning. That's what it smells like down here. Red room. Red room.
I can't touch anything in here. Red room. Red. How do you do it? Let me see if I can do it.
Red room. Red room. Red room. Pretty good. Pretty good. Pretty good. Um there's nothing back here.
Maybe go back out to the other. Out to the other area. Please tone it down. My kid's trying to
sleep. What headphones is it? And why? This is a scary thing to have on the tv. I'm gonna go back.
I'm gonna get out of here. You keep walking right by it. Dude don't even tell me I'm doing that.
No that's down there. Can I go down? I can't go down here. I keep walking. I keep walking by it.
I didn't. This is the first skeleton person I've been able to interact with. How am I supposed to
know I could touch this? How am I supposed to know I could grab this thing? You know what?
Monka S. Monka S chat. Open up. Did they get it? But what did that do? Oh it's just the wires cut.
This doesn't this is not connected to anything. Wait is this creepy? Um oh hey hey hey what the
fuck? What the hell was that? Okay well this is that. This is that. This is that. So I could have
used the elevator. Okay this is that. The red room. I need to come back to the red room. I'm
imagining I have to open those three things. Okay now we're up. Oh god. Little weirdo. All right
what's over here? Nothing. I like this game. Whoa okay. Oh fuck. Dude look at all this over
engineered alien tech. Wait why am I I can do this from both sides? Wait hold on. I'm confused right
now. What just happened? Wait what would I do? I'm confused. What's going on? Just make walkways.
Yeah it's true. This over engineered alien bullshit. Just make walkways. Why does this
shit have to exist? This is just overdoing everything. Uh oh. I don't get it. Okay so there's
red room. I have a key now. Probably for this. Whatever this is. Yep. Oh boy. If I said it's my
turn to use the xbox would you guys think that was funny? Oh I don't have one of those things on.
All right so I gotta get one of those arm uh augments. Come back over here. Into the
middle of this thing. Use it. So I have this this key now. I can probably use that. Back down the
elevator. Use that in the red room. What side is this on? I don't even know where I came from. Over
here right? So this is the leftmost um pod right? Oh how do I get out of here? So then it would be
the rightmost one. Is it this one? Oh shit. Okay hold on. Can I make for them? Whoa what happened there?
Oh um I definitely have to turn that off. Oh pull them all. One two three. Got them all. All right
cool. So that's a shortcut. That didn't work. Holy shit. Huh? All right that's weird. Oh he's just
ugh. Okay so I'm gonna go out of here. What can I do with this? I can go through the blades? Let's
try that. I'm eating. I mean I'm I'm playing scorn but I am very overexposed over here.
Aren't I? I'm like look at them. They're bright. What's going on here? Is that better? Lights off.
Lights off but it'll look weird. Right? Is it gonna look weird? I turned the lights off and somehow
this is what happened. I don't understand what just happened. Why did this happen? Why did the
webcam just break? Hold on. It's because like auto exposure. Um give me one second. Dude why does
this look so fucked up now? Am I at 60 fps at least? Hold on. That's 2008 scorn playthrough.
Um I don't I don't know why it's doing this. I guess I could do this. Why is it so frame ratey?
Dude what is it with? Somebody explain this to me. What is it with webcams that they just they go to
2 fps if the like exposure is brought up. It's like does this thing only operate on an auto shutter
that can never be fucking overrided and you need like six floodlights to make it even look remotely
good looking. Why is it slowing the shutter speed? Just put the gamma up bro. Okay well this is
obviously not going to work. So let me go back to what this looked like before. I mean computers are
stupid. Why I'm like orange. Why am I so orange? All right that's better. That's that's a little
creepier. Right? There. There you go. All right we're good. This is like scary lighting. Right?
Okay let's go. You're still in the tutorial. I'm not in the tutorial actually. Is this quick
size yet? This thing is so bright now I can't even see the screen. It's like oh my god. I
just put like six lights in your face. Is this is a shitty frame rate? Is it that it's still okay?
We good? It's definitely shitty frame rate. I swear to god. I swear to god all these webcam
companies have not upgraded the technology since 2006. I promise you. I don't think they've updated
the chips inside of these things since like 2007. I don't I don't think so. I don't think so. So
this is where I was. I want to go back out to where the fan is. Isn't it so weird that ever since I
got the that old like I got this this old Logitech webcam. I remember using it. It was like a C like
20 or something. Right? It looks identical to this. That was 10 fucking years ago. It was
literally 10 years ago. In fact it looked better. All right I'm gonna play. All right so here's this.
This is a shortcut through the blades which puts me here. Okay so that is just an easy way to get
back to there. Right? So let's do this. Does this do anything for me? Didn't I already do this though?
Wait what's going on? Why am I doing this again? Do I have to do this again? Stop. I mean you look
like you're covered in cheeto dust. I don't know. This is a Logitech brio. I think this thing was
a hundred fucking dollars. This thing was expensive. Okay so I got that. I don't know why this thing is
so bad. Okay so I can't go this way. So I have a new thing. Back to the red room. Right? So I'm
going to try to do. So let me go back here. Yeah I think I am just going to set up my that DSLR.
Okay so I got that. Cool. Let's go here. What is that? Can I touch this? Oh nice. All right I
got the thing now. Do you have an intentional orange filter on? Okay so this opens. This is
another shortcut. So I'm kind of just opening up this whole area which is good because now
do I need to do? No I did that one already. So I gotta go back to red room. Right? That's the idea.
Okay red room. Red room was around the corner here. Where's the red room? Where's the red room? Down
here? Dad's over here. Okay. Can I like practice or something? All right. I have a new code. All
right. So I gotta get. There's another one. There's one more I gotta get. Yep. I gotta get
one more. What is the axe stream? You'll see. You'll see. Okay so very obviously I gotta get
one more of those and where the hell is that? That's a great question. So I'm missing one code
for my power glove. Whatever it is. Okay so where would that be? Probably up where I was
because now I can wait. Uh-huh. I can go back. I have the thing for my arm. Let me see if I can
backtrack to where I was. I got the thing for my arm which I need that to go up this way. I got
the thing on my arm. Right? And then I did that and this is the fan unplug. No. Wait. How do I get
back to? How do I get back to that area? The other elevator. Because I put my hand in this right? So
now I can use the thing. Where were the fans dude? I just don't fucking remember. I just really don't.
I feel like it was like no this is it in this way because that's the red room. This is going back.
This room which I don't think I'm supposed to be here. No. I need one more of these fucking things.
It's not this. But is it? All right give me help. Is this the red room elevator? Then it was not
just up here? Tubes. Okay right so now I'm back up here. There's nothing over here. All right so
this is back up this way. Where would the other hand arm thing be? Back up through the tubes and
then it was to the right wasn't it? It was the left. I thought I got spun around. Dude have you
been exposed to radiation? No dude I'm fine. All right so I did this one. I got that one. I can go
in this thing now. I can touch this. Right? Yeah. All right let's go. Let's go. I get it. Okay well
um do it to the one that's blocked. Okay then go that way. I think that's the only one. I gotta go
that way. Okay. Okay. I got a feeling it's gonna be right here. Remember do you think you have what it
takes to be America's next top model? Yes. One more. Lock it in. Where's this one go? On here.
Wait for the click. Thank you. I know a thing or two. Okay so I got everything. It's time to get
out of here. Time to turn on the red room uh and see what happens. I'm very interested. By the way
make sure you get hype for the I'm going to dodge your battle act stream. Coming to you very soon.
Well relatively soon. All right so um I want to go over here right back down to the red room.
Okay here there's the red room. Back down. All right let's get the heck out of here. Bingo. All
right what happens? Took me 40 minutes to do this shit. Oh what's that? You have to rev that up.
Okay hold on. What is this? Interesting. All right turn it on. Um that's not gonna work. Um
shit. Okay I'll be all right. Stop. It's a puzzle. You don't beat him instantly. Nobody opens this
game. I'm sorry. Nobody does this. Everyone that's like oh my god. He has his brain.
Just hold on. You don't open this and go like. No it takes five minutes to do. It takes five
minutes. See it takes five. It takes a few. That's difficult to do that. You don't just solve it
instantly. You don't solve a puzzle like that instantly. I don't. Nobody does that. I bet you
half of you guys took 15 minutes to do that. I still have that thing attached to me. Oh geez.
Are you gonna get up? I think this person's gonna get up. All right I got some device. What is the
device for? Does that open doors? All right that opens. Logitech Brio yellow color correction using
OBS. I don't. Do I have to fix this right now? Hold on. I'm gonna fix this right now apparently.
Well I'm into it. Let's go. Got it. Got it right. There it is. There it is. I'm good. Let's go. All
right so this is gonna open doors that have the symbol in the top left which I'm imagining is the
one upstairs right. The one that I walk by all the time. Let's wait is that up and over or is
that over here? It's over here right? Right here. Okay. So what's in here? This seems creepy. Come
on the other side. Don't you think that would add some atmosphere if like after every major kind of
area and every puzzle was like music played and you just heard it's going. That'd be kind of cool
I think. Oh okay. I can open that door. What's over here? Weird. All right doesn't have a sword in
its hand. Okay crazy. All right let's go. You're doing well. I'm just having fun man. What's your
opinion of garlic and onions? It pretty much makes any food better. That's just a fact. Who is
disagreeing with that opinion? I feel like that's the safest opinion you could possibly have.
In fact I don't think there's a safer opinion than saying that garlic is delicious. Garlic and
onions make things taste good. What a- that's not a thing you'd even disagree with. Oh shit this
thing's moving. Get it out. Get it off of me. What do I do for it? I fill it with like blood?
Okay. I'm doing a lot of like internal burping this stream by the way. It's gross. This is
important. I'm back. All right. Okay I got that whatever that is. Is there a filter on it?
There shouldn't be. This is really creepy. All right I'm going around here. Oh my fucking god
give me a break. Are you kidding me? I've ruined everything. Jesus. God damn it. Fuck.
That's fucking creepy. Come on. I'm actually pissed off right now. I'm truly- I'm not- I'm very
unhappy. I didn't turn the stupid filter off and I see people saying filter filter. I thought
you talked about the webcam. Whatever. Let's go. Jesus. All right open the door. Did I beat like
the first zone here? I haven't seen anything else. All right I don't know. Okay interesting.
Let's go straight ahead. Okay there's a light right here. Very cool. Jesus. Oh what the fuck?
Did I get a new power? Oh this is a new power. I can open up doors that have that. Okay so let me
commit this to memory here. So I have two keys technically I think right. What's down here?
Blood. Lots of fucking blood. Lots of blood. That's a lot of blood. I have to be better at
fucking acting. I have to be way better at acting. Oh I need to move this. I need to be a fucking
better actor. All right so I just walked in a circle. Nothing over there. So I gotta get down
here. Oh all right I got that. I can probably move this somehow. Was there a door that I walked by?
Maybe. Oh I couldn't go this way. I'm sorry I can't do it. The problem is I can't see where the
board is right. So I have to put my arm over here without looking and press the button and it's I
can't. I need to I need to put this somewhere else and where I can like just I can't fuck this
up anymore. I gotta stop doing this routine for a few minutes. It would make sense if I wasn't
Okay I gotta find that button and it's right there. Right there. From here. Right there. Okay I
got it. Can I actually not go down anywhere from here? Where am I supposed to go? Because this
just wraps back around. I have a second key. I guess over here I could go. I mean didn't I already
do this? This is the elevator. I can't go back up. What's the one place I didn't go this way?
Like over here? Did I not go over here? Oh okay yeah yep yep yep we're good. I have to kill this
thing. Oh jeez. All right these things are alive. Is it alive? Fucking scary. Uh hello.
What the hell? Why can I not attack?
That was. You dead? Geez. Okay so that's that. Why would I do this twice? I wouldn't keep it there.
So now I go up and I can. Okay so I have to move this one. Does this one have a thing?
Now I just need to get up there. Elevator right and walk through. I have to actually start fighting
enemies now. This is gonna be rough. Stop! Stop! Ow! Okay that's so you can kill them pretty
instantly then. Up here I need to get to that walkway. Which is it right here? Is the walkway
right here? I don't know. I think so. And I walk this way. Yeah one and then two but wait a second.
I already got that. Press E to heal. Are you serious? Oh my god you're not a liar. I thought
you lied. I don't think I. Is it a full heal? This is fucking hurting me. What? This is actually
hurting me. This thing is still killing me. I'm gonna have to be able to get this thing off right?
I'm gonna sit in the like a meek grinder machine and this thing's gonna get.
A blade's gonna go under its back. Okay oh boy. Okay oh no no no don't dark souls me please. Oh
my god give me a fucking break. Yeah okay get me please get me back the other way. What do we have
here on the machine? I think about that felt weird. I hated that. In the head. In the head. In the head.
In the head. In the head. In the head. Directly in the head please. Why is it not grabbing?
How come I can't grab it? It's fucking. Why can I not hit him in the head? You just got a rare
animation. Wait I have to do this all over again? Oh god damn it. All right I'm not gonna fuck it
up. It's not that. I'm all right. I'm all right. I'll be fine. Heal. How do I get out of here?
I just wanted to leave the globe. Pull this. All right we're good. Dermot your mother's watching
the streams. Don't waste her time. My mother would probably open the stream and go what is he doing?
What is this? And she would leave.
Dude what does the bar on the right side even mean? Oh it's a stamina bar. Okay I thought it
was a stamina bar but it was hard to even tell where the bar was. All right so you can do it
twice. Is there a block or anything? Can I pull the thing up? Okay so that's my health bar. Wait
okay the top row is the amount of heals that I have and the all right so the squares are actual
health. The thing's much bigger than the other ones. I don't think I can do anything with that
right now. It's scary. I don't want to get overwhelmed here. This is this is a huge area
so let's do this slow and do this right. I'm gonna go this way first and I'm gonna go up. Oh I'm gonna
get so fucking lost here. I'm gonna get so lost. There's gonna be a big ball there. Okay so there's
gonna be a huge ball that I have to get on that. So that's a good place to start. Okay so let me go
over there I think. Sure yeah it sounds right. The track here. All right so this is a uh for a
teleported ball. What's on the other side? Okay one of these. Oh no that I thought that was a machine.
No it's not. All right there's nothing over here. All right let's go. Who just said what's the point?
I don't know of why would I why am I playing this because it's uh it's halloween time. What's the
point? Oh wait a minute it's new it just came out. This was a pretty hyped up game from what I
remember. Didn't I what we watched the e3 trailer or something right? All right where am I? We did
I think we did yeah. Is that the thing I needed to grab? Oh please please don't.
I have this more to do. I think I have to bring it all the way up. Oh health refill. Cool. So this can hold two charges and each charge is four health.
Totally eight health. All right what else is here? Anything interesting to do still? Anything at all?
There's probably a few of them. Oh you're dead? Stop I can't move. What's up with your face today?
I don't know. Oh did I do anything with this or just it's just annoying and in the way? Hey
why does he only read mean messages? No I've read some nice ones. All right so now bring this all
the way up and then I can go pick it up. Wow I gotta turn it down. All right so that's all
the way up there now. Two oh shit. I don't have invincibility when I'm doing that to someone.
Shoot. We're good. It's all the way up. I think I just need to grab it with the uh the big claw hand
right? Because I think that's what I have to do. I'm out of I know I have a little bit I've got more.
I'll get to full health. Snore? Don't even. Don't don't even. Don't even. Don't even start. Don't even.
Okay now uh do I do now? I guess I can I don't know. I'm gonna activate this. Oh that's giving me an
area to go. I'm gonna go that way just to see what oh I can't wait just moving on its own.
This shit's moving on its own. So now I'm imagining I get in and then go down or get in and just run
across. I think we're gonna are we gonna see the end of this arc here? No. What is the end of that
arc? I definitely get it ripped off of me right? I have to. Yeah right there. I'm gonna sit in this
I'm gonna sit in this and it's gonna take it off of me. Watch this. What am I looking at? I don't
know what I'm I don't know what that does. That's cool. All right this thing's coming off. Ammo. Oh
I have all right cool. So weird. All right so this thing's loaded. Probably gonna be using it right
now to shoot something. Yep. Stop. Score. Cool. Now this looks interesting over here. It doesn't do
it. That's not it? How's that not it? How am I supposed to get that to go? There's not enough
pieces. There's not enough pieces to do this. I mean do I need another piece or something? I don't
get it. I had all three of them lit up. All right the only time I can light this one up is if it's
touching the one on the right side here. That's the only time the middle one lights up. No. So what
is making it do that? I got it. That was weird. Score. All right this is goes into the elevator
upstairs. Oh no I gotta do this again. I gotta do that again. It's gonna be harder next time.
Please. Um okay. I'm going. Let's go down. So I need to put the you know what I'm saying? I gotta
put the thing in to go down another level or should I just go down with it right now?
Should I go and put the thing in or should I just go down to that second level?
Get more ammo? Uh I think this is only one use. Yeah I can't get any more. I'm just gonna try
going down. How come these aliens build their spaceship with a bunch of annoying puzzles?
Well think about it. If an alien landed here and you told them to get in a car and go drive on
go go anywhere on like a highway they'd be like what the fuck is all this? What's this weird system
of lines that you have to go on with this thing? They'd say the same shit. Our highway systems
would confuse the fuck out of an alien. So I mean is this the equivalent? Probably. I need that.
There it is. So what should I put in the middle one? Puzzle complete. Is he okay? Better than
ever. All right go down. Do that other puzzle right here. Very cool. Very cool. Hey dude you are
making me angry. Uh oh. How do I get more weapons? Can I do it? I can't. Where's my other gun?
Uh oh this is bad. Um I don't I can't reload. There's nothing in the gun.
Do I even need to kill any of this shit honestly? Press one. Oh oh my god okay I was doing mouse
scroll. I was trying to scroll for new weapons but it's just okay I got it. Cool. Cool. That's
weird. Is it gonna melt? This is a weird request. Dude can you do Alex Jones stuck in the scorn world?
How what how somebody is next to me right now. Let me figure this out first because this is
gonna take me a little bit. All right I can turn this one. Oh fuck the whole thing has to be done.
No no no no no no. Okay hold on. You gotta just get them all matched up.
How do I get them to turn together? Oh that's how. All right hold on. I gotta turn this how
many times? Like two more times? One two three four that. Okay so now oh I'm so goddamn close man.
So I need to keep this uh yeah. Scorn. Okay cool. Now I go go back put this in and go all the way
down. This guy's supposed to dodge a battle axe. A puzzle is a video game puzzle is not even close
to comparing me dodging a battle axe. They're two completely different. Oh whatever. Just run.
It's basically the same thing. No it's not. It's not even close. Are you gonna practice for the
battle axe stream? Practice what? Do you think I need practice? I don't I couldn't I don't think
you know who the fuck you're talking to. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Hold on. I'm sorry. That was
let me let me cool it off a little. Let me cool it off a little. Do you know who I am? Do you have
any idea who I am? Do you know who you're talking to? You think I can't dodge a battle axe? Oh okay.
Sorry I'm gonna cool off and I forget where I'm going. I knew I had to go up to go to that device
to put the third plug in. Um I forget where that is. Oh you have any idea who you're talking to?
I need where is this machine thing? It's up here somewhere over there. It's across the way right?
Did I go did I run by it? I mean I'm sorry I'm looking at chat people are telling me to do an
Alex Jones impression. I'm trying to pay attention to this fucking puzzle game. Okay here this is not
it. Where is this thing? It's right there. Jesus. How do I get over there? Wait what? How the fuck
do I get over there? Other way was the oh god you were just there? It's right it's right here. How
do I get over there? Oh my god I was already over there. All right. All right. No it started. I'm
not doing Alex Jones ever again. No I'm not doing Alex Jones ever again. In fact yeah you're gonna
get punished with a Stewie Griffin impression. That's what you get. You're gonna get punished
with a Stewie Griffin. Here it comes. I say Ryan. What? Then we go down all the way. Most streamers
don't punish their viewers. I'm I'm punishing you with a Stewie Griffin voice. I think I think it's
gonna be okay. All right everything has been done. Now I have to grab the ball. What's down here?
Nothing. I have complete I have uh wait did I explore down here completely? I think I did
right. Is there anything else to do down here? I mean I could just turn this on. Will this get
the thing I need? All right we'll get it. Okay so what did that do? Can I get in? Oh now I can grab
this and take it over here. Uh all right um now what? Uh I think there's another ball to grab here.
You're doing great. Oh thanks. Funny when he starts doing a bit and you can tell when he gets
completely distracted from whatever he's doing in the game. Yes that happens very frequently
because my problem is I don't stop moving right. I don't stop moving. Usually when I start talking
I look in the chat. I'm just I'm just walking right. Just walking straight and turning corners
and stuff. So what I disconnect from the game when I'm talking to you but I'm still moving.
So I need to just take my hands off the keyboard when I start to talk and then oh I'm still in
the same spot. Okay I can kind of get and plant back in. All right so what does this do? Nothing.
Okay um should I just go in here? Ball ball ball gg gg there's no ball. What do you mean gg?
Now I'm gonna go down and then I'm gonna it's gonna grab it out of this hand it off right.
Can I just hand it off? Can I drop this here? Oh all right nice very nice. So now we got
two balls over here. Looks good. All right I'm gonna get in this one but not yet. What is the
point of this one? I guess I could bring it. Where am I gonna bring this? I guess that makes sense
and then I go in that. All right um let me just check back here because I don't want to miss
anything. Did I go down here yet? I don't think I did. There's an alien down here of course I didn't.
Oh this thing's dead. Did I go down here? Did I come down here? Oh I did yeah this is where that
thing was crawling around over here. All right I'm going back up. I've been down here. I just dodged
so much. Why am I even fighting you? What are you what are you doing? Get it off. So I'm gonna go
in that ball. I think that completes this section. Interesting. I need ammo again with this monster.
Wait that's hurting me every time. Really? Can that thing actually kill you and just
softlock you in the game? I'm assuming yes. Oh thank god. Oh all right another one of these
which I probably have to drop all of them. Okay what? Can I not go this way? Okay I can't go that
way. So what? Okay I've already been here. Shit. All right how do I get down there?
Can't go that way. Do I have to do something with this? This game reminds me of seafood.
Weird. Um I'm gonna go this way and down. Whatever. Not even gonna give you a chance.
Um oh I can't move. Wait should I stay in here? I feel like I'm okay. Okay it doesn't move. These
guys probably jump off and follow you around. I'm gonna kill them every time I see them.
Yeah what's that? This is gonna be such a huge pain in the ass I can already tell.
I gotta move all these. When I move one of these gates another gate closes in a different place
and then oh shit there's a new enemy. Oh dude it's a new scorn like game. That was a good one. How
far back am I? Scorn like game. I'm about that far back right? No. No not really at all. All right
let's keep going. Shut up. I don't want to shoot you but I'm- oh my god the little shit enemy killed
me. How many takes of this did I do? Scorn. Scorn. Scorn. That one doesn't have any effects on it at
all. That was just a guy. Scorn. That would probably be annoying after a while. I think I have- no I
don't. Just kill it. It's not annoying. Yes it is. I know it is. All right now let's get ready.
This thing falls. Oh look out. Okay we're good. It doesn't go anywhere. This is where the enemy is.
I got a full clip. Okay turn this on. I need health. Bad. Let me check over here first.
It's probably health or something right? There's really nothing over here.
Dude what is that sound? No there's nothing here. Okay let's try this again. Hopefully I don't die
because I'm going to start over. Very saturated. Yeah. Have you considered reloading? I got a- I
have a full magazine. All right here we go. Here it comes. All right let's go. All right.
Shut up. Shut up. I'm fine. Scorn. I have to do that whole thing again. How am I gonna- nice
indie filter. I need health. I don't have any health potions or anything. If I get hit once I'm
dead. All right I just have to- I can't run in the hallway. He'll kill me if I run down the hall.
Go go go go. I know where I'm going. Come on. Just watch this hall. Okay so I'm gonna just
do this and then run away because I will just- I'm gonna just run him around this circle. He
has to follow the same pathing rules that I do. There he is. All right. Get out of this tunnel.
Thought I could stagger him enough times. Don't just run. Don't try to kill it. Really?
Yeah. Don't be greedy. I was under the impression that if I shot it in the head it moves around and
I can shoot it like four or five times. It was my mistake. Okay let's try this again. Look I can die
in one hit anyway. I'm seriously- I'm just rushing now to get through this. Yeah I know. Come on.
Come on. Yeah whatever. Okay I'm going to just run away. I'm not gonna fight. I'm gonna just run.
I'm not gonna waste ammo. I'm not gonna waste an entire magazine on this shit. Where is the
path I need to take? Through here and then I want to just wrap around.
Pretend every enemy is a battleaxe. Well I'm not actually moving to get out of the way.
All right. Where am I? How do I get out of here? What's the correct way to go?
I think I have to go that way. All right let's run you around. Yeah I actually have to go
where he came from. All right that was much easier than- he's not still behind me right?
Oh let's do something. Move. I'm gonna get up. Oh thank god. Do I have this? I don't. I need the
other piece. Where is it? Don't- don't come at me please. Don't just doom three but it's awesome.
I mean it's really really cool. The atmosphere of the game alone is worth playing I think.
I don't know honestly much else to say besides that but I mean that's carrying the whole game
for me right now. This is like how weird and interesting this place is. All right I'm gonna
die in one hit down there. I'm gonna shoot it. I'm gonna shoot this guy. He hates it. He loves it.
I have to give my full assessment. Where are you? You're just fucking around. Are you gonna get up
if I- I mean I die in one hit so okay. This way. Dude if I would have just let you in
I would have just let this thing in. Oh god. Oh wait oh goodness. Oh thank goodness.
Okay we're good. Is this health? What is this? Oh it's the key. Is this health? This is ammo.
I need- oh shit. Can I get more? All right well I guess I'll just fill the whole thing.
This should be enough for another view at least. That's good. Let me get the key and then I have
to go back through that. It's gonna be annoying. How do I get back there? This is a disaster.
I'm just gonna run. Don't go down there. Okay and then it's this way and then I think I'm kind of
lost. I think it's this way and up to get to that door. He's not gonna follow me all the way over
here right? I don't- I don't remember. It's up. That's all I remember is up. I think I have to
plug in this thing. Yeah where are you going? I don't- I'm trying to backtrack back to where
that door was. I think it's this way. I hope I'm right. Is this wrong? This is too far back.
That was right. No no no no that is right. Wait what? You scorned too much dude. It is right.
Is the dev in chat? Is it right? Can the dev tell me what's right? Dude you scorned too much.
Oh I went too far. Did I go? Help. I actually want help. Backseat me please. It's too far back.
Okay. Too far back. Phew. Are we doing good? Yes. My scornometer is low. I can help you out
there in a minute. Oh thank goodness. I'm gonna leave it at that. Full ammo. Pretty much full
health and on to the next area. Looks like I am gonna heal again. How's the audio? Are we good?
Are the levels good today? It's this way. Huge guy. Okay huge guy. Check over here. Hey! You know
what? Oh there's two things over there. Oh my jeff. I've had enough of that bullshit.
This is really expanding here. This is going a long way. I don't even remember where. I gotta
go all the way back for stuff maybe? I don't know. Okay. Oh shit. Um okay. This way? I guess. Hey
Jerma I'm the creator of scorn. Just wanted you to know the easiest way to complete the game.
All right. Music just changed. What is that thing? Oh my god. I'm not gonna. Am I? No I'm not.
Who's responsible for this? Yous?
You're still. Ah! You're gonna stop me from doing this? I'm just going in. Oh all right. I'm in. I
made it. I made it. I'm good. I'm good. Is that a map? It's like where I. No it's a puzzle. Okay.
I'm going back up. Ah! I'm fine. Am I going the right way? I don't know. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Come here. That thing is terrifying. All right. What a weird thing. I hope I'm going
the right way. Is this right? I don't know. Oh what's that sound? Oh it's one of those things.
Okay all right. I'm good. Would you ever play this in VR? That would be horrifying. Go that way
too. Boy. Oh! Health. It has hands. How much health do I have? Let's take one. Okay so now I can
go down. Oh my goodness. They're everywhere. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Die already. All right. We're good. I need four dots to get in here. This game so looks so cool.
It really does. It's. All right. I. It's good. It's very good. But I don't know how good.
Does that make any sense? So now I got to get back down. I think I have to walk just straight
down right? Down here. Jeez. All right. Now what? Dude. Now what? What am I like turn? Am I turning
into something? All right. Here comes the puzzle. This is impossible. This is not possible. Oh.
Um. I mean this is where I came from. Isn't it? I missed the hallway back here. Did I? The puzzle
room down here in the bottom layer. I mean like here. Um. I didn't go over here. Right. Well I
can't go that way. Did I go both directions here? I can't go over there. Did I go this way? Yeah. I
can't go over this way. All right. Um. I don't. I don't get it. If I can't do that maze puzzle.
I'm gonna. I'm gonna say go down. Hmm. Like down here. I don't have one of those. This is a new
weapon. What is this? This is like a shotgun. Cool. Oh the middle ones are shotgun. The outer
ones are pistol. So I must have all the weapons in the game now right? Yeah. I have to. I have
all the weapons in the game. This is the. I don't want to use this frequently. Although let me
reload it. Three shots. Good to go. Good to go. Let's go this way. Can't go that way. So let's
go over here. Well I'm gonna use it because if there's a time to use it it's right now.
Two shots to kill the big guys. You got it. Okay. Where are you?
Where are you? I'm moving so slow. Holy shit. I'm moving one mile per hour when I reload.
You made me cry today. I'm sorry. Whatever. I didn't do anything. What about the time that you
made me cry today? Jeremy you're stupid. You didn't do the puzzle fast enough. Stupid. Oh yes. So good
luck trying to remember where the hell all these were. I know where this one is. It's right here.
It looks like I only got two more bubbles. How close am I to the end of the game? The last third
or something. Two more bubbles can fit and I have all the weapons. You're close. Two bubbles. I think
I'm alive. Oh it was a shortcut back. All right. So where were those two? I already got that. Okay
looking for the door of the bubble doors. Wasn't there a bubble door up here? I feel like there is.
Right. Where's the bubble door? This way. I'm going in. All right. Can I do this one? No. Oh that's
the- I gotta get all three of them up there. I get it. All right. So how do I go? I gotta go to the
other bubble door and come down. All right. I know. I know. I'm going. Here we go. There's another
bubble door. Where is that bubble door? Is it straight down? It's all the way over here right?
Is it on this floor? Can you please say bubble door ten times fast? Bubble door. Bubble door.
Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Hold on. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble
door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door.
I can do it a few times. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Bubble
door. Bubble door. Bubble door. Is it a handful of times? It's not this way. Is it all the way
up or down? I don't remember. I think it's over here. It's down. Down. Down. Down. Down. Down.
Far left. Um yeah but I mean I uh far left from where? Like from where I'm standing right now
this way? Like this way left? Because there's nothing here. I swear to god I saw it. Where?
I gotta get around there. I have to keep going down. Down. Down. Down. Down. How do I get down
from here? How do I get down from here? Can I go down from here? I think I can get down here right?
Can I get there from here? No I can't get there from here. This is all blocked off. Um and there's
nothing this way. Ceiling? Down around here? It's not this way right? Yeah scream at me if I'm going
too far the wrong direction because I genuinely don't fucking know where I'm going. Um is it though?
It is isn't it? Yeah. I wish I had like a fucking compass. All right so from here I have to be down
you're saying. How do I get all the way down here? Can I go this way? And then backwards? No? And then
down this way and then around and backwards? Oh there it is okay. Score! I was gonna press it but
oh okay. Wasn't there a huge guy over here? I distinctly remember a huge guy. Can we see
the other side? That's like a shortcut back. All right so what do I do now? All right I open that.
Okay shotgun please. Geez. Candy corn? If candy corn had 30% less flavor I'd like it. All right I
got health. I'm out of ammo though that's bad. I have zero ammo. I hope I don't have to kill
anything because that would not work out. Um there's another one of these I can activate back there.
I wonder which one it is. All right let's open it. Why are you playing this like an E3 demo?
Uh am I? No I'm not. Why? Is it because of the amount of times I've gone? Okay so okay.
That's why. It's because the amount of times that I've done something and gone.
Okay. All right so I think we're going left. What do you want? You want to be quiet? Would
you want me to not say a word? Fine I'll give you the anti-E3 playthrough.
This is unfair. Unfair horse shit. That's unfair dog shit. I better not be far away. Please don't
put me far away. This is not bad. What the fuck? Okay whatever just go. So I have to fight two
huge things. Okay good to know. Take the shotgun out. It's two dodge two. I could also run. I'm
gonna run. Is there anything else over here to do? Nope. Go run. I forgot you go one mile per I can't.
Ah go go go go go up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up
hurry hurry go go go go go. I'm good. Another super hard section. Did I miss? Oh my god.
Are you still alive?
All right time to go complete this. Good luck remembering how they get how to get back there.
Can you just help me? Wait what from here? Where do I go? All right I got it. Thank you.
So now the machine is over here. Right yes. All right it's time. It's time to be time to complete
a puzzle. Go out that way. All right let's go. How does this work? I I don't I don't understand
what's happening. Oh I do understand what's happening. All right. Okay wait I need to get
it up. Okay where do I have to get it? It's got to be up the top. How do I get it up there?
How do I get it up in the two slots above where I need to go? You know what I mean? I I can't move.
I there's nowhere for me to put the ball. Even up there I wouldn't be able to connect it.
So the ball is staying in the same place but it's three different mazes. But the issue is
how do I get the ball up to the top when there's no way to move it to get it into those two slots
at the top? How do I get it up? I don't get how I get it up there. Oh I see. I see one. I see. How
do I get it up there? Yay. I can't let go of this. Um where do I go from here? What happened? What
the hell happened? Oh the okay that was weird because look it was it was blocking me on. Wait
that was really weird. Okay I thought I couldn't go up here. I had a lot of collision on that. I
didn't I actually didn't think I could cross over it. No no like I'm serious. I got stuck. I thought
this was like I thought the I thought this was blocking the path because I got stuck on it.
You saw I got stuck. Like yeah see I was like oh shit I can't go up here. There's collision on
some of that stuff. Weird. What happened? Nothing's still alive. Oh I got like ripped. Jesus.
I won't do that ever again I promise. I'm done with that. You're not going to hear that for the
rest of the day. I've almost completely turned into whatever I'm turning into. Am I controlling
it? No. Where even are we? I got out of my system. I'm gonna clear these because I don't want to do
them again. What's going on over here? This area is cool. Very interesting stuff. Very interested.
So up I guess. What is in here? All right that wasn't easy. All right I'm done. I get it now. I
know what you mean. What is in here? Go in and fucking find out. Why you oh what is in here?
Go in and find out. Like why would I ask that like rhetorically out loud?
That is that is E3 demo talk. I get you. I understand now. Wrapping around this corner
right? I know what you mean. It fills air. Interesting. Okay so this is all right so an alien
species landed on earth and started to like assimilate people. I mean this is like oh look
we're this right this looks kind of like old god type of stuff. Jesus. I guess they've grown
under their heads. Alien tech yeah. What's the point of doing that? Oh yeah um just like open up
their rib cage and like peel their skin back and just peel it and just staple it. But what why?
But what? What's this for? It's just unnecessary. Well that's weird. I can go down. I can go this
way too. Looks like there's a lot of places to go. Um let me go up first here. But this is
different. What's this? Babies? Okay we're gonna go this way. No we're not. We're gonna go the other
way. I'm talking. It's a gel. Okay is it I don't know like I don't get it. You just stole Austin
Powers mojo. So what do I do with that? I guess I'm gonna wait is there another place to go? No.
Do you want to play the Austin Powers theme song? Would that be good? Would that be fun?
I can't take this back. I don't want to play the Austin Powers theme song because I feel like it
would ruin the rest of the game and we're getting to like the big climax. Look at those faces in
here. Oh I should have done that. I shouldn't have done that. I should not have done that.
I don't I shouldn't have done that. Did he get up? I don't think he gets up. Not yet at least.
Plenty of health. Nice. All right good. Very good very good very good.
Ammo. Fill it up. Looks good. I'm gonna load the guns all up. That one's all good. This one is all
good. All right um so I imagine I take this one too. Will they fight each other? Excuse me. I don't
get it but whatever. I take this fucking thing. Do you fit in here? No. I don't know where to take
this. I can't weigh this down. What do I do with this body? I don't want to keep holding this. This
is fucking weird. This is gross. I don't want to keep holding this. Um where do I put it? If I run
this way what do I do with this? Jesus. Okay it's a full thing of uh of juice. Wait. Uh oh. So I put
this back on here and I filled this. So this person's- I'm gonna ruin this whole thing if I do
this. I'll do it for one second. No I'm not gonna. Fine. Fuck it. What if I care really?
It didn't do anything. We need two of them. You need two. So I gotta get the other one or whatever
okay. This one's gonna get up and I have to fight it. Can I go back this way? It's blocked off right?
Mm-hmm. Yep. I'm in. This time it's gonna get up and fight. Yeah there's no doubt in my mind. Time
to fight it. Why am I- why am I- I'm like a tree. All right I gotta shoot the sides right? Are those
explosive? Oh my god they are. Oh my god. I think I'm dead in one hit. Move. See ya. What? Oh come
on. So you gotta wait till he runs out of gas. You've run out of gas already. Run out of fucking gas!
Oh you just triple- what would he get the lock and load? I just got triple tapped
direct by two free grenades in a fucking row. Are you kidding me? He led me and lock and loaded me.
What do I do? What? Oh shoot him in the- I don't know what's going on. What do I get that? I don't
get it. Did I screw up? I want to shake your hand. Dude just fucking get out of here. Should I shoot
him in the legs or something? Okay this guy. If you kill me right now I am going to eat this keyboard.
Do you understand? All right open up! Open! What's going- dude how do I- the back is back is back. Oh
my god damn it dude. Come on. It takes some- freak it! Just move your fucking hand.
What? Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Oh shit another gun. Jesus.
Give me a fucking- that's not enough. That's not enough. I need another one. Is there another one
even back here? Oh this one. How do I get over there? Good luck. Oh look at my health. That's bad.
There's a claw. How do I get that to move? I don't know. I actually don't know. Kapow. Kapow. Kapow.
Shoot it? That didn't work. What? Did I shoot this? Holy shit. Okay. Do I have to fight this again?
I hope not. Do not. Dude no. I have to fight another one of these. I have to fight it again.
You've got to be fucking kidding me. I don't want to fight this thing again. I have no health. I'm
gonna lose. Dude this sucks. I don't want to fight this thing. Shit can I- what if I explode it?
When it goes down for gas I'm gonna shoot this. Going down for gas. Oh my god I just did it.
What did I just do? Are you dead? What did I- did I just do it? Cool. All right. All right I got it.
What is even going on? I have way more questions than the beginning of the game.
What's happening here? Um I can't use any other weapon. I can't take this off. All right well
we got both of them filled up here. Wait is it saying I can't pick this up because my hands
are covered in weird tree shit? Are you serious? I can't do this. Um how do I get this off? Okay.
What's this? That scream. It's like a Tom and Jerry sound. Excuse me where's the health?
Score. Reload. I think you're actually soft-locked. What? No I'm not. I bet you I jump in that suit
and I get healed. Yeah I just gotta get the thing, run to that suit, and jump right in it.
All right I can't do this. So I have to go over here and then down. What's this? Okay.
Wait should I just get in this now? I can't. All right so what about over here? This looks like a
track or an elevator. I have this key. Oh come on. No. Oh yes. I was gonna say can I not interact
with it? Right I can't do this. Okay so now rip it off. Get in the suit. What else is over here?
This is a five bubble door. I don't have a five bubble key. Am I seeing this right? What's going
on? What is happening? Don't look. Score. I'm not pressing it again. All right so let's get this
thing ripped off. Okay and let's go. That's just it. That's just ammo. That's ammo for the gun.
All right um what's going on? Did you just come back? Shit um okay. Really? Okay I'm gonna get
the thing ripped off. I'm gonna open this door. Okay what does that do for me? What is happening?
Ah should I shoot this? Oh fuck. Okay hold on. What? Why am I? Dude are you all right?
Uh dude are you cool? What's he doing? Hello? Score. I got scorned. It was poisonous. What do
I do here? Should I just reset the game? All right I'm gonna quit. Now go to main menu right? Back to
main menu and then continue the game. But don't do that again. Okay so now this is I have to go get
bit by that thing again. Pick up the ammo. Let me heal. How much health do I have? Let's heal.
All right so get bit. Pick up the thing. Grab the key. Pick it up. All right good. Nice.
So now I have the key to get out of here. I've got full stack of the bombs. I'm okay.
All right where's the door? Isn't it over here? Okay it's right here. So I get bit. Wait no I have
to get bit and then come do this. Whatever this is. Right so let's get bit. Come do this. No just do
the door. All right what's the fastest place to get bit? Right here and then run across. Let's go.
I need the mojo. Where's the mojo? Where is it? Where is the mojo? Is it on my? Let me just open
this door. It'll stay open. Okay where's the mojo? How am I gonna get back there? Okay how am I gonna
get bit and run back and do this? Am I gonna have enough time? Run run run. Maybe I might just have
just barely enough time. Okay I'm gonna try it. Okay here we go. Thanks for lying. Thanks for the
whole experience bubble of Warcraft experience taken from me and health. I appreciate it.
Just going straight. Damn okay. Oh it's just like the this is like the extraction machine I think.
Do I actually have to? Can I even make it from here? I feel like I'm not gonna make it.
Isn't there it was a close there's a closer one. No I'm not gonna make it.
This is longer. I'm just gonna try it. Whatever I'm just gonna try it. Go go go go go.
Huh wait I have to perform surgery on myself? Oh my goodness. Dude what? I got my mojo back baby.
Oh shit they're all coming for me. I got my mojo back. All right I'll get me out of here.
All right wait you blocked it back. You blocked it off. That gives me a headache.
Look down. I know I see. I'm holding my intestines. Bro give me a break man. Are you kidding me?
Geez. Holy Jesus man. Fucking relax. What the fuck? That's huge. That's all right. What's going on?
I still have no idea what's happening. Oh all right I'm going back. I'm going down.
I can plug the other thing in right? Let's go. Oh wrong way. All right here we go.
What happens now? We're going up. I can hear somebody moving. What the fuck? What the fuck was
that man? Uh what? Switch? What do you mean switch? Wait how do I switch? Oh wait what are they doing?
How do I switch? How do I switch? What button is that? Switch what? How do I switch this?
You wanted to go first? I don't have one of those. Do you? I don't have one of those either.
Shit. Well the grand alien plan is ruined. We can't move. We can't go anywhere. Why
won't this open? What's the problem? All right you stay here. I'm gonna go investigate.
No? No am I crazy? I look like I made it a plastic. Oh here it is. Are we aliens or are we
what are we? Are we aliens? Uh watch out behind you. These should both have it right? Sorry.
There can only be one. Am I missing something? The way this camera angle looks like a piano is
gonna fall on this guy. Any second now. Um can I move this or something? I'm missing. Eyes, fire,
go right to the goal. Eyes, fire, hoof to the goal. Should I just? Should I go? I'm biting my lip like
crazy. Should I just go this way and like explore over here? Can I even walk over here? Can I like
stop this from happening? Wait what am I doing? All right they both need one of these. All right
they both need one of. I don't put his hand on it. Do I just put can I place the body down here?
I feel like that's what I have to do. Do we weigh more? Oh shit what's happening? I can't move.
I can't turn. All I can do is walk straight. Wait what? This this for this thing again? What?
Hey thanks for fucking standing there the whole time. Thanks for standing there. Really?
Did I not wait did I not make it? Is that what we're implying here that I didn't make it to the end?
Wait what? We're 10 feet away from whatever we were doing? That's it? Score. I was really hoping it
was gonna say then it was gonna be on screen. Okay um that was weird so it's oh you're trying to
continue whatever civilization or something but they were these mutated monsters that are stopping
us and I get right to the end and I almost get through whatever the birth canal or something and
then the thing stops me and eats me and consumes me we didn't end up actually doing it. I got there
but I didn't make it. I'll just I'll just watch a baddie video about press continue. Okay can I
I'm curious hold on a second can I walk through with this one or do you have to walk through
with this one? No okay that's the only way all right. Why do I keep stabbing him? What's with
the keep stabbing stab stab? I don't get it why do I have to keep stabbing this? I think this is
bugged up. There's no definitive answer for anything. I mean that was crazy that was okay
that last 20 minutes was that was insane. I'll watch a couple videos on it. That was that was
good that was cool. I like that. I very much enjoyed that. And then that's a perfect time to
end the stream too. All right so listen to me this is important. We've got a lot going on this weekend
on Thursday. Thursday I'm going to be playing Gotham Knights sponsored. Are you ready for this?
Friday I'm going to be playing Gotham Knights sponsored. Saturday I'm going to be playing
Gotham Knights sponsored three days in a row. But here's the thing. I'm not just going to play
Gotham Knights. We're going to do another Omega gaming weekend. It's an it's an Omega sponsor
it really is. It's like free. It's like let's go you know what I mean? Like sometimes you just
say fuck it let's go. So the Gotham Knights portion of each one of those streams on Thursday,
Friday and Saturday are only going to be for a couple hours. Then for the remaining three four
five plus hours whatever we're going to do something else. So keep this in mind I am
contractually obligated to stream three days in a row. Some of it's going to be Gotham Knights.
So I have to be here. I am not going to say to you guys oh you know it's like I just streamed
on Thursday. See you on Sunday. No I'm contractually obligated to be here. So we're going to play
Gotham Knights for a few days in a row. But we're also going to do a bunch of other shit too.
I want to play horror games this weekend. I want to play the puppet combo games the new ones that
came out. I want to play Breath of the Wild this weekend. Yeah Gotham Knights looks like it could
be really fun. I don't know very much about it. I know it's um it's a game set in uh Arkham. That's
not not Arkham. I meant to say Gotham. It's a game set in no Gotham is the city. Arkham is not the
city. Gotham is the city. I don't know why I thought it was Arkham. That's my bad. What a fake fan.
No I just screwed up. I was trying to say that the city Gotham it takes place in Gotham not Arkham.
Anyways we're going to play Gotham Knights for three days and a bunch of other shit. I'm actually
pretty excited. So I'll see you on Thursday where we're not going to start with uh with Gotham
Knights. Gotham Knights will appear for like a couple hours right in the middle of all these
streams. It's going to be super variety. We are going to be changing games every two or three hours
and I'm going to wear the Nightwing shirt. You better look at your ass. I'm gonna like why am
I such a frog today? Well that's going to be the end of this stream. I gotta why am I so froggy
today? Listen to this. I'll see you guys on Thursday, Friday, and Saturday starting around
uh four o'clock pacific. Gotham Knights, Breath of the Wild, Puppet Combo, and some other shit.
We'll see. Scoring was cool. That was a lot of fun. I the first 10 minutes I was like oh shit this is
a puzzle game. But there's enough interesting stuff happening and I think a lot of the weird
horror elements were enough to really keep you going. I think it's good. I thought it was fun.
It was it was definitely an experience. I'd say that. But yeah I'll see you guys on Thursday
or uh well is it Omega gaming weekend or is it just Thursday, Friday, and then one day on Saturday?
It's good to be back. Omega sponsor weekend. And I like you know it's kind of interesting though.
I will have a hard date for you guys for the Battleaxe stream within the next couple of weeks.
This is happening really soon. What's the Battleaxe stream? I'm gonna dodge a Battleaxe
in real life. That's it. Is the stream is that stream gonna be 10 minutes? It's gonna be as
long as I want it to be. So I'll be don't don't worry. Oh all right I'll talk to you guys soon.
See you later. Good night. Thanks for watching. See you Thursday. Goodbye.