Okay, hello. I had to take care of Otto. Kill him? Take care of Otto. This game's kind of loud.
There we go. All right, so what do you guys want to do? I don't know. Do you want to do? Oh,
we'll go open it. Open up my stream. I'm opening it. Okay. It's like you're getting tea. Not for
mine. Mine won't start for some reason.
Well, it's a good to do window capture or fuck it. We'll just do this.
It's already here. All right, so we have trivia murder party. A serial killer is running an absurd
trivia game out of the family run murder hotel he grew up in. Can you survive? Role models. Excuse
me. Did you say family run murder hotel? Yes, that is that is correct. That is role models.
Everybody's somebody. So who are you? The planner, the flake, the sassy one.
Step into the lab and find out. We just do them all. Let's start a trivia murder party too. All
right. Trivia murder party too is what we're starting with. Wait, it's coming. I'm going to
give you guys. I'm going to tell you guys the secret code. Oh, if it'll load. Is it going to
load? There we go. All right. I need to set up some stuff. Audience full screen. Turn it down
a little. That's it. Could be a little loud. All right. Now I have to do this. I do the hide
subtitles. Max players. Eight room code hiding. I got it. Don't worry. Okay.
Filter US centric questions. Reduce the number of US questions. What? Why? Require Twitch.
Require players to be logged into Twitch. I kind of need the tutorials. I don't need extended
timers. Okay. So now this thing is, let me just do this for a second. Hold on. Hold on. Everybody,
everybody relax. Okay. I'm going to run bathroom. Go to the bathroom. Go to the bath. Go get tea.
Cause something, something's messed up over here. I need to look at this. This shouldn't be doing
this. What's going on? Turn that off. Why is it doing this? So is this trivia about murderers
or are they going to murder us if we get them wrong? This trivia is about surviving. I don't
know. I'm bringing up murderpedia just in case. Is that being captured? It's glitching out of it.
All right. I think I got it. I got it. I got it. All right. That should be fine. All right.
Let me make sure this is going to work. All right. I have a room code here for you guys in a second.
In just a moment when he's ready. I got to break this down. So then I can put it in the discord.
This code is going to be in the sub discord. Those of you subs, it's going to be there in
just a second after they get it. I'm ready. He's done. I will just tell you what it is.
Wait, is he streaming still? No, no. All right. I'm going to mute and I'm going to tell you what
it is. Are you ready? Where do we type it in? I was in the back. You go to jackbox.tv
and you are going to write in the room code. Okay. Ready? Yes. I'm about to mute.
But I have to get in first here. The code is I remember this. I have to get in first
like on my phone. I have to get in. I remember the shit. Well, like another browser, right? Yeah.
I fucked this up last time we did this. They would try. They've nobody said anything
trying to get me to fuck this up. All right. The code is. Okay. Room requires Twitch login.
Yeah. You have to be connected to Twitch. Yeah. You're not. Yeah. I got it. Yeah. You did. There's
a little dropdown that says Twitch. You clicked a little top left dropdown and click on the Twitch
button and you should be able to log in. Yeah. Okay. Now what was the room password? The room
password is going to work. I'm in. So now, Hey discord, Hey discord, you're going to want to
type in. Here we go. Same joke again. Yeah. You'd be doing the same thing again. Just the same joke
again. Go for it. That's all I have. Some people have gotten in. Bye. And there's still some slots.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. No, there's not. Join it. There was like a little
bookshelf thing. MCFN on jackbox.tv. You can participate in the game. Oh, your little dude
looks like Easter. Like a total nerd. Ready? Everybody's in. Okay. Sit back and relax. Where's
the everybody's in button? All right. We've got MCFN join it. What about me? Yeah. I feel like
my browser is in control of this because I'm the one that enabled it to start and I have a skip
button for this. I think, yeah, you are. I don't know how I got VIP. You got VIP because you got
in first and I didn't. As long as one of us is out there. Okay. Oh yeah. I'm in control.
This is your wake up call. Welcome to Trivia Murder Party. Those free vacation coupons you
received in the mail were a trick luring you into a game with deadly consequences.
How are there 4,700 people in the audience and 3,500 people watching? What is going on?
Whose memoir is titled? Is everyone hanging out without me?
Use your device to answer the question. Whose memoir is titled? Is everyone hanging out with me?
Who are these people? I know who. Two of these people. I know one.
And we die if we don't answer this. In the correct answer. Who got the question right?
I got that wrong. The rest of you come with me. American questions off. Why would we do this?
The three of us are Americans. I don't want to be American. The hairdryer is broken. Sorry.
I can't believe there's 7,000 people in the audience. I know. This one's real straightforward.
A player who rolls the highest will die. What? But we've got some help to make this more interesting.
You have an extra die that you can give to whoever you want to make their odds worse.
I didn't know who wrote that memoir. Oh shit. I need to read more books. Well, good luck, Star.
More celebrity memoirs. The player with the highest total dies. Oh no. Awesome sauce is dead.
That's the worst way to die. Kill bonus. Holy shit. Wow. We have 15,000 people in the audience today.
Don't freak out. But you're a ghost now. Keep playing and you just might steal some
life force and win the game. Oh, by the way, the audience is a player. Now you can join
the audience. Whatever. It's like super low pressure. This is just fucking up everything.
Let's keep moving. Did I not get name dropped in the song? Oh, I know this one. I know this one.
I heard that shit. I know the song.
Do I get points for answering it instantly? Time's running out. I don't even know who made
this song or what the song is. It's like a song for a Girl Scout camp. It's like a little kid song.
Oh, I got it wrong. Fuck. Why do I know this? Because I have a shitload of nieces and nephews.
I hope you're good with instructions. Follow as many rules as you can before time runs out.
The player who follows the fewest rules correctly dies. The rules are already on your device. Go,
go. The most disobedient player dies. Star, what's going on, Star? Star, what are you doing?
I'm so confused. There's not a lot for me to do during this game.
I guess I'll update my LinkedIn account. Almost out of rules time. Star, I didn't realize it was
timed. I didn't realize. I voted for Star. I wrote this next question just for you. If you get it
right, I will punish everyone else. Wait, what? Where do I keep more than half my bones?
How come this person gets to punish everybody? And I guess the audience can answer too.
What, me old bones? What are these questions? I think you have to pay attention. I think he
said like a line. Well, I have to stream mute it because then I'll hear myself. This isn't fair.
Time's almost up. I can't do like a delay. Did you get the question right?
You succeeded. There's subtitles. I can't read. The rest will suffer.
Yeah, I got subtitles on. Oh no. It's the classic game Chalices. I've given each safe player a
poison pellet. Pick a chalice to drop your poison in. What do you mean? This is freaking me out.
Now it's your turn to play. Pick a chalice to drink from. Oh no. Drinking from a cup with a
poison pellet will kill you if you trust doctors. Drink, drink, drink. Yeah, I mean you have to go
now. Let's see what everyone drank. A big skull. Yeah. No, I'm not going to put the poison in the
skull. That's too obvious. You know, that's why I clicked. I'm safe. A clever. It was too obvious.
That's why I didn't poison it. Why there's 17,000 people in the audience game part?
Because somebody has like four computers turned down and they're going to burn down their house.
Next question. Yeah, bot farm. Bot farming there is somewhere. What's inside a down comforter?
I don't know. That's a pretty easy question. Cigarette butts. It's not even out.
Who picked this? Everybody. One of you is still alive. Packing peanuts. What's the significance
in me being dead? I can't play anymore. I think you can influence the game. Ah, the lost art of
letter writing. I'm going to dictate a message to you. Write down as much of what I say as you can.
Everyone else will be typing too. And if anyone does a better job than you, you die.
Get ready. What are we doing? Starting letter now. Dear local action news team. Do you take requests?
I would like to see more of this future story. What are we doing? That share positive images.
And last segments about the crimes that I have committed. What's happening? Just wait. Viewers
are tired of all the sad stories I am directly responsible for. Okay. Time's up. Now let me just
see what we have here with a quick scan. What's the result? No, you tricked me. You were supposed
to type out what that said. But did anyone do better than you? We were supposed to type that
whole thing out. You got outperformed. That's not even close to what I said. Again, I can't hear
anything that's being said on the screen. I hear this guy talking. Oh God. It's all right. I'm
still doing all right. Dead last. We're good. Let's try another one. I like what has three hearts.
You could be good on that one. You guys confused me so I stopped.
This is a trick question, I think, is it? Almost out of time. A lobster doesn't want lobster.
This. I want to show you something. This is the one with the big creepy mirror.
The ghost of my aunt Mildred loves to write words on mirrors. Yeah. She has her own consistent
handwriting. Now aunt Mildred is going to write a different word. What? But so will everyone else.
Draw a word on the mirror and maybe you'll trick someone into thinking it's aunt Mildred's.
I let the drawing begin. What the fuck attention to draw word here and try to spot my auntie.
Oh, I got it already. I got it.
Everyone's going to write some stupid nonsense words to choose from.
Oh, I got it. Type the word that aunt Mildred wrote or you die.
You can tell because aunt Mildred did not write sucks. With the real aunt Mildred,
please stand up. Yeah, we're good. We're safe. Oh, you got it. Oh, man. Mirrors are such bad luck
for me. I wonder if this is more or less ghost than you find in most elevators. Makes you think.
Let's keep moving. I want a germa to die. According to his website,
what does my boy Bob Vila recommend I use to get the blood out of the lobby carpet?
This is this old house. This old house with Bob Vila. My father used to watch the show every
fucking day. Time's almost up. I don't think I got this right though. It feels like boomer questions.
It is. Who picked this? I was going to pick that too. Everyone is wrong. Time for consequences.
I'll remember that though. Yeah. Good advice. I have a lot of scratch tickets. What a quirky
last minute gift. Yeah, there's going to be a scratch and find three dollar signs to live.
Do you want me to screen share to you on discord? I'll give you cash for every dollar sign you find.
But if you scratch off even one skull, you die. If it doesn't mess you up. Shouldn't. I'm reading
get to scratching some titles and everything now like a good boy.
Come on, you could scratch more. Oh, I think I'm dead.
I already scratched. What? The contest is almost over.
How the fuck did you do that? That's bullshit. No way. No way. You've got. That's wall.
Act. You're all dead. Only one of you is still alive. I'm dying too. It makes it better.
Now, let me see if I can do this. Congrats on making it here. I'm going to give you a category
books written in the first person. Tap each answer that fits the category and then press submit.
Does that work? You just mute it. Time is almost up. It's really laggy. Let's see the right answer.
Yeah, too laggy. You move forward one space for each correct answer.
Yeah. Well, then I guess you guys can see the code. Did you think it was going to be just you?
That's cute. If it goes, then they can try to escape and win the game.
Here's everyone's next question and they get a third chance to help them catch up to you.
Time is almost up. I think that's I think that's right.
Comes the next question. Plagues of Egypt in the book of Exodus.
Lightning. Zap. Yikes. There's a ghost right behind you.
You're better than I thought. Closing in. Uh oh, here comes trouble.
It's only darkness. Can't you land locations? Everybody knows that.
No, I don't. Everybody knows that out there. No such thing as peanut acres.
Of course peanut acres is real. It's the only one I didn't pick. How do you know?
You stole some yummy life for us. There we go. The darkness approaches.
Beyonce albums. I don't know. Only boomers would know any of this shit. I got them both fucking
wrong. No, I didn't. Another life force swap. Come on, Star. Stage names. Bingo.
What? That's Val Kilmer. It's not Val Kilmer. Metric system units of measurement. Oh no,
Americans. We're Americans. Time is almost up. Am I muted? I shouldn't be muted. Am I muted?
No, I've been hearing you. Don't listen to her. Rise. Okay, now you're muted. What the
fuck is a sausage phone? A sauce-a-phone? Susophone. Oh, I thought it was sauce-a-phone.
Fuck, I'm gonna listen. You said sausage. Another life swap. Sauce-a-phone? I thought it was an A.
Where do you think you're going? You need a perfect answer for your final escape.
Oh, that's why I can't hear him. And that includes the third answer choice now too.
No, that wasn't Miss Melissa McCarthy. Yeah, somebody made it already. No, it's over.
Okay, apparently you just killed. All right. Awesome sauce wins. All right, that's it for that
one. That was all right. A little too draggy for me, in my opinion. I don't know about you guys.
I think I felt the same way about the last one too. I don't understand a single thing.
Wait, I think there should only be video game questions to cater to us, you know? Yeah.
Where's the questions like, you know, what character from The Legend of Zelda has
the biggest heart instead of which sea creature has three? You know, we don't. We all know that.
That's the question I liked, actually, because I got that one right.
Yeah, where's the video games only? All right, we're gonna do what's the one below it?
At least like big fucking nerd questions. We need a new code just to be clear that you'd be
showing on screen. Yep. Okay, and you should join before me so that I'm not the master.
That's what I'm gonna do. Role models. Everybody somebody. So who are you? The planner? The flake?
The sassy one? Step in the lab and find out. I'm getting, okay, hold on. I'm getting a huge
amount of people are saying this one sucks. Okay, I like the sound of joke boat.
This one is all this one is friends only. This won't work with chat. Oh, awesome sauce
because they won. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Fuck yeah. Yeah, when you win, you need
to give us money. It's not serious. Thanks a lot. I will do joke boat people saying joke boats like
the actual like the good one bro models, I guess is only with like people that are present.
Oh, we'll try. Yeah, make sure this is set correctly. Plays eight subtitles on
allow room code hiding. Thank you. Twitch integration.
Manual censoring. Yep. I don't want to have any fucking issues there.
Audience. Okay. All right. Twitch is required. Good to go. So I hold on. Let's see what happens.
I could do the same joke again. Welcome aboard. I'm Chuck Hull, your captain and
go ahead and sign in. We just joined first. And then I will just I'm just gonna. Oh, wait,
you guys can see this. Oh, yeah, don't go and don't come in yet. Anytime now. And hold on.
Why is it taking so long? What's wrong? Come on jackbox.tv servers. What's going on here?
All right, I am in. Oh, please. Whenever you're ready.
I beat you. How did you beat me? I beat you by a lot. Wait, why did you beat me? Okay, I got
day discord. Wait, wait, make sure of actually gets in. Okay. Okay. Discord. Quick before the
ship leaves the dock. You ready? Here it comes. Fuck, I forget it. Hold on. It was literally four
characters. Let's move it, people. Yeah, our character portraits are mixed up. What are you
talking about? I look like you. You look like. I don't know. Ashley has pigtails for sure.
One more person. Come on. And then I'm I look like Ashley Lang. All right. Oh, please. Here we go.
You're ready. Everybody's in. Everybody is in. There's the code on the screen. Join the audience.
This is the joke factory. Whatever. I don't even know what it's called. I get it. Get it.
Here's tonight's itinerary. We're going to write some jokes and then test them out on stage. But
first things first, it's brainstorming time. Before we jump into the jokes, let's do a little
writing exercise to get inspired on your device. You'll be prompted to write various topics like
animals, people or objects. Fill in whatever you think has a lot of comedic potential.
If another player uses one of your topics in a short, you'll get a bonus. Bobby, generate as
many as you can. You have 45 seconds starting now. Great joke topic. This writing exercise is
ending soon. Follow the steps on your device to write two jokes. I did so bad. Trust your
instincts. Okay. Yeah. None of mine were funny. No. Okay. Hold on. Complete the jokes on your device.
Okay. Um, this is, how, how can I make a punchline from this? I can't think with you talking.
If I'm ever going to be a comedy writer, I have to fucking nail this.
There's a joke for me button. Please make it funny for me. I, but this is the, this is,
uh, God damn it. I have to do this. I have to do this.
We're going to find out if you're a real comedian or not right now. You'll find out.
This is your legacy. Yeah. No, no. Fuck. I shouldn't have done that.
I want to redo on mine. I didn't realize I had another minute.
Now we're talking to comedy. Oh my God. Damn it. I want to redo. I'm done with my jokes. You guys
done? Yeah. That's why, like I, I don't have a timer in my window, but if I realized it was
like 50 more seconds, I would have thought. Oh, we have 50 more seconds. Shit. Yeah. I thought
it was a race. I want to, can I go back? Joke boat. Captain, let me in. Oh, the time pressure was
like happy music in the chat, like scrolling so fast. Yeah. And Jeremiah talking about his,
his life story. Mute me, mute me, mute me. I thought I had like 10 seconds.
I did not write poop for the record. Here we go. You ever notice how cruise line captains drive
like this, but barge captains drive like this? No. Okay. Here's our first comment. I apologize
for my joke already, even though, you know, it's exactly, here we go. Remember to say your catch
phrase. A group of spoons walk into a bar and pee pee poo poo. No way. No bubble wrap.
You got to read it. What does perform the joke mean? I guess you've just, I don't know. Just do it.
Oh, the buttons went away. I'm so dumb. I thought rap songs were good. Okay.
What? They call me DNA. What the fuck does that mean? That was pretty cool.
Better joke. Look now. Well, I really don't want to compete with pee pee poo poo. It's impossible.
You can't compete with pee pee poo poo. You know, you're talking about Twitch chat.
You lost. Whoa. It like rap. That's what it is. You hit them right in the field. They're like,
to you. Wait, you got a bonus? Get that lights mattering of a pause going.
I call my bedrooms a hell because I'm Satan.
My love life is like Napoleon. They always run away. Not your dad's compact car. What?
This is catchphrase. Vote for your favorite joke now. I wish this was like the horror man.
So we get to vote which person dies. No, we're being thrown overboard in the end. I'm sure.
Seven, 70. Our next comic needs an introduction. It's me versus you. My jokes aren't jokes.
I'm a nasty little dry erase board because I'm soaking wet.
Who ordered the flight attendant? I thought it was going to be me. Don't worry. They're all
going to vote for you anyway. I'm going to open up a store that only sells walruses and call it
Walrus Mart. Don't get your strong. Can you explain the joke? How do you not get mine? It's
the perfect setup. It's like a perfect setup. But you're a dry erase board. Don't you get it?
No. I don't have to spell it out for you? Yeah. The one on the right just added
March to the word Walrus. Yeah, but at least it's made sense. And a tip of the hat to you.
What the fuck? Here's another comedian whether you like it or not. I like my friends like I like
my cars. Oh, it's a bitch. This one's going to damage your windows. It's just compacting it.
This whole bit is compact cars. Every joke, the punchline is compact cars. Why are they called
flat earthers and not should be called flat scurfers? Is that your seat? No, I haven't like
bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro has gone twice. I haven't gotten up on the stage once. I'm scared.
I'm going to vote for the compact car comic is better. Sorry, German. I just like the theming.
What was it? Is it his theme? It's not really original. I mean, he's winning.
And how about some points for you? Would you guys know the jackbox meta? Whoever's live stream
is currently live streaming our next comedian. Just go after. Am I, am I allowed to tell my
jokes? Tell them. What are you talking about? They're not other like they just keep calling
people up and I'm like, you're doing so bad and you're so comfortable. Okay. We didn't have
hashtags at tic tac toe. That is very boomer joke. There you go. Here's yours. Oh God. Oh God.
I'm not ready. I'm scared. Go after all that. I'm voting for you, baby. You ever notice how Mr.
Peanut looks like a peanut in a suit? If you win and I, if I lose,
it's a comedy error. People think that's funny. People, people are saying that that was a funny
joke, but my joke that had like setup and new ones. I'm just also, he's not in a suit. That's
right. I'm so brilliant compared to German. Thank you. Thank you. My adoring crowd.
Folks put your hand and hook together for our next comedian. Oh, they want me back.
Encore. They say encore. Give me a break. Have you heard about the big bad wolf challenge?
It's where you exercise till you puff and puff. That's, that's as bad as mine was.
That's actually the auto-generate joke. You, what? You hit the auto-generate button.
I thought I had 10 seconds. Oh my God. I honestly thought if I didn't type it in the next three
seconds, it was going to do nothing. They turned on you. They turned on you real quick. Okay.
Yours was auto-generated. So I have to pick the other one. I still pick the AI over a joke
that bad. That's like when like robots are going to take over the world and you're letting them.
Wait, no, you wait. Yes. Which one is better for me? It even tells you joke for me.
Joe, please joke for me. What a fraud. It was the time. I don't even, I don't remember
what my other one was. Let's keep things going for the next comedy. Okay. We're playing this game again.
Yeah. Now that we all understand, I'm not going to let this smug ass parrot.
My family is like Bigfoot. Don't photograph well. Is that auto-generated?
Yeah. That seems, that seems like a joke for me. All right. German is going to take them down.
Here we go. The big reveal. Let's go. If people think this, whatever.
Hello. My doctor said I have a bad case of the soap operas
because I'm the cleanest I've ever been.
It wasn't an auto joke. Well, that's, I guess I have to pick it. No, it tells you after the vote.
I think if it was. What? Yeah. It's stamped it after. That was a joke for me. Yeah. You guys
voted for the auto joke. Your doctor says you have a bad case of being clean.
A bad case of being cleaned. That's the point. I can't make some noise for our next comment.
I don't choose the prompt. You did get to choose the prompt in a way. What's the difference between
most people and people and people has an end. Oh my God. It made no sense. I didn't pick the most
people and people. Oh, she didn't get to pick the prompt. I didn't. It's very literal. He wrote
the word boomer. He wins. Man. First I compete against pee pee poo poo and now I compete against
boomer. So old I remember when Elbertson was a boomer. Click it. Everybody click it.
What? I forgive you though, Ashley, because you had my top joke of the entire thing which was
I remember people. Thank you. I'm here for you. Oh my God. You won anyway. Nice assist. Assist.
Thank you, Chad. This is a horrible cut up. Let's see.
Yeah, just wait for it to end too. Oh, I'm beating German.
Wake up screaming.
Both of you. How about that?
Well, we're sinking again. There's no time to write jokes from scratch. So here's the plan.
Let's rewrite another comics joke. You'll use the same setup, but we'll attempt to write
a funnier punchline. The better the original joke did, the more points you'll earn for beating it.
Can you steal the spotlight before the boat sinks? Let's find out. I think I understand.
Okay. Wait. That was me. Mine was me responding to it. I'm sorry. I fucked it up. That was me
respond. Whatever. I can't believe I wasted my joke on this. Me too. I was like responding. Fuck.
Whatever. Okay. I need to be clear. When my joke comes up, it's not me telling the joke. It's
Dennis. It's a character thing. That still doesn't help. Hello. Is that your way to pass
off like an offensive joke or something? No. It's not me doing it. It's not me writing this.
It's my character saying this. I'm just waiting for the full redo. Well, full redo. We're going
to the next game after this. Here's the number one. What's the difference between most people
and people? Nothing is the same word, dummy. Oh no, he got scooped. Which version do you like
best? Obviously, and this is not fair to the original comedian because they have time to
figure out what they want to say. Those seems lopsided. You can replace it. Also, like in the
world of comedy, I just feel like bro Baruto just ripped off Ashley and he loses a lot of points
for even trying to reiterate on the joke. Oh, I still won. Yeah, through that guy. He just stole
your joke. Well, we're all stealing jokes here. Yeah, that's just not cool. Remember when that
one comedian did that? My love life is like Napoleon. Significantly shorter than I would have
wanted. A real clash of the titans. That's pretty good. Sorry. Sorry. I picked really bad nouns in
the beginning. One of the questions was two spoons walk into a bar. I got to take responsibility
for writing the word spoon. I don't know. No, no, no, no, no. I'm going for Satan. That's way
better. That little face. It's not me writing this. It's somebody else. They're both good.
I've been watching it all the time and remembering how Dennis definitely is a serial killer. Yeah,
you have to read it in his voice. No, well, don't worry. Okay. Let's all make fun of German
now. You're going to laugh at my joke. Why are they called flat earthers and not go read any book?
What do you think? That's the best one yet. I was merely responding. Maybe phase two of the
boat isn't that bad. You have some comedy. Any book. That's not a joke. That's just a harsh truth.
All right. Gurpers though. Come on.
Notice how Mr. Peanut looks like
fancier German. No. What? Well, you said the name of the streamer. So I don't know. It's going to be
tight. I wrote peanut. Oh my God. 4555. Oh, you beat the reference.
All right. My doctor said I have a bad case of the soap operas because he doesn't have a real
me. You know what I mean? No, I didn't write, you know what I mean?
I do that all the time though. You know what I mean? You guys know what I mean?
I do that all the fucking time. What the fuck just happened? It added you know what I mean on
the end because I didn't I'm still trying to
people voted for it and that's that's even worse. Whoever you are, you're a hero to me.
And you know what? I got you more points. Thank you. I appreciate that. Just throwing throwing
I'm gonna ask you a little dry erase board because dear God, this joke is so bad. I can't even save
it. What's not to understand? Explain it. I can't. I'm not going to explain this. I'm a nasty dry
erase board because right, but you can't be a dry erase board if that's why that's the joke because
it's it's it's sexual. I didn't pick. How am I going to explain this? I mean, I get where you're
going, but it doesn't make any sense. It's like it doesn't work. Oh, he beat you. I wasn't expecting
that. I like my friends. I like my cars. Rumors only. It's gonna be tough. We've got two stream
references. Compact guy is the original car jokesman. It's pretty split. No, that was pretty close.
Which comedian is leaving with me in the lifeboat? Let's find out who deserves it the most. That's
kind of scary. Wow. Okay, we actually if we voted against compact car guy, then German would have
won. Yeah. Well, that was fun. All right. Let's go to the next one. We can do it again. We'll do
we'll do this one again like after we go. We need the redo new players.
Hold on. Wait. Whoa. Whoa. I'm in control. Oh, yeah, you are in control. Oh, well, I just get
I click the board and I'm Chuck Hall. I'll be your host tonight. Tell me what you're doing.
I'll behave. All right. Don't do it yet. Let me don't like don't even press the button.
Toot toot. We got a scoot. Everyone, you know, think of some funny nouns like boomers and, you
know, excellent, which means a toot. Yeah, that's that's good. All right. Join a poopy
pee pee poo poo. Join it. And then when you're in, put it in the discord. We don't have all day.
Ashley's in. And so is star. Okay. Now, let's put this in the discord.
Ashley changed. We all change bodies. This is how it was supposed to be. Just like in try. We don't
have all day. Bagel boy. My more. Oh, oh, okay. I just realized. Okay. Derma put. Derma put what?
Anytime now. Come on in, everybody. Derma puts what? Well, you need to click. Everyone's ready.
I know you got max players. Just making sure because you haven't done it yet.
I got you. You better not talk to me once. I gotta get everyone. This is writer's room.
Silence. Quiet chat. Derma put sun chips in F tier. Let me ask both of your questions really quickly.
Are sun chips good? Would you pick sun chips? Comedians. Here's tonight's itinerary. Yada yada.
Moving on. Okay. There we go. Star.
Star. Really? Okay. I guess it makes sense. Just like my premium cable bundle, this writing
exercise is ending soon. All right. Now it's time to write some comedy. Follow the steps to construct
two jokes. Oh, I forgot to do minus two. Nobody did anything. You talked about sun chips. Oh,
I said the word sun chip. Yeah. I ain't picking that one. Oh God. I should not have picked this.
The only jokes I can think of are very bad. Don't stop it. Very bad. Don't get out. I will. I will
censor your joke. I'm not doing it, but I just like, I, I am in a situation now where there's,
this is very difficult to not make this. Don't do it. Awful. Don't do it. Do something. Skip.
Do something else. Oh God. I'm sorry. You, I fucking around. I will actually boot you from
this call and I will boot you from this. I will censor you. I'll do it. Don't make me do it.
I'm going to do a joke. Okay. You should be starting on your second joke soon. If you
haven't already. I, what am I going to write for this fucking thing? Oh yeah. This is also awful.
This isn't like bad. Awful. This is, uh, just, I, I, uh, whatever. I don't care.
Uh, these are, these two are such bad prompts. Um, time's running out. Submit what you can.
I don't know. Whatever. I don't, whatever. I don't care. Mine are terrible. Looks like some
of you didn't finish your jokes too bad. God, this is going to be worse than the first one. I
can just feel it. I am ready. I'm ready to fucking get ready. Wow. Talk about close
quarters. Why are all the setups the same again? Dang it, Chuck. You screwed it up again. I got
like the exact same one. Here's our first comic. How many boomers does it take to change a light
bulb? Three. One to screw it in and two to complain about millennials. Is that auto generated?
That, that is, it's definitely not, but that's so bad. It's an auto complete.
That's a spicy controversy.
What's the difference between most people and sheep? Most people have their own opinions.
Okay, judges, render your verdict. He told it backwards. Well, you don't, you don't get to
choose the first half of your joke. I don't even have a choice. I do believe you're owed some points.
Why? Because why boomers? I don't understand. A round of applause for our next comedian.
Hi, Jeremy. You're muted. Why do you keep doing that? Wait, what? Cause the letter L.
I'm so old. I remember when Doopey. Doopey?
It asked me to type in a player's name, a person's name and I got confused and I wrote Doopey for a
person and then he picked that one. Doopey. Oh, that's your fault. Yeah, that's my fault.
I love this. Yeah, these are the worst things I've ever thought of.
Marriage is a lot like, you know what I mean? I mean, that's funny in its own way, but I don't
want to, I don't want to, you know what I mean? God damn it.
It's so funny. You know that there's something wrong when, you know, this is like random chat
members here that could write crazy shit and I'm concerned about the guy in the call writing the
crazy shit. You're going to read my joke. I was going to write gross. You got to write shit.
Oh, I'm fine. I don't know where he got it.
I thought mice were a bowl of feeling love. That's just not true. That's just not true.
Is this like a furry thing? Trucks. Imagine fighting the truck punch line.
Yeah, you got, you got to go to jackbox.tv and then put in the code. H J I I.
All right. Let's hear it for the next performer.
I hope I'm up against you. I'm going to take you down.
It's, it's guaranteed to win. I'm guaranteed to win because you just got,
I'm going to just censor yours. So it's okay. Oh yeah. Don't forget to say your catchphrase.
This is bad. I didn't have any time. Why did the weighted blanket cross the road?
It didn't. It's a weighted blanket. Oh my God. I had, I was too busy. Look,
oh my God, I was too busy yelling at you to not be offensive on stream.
I wasn't. We were typing. My joke was very appropriate. Um, in good taste.
I have more convertibles than a person who thinks rain is a myth.
That's not very many people though. You don't have, you have like none. How many do you have?
Zero. Imagine when Jerma wins this one. Yeah, nice. They give him the softball.
Oh, it's comedy battle night. Let's bring Jerma nine eight five up and his opponent,
a beach ball. And that was, I still win. Oh, he was a joke for me. I still win.
Okay. Up next. Eagle boy. You had one zero so far. Let's see what you got now.
My love life is like the Hulk. I feel nothing but frustration. Give me body wash.
I don't know why it asked if you're ready. These are both very literal and
just go. Just don't. It's just, you can explain the joke. It don't have to.
My nickname is plunger because I love my work as a plumber. It's just
I sent you up with a funny toilet object and you give me that.
I was not at my attention. I don't have my full attention on the game. Did you? I wrote plunger.
I wrote plunger. Did we both write plunger? I think we both.
Wow. All of the nouns in the world and we both picked plunger. Holy shit.
Yes. Yeah. No. All right. So let me just, let me, I gotta defend myself.
During this, you were going during this whole time, you were going, Oh, I can't write this.
Oh, no, no, I'm going, I'm in trouble. Have you tried trucking? Have you ever tried trucking?
That's when you have given up. I gave up on the joke.
I got a stream to run and you're sitting there going, Whoa, this is going to get TOS.
I want to open a store that only sells Cheetos and call it cheesy German bloomers are us. Well,
fuck, I'm censoring you. Do you have a sensor button? Oh, he does. Oh my God.
Don't censor me. Oh my God. Ashley just keeps giving up.
Heck yeah. You better not censor mine. I'm going to censor it. This better not be bad.
I'm going to be actually IRL upset. It's fine.
That's where you be a white and don't bring one to school.
Fuck. Get out of here. You're out. You're out. You're out. You're out. All right. Let's hear it
for our next comedian. Me again. What? You both failed. My grandma said the best thing about
reality shows is that Bob Barker is freaking cute. No. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no,
not another one. I want that. Wait, wait, this better be like, this better be like a knock,
Joe. If this ain't like I'm an Asti little Rubik's Cube.
You just got to censor everyone until you win and feel good about yourself.
Who is currently winning comedy? Let's see. Oh, who's winning comedy? I wonder. Oh,
third place. Look at me. This whole thing's rigged.
All right. Here's where we're really bad. I got my finger on the button.
PG 13 and no offensive bullshit. Well, we're sinking again. There's no time. Okay. Yeah,
you keep swearing. You know the drill. Oh, no. These both of these setups are awful. I know.
Uh, I love this one. That's terrible. Fuck. I can't admit it.
Germa is allowed to sexualize dry erase boards, but Kurt Starr can't make a sexy Rubik's Cube
joke. Exactly. Someone gets it. Get out of here. Germa was the original R rated Joe after your
first fucking material there. I had the, I, excuse me. Oh, we just pretending like the first one
didn't exist. And German, you can't, I don't even hear you. You're muted again because you
typed an L. Well, you just turn on the stream. Women and children go in the lifeboats first.
Everyone else stick around and welcome back our performers.
What about the Bob? That was just accidental. I've deleted like 30 videos accidentally. I'm
accidentally going to mute someone. Marriage is a lot like germs. It makes you sick.
That's pretty good. That's a pretty good PG PG like 1950s comedy. Did they successfully beat this
joke? You know what I mean? Marriage. It's the same joke, but just told differently. Yeah. That's
the beauty of comedy. Oh yeah. You didn't do anything. I didn't do anything. All right,
bagel boy. What do you got? I'm a nasty little tornado because I spin out of control. Like this
game of joke boat has which punch line is better because I, Oh, he's up against that one.
Because that's, that's, that could be stars joke. Number one that I censored could be one of the
three I censored. No, no, he's like up against the AI. Yeah. Cause I deleted three jokes. Oh,
Oh, so they don't even get to go up against mine again because I was censored that much.
You got a double censored. Okay. So I just don't even exist anymore.
You are like face down into water. He asked nicely. What? Kill him. That's way better than mine.
Okay. Star, you're going to be really bad in about probably one to two minutes. I think
why? Cause you're going to censor me again? No, cause there's nothing for you to censor.
There's nothing for me to censor, but you're going to be very upset about this in particular.
I'm just kind of seeing it already. Oh, you lost. Yeah. You're going to, you're about to be very
angry. Did you just like take my joke and rewrite it? No. My love life is like the Hulk starts out
small, but then it gets big and green. I should see a doctor.
How come you get to keep writing sexual jokes? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Go ahead. You can't, you can't. I, I have all the power. I have all the power. Yeah.
He's a hypocrite. He's a hypocrite. Hypocrite. He's a fucking hypocrite.
Shut up. Silence. I just stood up for my fucking throne. You don't make me stand up from the
throne. You better try trucking. That's when you and your truck friends all go to the bar. I like
that one. You? Well, it's better than mine. So quarantine. Jerry was going crazy from the power.
I thought somebody went for me.
He's rubbing his hands together. You heard about the jack box challenge.
That's where you censor everyone's answers until you win.
It's funny because it's true. Oh, I mean you asked for it.
What? How? You're not supposed to be able to participate. What happened? What, what, what
madness is this? What? My power. I'm so dumb. I thought mice were. What happened to my power?
Laugh. I'm censored. Oh, no. He's just waiting till the last second. There was nothing to censor.
I mean, you just said it. I didn't see how to do it. Funny callback though.
Come on. Thank you. Thank you.
Jerma is fucking shaking. Resisting the urge to censor. No, I got the way to blanket across the
road any longer. You know what I mean? That's the best joke of the whole night.
That's the best one of the whole night.
But you know what I mean? Really? The end, the end really ties it all together. I think
seriously. Perfect. Those. Hey, thanks. The 60 people that voted for me. You're loyal.
I recognize that guy's name. 3% of you. You're loyal. I check you on the ballot. I knew it.
That is my King's God saving when the ship capsizes. Let's find out.
Oh, dude. The best. Good job, man. I wish I would have gotten to participate.
Because I wasn't censored. Yeah. Yeah, you're stupid. You flew too close to the sun.
You see how I got 97% of that vote? I did, but like, come on. All right, let's do another one.
Oh, freester. Let's do the one. No word. Censor it, dude.
Is this how the king dies? No, it can't be. I'm choking on my own water. All right,
what should we do? Push the button. Vocabulary game. Dictionarium. Humans have been inventing
words and phrases for centuries. Now it's your turn to contribute an entry to the pages of the
Dictionarium. This seems fun. Let's try it. Push the button is the best one. Okay,
we'll do it after this. What time is it for? Yeah, we've got like another hour or so.
Like an hour and a half. Okay, archive. Am I allowed to play this one? Yeah, if you behave.
All right, you just gotta promise me to not say anything sexual and I won't either
because you're the only one that can get me going like that. You know what I'm saying?
All right, that's enough. That's enough. King is spoken. You know, I don't want to be the king.
The king always just dies. Like it sucks to be the king. The king always loses always every time.
Want to be the jack? I kind of just I want to be like the guy that makes the bread. That
guy's life is always fine. Yeah, people always need bread. All right, so I have to get rid of
this and don't go in yet. I know that you two are going to be raring to go, but hold on. Go ahead.
Only win. Yeah, get in there. All right, discord. It's your turn. Come on in. Three, two, one. Here
it comes. And now it shows up. Cool. Hey, everybody else. Go on if you want to.
All right, we got it. All right, we got it. We got it. How do you boot?
Can you? How do you keep? Can you? He got in fair and square. Do not censor him. Don't.
There are thousands of people who want to play. All right, now you're going to make me look like
the bad guy because let's go. Let's go. I'm not. I'm the bad guy. Bad guy. Bad baker.
Word game or slang phrase game?
What an intelligent crew in the dictionary. You will create a dictionary entry for a made up word
and you will win if your answers get the most votes. Oh, that's fun. Oh, P.S.
Feel free to join the audience. Enter the room code to play along. Let's rock.
First things first. I am assigning you a word.
What do you think this word means? Write it down on your definition for the new word on your device.
Fun fact. This word is banned for most aquariums. So we have to do definition for that word. All
right. Let's see. We can't. As long as you're using letters, you really can't.
Letters are disappearing. It's a timer. It's like a minute. I can't think of anything.
I know it's hard. It really is hard to come up with like something like that.
Somebody throws at you. It would help if I know how to spell this word.
I mean, you got to submit very, very soon. Like right now. I don't know.
I think everybody's reaction is always, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
That's what the word means. I don't know. Show me the definitions.
Okay. The time has come to vote. Pick your favorite definition and quietly admire the rest.
All these answers are terrible. And remember, you can award bonus points to the ones that
stole your heart. Are any of these like supposed to be correct? No, you can't be correct.
It's not a real word. It's whichever one speaks to you. Come on, vote. What? It takes so long to
decide. Oh yeah, but then we all have to vote.
By the way, the official note take backs definition for the word is
when you eat too many trains.
You go to bite your food and end up falling down the
train. To slowly stroke a chimp's hair, a loser chimp,
but with an E, you know what I'm saying? No, we can't. No more. You know what I'm saying.
Definitions are like children. Pick your favorite.
A chump, but it's a chimp. Vote for your favorite before this is gone. Vote right now.
Do you like the sentence where you're stroking your hair to chimp a chimp?
That kind of pulls it together. The audience likes a loser. And the winning definition is
I like it too. Nice job, Scoob. Stir. Yeah, 420. If you say that, you should get points deducted.
I was waiting. Yeah, 420. Chomp, chomp, chomp. This dictionary is hungry for a synonym.
Write down a new word, something that matches the definition on your device.
Round two. Here we go. The time is slipping away, so submit your cinnamon.
Choose the word that best fits the definition.
Diaper monkey? You just added the word diaper.
You can't improve on chimp. That's what I was saying.
Yeah, this is pretty good. It already is. Why would you ever use the synonym on it?
That person should vote. And the winner is
None of these are synonyms. Mine vote? What are you talking about?
You know the drill. Vote on the word that best fits this definition.
You eat too many trains. What am I looking at?
It kind of sucks. I don't know what this means.
Caboose, Caboose. Choo, choo, choo.
That person did not know how to spell Caboose. Vote, vote, vote. Vote right now.
Y'all are bad at this. How do you be good with like nonsense?
It's not even real. Boulder Dash gets the words in real.
And the winning synonym is
You know like when someone walks up to a comedian it's like oh you're a comedian tell me a joke.
This is like doing that but also you have to use a word that doesn't exist.
Oh I feel that. I feel that.
In round three you will use the word in a sentence.
This is your last chance to add to the dictionary of entry so make it count.
Write a sentence using the word on your device.
That really is the equivalent of like going to like somebody's house that you're dating
and meeting their dad for the first time. It's like oh you're funny.
Like you said tell me a joke son and you're like eating dinner.
It's not a joke but also use it in a sentence with the word
Caboose crew. Tell me a joke son. I don't know. Put your fork and knife down.
I'm gonna throw you out a couple of verbs. Give me a story.
All right I heard a sentence. Wait this is more like choo choo stuff.
Die for monkey a lose. This is all wrong.
That's not even if that's the wrong.
That's the wrong means of transportation. Whatever.
Oh man you never finish.
Let us behold the sentences.
Near station order their biggest choo-bee but that's not but that's not an item.
It's rename train gore to choo-bee in my what?
Kevin was never allowed to play with the other chimps and it was resigned.
What? Yeah that's like yeah where's mine?
Where's mine? Train gore wins.
I didn't censor anything. Like oh my god.
I love this game. Do you? Yeah this one's good.
But actually to be honest as much as this one kind of sucks,
it's so much better than the haunted house thing. Yeah well yeah not hard.
And the winning sentence is choo-bee my choo-bee.
Die for monkey. Look at those monkeys son. Oh no that that's the die for monkey. What?
They were both on the screen. Why is mine gonna be on here?
Did you pick the wrong one too? Yeah what? See?
It's fucked up man. It's fucked up.
So wrong. Dude this chap looked down at the die for monkey.
This is a verb.
Who the fuck wrote this? Me.
Me. You did? The choo-bee at the bus stop is mine. No. No I'm the comedian.
Which one are you laughing at? Even the chap looked down at the die for monkey.
I thought you were laughing at mine. That was me.
I know how to make my words. Yours didn't mean how is that possible.
What a perfectly fun funky fresh dictionary entry. I'm in awe. Oh my stomach hurts.
Die for monkey. A loser chimp. Derive from chimp.
I just found the new word dancing naked in the darkness.
All right let's do push the button.
No end of the game songs. Not good ones. All right push the button. Okay.
This one better be fun or I'm blaming you. Me? Dangerous.
People said it doesn't work with random people. Oh. Everyone said this is the best one.
Should we do a one like is it does it just work with the three of us? Oh no it doesn't.
But people are saying it does. Does this work with three people?
Does not work with. Oh it has no audience. Oh we would need an extra.
Everybody somebody who are you? So wait what was wrong? We skipped this one. Why did we skip this
one? Well the chat said it was dumb. Yeah the chat said the one was very dumb. Should we even just do
it? Just wait we have the pack. But it's dumb and those other ones are so fun. I want to do
Dictionarium again now that I understand what's going on. Okay can you guys like not
define the wrong word and still win? There was two and one on the screen. I wanted to pick one of
them. You could. You probably just picked the wrong one. We'll plan like another night where
we can have like four or five people do it. I mean I'm certain Ronnie's not doing anything.
I just know.
Do you think we could do that? Is he interested? I'm certain he's interested. There's two things
I know about him. He's not doing anything and he's interested. Oh okay. It does work with chat.
People are saying. Does that work? Well let's just try and see why it wouldn't. All right let's just
see. What's the worst thing we could do is waste time? Summon Ronnie in the meantime. I don't know.
What is it? Let's see. You need like ten people. People are saying. Ten people? They said four to
ten. It technically works but everyone needs to talk to each other really. Well I can call. I
can add Ronnie if we really want him. Well let's just. Wait max players. What if I do okay four?
Hide the room code. Censoring. Quiet twitch.
I'm trying not to think about it. Ten sucks you guys are nuts.
All right well it just is like Ronnie right? Did you like tell him? Yeah he'll yeah.
If you just if he's just sitting right there then just yeah if you like told him hey let's play then
yeah then yeah let's go. He's here. Wait Ronnie's here? Yeah. Ronnie. Ronnie.
Ronnie. Hey. Hello. Hello. All right let's do it. Welcome Ronnie. It's jackbox.tv Ronnie if you
missed that. The links in the chat. Jackbox.tv yeah. What's uh is the code in the chat yet? No okay.
Can you see the webcam? Uh yeah yeah I'm looking at the screen right now.
The screen grab. Let's say gross Fluter. Aw Fluter I love you. Get Kim. Kim is at work.
Sorry guys. Imagine working. On a Sunday. On a Sunday. Get her anyways. What the fuck. All right
let me get this set up. Manual censoring in case you know I have to do that. Room code hiding. Max
plays four. I guess it really doesn't matter. There's this. All right here we go. Play. Push the
button. I said cake throat. All right uh you guys can see the game right so all I have to do is
this. Uh don't join it yet when they get in first. No although it really doesn't matter. It's just
the four of us anyways. Just the four of us. You and I and I and I. Ronnie is fucking infected.
What? Uh it's making me twitch log in. How do I do that? Here we go. I'll log in real quick.
Top left setting bar. Yeah yeah yeah. All right here we go. That was easy peasy. All right so uh
I've we're gonna get a tutorial. We'll see how this works. Let's go. Everybody ready?
Yep yeah this is MVM music. Oh this one actually is an animated background. That's cool.
Sorry to interrupt your cryo sleep but I thought it worth mentioning that I your digital officer
during emergencies or DOTI have detected an alien biorhythm on this ship and just as I suspected
the aliens uploaded a virus which is slowly deleting my program. I'm here to guide you through
if you'd like. Uh we should probably figure out what the hell to do. Uh guide me. Fill me dude.
I'm now initiating security protocol alpha bravo caret which is a series of tests designed to
evaluate your humanity and reveal any aliens hiding amongst you. I have determined that one of you
is secretly an alien. Please look at your device and confirm your identity. Your device can tell
you if you're a human or an alien but not the identities of your fellow players. I'm Satan.
Figure out who. But my calculations will have 12 minutes before I cease to be so I'd appreciate
it if you could figure out who the alien is and then push the button. We're trying to be killing
each other. You will be our first captain. I have repurposed the ship's quarters into unique testing
areas. I'm pretty proud of it. Choose an available room and your desired participants. Oh drawing
quarters. You know what's going in there. Fucking artist. Uh let's break out the tablet. Get me in
here. Wait don't invite Jerma. Hey. All the artists just gonna jerk off. The two artists
join the drawing room. Yeah let's get drawing. Whoa there's so much dicks. Where's the fucking
loud talking clown. The drawings are revealed.
Oh I gotta get my tablet. What are you guys doing in here? Hold on how much time do we have?
You got like 12 minutes before we all die. How much time do we have to draw? A minute a minute
and a half. Okay because my tablet I'm trying to get it to work it's not working. I don't understand
what I'm supposed to be drawing. It says a thing on top of your screen like above the drawing.
You will understand what I mean when I don't understand what it wants me to draw.
Get the hurry up button. But when do I hit the hurry button? If you're dawdling with your doodling
I can't tell who you're doodling. Go. I'm doodling. Doodles doodles doodles. Fast fast fast. Yes that
is womp ronnie. It is the real womp ronnie. I did it. Okay what did you do?
Okay sick. And the human prompt was
and how did the subjects respond?
Do any of these answers seem suspicious? Keep in mind someone may have gotten a bad prompt
or they could just be a terrible artist. That's Sean Valjean if he was a um if he was a captain
of enterprise. I think I think you know how we draw there's like that's how we both draw.
We're not alien. What am I trying to pick here? You're trying to pick who the alien is
I think. But why would draw indicate that? What are these what are these are drawing tap the alien
icon and any responses you don't draw. You're the fucking alien. The player seems to be taking way
too long to move on. You can tap the hurry up button to speed up the timer.
We're on the clock here people so let's keep it going. I trust you both.
I think you just wait out the timer. Oh yeah you can speed it up. I'm speeding it up.
My tablet still isn't working. I'm very sad. Wait have you been tested? Okay next captain
you're in charge. All right you're the captain. Okay let's get a move on. Pick another room. Oh
the clown room. Oh there's less than nine minutes. The alien's the captain.
Welcome to the writing pod. We'll see who's really good at writing jokes. Answer honestly
because it will be scrutinized. Okay the alien virus will allow the intruders to get something
similar but not quite right. When the correct prompt is revealed it will be up to you to
determine if any seem odd. As time winds down I'll do my best to send the alien some real
stinkers. It's the least I can do. Okay. So you draw stuff and then the computer. Let's see the
human prompt. The last movie I saw was. Okay what can we harp on? Look for any written answer that
doesn't seem quite right and don't forget to hit that suspicion button. It's Ashley. Is that even
a movie? I think you're supposed to give vague enough answers that like you. I think. Are you
voting on me as alien? What? Yeah I'm gonna walk over to your room and shoot you right now.
Alien viruses capabilities. Aliens now have the ability to hack the prompts. I know what movies
you've watched. Okay. I know what you've seen recently. An alien can select any human and
secretly give them the alien prompt. To make things worse aliens can choose to help themselves
and switch their own prompt. I hope you got all of that because there's no way I'm repeating it.
Dr. Strange came out three years ago. Okay next captain you're in charge. Yeah I just saw it like
I just watched it. All right here we go. You're picking drawings order. No I'm not.
Wait I want to go to the place we haven't seen. Husband versus wife. Deliberate off.
Humans will be given a difficult decision and must choose which answer seems appropriate to them.
Aliens will see no dilemma and must choose their answers blindly. When the crew sees the full
statement aliens may have to justify their random selection or face suspicion.
Make your choice. Let's see what these players choose. If they're an alien I bet it's peculiar.
Would you like to play a game? Finished. Only seven more minutes. Humans received.
Every time you eat cheese you destroy a small sentient universe. You must.
Do any of these seem stinky? Now you have to decide who's an alien or just makes terrible
life decisions. You must slow down. And don't forget about those alien hacks. A smart alien
can make someone look suspicious by flipping their prompts. I know that when you say something like
oh Monopoly is my favorite board game everybody goes holy come on man what about like Settlers of
Catan. To me like this is the Settlers of Catan version in this game. I kind of want to go back
to Monopoly. I don't follow. Is the glitching getting worse? I feel like it's getting worse.
Look at your device. You can now reach the button and take us to the extraction room
but I would recommend you only do this once you complete your suspicions.
Okay next captain you're in charge. Because it's Ashley. What? The game's over because
Ashley's the alien. Star is pretty quick to accuse Ashley. Welcome to the extraction room.
Check it out I've stopped the timer. It's costing me a lot of cpu but I don't want you to feel rush.
Since you were the one to push the button. I think we're supposed to be talking to each other.
You believe is an alien. We are. We're having a fun time. Yeah you're supposed to quiz people
on what their answers were. If you all vote yes and this player is an alien.
I'm not the alien. Why would you put me in here? It's curtains for us all.
This is no no no no no this is where we talk. I am not I'm actually I don't understand how the
game works but I know that I'm not the alien. She's the one with the button. So why did you
put me in here? Because I wanted to see how it ends. The crew member who pushed the button
can no longer push it. I also don't really understand the uh acts. I guess you can change
captain you're in charge. How do I push the button on someone? I think a lady captain can do some
stuff. Uh drawing oh I'm gonna go back to the drawing quarters. On my tablet. Just because
I like drawing but I'm gonna bring oh I suddenly suspicious of stir here. Two players to test oh
okay. Another drawing test I approve. You guys talked over the instructions. I tried to tell
their drawings could reveal an alien. Oh I wanted to draw that's okay. Oh yeah oh I can't just like
make it go really fast. I tried to just like say hurry up so you guys had to go really fast.
Did I mention that if humans use all of their button pushes without success you lose? Well you
do. Two total hacks. With four people the ability doesn't hit as hard.
And you can push the button and vote at any time. Okay I see. Sorry if you heard that
gulping. It was pretty sexy though. I'm like way down with my oh wait I can submit.
Yeah yeah hit submit. The prompt humans saw was draw shirtless Abe Lincoln.
Shirtless. Ashley's has a shirt. Like it's fucking. No see the whole time.
Ashley's is clearly wearing a shirt. Look at that. That's got a collar on it. I did not say shirtless.
Oh you're the alien. That's oh.
Is that how we push the button on her? Alien. Oh you're the alien. I hope you're not wasting
my time. This is just general Abe Lincoln. He's clearly wearing his clothes. You only get one
minute so act quickly. Okay yeah I want to yeah. Okay time to vote. Yes. Yeah. Oh come on dudes.
The vote passed. This is what it's like to be in prison. So is it did we do it?
Yeah. So I did.
Because it wasn't me.
Joking that's. I regret everything.
Die human.
Good job idiots. But you're an alien. I'm not. Why'd you draw a shirt? I thought this is just
the tutorial. You didn't say shirtless on it. Okay I get it. So Ronnie gave you the prompt to
draw a shirt. Oh yeah I'm dabbing. Let's go. So who was it? It was Ronnie. Ronnie was the alien.
Because it told me to draw Hamilton and I thought they meant Alexander Hamilton and I drew just a
dude with a skull patch because I don't know what Alexander Hamilton looks like.
Protocol zephyr nine.
It was a play that was popular for like five minutes. We got it this time. Wait are we doing
it again? Please look at your device and confirm your identity. Your device can tell you if you're.
All right I'm gonna listen to the instructions. Yeah we need to actually debate each other so
they can figure it out. You guys were like silent after everything. Hold on that whole time you're
like it's Ashley. Ashley. Ashley. Just do it. It's Ashley. Skip it. It's Ashley.
That was the whole last 10 minutes. It wasn't. Ashley and Ronnie were messing with each other.
Choose an available room and your desired participants. I've got too many windows open.
Uh operation deck okay. Uh two players to test. I want Jerma versus Dirt. Jerma versus Dirt.
I actually just got out there. Not the fucking aliens. Answer the question. Turn and get a voice.
And the prompt for humans was.
A hacker wants $50,000 or they will release your text messages to the world.
You would say and this is how the participants responded.
You don't think you would say like hey I want 50 grand. Like no because I have
nothing to hide. Well neither do I but what else do they have?
They have your text messages. They get your text. They're in the cloud. They have everything else.
They have all the pictures of you like bending over to look at your asshole.
So they have all the pictures on your phone too and you don't want you don't want people to see
that. We're on the clock here. For medical reasons. I need to look sometimes. I don't think you're an
alien. I just think you've got some perverted shit on your phone. You talk a lot of stuff and
centering people for making. You want to give $50,000. Remember when you were sitting there
with the bread loaf. I'm just saying if they've got text messages they've got
they've got like they've got probably bank accounts. They're going to take the 50,000.
Bring it down to eight and I'll do it. New captain. Give someone eight thousand dollars.
No you're just a sick sick man.
Waiting pod. Writing test.
Oh finally. Write an answer to the comms on your device.
I bet you're naked under all those clothes. Yeah. What's that guy's name? Forget about under the
clothes. I'm not even wearing any. That's common knowledge. And here's what humans saw.
The actor or actress I want to play me in a movie is
anything odd. Okay that's pretty suspicious. Wouldn't it be awesome
if Peter Dinklage played me and everyone else in the movie acted like I was still me.
Yeah but that's I mean and they don't they don't look down to make eye contact with them either.
They're looking up because like they see me but it's Peter Dinklage.
Okay so they're definitely not the only one.
Let's keep it going. What? Why would he not be the? Because all these responses are very honest.
Yeah but that I mean that's a very clear like mind gymnastics. That's 100% my answer. Like if I had
the power it's him. Yes. He has to do that role. His agent comes to him with he's like no no god
they force him to the drawing quarters. Drawing quarters? I don't want to draw.
I'm sorry you keep getting left out of these German but. That's fine. It's art battle.
No it actually needs to. Hey thank you. You have entered the drawing quarters.
All right here we go. That's gotta come up with a grand. Draw the prompt on your device.
I'm getting hacked. What does it mean when it says total hacks at the bottom?
Uh I think that's at the amount of times the alien can interfere.
I wouldn't know. I'm just guessing. If they're taking too long to draw the
hurry up button can help pick up the pace. Do I get a hurry up button? Oh that's the total.
It's way at the bottom left for me. Hold on so there's a some whoever the alien is has
already done two hacks. That's the total amount of hacks total. Not how many you have left.
Yeah. Somebody is fucking with us. Somebody said no. Is that one guy?
That's completely wrong. We've only had two. So I had it right the first time so that's the amount
of hacks that are available. I'll be honest I don't know how the hacks work. I don't know
what they're for. It's to mix like to make a human get an alien prompt or like switch it around so
a human looks like an alien. Gotcha. You read it wrong you're the one guy.
Let's see it in the chat. What the fuck? And the human prompt was
draw yourself in the future. Oh my god no way. What do we think? I mean Ronnie what's going on
here? I have no idea. It said draw myself the future and I thought Dragon Ball is just a super
future. Maybe I'll be I'd have no idea where. Why do you say pulled up? Because I thought once
after I drew him with his hands up it reminded me of that meme image. The fallout guy. We're
on the clock here people so let's keep going. Alien. Alien. I don't know I think he's a robot.
I mean Ronnie would draw himself as Vegeta in the future but the hold up it's not adding up man
and everyone knows you don't write words when you're doing draw my thing or draw anything.
That's a good point. And only an alien would not know to not write words.
Yeah let's stir in my picture. We're on a dolphin. Nice. Also this is really funny to me because
anytime for years when someone's drawing something I tell them to draw me for the future
or draw yourself for the future and Ashley got to do it.
Why can't emergencies have calm alarms? Next captain. I uh I'm gonna go ahead.
Uh there's a the bio there's whoa hold on a minute here there's a bio scanner.
What's the bio scanner? Put Ronnie in the scan me. Let's scan him. Come on do it. This is the
bio scanner. Good luck. I hope you've chosen a team. Oh you didn't put yourself in did you? Captain
I'm sending you the correct glyphs now. I don't think you can. Wait I gotta hold on I need to
look at this. Wait what is happening? Uh hold on. Describe your glyphs Jerma. No. Yeah you have to.
Oh oh oh oh describe the symbols. Okay so all right so we got describe the symbols below that
that okay so we've got select I got a um Jerma. Hold on person standing at a bus stop is one of
them. We also have uh the man falling down or man diving and then we also have uh a conjoined a
conjoined uh conjoined twin conjoined twin so we have man standing at bus stop like actual bus stop
like the bus stop man falling straight down or diving and then uh conjoined twins okay okay
all right how we doing you hit a button yeah hurry up i'm done okay what do we got the test has failed
how did we both get it wrong okay that was suspicious maybe test humans next time
hold on a second this one's hard okay so might have been it hold on star what he said man diving
man diving the man falling down diving is the middle one here people so let's keep it going
me and ronnie have just about the same ones but we were super like yeah i think we were different
that match what you were saying i think we just differed there yeah the man falling down was the
one that i didn't quite because mine's pointing my diving of falling down and you have man going
up in the air you have a man falling down on your panel star why did you not pick it which one is
the man falling down the one the one literally right next to it on the right which one two headed
no i'll start on your look at in the middle you have that in the middle you picked the right one
my middle selected one with the three like fingers going down was my man falling down
next captain please why is it going up you had one going down there's less than three minutes
let's not go to the bioscanner again oh we only have two minutes oh oh gosh okay uh drawing i'm
gonna get germa in on this one and ashlett i'm sorry sir have you even gotten to draw
i had the previous one okay draw response draw it's germa wait what give me it's like
it's tiny text above the drawing thing it's real tiny uh ronnie hurry him you have a hurry
button on the bottom left all right hurry up no no no no get rid of that
probably stop drawing me so weird is that fun drawing the more details you add
the more trouble it can get i ran out of time draw a mirror draw a mirror any of these answers help
uh none of those makes oh i get ashley's i was germa's yeah no no no no no hold on a second here
i got fucking hacked i got listen to me don't do it yet i got hacked i got hacked i got hacked
how did you tell you to draw it told me to draw a magic portal isolate since this is our first so i
was making a guy i was gonna have a magician in there a magic portal why would i draw a big
circle like that it's ronnie now the non-isolated member how do we how do we pick the guy wait no
it's germa in there yeah it's him no it's not me you don't write hold up on bajita that's right
what wait wait wait wait star star why are you why your star is incredibly gung-ho about this
whole thing why who did you put it this either you were you drew a black hole there's still two
hacks get star in there no get star in there get him in there unless it doesn't tell you if a hack
was used no steve's answers were so honest oh no they were not yes they were peter dinklage come
on peter dinklage yeah absolutely trying to come here to the bus kill him i yeah and it was star
that good work everybody nice work you killed an innocent man oh i just don't know how the ui works
to get ronnie in there instead
we had 20 seconds left in 20 seconds i'm gonna figure out how to get ronnie in that room
i'll just take a bed and kill germa you could have just voted for me and then uh it would the
vote would have canceled the vote that i had was no or yes for germa that's all i had then you hit
no and that would have been in yeah well i mean i figured that's what i'm saying is i don't know
how long it would have taken to set up the ronnie vote because i don't i don't like this game oh it
even needs more people yeah i think even harder i think it'd be fun if it was even just two people
i mean this is still interesting but with like maybe like six people i think would be perfect
yeah ten people would be too crazy
so
why did you write hold up ronnie yeah i don't know i completely flubbed that because it said draw
yourself it didn't say draw yourself in the future it just said draw yourself because i thought why
would it make me draw myself i'm the alien it's lying to me i'll draw something else and talk my
way out of it so i said all right i'll draw vegeta because maybe it'll say what's the last movie you
saw or something and they're like oh okay i could just say obviously and anything in your life you
could relate to dragon ball so it was a good play yeah all right uh you guys want to do
one more before because i gotta get going soon yeah yeah yeah let's do one more of this so you
want to go back and do like the dictionary one i feel like we need a sort of round two for dictionary
uh streamer's choice yep yeah i feel hold on let me see streamer's choice do you want me to
leave for the next one no you're okay i mean you were the alien and killed us all twice
i said i know i haven't even seen this one is this one really that bad to like not even play it once
in the in the whole pack why don't we just do it we're gonna do it fine fine i mean we have what
we're just gonna play jack box six and just skip one of the whole games in here well we gotta put
a nut in to make the others feel better yeah it's actually okay with four people
so we just don't just do this with four people don't just have to be a private game it'll be
worse with chip okay all right screw you chip all right so also your jokes were so
shit last time i need to do something to like fix this me what those were bad jokes oh my god
y'all y'all didn't write a joke on the spot what that's a big word stir had one good joke
i don't remember what it was all right ronnie hold on you're like the guy that goes to the comedy
show and then goes i can do i can do better than that guy that was bullshit yeah i'm the drunk
not funny put ronnie on joke boat let's see how it goes
so we're all right i want to see what this one is
i'm just trying to earn my keep all right so we're just gonna do four should show should the
audience be disabled just turn sorry no audience at all audience is fine the audience needs those
votes but just don't keep it on all right uh here we go this is called role models
yes listen now we're gonna ruin the game whatever you must be the guinea pigs i ordered
sign in with the room code and make sure to snap a selfie or draw yourself for our records
oh we can't draw ourselves oh you get to draw yourself cool yeah draw for cheetah again
all right go ahead and come in you guys all in yeah okay so change name well what do you mean
change name no it's fine you guys drawing yourselves yep wait i need better than that
let me know when you guys are ready draw me draw me this is my favorite thing about this so the
three artists you know what i mean they're like i just drew like a dumb face and the three artists
just bang i can draw let's go but no it stars what the hell are you doing i drew a black oh
these are faces oops wait yeah why you can we start over just you can draw yourself it starts
over yeah draw do it again do it again yeah okay i got it oh wait yeah you don't have to draw the
head you don't have to draw a circle it's already the face yeah it's already there i get what you
mean all right i'm clicking everybody's in in 10 seconds okay this is how people will see me
all right your hands are whatever
if you have any questions about our process you're not alone here at the lab we've spent
years searching for the genetic magic that makes each and every human a truly unique individual
but that was hard so we found a shortcut we theorize every friend group has some version of
the smart one the popular one the troubled loner who i can change you get all of those
and these roles make it a lot easier to figure people out with science you guys are going to
match your fellow test subjects to the roles that fit them best my lovely assistant will
put all the data into the tubes and at the end we'll crunch the numbers and tell each of you
who you really are okay i moved all the chemicals out of licking distance so let's go i need a
category to get us started vote for your favorite but try to make it something everybody knows a
little bit about everyone knows a little bit about their deepest fears game of thrones that's what i
oh i might be able to oh i'm gonna smoke you in spice girls you freaking millennials
um ronnie ronnie i'm 34 which of these is secretly your deepest fear so on your device
you've got the names of your fellow lab rats drag each one to the room you think fits them best
you have to drag these to the people you think fits this best you'll see a little 99 sign next
to each room tap that to lock oh god your 99 will match what everyone else picks i'll make
it worth your while if you're right so make sure to pick someone when everyone's given out their
roles we'll check out the results i think i got it i think i got this mail why does it say hold up
let's see where we landed let's look at those votes get rid of the outliers
we have our winner is scared of snakes how do you win being scared of snakes i win so i'll give
you guys these nutritious science pellets whenever your answers match the group whoever has the most
at the end of the month plus they're a healthy snack subjects who already have a role don't need
so let's lose these votes stir knows me way too well why did it was two v2
oh we both know ashley hey given public speeches before i was good
fuck you good how why would i be afraid of something that i know i just love the word
clowns that i put you on this yeah we all knew you'd be a person well i just got a super pellet
thanks guys you got the clown streamer afraid of himself there's our line up here's how you're
doing on science pellets just a reminder i'll reward you with pellets when your answers match
the group or when you do the best in a type breaker experiment keep that in mind if you
want to be the lab rat of the month what's our next category all right uh next category i don't
know anything i don't know anything about writing it i got i got way too excited about clicking
dwarves i'm i i'm only doing this because i know i know them all me too yeah you know them all
don't give it away sleepy bb bb bb which of the seven dwarves are you don't overthink this
and remember to tap the 99% most strongly about
ronnie bashful i think oh yeah you just say well it's just okay let's all follow ashley's answers
also is doc a roll what doc is he a grumpy or a doctor no he's just like the average he's like
the super mario the door is the super mario some would call some would call him potentially the
like the ultimate dwarf yeah he's got everything very basic and smash where does he even get his
degree go to the road oh i forget this let's see that data does it not seem so white
you really actually or at least what your friends think wait yeah we we're not supposed to because
we're not supposed to influence each other without really just picked it
yeah ashley ruined the whole experiment why'd you go with what i said i didn't you're grumpy
i made you seriously i wanted to pick yourself as grumpy yeah ashley's grumpy look at her face
sorry you earned the role with a highly motivating audience bonus i think our control group likes you
the edge you hate your wifey adopting myself as doc because i'm too smart to follow naming
conventions oh crap what was the other one all right now don't talk about your answers
nobody's fine because we gotta it's gotta be real here's how it all shook out yeah unless one of
the choices is like idiot you are scary good at this do you want a job oh i'm scary okay you've
each got some roles under your belt let's see what the data tells us
i think the faces are influenced by your roles your total opposites from a very specific point
of view anyway we're gonna pit you against each other and see even the game knows you're turned
10 years old again for one day what do you do i want both of you to write an answer that
ends early right right the others will decide who did you're talking with the instructions
is 10 for a day oh god my answer is terribly here it is oh shit devices now super easy
these are both good though actually i mean and it totally tells our age yeah answer match their
characteristics the best not whose answer is the best yeah we both keep the same answer i mean
seriously carefree buy bitcoin worry invest in apple this is pretty damn good
points we're going with you bitcoin when i was 10 you guys i would make my plans tell me you've got
something in common i can't stand not knowing who's better introvert you've been pushed on
stage to do stand-up comedy at an open mic you have nothing prepared how do you start answer
the prompt on your devices and we'll settle this once and for all oh that's easy uh
yeah what if we choose the same answer yeah probably will
okay there's the data apologize
i mean these are oh we were all thinking the same thing on that one
comedian comes out normally like so happy to be in new york i'm so sorry i'm in new york
i'm so sorry i'm here i i really i'll just go i'll go this will be our last category so choose
wisely oh one of these is banned let's make that joke pizza toppings these are all what what is
college part all right we're doing bonnie just click pizza toppings pizza all right these are
all bad so are we only gonna get pizza toppings yes we're only interested in pizza toppings
oh one of these is bad which pizza topping fits each of you best don't make those matches
i know what everybody's gonna pick for me but i'm gonna pick something else for me
let's see what everyone picked alone time i pretend my pizza is my friends
i knew you were green peppers oh yeah yeah how many times can germa talk about peppers
and not be peppers guys smile and say see that was definitely ashley to me yeah yeah
just cheese stir is so normal it would definitely be if i'm counting right that's a tie
time for another test to see who gets this role
here's what i want each of you to do who goes first is up to you the other lab rats will
decide who deserves the role show even if you're not sure you want the role
i'm handing out science pellets to the winner so do your best it's an experiment man you think
schrodinger's cat always wants to get in the box are we supposed to be in the same room is that
what they're assuming i don't have a shirt on i can't do this hold on i don't have no we're not
no don't turn on your camera it's fine all right all right yeah describe it all right dance i
crumple down into a ball and lie down in a semicircle and just like kind of shake
that's a good dance stir um um i hold on 20 seconds i can think uh germa's beating you
look at him shaking down there on the floor i mean i'm still going he's going nuts you're you
standing there point out how like every individual acne on my face and say i'm pizza face over and
over again it's like it's like a face pointing dance that's you being like a self-deprecating
like psycho according to our disturbingly sentient algorithm the role goes to you what is it pointing
dance performing the best in this experiment is definitely worth a few science pellets
just don't spoil your dinner
um you only got one vote but you're still the best person for this role science can be weird
what pineapple and our audience control group but you're the wackiest topping you know you're
the pineapple on that beach you're the one some people like yeah you don't belong in everyone
hates you here's where we ended up punch punch him punch him punch him one last thing before
i think i'm winning at being the most predictable let's see if there are any more interesting
patterns in those roles you judging by your roles you're this and you're also this i'm very
dependable that makes no sense to our algorithm we're going to find out which quality fits you
better what's the first thing you look for when shopping for a new car wheels this prompt on
your device then the other subjects will vote on your response make sure it has wheels
if it doesn't have wheels you just walk away how many clones can you fit money
how much money is in the wheels yeah how much money could i fit in the wheels for all my cocaine
dealing yeah that's what we're working with vote on your devices now read the context make sure
no puke is that dependable or why that's both of them again give it to me more of i feel like
wildcard always trumps dependable because you know by its very nature is the wild card trumps
everything in science we call that a shutout your roles tell me that your polar opposites
at least in this one extremely specific way we're not leaving
hello has been retired you are allowed to pick the new universal greeting what is it type an
answer on your device pineapple oh god my brain's are the worst possible thing it could ever be
mine does too i can't do this yeah it's gonna censor me don't do it this way chat said hold up
hold up look at me
fart sound three seconds three seconds of silence followed by a slap to the face
there you have it whatever vote on your that's called bowing and they do it in japan
or do you bend over the opposite way yeah it's just bowing like genitals forward head back
who answer match their characteristics the process serious oh that's funny mine's very
serious that's dead serious that's scary so you're not serious you you weren't you've got somebody
scream in your face allow me to present your final that's not funny determined by everything
that's fucking serious said about you steve does all the time constantly
and my favorite little child likes wait what do they call you science pellets is
once again i am the largest quiet mega introvert please don't call me a mega introvert i don't need
that on my personality i don't need it to be an advanced enhanced version of negativity these are
too accurate are they even the nostalgic are on here he's talking about 80s shit i am extremely
nostalgic and what was your wait what is germans again childlike you mute it germa i'm here
i'm here can you hear me nostalgic quiet childlike pseudo killjoy killjoy extremely carefree coward
cautious guarded grouch that's your that's definitely going on your eulogy somebody that
deliberately spoils the enjoyment of others through resentment or overly sober behavior
like a buzzkill remember when you censored us all you killed joy
okay i can see why i wouldn't work with randoms yeah that would not work with randoms thanks chat
you gave us good advice for once you did it they said suedeau suedeau killjoy means could be but
sometimes you don't oh we wear suede all right uh i have to go have time for one more of these
we'll do this again do you guys want to do this again this one's fun wouldn't it be the same
let's just make sure we pick different things i guess different categories well uh we can
let's do the dictionary one again all right yeah i didn't do that one last time so that'd be good
ronnie's been talking a lot of shit about the boat yeah boat is like hard mode a boat might
take too long though yeah okay i really only have like another uh like 30 minutes or so
like 25 minutes 30 minutes chat equals champs
that's my favorite still all right i gotta call on all of my portmanteau and
pun experience for this one okay this is good to go and we can add four people for this one
too so this will be the last game let's go ahead and i'm gonna put this uh well not yet have you
done previous jack boxes yes on stream i've done them all i have done them all some of them are
really good but some of them are oh well ronnie you are the uh you are the leader you are you join
first so now you control everything oh i'm sorry that's okay press like one button when everyone
joins and you just you all you have to do is just uh you have a sensor button if somebody
writes something inappropriate uh you can just remove it that is a lot of pressure i'm a born mod
all right guys here it comes last game sub discord here it comes in 10 seconds
everybody's name these names look like they have never been shown before
to the dictionary it's a word game and don't ask me where i'm from it's a very complicated story
oh i see i am in very good company in the dictionary you will make up a dictionary entry
for a totally fake word there is no right answer but the most popular one wins so stay on your toes
oh and for anyone watching join the audience just input the room code and play along
let's get started room code top right jackbox.tv look your twitch i am giving you a new word
now write out the definition that fits this word hold up i heard this word singing in the sewer
and i said come up little word and it did think too hard about it or if that doesn't work try
thinking really hard about it done i'm done done submit time is almost up
good luck let's see what we got this gossipy horse in the herd
typically used as a finish on pork when you want someone to hold up but your mouth is full of
m&m's and baileys what successful cat call what what was that okay the time has come to vote
pick the definition that makes you feel i know that stirs because he immediately explained
i gotta explain it there's logic and remember you can award bonus points to the ones that stole
i don't understand m&m's
do you not know what m&m's are is that the hold up no it is but why m&m's and baileys
what's an m&m why not like nostalgic and the winning definition to be recorded forever in
the because that's the definition now he's winning ego is growing he's winning now let's do it again
for the other word shirt you work in but in ireland shirt dunked in coffee for the smell
man turns into a shirt when he sees a full moon after you take off your shirt
we're sure it's like a one-shirt but different pick the definition that's so accurate it makes
excellent luck these are really good after you take off your shirt it was a shirt someone still
has not broken that person should vote for the smell for the smell and the official note take
back definition for the word is right it is in logic
okay
round two this dictionary entry needs some synonyms to flesh it out ill flesh
give me another word that could mean the same thing as the definition on your device
round two goes fast so type type i hate this one because wear shirt is perfect
yeah how do you
yeah i got it the time is slipping away so submit your cinnamon
i see a really good one in check new words did i get it out choose the word that best fits the
definition he had an e can i just not vote for any of these because i hate the other answers
i hate them all too especially mine it's not my answer don't if i'll vote for the least likely
one that way it can't win someone still has not voted this is a pokemon name
yeah you better give me 72 percent and the winning synonym is
i had like two and then i don't know what lightning lightning throw is like another
word for werewolf man you know what to do vote again
mongrel mouth oh sorry i'm swaying the boat sorry i shouldn't shut up bailey
it would be who you devote right now the drunken ems is what you're eating but the sound you're
making is mongrel mouth or osa i don't understand i thought like cinnamon explaining someone else's
yeah i mean i'm explaining yeah
ronnie banging it we have a brand new word and definition let's use it i need this
the only way i can feel a sentence using the word on your device
the sentence you're working on right now is perfect keep going don't doubt yourself oh dude
dude
no he's laughing at his own joke no i'm laughing because uh i i looked at the clock
i am thrilled to present your sentences
is
somebody said when did star last speak
no and the winning sentence is they're killing us all right i'm just getting buried i was really
worried he was going to turn into a werewolf but he's just a size medium
the lichen tea was briefly seen at las vegas furry convention tod was the hairiest lichen
tea in town so when he changed into a sweater no one could really tell the difference
lichen tea is the shittiest werewolf power ever i don't want people wearing me what
it's true where means uh well interesting because lichen means wolf but where it means man
so do you type lol xd when you just like want to lose or
i mean i that these are all these are all good there's pretty good ones in there that's for sure
come on vote already
yeah i mean that ashley that was just like
terrific entry in the dictionary you should be proud
a man that turns into a shirt when he sees a full moon to write from wear shirt
add it all up and you've got a big important word thank you and now let's see the winner
oh that's what we call a shutout
please return to me
it's been a long stream ronnie came in fresh it's kind of cheating yeah ronnie came in
fresh like you came like we've been draining threes you came in and like drained like five threes
i drank let me explain just wait wait wait the song is yelling in my ears and i had i did my
the sentence came out wrong all i hear is that you don't forget to put it in the oven at 203
it's okay i drained five threes that's all i needed today
all right shut it up i don't know how to shut it off it's you it's me i had just hit escape
i had a good basketball analogy and then i just heard like a the nursery rhyme in both ears
all right i gotta go
here that was fun yeah thanks for playing thanks for coming in ronnie thank you for
jumping in everybody that is the wonderful womp ronnie everybody's account yeah go check out the
comic the womp comic at least i could do yeah is it wompcomic.com what is it and then control
yep okay no it's not what what i'm typing it in chat okay it's uh it's penny arcane stop it
censor him censor this guy see how funny he was in the games that's how funny is in his comic no
no no he was lucky see me on the boat and thanks also to um the star and ashley always trying was
fun and so was this so i gotta go i'm gonna do my send off uh see you guys later happy halloween to
all of you and i will see you guys later thanks for playing guys that was star as well star and
ashley give him a follow no yeah i guess star and ashley will oh yeah but those these other
people by the way they yeah whatever oh whatever i think if you get the three sensors it's strike
three you know i don't i don't have to plug your stream yeah i think it's censored hey twitch.tv
slash what is it ashley ashley wait and by the way uh buy the shirt because she made it is it
a glue man shirt or is it a new one is a new one i mean both or the glue man and the planet shirt
the planets yeah nice yeah oh yeah y'all gotta buy that that's like you gotta get that in the
grocery store it's like the fine wine of shirts all right i'll see you guys later thanks for playing
take care all right now now for you guys as for you uh if you don't know those of you have no idea
what's going on i am not going to be around until the 31st the halloween stream is going to be
hopefully a lot of fun the secret slime stream that's what's gonna happen i'm gonna do a bunch
of activities it is slime time so i will see you guys in a few days on the 31st and we will do the
bits i still have time that's why i want i need to go i need to make sure there's still time for that
which there is where was my um pay no attention to the bottom stuff still fucking wrong but that's
all right take care see you on halloween if you don't uh see the halloween stream
maybe we'll see you again next time we're gonna start either outer worlds or dead rising when i
come back and there's also going to be another community content night there's lots to do oh
by the way this is uh i wanted to give a link to this is uh ronnie's comic
whomp that was whomp ronnie whomp comic i did not link it so all right let's do the bits
see you guys on halloween and here we go earlier we had about five hours ago it's time for slime
what a perfect perfect first bit uh donation here thanks for the 500 bits now that oberdin is on
switch you should play it during your upcoming travels it's great and not very long so you can
definitely finish it during the trip unpopular opinion you shouldn't play it on stream chat will
absolutely spoil it for you every single step of the way it's such a wonderful game though i hope
you enjoy it on your own time well i do have an upcoming very long plane ride so maybe yeah it's
on the switch maybe i'll just get it just disable chat i actually i do want to play it but it was
one of those things that just never ended up happening it's a lot of games too many games
hey superintendent chalmers thanks for the 250 bits and it is a uh an image it's uh me with my
hands up like with a scary face like i'm gonna strangle somebody uh this is like i'm gonna
strangle you thanks for that appreciate thank you superintendent chalmers uh thank you gnarly
for the 250 hey germa didn't have a dream last night what the fuck i'm sorry i mean actually
dreaming kind of sucks i don't know if this happens to you guys but after i have a vivid
dream that i remember i feel like shit the next day and it travels with me all day you just feel
like crap you wake up slower you have a step lost
it's just one of those things i feel dehydrated yeah it's weird
sometimes i wake up with a headache even if it's a very normal dream
it's very weird but thank you gnarly for the 250 thank you too uh thank you emmanuel depressed
for the 500 bits germa if you don't count streaming as an official job kim is dating
a retired balding substitute teacher okay what subjects did you teach uh i taught i didn't
teach anything i did substitute teaching so i filled in wherever it was available that's it
that was a childlike killjoy yeah you want to talk about killjoy did you entertain your class
yeah i told you one time i just started speaking i was just talking with a british accent the whole
day and i think the principal of the school actually asked me like hey are you doing that
and i was like oh yeah i guess i am doing that do that now is that why you can handle the chat
thank you emmanuel depressed for the 500 bits appreciate it uh thank you cleb man for the 300
bits hey jeremy i just looked up your name on imdb is it really true that you were in neil breen's
fateful findings that's the thing about imdb uh anyone can edit that shit so um no i don't know
what that is i think editing imdb is easier than editing wikipedia you know why because
nobody gives a shit when you're on imdb people actively try to fix wikipedia who's actively
trying to fix imdb but anyways appreciate the 300 bits thank you bone jackal for the 500 bits
i don't know what it is but something about your streams just makes me so gassy you guys ought to
start calling me i'm not gonna read this name out loud because i'll be heading to the super
i don't even know the toilet whatever thanks for the 500 bits smelly boy thanks for the 250
hey jeremy i love your gaming and gamer gaming stuff do you prefer your pillows really
puffy and fluffy or really squishy also do you sleep better in warm weather or cold weather cold
weather absolutely uh you know actually that to get the best sleep you're supposed to sleep
in a cooler environment that means turn down the heat during the winter
sleeping at like 78 degrees is actually really not that good for you that is real yeah it's true
but uh pillow wise um i prefer i like squishy pillows because really like fluffy pillows you
you sink into them and they end up just turning into a little bunched up piece of crap whereas
a squishy pillow holds its form and can read you can lie on it you can put it on your uh especially
considering if you sleep on your side and you put your hand under your pillow a fluffy pillow
you end up with a you know you can get pins and needles in your hand and stuff no it's uh squishy
for me 250 awesome sauce you gave that 10 community subs thank you earlier speaking of subs
let's see let the credits roll here it comes i really hope you guys enjoy the halloween stuff
this is a kind of the continuation of what i was saying a couple months ago where every every like
one to two months i really want a kind of a big stream so hopefully that we can keep this going
and i hope you like it we're gonna try it should be fun thank you everybody for subbing as always
hey doc thanks with 300 bits doc 3660 my love life is like germa's youtube channel
dead and filled with past memories those memories what those memories are great
those memories are great i loved every second on youtube it was an awesome time in my life
yeah thank you though uh inferno thanks for the 400 bits uh are there any smilers here in chat
any smilers maybe rare pepe body lotion thanks for the five community subs thank you
appreciate it rtm 47 thanks for the 250 my birthday was yesterday and i missed it so this
is pretty cool to catch can't believe it's been about a year since i found your stream
here's to another year watching whatever you decide to do for us germa hart happy birthday
yesterday feels birthday man right happy birthday hope it was a good one yeah happy belated birthday
and yeah i'm here's to another year we'll see what happens over the net up some some pretty
it's it's the sum over the next like six to 12 months i'm gonna keep doing stuff like you'll see
on halloween and like you saw at the carnival and even after that there's already like a bunch of
things already going forward so i anticipate the next year to be the most full of stuff like from
from like september to next september it's just gonna be full of stuff full of things
and we'll see how it goes but thank you our team happy birthday and then finally volemy right now
300 bits germa do you prefer squishy or fluffy tails what does that even mean a squishy tail
what tail is squishy stop stop stop stop stop it will be fluffy because it's like a
i just like i like like hamsters and stuff this is a trap jeremy about whatever
germa don't answer this it's fine i don't know whatever it's fine whatever i whatever
i like animals all right i i love animals is it okay that's it and that is it thank you for
watching you'll see me again on halloween just to go over again what's going to be happening
halloween is there's going to be a secret slime stream there's going to be uh actually i
i guess i could just tell you so you can prepare for it there's going to be
trivia you're gonna have your own podium it's not really a secret you kind of need to know
because i don't want to spend that much time explaining it because i'm gonna be live and
this is gonna happen so we're doing a trivia night doing a couple other things slime secret
slime actions if you have no idea what's going on go to the secret slime discussion channel
and the uh actions channel and look at the description there's about a two paragraph
description of what's gonna be happening it's gonna be kind of like circa 1995 nickelodeon
should be fun what time is it starting it's probably starting around probably 4 pm eastern
between 4 and 5 pm eastern i'm gonna lock that down we just we don't know yet we will know very
soon it's gonna it's not going to be like two pacific it'll be like around four four or five
eastern bilge berry is gonna have his own podcast now i don't know who knows i don't know what the
fuck his schedule is it's hard he's very busy hard to lock that guy down 4 pm eastern is is earlier
than i start here so that would be about a 1 pm pacific start it's i mean i typically start
between like like 120 130 140 so that's earlier than i start now somewhat it'll be sort of around
that same time frame hey mr comcast thanks for the 500 bits who's gonna win the slime contest i have
no idea because there's a lot that can happen uh thank you mr comcast with 500 bits hey germa
normally i make a funny john comcast message uh but recent circumstances have let me left me
unable to do so i was involved in a pretty bad car crash a few weeks back and i have been
hospitalized since then holy shit i found it a few days ago that i'm gonna have to have my leg
amputated so it's been a very scary time for me i just want to let you know that you're one of the
main reasons i've been able to cope thank you for bringing laughter when nothing else does and keeping
me sane i'm so fucking sorry to hear that but you've been coming in with funny shit for a long time
i'm really sorry to hear that that's happened to you hopefully everything can go as planned
hopefully i'm so fucking sorry to hear that but you've been around for a long time like
look at this chat this is just support each other guys seriously much love to you i hope
everything turns out okay i wish you an extraordinarily swift recovery and thank you
for being part of this community and thank you for continuing to be part of this community
and i am going to take off because i have to get ready take care everybody have a happy halloween
if you are not going to participate in the stream what time am i going to do what time will what
game will you play for the secret slime though that's you'll see he's going to miss his screening
of the departed yeah don't you know if i'm going like if i'm going back to boston
i've got to watch the departed twice before i get there just so i can make sure i'm like up on the
references they don't know all right guys see you later see you on halloween take care of yourselves
have a great night see you soon take care everybody uh hall hall lulu 250 bits says chat hug
hell yeah good night guys see you see you on halloween