Okay, see? I'm early. I'm early. I mean, I said I was going to be much earlier than this, but,
you know, take what we can get. Four minutes is fine. By the way, I looked over here,
and right when I pressed the go live button, I saw somebody say,
oh, like he farted or fart fart or something. And I was like, oh, what? Because I did.
Right before I pressed the button. I was like, how is it possible they could know that? But I forgot
that's like one of your guys' favorite words. So like, oh, of course, that somebody probably
writes the word farts in this chat, like once every, I mean, it's probably every like two or
300 words. So yeah, didn't catch me. Okay, hi. How's it going? Welcome to the stream.
Somebody said, great. Yeah, like, okay, great. Today, we're gonna look at him. Hmm. What are
we doing today? We're playing the logical journey of the Zoombinis. I played this game 30 years ago.
I also played this game about six or seven years ago. It's been a long time. It has been at least
five full years. Don't you feel old? 30 years ago? I mean, when did this come out? Okay.
Logical journey of the Zoombinis. This came out in 1996. That's 27 years ago. Yeah, 30 years ago.
People were question marking when I said 30 years. Hmm. Damn, you're old. Yeah, but we're
gonna play it. We're gonna get to my favorite part. If you don't know my favorite part,
it's the narrator. And it's when, you know, for all the new viewers, we'll let you experience it on
your own here. It's a puzzle game for kids. I seem to be on a trend here playing puzzle games for
children. I feel like I did that a lot. But yeah, let's go. It's a shame you don't have any brain
fluid. Wait, was this the brain fluid stream? It was. Okay. Yeah, it was. Here comes an embarrassment.
Well, the thing about the logical journey of the Zoombinis is you can change the difficulty to be
as easy or as hard as you want. You can make this game impossible. Okay, you know when you're in a
character creator, and you can just go to the hands, and you can make the hands just scaled
500 times. It's like, holy shit, that's kind of ridiculous. The Zoombinis you can you can scale
the difficulty up almost impossible. You'll see. So is this like Street Fighter? Dude, you're playing
a 30 year old game and not Breath of the Wild or Tears of the Kingdom. Hey, I'm the fart simulator
guy. I'm the fart simulator guy. I'm not the Zelda guy. Do you know what I'm saying? You got to do
what you know. All right, is Zoombinis some of the most important media? I'm kidding. All right,
let's go. Actually, yeah, it kind of is educational, fun, engaging. I think it was pretty formative.
All right, so we're going to watch the intro because I want you to see it. Here we go. All right. All
right. The intro is not clickable, so never mind. We're going to skip that part. Zoombini Island.
I can't watch the intro. Why? Don't skip. You hear me clicking up. I am clicking as fast as I can.
Will you play Left 4 Dead 2? Not right now. Watch the intro. I'm trying. I can't. All right, the
intro is just the Zoombinis need to find a new place to live, and they've picked an area that
they just need to traverse dangerous world to get to. We have to make our character. So the whole
point of Zoombinis is you have to make a bunch of Zoombinis, try to get them all. That's right,
I said all, not one, not two. All of them to survive to the end. So let's start. Okay, I'm
making this. I'm making that. And you could just make it all random too, which is probably what I...
Oh, they have names. Oh, I just randomized the entire group. All right, we've got a lot of
pink noses. And this matters, by the way. This is incredibly important.
He did it again when I did this last. I did this six years ago. I just programmed to do something
wrong. I did it the same. I did that already. Why am I programmed to do this wrong? All right,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Can I go back? All right, how about we'll do half? Okay, we'll do half
randomly generated because it's fun to be because randomly generated. It needs to be this way.
I'll make three people. Why was more springs? We don't have any springs. What is going on here?
Uh, let's get a... How many... What do we have? A lot of green noses. Not a whole lot of blue noses.
Where's Gunu? That's a different universe. All right, I like that. We got a lot of pink shoes.
I don't know if I want more pink shoes. What do you guys think? I think we need more wheels.
No, what do we miss? What if we don't have a lot of blue shoes? Need more springs. Oh yeah,
we do need more springs. Spring, red nose, sunglasses. We have a lot of sunglasses. We don't
have very many of these eyes. Okay, only a few more. All right, another... Should we do a cyclops?
Okay, a lot of this ponytail here, these little guys edible. How does the game work? You will
see very shortly. Need another one of these. Yeah, let's do, uh, that green nose. Oh, that's it. All
right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. It's all right. It's just it's old. It's an old
90s game where the cut scenes were dialed up times a thousand in audio. All right,
are we ready? I'm excited to play the logical journey of the Zumbinis. So we have two bridges
here. Probably asking, okay, the logical journey of the Zumbinis. We just across the bridge, right?
Let's go. Let's go ahead and do it. Let's go ahead and do it. Let's send somebody across the bridge.
Made it over safely. Safely. Okay, so let's deduce why that happened. Well, should I let you figure
it out? Let's find out. Okay, ready? Let's have somebody else go across. Okay, so there was a
problem there. I could not bring this guy over and the reason for that... This is not my face.
Why are you everyone saying Jerma? Jerma? All right, so this one made it across. What do you
think is wrong with this one? You think it's the different nose color because that's what you have
to figure out. Let's figure this out. All right, is it yellow noses are allowed to cross? Uh oh.
And by the way, they can die. Just so you understand, they can die. You get it? Do you
see what we're dealing with right now? Okay, is it... It's not the nose. So is it the hair?
Or is it the wheels? All right, do we have any other wheels? All right, wheels and a completely
different hairstyle. But the eyes are... All right, everything is completely different but the wheels.
If you have wheels, please go on the bottom bridge because that is what it is. Okay, so
what about springs? All right, people are gonna start dying. Uh, so springs... Can springs go up
here? Yeah, they have to be able to go through. Right, okay. All right, so they get a little
excited. Who couldn't make it? Okay, what about you? Yeah, you're fine. You're fine up there.
All right, you're fine up here. I think it's only based on the shoes but I don't know about those.
Let's just get everybody out. I think I'm just on the regular difficulty as well. You... I think
this can be much harder as well. As well, as well, as well, as well. All right. Settle down. All
right, it's time to... Like, what? It's all right. We got... All right, we got everybody.
Everybody has safely made it across and now they're all gonna go...
Watch. You've done quite well. Well, I did that sound so that's fine. Where's the Diablo 4 end
game stream? You don't want to hear my D4 thoughts. You don't want to hear how I feel about D4.
I don't think you... I don't think you want to hear how I feel about that game.
I don't think you want to hear it. These stone guards have their rules so do proceed with skill.
All right, this one is like the bridge but there's more... there's more places for error.
What did we do to deserve this? More of those little pebbles. Okay, so just like the bridge,
this one is also about letting people pass depending on like the shoes they have and the
hair they have. But as you see, there's multiple points of failure because if this rock is fine
and doesn't care, this one might care. So we have to deduce. Hey, it's logic, right? You're always
gonna start somewhere. We're going pink shoes. We're going straight in this way. All right,
not happy about that. So some people are probably gonna die here. I just want you to understand.
Okay, so something about this I'm gonna say. Let's go left side. You're cool with this. You are not
cool with that. Okay, so what is it? What is this? You've got red nose, pink shoes, glasses. All
right, maybe it's glasses. Is it the glasses that you don't like? Let's see. Okay, who's got glasses?
Excuse me. Okay, so it's the feet. Yeah, it's the feet. All right, so propellers cannot go this way.
So propellers have to go this way. Can the propellers go here? Is it based only on propeller
for you too? Are you good? Okay, that's weird. All right, do we have pink shoes? Okay, this is based
on shoes. These. Okay, all right. So what about spring? You don't want spring. Do you care? You
both don't care. Nobody is going up here. Enjoy yourself. Speedrun the game? All right, what about
this way? Wheels? All right. Wrong way. Okay, with it this way. Oh, shit. Wait, what? Sorry. What is it?
Oh, so what is the problem? Have a good time. Have a good time. This process is pleasant.
Why are they doing this? Are you enjoying Final Fantasy 16 exclusively for the PS5 as a timed
exclusive? Yeah, I actually think it was fucking phenomenal. Okay, all right. What about blue shoes
this way? Welcome. I think we got it. So what was the problem? What does she just want? Anything?
Enjoy yourself. This is just practice. We're gonna do this again on hard and you'll see how
impossible the game is. Here's the best part of the whole game.
I used to sit here when I was younger and the reason why I thought this was my favorite part
of the game is because when you're younger, just making food. Oh, look, I made a, I made a jalapeno
and pepperoni pizza. I say, oh, okay. You get to like make stuff. All right, we got to go simple
though. Okay, well, let's see. All right, you have to, so we're going to play this again with the
other characters. Don't worry. I'm just, we're doing the tutorial. The tutorial is can we get
all 20 zoom beanies to the end on normal five-year-old difficulty. All right, so he doesn't
like it. He's something something on this. He doesn't like, so let's just try this. A regular
cheese pizza. Okay, you like the cheese, but he wants toppings. Okay, so what? Okay, something
maybe was it the, I don't know. Maybe just pineapple. All right, we got it. Pineapple and cheese
pizza. I would have said gross. I have absolutely fucking said that before. You got them all.
Play the harder difficulty. Yeah, I just, we're just doing the tutorial. I think we have to go
through it once. Eventually there are three different tree characters here and they're
very specific, but let's keep going. How many hours do you have in this game? I don't know.
Like four.
What the duck.
Right, so this game is kind of, let's turn the difficulty up. Why not? Let's go for it. Oh,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not yet. If you don't have enough
zumbinis you have to have 16 if you don't have 16 you have to play the game
again but you have to get enough in the first three levels to be able to
continue on and we can go up or down too you have 16 yeah I know I'm just
showing you how it works you know when you do your full playthrough you'll
you'll see all right up or down I forget I forget what direction is easier go
down down is better I don't remember bro no one's gonna play this other than you
this is tutorial mode well it's just easy mode we'll go through it another
two or three times because if well I mean I've played this game a lot this is
like one of my favorite games I haven't played the game in six or seven years
and then before that it's been like 15 or 20 or something but you know you get
the idea you have to get a ton of zumbinis to the end to beat the game
this is one of my favorite games you got a problem I'm just going down you got a problem like do you
have a problem with me is that like I'm asking do you have a problem with me
sitting in the chair like I'm playing this you got a problem there's no sense
leaving it up to chance no the flings off the tree branch oh the flings that's
right all right you wonder why I like this game so much because all the
zumbinis just go like yeah of course I'd like the game all right so each
fling is matched to each individual zumbini so we have to figure out what
is matched with what so we're just gonna sacrifice somebody all right so blue
shoes is the treads these eyes are the mask the little hair
follicle is the helmet so we need to knock them off of this branch so we need
to find a hair follicle with those eyes okay hair follicle with okay and then
the tank it's gonna be old and unhealthy yeah
zumbinis are I love this game I used to play this when I was younger I'm just
trying to desperately key hold on to my youth okay so we don't what's the what's
the mohawk we know that the spinny is the tank green nose is blue okay so
somebody that has these eyes and a spinny yeah okay ponytails mohawk so we
have a few more options oh no we don't no it's like just two okay that's this
one it's gonna match that rock out break big brain moment I actually don't know
how much harder they make that at the higher difficulty
this sounds like a garbage disposal garbage like wait in that rock song yes
ah yes I'll be right down make yourself cozy oh that's right we have to you're
just in time for tomorrow's concerto help yourselves to a room if I remember
rehearsal go ahead find yourselves a room as the game gets harder I think they
the room stack up this tall and this wide so it gets very hard and I think
there's a timer all right so we have to see who can like be in this in like a
same hotel room okay is it about is can you go in okay is it it's probably just
shoes we're on the easiest difficulty it's definitely just shoes it's not okay
is it oh is it I don't know noses this is too blue this is blue and red eyes
it's its eyes that's the eyes all right so we need any more okay okay it's the
eyes you guys are so smart no help we have to get one batch of zoom beanies
across to the end because when it gets harder it's easy to lose people all right
yeah this plays out hey that's cool a place for everyone and everyone in a
place please protect the red glasses with you all life I'll try
mud ball wall I love this one I used to just bail this one deliberately because
it was fun just to use the toy okay so where so this is green ball with square
fire it I just went a hundred million miles per hour I got it right all right
so that was very fast I think the game is running at 60 FPS so the the game
runs at 6,000 percent speed so this is how many we're allowed to bring up so
that was a green square what is red square is red square gonna be over here
not okay so color is the column and shape is the row all right so we're
looking for I think let's just go blue and got it all right so no more just
scared me or second I thought they were doing a frog noise I was like no we're
in a swamp Chad is so stupid to find this confused confusing wait do I know
something the chat doesn't know this doesn't make sense wait am I better at
chat at a logical journey of the zoom beanies puzzle game you don't get it
are you struggling to do it you don't get it oh bad all right so let's do
triangle blue let's hope it's right there no it's right there that's fine
star blue is it has to be at some point down here all right that's fine it's
what it's circle and diamond now I get it yeah you get it eventually this gets
to be like three different colors and the board is like huge with like a
thousand different combinations all right so triangle yellow yeah triangle
pink hurry up all right we got him now we need to do star green educational
experience how can you keep mentioning the harder difficulty I don't know I
still don't get it so color is going to always be part of the rose that's my
favorite character and he's proving to you why all right here it is here comes
the best part of the whole game this is the single best part of the whole game
is right now you keep saying that no I mean it
why is he evil laughing I always found that so funny since I was younger just
because why is the narrator the narrator is trying to guide them and help be
like oh there's some beanies finally a campsite and then you're gonna do an
evil villain laugh this game formed your entire personality
these gloomy mountains strange carvings left by ancient peoples twist villain
all right I forget this one I think it's just like noses I'm doing easy first so
people don't omega well he has to be pretending in the first 30 minutes of
the stream all right it's it's gates this is just noses and then do we have
any more blues we yellow oh oh shit okay wait oh there's another blue nose I can
feel you breathing down my neck you know what I mean I don't know why right now I
just decided I was because this is simple but I don't know why I can like
oh okay I don't actually don't screw this up you save them all go okay
tutorial complete wait there might be one or two more use the crystal filters
to change the zoom beanies reflection it will give them crystal slamming
protection this is the Rube Goldberg room oh no that's not this way all
right what is what is this one I forget this one you have to put it's just a
mirror I forget okay I killed the only one everybody cared about okay um what
did I do wrong here I forget how this one works is it opposites no wait a
minute no I can't I can't put two on here I can't put two I think it has to
match somehow but match what there's two seats yeah but I can't see I can't um I
cannot click and drag anybody else over oh wait a minute wait a minute wait a
minute okay somebody is here oh okay somebody is I thought I was like
matching noses okay I get it I get it I get it I'm not pretending it's been 25
years since I played the game seven years ago I it's been seven years since
I played this game a lot a lot of happened in the last seven years okay
what who is this we have this one yep all right that one's match and then it
resets okay good does it no spring blue nose no spring red nose no pink blue
pink no no this one here operate don't be silly I just did it all right who
else I can't believe I killed the only person everybody wanted me to save and
that's the only person that's not gonna make it to the end that's the only one
the only one that didn't make it all right we got not this one yeah I've been
like just a burpee I'm not I don't know why it's happening to my body of my
body is turning old okay getting old and burpee happens to the best of us there
we go yeah I'm speeding it up I'm speeding it up I'm going much faster than
I was before all right I can't believe I killed that person okay restart we're
gonna restart okay I'm looking for no you're this one here some beanies do
not have an afterlife oh I'm sorry how do you know that it'll start getting
easier here hey pink shoes yeah here we go but they're lying they have an
afterlife but it sucks okay pink shoes oh I almost did this
one green nose who the hell is it pink nose it's gonna be one of the springs
right has to be has to be spring no I think it's this one why am I doing the
Bioshock infinite thing and it was a price I paid price I paid all right how
you doing today I'm doing good you're doing good too you good we're about to
be there we made it to some beanieville no this more this is the one that gets in
my head because you have to put this two entry points and depending on what they
have for features they move in a different direction so I have to be
careful so if somebody goes here and they have these eyes they're gonna stop
here and move this way then up up right so anybody that has these eyes is safe
but wait I don't want to do that yeah I do what if you don't okay if you do not
have these eyes you're dead if you go this way so let's get this right because
I don't want to lose anybody else so let's say you are a spring and I put
you this way you're gonna go straight through that you're gonna go up right
down left up right right okay it's gonna turn this thing that way I mean no I
mean she's dead no she's not oh fuck she has the hair oh that's right it's
all right everybody wave bye when she passes by am I gonna make it oh I don't
know if that means but hopefully it's yes yeah okay well hold on I always had
trouble with this one even on like the kids difficulty okay so up you don't
have those eyes you'll go right if you have the mohawk you're gonna go down up
down left die shit let's just get everybody over there that we know we
can get over there okay so if you have hair you need to go now because no yep
so all the eyes are gone so if you have this you're gonna go up you're gonna go
through this right okay here we go I mean no I mean wrong bad what you made
it we talked about that I made it it's correct okay so now if I do a mohawk
it's gonna go up up right down left up right so we can't have a mohawk go that
way chat is waffling do more funny murders ha ha ha this is only gonna get
way harder so trust me if you're sitting here waiting to make fun of me hey Jerma
I was watching your stream yesterday and I didn't have a chance to make fun of
how stupid you were I'm kind of bored not being able to make fun of you not
being able to do this children's puzzle game so I just I think I'm gonna take a
break of watching your stream for a few weeks just wait just wait till we play
on the medium and hard difficulties because you're probably gonna be gonna
get your your fill of that okay so now I think I can just alternate because if I
do the hair now all right is this right no yes it is okay is somebody dead here
okay you go up right okay yeah we're good only one person done we got what
14 out of 16 we're good hey what happened to the red glasses well we
tried to hold us together that you just reminded me we did it
all right how many did we get 14 yes this windmill was brought to honor the
Zumbinis who flushed the finicky flings in hotel dementia had pleasant dreams
and catapulted cleanly over a mud ball wall and the traveling was not so easy
okay look at all of our friends that made it as you bring Zumbinis to Zumbini
more structures are created more stuff is available as you see we got the
windmill and now let's go back very cool okay not so easy very hard very very
hard what is it okay there are 384 Zumbinis so how do we change these I
forget I'm not press it because for journey of practice we're not taking
anybody how do I make it harder it scales with you how many you save oh
okay all right so we're gonna go up this time we went down and took us this way
up is gonna take us around this way so let's just do it again
journey just gets harder okay yeah let's go let's go let's get all 384
glasses glasses glasses glasses that's too many glasses way too many fuck it
all right now we speedrun now we understand how it works we go fast
tossed about by a stormy sea the Zumbinis reach the shore speed runtime
so you get how it works we have to get all the Zumbinis over to the Zumbini
island remember how this one works we're just gonna go all right good start let's
see if it's probably just wheels it's definitely just wheels we're still on
easy I think oh oh oh oh they made it harder maybe it's noses blue got it got
it all right what about pink let's go pink up here pink is also down here the
rock does look like you this does not look like me at all this looks nothing
like my face it looks zero and I mean zero wait a minute so what is it then
why did you not is it not noses okay so it's spinners blue shoes are and is that
correct no that's not correct you're gonna kill these things is it the hair
no it's not is it that I think maybe it is the hair all right this one is a
ponytail snap made a Zumbini okay I'm gonna put this on screen I like this I
like this I'm putting it here although it's the shoes from Jen loss that's
funny there we go all right I'm in all right so was hair okay is it mohawk these
ones were okay yeah all right we're good let's go that's good cuz I could have
only made one more mistake I'll lose oh what about I gotta do me too okay let's
put me over here oh fuck I die I can't keep going I got I got eliminated these
stone guards have their rules so do proceed with skin zoom beanies one guard
won't allow surely here we go again all right little pebbles don't screw it up
because if you lose anybody in the early game you may as well just restart
just gotta pick up pick it all right all right what about this side okay is it
propeller it's not propeller it's also not potentially not even knows is it
eyes enjoy yourself okay but you might not be happy with okay
glasses all glasses this way you're gonna stop one of these I know you are
don't be shy good welcome propellers good all right what about skateboards
hello skateboards step right up okay propeller spring this way we must be
selective about our clientele well welcome hello this way welcome all
right pink shoes this way have a good time nailed it oh what's wrong with this
character blue wait what no glass oh have a good time you did it you'll save
them all you're throwing I'm all fine you've done quite well how delightful
so stupid travelers continue on through this dusty wasteland you have to deduce
it first man all right pizza troll time should still be pretty easy
whatever you are always start with cheese every time okay let's do same
thing as the last time let's see if the RNG gave us the exact same thing based
okay what about just helping us more stuff more stuff I think this guy in
particular formed my entire personality somehow more stuff so if I I gotta get
this right don't like that maybe something Moscow okay so it's mushrooms
and jalapenos I love the other two characters in this eventually as you
keep going and progressing you get harder the other two characters are
great too you have to please three different people with tons of toppings
boilers why this a campsite with hot soup all ready to meet but when they're
ready to move on they'll need a group of 16 along the way go up we do not go up
yet beanies must have something in common with their neighbor to sit on
Captain Cajun's oh you need to match somebody this gets ridiculous I
remember later on that's be perfect welcome to the boat about right they
have to have something in common whatever you want to I don't really
have to have something in common with your neighbor blue noses do hair we'll
do noses first blue nose and then hair and then wait there you go you got this
green bring hair there you go you got it okay hold on you blew it this is not
on a time list no what what hair oh shit right sure shit hold on is there any
yellow noses this will do it right well it's no yeah I need a yellow nose at the
start what if I did this and go I'll give you a little bit of a tidbit in
30 years that I've come back and played this game every like half deck every
so I've never beaten this truly it's always wrong especially the medium to
hard ones I think is impossible I think they actually made it not possible so
you guys can help when we get to hard because it's actually not physically
possible to beat it this is on easy okay um so what happens here is I believe you
put somebody on a frog and they jump out and they have to match a path based on
the color or the shape because you can't move anything so I have to put
this somewhere where it's gonna get to the other side based on I don't know
shape this one is shaped like the lily pad here so if I put this one here it'll
go up and then they'll die I think I'm just gonna I will have to figure it out
I'm just gonna go for it because this one is blue that you can only put this
on a blue so they're based on color and shape so okay if I put this one here
this is what the three leaf one no okay this where am I going oh should have
missed it this one is correct but three leaf because it'll go here and then
it'll go up okay so this one is correct for the three leaf get somebody on here
all right yellow let's go this way but wait a minute is it the flower it's
looking at little four leaf or leaf what can I start here okay start here I just
do that as many times I want four leaf does not have a path I don't think so
the line is the color yeah so if I go pink pink can know yeah wait all right
pink can do it right here each frog can be used twice okay that's good to know
what about blue this looks pretty solid yeah it's a solid for blue with X X does
not have a starting path so fuck with this one this one also does not have a
starting path dark blue has a path what about the pac-man pac-man has a starting
path and doesn't go anywhere no wait all right pac-man has the correct path here
for red what about this shape yeah all right this shape has a path right here
it doesn't matter right each one can be used twice so this is fine what yellow
yellow yeah yellow it can do it too will they hurt each other if they run into
each other which one was it this one right yeah this one here okay what about
this I can start here oh no this doesn't work here this doesn't work either I
don't think this one works at all what about X no yellow yellow can still go I
need four more diamond does work where are you seeing diamond working does no
diamond doesn't have a path where do you see diamonds path down up turning it does
it doesn't does bottom diamond at the bottom works huh right right down no it
doesn't it gets stuck right here no wait like diamond diamond diamond diamond
diamond diamond no middle middle middle teal diamond no look look see it gets
trapped right here ah three leaf well any three more it was a three leave that
worked already wasn't it because this one here yeah it's this one here
oh is that pac-man one over here right why so many ads you should not be
getting any ads I mean when you come to the stream you get when I can't turn
those off there's a lot of ads right now I didn't run any all right one more who's
the last one the diamond okay I haven't gotten any I've gotten 12 I think you're
making that up we want to play an app do you guys remember when you guys would
force me to run ads and you pretended to like it it was really weird it was like
ads oh my god pogchamp please more ads and you guys weren't hitting you actually
wanted me to do it me it was very funny and weird I feel like the the upper path
is the hard path because I remember some of these being very very very hard later
this being one of them I don't know what this wants me to do so we're gonna have
to figure it out I think it's hair has to match hair so there and there nobody
has this haircut nobody else has this haircut nose and nose was a green nose
did I kill that okay I thought I killed that person I did I just misclicked okay
that's nose how do I how do I get there are 16 slots right nobody has to go here
oh it's not this haircut it's any I thought let's this haircut let's just get
everybody out there and figure it out eyes this one the rest of eyes you saw
me click in the right spot you saw that happen okay so who has glasses you've
got glasses so you could go here you've got glasses you could go here does
anybody have a green nose that can move down this way all right does anybody
have this haircut that can come up here you do there it is oh fuck I need a blue
nose to be here what's a blue nose that can come over you have a blue nose blue
nose eyes I need these eyes need to be the correct match go back so bad I'm
fine stop okay I need eyes then the hair needs to match over here the yellow nose
I need that hair cut I need a pink nose you have it I do I 98.5 bottom left it's
why do I only make one spring person the eyes do the eyes the eyes the eyes wait
pink nose wait stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop I got
it I got it I did but I genuinely I all right they can't see now those of you
that have ad block all right fine but like at least I can block out for a
minute right like help me what do I do what do I do help me what do I do I we
got a minute how do I do this so I can fucking when they come back from the ad
I can really make myself look really good you've got like 42 seconds you're
like 40 seconds left no help yes you know to which one which one which one
which one move yellow nose left okay that way hurry hurry hurry hurry before
they get back swap yellow noses we got 20 seconds yellow nose do the yellow
nose again the other one other yellow nose I fucked it up I fucked it up I
gotta get it right though move I don't say I don't even know who I clicked on I
don't remember who I clicked on I don't just blend it together I don't know who
I clicked on there's no undo the yellow noses together I just I did I did I did I
did I did I did I did I did this one hurts my head I have to I run more ad
so they have to wait and they could be hold on the other one what the fuck just
happened there's only four there's only three
yellow noses you guys back from the ad is the ad done you save them all I got it
That nearly killed me. Just wait till it's on hard. It's unbearable. I'm never gonna be able to do it.
I remember when I was younger. I think I even asked my mother to help me do some of these things in this game.
And she was like, I just I can't do this, Jeremy.
Just like, I can't, I don't understand, I can't do this.
Yo, just wait, you'll see.
You'll come!
All right, we got her back.
Throughout these gloomy mountains, strange carvings left by ancient peoples are everywhere.
Well, I just turned off pre-roll ads for how long did it say? Like 20 minutes? That's like not a bad thing.
Okay. All right, here we go. You gotta go buy glasses.
So glasses first. I thought she was gone.
All right, we're good.
What is that? I can't tell what that is.
And then sunglasses.
What?
Oh, no, it's not. All right, don't close the gate on them.
Uh-oh. Wait, what's? Oh, there's one more of these.
World trusted guide.
You run a few minutes of ads in a row and you can disable them for an hour.
I really just hate running ads. Use the crystal filters to change the Zumbini's reflection.
It will give them crystal slamming protection.
All right, I've got all 16. We're almost there.
Okay, this one takes the most time, obviously.
We have to get it right.
I have to pee so bad, but no, I'm not peeing until I beat the Zumbini's.
At least get
this group over.
Oh, right here.
Okay, next.
I love that little like bird sound, whatever it is. It's like bats.
Right here, a diaper.
I don't trust that, honestly. I don't need it, but I don't, I don't, I don't trust it.
I just don't trust it.
An adult diaper to me is like, I don't know. I feel like I
Sometimes I do like a full 60 second piss. I don't think it would work.
Okay. Oh, there we go.
60 second piss is easy. I don't think so. Spring?
Well, there's only two springs. So if it's a spring and it doesn't, yeah, it's not gonna match.
How much is 60 seconds to gallons? I don't, I don't know. Gallons?
I wonder. I'll figure it out one day.
Okay.
I'm eating a whole tray of ice. Why are you doing that? Did you make ice popsicles? Because if you did, cool.
But if you didn't, then
what are you doing?
Okay.
See, this one takes the longest, but this is the patience.
This is the patience part of the game.
It's really easy to be like, oh, just let's go and hurry up, but you'll make a mistake.
Bottom right. Hurry up.
I just did it. Okay.
What is wrong with the stream tags?
Um, he's having enough fiber. See, see how it off-brand eats bugs.
I don't know because I don't, I don't, the tags just don't, I don't really care.
Almost fucked it up. See, that's what happens in your rush.
How does the mail work?
Um,
go look up like a science fucking video. I don't know. Like, I know, but I don't want to sit here to explain it.
It's like, I don't know. It's a big long complicated process with a lot of moving parts.
It's probably a YouTube video about like, how does the mail get sorted and shipped?
Why do you want me to tell you that? I don't know.
Hey, dude, how does it, how does a mail work?
I don't know.
You put it into the mailbox and the
carrier picks it up, brings it to a sorting facility and
sends it out with different carriers.
Oh, look it up.
All right, I'm gonna mess this up. I have to pay attention.
Okay, only
ponytails can go this way or they die.
So if you have a ponytail, you cannot go this way. You are dead. So all ponytails, please
line up at this one.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. That's not necessarily true. Hold on. Yes, it is. How much is this game?
Um
Owned it for a very long time. How long I think it's like
10 bucks 5 bucks 20 bucks
It can't be more than that
Okay, so let's get this right because I see a lot of bullshit over here
So if I take this person with the glasses and I have you go up here, you're gonna go right
Up, you're gonna pass this you're gonna pass this and you're gonna be fine
so now
Glasses goes this way if I put glasses here again, it's gonna go right up and then get
Completely screwed up and die. So
It has to be somebody with
What about sunglasses if I do sunglasses?
We're good. So we have to alternate until there are no more glasses left. No, what do you mean? No what?
No, that's right. I got it. So then I do the the glasses will go up and be fine
I'm fine. What do you guys chat? What are you going about? Have you gotten the grimace meal yet? No, I'll probably try it eventually here
I got it because now i'll do the glasses will go up into the right and then be fine and then we do sunglasses
I didn't fuck it up. Oh, no, I got it. You guys are just you gaslighting
Okay, now it doesn't matter now everybody can just go on it. I hope this is right
Yeah, it doesn't matter anymore. I got it
All right, all 16 made it
Everybody died
Let's go
One died in the crystal. Oh
This is this be the place they've been seeking
I like when he does the funny voice. Yeah, I don't know if you can hear the audio wine
it's like
Got a house
The schoolhouse salutes the zoom beanies who?
armed captain cajun rode tattooed toads and knew how to network
Got a house
Trying to get some uh, some dwellings here this clock tower
Cool building out the village
Okay, still doing the journey
It's still on a pretty we still we still on easy. Let's try to speed run after I p I'll be right back
Give you a warning that the music was stopping and I saw a monkey ass. Yeah. Yeah, I see if i've seen a few monkey asses
You've gone for a long time. What was I? I wasn't gone for that long. Well, I had to pee and then I had to refill my water
Beverage, why did you say it like that?
Why didn't you just say water you said water and then pause and said beverage
Why did you why did you pause? Why did you couldn't you just you could have just said water what's in the water?
a little bit of a uh
a bit of a tea
Powdered drink thingy having it today
Okay, let's go. It's like I fuck with you guys and then I end up just fucking with myself
All right. Is this a good makeup here?
I'm speed running is i'm gonna go as fast I can now because I think after we do this next one
We should unlock the next difficulty. So let's go i'm going doesn't matter what is i'll make it work
You want variety? Yeah
I think this is pretty good. Maybe some more of the smaller eyes like this. Just make them all the same
I think you actually get soft locked if you do that
Because if one of the bridges for instance doesn't allow red noses and everybody has a red nose you they all die
Also, um, can we get a pole?
Do you want me to skip the intro cut scenes for each little game?
If we speed right, you know what I mean? All right, let's go speed run
All right, it's gonna be shoes probably, uh, we got pink shoes going up here
Is that correct? This looks pretty good. All right, what about um,
No, that's not right
So what is it then?
Okay, it could be
Different eyes. All right. What about is it eyes?
Might be looks good so far
Uh-huh. I think it's based on eyes
up
Is it not eyes hair
So what makes you able to go up here nose? All right, it's noses
What?
It's only pink allowed in the bottom
So many people are going on this first bridge
Okay
well
Uh, I actually can't I gotta be careful because
All right, can yellow go here?
Okay, i'm gonna everyone's dead. They're all dead after this
Because I okay. I know you go
Up here
Does everybody go up here but pink if I get it wrong, they're dead
Only pink at the bottom
What?
That's weird. Okay. Well, we made it
You
You'll save them all. Are you dumb? No, that's a weird
Only two people go on the bottom bridge. That's weird. This doesn't usually happen that way guards have their rules
So do proceed with skill
Zumbini's one guard won't allow
You are dumb. Hey, i'll run another ad if you say that again
I'm not actually gonna run another ad. Welcome
Okay, let's just go. Okay
We must be selective about our clientele. Have a vote over here
Let's try um noses enjoy yourself. Okay, is it all yellow noses? Is it a nose playthrough this time? All right
Enjoy yourself. Okay blue noses
What's the problem? Welcome
The hair
Enjoy yourself
I misunderstood what this stream was gonna be. I thought you were gonna drive around on one of those ice cleaners for skating rinks
I mean that's
That's funny. All right hair who else has that spiky hair you do. All right you
This way, okay
Speed run go
Okay, not a single person has been able to go up and to be selective about our clientele
We can't go up in this area. Why? Okay by me
Have a good time
Uh, oh they're okay, right?
We're good
Splendid say hi to arno
Say hi to auto our brave travelers. I'll say hi to auto this dusty wasteland until they meet
Oh
All right, still simple still basic we're good
Whatever you are
So this formula starts to become impossible to we have to go a little bit more detailed but no cheese
All right, so you like pepperoni and mushrooms
More more, okay, crony mushrooms and peppers
You want them all? All right. Well, here you go
I think eventually you start making ice creams too for them, right?
Spoiler, I know but whatever it's fun. Everything but cheese
You're adjusting to the trials of the journey like look she messed up if you must we're going down
I'm going down. I'm not the up is harder
There's no sense leaving it up to chance
Okay, this we know this one. All right, so let's just get somebody to go forward
All right, so spring is
uh heels
Can we match anything here? All right, so we got all right these eyes. All right
I would say the same like three words a lot today
What about the hair? All right yellow?
Shit, all right. So yellow noses are blue noses
Just take a guess here. All right. Shit. Stop saying that
Fuck it in my own head
I can't I can't help but I have to it's like a filler word for my brain
So it has to be these two. There's only two more yellow noses
Yeah
This one
It's almost no more room on the tree oh it's pink shoes pink shoes this one
All right, this one's easy i'm skipping I know
I know don't skip don't skip. How could you skip zoom beanies intro cut scenes? I know but we'll watch them again
See if it's hair it might be here it might be noses too nose it looks like it's noses again
All right, so if it's yellow noses then
That's it green
The door opening noise is the same on the tf2 team selection screen. It is you're right
Cool a place for everyone and everyone in a place
You know that although I say that but I've I hear sounds in games and in movies and I go I know where that's from
My favorite puzzle
All right, let's get us squared up
Okay, so this is green
So triangle yellow
Oh red
so red
Some of the shape of triangle blue
Oh crap
Whoa, what am I doing? It's pink. Okay
Yellow
square
yellow
circle
What the fuck is this game?
Laughing my ass off
Logical journey of the zoom beanies
I don't want to run out of juice here circle red
red triangle
Wait, what? Oh shit. No, no, no triangle blue
Whoa, wait, what's happening blue? Wait blue circle. I'm gonna people are gonna die people are dead
I have one shot left. It's pink diamond
I have enough for one more shot. It's pink diamond
Thank god, that was it I would have lost I almost just threw one easy
Another relaxing campsite ready and waiting for zoom beanies
And they'll need their rest
The darkest most dangerous part of the journey is yet to come
There are two other zoom beanies games that were apparently dog shit
I want to play them. I never played them even when I was younger
They were good
How do they compare to the logical journey of the zoom beanies?
Mountain rescue is super good. All right, i'm willing to try it spring. This pace is so much better
This is way too scary
What are you talking about got it right off the bat
I gotta go fast. I told you I was not gonna just mess around right now. Here we go. All right
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh
Trembling and shivering and sweating because this game is so scary
Well, um, I don't know. I wonder how well you do with the back of cereal boxes because that's the same amount of fear inducing
imagery
So I I don't know what to tell you
Yeah
All right, we're gonna go by noses first let's go red nose
Um
Nope, that's wrong
How many zoom beanies you think you could eat I don't know how big zoom beanies are I think they're really small
Why would I want to eat the zoom beanies
I'm not even gonna give that a response because it was so
Unbelievably stupid. Okay
They look delicious
Unbelievably out of bounds. Okay. All right. All right. They look like candy
Gargamel there's gargamel from the smurfs
Wait, so gargamel's whole thing was he wanted to eat them. That was his whole villain schtick because I'm going to eat the smurfs
What why?
It wasn't about like world domination or something
It was he just wanted to eat them because he thought they looked like they would taste good
Because they have an eternal life
The smurfs live forever. No, they don't the smurfs do not live forever. They don't have eternal life
They'd live
Like as long as a crane fly
Like fucking four days. What are you talking about?
No, dude, but what about papa smurf? Have you not seen the movie?
No, i've not seen any of the smurf movies I can't say i've witnessed any of the smurf movies
I've seen some of the old smurf cartoons
from the 80s and 90s
But not any of the movies when they went 3d. I haven't seen any of them
Where's the zoom beanie the lower button? Oh, it's gonna mess me up
Didn't you play smurfs dance party smurfs smurfs quests
Quests i'm gonna mess up your brain for a little while. Our language is so weird say quests
quests
We make like a
Quests quests. Oh, I have to do some I have to do some quests. It's it's a double
I didn't realize you're doing it
quests quests
quests
You're never gonna be able to say that word ever again
That's just you
That's not quests
Forget the stream by tomorrow, dude
I'm trying to figure out if that's like some kind of an insult or if that's just your just like I don't really care
What is that? Is that what was that like an insult that sounded like an insult?
I don't think that's what it was though. I think it was just purely like I dude
I'm not gonna remember this tomorrow like you saying this shit
Was it an insult?
All right, be careful
All right, if you have a red nose
The left side
Is always safe. You have a red nose and you go on the right side. You will always die
Let's just get that out of the way
for the rest of you
Everybody else has to go this way, but we got to do this right
so
up
if you have we have to alternate between
the
Eyes and the glasses so we want to do glasses first
First then these eyes then glasses and glasses
And eyes and glasses
Now everybody else should be safe
Yep, we're good. Oh, oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what'd I do?
No, i'm fine. I'm fine. I'm good. I'm good. It's a full party
We need to report on the smurf movie by the next stream. Okay
Do you do you want to give me homework?
Do would you like me to live?
Tweet the smurf movie and when I say live tweet, I mean just write a bunch of notes about it
Yeah
Which one so I every like five minutes or ten minutes I will write
I will do kind of like I did for uh movie halloween
Just the just the smurfs movie the first original 3d one that one
Okay
Yeah, now i'll do it
I'll give you like a i'll come back with a full thing of notes on the first smurfs movie
We'll go over it
This be the place they've been seeking a place of hope and prosperity
How much time do I have I could do this by next stream?
Oh, we got a bowling alley
Look what we got
nice
Any other new buildings?
Cool house more dwellings
Uh-oh. All right. The game just got harder
It decided to make this path these. Okay, the game is harder now. Here we go. Who's your favorite smurf?
I don't even know. I don't only only know is that this papa smurf
and then
What are the smurfs are there?
It's like a sleepy one. There's a sleepy one
The one that has like this there's a sleeping one, right?
What about smurfette? Where's the sleep is a sleepy smurf. There's a doctor
there is
A angry one. There's an angry one. There's a grumpy one. There's a sleepy one. There's a
medical one
Those are the seven dwarfs
Yeah, they they they copied the same thing. Wait, how many
Different smurfs are there? Uh, there are a hundred smurfs in total ever
Wait, there's only a hundred smurfs. Why are they only a hundred? Is this like a
It's not like like like a sparta scenario. It only took 100 smurfs
There's only a hundred smurfs list of the smurfs characters. Hold on. Okay smurfette. Okay papa smurf
clumsy smurf
Brainy smurf grouchy smurf hefty smurf greedy smurf jokey smurf chef smurf
Vanity smurf handy smurf scaredy smurf tracker smurf. I was right
Sloppy smurf harmony smurf painter smurf poet smurf
farmer smurf
natural smurf
snappy smurf slouchy smurf grandpa smurf baby smurf
sassette smurf
Wait, there's an alchemist smurf
alchemist smurf
timid smurf architect smurf baker smurf clock a clockwork smurf
There's a clockworks. What is what the fuck is a clockwork smurf?
Smurf
What the fuck
Uh is a wooden robot who is built by handy smurf. There's a lot of lore here clockwork smurfette
dabbler smurf
doctor smurf
Dopey smurf enamored smurf finance smurf. There's a fine. There's a financial advisor smurf guys. There's a flying smurf
Okay king smurf if king smurf exists, then how does papa smurf have any authority? There's a king smurf
There's a lazy smurf
There's a miner smurf a local miner of the village. He runs the mine in the forest where most fossil material
I was you guys gave me shit and it's just the seven dwarves a hundred times
You gave me a lot of shit for this and I was right nosy smurf
nanny smurf
editor smurf the smurfs residential editor in chief for the newspaper
reflection smurf
reporter smurf
Which smurf are you smurf personality test I have to do that at some point
Wait, this website is from like 1995. All right. Well, we'll put it on the list
I want to do like a browser stream again soon
Sneezy smurf stinky smurf sweepy smurf
Taylor smurf i'm reading all of these and it's gonna be painful for you. I don't care weakling smurf
Wild smurf tuffy smurf weepy smurf woolly smurf nurse smurf
Lucky smurf lumberjack smurf
Pretentious smurf pastry cook smurf. There's a pastry cook smurf. Let's do it all together
All right. Let's do it all together. Is this is this a real website?
Can we can we confirm this website's like actually a real place? Let's all take the smurf quiz
This is a real website. We'll take the smurf quiz right now. I think it's just scuffed
Okay. All right. Give me a second
It's just scuffed. It's a website called
Blue buddies dot com. This is a real way. Can we just check to make sure this website's like safe?
It probably is but you know, I I don't know who knows
This is like which smurf ultimate smurfs quiz
Interesting. Okay
There's a few of these which one includes. Okay
There's like I see like three or four of these which one of these includes all 100 smurfs. Oh shit. Did we?
Crash the site. Oh, well, I don't think we can take the smurf quiz anymore
uh
Well, I i'll take this one. Which smurf are you? All right. I'll just take this one. I apologize to the
blue buddies
web
owner webmaster
Sorry
Okay, let me
Do this. No, I don't want to i'm not watching that again. Sorry. Okay, I go like this. I should be able to pop it up
and
Okay, let's start our smurf quiz
Which smurf are you?
Oh shit. Hold on. Let me give me one second. I fucked up my capture stuff before
It's probably much easier to do it like this
That looks better
That's so dark. I always have trouble capturing a browser window
in uh
OBS I gotta have like a new system for it turn on the face cam
No
No, like it won't show up on
I can't like grab it. It's like in a weird window. I don't get it
Why is it doing this for some reason every time I capture a window in obs it just it just is like
Oh that window doesn't exist. You have to like search for it on the scene. It's weird. I don't know why it does this
um
Okay. Well, you can't see it which is annoying
Why?
Can't you see it? Why does it do this to me? Are you streaming naked? No, I need to get a different obs
I've been using the same one for so long and I hate it and I keep saying I want to change but I just don't
Oh, hey, there it is
It showed up. You should be able to see it now. Yeah. Why what the hell what happened? That was annoying
Okay, what smurf are you? Let's take it. I'm just gonna go for it start quiz
Let's get it nice and clean so I can fill the area. Okay start quiz question
Just 12 questions. You're at your cousin's wedding and no one is up and dancing yet you
Grab your date and go out to the middle of the dance floor
Look awkwardly around and wait for someone else to start dancing
Wait for a slow song to come on and ask the hottie beside you to dance
Okay
Tell the dj to put on the ymca song
Honestly, it's probably this one because I never want to be the first one to go out there
I'm waiting to see okay. All right, everybody
We're putting the music on now and two or three people go then four or five and then all right now
Okay now i'm ready to go. Yep that one your car your car stalls and you're in the middle of nowhere
Your cell phone is dead
so you find the car manual study it find what's wrong and
Fix it
No way to flag the next car that you see coming
No, look under the hood and immediately see the problem. You are on the road again in about 15 minutes
No, relax knowing it was a good idea to have a gps put in the car with a lifeline to triple a done
I don't even need to read the other ones. You are so bored with your boredom
You decided it's time for a change and you pick out a bold
Red and love it. Are we talking about clothing?
This wrong
You are so bored with your boredom pick out red I was like what the fuck are they talking about?
No, I don't want red in the bedroom
That's like too too much
Find the brightest yellow you can and make your room into a sunshine paradise
No, I don't know. I don't yellow either go sophisticated and classy. No. Yeah, rearrange the furniture get some new sheets study about 20
No, we're just gonna we're gonna move the bed
To the other side of the room and get fresh sheets done
Okay, your best friend tells you she's moving four hours away
You make a scrapbook of all the good times you've had together and leave a bunch of blank pages to fill in with the days to come
Start crying immediately and plan for a major. Goodbye party
Thank god for facebook vow to visit her your friendship is worth a long drive
We miss her terribly, but you know a friendship like yours can never be hurt by distance
Four hours is really not that far four hours
But that that's not it's really not a huge
Start crying immediately
Uh, I it's worth a long drive. Let's go
There's been a massive heat wave for about a week
Your most likely course of action is to go outside and just just bake in the sun. Yep this one
This one's comfortable, but personally go check on your grandparents
Um invite no this one, which of these would most improve your life saving more money learning a new skill
Protecting yourself online taking a trip learning a new language or getting hbo
Uh, I would learn a new language makes like I don't know sense to me. What language do you want to learn?
It's more spanish. The best way to see a movie is
Grabbing your wait alert alert alert mod chat. You have to take a survey to get your results
They won't let you get your results. You have to take a survey. Oh, how long is the survey?
Do I have to take a survey? I don't know lol. I didn't take it. You can skip it
I don't but I don't want to no. No, no, I don't i'm not taking a survey. Is there a different one?
Fuck oh no
just
All right. All right. All right. All right
the best way to see a movie is with a good friend going to the theater for a
Matinee grabbing your pals and jamming into the car to go to the drive-in
On your big screen tv with the surround sound. No, I don't like that. I like I watch movies
I'm such a shitty person to watch movies with people probably hate sitting there with me and watching tv shows and stuff
I turn the volume way down. I hate loud ass movies in tv. It just annoys me
I hate very loud movies in television. It's like I want I want to be able to understand it get a good
Kind of grasp of what's going on. I mean it's it's one of these
I'd say one two or three
It's probably one
But the drive not the drive-in though
But i'm gonna pick this one
You've been given the opportunity to choose one superpower to possess for 24 hours
You choose to go back in time to be invisible to be a speed reader
To fly or to be super why to be a speed reader who clicks that which what do you clicked on that one?
You can choose between speed reading books or flying. I think time travel would be interesting
Your sister needs you to look after her three kids for the weekend you
Rent a bunch of movies and make popcorn take them to the museum to see dinosaur bones
That's pretty cool
Take it to the fair and let them eat as much cotton candy as they want
Set up a tent in the backyard and tell them not two spooky stories around a campfire
Spend the weekend getting to know them better and are sad when they leave. I want to tell you it's this one
But realistically, it's this one
I want to pretend like it would be this one, but we all know it's this one
You go to an amusement park with the gang your favorite part of the whole day is
Crashing and smashing on the bumper boats screaming until your voice is gone on the scariest roller coasters
You hate them, but you love them going on the ferris wheel and looking for your house from the top
Taking pictures and just hanging out with your friends playing games and winning a stuffed animal for your crush
Now too much movement, especially if you've eaten during the day this one, but I don't screaming. No, I don't scream on it
I'm completely silent anybody else silent roller coaster enjoyers anybody else just kind of sit there with a stone
Just cold face just moving and okay
I'm not a whoo-hoo hands up kind of guy. I am a
Internalize this and enjoy this I don't like make any noise. I mean, that's not true sundaes were meant for
Shutting the world out. It's just me time crafting and creating masterpieces going to church shopping and grab
Gabbing with your best friends catching up on housework. I mean, it's definitely just I mean if it's the me time right sunday sunday
I mean, uh, I when I think about like, okay sunday later. I want to relax
I want to hang out maybe catch up on housework
No, it'd be probably this one
You invite a bunch of friends to go to the mall when you are there you see someone you totally forgot to invite
You call her later to say you're an idiot and you're sorry call out her name and beckon for her to come over
Ask her to join you and apologize for forgetting her don't know what to do
She walks by and you just look the other way
Gasp and duck behind a display and stay hidden until she disappears. Well, there needs to be more context here
You invite a bunch of friends
To go to the mall when you were there you see someone
You forgot to invite is this a friend or just a person I know that's incredibly important
When you you see someone you totally forgot to invite if it's a friend
And I do how often do I see this person? Do I hang out with this person a lot?
Is this a friend that you see like once every few months? Is this a friend? That's always you know every day is a daily
Friend, this is a monthly friend. Is this like a every six to 12 months you see this person somewhere
This is really important and I don't I don't know which one it is i'm going to treat this like it is a
A like daily friend like a friend that you see a lot. It's probably this one and I would be like, hey
Hey
Come over here. What the were you serious? I'd be like I didn't think you I thought you're gonna be busy today
I didn't I I didn't know you were gonna be here. Yeah, whatever
You just had a very stressful day at work a very stressful day
You are looking forward to finally getting home and relaxing when you get there you
Write in your journal for an hour and get all your worries out on paper call up a friend and fill her in on the nastiness of your day
Pull on your sweats and do some pilates
Yep, this one right here
Put on some soothing music get some vanilla scented bubble bath going. Yep, take off the music though
All right. Are we ready? I don't want you to see it until I do what you are clumsy smurf
You are so loved by your friends that they find your constant silliness enduring you definitely can act goofy at times
But underneath that armor of humor, you're actually quite a deep thinker in a word. You are fun. Okay
How would why would I have gotten how did I answer clumsy stuff?
Okay. Well, that was the smurf quiz. That was fun. You're the main character of the smurfs movie
How do you feel? I feel like I want to read the rest of the smurfs
Nobody smurf a smurf who always gets overlooked hunter smurf fisher smurf narrator smurf passive aggressive smurf
Panicky smurf social smurf smooth smurf clueless smurf party planner smurf vexie smurf
hackus smurf
complementary smurf drummer smurf
schemer smurf
dreamy smurf gullible smurf paranoid smurf policeman smurf
magician smurf mime smurf
Table-eating smurf as his name implies the smurf likes to chomp down on the edge of tables
Even popper smurf seems confused by his behavior by the end of the movie two female smurfs from the lost village join him
In his bizarre habit. I fucking got a spoiler. How am I ever going to do the homework now karate smurf winner smurf?
loser smurf smurf willow smurf storm smurf blossom smurf filly
smurf begonia smurf begonia
smurf melody smurf jade smurf petals smurf clover
smurf meadow smurf daisy smurf holly smurf hazel smurf honey
Miller smurf
This is a beer drinking smurf like what miller smurf is a smurf who wears a blue and white striped smurf hat
And the clothes of a dutch mill operator smurf moose
Holy shit. I didn't know the smurfs were that intricate
mid-life
crisis smurf
Well, that's all of them. Okay
Back to the uh thing we were just doing I did not know the smurfs were that intricate interesting interesting stuff
Okay, I will watch the first smurfs movie. I'll come back to you with a detailed report of how it went. Let's go
Table eating smurf that's i'm it seems one i'm really curious how that works has built up immunity at last
All right, so this one is harder we got to be prepared for this
Okay, let's just start simple is it the all right looks like spring
No, it's hair
It's definitely here
Oh fuck. It's not no no no get off off off off off off off. I can't I can't cancel it eyes
Okay, let's try down here so far so good
We're good. Yeah, I think this should be set now. All right, we're good made it
Oh whoops
Okay
You you saved them all
How many times will he repeat playing this game on multiple streams? This guy is this game? He's gonna play in his death bed
I mean, I played this once on stream
So do proceed with skill in 2017. I played this for two and three hours tops
You've never seen this game ever again since or before that
Here we go again
What did we do to deserve this?
Okay
Remember it's hotter don't be shy
Let's go spring
Okay
It might be noses
Okay, it might be hair
Is it hair?
shit
Not all doors are open to you
What do I do is that the only person that can go in there
Glasses
Okay, this way
Okay
So what is the difference between these two?
Have you go all the way up here?
You don't like the nose maybe
Okay, let's just see what happens if I go this way
Let's try yellow nose this way, okay, I think this is good maybe it is noses
one of the chosen few
help
What's wrong?
step in
Move it
What the hell?
this way
Uh-uh
step in
How many times has he played this game today? I started it three hours ago and i'm still here
What the hell do go in?
Certainly, okay
Oh
Welcome all right green nose green and red nose. I think you can go this way
You can let me in why?
wrong way
Enjoy yourself
Hey
Nice try
I'll get it. I got I got I got it this way
Let you better let me in away you go
You've done cool, I knew they could do it
All right, this is a higher difficulty pizza one finicky eaters one troll's poison is another troll's pizza
pizza for lunch and snacks and dinner and dessert baby would
satisfy me
New character
This is where it gets hard
So there is ice cream now
So here's the deal we're gonna go
Just this because we want to see if either one of them will eat whipped cream
I'd appreciate more toppings. Okay, so
she
Wants the whipped cream in the cherry, but he does not so we're gonna start with her
What about sprinkles
Something on that I don't like
Some of those toppings are distasteful. Okay, no sprinkles. What about pineapple?
Something on that I don't like I'd appreciate more toppings
Okay, so you want more than that
What about that?
Something must go
Some of those toppings are distasteful. Okay, so
We have I got plenty of I got this plenty of space that's gotta be it
Something's wrong, okay, so it has to be mushrooms
Little pizza makers
There it is. All right. Good
So you do not want this
So we're gonna have to just go and there's no cheese option either. How about just how about we'll just go musk make it easy
Make it simple
What does do you just want a sauce pizza
More topping, okay. All right. All right. All right. So let's do
I think this is gonna be
Just punch me in the face
Just punch me in the face. He punched me in the face. Okay
More toppings
Oh
That's all right. Bye. Uh-oh
Okay
So you don't like mushrooms
This is the pizza that you want unless you don't want pineapple, but you want sprinkles on the ice cream
Their stuff I don't like you piece of shit. He's gonna kill somebody else. He's gonna kill another
Shit. All right. Well, we did it
Thank you. Thank you. It's all good
We lost two but that's we'll be fine
That was challenging
But you did it. You are a bright one. Oh shit. We can't go any we can't go forward
We have to store everybody I can't move forward without 16
Yeah, we gotta go back I can see how you shaped your personality. Yeah
What is this freakish little game? That's a weird way to put it
All right, let's go
How about here?
Is it glasses or I mean these are pretty much the same let's try glasses
Nope
It's probably hair or feet
Try hair. Well could be either one. Let's try feet. Okay, I think that's correct
Oh
Maybe it is hair
So, okay, it's hair is it hair though all the same shoes
Slow down slow down slow down slow down. I'm good. I got it. Okay
Okay, I hope I don't get this wrong because
Did you add that as an emote? That's fine. All right, you've done quite well
These stone guards have their rules so do proceed with skill
They're blue
What's the point of the game is to try to get as many zumbinis to the zumbini ville town without losing any of them
But you will
Chosen few let's go pink noses this way see if it works. Uh-huh blue. All right blue noses
one of the chosen
What about green noses this way?
All right, what about this way not all doors are open to you
This is almost the exact same character. So, uh
Let's just assume that this is gonna get through assume this one will get through as well. No
Those eyes away you go
It's not hair. It's not feet. It's not nose. It's eyes. Okay
Step right up
Any more glasses up this way?
Okay by me
Do go in
Okay
Step in why is this one over here? Oh blue nose, right? The blue nose does it?
Okay, I think they all just go this way. Yeah, we're good
Glad to drop in don't mess up the pizza stuff now
Make me a pizza
All right, same deal. We're gonna go just
like this
Some of those toppings are distasteful. They both don't like pineapple
They're both hyper intelligent beings
Hyper intelligence. All right, what about this?
Okay, there's something there I hate oh good. All right, so you both don't want that
So what about sprinkles and then we're gonna then we'll go forward from there
There's stuff on that. I don't like
More toppings. All right, so we gotta we're gonna do hers. Okay, here we go
So you both don't want pineapple? How about sprinkle and
Maybe she'll just want it
Okay, so you don't like any of this shit
Something on that I don't like do you want a plain pizza possible? Sometimes it happens
You might just want a plain sauce pizza well find out right now
And nobody had to die
Is it why are you moaning in the background? Where do you hear that?
Is that you
That was challenging
But you did it. You are a bright one
Yes, you are
I'm not going up until I have to
There's no this one might be my favorite game besides the pizza one
This is my favorite non pizza related minigame
any of these match
All right, so it's a green nose and that's it. So we single out the green noses
And this one looks very different
So it's the green nose this hair
and pink shoes green nose this hair
And this is it right here. No, it's not
Yes, it is
Breaking news germa's favorite non pizza related minigame revealed. I got deleted by nightbot. Sorry
You used too many capital letters. I think all right
Okay
So green nose
Different hair though this one
No
So it's pink shoes and green nose
this one
That is really loud for me. Hopefully it's not loud for you
This entire game is food mode
Yeah, that's fine
Let's just go for shoes
No
Is it glasses?
It might be nose or glasses. Let's try glasses with a different color nose
Oh
It's noses always do noses first. What the hell am I doing? Am I dumb? Am I am I dumb?
Why would I not start with noses? I love this song
Hey, you're ready to snooze dream a little dream
Gonna play final fantasy 16
I can tell you the answer to that question is yes
I'm gonna play it at launch and and guess what?
I'll be sponsored to play again. Let's fucking go
You love saying let's go no, I just think saying let's go makes me
More relatable. So I try to throw it in there every now and again
Is it working red?
uh triangle
Can you say let's go zoom beanie gang that is like a youtube video
I'm gonna do like a tuba intro. I could if you wanted to see
I just got this incredible urge for tabasco habanero sauce
Just I had this
Immediate urge to just eat it. It was immediate
pink circle
Wait, oh, I thought I clicked circle
All right circle
What is it pink star? No, it's pink triangle. No pink square
How do you pronounce this pico de gallo you can put your head down in shame now because you thought I was gonna say it wrong
All right blue diamond
No
Well blue star
Good blue circle. Did you want me to do like a hot sauce a hot sauce burn my whole face?
List. Oh, this one is so hot. You want to do that? I'll do it
You catch up is too hot for you
Actually, that's kind of true in a lot of cases
Ketchup can kind of be a little too much
Good work. Can you brave the challenges of not spicy but like annoying?
The new dangers of the mountains of despair
Not spicy i'm just saying ketchup ketchup can kind of be annoying on food sometimes
I wouldn't want ketchup on let's say
I'm trying to think of what like would be kind of geared on
the little too
Tangy and acidic strange carvings left. I'd say the same thing about a tabasco sauce
I wouldn't want that on everything. It's like a little too harsh
What is this even telling me these hair styles? I think these are hairstyles
Can you eat a carolina reaper hole on stream for the haters?
I would want to like
Eat a bowl of soup for the haters. You understand that that would make the haters happy
Why would I do that for the haters?
That would make the haters be very pleased
The haters would be very unhappy if I was just eating soup on stream and I was like having a good time and normal
What do you what do you mean for the haters?
Me being like
Like on stream is like yeah. Yeah, fuck you. I fucking hate you fucking I hate him like I hope he fucking gets hurt
I'm waiting for the haters
When you're gonna eat soup on stream, I don't know never you should stream soup then for the haters
Okay, I can't tell what hairstyle that is. All right
What about where where's the soup tier list I want to do the frozen food tier list
You know what let's just stop talking about it and get a crystal filter
Let's get it a plan for it
Here's what I want to do
I'll talk to the mods and we will get a system where we can figure out what the best
frozen foods are
I'll get a bunch of them
And we'll do it
We'll talk after the stream get some guys so you can recommend like oh, hey, you gotta get the like the stoffer is
fucking meat and potatoes meal
Right, you're never gonna do this. Oh, I will I will like tv dinner. Yeah
just like frozen meals
frozen foods
Maybe like three or four from each major brand
Okay, here's the thing
I want to make sure that I can take at least enough from each one
And to be able to save the rest of it to eat later or if it's gross, you know
Obviously not gonna keep it. I think frozen meals is where we start. Jimmy Dean breakfast bowl
Okay
Fish sticks when you can do the baby food tier list
Your microwave is going to be working over time
Can you explain this minigame for the haters? Um
Yeah, that's fine
so in this game mode
You have to match the zoom beanie with the one of the mirrors and there are five to six fake zoom beanies up here
To throw you off. So I have to take one of my zoom beanies
and
Match it to this one. I can't like do this
Why am I having so much trouble with this? Oh, I don't know this one. I don't know whether it's getting an exist up there
a lot of pink shoes
You seem to be really bad at bottle flipping
Yeah, I am. I don't actually I never even tried it. I might be good at it. I've never tried do a bottle flipping stream
Is this game an analogy for children's journey through life to reach god in eternal paradise?
um
Media you can interpret. Oh, you know certain ways. How have you, you know feel like you interpret the media?
I interpret this as
the struggle to relocate
the hardships that come with relocating
and man's
constant struggle
With who we are and what we're what we're doing on this planet
And our ability as humans to overcome anything
That's what I think it is. That's how I believe it is
No, it's not
Just a fun game for kids about matching puzzles
Dope you got that from chat gpt
Does chat gpt even know who the zoom beanies are?
You should ask it
I've never used chat gpt. I just hear about it
Do you want to know the fastest way to make me never do anything have the thing?
that
Is something that to use have any kind of account sign up beforehand?
And I just won't use it
Ever the zoom beanies are a fictional group of small blue creatures who star in a series of educational puzzle games
First game logical journey of the zoom beanies. Okay. Well, they know
It's just a search thing, isn't it?
It's not just a search thing. Well, I mean if you okay if you type into chat gpt, what are the zoom beanies?
It's going to find it. It's going to figure it out
You didn't write what are the zoom beanies favorite foods or like how do we stop the zoom beanies or?
That's you're asking it a very simple question
You stop by not playing you killed one what no I didn't
Oh shit, I killed one
I wasn't paying attention. I wasn't paying attention
I was looking over at chat. I was talking to you guys
I was talking to you guys. I wasn't even looking at the game. I was just hanging out
There is no need or reason to stop the zoom beanies as they are fictional characters from a series of education educational games
Some beanies exist solely within the context of those games and do not pose any real world threat
However, if you're referring to a specific challenge or obstacle within the zoom beanie games that you're having trouble with
I'd be happy to help you with strategies or solutions to overcome it
Just let me know which part you're struggling with and i'll do my best
All right, how many people there's like 17 000 people here you are training
You're training the language learning model right now
People are going to start getting zoom beanie lore in their random fucking generations
They do chat gpt is just going to think that the zoom beanies are incredibly important and to start putting them in other places
Well, they are important. So
I can't believe I killed one. Can you please turn on the mic camera?
I haven't showered today and i'm naked. So no search first
All right, let's do this one. This one is got shoes in the mix now
So if shoes go pink shoes go up this way, they always will bump that way
And then be safe if pink shoes go this way. They will always go this way
And then they always die. So if you have pink shoes, you have to go this way. There's no other option
Wait, yeah, okay. That's right
Okay, so now what so it doesn't really okay. What about hair?
So this hair is going to go up this way. It'll go all the way up
down
All right, so no matter what
Hair has to go this way
Wait, no, everybody dies if they go that way
They have to alternate so as it stands right now
This has to go
This is right. Wait, hold on
If you have one of these hairs you go up
Up into the right down up. All right, so hold on. I this i'm gonna fuck this up. I think this is great
I think this is correct
Can we play Vinnie in street fighter?
I mean, it would be an absolute fucking massacre. I don't know. I don't think that's a
Probably not a good idea
It would be an absolute massacre. I'm telling him you said that
I'm talking about me losing
Before you go tattle tail on me really
Wow, okay
All right. So now I have to go up right down up. Okay, so if I put
this person with his hair
that's correct
and we do the
This hair and this should be fine, right? I believe that's correct
Let's love to worry about this
so now
Okay, you can go
and then
I think I fucked it up
No, I got it
Game sounds are too loud. It might be one guy, but i'll do it. Is it a one guy?
I turned it down a little bit. Are you slippery on a milkshake? I wish
You're wearing a star wars shirt today. No, not today. Can we get to a hundred zoom beanies in zoom beanieville?
We're definitely gonna get to a hundred there's no way we won't oh what's this swimming pool
They got a pool now
Okay, things have gotten harder this way. There's 60 here. Okay. Let me ask you
Should we continue to do just the journey and bring more people?
Or do you want to see how hard this game is because we've been playing it for three hours
What do you think let's get a pull-up you want to do the hard stuff and we'll play some hard minigames and then
See where we are journey or go to hard i'm seeing a lot of hard
Yeah, this is actually almost impossible for me on some of these you wouldn't last a day on hard
I know I I won't they're actually really hard. All right, so we'll let's do
Very very hard for pizza because everyone wants to see that. Let's go
So there are three
You won't last a minute playing this game on hard
That's not what you said
Oops, okay. So
We already have some things they don't like
I don't know if it's cheese sometimes hard to tell so somebody doesn't like mushrooms
Sprinkles or cheese i'm gonna go pineapple plain
go
I'd appreciate more toppings. Okay
All right, so let's work on hers so we got pineapple
And cheese is that is that good?
Getting there gee I wasn't expecting that one
So they all don't like sprinkles apparently
Because she likes cheese
So she doesn't want sprinkles. What about a cherry?
All right expecting that one so you all right
All right. All right
It's not pepperoni it could be mushrooms
Little pizza makers
So
What do they actually want? Let's just go chocolate sauce
more toppings start
Oh
Something's wrong. Okay. Well, I don't care. I got one
Okay, so
I don't he didn't like cheese did he doesn't want pepperoni doesn't want sprinkles. He didn't like the pineapple
Okay. Wait, what about the mushrooms down here? What about cheese and mushrooms and shit?
Didn't he not like cheese?
No, he didn't like cheese something on that's not good for me. Okay. I don't think he likes cheese
That's gonna be it
What?
What the hell do you want do you just what something's wrong
Wrong
Do you just want a cherry?
This is a fucked up meal
Well, maybe not. I actually think a tomato based pie. No
Something on that's not good for me. What does he want?
Doesn't want cherry doesn't like peppers doesn't like mushrooms doesn't want cheese. Is it pineapple? Didn't he say?
Yuck. No, he doesn't like anything. Maybe it's just cheese
Oh
Kill the log
All right. So you want pepperoni and chocolate sauce? That should be it
Yep
I've no idea what this guy wants. I don't think he wants any ice cream stuff
Let's check it
I have three or I feel like four more more please. Okay, you want sprinkles. Why do you uh,
Hey you that you liked it. That was a that was a happy punch to the face. Okay, whatever
No cheese. I don't think he wants cheese
Sprinkles and cheese is here and it's down here. No mushrooms either sprinkles and mushrooms and he's like get that shit out of here
So what about um pepperoni?
Gee, I wasn't expecting that one
Thank you, yes
Oh that one on the right was pretty doughy that one on the right did not look very good
Cool. All right
So, can I show you how hard this is on very hard? I don't even know why I don't know what this is
Okay, so because there's
uh
All right pac-man. No
Pac-man. No pac-man has nothing this
Can go down down
No, nothing. This can go. No, nothing. It's gonna go right. Nothing
This can go nothing
uh
This can go blue
Um
Wait, they're changing them. Do you see what's happening?
What see how fucked up this is look at what's happening. This is uh, I don't I can't even do it
I can't do it use the magic wand to do what I have to go really fast
I can't I can't look at it. I actually can't look at it. Watch this one
Those of you that thought this was a kid's game. Good luck because uh
Okay, let's try to get one person across so if this one goes up
It's gonna go up. I don't know what this is. We have to test it. What does this do?
Is it a teleporter?
No, it freezes them in place
So this is gonna go up and then a red I need another red nose to bump
Why would anybody get sent up here?
Uh
Wait, what? Okay. If I go everybody has to go this way. Oh, wait a minute. I can bump you this way
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, no. Um, oh, there's another path to wait
What i'm not gonna be able to do it. I don't I don't think I can do it. It's too hard
It's not even too hard. It's just too much my brain to look at I have to get one person over there
How do we even go this way? I think this is just death for every single character
I mean not really how to because that's changing this to go that way
Now this one wants to go up if it goes up. It'll hit the green marker hit the green and then it's stuck here
This made this one turn right so this one now is gonna go right right if you have one eye
Which will make you go this way then up got it
We're gonna save at least one person
Because now I can focus on the green and glasses. I can't I don't want to look at it anymore. Check this one out
I actually really like this one. This one is fun to do. So let's go. Let's just start blue square blue interior
blue
Square red interior blue yellow interior
all right, so what
Does this mean this is yellow internal square is up here red internal square is here red internal square with blue
with a star
Oh, that was so completely wrong
triangle
Each one of these is it's okay. Hold on. So it will be green with a square. Okay
the square
Red interior square triangle. No shit. It's not a red interior square
pink
red interior square
Yellow
Get this guy some lithium. Remember we don't get this game. Let me help you
So I have to pick a color the color is corresponding to a space on this board
The square the shape is corresponding to a space on this board. You get it
So all red interior
Shapes are this row you see what's happening all blue
Interior shapes are on this row all yellow interior shapes are on this row
So to get this it is a red interior shape. We have not seen circle
So let's try it
Okay
So this is a circle. This is a circle with a green
exterior
You couldn't possibly know that I do
So the problem is not knowing
what
Interior color this is i'm gonna say pink
Okay, i'm almost out of power. Fuck you. Why is that over there?
Fuck you. What?
I want let me restart. Let me restart. I'm going to try again. What are you gonna do et atari?
I don't know. We have to get a center. So this is interior yellow triangle interior pink triangle
interior
pink triangle
red
interior pink triangle green
interior
pineapple
interior pink triangle yellow outside
star
Interior pink triangle yellow outside
Wait, i'm confusing myself. I just had it. I just hold on. I had it restart. Okay
Okay, the rules change every time you restart. Are you serious? Oh fuck. Okay, that's why I was screwed
All right. All right. All right. I'll get it. I'll get it. I get it pink interior
Red triangle red interior red triangle
Looks like it goes this way blue interior
Okay, good guy
Here we go. So that means that this is red. Would this be all red?
exterior red exterior
red
star
shit
Wait, what?
Why would that not be in here?
Exterior is the columns. So what about blue?
I dude I had it I had it and I just like fucked it all up
Interior is the line this time shit. I like okay
You know when you when you have something in your brain and then you you think about it more than once
And then it just completely disappears and it's as if you've never played it before it's just gone
Just it's gone like oh pink interior a red exterior shape
Is in this column in this row. Well, i'll try it again one more time. It was a good guess
So they're both squares they're both blue exteriors
The only difference is their interior is a different color
So what does that mean? Why is that on a different? Why is this in a different spot? I'm going to try something here
What is blue exterior?
square
Green interior. Oh, yeah, so all squares are here in this zone
all squares
In this zone
No, all blue exterior is this zone wait that might be right i'll test it one more time
Okay
So i'm imagining this is all green. This is all blue. This is all red. So this is all blue
blue
Interior no shit. Don't nobody stop talking. Hold on. Wait, this is oh i've had it. I lost it. Where's it?
This is blue. Yeah, i'm losing it. Stop just sit down for a second blue interior blue exterior blue interior
Is this so this is not star. Let's try circle
What this is all blue interior?
What diamond god damn it
star
All right. I got it now. I actually I have the pattern. I have the pattern so this means this is this is blue exterior
Okay
Blue exterior. It's not green, but it's a square. I guess we'll try pink
What i'm so confused. No
Okay, it's
Green that it has no the yellow interior
no
What the hell is this?
yellow
square
Okay, this is a the shapes don't match up. So this is a yellow interior
It's what that does not match up though
All right. Good luck trying to figure out the rest of this shit. It's not fucking hard
It's not hard
Jerma, it's called a pattern. I just got to recognize it and figure it out
And it's not even really a pattern because look at this like these shapes are not even in the right order here
This should be a square. This is not this is completely different in each row. So sit down relax
Hey, sit down. It's going diagonally. You spoken crack. All right, so let's drive red
Let's see where this goes
Okay
Red so I need red exterior
square
Is here with a blue interior circle
I do blue interior. What does it go? Where does this go? Is it going to be?
All right. So this is this matches so it does match
I didn't know if it was going to be scrambled in every single one of these quadrants. Okay, so go diagonal
So this is a no no, this is not I do this
the red exterior
shit
A red triangle then
Okay, so red triangle will do that
Can I have the controller you can download the game?
I'm sorry. I'm already out of juice. I might accidentally get like two of these. Let's see
So I don't know what the leftmost thing is. Okay, so hold on. What is that? I have not figured that out
What is this one? I have not figured that out. This is a square. So this is a square. It is a
Interior blue square and the color is we don't have any idea
green
What is here?
It has to be
You don't have any mud left. No
Okay, so green exterior
No, I want to do
Circle what color inside red?
Yep, i'm out of juice. I stopped paying attention to the puzzle. I feel so lost
Is there another shot left? I'm able to get the last at least two people. I got one shot left
All right, so this is either yellow or pink. Oh, no, I lose
Okay
Check this one out on hard
We're going on tour, but thanks to you good luck. This place has grown can't drop down right now
But a half it's better than having none. Okay, I don't I don't even I don't know what they want me to do
But i'm gonna just put people in places
This shouldn't even be that hard. What about noses? But can't I just put everybody in an individual room?
There are more doors than zumbinis. They have to go in a specific spot green noses the door pattern
mmm door pattern and the floor pattern so that would be
Uh to make me cry if I was playing this by myself. I don't I just genuinely don't really know
And I I already lost right springs. Um, well at least one person survived
Somebody said this one feels legit impossible. I don't think it is. I think but maybe it is
I don't know. Let's do the fleeing one. Let's see how much different difficult this one is
Because how much harder could you possibly make this one?
It might be opposites
All right, so let's just go by what we know the hair is all this stuff is wrong
None of this matches. Let's just put another random person that it has nothing in common with you. Okay
Do the glasses match?
Pink nose. Okay. Hold on. So red nose is purple nose. Maybe red nose and glasses. Do I have one?
I don't have a red nose and glasses
What the hell is this criteria spring is high heel bike is also high heel
Yellow nose is also purple nose as well as red nose. What about you? No you
Okay, it's the hat one two three hats left. Are there three of these hairs left one two
Three there is all right
Um, the glasses are the feet. Oh, that's true
so glass so eyes are feet so that means that
Hurts my head eyes are this so cyclops. I will just see what this does
No
Okay. Well eyes
So this is a a cyclops. There's only one cyclops left. It has to be this one
Right. I think so
Yep, his feet hair
Noses eyes eyes his feet hair his nose
Noses eyes
What is hair?
Beat his hair. So it's one of these four. Okay, so feet is
So it's not this one. Wait, maybe it is this one. It's this one, right?
Oh fuck
Yeah, it's that one okay and then it's this one
All right. Well, okay. That was hard
Cool. What else do we try very very hard?
What is this one on very hard?
Uh, it doesn't tell you you just have to figure it out. All right, let's start with you
now
How about um spring?
What about uh yellow nose and spring?
It's probably hair
I think it's hair
It's not hair
Is it eyes?
It's not eyes
Is it noses?
What is it? Is it feet? I think it is feet
Whoa, what?
What do you mean? Wait, wait, what why did that not happen? What is going on? Oh, they're all locked
Blue should wait hold because this sorting by multiple traits at once or by feet then eyes, etc. Okay, that's hard
What about this one? Wait, what?
Okay
What are we doing? Uh
Huh
They're changing so I have to match this one. I can I have to so I need a spring
No, I want this to be a spring
How do I get that to be a spring pass through the ice that matches them? I have to match in the middle
What the fuck? Okay. Um
Dude, i'm not doing this one. I don't care
It's too much
Uh, what about this one?
Yikes, no fucking way
Not a chance i'm doing this one. I'll give it a real try but no I can't I can't even look at it
Huh? This is not wait. They all have to be connected. I can't do it. What about this one?
This one might not be that bad
Okay, so they have to share
They have to share a trait with
Somebody that in adjacent to them, right? So you have to go here. This is gonna be a nightmare, but i'll try
Oh, you got it. They have to share some kind of trait. What's wrong the shoes the shoes match
There's a page on making an algorithm to solve this specific puzzle on zoom beanies. By the way, what?
Dude, how about this?
Try to do one for 30 minutes and we'll gamble that's a long time 30 minutes sub only
30 minutes that's
That sounds boring. That sounds really boring
That's like a third that's like 20 of this whole stream so far making an hour. No, that'd be horrible
How about 10 minutes 15 minutes 15 minutes? Can I complete this in 15 minutes what i'm looking at right now?
I'm getting bored 15 minutes the deal do one that you're at least comfortable with
I think I could do that one. It's gonna be kind of hard but I could do it
So this one again is if they have to share a trait with whoever's adjacent to them
Yeah, put it in emote only 15 minutes. You got it. I'll try you'd better beat it
I'm I can't tell you that's gonna happen in five minutes
I might realize I can't do this and get up and go get like a snack
Just be aware of what you're betting on here
This is very very hard zumbini's logical journey this shit is not for kids kids can't do this
This is not even for adults computers have problems doing this they made an algorithm to try to beat this game on very very hard
And that even struggled so just make sure you understand what you're betting on. All right, ready and go 15 minutes
All right, let's go
Looking
What do I have the most of this hair there you go, you got it
What's the matter, uh
Why not
He just drowned that person why not is it only based on hair
Hold on nose. Wait
It's got to match everybody so I need
Oh fuck
You cannot help me with emotes it's not gonna work this isn't breath of the wild
Nope, what do you mean? No, why not glasses shoot? What what?
All this dickhead down here
I screwed up so bad. I need to go buy feet and hair and nose
And eyes, this is impossible. There you go. You got i'm going i'm going
Uh, how much time do I have left? It's been five minutes already. What?
All right, i'm gonna lock in I have so many of these pink shoes
I don't know what to do with them eyes and hair eyes and hair eyes and hair hair and eyes and nose
Okay eyes
nose
hair, okay eyes
hair
eyes
Oh
This is close. Okay, if I move the one to the left and switch it with somebody with shoes, hold on
Why no I can I can I can yes I can
It's so close and I just I need to move like one person
Uh
Who needs to move to make this right pointing at me outy. What does that mean?
You trying to tell me something sunglasses down hair left eyes up. Wait if I
Gg gg gg not yet. There you go. You got it. What why?
No, what are you talking about? What? Oh, i'm very confused right now. Explain this pink shoes pink shoes to the left
Uh the eyes that are kind of half closed down eyes that are half closed
Oh the person on the right. Yeah, there's only two. Come on. I can do it. No, I wanted to put you there
Time seven minutes. There you go. You got it. Shit
I need to rethink this
It's just like it's like four distinct different variables to be aware of i'm so close, but i'm so far away
For the two of you why?
I can't do it. I can't do it. It's just it's so tricky
It's a lot of it's a lot of ifs thens or buts and then there's a lot of moving. It's huh
I got five minutes. Hold on. I didn't put any springs down. Oh
Not this one
But wait, no it
I think I lose. Sorry everybody. I was like I can do it green nose green nose. Wait, hold on
Green green green
and then
No, and then no, I need a different nose. I need a different nose to go here. We're in a different nose
Our computer had prob they made a computer program and it didn't do it. This is so hard
Everybody has to have something in common with everybody next to them and it's just like hurting my head
Nope, no, but it's always always a problem
It's a it's always a problem see because like there's always somebody that doesn't match there. You got it. It's always a problem
Okay, hold on there. You got it
I think it was a it was a good attempt. It was a pretty good attempt. I think it's over though
I think this is far too difficult. It's not over yet. Hold on. No
Shit, i'm not happy right now. I'm very unhappy. No, what do you mean? No?
30 seconds
Nope, can't do that. I lose it. It's over. I just end it. I lose it's over. I can't do it
I can't do it
It's over. I I can't do it and it
It's I just can't do it
Let him out let him out of emote only I came kind of close but not really it's like a rubik's cube
Where somebody's probably just like oh dude, it's so easy
Just put the green guy over there and then put the fucking purple guy right here and put the blue guy over here
It's so simple
Hard sorry everybody you fucked me bro. I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you already
Can I do the pizza one? I'm very very hard
Bet on me. This is my game. This is my game. This is my game right here
Another bet 10 minutes. This is my game
I did it before you watched me do it before
How could you make it up to my grandma? Huh? She went all in she has nothing now your grandmother
Probably has like 12 channel points on this stream
She probably opened it was checking in to see what her grandson or granddaughter was up to
And closed it in five minutes. So
Okay, we ready
Have faith in me with the pizza mini game
I'm telling you you I just did it on very very very very very very very very very very very very very very hard already
I got it. I got it. Why do you play puzzle games on stream? You don't like it chat doesn't like it
I don't like it. Can you just go back to playing ass fart simulator? I mean, I like it. I think one of my favorite games
I love how you're separated from that. You don't like it chat doesn't like it. I don't like it
Aren't you a part of chat? How come you're separating yourself from chat? You're in chat
You know, you don't like it. I love this. I love this pizza game. All right, we ready
I hope you bet on me because i'm gonna make you a lot of channel points if you did in three
Two one go
Good toppings are distasteful where it doesn't matter
That's fine. We already know we're going for the uh, we're going for the trunk right here. Okay trunk
Very much would have been happy about this does not want
jalapenos jalapenos, I know how to say it. Why did I just say it weirdly? Let's go like this
No cheese got it. There's something there. I'll remake it. I'll remake it
I'll give you a refund. Just give it back
So you don't want cheese you don't want peppers. Do you want pineapple?
Those of you that have just lost a shitload of channel points, I just want to say
How could you have possibly bet against me in my favorite mini game in my favorite game of all time?
I'm just shocked really I am
Okay
What about just sprinkles?
Something on that's not good for me
Okay, well i'm gonna do something here that it might be a little unorthodox and it was because I didn't even look
Yeah, that's really unorthodox to a point where it was completely wrong
I just didn't even look over there. Okay
Nobody wants cheese. I'd appreciate more toppings good
There's something on that. I don't want time check. What do I got seven and a half minutes?
Uh and pepperoni
There's something there. I won't eat you don't want pepperoni
There's something on that. I don't want she might actually like pineapple because the cherry was there so he wanted it. I'll try that
No, okay
um
so you want
That one you want pepperoni sprinkles and jalapenos
What no, wait, what's going on?
Something's wrong pepperoni. What's happening pepperoni?
What doesn't want pineapple doesn't want mushrooms doesn't want jalapenos. What the hell do you want chocolate syrup?
Is it cheese?
I thought everybody didn't want cheese. Oh, it's because that one has a
Fucking cherry on it
What?
There's something on that. I don't want what it's mushrooms. Oh my god. What am I doing? It's mushrooms. It's mushrooms
Okay, I got it. I got it. It's mushrooms. It's literally mushrooms game over. I win
What toppings are?
Wait, what's happening?
What's going on?
I thought she liked mushrooms, which does she not like pepperoni? Was I not paying attention?
What happened? No. No, i'm serious. What happened? I thought she liked the pepperonis. She liked the mushrooms
I'm very confused right now. What did I just do to what happened? I just like blacked out for five seconds
I did she not want pepperoni. Why did what's going on? I just lost track of everything because look at all this shit
What happened? I got five minutes. I have to just start from scratch here. Okay, let's um, she likes mushrooms
Mushrooms and pepperoni just do it again. Just do it again. I fucked it up. Oh my god. What's happening actually fucking being stupid
Okay, she doesn't want pepperoni. Why did I think she wanted pepperoni? Why did I think she wanted pepperoni who why?
I don't even remember what made me think that what made me think she wanted pepperoni on this
Nobody nobody it's cheese
I got it. We're good
What the fuck are you talking about?
How did I just black out the last like two minutes, I don't even know what happened
Oh shit. Okay. So what do you?
On your pizza
Is it no you don't want pineapple? Maybe it is pineapple because there was
That topping no, it's not pineapple
There's something on that. I don't want dude
I can't even read the chat and i've and I like I looked over here and forgot the whole game
I'm gonna get it right now. I'm not looking over at chat. I looked over at chat and I forgot the entire game
I like was like, oh, what are they doing over here? Oh interesting and I look back over and i'm like I forget the entire experience
All right. I'm not looking at chat ever again. What do you want?
You want this shit and you want jalapenos on it, too? That's a guarantee
Hmm little pizza makers good. Okay, let's go. Let's go. I got four minutes. I'm good. I have three minutes
What is this? What do you want? You don't like anything? This guy doesn't like anything. Let's just do um
This like more toppings, please. All right, good start
You don't want jalapenos. How about um, how about uh, uh
I gotta start from scratch. This is gonna be it
No, no cheese. All right, so we know no cheese
No cheese
What about just mushrooms?
Okay. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. No cheese. No mushrooms. What about just pepperoni? We're gonna get it
What's the time time? That's time. That's time. That's time. That's time. That's time. That's time
That's time how much time was left 150 seconds left. We got it. I completely forgot her entire order
Jesus
Don't have a bet against me and pizza maker
Have we not seen one on very very hard?
We haven't done this one here we go again
More of those little pebbles
And you can let them out. We don't need to bet any again. We don't have to bet again
Anymore I made all your money back
As it knows
You do not okay, maybe hair
What about hair? Let's try hair. What the actual hell did I just tune into the logical journey of the zoom beanies?
This way
Go ahead
Do go in
It was the easiest money of my life. Uh, can I go this way? Are you okay with me coming up? No, you're not
We must be selective about our clientele
So why can you go here but you can't what's the difference? Is it eyes? It has to be nose, right?
Yellow nose this way. No
Yellow nose this way
Has to be noses for the top bro
Okay
really
So this one must be eye no
hair
I have no idea
I guess we just figured it out
Uh, let's try that then
Okay
I think this is correct. No, it's not
Spring probably has to go up this way
Red nose over here. No red nose this way red nose this way. No. Oh, sorry
this way
A blue nose with this hair going this way. Nope, that's wrong. Enjoy yourself
That's correct pink and then there's there no green noses where the green noses go probably up around
All right, let's see happen. Do you want to see what happens when you lose? It's pretty bad
Ready? Why is it not happening?
Can you lose on practice? Oh, yes, you can. Yeah you can
Can't let you in this whole place is gonna fucking cave in
They're very forgiving on this level unlike every other level in the game on hard
Why do I remember this being way more morbid? I thought the whole thing caved in
All right, that's probably it. That was fun. Any encores you'd like to see before we stop any encores do the lion room
Do pizza again paint wall again. Let me do paint wall on the on the very hard. Not very very hard
Okay, that's very weird. I don't know why they'd be this far away from each other
How would these two be this far away? They have the same hair. They have the same feet. Okay blue pink blue
pink blue
I don't know pink pink
blue pink blue
Pink blue
blue
Blue pink blue blue blue pink pink
pink green
Green
No
It's the eyes. Yeah, I know but but who goes where because I can't just put this guy right here the hair and the eyes
Eyes, then feet so it would be that
Okay
Um, i'm gonna imagine it's this and then this and then
This but what how do I determine this then like this?
Very very very hard. Very very very hard. This one is not on very very very hard. All right. Good got it
Interior blue
Exterior blue diamond. Why did I just do that twice? I need to go eat a fucking jar of peanut butter
I thought that was wait. I'm confusing myself. Here it is. I had to mute you dude. Sorry. You're annoying
I had to mute. What are you doing here?
Okay, how about that?
Nope a jar one of the whole jar a like a few spoonfuls. All right, so this is blue
red
Let's just try pink
No, okay. What about yellow?
Got it yellow with a diamond
interior
circle interior
Why peanut butter protein protein good fats?
Okay, so we need to find a different
interior
Okay
Red interiors. I need red interior triangle
yellow
This is green
exterior
Red interior triangle, okay
so
yellow interior
square
green
exterior pink
Interior there's only two places it could be pink interior or green interior. We're gonna do pink interior which hopefully is over here
pink exterior
square
right
Ah
It's right here. Do I have enough shots to do one more? No, there's no more mud. Damn it. It's all right
It's okay. Do it again. All right one more time that one. This one's fun
This time I don't want to waste that much. Let's go
All right. So what does that mean? Let's try a different one. Let's try like just like circle
Okay
Shit okay, this is gonna be weird. So this is yellow
diamond
so this would be
God, I don't know. It's all green exterior in here
When the interior is in the same area like this, it's kind of hard. I'm gonna say red. No blue interior and
star
Nope pink interior
square
Good. All right. We're gonna go red exterior
pink interior square
I'm hoping it's this one right here. We're gonna do blue exterior red pink interior square
So what is all what would be all the way to the right circle? Right? No star. No square. No triangle yellow interior
Is a his here blue exterior is here. It'll be triangle. Okay
blue exterior
green interior
Triangle I am so
brilliant at this
Okay, I think i'll get it this time yellow exterior
We're hoping it's this one yellow exterior
square
pink
Ah
What no I fucked it up yellow exterior blue interior there it is
I have two more shots in here for sure
pink exterior
What's in the middle star?
and
yellow interior
Oh, no, no, no, it's the third slot. What's the third slot trying diamond? I got one more shot. I'm good
Let's go get it right. All right
I got one more shot. This is triangle with a pink exterior
And a blue interior think that's correct. All right, I got it
I got it earlier in the stream. You said you don't know mountain rescue, but you literally streamed it
I know but here's the thing dude
I've played like I've played like two or three thousand video games over the last 12 years doing this
I I don't remember all of them. I just really don't I just don't remember
some some of them like
Like seven or eight nine years ago
I don't I don't have the capacity to remember every single video game
I played five to ten years ago, like if you put it in front of me, I'd be like, oh, okay, right
All right, but there's been
Millions of pieces of information have gone through here over the last 15 years. I win. All right, and that's it
I'm just trying to get one across
It sounds like a lincoln park sound it kind of does hey one survived. All right, these are impossible
All right, that's gonna be it. That's all the plan was today. Let's play this for a little while
Look at how much easier this is one easy
Okay, you guys ready? I literally thought the perfect game you should play it's called you're in the movies. I played that already
So here's the thing. What is
What is a good game that I can play? I have a couple of options here
I'm not talking about today talking about the next time I stream. I've really been playing this for five hours
It was fun. Maybe we'll do like a grab bag stream
next stream
Yeah, so s3 is still on the 24th because we we got through the things I wanted to get through
I wanted to play zoom beanies. We did that. I wanted to
Play katamari and finish it. We did that do the lies of p demo. I'll probably just wait for the full game
I'm imagining the lies of p demo is the tutorial zone and the tutorial boss and then that's it
I'll just wait till it's up. Maybe we'll do a grab bag on
Monday. I'll see you guys on monday next stream do more infomercials
Maybe a reverse delay maybe a reverse delay in the future
It's possible. I just stream on sunday
But let's plan for monday and then maybe i'll show up on sunday. We'll see keep an eye on the sus
It might change it definitely won't be later than monday, but it could be sunday. It won't be it's not gonna be tuesday
It's not gonna be tuesday. It's gonna be
At some point as at some point as of monday there will be a stream sunday or monday, but that is the end
Have a great night. See you guys later. See you on monday or sunday. He's gonna delay till wednesday. No, I will not
I will not delay till wednesday
Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for hanging out. That was zoom. It's on steam zoom beanies is on steam if you feel like playing it
It was a good time. Thanks for hanging out. See you guys on
monday or so
Somebody said nah, i'm good
That is so much more. All right, they're like nah, i'm good
It's so much worse than no than just saying no, don't you think so?
Saying i'm good means you've really thought about it and we're like, nah, nah fucking i'm i'm good. I'm good
That would make it bad. I'm good over here to me. That's more insulting than just saying no like oh
You're gonna be there on monday?
No. Oh, okay. Cool. Hey, you're gonna be there on monday. No, i'm good because to me i'm good means
I thought about it and the answer is no no means there could be something else going on that you're missing the stream for
You got homework. You got friends are coming over. You got some stuff to do
You don't feel like watching twitch that you know, it could be it could mean anything. I'm good means you've already thought about it
Banned that person for life by the way. All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching. See you on monday
Goodbye. Good night. Call your mother. See you soon. Take care of yourselves
Overthinking andy i'm i'm kidding. Don't worry. Well, the credits are over
Oops
All right. Good night guys. See you later. Have a good one
Also, I want to talk quietly in case anyone was
I'm still here
I'm waiting till it's exactly five hours of stream time
Because I can't 459
Is is just killing me here has to be five
And it has to be that's gonna drive me crazy
All right. See you later