Okay, I am back. Hello. How are you? Good to see you.
Yeah, before we get started before we like kind of continue though. I um, you know, I'm thinking about retiring.
No, I'm getting older. So I'm just thinking about. I'm thinking about retiring.
I'm thinking about retiring.
No, I'm getting older.
You know, I mean.
Oh shit, I have to gift subs. I can't though. I don't have it. My money won't go through to Twitch.
I didn't say how many I'll give you. I'll give you an extra ten. Okay, that'll be a hundred and ten.
I was making a joke. It's like I talk about this shit all the time and I'm just a fucking like, alright.
No, I'm not gonna talk about retiring anymore.
I'll give you ten. I'll give you ten.
I can't even fucking connect my Twitch to my fucking payment stuff.
Just real debt. Add it to the tab.
Alright, let's do AI dungeon. Isn't that gonna be fun guys?
Maybe I should get some music for this.
Like epic royalty free music.
I don't know how it works, right?
Yeah, I'll get some epic royalty free music.
Uh, royalty free scary.
Okay. This one sounds promising.
One hour of royalty free horror music.
Do a clash of clans.
Well, this is just to have the background sounds for when we do our adventure.
Epic royalty free music.
This is uh, okay, this is called fire and thunder.
What does this one sound like?
I like it.
It's not bad.
Okay.
We need a, like, just generic general medieval music.
Okay, this is um, fantasy medieval music, instrumental, no copyright.
Okay.
So, apparently, AI dungeon is a lot different now, I guess.
Right?
I don't know exactly what that means, but I know that apparently it's been, it's changed.
Now, I don't know exactly what that means, but I'm gonna try to figure out what it means.
I have premium on AI dungeon, and I have premium on novel AI as well.
I'm gonna do face cam finally.
I'll put it on for a few minutes.
Go ahead and do this.
Close that.
I need to put some lip balm on, though.
I gotta change the, uh, we aren't flipping, we are building.
I guess that could make sense in AI dungeon.
Okay.
Looks good.
Move this.
I have, like, the Voyager thing.
I don't think that really matters, though.
Okay, so this is, this is what I remember.
Move the screen around for you.
Can you see it?
Not yet.
I got a clue.
Like, this is still open.
Okay.
Make sure you can see the chat window.
Important.
Make it a little bigger so you can read it better.
So, what do we want to do?
Where do we want to go?
What setting do we want?
Fantasy, mystery, apocalyptic.
We can make, just make up one on our own, too, right?
Where should I be?
Oh, I gotta turn my ring light on!
I can't be sitting here like this.
Oh, okay, let's do, let's do, uh, apocalyptic.
Oh, a nice warm light.
With a coffee.
That's better.
There.
Although, why am I so frame-ready?
I'm too, like, I'm too, I look weird.
Why?
Why does it, why do I look weird?
I look even weirder.
I'm, why is it so frame-ready?
You guys see what I'm talking about?
I shouldn't, there we go.
That was weird.
Now I don't look like I'm red.
Too much lip balm?
Alright, you don't need to see the Reddit shelf anymore.
I look a little disheveled, don't I?
Alright.
Here we go.
So, what music should I have on?
I got my coffee right here!
I told you I was gonna make one.
Ah, harsh noises.
Where?
Alright, what should, let's go.
Uh, it's been a while.
Let's go ahead and do, let's do apocalyptic.
So, we'll do four.
Do I have to click it or just say it?
What do I do, nothing?
Okay.
What character do I want to be?
How about a, um, what character?
I don't know.
What would you guys want to see?
How about just, like, a survivor?
Survivor sounds good.
Your character's name.
Let's get some good music here.
Gotta make sure this just sounds good.
This doesn't make much sense for where we are, but whatever.
I gotta make sure my voice changer works, too,
for, like, the monsters and demons and everything.
Hello.
Hello!
Oh, hello there, traveler.
Yeah, okay, if that sounds okay.
Ed, Edgwood.
Edgwood.
Okay, here we go.
Ahem, ahem.
You...
Wait, this pictures now?
This is one of their photos.
Okay.
You are Edgwood.
A survivor trying to survive in a post-apocalyptic world
by scavenging among the ruins of what is left.
You have a backpack and a canteen.
You haven't eaten in two days,
so you're desperately searching for food.
You enter a run-down building and...
find it occupied by a man and his two children.
They lit a fire in the fireplace to keep themselves warm.
You can see a sack of potatoes on a shelf
and a closed tin of peaches in the fridge.
As you reach to grab the peaches,
you catch a glimpse of movement out of the corner of your eye.
Don't move, the man says.
Did I just, like, break into this person's house?
What happens now?
Okay, so from what I remember, you have to, like...
Do, okay.
Do, what do you say, what happens next?
So what do I do?
Take the peaches out of the fridge.
Does that ma- Is that okay?
That's okay, right?
You take the peaches out of the fridge.
Training the AI, please tap on the response
you'd like to keep or hit undo.
I've got the peaches, you say in a cheery tone.
Oh, thank you, thank you so much.
My wife and I have been eating those for two days
and she's got nothing left.
No worries, I'm just passing through.
Don't try and stop me.
There's a lot of zombies out there.
Or you quickly put the peaches back into the original sack.
That done you turn to leave, the man is suddenly on you.
Where'd you get those peaches, he asks.
Why, are they gonna hurt me?
No, but I'm going to.
Keep them.
The man then draws a gun and points it at you.
We're gonna go with this one.
Why did I make this decision?
I don't know, it's, it's funnier?
Okay, the man draws a gun and points it at you.
I'm gonna say, you would shoot me in front of your children?
You would shoot me in front of your children?
Turn that feature off, yeah, I will.
I might, you wouldn't, try me.
Fine, I won't shoot you.
Good, now put the gun down.
He does so, you slowly approach him,
still not taking your eyes off of him.
You're only a few feet away now.
Keep a lookout, you whisper.
I know.
So the gun has legs.
Who is this person?
I grab the gun out of his hands.
Grab the gun out of his hands?
You grab the gun out of his hands and turn to leave.
Where are you going, he asks.
I'm getting somewhere safe.
But I thought you, oh, never mind, it doesn't matter.
He then picks up the gun again and points it at you.
I took it from him, that doesn't make any sense.
He got that from somewhere else.
Point my gun at him.
You point your gun at him.
Don't you shoot, he says.
I won't if you don't.
You're a good boy.
You'll get your fill of good food and nice warm beds.
I hope so.
Now get out of here.
I've got a business to run after this is all over.
Bye.
Shoot into the ceiling.
You shoot the man in the head with your gun.
He slumps down.
You quickly look around and make sure his children have not seen you or heard this.
They haven't.
You then leave the room.
You exit the rundown building and find yourself in a street full of overturned vehicles and debris.
You see the man with the two children coming down the street.
Um, I wanted to like be like, boom, like, see you later.
I'm not pointing my gun.
Exit the rundown building and find yourself in a street full of overturned vehicles and debris.
What should I do?
This is a post-apocalyptic.
Okay.
Run towards the zombies.
I'll lose him in the zombies.
You run towards the zombies as fast as you can.
You are worried about being seen by the man with the gun.
You're also worried about the safety of the peaches.
Because, heaven forbid, something happens to those.
You continue moving towards the zombies when the man with the gun fires and the bullet hits the zombie in the chest.
You hear a satisfying crack as the zombie collapses to the ground.
You keep running.
Protect the peaches.
You protect the peaches.
You grab the peaches and tuck them into your bag.
Don't shoot, you yell, as you continue running towards the man.
No, I want to run that way.
I didn't shoot.
The gun went off by itself.
I was just reaching for the bullets to stop the bleeding.
Shut up, you say as you run.
You need to get off the street.
This is stupid.
Eat the peaches in front of the man.
This AI imaging is just so fucked up.
You bite into a peach and you find yourself in a world of flavor and sunshine.
You smile from ear to ear.
You should have shot the bastards, the man says as he picks up another peach.
I can't shoot straight, you say.
That's what you get for eating garbage, he says.
What the fuck is happening in this story?
I'll say.
Do you want to join forces?
We could work together.
Fight zombies.
Ashley is pretty accurate though.
We weren't supposed to talk to each other, he says.
We are not supposed to be here in the first place, you yell.
You're right.
Let's work together.
You decide to work together.
The man pulls out a canteen of water and gives you some.
Break the entire canteen.
Please verify your email address.
What?
What do you mean verify my, I already did all this.
I already verified my email.
Hold on.
What do you mean, verify my email address?
That's part of the story?
Try the other one.
Should I try novel AI instead?
I already did verify my email, that's fucked up.
I'll try the other one.
Is it that much different?
Okay, text adventure.
Should I do this one?
Which one should I do?
Tall streamer at hotmail.
All right, I'll do text adventure.
All right, what do you, let's just, I guess we can just do this one.
AI dungeon lost the rights to use open AI so they had to make a new AI and it's just not as good as that.
Really?
Well, I got a change that says I'm playing.
Does it have a thing on Twitch?
It does, okay.
Okay.
Well, we'll just do this one.
There's other stuff on that AI dungeon website though that looked interesting.
Okay, so let's get started here.
All right, new track.
What would you like to do?
Story.
Okay, let's start a story.
You are lost in the woods.
Your name is, you are lost in the woods.
Your name is Edward III.
Your father is Edward the Great.
And he has sent you into the woods to claim a relic that has been lost for over 200 centuries.
Is that long?
Edgeworth?
What's Edgeworth?
Edward.
This is a run-on sentence.
The AI doesn't care about run-on sentences.
You have a rusty knife and a trusty sword.
Begin.
As you walk deeper into the woods, you see an old man sitting on a rock.
He looks like he's sleeping.
You approach him cautiously.
But as you get closer, he suddenly sits up, staring at you with bloodshot eyes.
That's 20,000 years.
Are you serious?
Say.
Dear old man, I'm looking for a relic that has been lost time.
Dear old man, I'm looking for a relic that's been lost time.
The old man laughs.
That's exactly what I am.
I am the relic master of the forest, and I know every relic in this forest by heart.
What do you want from me?
Holy shit.
Do you know where the heart of Edward is?
He laughs again.
Of course I do.
It's right here in my pocket.
But before you can grab it, he vanishes.
You're standing near a dead tree.
There's a large hole in the ground nearby and a wooden stake sticking out of the ground.
I shouldn't have said that.
Lie down in the hole.
On my back.
A moment later, you hear a strange sound coming from below you.
As you look down, you see the old man sitting on the ground, smiling at you.
Hello there, he says.
Wait, am I on top of him?
He's lying down on the ground too?
Wildcard, type only a question mark to ask and wonder.
Okay, that's...
Where did you go?
How did you disappear so quickly?
Oh, that was just a little trick I learned when I was young.
I can disappear and appear at will.
Can you teach me, old man?
Sure, he says.
Come on down and we'll have some fun.
You descend into the hole, which seems to be a small cave.
The old man follows you in.
I gotta be very cautious.
Keep my hands on my knife, on my sword, while we walk into the cave.
As soon as you enter the cave, the old man grabs his pocket watch and starts ticking loudly.
Suddenly a huge creature bursts...
Suddenly a huge creature bursts out of the ground behind you.
It looks like a cross between a bull and a bear.
Watch out!
It turns around and sees the old man.
It snarls and charges at him.
The old man jumps out of the way just in time and the creature falls on its side, stunned.
Kill it!
You leap forward and swing your sword at the beast, cutting off one of its legs.
It howls in pain and lunges at you.
You dodge the attack and stab it in the eye with your sword.
Old man!
Grab me the holy water from my backpack!
You run back towards the old man who is still holding the pocket watch in his hand.
He takes it out of his pocket and flicks it open.
Suddenly he screams and drops the watch.
Pick up the watch.
You pick up the watch.
The watch is cracked and covered in dirt, but inside you can see a tiny fragment of white bone.
You take the watch out of the pocket and put it back in your bag.
What does this watch do?
Nothing special, the old man says.
Just a good luck charm.
You leave the cave and head deeper into the woods.
You are now in the clearing where you found the relic.
Okay.
Why did he scream?
Why did you scream after opening the pocket of the watch?
Oh, that's just something that happens sometimes, the old man says.
It's not important.
Just don't open it again, okay?
You are standing in a clearing to the west of the small hill.
If I open this pocket watch, what will happen?
Don't open it again.
And make sure you never tell anybody about this place.
You reach into your bag and pull out a small metal box.
It is engraved with strange symbols.
Open the pocket watch.
Suddenly the old man disappears.
You feel yourself falling through the air and then everything goes black.
You are lying on the ground with the old man kneeling beside you.
He's holding a flask of water.
Where are we?
We're in the forest, he replies.
I had to bring you here because I couldn't find any other way to contact you.
Why?
Because if anyone else finds out about this place, they might try to come here.
How nice is it?
It's a time machine.
What year is it?
It's 1827, he replies.
How long have I been unconscious?
About two weeks.
You sit up.
Thank you for saving me, old man.
Open the pocket watch.
This might be the relic.
This is the relic.
The old man screams and drops the watch.
You open the watch and see a piece of white bone.
You close the watch and put it back in your bag.
You stand up and walk over to the old man.
Am I in the cave?
Is that the relic?
Yes, he says.
That is the relic.
You take the relic from him and put it in your bag.
Now let's get out of here.
So that's the heart of Edward's heart.
That's the heart of Edward.
They leave it.
Heart?
Edward is in my hands.
Father will be most pleased.
No!
The old man shouts.
This is evil.
We must destroy it.
But why?
I've been searching for this for years.
Because it's evil.
What makes it evil?
It's cursed.
He replies.
If you open it, it will take away all of your memories.
And then you won't remember anything.
You hold the relic in both hands.
Open it.
Suddenly you are standing in a dark room.
You are holding a glowing blue orb.
You look around the room and notice that the walls are covered in strange writing.
You read.
The first man, Adam, created in the image of God, was alone in the Garden of Eden.
Keep reading.
Until Eve, the second woman, was brought forth from his rib, Adam gave her to his son Cain.
Adam gave her to his son Cain as a wife?
Cain slew his brother Abel and fled from the Garden of Eden.
Then Enoch, the third man, walked with God and was taken up to heaven without dying.
Enoch returned to earth and told his people that the world would end.
After many years, the Great Flood destroyed the world and Noah built an ark to save his
family from the waters.
The ark floated for 40 days and nights until it reached dry land.
Keep reading.
The ark landed on Mount Ararat in Turkey.
God commanded Noah to build a tower to reach heaven.
Noah obeyed and constructed the Tower of Babel, the first human structure ever made.
Is this all real?
Does this happen?
Keep reading.
But Satan, the god of this world, the hunters, were becoming too powerful and tried to destroy
them.
So he caused them to speak different languages, and they began to fight amongst themselves.
Keep reading.
God scattered the humans and scattered their language.
When Moses led the Hebrew slaves out of Egypt, he was given the Ten Commandments.
Moses returned to Israel and built the Tabernacle, the first temple in Jerusalem.
King Solomon built the first temple, and the Ark of the Covenant was placed in it.
Solomon also built the second temple, which stood until the Romans destroyed it in 70a.
I wonder where Satan was at this point.
Satan was banished from heaven and cast down to hell.
In the last days, Satan will return to earth, and the Antichrist will reign over the world.
The Bible is a book of prophecy.
Keep reading.
The Antichrist will be a false prophet who will rise to power in the Middle East.
His name is Muhammad, and he will rule the world.
At the end of his reign, Jesus Christ will return to earth and defeat the Antichrist.
What?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Jesus will establish his kingdom on earth and rule as king of kings for a thousand years.
After that, Satan will be released from prison and tempt...
What is happening here?
Say, this doesn't sound accurate.
It is true that the Antichrist will rise.
He will be defeated by Jesus.
Also, the Antichrist will not be the only false prophet.
There will be others.
I don't think this is what happened.
Who is talking right now?
It's me, the old man says.
I'm telling you what happened.
You continue reading.
Aren't I reading this off of a wall?
After the a thousand years are up, Satan will be released from his prison and will deceive mankind once more.
Keep reading.
No, I don't want him to keep reading.
I'm telling him to keep reading.
Hey, I'll go. Keep reading.
This time, he will be able to use the powers of a fallen angel called the Beast.
The Beast will rule the world for seven years before being defeated by Jesus.
When Satan is imprisoned again, the devil will be chained for a thousand years.
Is Thor in this?
Yes, the old man says.
He is mentioned several times in the Bible.
You continue reading.
At the end of the millennium, Satan will be loosed once more and will tempt mankind to rebel against God.
Can you skip to the part with Elmo?
No, the old man says. There isn't much left.
During the rebellion, the Antichrist will be killed by the archangel Michael.
Michael will be rewarded for his bravery and become the leader of the angels.
Is Elmo in this?
No, the old man says. He does not appear in the Bible at all.
Oh, okay. Phew.
Elmo is not in the Bible.
What about Kermit the Frog?
Kermit the Frog is not mentioned in the Bible.
You continue reading.
Okay, please, please finish the story.
After that, Satan will be chained for a thousand years.
Alright, he's stuck.
Grab the book out of his hands.
I am finished, the old man says. You can stop reading now.
You take the book out of his hands and put it back in your bag.
Wait, what about Elmo?
You're now standing in the clearing where you found the relic.
You're standing in the clearing where you found the relic. To the west is a small hill.
To the east is a path leading north into the forest.
Okay.
Yell, where is Elmo?
My god.
You shout, where is Elmo?
Suddenly, the old man appears.
Where is Elmo, you ask?
He's gone. I sent him away.
You reach into your bag and pull out the pocket watch.
Fuck this Elmo-less timeline.
I'm out of here.
Suddenly, you're standing in a dark room. You're holding a glowing blue orb.
You look around the room and notice that the walls are covered in strange writing.
You read.
The first man, Adam, created in the image of God, was alone in the Garden of Eden.
Read the part about Elmo.
Until Eve. Come on.
You can't give me like, Elmo is like Eve or something.
The book of Elmo.
Run out of the cave.
You run out of the cave.
You're now standing in the clearing where you found the relic.
To the west is a small hill.
Head towards the hill.
You climb the hill and are standing at the top.
To the north is a path leading south into the forest.
To the east is a path leading south into the forest.
To the east is a path leading north into the forest.
And to the west is a path leading north into the forest.
Ask the old man where to go.
We need to find the relic. It is buried under the hill.
You ask the old man where to go.
We need to find the relic.
We've time traveled.
Explain to the old man.
How do I say this?
Explain to the old man. You explain to the old man time travel.
Time travel is impossible, he says.
Only God can do that.
That makes me God then.
That makes you God?
You ask the old man where to go.
We need to find the relic. It's buried under the hill.
That makes me God then, you reply.
Why?
Because I am the one who sent you back in time, he says.
We need to find the relic.
We're combining like three or four realities.
Dig under the hill for the relic.
Are we gonna find two of them?
You dig under the hill for the relic.
We need to find the relic.
Find the relic.
We're in a loop.
You find the relic.
We need to find the relic.
Start shaking the old man.
You start shaking the old man.
We need to find the relic!
Break, smash the relic.
You smashed the relic with a hammer.
slap him it's over we're stuck in an infinite loop now the old man snaps out of it both venture
to the small hill where the relic is buried will that fix it wait do a new story about elmo okay
all right that was fun new story you were the old man the whole time an old cartoon
actor made popular by sesame street oh we're not an old character friend
they spell antarctic sounds good 47 you have to 47 you're searching for elmo an old character
made popular by sesame street elmo's very elusive and would not be easy to try that really does read
like diana door swings open revealing all right we need different music how about happy kids music
right happy like kids cartoon music happy royalty free cartoon music happy background music for
videos no copyright i gotta skip that one okay that's all right okay the door swings open
revealing a dark tunnel beyond you can see a ladder leading up to a trap door above
a huge metal box sits on the floor of the room it looks like it might be heavy enough to crush
you if you were foolish enough to try lifting it okay i think i'm gonna just head down the tunnel
lift the lift the box lift the box it's too heavy for you to lift you'll need at least two people
to move this thing it's too heavy you hear a noise from the north any two people are gonna find a
party member ed north you're standing near the exit to the end of the world tunnel michael is
waiting outside he waves as you approach hey there mikey he says hi michael um what are you doing
here i was hoping we could talk about what happened last night i know it's probably hard
to remember everything that happened yeah sure whatever okay well maybe you could tell me how
you got home last night uh michael the important thing is tracking down elmo he's here somewhere
they spell michael a what i spelled oh okay michael the important thing is tracking down elmo
he's here somewhere right right i guess we should get started then michael nods and takes out his
notebook you turn to leave michael stops you hey wait mikey let me just make a few notes first
okay what are your notes oh nothing important just some things i want to check back on later
all right michael begins writing in his notebook you turn to leave michael stops you
what are you writing what are you writing just some things i want to check back on later
all right you mike continues writing this book you turn michael stops you again
stop stop moving i don't understand why you're so worried about this elmo guy we've only known
each other for a couple of weeks why do you care so much well i don't really know him personally
but my parents always talked about him when i was growing up he was always teaching us things
not to count out to eat right he always seemed like a pretty stand-up guy yeah i guess that's true
so what's this all about are you gonna help me find him or not i'm sorry mikey but i'm afraid i
can't help you why not because i think it will be dangerous to go looking for elmo dangerous what
are you you talking about dangerous i mean any more context or what did he teach you he taught
me a lot of things but i didn't really pay attention to most and telling me how to count
and how to read why is it dangerous to look for elmo i'm afraid i'm afraid he might be dangerous
what makes you think that he's a monster what kind of monster i don't know i guess i never paid
attention to what he looked like what do you think he looks like shit retry uh undo redo redo
redo no no no undo undo okay what does he look like i got it something stupid's gonna happen
i don't know something big like a bear but he doesn't have claws or fangs does he no i don't
think so and why are you so scared he can't hurt you i know but still i don't feel safe around him
i don't know michael please i need your help if we can find elmo we can bring him to justice
what did he do nothing really i mean he taught me stuff but he wasn't really a bad guy i don't
know why he left did he ever threaten you no what makes elmo dangerous i don't know i'm just scared
you're being silly michael you shouldn't let something like this scare you i know i'm sorry
i just don't feel comfortable with the whole thing play in editor mode it's less likely to get stuck
in a loop oh how do i do that we've got a dev in chat in the discord they might have some tips to
make the a work better i think i'm i think it's working pretty good this is vaguely intimidating
elmo okay i'm gonna i'm gonna walk this way walk through the what is the tunnel you enter the end
of the world tunnel michael is waiting outside he waves as you approach hey there mikey michael
stops me uh-oh listen to the dev yeah no loops how where's editor mode though how do i do that
why is he saying his own name let me let me look at the discord for a second
hold on let me hold on what do i need to do do like editor mode find the relic let's see all
right what do we got start a new story click new story then editor mode instead of adventure
go to okay go back here the text editor so okay so instead of instead of adventure mode we do
just like just text editor yes okay enter your prompt here okay you are searching for elmo what's
with the beach music i know hold on this music is like way too like tutorial all right you're
searching for elmo you're searching for elmo one of the most beloved children's television
personalities he has since gone into hiding no that's weird into hiding in an undisclosed bunker
somewhere in the ant oh it's just fucking burped i'm sorry
you're antarctic nice about hiding it is your job to track down elmo and interrogate
okay so now what send i can't take this fucking music anymore okay your first stop will be the
national archives you've been granted access to the files there you should find some useful
information about elmo's background and history including a file on his family tree
pull up his family tree to further investigate elmo's father was named william t sesame his
mother was margaret m sesame they were both born in brooklyn new york they had three children
together a son named peter j elmo was the oldest followed by a daughter named sarah elizabeth the
last child was a boy who was given the name thomas james elmo unfortunately he died before
he could say his first word after the death of their youngest child elmo's parents moved
to san diego california where they started a um baked goods store this business did well enough
that they're eventually opened a second location in los angeles they retired from the bakery after
20 years and decided to move back to brooklyn to be close to the family the day they arrived in
brooklyn they found that their home had burned down so they went back to san diego bought a new
house and started all over again after five years of running the business elmo's parents sold it and
moved back to brooklyn elmo's parents never spoke of their time in california or why they returned
to brooklyn unfortunately how do you spell that how do you spell i don't want it to help me
unfortunately unfortunately unfortunately unfortunately how do i spell it i don't want
it to help me i want to get this on my own unfortunately unfortunately unfortunately
the house was burned down when they went back to brooklyn so they went back to san diego
this time they bought a house that was still standing when they got back to san diego they
learned that their house had burned out again and this time they couldn't afford to rebuild
what the fuck no we're looking for elmo here okay all right so now we know the backstory
knowing the backstory i ventured to the antarctic looking for clues on elmo's whereabouts
i located a small this music's gotta go it sucks i don't it doesn't suck but you know what i mean
all right new song here we go this is literally the frankenstein plot i located a small deep
cave within the ice inside the cave i found elmo sitting on a rock with his arms crossed
he didn't look happy to see me who you stared back those soulless eyes
muttered the phrase i'm going i'm not george fucking rr martin okay i'm getting too into this
retribution let's retry that he began to shake no no hurt me please don't hurt me why should i
not hurt you because i'm innocent i'm innocent i swear tell me everything this is fucked up
tell me everything elmo all right all right i'll tell you but you have to promise not to kill me
of course i answer but i will take you prisoner until i can figure out what to do with you
so spill it what did you do what did you do to my friend gwen what do you talk gwen since
she saw you leave her house what the fuck what made you flee to antarctica it's a long story
just trust me i didn't do anything wrong i was just minding my own business and this lady came
along and told me she wanted to buy my life what does that mean elmo well let me start at the
beginning i can't do this fucking voice come on gwen i was walking through central park one day
when this woman approached me she said she wanted to buy my life i thought she mentioned would pay
me to go away but i soon realized that wasn't true what did she mean what did she mean she
explained that if i agreed to sell my life she would give me a million dollars she said i'd get
the money right now and i wouldn't have to work for it did you sign a contract was there any
paperwork involved not really she just gave me the money and said to leave town immediately
that was the last i ever saw of her mr noodle and you left town what did you do with the money
where did you go what did you do with the money i went to atlantic city and played blockjack
i won a lot of money and i kept winning more and more as time went on i became a millionaire
in a few months what much were you getting paid on sesame street it had to been a lot right
thousand dollars a week so you're telling me that you've been working for free for the past
30 years how do you feel about that that's four thousand dollars a month i don't know did you have
any investments did you put any money away elmo please no i gambled it all away i guess i didn't
think i would live that long do you have a family where's your family
passed away a few years ago my dad died a couple years after that they were both in their 70s
why are you going to kill me please no i'm not going to kill you i just got hurt you real bad
unless i need to i'm not sure yet maybe i'll just lock you up in a room and throw away the key
okay okay do whatever you want just don't hurt me good put in the back get in the back of the
fucking squad car now get in the my detective i don't think i can get away
we're in a cave get in the back of the squad car get in the back of the squad car i took him to the
police station and locked him in a cell i called in a couple of the detectives to help me interrogate
him they brought in a camera crew to film the interrogation we began to question him elmo have
you ever done anything wrong have you ever stolen anything have you ever committed a crime no i
haven't done anything like that i don't understand what you're talking about sure you haven't done
anything wrong you're stolen a candy bar corner store little shit stole something from someone
cheated on your taxes faked your income tax committed a fraud no i haven't done any of those
things you ever lied to anyone i point the bright light into his face like no i've always told the
truth you haven't cheated on your wife you've a lied to her you've a betrayed her you've spoken
badly behind her back just send it send it no i've never done any of those things you have any
enemies yes i have several enemies can you name them sure i have a few people who hate me one
person in particular hates me very much who is that his name is jim henson and he runs a company
called the muppets bullshit you are a part of the muppets i know that elmo i know that he's a part
of the muppets he's part of the same group that made all everybody else all they were all created
like by the jim henson company bullshit you're part of the muppets you're a puppet i know you're a
puppet you're a fucking puppet i'm not a puppet i'm a real human being i'm not a prove it prove
that you're a real human being tell me who you are how do i do that tell me who you are i'm elmo
a monster uh-huh not a real boy are you
hmm not a real boy are you you can't prove it can you elmo okay okay i'll prove it here look at
this picture he pulled out a picture of himself and showed it to us this doesn't prove anything
we are gonna need far more we're gonna need a lot we're gonna need more evidence what else do
you want me to do i want you to do the same thing that you did in the picture
what what are you talking about see where your arm is that look on your face do that right now
he did what we asked he stuck his tongue out and wiggled his ears he did a bunch of other
stuff too but i don't remember exactly what he did it was pretty silly see i'm not a puppet
i'm a real human being i'm not a fucking puppet okay okay okay i believe you i believe you i
believe you but he doesn't i point over to the cookie monster but he doesn't the cookie monster
is here to testify elmo that you are a puppet the cookie monster is lying i'm not a puppet i'm a
real boy we believe you elmo now i'm going to let you go put a plate of cookies on the counter
the sign that says three cookies see the chaos fucking happen here if you come back to the
station you can have as many as you want go ahead and eat them all you deserve it thank you thank
you very much he ate the cookies take elmo out of the interrogation room and into a cell
and in they spell interrogation we take him out of the interrogation room and let him go free
terror interrogation you can go now he leaves the station and heads back to his home in brooklyn
we watch him walk down the street we follow him as he walks away i turn to the detect detectives and
say that was easy oops i spelled detected wrong what do you think kermie i haven't been talking
like that the whole time i think we should interrogate every single puppet in america
we should bring them all in for questioning yeah who's mr bibb that's like a soft drink guy
that's not even a puppet is it mr bibb like it's like a doctor pepper ripoff guy
oh no this we're just good why would we be going after this guy he's not even a puppet
oh no no more national archives all right new story new story god that's so stupid okay
that was that was fun yeah this is much better okay how about um let's give me some prompts what
do you think give me give me some things to work with toaster and do i love toast crispy edges
buttery surface area and the smell of baking bread you can really put anything on toast
and it will be good usually this is yeah let's go a piece of cheese check sliced tomatoes check
yum peanut butter yes please jam hell yes honey duh it's like a blank canvas that you get to fill
with whatever you want that was way that was just what i wrote but five times better okay
i've been on a toast only diet for several years now following the diet guide
just toast i seem to have much more energy my hair is shinier than ever before and i'm totally happy
with my life now i'm in my apartment eating some toast when i hear a knock at my door i look through
the peephole and see my neighbor across the hall mr fitz standing there i open the door and let him
in music hello move camera here we go okay hey mark he says as he walks into my apartment he
looks around taking in the living room i see you again thanks it's nice to see you too i offer him
a seat at the table the freshest in my fresh toast i had brewing the last few hours what brings you
by he sits down looking at out the window at the view well i wanted to tell you something that
happened at work today oh yeah what did you hear that you were fired from your job well i was
why would they fire you not because i killed someone you what yeah you didn't know well i
guess i'll tell you a little while back i worked at a place called the midnight sun i was an
assistant manager which means i did all the dirty work i got up early to clean the store and make
sure everything was stocked and handle any issues that came up during the day i also made sure that
everyone who worked there had their schedule paychecks and benefits okay one night a couple
months ago we were short staffed so i had to stay late it was already after 11 p.m when i finally
left the building as i was walking home i noticed a man who looks suspiciously like my boss mr fit
walking towards me i thought maybe he was just going home from work too but i decided to call
out to him anyways mr fitz i yelled wait up he turned around and walked over to me what's up mark
is this really you yeah what are you talking about this isn't the way you normally walk sir
you always take the long route home oh sorry sorry i've been having some trouble with my
knees lately yes i could tell are you okay i'm fine he obviously was not fine so i offered to
carry him i offered to carry him home we got to his apartment and he seemed pretty drunk
i helped him inside and he fell asleep on the couch i covered him up with a blanket and left
him to sleep at all close the quote wait what close your speech marks i yelled wait up he
turned away i'm not i haven't been writing this the way he obviously was not but that
that's me talking so i'm saying that right like he obviously was not fine so i offered to carry him
home like that oh close that okay i see what you mean i get it like that no no don't worry about
it i'll be fine i just think i need to rest for a bit i helped him into his house and once inside i
saw that he had blood all over him i asked him if he needed help getting cleaned up but he told me
to go ahead and leave so i went back outside and called 911 when the police arrived they took him
away how did i kill someone about two weeks later i was called in to meet with my boss
i was told that he was going to fire me for causing him to lose his job i protested telling him i
didn't do anything wrong but he wouldn't listen i told him i told him he wouldn't listen he kept
shouting blood i'm shouting the blood and pointing at me finally i gave up and accepted my fate
a few days later i got a letter from mr fitz thanking me for helping him he said that he was
grateful for my assistance and he was going to give me a raise and a promotion
i said thank you but could not understand what no i said i said let me see how do i get this i said
thank you but he defined the relic the same development he said where does the killing come
in i declined and decided quit on the spot when i told my neighbor mr fitz he told me that i was
crazy for losing such a great job and that i should have done everything i could to save it
but i knew that i couldn't risk losing my job because if there's something i did accidentally
so here i am unemployed and eating toast mr fitz walks into the midnight sun and i see him sitting
at a table wait this is like are we going back to this moment or something i approach to shake his
hand and greet him but he doesn't respond mr fitz are you okay he turns to me and says i'm fine are
you sure i lean over see if he is okay and a few crumbs yet on his shirt he's furious he becomes
enraged get out of my sight you stinking rotten lying piece of shit well what's wrong i ask
confused nothing's wrong you stupid asshole as well as your quotes who did this to me who spilled
toast on me i don't know what to say i look around the restaurant and notice that there's
a waitress a cook and a busboy i think because i'm too embarrassed i think it was the cook
i think it was the cook he has been making pizza back there where is he now i don't know he ran
off when he started yelling find him now sir i don't think he should yell at us like that
what's his name calm down mr fitz don't you calm down me find that guy and get him out here or i'll
do it myself all right all right i'll find him i'll find him i find the cook in the back and have
him follow me back to mr fitz's table here's your pizza sir get out of here now uh i can't do that
why not because i'm the only one who knows how to make pizza they spell cleaver only i know the
secret recipe for a perfect pepperoni they spell pepperoni you're lying you're trying
to trick me into letting you go no i'm not then prove it how by giving me the secret recipe cook
reaches into his pocket and pulls out a large a piece of paper that has been rumbled up on the
paper is a list of ingredients this is the secret recipe i wrote it down so you won't forget it
give it to me and i won't fire you fine i will but you better keep your word why do you think you
can fire somebody in a different place the cook hands me the recipe and i walk back to mr fitz's
table here you go mr fitz thank you mark okay i'm very grateful for your help no problem for you
mr fitz see you tomorrow goodbye mark i return to my station and tell the others why am i a cook
i notice the cook laughing i wander over to the cook's station
and ask what is so funny i just wrote down three i just wrote i wrote down uh how to make like
formaldehyde i wrote down how to make rat poison i wrote down how to make rat poison what i figured
since mr fitz is a rat i would give him the recipe for rat poison what are you talking
about he's a rat i told you what do you mean you remember when i said i had to write down the
recipe for that rat poison well i used my finger to write it down you wrote the recipe for rat
poison with your finger no way well i can't believe you did that that's horrible what do you mean
horrible well you could kill someone with that like really how it's easy just mix it with water
and drink it you're joking no i'm not if you do that you'll die run into the lobby to find
mr fitz about to drink out of a glass of water i grabbed the glass of water from him and poured
on the floor hey what are you doing what do you think i'm doing you almost poisoned yourself
why did you stop me because you could have died i don't want to see that happened
you saved my life no i didn't just wanted to yes i did i'm what elaborate you hadn't stopped you
would have died so you're saying that you don't care if i die of course not why would i want you
dead sneered at me sneered at me whatever you understand what you just said i'm sorry i didn't
mean it like that i know you didn't don't worry i forgive you i gotta okay i gotta get more
elaborate things to do i can delete text holy shit wait wait can i have my job back sure no problem
hold on i just i like bit like a piece of skin off i don't want you to see that okay can i have
my job back sure no problem do this like music i like it but i returned to my station to resume
my duties as assistant manager i look at my watch and realize that i'm late for a meeting i rush
out of the restaurant and onto the street as i walk by mr fitz i notice he's turning green he's
turning green are you okay mr fitz yes i'm fine are you sure yes i'm fine he stumbles forward and
falls to the ground he hits his head in a lamp shade it starts bleeding mr fitz are you hurt
no i'm fine he gets up and walks over to a trash can he pukes up all the food he pukes up
he pukes up all the food he ate at dinner and then collapses on the ground
i rush over to him and sit him up mr fitz are you all right yes i'm fine are you sure yes i'm fine
i take him to the hospital where they determine that he is internal bleeding
they tell me they don't they he might not make it oh jesus it's like the stranger things music
it's just the fact that like why would you get up and then go to the trash can like this is so
fucked up i ask the nurse what kinds of vitamins they are giving him in his ivy
she tells me they are giving him vitamin k vitamin k yes vitamin k helps your blood clot without it
you would bleed to death you mean he might die yes that's exactly what i mean i tell her to
give him more vitamin k is there anything else i can do yes you can donate some of your own blood
okay take as much of my blood as you need you take some of my blood and gives it to mr fitz
i thank her no no no no no no no no no no he seems to have some kind of reaction
his skin turns blue and he stops breathing help i scream the nurse brush it and begin
resuscitating him after a few minutes he comes back to life but he's still blue what's going on
i ask his heart stopped beating for a few minutes what do i do now you need to keep pumping his
chest until he wakes up oh my god isn't he awake you need to keep pumping his chest till he wakes
up i continue to pump mr fitz's chest and after a few minutes he opens his eyes mark mr fitz what
happened i don't know i was just walking down the street and suddenly i blacked out
mr fitz you ate rat poison what i know i made you eat it i'm sorry why would you do that
i wanted to get fired but i didn't do anything wrong well i need more i know but i couldn't let
you get away with poisoning people i don't understand that's okay neither do i it was just
a gut feeling here there we go the chef was trying to kill you because of how rude you were
wait i never said anything bad to him yes you did i didn't yes you did and also you called me a rat
wrong person all right so now he's gonna do the thing where he gets up like in the movies and
like i'm done with all these things in me right mr fitz stands up and pulls all of his ivs out
like all right i'm out now you're going to pay for what you did to me he storms out of the room
the next day i receive a letter from mr fitz thanking me for saving his life he says that he
is grateful for my assistance and he's going to give me a raise and a promotion i decline and
decide to quit on the spot hold on wait wait wait the nurse runs in the room and puts them
back in you're not going anywhere till we get these ivs back in fine but you better put them
back in soon or i'm gonna find the chef the chef walks in with a bouquet of flowers hi mark hello
i brought you some flowers thanks you're welcome mr fix walks over to the chef punches him in the
face what was that for the chef asks calling me a rat you punched me and now you're going to jail
no i'm not rips out his ivs again and lunges for the chef stop i scream oh you want me to stop
yes please stop sorry i forgot to mention that i'm a vampire what i watch in horror as mr fitz
digs his fangs into the chef's neck i scream as i watch the chef turn into a bat and fly away
what are you doing i'm killing him why is he trying to kill me you can't do that why not
because it's illegal then call the police they won't help you mr fitz turns into a bat and flies
at full speed into a window stop i scream you want me to stop yes please stop fine i'll stop
mr fitz stops and flies back to his table window breaks and he flies out into the city i watch in
horror if mr fitz continues to fly through the city and eventually crashes into a building he
hits the ground hard and dies instantly i rush over to find to him and find that he is dead
his eyes open wake up i shout i can't you have to wake up you're dead no i'm not he opens his eyes
he closes his eyes he opens his eyes again you're not dead i don't know why did you try to kill me
it would be funny you're a sick man mr fitz i hover over him small few crumbs toast breakfast
all directly into his mouth bread crumbs yeah bread crumbs what are they doing in my mouth
i put them there why because i wanted to see if you would eat them uh mr fitz sinks his teeth into
my neck but there is no blood only wait no even no blood only garlic flavor see when one eats
garlic toast every day seems to come in handy against vampires what an awful sentence
it tastes like garlic mr fitz says yeah i know why because i eat garlic every day
really yes really what happened happened happened his eyes lock mine we both stare
into each other's very soul he realizes what has happened he will now die from garlic vampire
he tries to escape but i grab him and bite him in the neck he screams in pain
stop what's wrong you're not a vampire anymore see the amount of garlic i eat i actually
can reverse vampirism oh by drinking your blood you mean i'll live yes i'll save your life i'll
pull up my knife and stab him in his stomach what i hold the knife in place and then start to cut his
stomach open i remove his intestines and throw them into a garbage can i take out his liver
and slice it up into pieces what the fuck i then take his heart and throw it into the trash can
with the rest of the organs i take a deep breath and inhale the blood that is in the garbage can
it tastes horrible but it works i feel alive again wow that was gross yeah it was
do you know how long it took me to get this organ back inside of you no i don't
about two weeks two weeks yes it was that bad i pull up my knife and cut off his head
i put it in the garbage can next to his body you're a murderer i'm sorry why did you do that because
you tried to kill me no i didn't yes you did no i didn't yes you did this is the most realistic
vr experience i've ever seen i agree can i use this to make a game of course thank you
exit the booth and walk back to the office what did you guys think of the demo i asked
it was amazing did you enjoy it i loved it good good now if you excuse me i have a meeting with
the investors okay bye i walk up to my desk and sit down my phone rings i answer the phone hey
it's me hi it's mark listen i got a call for i just got a call from an investor he wants to
talk about the game okay okay i'll be right there i hang up the phone and look at the clock
it's already three p.m i rush out of the office and head over to the meeting
i arrive at the investor's office and knock on the door the investor answers the door and invites me
in hello mark how are you i'm great thanks for having me today i'm glad you could make it i'm
sorry i'm late it's okay i wasn't expecting you until four p.m we sit down in the conference room
and wait for the investor to finish talking to someone on the phone he hangs up very upset
it seems the investors do not think vampire chef vr will sell more than
eight copies i'm sorry but i don't think we should invest any money into this project
why not that's too risky what do you mean pulls out a graph resident sleeper this is a chart of
all the games that have sold for over one million copies so see vampire chef vr has only sold
7500 copies that is not enough for us to invest any more than we already have 7500 copies that's
it yes that's all i look at the graph and notice that all the other games on the list have sold
hundreds of thousands of copies why well it's simple most people don't like vampires and
fact i bet most of those who bought the game are children children but i'm 14 years old wait what
14 year olds don't buy games they play them on their phones and computers i don't understand
i'm sorry but you don't have the right demographic what if we made it a mobile game took out the
blood and replaced it with a match three match three game where you periodically
clean up a house or a garden with points from the match three game we could lose the vr experience
what if we kept the vr experience but made it a different game a different game you know but
that wouldn't be a vr game yes it would you would still be using vr you would just be playing on a
different screen i don't know you could hold up two copies of the game in front of each eye it's
the same no it isn't yes it is no it isn't yes it is no it's not yes it is i don't know i just
don't think it would work well we'll see if you're interested give me a call tomorrow morning all
right thanks lunch forward and bite his neck he falls to the floor and i take his heart and throw
it into the trash can i take a deep breath and then exhale i turn around and see the investor
staring at me who did i do this to who did i do that too i just saw you bite his neck and then
take his heart out of his chest oh i was just showing him what happens when you don't listen
to me i leave the office head home and walk into my apartment and sit down on the couch
i look at my computer and realize i need to do some work i take out my laptop and plug it into
the wall i bite the computer's neck and pull out its brain i put the brain into a jar and then put
it in my fridge what are you doing i'm working i put the computer into a vr headset and i begin
to work all right i'm going off the rails yeah this one's over it's an email from an investor
all right i think i'm done do a master chef episode all right one more one more one more
i'm a contestant on the hit show chef time some of the most prestigious
i don't i don't know some of the most prestigious chefs in the world will be critiquing and
f time so what is chef time i'm a contestant on the hit show on the hit show chef time
the game show is trying to find the next big chef in my area in my in world one of the most
prestigious chefs in some of the most prestigious chefs act as judges and contestants are eliminated
based on the quality of their cooking let's go it's a high stakes competition with some pretty
amazing prizes i'm not sure how it works but they say it's like a reality tv show where you get to
be the star the show airs on one of those channels that my parents never let me watch when i was
growing up why but now i have access to all kinds of great shows and i can't wait for them to air
so i can tell everyone about them i've been watching a lot of different shows and getting
ideas from them both back i enter the arena and see a dozen chefs all standing with their arms
behind their backs and wearing the same branded aprons there are cameras everywhere and a few
people who look like production assistants stand nearby i'm feeling very nervous but also excited
this could be my chance to become famous i walk into the kitchen and immediately fall feel out
of place i bite their necks okay i walk in the kitchen immediately but i place
suddenly chef suddenly chef greg rampson walks in in front of me he looks at me and says ah you're
one of our mystery contestants i have no idea what he means so i ask him what he's talking about he
smiles and tells me to follow him you're one of our mystery contestants follow chef rampson
into i follow chef rampson let's see where are we going which turns out to be a changing room
there are a bunch of other chefs waiting there too they all seem to know each other and some
even seem to be friends so it's like what like a green room like what do you mean change what do
you mean changing room why is it usually there's like a green room where everybody hangs out
why are we all hanging on a changing room sit down at one of the tables and try to relax it's my big
day i need to prove that i'm the best chef here relax chef rampson comes back into the room and
tells us that we'll be starting soon we all put on our aprons and head back into the kitchen
kitchen has two huge burners a grill a fryer a steamer a wok a cutting board and an oven it's
a lot bigger than i expected it looks like the kind of kitchen you would find in a restaurant
i start to wonder if this is really going to be a game show or something else entirely
rampson approaches rampson approaches us and a big timer shows on a billboard behind him
it is a countdown for the start of the show it's my turn with the cutting board
oh shit on a okay here we go the chefs take their seats and the hostess starts introducing everyone
she introduces me as a contestant from the united states and goes over some rules of the show
then she introduces chef greg rampson who will be acting as a judge i wanted to explain the rules
the rules are explained as right the rules are explained as well and i realize that i've been
given a great advantage by being able to cook without using any of these tools i can just use
my hands to make food what the rules are explained as follows each round will last five minutes and
each chef gets one minute to cook if a chef runs out of time before they finish cooking they lose
it will be two rounds per episode with four chefs competing in each round one minute to make food
okay in the first round chefs will prepare a dish using ingredients provided by the producers
in the second round chefs will create a dish using whatever ingredients they want
once a chef is finished cooking they will give their dish to the judges and wait to hear their
scores okay the first round is about to begin i get to work immediately because i know that i
don't have much time i make my way to the oven and set it to 400 degrees i add a little olive
oil to the pan and start sauteing the vegetables i also crack open a can of tuna and drain it
i add a bit of salt pepper and lemon juice to the tuna and then mix everything together once the
veggies are done i throw them in a bowl with the tuna and then pour that all into a baking dish
i put the whole thing in the oven for 15 minutes and remove it when when i taste the dish it
tastes great it seems like everyone liked my dish chef rampson says that he loves the flavors
and wants to see more from me i make it to the next round i make it to the next round round two
this round is called soups and it's about to begin i get to choose what type of soup i want to make
i decide to go with the chicken noodle soup i've always loved that flavor i make my way to the
fridge and pull out a couple of cans of chicken broth i take them to the stove and heat them up
then i grab some carrots celery and onions and cut them up i saute the veggies in the
broth until they are soft and then add the noodles to the pot i let the soup simmer for a while and
then serve it to the judges i think the judges like the soup but i'm still nervous about the next
round the final round is called the pasta it's called pasta and it's about to begin i choose
what type of pasta i want to make i decide on craft macaroni and cheese i decide on mac and
cheese staple from my childhood i decide on hamburger helper that's better i decide on
hamburger helper i figure it would be easy no i decide on hamburger helper let's see what the
fucking ai does with this one i head to the pantry and grab a box of the macaroni and cheese
i also pick up a can of tomato sauce some milk and a pound of ground beef
i bring all these items to the counter and start making my hamburger helper
i decide to really wow the judges i'm going to add an extra three pounds of ground beef
i add a little salt pepper and garlic to the meat and then mix it with the macaroni
i pour the tomato sauce into the pan and then turn the heat down to low
this where's the pasta i throw away the pasta i take the hamburger helper off the heat and
serve it to the judges i think they like the dish but i'm still nervous about the next round
the last round is called cake and it's about to begin i get to choose what type of cake i want
to bake i decided to make a carrot cake i make my way to the fridge and grab a couple of cans of
pineapple i then take the cans out of the oven and let them cool i open the can of sardines and pour
them into a bowl i add a little salt and pepper to the fish and then mix it with the frosting
i take the carrot cake out of the fridge and spread the frosting on top
my shoes and put my bare feet all over the cake i then use the sardine frosting to draw a face
on the cake i finished by adding some sprinkles and putting the cake back in the fridge
i think the judge is like the cake but i'm nervous about the next round
nothing is gonna fail i made it through the entire competition i'm so happy i'm ready to
win the grand prize i make my way to the stage and give the hostess a hug she introduces me
to the other contestants and tells us that we're going to compete in a dessert challenge we're
given a list of ingredients and told to make a dessert using any combination of them since
i won the last competition i now act as judge i taste the desserts and give each chef a score
i also give the winner a trophy and a check for fifty thousand dollars the chefs who didn't win
are awarded a consolation prize i get to sit this one out and watch that's very better i hope that
the other contestants can do better than me the first contestant makes a fruit tart which looks
delicious the second contestant makes a chocolate mousse which is also good the third contestant
makes a banana split which looks absolutely amazing the fourth contestant opened a pre-made
cake from the grocery store placed it on his seat and sat on it it was hard to tell if he
actually made anything at all fifth contestant was a woman named kelly she had a really nice
smile and seemed like a sweet person she brought a cake with her and she started to decorate it
right away fourth contestant got on top of the table and sat on her cake too kelly tried to
make the best of the situation and decorated around the cake her cake looked amazing but
the judges said that she would have taken care of the cake before she should have taken care
of the cake before decorating it sixth contestant was a man named tim he didn't have much of
personality and he didn't talk much either he just worked quietly in the kitchen and kept to
himself he had a big smile on his face though which was nice to see seventh contestant was
actually just the fourth contestant was in a mustache he made a rack of ribs and it was
immediately disqualified i mean it's supposed to be dessert how do you spell immediately
immediately thank you what's wrong immediately what i'm not i'm not an english major why are you
saying that i'm not an english major thank you holly immediately disqualified the eighth
contestant was a man named bill he was a very quiet guy but he seemed like a genuinely good person he
made a chocolate souffle and the judges thought it tasted great how many contestants are there
the ninth contestant was a woman named ashley she had a beautiful smile she seemed like a nice
person she bought a brownie sundae which looked amazing the tenth contestant was a woman named
alice she had an amazing smile she seemed like a nice person she brought a pie the judges thought
it was delicious the 11th contestant was a man named sam it seemed like a nice guy but didn't
say much he just worked quietly in the kitchen company he made a tiramisu the judges thought
it was great contestant 12 through 2500 all made their way through the competition i couldn't
believe that i made it this far i was so excited and was ready to win the grand prize the 13th
contestant was a man named will seemed like a nice guy but he didn't save say much
the 2615 contestant was frozen outside because it's minus 20 degrees out and we didn't have
space for everyone i was really nervous and i felt like i was going to throw up i made my way into
the kitchen and started working the 14th contestant was a woman named julie she seemed like a nice
person she brought a hot fudge sundae which looked amazing it's looping uh yeah we're looping
like the the final contestant made their way into the arena and gave the hostess a hug they
introduced themselves and told us that they were going to make a pie i was really nervous and i
felt like i was going to throw up claustrophobic claustrophobic uh i i feel like i'm gonna throw
up i threw up into contestant 650s baking pan there were people everywhere it was very claustrophobic
and i was about to pass out i made my way into the kitchen started working
it's people every there's too many people chef rampson bolt the door closed they are over running
us and i'm about to die i made my way into the kitchen started working the 17th contestant was
named james something really nice guy he had a beautiful smile we're being overrun i lay it
and we're no no whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa too many chefs i fall ground i fall down to the ground and
die the hostess asked the contestants who they think should win the grand prize everyone answers
at the same time all talking over each other the hostess tells him to stop yelling at each other
and to answer her question jeff rampson says that he thinks i should win the grand prize i'm so
surprised i'm dead on the floor so they have to give it to someone else i'm sad that i didn't
win but i'm happy that i made it this far i make my way back to my house and think about how i
could improve on my dishes a repetition penalty yeah add some quotation marks this is so much fun
though it's just so stupid tuna noodle soup because it turned out great all right i think
that's gonna be it i'm actually getting hungry now mr fitz revival i look weird today has this music
been annoying hopefully hasn't been like irritating i've been listening for like 45 minutes that was
fun that was a good time thanks for watching everybody we'll see you when does elden ring
come out what's the actual day thursday i'm gonna be ready to play that game i'm gonna be ready to
i'm gonna lock myself in here and play that all day it's four days in one hour so that unlocks
at like 9 30 i don't think i want to start my stream at 9 30 9 30 a.m because that would be
noon on the okay i won't be starting that early but i'll i'm when i get up i'm gonna get right
over here thursday at 9 p.m really i can't be right right all right we'll figure it out
uh if for some okay here's the here's the plan if elden ring actually let me just close this if
elden ring let's see elden this is technically it comes out at midnight eastern on the 25th
that's yeah that's 9 p.m on the 24th do you all right let me ask you guys this
i mean do you got what do you want me to do like a launch like 9 p.m stream
or should i just wait and do it on friday i could all right here's a plan if i'm going to do a 9 p.m
stream just like a launch stream and just play for like at least well because yeah i'll play it the
next day too yeah let's do it let's fucking go i've never done that before i have absolutely
never done a launch game stream before when it comes out the second it's available i'm going
to stream on the 24th at 9 p.m pacific we're going to play for at least four three four five hours
and then i'm going to go to bed and get up and we're going to do it all over again on friday
did that with monster rancher yeah i'm a liar you're right so we'll do a launch stream let's
go so i will be live on the 24th at 9 p.m or 9 30 maybe to give it like 20 30 minutes to unlock
make sure i can actually do it yeah that sounds fun thanks for watching the first game was really
cozy i really enjoyed that and it's always fun to mess around with i there was a couple things in
the ai novel ai stuff that was really funny i will see you guys later have a great night
take care of yourselves i'll see you guys on the elden ring launch be ready see you guys soon