All right. God, I hate. That's the worst comment of the whole year, but somehow also the best one.
All right, got a uh water. Stay hydrated, right? So the plan is to do speaking stimulator.
That's what was voted for. That's what was- that's what people voted for.
Why don't we just play- okay, listen to me. Why don't we just play it for like 10 minutes or
something? And we'll figure it out after that. Like, you want me to veto this?
Should I- should I veto this game? I already bought it. What do I- I might as well just play
for like 10 minutes. Play it for five minutes. All right, I'm gonna play it for five minutes.
Who cares? You haven't streamed in a week. I streamed like three days ago.
I've streamed in a week? Just refund it on stream. Same difference. All right, let me just come back
here. Uh, we can get this off the screen. So I'm gonna play it for five minutes and then I'll give
you- I'll give you some of the- you know, let me see. What have I got for- for veto options here?
Let me take a look. What do we got? We got- all right. Oh, you know what? I got elderborn.
Elderborn looks like it's- I was gonna play elderborn anyways. All right, it's either gonna be
elderborn or- I'm not starting the surge, too, right now. All right, bear with me. I'm gonna
play speaking simulator for five minutes. Put a countdown. Elderborn is snooze. It is? It looks-
it looks pretty fun. I'm gonna open it. I'm just gonna try it. I'm just gonna try it. All right,
I'm trying it. I just wanna try it. I just wanna play
for a few minutes. I'm gonna change the- yeah, hold on. Counting paper clips? That's not correct.
Here. It's even in the title, guys. All right, help me. Who did this? How about we do, um- help
me? Tongue movement, click and drag, lips, eyes, and brows to smile. W A S D's tongue.
Sorry, but you are now alive. I hope with your condition- I thought I was gonna read it.
How about that infiltrate and destroy human society? Okay, so hair. Meal, food, one? This is
not very much specified. Chunk? What? I don't understand. Okay, this is you, a perfect human
replica, the peak of our engineering technology. Not this game. I know. Look at the title. Wink?
All right, let's go. Try the jaw mechanism. Look on your mouth and drag it down. Okay, that was
inspiring. You're very inspired. Very good, very good. Let- let- let this praise wash over you.
Good. Now that you're sufficiently motivated, you will learn to stretch and pucker your lips.
You can drag outwards from the lip center to stretch. Drag in towards the lip to pucker.
Okay. Activate tongue. Use W A S D to move up, down, left, and right.
Push the green buttons with your disgusting tongue muscle. Okay, I just did. Despite being an
unfeeling AI, I'm proud of you. You're ready to face real humans. So I have to talk? You have to
talk. Level one, the date. Can you stop playing now? Just read the title. Manager of human
resources, Karen, has asked us to meet at this human food dispensary. We do not know why.
Show caution. It is possible that they suspect we plan to destroy humanity.
Sorry I'm late. Traffic was terrible.
What button do I have to press?
Oh, I get it. Okay. I am glad we're doing it. Thank you. That knocked all my teeth out.
There's something going on here. Nothing is going on. I am just a normal person.
Okay, I got it. I think something's definitely going on. I think we both know that there's some
attraction here. Yeah. I don't understand. Say it. I got it. You have such a flirt. I love it.
Let's get a drink and you can tell me more about how you like me.
How many units currency are required to purchase two fermented ethanol beverages?
This game is me. Why have you been playing this game for six hours? I've not been playing this
for six hours. Let's look at the menu. Okay. Imagine playing this for six hours. It hasn't
happened. Please forgive my error in requesting mechanical maintenance fluid. It was merely a
Somebody likes this here. Somebody likes this. I know they do. All right. My tongue's fucking
fucked up. Come on. Say it. What a treat. Not only are you gorgeous, but you get a sense of humor too.
I'm going to have some fun with you. Aren't I? I am a fun human with many fun. Come on. Get it.
Touch it. I am an elegant mate. Got it. I was not expecting this to get so saucy so quickly. This
is going to be a great night. Incredibly normal. Even kind of cool. All right. Back to the base.
Upgrade the station. Let's do it. Pull out teeth. Why am I pulling my teeth out? What? What's this
for? Smile. Smile. Express your innermost feelings as if they exist. All right. Let's get it. Smile.
What else can I do? Left, right. Gain system control of your eyes. Okay. Sure. Now the game
got harder. Yeah. That is actually what's going on here. It's been 10 minutes. The office. Job
interview. Yes. Yes. It's actually. No. Hold on. It hasn't been 10 minutes. All right. You've been
working for a month. The great leader has summoned you into their office. Be on your guard. You must
secure this position. You're great to meet you in person. I've been reading your resume. I'm beyond
impressed. What? Look happy. Isn't that happy? Oh. Exit this game. No, no, no. Not yet. Please call
me Grant. All right. Well, let me at least like close face up. Pressing it. I'm pressing it. Why
can I not hit this? external matrix. Chad wants out. Just wait. I bought this. It's not even that.
It's a game where they charge. This game is ridiculous. All right. Just, just do whatever
the weird thing is. All right. We're going to open up elderborn. Okay, guys, we're going to open up
the game elderborn. Jump king. I'm not. What do you mean jump king? Don't make me play jump king.
What do you mean jump king? Don't say that. Why are people saying that? Don't do that.
It was fun. I told you it was going to be 10 minutes. I can't play jump king. I haven't played
it in so long and I'm going to be so fucked up. I can't do it. Let's try elderborn. If elderborn's
not fun, I'll play jump king. How's that sound? Rain world. What the hell is rain world?
Rain world? What is this? Rain world. He plays like a slug cat thing. No, not today. Not today. I
want to, I want to swing swords at people. Elderborn opening up right now. Speaking simulator.
We got a wink. Hold on. Game capture. And here we go. I actually have wanted to play this for a
little while. This was on the list today. All right. Wait, wait, wait. You'll get your wink.
Two winks. All right. We got sound. Let's turn subtitles on. Ambient volume. A little bit lower.
Music volume. A little bit lower. Sound effects. Global volume. All right. Three. What? Do you see
my cheek? That's like a spasm. I'm spasming. Gameplay. Difficulty. Elderborn is fine. Elderborn.
That's fine. Auto aim. Disabled. Gore. Particles and decals. Crosshair. Enable. Dense indicator.
Hit value. Fine. Field of view. Let's get that up to at least like 90. 90. I don't want to puke.
Controls. Mouth sensitivity. We'll bring this down a little bit.
Let's take a look. Change the title. Oh, shit. Yeah. Hold on. Play it for like 10 minutes.
Uh, first per FPS. What the fuck do I even title this? Should I keep it playing this for 10
minutes and I'm out here for like two or three hours? How about Elderquop? Here. How does this?
This is better. So then people will come to the stream and they'll do the uptime and be like,
what the fuck? All right. Let's go. All right. I'm going to just ready. Let's get ready.
Right in the middle. This game looks fun. We've been told legends of the day that the sky has
fallen. The world filled with death and despair as the land of our ancestors turned to ash.
But the tribes, we survived. At the center of all destruction, a mighty city rose in the desert,
Yurmum. Feeding off the strange power flowing from the never-ending...
It's a webcam mic. It remained unconquered. A webcam mic. Relax.
Yurmum and its golden army was the bane of the realm for ages. The tribes toiled in shadow.
Its relentless grip enslaved and oppressed. It's just a little compressed because it was
big. They want to make it under like six gigs. United our tribes and led them against the city.
His name was Yannis, a hero anointed by elders, standing a giant among...
You making excuses? Yannis' warriors never returned, but the city fell silent.
Sealed shut. Dormant for centuries. But all of a sudden you guys care about voice acting?
Silent Hill 2 is some of your favorite game ever made. Our elders are the keepers of the past.
They tell us the city holds a great prize, the very secret of eternal peace.
Resident Evil 1 is like some of your guys' favorite game. You really care about voice work?
In every generation, a champion of the tribes is chosen by the elders. With their blessing,
they are set upon a holy pilgrimage to explore the city. The champion is decided in trial by
combat. I've mastered all my brothers and sisters. In this generation, the holy quest is mine.
Leaving the familiar desert sands behind me, I enter the Forbidden Caves. This is the only
remaining way to the sealed off city. No one returned from the pilgrimage. Yet there is no
fear in my heart as I stare into the darkness. Gripping my weapon, I step into the shadows,
and the shadows come alive.
Some mechanism is working nearby. Activate a fountain to save progress. Drinking from
an active fountain will heal you but also bring back slain enemies. Dark souls!
Fix the FOV? What's wrong with it? What? Was 93 too much for you? Make it higher.
Left shift to dash in any direction. You can perform attacks while doing so. Use this to
your advantage.
Pay attention to the icon. What's that dash? Okay, you can only do it for like one second.
That is the Dark Souls sound. That is the quake FOV. What are you talking about? What?
Do you want more? Left kick. Oh no, you're gonna make me f**king puke.
Oh, there's stuff in here. I want to change kick to... I'm gonna change kick to one of the
worst mouse ever buttons. Kick is not going to be F. It's going to be this button. Okay.
Use healing file. Okay, that's going to be this mouse button. Next weapon, that's fine. Quick
swap is fine. One-handed blades. Alpha one. Alpha two. Alpha three. Oh, spoiler. 270.
Gamer mouse. All right, let's go. Is this death? Do I die if I go in here?
This guy's got a shield. Mouse three to kick through your enemy defense. Watch for counters.
F**k. This isn't Rain World. No, and you know what? You know what? I ain't ever gonna play
Rain World. This might be useful. I ain't ever gonna play Rain World. No, I can jump up.
You weren't going to anyway. Maybe not. Maybe not. It depends.
That's key. Key fits. Open it. All right, here we go. First real test of the game.
I'm dead. I'm dead.
All right, I'm good. This door is open. Do I pick up souls or anything?
If you died in the undead asylum, give it a rest. Okay. All right, let's go.
Do I have eye frames if I dodge with this? Apparently not.
Die. Will you marry me? No, absolutely not. My girlfriend would have a real bad problem.
That one. Oh, there it is. Cover the souls? Got it. Five hundred and ten.
F.A. hands. Why? Interesting. Catacombs. I have a girlfriend. I'm not marrying somebody in chat.
Mouse four to heal yourself with the luminous file. All right. How many do I have? Just one?
I feel like I could get used to this and it'd be pretty fun.
This might be useful. Stop selling us on this game. I didn't do anything. Just playing.
It's all about the block. Here's the door. Is this too loud? I think it's a little too loud.
Not anymore. He's doing a gameplay voice. What's a gameplay voice? What's a gameplay voice? What
does that mean? Gameplay voice? I'm just fucking talking. I'm talking. Does it wink? Can't get this
open. That was actually mad. He's in undead asylum. Dying in undead asylum. No, I'm not.
E3 game trailer. Let me just enjoy this. Oh, it slows motions. This feels like Oblivion.
So what do I do with a full meter? All right. I'm going to start talking like this for the
rest of the game so people don't fucking say that I'm doing an E3 voice.
No, shit. That is an E3 voice. Look, I'm a relatable guy from a city. I'm from Boston.
I'm relatable to you. No, that's worse. All right. Just do Bugleberry. No, I don't want
3,000 people to leave. Do the auto voice the whole time. That is E3. How is that less E3?
Challenge completed. What is that? Challenge completed. What the hell?
Uh, might, speed, and resilience. Your attacks and skills deal more damage. Wait,
can I put points into this? You move faster and your attacks are more fast. You have additional
hit points. Claim reward? Okay, I claimed it. How do I use it? I claimed it apparently.
Go back to universal paperclips. I beat it. I completed it. I beat the whole game.
This stream feels longer than 20 minutes. No, it hasn't. It's been, I don't know, like 15 minutes
so far total. Should I even be opening these? I have like a max bar. What's it doing?
I regen health for the full bar. Oh, that's kind of cool.
Somebody said super frog. Speaking of super frog, uh, got something. I got something.
I'm gonna die. Get out of my life, please. All right. Now what? Got candy. It does have candy.
200 essence. Do I have a super frog? Uh, I have something coming up soon.
You guys really gonna like? Don't kill me, please. The fuck just hit me? I have a game compilation
that was highly requested. I got it. The orange box. I finally got the orange box. I'm trying to
see what like the big hype about it is. Nothing in there. Fuck. This area kind of sucks. Finally
got rain world. People want to see you finish jumping. That's not gonna happen. I've been out
of the game for so long. It would take me like a whole, typically like three days to get back
to where I need to be to beat the DLC. I can't do it. No way. I got to, I got to where I wanted
to get to. Shit. Oh, fuck. This is bad. This is bad. Just kill him for me, please. Kill him.
Oh, Jesus. Come on. Here again. Keep going up. Irma the turtle. Yeah, I'm level one. Of course
I'm going to be a turtle at level one. I know. What do you think? I am like level 30. I don't
want to lose this. If I lose, I'm going to move on to Jump King. Can I throw something? Missed.
Missed again. Oh, that was actually pretty cool. Whoa. That's a lot of people. That's a lot of
people. This game looks like Sea of Thieves. Stop. Don't make me laugh right now. I don't want to
lose. There's so many people here. Oh, fuck. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. I'm okay. I haven't fallen.
Oh, boy. Come on. That was pretty good reaction to anything. Sea of Fucking Thieves. Come on, man.
Oh, boy. Still alive. No, no, no. I want him to die. I want him to die. That's what you sound like
right now. How much further does this go? I probably have like six million HP. Oh,
what is that? Is that alive? Can I upgrade? I probably can. I hope so. Activate the thumb.
Made it to a fountain. Tab to level up. Leveling up is possible when the icon below is displayed.
Okay, let's heal and then let's level up. What should I do? Speed? Speed, damage, or health?
What do you guys think? Speed. One percent. Two percent. Three percent. Five percent faster. I'm
five percent faster. Didn't I claim this already? All right, I'm good. I got the fountain. I've
leveled up. Let's keep going up. It's probably a boss right here. You guys are going to see me
play this boss and then all of a sudden like this steam page is going to get like 600 people new
traffic and there's going to be like 350 fucking new sales. It's going to be like,
oh, that was awesome. I'm going to fucking beat this before he does. There's a lot more people
here. Dude, it's an ad. It's not an ad. Rain World now. I've never even heard of this game.
Oh, shit. Don't. It's a bad game. I don't know anything about it. There's no iframes.
Who the fuck said that? You got the logs. How do they not block that? Are you kidding me? Come on.
Do it. All right. Can I kick you off? What you? Hold on. You stay planted? What are you talking
about? Do Rain World or I leave? We'll see you later. I'm not playing Rain World right now.
Get rainers. Get ready to riot. Where did this even come from?
Do I even have stamina bar? I don't think I do. All right. There's a shitload of people up here.
You didn't want to play it. So chat now is doing this because they want to be funny.
Play right. All right. I don't back up that much. I'm going to die. Wait till he swings.
Gameplay voice. All right. One, two. There it is. Opportunity comes up. Nice job.
There's a couple of swings. Do it again. Gameplay voice. Okay. One, two. No, let's try to get that
one. Tuber voice. I'm the ultimate tuber. Name me a better tuber. Come on. Can you?
Don't you remember Face Camp Fortress 2? I do. All right. This is somebody said Sea of Thieves. No,
this is like Riddle Hollow and Outer Wilds. Oh, no. What's it called? What's that one called
with the black hole in the bottom? A Kinect game. Stop. All right. More speed. Sure.
Successfully parry a projectile to launch it at the nearest foe. Spend less time chasing after
essence. It will fly towards you on its own. I mean, that sounds, that sounds pretty good.
So when I parry now, it'll launch at somebody. All right. That's cool. That's pretty cool. Let's
keep going. This doesn't open. Let's test it. Shoot at me. Shoot an arrow. Is that not a parry?
That's a projectile, right? The parry. All right. Where am I supposed to? Oh, there's a lever over
there. Okay. Am I supposed to jump and get this? No. Oh my God. Hold on. Fall off. No, there's no
fall joke here. All right. I'm ready. Just pull the lever. Shit. I actually have to fight my way
down there. Oh, come on. What is this? A fighting game. Jump King now. No, I'm not playing Jump King.
That was a lie. So why is that? Am I not parrying correctly? I don't get it.
How's that on a parry? It's not. I'm very confused by that. This game is supposed to have music. I
think it's playing. I need a different weapon to parry. Oh, somebody's running behind me somehow.
Open this fucking door, please. Eight. Oh, down there. Come on. That door now opens.
Does that stay open? Can I save the game? This is pretty cool for on PS2.
All right. That's a level up right there. Let's go. Speed. Okay. I don't have enough essence.
All right. I'm 10% faster. I can do more damage next. Nothing stops the rain. I'm going to open
up rain world and people are going to be like, I don't like this. This is what's going to happen.
Character sheet. All right. Kill count. 83. Time played. More than I've said I was going to stream.
Chests open. What should I get to a boss? What do you mean no bosses? Let me just get to a boss
first before everybody freaks out. I mean, I'm not getting the essence for this, but whatever.
Easy to get rid of them. This game's too violent for me. I'm sorry. This is what we're doing,
though. Need more enemy variety. Well, it hadn't been very long. Really? Breaking this will require
some heavier tool. Oh, great. Can I go anywhere else? Wink. If you speak while playing a game,
an E3 presenter. I can't even talk. Otherwise, I'm an E3 presenter.
Guys, I can go this way. I can go this way. Remember, if you say the thing you're doing,
you're in. Blame the E3 gameplay fucking demos. It's nothing to do with me. Pick up.
Ooh, and a block. Ooh, that looks like a parry. That's a parry. That's absolutely a parry.
Wink scam. You only got like three more days on that, by the way. Well, I didn't die,
so that's good. Sell them now. I don't even need to jump. You just go, you walk up these
and you get 5,000 points in three days. Probably. It'll probably be all right.
This is not... Oh, is this not a heavier tool? Wait, this is not what I was supposed to do?
Spear is not heavier than a sword. Well, okay. Refuge. I call this place a refuge with dark
sarcasm. It seems less dangerous than the fire pit below. Fire pit below. You got it. Dark sarcasm.
Tap right mouse button at the right time to parry. You can parry unblockable attacks.
Attacks marked with that icon cannot be parried. All right, nice.
That was fucking cool. That was really cool, actually. Are you gonna do something?
What? How is that not a parry? Nice parry. I thought it was. What? Okay.
Why did it work that time? He was slightly too early. That's all right.
All right, look for a tool. A heavy tool. Well, are they fighting each other?
It's a fucking scorpion down there. This is really confusing. So, is it gonna be later than this?
All right. Oh my God. Monka S. Minus 300 viewers. Monka S. Ah! I thought it was a set piece.
I thought it was a set piece. I thought it was a set piece. Oh well. I thought it was
calcified or something. I don't know. I didn't think it was alive. There's only 500 viewers left.
Shit. Fuck. I better play Risk of Rain. I better hurry up and get on that. Die here?
So, I'm gonna have to parry this. These scorpions are fucking scary. Here we go.
Parry. That happens very quickly. Holy shit. I'm not supposed to be down here. I don't think I'm
supposed to be down here. Holy shit. I'm not supposed to be down here. There's so many
fucking scorpions. I'm not supposed to be down here. I'm hiding. Is there a fountain?
I'm definitely not supposed to be here. I need to find a tool. Okay. Well, I'm up here. What? So,
am I not supposed to go down this way? I don't understand. I died in like one hit down here.
Find a tool. That's better. I'm almost dead again. Did that guy just spawn? That was weird.
Wink scam? God. It's getting deleted. Use them now. It's gone in like in less than 24 hours.
I'm absolutely not supposed to be going down here. I'm already dead. Is there a different way to go
besides? Hold on. Play funny jump game. No. No. There's a fountain right there. Why? I'm just
keeping it on. I didn't press any button. Stab each other. I killed it. All right. Now what?
You don't have to parry every attack. If I don't, I'm going to get hit and die. I'll be dead.
Watch out for that fire. Don't touch it. Give me that. Say the funny word. What's the funny word?
What do you want me to say? Maybe getting hit and dying is a good thing. I don't think so.
Like five people said they were coordinating in like a discord.
Play this rain game and now all you guys are latching on to it. Don't get manipulated.
Play Wayne's World? Am I reading that wrong?
Somebody say play Wayne's World for Super Nintendo? Okay. Still going good. Hello board?
Somebody's shooting arrows at me. From where? Oh, over there.
Wait, I can. That hurt. Never mind. Wayne train leaving the station.
Get out of here. What was that fucking hit box? Am I like 60 feet long?
I don't even fight these things. I don't even worth doing that.
Like King's Quest? That's not a bad idea. King's Quest is pretty fun.
People could like talk shit and stuff and we could have like a fun back and forth about like
what do I do? What do I do with the bubblegum? Do I combine the bubblegum with the stick?
And everyone's going to be like not like this fucking idiot. What are you doing?
Sounds like fun. All right. I'm not done yet. I'm not done until I get to a boss
and then I uninstall the game. Oh sick fountain. Let's go. I haven't leveled up yet.
Dude's sick. Dude's sick. He thinks there are bosses. There is. There really isn't.
Need a tool. Oh, there's a key. Let me get this. All right. Now I get the key to that door that's
over there. I can level up. There's another one down there, but not worth it. All right.
Now let's go open the door that's over here. Where was it? Down? Where was it over here?
I can't get back up here, can I? I think I have to drop down. I guess I gotta go down here.
Fire pit. Interesting. Okay. Interesting. Let's see if I can kill these guys. Oh,
there's three of them. All right. I'm ready for. Hey, here we go.
Um, this is, this is like fucking a hundred over here. Who cares? I got a door to open.
Oh, come on. Come what? What? Give me a break. Why? Where was this door? It was back here,
wasn't it? Do I still have the key? Thank God. Somebody's probably behind me too.
Everybody careful. I told you there was bosses in this game. What did you? I told you there was a
boss. Give me the hammer. Oh, I got a hammer now. Game just got way better. Okay. I can. Okay. So
now we go. I'm going to go back to where that down here, right over. Will you please? Why don't I
put this up to my face? Me mad? Who? Who is over there? What's the name? Why are you so? Why are
you mad about them? What are you mad about? What's wrong? What's the matter? I'm going to
kill them all in one swing. Ready? Watch this. Close enough.
All right. This game just went up a fall letter grade because of this weapon.
Wham. You want rain world. Wham. You want rain world. Shit. Come on. Just hit one.
Why? No, don't activate it. Activate, activate, activate. Okay. Let's get up.
All right. Can I not get up from here? I think I'm stuck down here.
Can I not get back up from this way? 600 people left. It's my fault. No, that's, that's on them.
Guys, for all you know, 600 people just got like a fucking call and they had to get on a phone call.
They had to go to like the doctor or something or they were going to eat dinner or it was not
going to bed. You don't know it was my fault. I had nothing to do with it. 600 people just got a
phone call. I can't get, I cannot get back up here. Can I?
It hurts so much. Just play rain world. I'm going to open rain world like three weeks from now
and play the first five minutes and then delete the game. Can I not get out of here?
How do I get back around? Uh, wasn't there another one of those patches somewhere? I mean,
there were two walls. There was another wall I could break. I don't know where it is.
Over here. Over here. Back to that boss door. I don't even remember where the fuck it is.
They use the wrong fountain.
There ain't nothing down here. Well, let me go back this way. I have to go through here, right?
No, do I? Through here and back up around. Go up this way. Don't get killed by a fucking scorpion.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Back up here.
Is that boss door thing? If I can make it by this without aggroing the whole room.
And you just, that was embarrassing. All right. All right. I've almost had enough. You died? I
know I died. What do you think? I don't have the same screen on as you. All right, pull these guys
out. Oh my God. Should I try to parry? All right. I just fucking annihilated this dude. Let's go.
All right. You know what? I don't even care. Let's just go. Like, what the fuck?
There's nothing even in here. Why is there a third guy? Shit. There's nothing even in here.
All right. I got to level up. I like sneak out of here and just check every crevice. Hold on.
All right. That counts as a boss. Is there a fountain up here?
Fuck. Oh my God. I'm in so much trouble now. Let me die. All right. Well, I know that my shit is
over there. It's a full level up worth of stuff. Okay. We're good. Oops.
It's a sticky key. Wait, why is sticky keys on? All right. I'm good. All right. I'm almost done
with this game. I wanted to play it. It's fun. I just mauled it into sticky keys. It's fun.
Quick. Get the fuck out of here. Sex is safe. Game over. We win? No, you don't win.