Somebody said, who's your favorite Vocaloid?
I don't know, I didn't know there was that many.
You done peeing? Yeah, I am done peeing.
You guys ready for Pac-Man Museum?
I'm gonna turn it down, at least not too loud.
I don't even know what this is.
We're about to find out. Yep.
Alright, let me capture this.
Max FPS.
No, that's fine.
Uh, that's fine.
Borderless window, yeah.
Okay, it's very loud.
Let me turn this down first.
I actually can't turn it down.
I have to go to the source here.
Alright, let's get back.
You can't see it yet, but you will in a minute.
Putting it together.
Pac-Man.
Where are you?
There you are.
So, let's go.
What are they doing?
What the fuck is going on?
Alright.
Welcome to Pac-Man Museum Arcade.
In this arcade, you can choose coins to play a variety of Pac-Man.
Oh, shut them all. Everybody shut up.
Welcome to Pac-Man Museum Plus.
In this arcade, you can use coins to play a variety of Pac-Man games.
When you want to play a game, move in front of it and select play.
The game will start.
While in the arcade, press Y to open the menu.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
This place is fucking annoying.
I wouldn't want to be in here for more than five minutes.
Alright, what do they have for machines?
Gashapon?
Spend coins on the Gashapon to get here.
I don't know how you...
Is it supposed to sound like this?
I gotta get out of here.
Alright, Pac-Man, Pac-Mania.
Huh?
Okay, I was gonna say I thought it was gonna be that small.
Let's get a few extra lives.
Got him.
It sounds like Miku.
It does.
This sounds like Miku.
I can't escape that game.
It really sounds like Miku.
I feel like my voice has changed in the last hour.
Got him.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Gwen.
You can jump?
What? I didn't know you could jump.
I'm never gonna get caught by a ghost ever again.
One, two, three, four.
Ooh!
How do we get a cutscene?
This is the best song.
This is the best song they've ever made.
What the fuck was that double bounce?
Screen settings?
No, I don't want to see her teeth.
I want the bigger screen though.
That's better.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I wasn't looking.
That's fine.
Alright, it doesn't matter.
I got four style...
I got four coins.
That's it?
I unlocked Pac-Mania cabinet, a gold container.
A...
Okay.
Please.
I got a cabinet.
Okay.
That fucking stung.
Stop.
Stop hitting me.
Stop slapping me.
This is the original Pac-Man.
Play Pac-Man in time two times.
Do I have to do the original?
Pac-Land.
What's Pac-Land?
How do you play Pac-Land?
Oh my god, it's this fucking game.
To control Pac-Man, run with the end of the direction of the arrow.
How do you jump?
I feel like I'm going max speed in Oregon Trail.
Stop.
I did it?
Let's go.
God, I'm gonna play that Bugs Bunny Smash Bros. game again.
So is that thing down there a timer?
That's money.
Oh, that's such bullshit when that happens.
Absolute horseshit.
Just total horseshit.
Play multiverses again?
I can't.
They turned it off.
The alpha's gone now.
They closed it.
When's it release?
Uh, July, I think.
July's the open beta.
This game's awful.
Alright, now what?
Get rid of Pac-Man?
At least it shuts up the people.
Okay, at least we can get away from that fucking song.
Oh, here it is.
The one where you could jump was really actually good.
Oh!
Here it comes.
I fucked this whole thing up so bad.
I tried to press up.
This game's fucking stupid.
Wait, what?
I didn't press it that many times!
Did you guys know that Pac-Man was originally gonna be a pizza game?
It was like you put like sauce and cheese on the pizza and stuff and you put it in the oven, but the game director
The putting the sauce on the pizza sound sounded so funny to the director of the game that
It's just like which probably maybe we should change it to like an eating thing or the pizza eats things
You lying come so easily to you. I'm not a liar. I'm a performer. Shut up. It's a performance. Shut up
I'm a performer. This dude is wicked soy. I'm fine. That was fun
Who he was gonna be called puck man. No, it's pizza man
Play pac-man two times. Okay, so I have to play this two times to unlock super pac-man. All right, I played it twice
All right, come kill me they found out in the US kids would edit the P on the machine to an F
Remember this sucks go back to Miku. I can't I'm too burnt out to do Miku. I can't do Miku
I can't play Miku anymore. I'm prime bars out from all the flashing colors Miku or riot. No, I can't right now
I'm just tired now. Look, I've got I unlocked um pac-man super pac-man. There we go. All right
What is super pac-man?
I've ever played this
Same one
This looks fucking weird. What the hell is this? I
Interesting don't you get all the keys pac-man would never eat eggs. They're too healthy. Wait, he eats fruits
Please my ears. It looks like it's turned on
What the fuck I got all the fruits it's all the keys
This is the kind of game that I would get
like my grandfather on his steam of his first steam account and I would go to check a year from now to see what my
grandfather had in his steam library, and it would be this and
I don't know dead space one and two because it's on sale for three dollars every year
It's the only games you have and all the free-to-play stuff and you'd go on it and see how much time that grandpa had
Playtime he hadn't even opened him
500 hours on path of exile
They go too fast. I I never was a fan of pac-man. I
Was I was never a fan of pac-man?
I was always I was more of a fan of pac-man's character than I was his video games
Pac-man super pac-man pac-mania
pac-man battle royale
pac-land pac-man
arrangement
Pac-pal
Okay, let me do pac-man battle royale say it and so I love pac-man
He's the greatest video game character ever but his I don't know these games were kind of the originals great
Pac-man's great adventure is great the one where you have to like point him in directions and help him
Why is that not here? This one's good, okay?
Eat power pellets
He's a cannibal
Fight how do I how do you win? Wait? You don't how do you hurt each other? I don't understand. What's going on?
Do I have to wait to eat each other? Ah
All right, that's all right. So I've won wait for next round. This is zoomer pac-man. No, it's not money in I guess
You play with like four people. That's fine. Does everyone have to have their own controller at the arcade cabinet. That would be fun
Kiss the CPU
Lost to CPU. How come there's only one CPU? That's weird. It's gonna be way more
That's how did I just lose that? You only have one CPU in your computer. You only have one CPU
All right. This this one sucks. This would be fun with like four actual friends sitting around
This is a scuffed version of championship edition
They have these at tape. They have these at I think they have these as table machines in some arcades
That makes sense
What's wrong? I'm not even paying attention. What just happened? Why is the sound getting faster?
This is a Dave and Buster's game
It really is
This is a game at Dave and Buster's
That's so funny
Yeah, and it spits out like 10 tickets
The shit you like. Oh great. Cool. That was fun. I guess I got like eight tickets
This literally is at Dave and Buster's
No, is it? No, it's not
It actually is deal or no deal is the best arcade game
Now we can maybe should I play dear or no deal on stream? I think it'd be fun
All right. Well that game was fun. It's fine. It's fine. My turn like pack land two times
I want to know what pack pal is right pack mania and pack land. Where's pack land?
Okay, so it's gonna open this and then close it because what is pack pal?
Oh it knows
I have to actually get in and die. This one was actually the best one
There's more games in the big machine
What was the pac-man game you played you made a video on like 10 years ago?
That's pac-man to the great adventure or something
It's not a pac-man game
It's a side scrolling directions game. It's really weird
I wonder if there's uh, if they might be in it
This one has a final boss it's not in this how why would this not is it a licensing problem?
I thought that was gonna be on here. That's why I want that's why I bought the game
I thought it was a pac-man museum plus. Okay, let's go
packing time
That's one of them that i'm thinking of right?
Okay, well what's pac-man arrangement, how do I not even know these games came out?
Instructions i've been i've been playing video games for
30 years
I feel like these were all made up today
And i'm being gaslit into thinking these are real
Well, i've never heard of these
Why is there a bunny?
This one's actually fun
I like this one. This one was good dash. Whoa. All right, that's cool
It's awesome just kind of fun to do that
Whoa, wait, you can do that
That's helpful pac-man arrangement that would have weird name. Is that why this game didn't do that? Well, because it's called pac-man
arrangement
I thought it was gonna be I thought I was gonna be making flowers or something
Painting game. I don't think it was gonna be an actual pac-man game
Get them all good go
Oh, i'm in trouble
Actually in trouble. Nope. I'm good
Why wouldn't it be a pac-man game?
Oh, they've made some weird ass pac-man games over the last 20 years
big fucking deal
I missed one little pellet really they make a weird noise. What's the they go?
Oh
You should have a pac-man themed wedding. I thought I would wait. I thought that was it. I thought this was a bonus stage
What the fuck?
Throwing for pac content. It is a bonus round. Okay. That was I don't know why I just got invincibility frames for a second
That was weird
Shit bad. What I swear this fucking goddamn controller. What the hell?
Oh, no
I'm pressing the buttons. What the fuck?
I'm pressing die. It's just he's fucking hits a wall freezes, bro
bro, relax
That was fun
I i'm literally pressing the button and just hits the wall and move this is what pac-man
Only works when you have the stick that has only the four directions
Anything else is impossible. You cannot play pac-man with a regular fucking controller. You have to have four one, two, three four
That's it return to arcade. Yes, please
Use the d-pad d-pad doesn't work either because sometimes you press up on a d-pad
It presses like left or right at the same time. I'm using an xbox one controller the d-pad
It's like all one gigantic button
You need a stick or arrow keys. Yeah, but i'm a fucking console gamer. Okay. Now what is it for this?
Play pac-lan two times
How about not play I already did play this once
Continue from pause date. Oh, I got sick. I got sick of it and didn't want to play anymore
Play deal or no deal. We'll do that on um on sunday
Here's your plan for sunday. We're gonna play we're gonna play um
trivia and and um game show games
How about who wants to be a millionaire?
deal or no deal
So maybe a couple others
We'll do that on sunday. I'm just trying to die
All right now back out come back in
I want to at least see each game once play the awful full-priced millionaire game that came out like a year ago
Yeah, it's probably when i'll play
Go buy more games
Hello, let me unlock these ones first
What about the oregon trail? I don't I think I have maybe once back during one of the dos nights. Maybe I think so
I just played it again. All right, let me be honest
I bought the fucking game. Do I have to really do you have to put all this shit under walls?
Like it's pac-man museum. Do I really have to do all this to play the pac-man games? I want to play
It's not a it's a museum. It's I don't I don't have to go look
At the mona lisa to unlock
The other fucking paintings in the museum if it's a museum just put it in the museum. Just put it in the museum
Just put it put it for display in the museum
Unlocking things is fun. You joyless husker human
Okay, can I please play the other game hacking pal eat the turn over the card and eat the flashing item give it back
I'm good. She's safe touch a ghost and you'll lose turn the tables with a special item press the button
That kind of hurts my head to look at
Eat the s we did it
One with the hat was better. I get the idea. The concept is interesting, right? But I
It's just modded pac-man
It's pretty awful
I'd say it's very awful. It's a less fun pac-man
Okay, so what are there any others I can do?
This one play pack in time two times. Where's pack in time?
Do I have to buy it?
What do I get it how do I get um pack in time
It's the big one
I can't play it pause saving is not supported. Oh, what the fuck
Our hero pac-man is the cool video game dude, we know and love okay
When the evil ghost witch and her ghost monsters invaded his world pac-man was there to defend it
Since then he's been living happily with his family in pac-land
But his fiendish arch enemy the ghost witch has vowed to disrupt his tranquil life
Okay, following the failure of her diabolical plan. She decided to eliminate pac-man once and for all the ghost which cast a
Forbidden spell on pac-man ripping him from his family. Oh my god
And hurling him through time to his dangerous past
The journey back in time transformed pac-man into a young pack boy
And the only change is he doesn't have a nose anymore the ghost witch sent him to a world which has never heard of the hero pac-man
though the witch's foul magic
The inhabitants of a once beautiful land have turned against him and the ghost witch's loyal ghost will do everything possible to keep him prisoner
Look at how cute he is
I love this version of pac-man
He's so cute let's find out
Okay
mountain
Huh? You have a it's like mega man
Are they trying to make okay the shoes the fast running they just try to make a sonic the hedgehog version
What does that do?
He's so stumpy how do I open this
How do I open the chest?
He looks like one of those custom south park characters that everybody used to have
Do you remember that?
Can I can I swim?
I need a key
Ah
I can't swim
Bro, I don't see somebody playing mega man that knows what they're doing and they're really good at the game
Some of the speed runners, right? It's always like they just like brr brr brr when they jump. It's crazy
How do I get through here?
Can I swim? I can't swim down
Use the item
What item?
A change. Oh left bumper. Somebody just said this sucks. How do I get down here? How do I break this?
Can I drop down? I need a hammer press a
Is there another item? These controls are gonna slow down slow down get the water hammer. Where is it?
This is worse than glover. No, it's not
Where's this hammer? It's in the water of what get me out of here. How do I get in the fucking exit?
I need all the rings all the dots. I can't even get back up here guys. I'm fucking screwed
I can't beat the level anymore
Where's the rope?
Why did the rope get taken from me?
somebody said
Reviewer gameplay. Oh, please
You don't know how hard this is to control. It's so weird
Ow
It's really weird kid. I think they're up here
He's so bouncy. It's weird. It's it's strange. Trust me. I'm so impatient. I fucking can't do it
That's fine. I don't want to do that anymore
That was a really cute one, but I don't want to do that
Pack and roll remix
Is this a game cube or something?
Is he yelling?
This is another Dave and Buster's game. I don't I disagree
check checkpoint
Get up there
It's driving me fucking crazy
It's just you like you can't control it. It's it just be so bouncy
He's so bouncy in these games. It's ridiculous, but I have to play this again. He goes too fast and he's too bouncy
I feel like my mouse sensitivity is too high
I games like these just drive me fucking crazy
I remember when I was a little kid snake rattle and roll. I I tried to break the nintendo controller in half
Like bending it this way because I couldn't I hated it so much
And all it did was just made really loud crackling sounds
like I was not strong enough to break it obviously, so it was just like
All you heard was just crunching stuff
Not strong enough to break it but strong enough to like kind of fuck it up
Just get me out of here. I don't want to play this snake rattle and roll is good. You just bad
No, I I didn't say that
pac-man 256
What is this?
Fuck is a mobile game
I just kept hearing a guy laughing. I just hear
Laughing
I want it again. What is this fucking horse shit? And why are you so fast? That's pretty cool
What the fuck? All right, one more one more and that's it. Why this is the best one so far
I need to get a thousand. I want to get over a thousand again
Move two thousand twenty five hundred twenty five hundred. I'm done. Oh five thousand and i'm out of here. Oh shit
Oh
All right, that was bullshit more tuba reactions. Yeah. All right 5k. That's it. I promise that's it 5k and i'm out
Is this on ipad? Can I get this on ipad? That's five. How do you get the multiplier higher fucking?
What are you doing? Do something? What the fuck? All right, what the hell was that? It's you gotta get the fruits
All right, let me see if I can get 10k. All right times two the coins don't matter that much
I gotta get fruits cherry
Times four come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on times six. This is gonna be 6k
Go
No
Please
Do I get anything from doing it? Do I don't get anything? Oh my god
Oh, i'm addicted to this stupid game get out of the fucking way. Oh my god
Oh
What's that stuff do I don't think i've never touched it oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
Which way was he going? Oh my god fucking damn it. I
Your mic is fucked up. I'm gonna fucking break it. Oh, come on
I have to get 5k or i've refused to turn the stream off
I am not turning the stream off till I get 5000 points in pac-man 200. That's a fact. Why did that blow up?
Don't even don't even don't even what are you doing?
Oh my fucking god jeremy
You had so many up quiet. You're moving too slow
Find me a path. I can go find me one path
Every path is blocked
Find me a single path. I could go down which path blocked blocked blocked blocked blocked blocked
I didn't get that fucking thing
I have to stop doing that. I need to build up a multiplier. No, no, no, no, no
Use the shop. Where's the shop power-ups collect coins to upgrade your power. Oh, I can upgrade
Add it to your loadout upgrade to level one. We're gonna be here all night. I don't like the freeze. That's kind of annoying
How do I activate one of them? Can I actually just use one? How do how do I use that?
Oh, that's just what appears I get it. Okay
Like I've way too gritty unequipped the freeze it kind of sucks, doesn't it? How do I take it off? Oh, okay
That's much better. Let's go
Yeah
Right
Yeah, right you stink. It's fine. I just need fuck. I need 5k big points coming up here tornado
No, no
No, why was he chasing me over here? I know what I can hate this
I saw I I love this game, but I hate it at the same time. I just want 5k and i'm done
You just fucked with me. Why does somebody ghost in the early game here? Get out of here
I didn't trust it you mother fucker
Come on run into me, please. Please run. I've got to get you
Got it. I picked up the fucking thing. I went over one of the pellets. Why are they not?
I don't understand. I picked up a pellet. That's fun. That's the best one so far
That's actually the best one so far orange always goes down
I feel like I should have gotten some points for that
Packing time two times pac-man arrangement under this one and then i'm done. I'll play this once and then i'm the streams over
This one is actually really fun. Isn't it? Yeah, this is just the other one but better that the last two have been way more fun
Yikes didn't want to pick that up. Wow, dude
The fucking analog stick just fucking goddamn controller. Give me the arrow keys instead. That was very greedy
Yeah
My fucking fingers. I need a stick. I need a stick so bad. I need stick 116 000
200 000 points. I think I could go for it. All right, one more go one more go last one five minutes
Let's go arrow keys. I'm going for it. I'm going for 200 000 risky
What who are you? What the fuck was that? Oh my fucking god, dude. Fuck that
unlucky
Me press the wrong fucking button
I couldn't touch it. I i'm seriously so pissed. I need a fucking stick. It's impossible without a stick
200 120 whatever that's so fucking fun. Oh, what a fun game. I can't do it. That's so good
Oh, all right. I think that's it. I'll see you guys. I've been speech jamming myself the whole time
I'll see you guys on sunday. That's gonna be it. We're gonna do some who wants to be a millionaire will do what's my voice?
Who wants to be a million? I just can't listen to it. It just it'd make it. It's making me talk weird
Okay, who wants to be a millionaire deal or no deal? Maybe some wheel of fortune or something. I'll get a bunch
So i'll see you guys sunday sunday
At i'll try to be here at three again three pacific. Let's see if I can pull it back to three
That was a lot of fun multiverses. I actually cannot wait to play more of that when it comes out in july
I want to keep practicing bugs
Even just let me play the practice mode
Kind of a lot. Uh, thanks for joining me though. I'll see you guys in a couple days. Goodbye
We see you again. We see you again those last two pac-man games man
I wish I played those first the seamless co-op mod for elden ring just came out today
I'll have to look into that. I'm very curious about it. You should play more miku that i've had a good time
Multiverses was really fun. Miku was really fun. These last few pac-man games have been really fun
I'm gonna be so
I really want to play that multiverses right now just off stream damn. Okay. I'll see you guys sunday. Take care of yourselves
Call your mother. You should do miku mondays. Nah, I promise the next time you hear me scream
It will not be distorted. I'm gonna get that audio fixed by sunday. I promise I will get it sorted
He's not gonna fix it. He always lies to us. That's his new face. It's a stupid. All right. Good night guys
I'll see you later