Hello. Hi, everybody. Oh, it's muted Marty. Muted Marty. No, I'm here. I'm ready to play a video
game called Yakuza Zero. And I'll give you a couple of quick things before we get started.
Reason why I wasn't live yesterday is because I want to be completely transparent with everybody.
I've started getting a little bit of cold symptoms, congestion in the nose, you probably hear it.
Uh, so I've taken a little bit of time off just over the last couple of days,
started getting a little bit of symptoms on Saturday. I have taken a COVID test.
So just kind of waiting to see what that says. I've been isolating. I haven't gone anywhere,
I haven't done anything. So I'm just gonna, I'm taking precautions here to make sure that,
you know, just in case. If I do, then I'll have to just kind of, I'll try to get through it,
you know, I'll get through it. But I don't think that's what it is. Because I've seen,
you know, how does COVID start, you know, that doesn't typically starts in the chest, but
who knows? I'm just trying to be completely cautious. I don't I want to be totally,
totally, totally safe with this, right? Can you smell? Yes, I can. I can smell, I can taste.
I just am stuffy and a little congested. And it's been like that for the last like,
probably four, three or four days. Hasn't really gone any further than that. Don't have a fever.
We know you smell. You're a baby with a head cold. But I just want to be clear,
if people are like hearing something in my voice and they're like, wait a minute,
what the fuck is going on here, Jerma? I want you to know that I'm already kind of on top of it. So
already on top of it. He's got a new mic. If you do have it go into it with the mindset,
you'll get through it no matter what. Yeah. I've been taking vitamins too. I've been taking
vitamin D. I've been drinking like some vitamin supplemental drinks. My immune system is pretty
good. But I'm we'll see, right? I'll know soon. What is vitamin two? What did I say vitamin two?
I didn't I said vitamin D. I said vitamin two. No, I didn't. Yeah, I'm taking precautions,
you know, I'm taking vitamin two. I don't know. Did I do that? Well, that's weird if I did.
Anyways, let's play Yakuza Zero. It's funny that the title of this stream is I promise I will not
quit this game after three hours like I did last time. I played this before on stream a few years
ago. I stopped playing after three hours. And now I mean, I'm a little under the weather. We'll see
if I get to three hours. We'll see what happens after three hours. But I'll come back to it. No,
I'm no I'm playing this for more than three hours. I promise it's already in the title. It
has to be there. And by the way, there was a bet in pre stream chat too. Let me get this up. Hold
on. It was a pre stream bet that I won. It was it will I will I start the stream before 3pm? And
the answer is yes. If I didn't start before three, I was gonna have to add 100 billion dollars onto
the debt. So I gave myself a lot of incentive. How's the audio for you guys? Can you hear it?
Is it good? A little bit louder? Oh, did I make a tweet? No, I didn't. I didn't even make a tweet
about this. How about Yakuza guaranteed stream? No, I'm already playing it. How about just Yakuza?
Here we go. Yakuza. I don't care. Yakuza. And people won't know which one. So they'll be like,
I'm curious. Is he playing the new one? And they'll come in and inflate my view count.
twitch.tv slash germa985. That's my name, right? Yeah. All right, I'm gonna give this a real shot.
Let's go. New game. I don't recommend it for players who are skilled at action games.
This is the but I don't care. No, not flying on hard. Not flying on hard. He's never gonna finish
this omega lol. Hey, I didn't say I was ever gonna finish it. I said I was gonna play it for more
than three hours. Play hard for 10 million off. No, that's not enough. Normal. I don't care.
You had an opportunity right there. That one guy was like, Oh, if that was like 150 million,
I would have done it. It was your opportunity. Okay, here's a fun experiment. Those of you that
watched the other stream that have access to it, I think it's only the archive channel, right?
Let's see how close this is to the other stream. Play them side by side. I'm gonna make the same
references. No, I'm gonna try to make completely different references. All right, what would I
have said right here? Hi. Nice shoes, man. I'm trying to be different. You're trying hard now.
Fuck, I'm gonna be trying so hard to make like things I wouldn't have made a reference to
be different. It's when he said chat raid forced Mr. Stark to play Nancy Drew. Nice.
Oh, and he did it. That's great. Actually true. He did it. That's awesome. Oh, no, you guys. You
guys now have a new Drew Crew streamer. December 9 1988 in Tokyo. This game about. Oh, the Yakuza,
right? No, Jeremy, it's about like growing up as a doctor.
It's a dentist simulator. Did people recognize me? Oh, I've got what did I say here? I said
something here. I remember this. I think I said like, oh, sorry, I messily ate a hamburger or
something, right? Oh, that was a really good double cheeseburger with extra ketchup. Run it back. Is
that what I said? You said french fries. All right. No, stop telling me what I said. I don't. I'm
going to just be me. You said cheeseburger from Burger King. Fuck. Here's something that I didn't
know. They drive on the other side of the road in Japan. I did not know that. Is the United States,
is the USA the only place that drives on the left side of the road? I mean, on the right side of
that. Wait, hold on. We're the only country on earth that I think is one of the country that
does that that drives on the right side. Arts of Africa do too. Less countries drive on the left.
Oh, at what point in this game do I go?
That was in 30 minutes.
I got a loan.
I got a loan. All right. I'm paying attention. Leave me alone.
I saw the word loan and my character was on the screen. So I was like, I have loan.
All right. Come work for me. Loan shark.
A lot easier than that Yakuza payroll.
By the way, I have to say,
what have you ever stopped and looked over your right shoulder while you were talking to someone?
What the fuck are you doing?
See you around. I think that would be kind of weird.
You just have to tilt a few more degrees and you and I are talking normally.
All right. Here we go. I mean, well, I meant like here comes the music.
Can you dance in this game? I swear to God, every TV movie and every show, every anime,
no one ever smokes a cigarette. It's lit in their mouth and that's it. And then you don't see it
again. Okay. Where's the cigarette? Where is it? He had it. It takes like 10 minutes to smoke
a cigarette. Where is it? Let's see. Nope. Nope. No, no. He had a lit cigarette. The tip was lit.
Oh, there we go. Tip. That's a full cigarette back there in the background.
Smoking is hard to animate. Come on. Have a lit cigarette. Have one, a lit cigarette with just
one puff out of it. Come on. Fuck. Doing the same jokes. Is that the same one? No, it's not. Show me.
That's not the same joke. Show me. Prove it. It can't be. No, it's not. This is where Nishiki said
to meet up me. I guess beat. I, Oh my God. Said he'd meet me. Guess I beat him here.
724106. Huh? That's code four. What you up to? I'm waiting for your slow ass to show up. Is this
when like twitch emotes become absolute language? May as well have a look around and see if I can
find him. Okay. Let's meet him. Find Nishikiyama. Welcome. Oh, this is a save point. Can I save it?
There's a big S. Oh, you can save the game. Use the, and use the item box. And you save.
Million yen vending machine. How much yen do I have? It's a dream machine. Insert a million yen
to make your dreams come true. Maybe. I don't have enough money. I don't have that much. Oh,
well, whatever. Is there a sprint? I'm gonna take a second. I'm gonna just take a quick second.
Okay. All right, let's go. Like I'm already like running.
Wow. While running. Is there a run button?
Let's get in there. Somebody help me, please. Running shakedowns on our turf. Somebody needs
to set them straight before they try anything really stupid. What do you want? This ain't a show.
Oh, it's not. Wait, are you sure he's not Yakuza? So what if he is? He's our age. If he's Yakuza,
he's probably just an errand boy. Wait, let me do this accurately. It'd be a lot lower than this.
And what if we are? My family runs this part of Kamurocho. If you were regulars, you'd know
better than to do anything stupid here. Excuse you? Where's a piece of Yakuza trash? Get off
lecturing us. Yeah, that's more accurate. You can still kind of hear it a little bit.
All right, let's go. No music. What? I remember the fighting in this game was really fun.
It has a really good combat system is what I remember. Holy shit, that guy's annihilated.
Press Y during an X combo to perform a finishing blow. No music? What are you talking about?
Turn up the music. I turned down the music because it's loud. Please, we can't hear it. Hold on.
Is it broken? Yeah, finishing blow knocks me down. The knockdown effect varies depending on
the number of times X is pressed. What are you guys on about? Wait, are you mad because it sounds
like it's coming through a wall? Oh shit, it is. It's like muffled coming through a wall.
What the fuck is going on? What? This is insane. Why do they have a setting where it's like you're
not at the party, but your neighbor is annoying? Okay. All right. I get it. I get it. Does that
just in the menu? All right, here you go. This is your music. This is a finishing blow. One, two,
three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. The yellow gauge on the top is to use your health.
The game will end if the yellow part is fully depleted, so keep an eye on your health at all
times. Yep. If the gauge flashes red, it means you're in a very bad shape and you should
replenish your health immediately. Use a health recovery snack or eat something. Yeah, okay.
Press B to grab someone. If an enemy is guarding to block your attacks, grab them and then attack
to deal damage. Hold on. This guy, why does that guy have rage mode? All right, come here.
One punch in the face. That's like WWF style. You're just letting me punch you in the face
as hard as I can. I'm turning that down. It's a little loud. Your training is now complete.
It's time to wipe the smirks off their faces. Let's go. Grab this guy. Punch him right down
his throat. Grab this guy. Punch him right down his throat. It's a bug. Wait, what? It's an actual
bug in the game? You need to put it in stereo. Wait, what is going on? Like that? Okay, I did it.
It's an in-game engine problem. Oh, well, it's all right. 2900. It sounds worse. What is wrong
with the audio? I'm trying to please put the volume in max.
Restart the game? Well, let me save it first. Hold on.
I like that suit.
The Joker? It's not the Joker. Hey, this came out before the Joker did.
The new movie.
Joker's been around for 80 years. Yeah, but not the new movie that came out like a year ago.
I should put Kazama-san's mind at rest. I don't know about that. He always knew all I could do was
fight. The other one was good at the dance. Different categories. Was it with dancers, fighters?
I'm just reading. I can't read it. Why can't I read this?
Do I have to sit back in my chair and smoke my half-lit cigarette for four hours?
500 grand.
Kazama's father is always in plain clothes.
Passion? Cool.
Oh, you fight this guy. Spoilers for the other stream I did.
Do it.
Signed her jacket. It's a nice jacket. Cigarettes gone, by the way. Cigarettes gone.
I win.
He ate it.
I like the way it burns when it goes down my throat.
Hey, let's go. So what do you guys want me to do? I always hate matching speed in games like this.
Because you always just look like a weird guy that just can't keep up with his friend like,
oh, shit, sorry. I have to tilt this thing. The way these two are interacting. This is just like
two drunk guys on the street. This is how they interact. Oh, sorry. Where do you want to go?
What's still open? That place is open. I don't want to go there, though. This place sucks.
Let's do one more. We can just walk to the hotel.
Same joke. I can't wait to get three hours into this stream,
so I cannot be told I'm doing the same shit. We will cross that threshold,
and I can't possibly do the same thing. We only have three hours of material. No.
All right, let's go. Let's do it. Let's have some fun. You got a Trojan condom ad?
Oh, aren't they targeted ads? Oh, I don't know what you're doing.
Max out the in-game volume? Okay, I will. All right, it's a fight. Oh, this is two drunk guys.
Oh, I remember this. Yep. Okay, avoid exact same thing. Hey, old man, quit talking to those.
We're not done here. Who's an old man? You snot-nosed little punk. Who's a snot? Whatever you said.
Oh, shit, he just did the fucking Pac-Man technique. Now you've done it. Screw it.
They're completely wasted. It's not worth the trouble. Let's take a different road.
I got a faster way to fix this. Oh, yeah, I just need to sober them up a bit with my fists.
Again, I can't tell if you're a sadist or a charity worker. No, well, you sweep the leg,
give them a blanket. Sweep the leg, give them a blanket, and put them in a safe place.
Brunkards. All right, heat gauge. Three blue glowing bars on the top left are called the heat
gauge. The heat gauge starts at first bar, and as your attacks hit enemies, the gauge fills up,
shifting to the second and then third bar. At each level, your speed increases, some moves
and require a certain level of heat. So once you are used to fighting, keep an eye on your heat
level. Once the heat gauge shifts to the second or third bar, Kiryu's body begins to glow with a
little aura. This is called heat mode, and it signals that you can use a special heat action.
Try using heat actions while sobering up the drunkards. What's this? It's CBD pen on stream
for 500 million off the debt. I don't smoke. I don't smoke. No, that's impossible. I don't
have a CBD pen. Okay. All right, press B with the heat gauge at the second or third bar to grab
enemies and then press Y. It's a super punch. That hurts you too. That guy won. How much heat
does this guy have? Okay, your training is now complete. That concludes the explanation of the
heat gauge and special moves, but the two drunkards still need some sobriety beaten into them.
If you take if you take a fighting stance using RB movement with the left stick will center around
the enemy in front of you. This is very effective when you want to focus your attacks on a single
enemy like this guy. Use RB and RB to lock RB to lock onto an enemy. Why do that when you just do
that? Right bumper. What I think I changed. I changed it. Didn't I? Losing to the drunk guys.
No, I have too much health to lose to the drunk guys. It's impossible. Deal update. No,
I'm not taking any drugs right now. Okay. I'm sorry. It's not drug related. It better not be.
If it is, I'm if this is drug related, I'm taking 100 million off the debt. Okay. New deal. All
money collected in Yakuza by the end of the stream will go towards paying off the debt.
Notice yen to USD conversion will apply all money collected. All right. That sounds pretty good.
So all money that so all money collected are all money that I have in my bank account by the end
of the stream. Wait with conversion, wouldn't that? Okay. Collected. End of the game. Whatever.
Okay, Mr. Hero, I'll walk you to the train. Take it slow. Oh, thanks. You're awful considerate
for a kid your age. All's well that ends well. One USD is 100 yen. Okay. Completing certain
challenges for your CP completion points. You can view them for the pause menu under completion
list. Some of the some of the things. Some are things that will probably happen on their own
as you play the game. But yeah, all right. Exchanging CP visit temples or shrines to
access the CP exchange menu where you can spend CP to earn special blessings ranging from being
able to sprint for longer distances or to earning more cash from fights. Okay, cool. What a waste.
A damn shame I say. So just out of curiosity. It's been like this game kind of slow start.
It's been 40 minutes and I've kind of barely just started doing stuff. How did I play this game for
like three hours and stop? I don't understand. What did I say? What? Why did I say? Oh, I'm done.
It's because I was just super like ADHD and I couldn't even handle it. Oh, okay. Yeah. You
want to talk alcohol. You're like taking one swig from a vintage bottle and tossing the rest.
Going from the look of you. You're Japanese mafia. Yeah. Hey, something like that. Yes. Seems like
you're pretty confident in a fight. A real dynamite boy. Calling me boy. Ha ha. Don't get ruffled
now kid. Compared to me, you're practically a toddler. Hey, hear you. What's the hold up, man?
It's nothing. Be right there. No sense wasting time with this drunk. Let's just go. Too much
booze is bad for you gramps. Take care. Hey, now hold up. Wait, I got one piece of advice for you
and I've got a friend waiting for me. If you got something to say, make it quick. Oh,
out for a night with your main dog? Me and the boys used to really wreck it back when I was your
age. But if you spend all your money playing around, you'll never get stronger. You got to
invest in yourself. What? Like a gym membership? No, no, no, no, no, no. That's no better than
spending it on booze. I'm talking about investing in yourself literally. Literally? What's that even
mean? Glad you asked, my boy. Here's a special lecture just for you. Upgrades are now available.
Cool. It's like Path of Exile. I have 232,000 yen. So what do I do first? Throw your entire body
behind a vicious kick. Cool. Max health. Heat gauge will slowly rise over time when you are wounded.
However, it will only fill up to the second bar. Okay. Two million? What is it? Yen what?
Sick. Okay, so the heat gauge just slowly rises when I'm taking when I'm hurt. Pretty sick. Hey,
spend money to make money. That's right. You got to spend money to make money. 200,000?
Oh, I'm considered a brawler. You keep pouring money into yourself with a little training. That
talent of yours will grow in no time. So keep the women in wine on a budget, you hear? Ah,
investing in myself, literally. Never thought of that. Yeah, I bet you're glad you stopped and
listened down, aren't you? Yeah, I guess I am. Yo, Kiryu. I'm coming. Oh, that serious talk killed my
buds. Time for round two. You have a good night, my boy. Is Blackjack in this game?
Whatever. I don't care anymore. What a weird old man. What's his deal?
A nice Irish Japanese guy. Well, it said foreigner, didn't it? Oh, yeah, it did say foreigner. Yeah.
Bacchus isn't Japanese. No, he's the god of wine.
Bacchus is, Bacchus is Greek, yeah. I know my Greek gods. I know when I hover over him in spite
and I select him, he goes, Bacchus. I know his name. He's a big fat guy and he's a big turkey leg.
It's Roman.
Hi, guys.
College girl slash hostess. Madoka-chan and Yui-chan. Hey, one dimensional gamer,
thanks for the den. Thanks a lot.
Well, I want to.
Don't be like that. Here, pick a card, any card. How's money? I thought I was doing like a cool
magic trick. Why don't you get so popular with the ladies? Wait, don't tell me you think I
just let those two play me for 40 grand. Oh, wait, that's, hold on. Who's this?
Okay, if you gave 40 grand to just two random girls that were like, hey, maybe this is the club.
I think you kind of did. You think I just gave two people $40,000 to have fun? Whatever.
I know it's 400, but if it wasn't, this dude's rich as fuck.
I remember when they used to have the two slots in the front for the audio video cables
and it would trail all the way to where your console was and someone would just trip over
and rip the fucking cables out and just ruin your Super Mario session.
It would be like, dad, you would trip and he'd be like, he'd get caught up and go, god damn it.
This is completely unrelated somehow, but it's made me think. One of my friends rented
Rugrats from Blockbuster one time and he hated it so much. It was such a shitty game
that he threw it down his stairs and destroyed it and they had to like pay for it from Blockbuster.
How old was he? I don't know, like 12.
The search for Reptar sucks.
I remember he had a really long staircase, like a very long straight down stairwell.
So this thing just sunk into the well. It was just like
a CD, right? Yeah, it was like PlayStation 1.
Maybe it was N64. It was one of the two. Rugrats was PS1. Yeah,
I like scratched up. It didn't work anymore.
Karaoke is a rhythm game where you press buttons shown on the screen with the song.
Yeah, make sure to press the correct buttons the right time.
When someone else sings, you can support them with interjections. Remember this.
You can choose simple or lively interjections. Sing along, tambourine, maracas. I remember this.
Yep, I do. Yeah, let's go. Oh wait, somebody's done. I have to fix the audio, don't I?
Judgment. I'm going to sing Judgment. Let me turn it up. Is this a meme song?
Oh my god, what is this? Fuck, it's not. I'm sorry.
I don't know the controls. I don't know the buttons. I swear to god.
I have to look down at it sometimes. I don't. Xbox and shit. I'm serious.
I memorize PlayStation, not Xbox. Is anybody else? Anybody else?
Oh, I could kill that. Hold on. I got so into that part. I couldn't sing the rest of it.
Nice, nice, nice, nice. Yeah, X on Xbox versus X on PlayStation. It just messes up my brain.
So I have in my mind have burned the PlayStation controller into my brain.
So if I see X pop up on Xbox, it's like, oh no, wrong. I got 87. That's fine.
Entertain yourself 10 times. Just burn your Xbox brain. You want me to burn my brain?
Let me try to do that fix that people are saying.
I can plant it in that drink.
English. If I change from Japanese to English at this point, I'm going to be attacked.
All right, let me see if I can get this right. So you guys were saying
turn the background volume all the way up. Okay. And then
it's kind of loud from the master all the way up and both all the way up.
What the fuck? Why is it like a waterfall?
Now this is wicked loud.
Oh, okay. So
I turn it down in the mixer.
Okay, I'm turning it down in the mixer and that should be good.
Get off me.
Why does it sound like we're at a water park?
This is just the sounds you hear when you're standing in the line.
Get off me.
Quit doing that like Naruto move where it like splits into two people.
Why can't you have normal audio? I didn't do anything. What did I do wrong?
I didn't do anything wrong. I'm sorry.
I turned the volume down and everybody got mad at me.
A lot of the young males are severely beaten in a quiet corner of Kamurocho.
You know what's happening so far? Yes.
Yep, we got we got cigarettes.
Two just a couple of cigarettes freshly lit.
I thought he was holding a cigarette too for a second. I don't know why.
Oh shit. That's the guy. That's the guy that from the beginning. Yep.
Why'd you do that? There's too many lit cigarettes in here. The fire alarm's going off.
Fellas, can you put them down? And like 30 people in the restaurant look over with the
lit cigarettes like, oh, yes. Oh, oh, sorry.
I'm doing the thing where
somebody that you're watching a movie with has their eyes down on their phone almost the whole
time. And they just say, oh, fuck. What? Because they're humoring you because you're the one that
picked the movie. And they murdered him. Murder. What the fuck, dude? I'm just texting my mom.
How did I not make it three hours? I must have just so badly wanted to leave the game last time.
Why? Because Ubisoft games are bad. Isn't this a Sega game? This isn't Ubisoft.
I've got to call the Jima family HQ. This should be a payphone. Find a payphone. Save. Save it.
Is this, is this in the trash? Where's the save? What? Oh, bro. I look, I'm just looking at the
minimap. A Twitch actor and the nominees for best Twitch actor of the year. German985.
Where's the payphone? Oh my God. Where's the trash?
I'm just sitting in the audience just like, yeah, I'm in the full like three piece suit.
Like clasping hands with the person next to me. The eyes closed and the winner for best
pretender on Twitch. And somebody else and my eyes open. It was supposed to be me.
What was your acceptance speech V? Yeah. Okay. My acceptance speech to win that award. I would
go up there and I'd be like, I would start walking down the aisle and I would trip. Oh,
but it was a joke. I was pretending. Oh, and I would just swipe my head when I got up like,
everyone would laugh their asses off. You do the Willy Wonka. Yeah. I would look around. I'd be
like, where's the podium? I put my hand up like I'm looking out over yonder on something like a
sailing boat. I don't see the podium. And everyone's pointing like it's up there. Oh,
he's lying to pretender. He's doing it. And I'm like, I can't say it. Where is it? Oh, there it
is. I spin around like five times. Pantomime the speech. I'd get up there and pretend the mic
didn't work. I'd be like just moving my mouth with no words. I wouldn't be saying anything.
Get out of the way. $470. That's just a real life children's. No, that's a clown. That's a mime.
I'd be a mime without the makeup on. That'd be so stupid. You're always a clown without the makeup
on silly. God, if I sometimes I wish I just could turn the webcam on right now and just start
going nuts making a balloon animal. Oh, I'll get that ready one day. Oh, that's the guy. I fight
that guy. Spoilers. You probably fight everybody in this room over the course of a 12 hour campaign.
Oh, it's a 70 hour game. Oh,
I feel like when you catch yourself sitting like that, you go. Oh, fuck. You set up straight.
Thank you. Oh, my God. What am I? I'm sitting so
good.
I feel like I posed these guys in G mod to take a thumbnail picture.
Oh,
how do we do that? We simply kill the Batman. Come on. No, I just said it. I just said it for fun.
I wasn't trying to be like funny. I just like had to say it.
Oh, that hurt my head. It probably hurt his leg. That sounded like it really fucking hurt.
That was right in the middle of the shin bone.
So
same joke. No.
Just wait till I get over three hours and I could just get a new goddamn material.
How am I supposed to? It was like three and a half years ago,
even longer. It was like four years ago.
You should have replayed the original stream. Oh, that would have been actually very good idea.
Let's see if you guys figure it out.
I'm going to play the VOD from this point. Let's see what happens.
Everybody hold on a sec. You ready for this shit? We're going to have a little bit of fun.
I'm going to play it from this exact moment. One sec.
This guy's name is Bacchus.
All right. How far did I get? Did I do things in a different order?
Okay. So did that happen yet? Did this part happen yet?
I gotta get the right spot. Okay. So right when the cut scene ends,
I don't want to see any of the jokes. I don't want to see if I want to see if I do it the same way.
Come on, give me it. All right. Here it is. It loads up right here at one hour and okay.
Now loading. I have a better computer. I have a better computer.
Okay. I got the spot. It's one hour, one minute and 27 seconds.
Oh, no, no. Fuck this game. This game sucks. I don't own it. I don't play it. I'll never play
it again. It's a dick. I hate this game. Bastion's not the most beautiful zone. Now,
Drac, this is not a cool. Obviously, I'm going to. All right. 101 27. I thought something was
really funny right there. All right. 101 27. Thanks for the 256. I'm going to be thanking subs.
101 27. Whatever the next cut scene is, I think I'm going to have to skip it.
All right. We're in an in-game cut scene. That might be that. Okay. Here we go.
And it's going to be like here. All right. Let's get this out of the way.
I got to get this in the right spot. Okay. So remember, it's like right when the camera pans
and we go wrong cut scene. No, it's not. Oh, sick cigarette. He took at least a third of that off
with that hall. By the way, I should probably mute this audio from me so I don't hear what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Keep it. All right. Fine.
Oh, Germany is German Spaniard. No, he's not. I'll make sure he's not.
Oh, you're bored already. No, I'm not. I'm just I'm not going to do this the whole time.
I'm just going to do this for a few minutes. He wouldn't do this if he wasn't bored. I'm not
bored. I'm going to give it the chance it deserves, but I'm just give me a minute.
I'm not bored. I'm not bored. Are you sure you don't like the TV show, dude? You're looking at
your phone a lot. Well, we say I'm watching some I'm watching the time that I watched the movie
four years ago on my phone. That's kind of fucking weird. Why don't you just watch
the movie with me? I was wondering what my reactions were four years ago.
Yeah, what a psycho. What like an egomaniac. Like dude, the movie's on the screen right now.
Man, you don't have to watch you reacting to the movie we're currently watching now.
Just watch the movie with me. I got to be way funnier than past Jeremy. This is important.
He thinks he's going to fucking win. Nope. Do the Mario Kart ghost. Yeah, I'm going to
I'll change that. I'll make the transparency smaller. I'll make it. I'll do it. I just got to
get in the right spot. OK, here we go. This is important against my ghost. Here we go. Ready?
I got to get a time that's right. Loading screen. Here comes the pan. And there it is. OK,
we have synced up the timelines. I am going against my Mario Kart ghost. Can I be funnier
than my Mario Kart ghost? Let's see. I got to change the opacity on it, though. Filter is
uh, opacity. Where's opacity? How come I can't drop the opacity? Color correction? No.
Maybe it is color. No. Promo? OK, here we go. This should be do it. There we go. OK,
there's my my my Mario Kart ghost is here. Should it be over the whole thing?
No, I can't. I can't. That's going to make people puke. People are going to get sick.
I'm going to drop the opacity a little more. That's too much. Mario Kart ghost. OK, it's at 50%.
All right, I'm ready. I'm ready. Here we go. You ready? I'm going to kick my ass. Three, two,
one, go. I'm going to get a text message from fucking what's the guy's name? Looks like your
loan shark has met me up. Alec, the guy that wants to go bowling. What's his name? The cousin.
Fuck, you heard GTA reference. Derek, what's his name? What's the guy's name that wants to
always go bowling? Nico. No, not that. Shut up, you. Stop showing me that guy.
Nick, not Nico. What's the other guy's name? Roman. Why am I still frozen on the other screen?
Not this guy again. Wait, why is this frozen? I think Derek. Wait, pause it. Pause it. Yeah,
the old guy from last night. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And I found this guy, too. No, it's frozen.
No, no, I froze it. I teach you how to put points. No, he's so much funnier than me already. Where
did it go? And this guy is. Why did that happen? Fuck. Hold on. Oh, fuck. Come on. The stupid OBS
sucks. Hold on. I'm going to get a text message from fucking what's the guy's name? Alec. Alec,
the guy that wants to go bowling. What's his name? The cousin. I teach you how to put. OK,
here it is. Oh, you're. Let's get it lined up. Derek, what's his name? What's the guy's name
that wants to always go bowling? Fuck Streamlabs OBS. It sucks. Stop showing me that guy. All right,
hold on. Here we go. Nick, not Nico. What's the other guy's name? Roman. There it is.
Here we go. Ready? Not this guy again. Oh, you're the guy from last night. OK, three, two, one,
go. Derek. Oh, the old guy from last night. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I've been searching for hours.
And I found this guy, too. For me. You Rika booze. You're wasted. I teach you how to put points.
I just. And this guy is going to teach you how to do things.
No, fuck. He's past German's going too fast.
That's somebody's having a good morning. They're really they're really angry,
really angry people in time to fight. I got it. I got to go faster than a kid.
Is this the same two guys, three guys that were in the alleyway before?
Yeah, you mentioned you've been looking for me. Actually, wait, hey, what'd you get? Hey,
what'd you get those elbow pads for football from the 1930s? Yeah, I did.
So we they're asking for money. Obviously, I'm going to kick the shit out of these guys.
I'm going to beat them up and he's going to teach me something.
I don't know which one's even real. This hurts my head. I can't look at this.
You think he'd beat you? No, I don't know. That's a great question to ask them. They're
really eager to talk to you. Don't take don't don't bait the streamer into doing something
stupid that he doesn't want to do. Oh, hey, speak of the devil. Here they are now.
Okay. All right, Gramps. Is this the kid? Yes, sir. My prize pupil. Sorry, pupil. This guy's
just like doesn't feel well. The million you lent the million yen loan that I get those two dead
beasts is way past due. I need it back. I ain't waiting much longer. You'll tell me about it.
Wait, I tell you about it. Wait, expect me to tell you. I can't even talk. I can't even talk.
I have to lower it. It's making me want to throw up. All right. There. That's better. Come on.
All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. All right. Wait, he's ahead of me. He's ahead of me.
This guy's definitely like a master boxer. No, no, no, no. Go, go, go. He's way ahead of me.
Okay. All right. Pay the money. Wise choice. You want to pay me double? I got to beat him.
No. All right. Let's go. Fight me, you bastards. Teach this whippersnapper how to fight.
You'll be fine. Just a little workout and fight. All right. I got to kick the shit out of this guy
right now. Is that me just daydreaming about how I wish I could do that?
I can't skip the cutscene. That was so much funnier. Okay. It's my turn. That's a great
smash intro. That's a great like I just won Smash Brothers against like four friends.
I did say this was going to be a movie in the very beginning. I tried to win you guys.
Okay. Here we go. I heard the word murder parade. He's fine. Told you. Didn't a big guy. I didn't
punch him. Go, go, go. That's the same joke but worse. No, it's not. It's better.
Okay. I meant when I said it wouldn't. You already saw the video. He said it.
All right. Then round two. I know how to play already. I'm going to kick it. Okay. I'm almost
ahead. I'm almost ahead. I'm almost ahead. It's free thug. Let's go. You can switch to rush style
by pressing. I don't care. I was going to get ahead of him. Old German was terrible at video
games. Actually, he's way better. You can evade. Yep. Evade nine times. How many times has he
evaded? He's so ahead of me. Come on. All right. Use rush style moves to crush Bruno and show him
who's boss. When using the rush style, you can stun enemies by hitting them a certain number of
times. Attacks on stunned enemies will knock them down without fail. All right. Let's go.
Old German pog. No, don't say that. Old German sucks. New German. New Vegas art. I think I beat
him. Wait, how much health? I'm beating him. I'm winning. He hit me with every move.
Come on. I got to dodge. I'm not dodging. Come on, please. All right. Give me a little bit of slack.
I'm hearing myself fucking talk and I'm hearing the audio twice.
It's circle, right? That's cool. Cool. All right. We're good. Are we done with the tutorial?
What? How much longer is the tutorial? No. Yeah, we already were. What family are you guys from?
Wait, you're a Yakuza? I'm so sorry, sir. I didn't know we work for Toko credit.
Name's Kiryu. Dojima family. What family are you guys with? Boss, the president. Wait,
you're a proper Yakuza? Sorry, sir. I didn't know we just work for Toko credit.
Well, there's no coincidence. I have business with your boss. I need to meet him. Fuck,
I got to pull that out. President, I figured he'd be at the office this hour.
I see. That's in a building on Tehei Boulevard East, right? I'll pay him a visit then.
This is the real fun stuff. Well, I can't wait to have a ton of fucking fun on Thursday.
I can't. I can't. It's hurting me. This guy's name is Bacchus. I'm sorry, guys. I just skipped a
little bit. This guy can teach me a lot about fighting. OK, in the parking lot. OK, so this
guy's in the parking lot. This guy hangs out and drinks and like levels you up. And there's a guy
at a bank like I know this is going to be fun. I can't wait. This guy wants me to box for a living
and like he wants to make money. Well, it's karaoke. You guys hear me? Anybody hear me?
I'm like fading out of it. I feel weird. What's fucking happening? OK, so I got to go to the bank.
Oh, no, no, I'm I'm denial. Oh, fuck. What an idiotic thing to do. I went back in time
and I fuck with the timelines. I'm trying to replace myself. No, this is weird. I feel like
I'm drunk. The fuck? Why can't I go in here? No, I'm I feel I taste I taste like metal
out of my way. Anybody hear me? Uh, OK, let's just do this. Get this out of the way. No, I have to
stop and catch my I can run more than this guy. How sad is that? This guy's like a mastermind
Yakuza assassin. He can sprint down an alley and then he has to catch his breath. I can run
like a mile like that. I could run a full sprint mile. This guy can't even do it around a fucking
corner. Get ready for this. No, go in the building. Like, what do you mean get go get ready?
I want to get through this as fast as possible. I'm ready. Oh, maybe I wasn't ready.
I'm ready. These guys all have like weapons. What are you doing here, punk?
It's like the same guy.
OK, no interest in speaking with me. That's fine.
This is the first test. This is the first test of real raw game.
Time to go. Oh, go credit men. They have pipes. Let's go into our dodge.
Um, that was kind of fun. But where am I? I better get moving. Come on, Bruno. Pick it up.
Wait, I just saw the birth of Jesus. And then it's it's it's leaving. It's leaving.
That's all the dinosaurs die. It's leaving. It's leaving. It's leaving. It's leaving.
No, no, no, no. They were swimming. What? No, no, no, no, no. It's gone. It's gone. What's happening?
I um, hey, tell me something. Oh, just who are you? Why approach me? What are you after me? Yes.
Well, people here call me Bacchus and I come here because you had me angry at one time.
Yeah, nice of you to dump him on me. Look, if you're in some trouble, tell me. Maybe I can help.
And that goes for him too. Those weren't the moves of an amateur. What's his deal?
A real steal of a deal is what it is. He's got a gig sweatier than honey.
He's fascinating to watch. You should go have a look too.
At Comedio's job, but he's homeless, right? What kind of work does he do?
He's a whatchamacallit. A fristing artist.
Whoa, that's not really my scene. Let's punch out.
Yeah, that. A punch out artist. A slip of the tongue. All right, so what's a punch out artist?
The customer pays a fee and then they get to throw as many punches at me as they like.
I don't think I follow. This is a new S&M thing.
No, nothing like that. Come on and watch. If you've got questions, I work in the Shichufuku
parking lot. Jimo-kun, he's got plenty to teach about fighting, my boy.
You'll kick yourself if you don't check it out.
All right, I'll get the picture. Parking lot, right? I swing by if I can.
It's Kira-san from the Dojima family, right? I'll be waiting. See you soon.
Okay. Sorry, what am I gonna go here?
Well, that takes care of my troubles for today, I suppose. Still can't convince you to take on the
world. The world? What does it even mean? Are you still trying to recruit me into the pro fighting
scene? It's exactly what it was. You got potential most men can't even dream about.
That would champ the title be yours. Sorry, I'm not the same starry-eyed kid who would fall for
that kind of line. You look at a scout, somebody keep looking. I'll tell you one thing, boy. You
keep living street fight to street fight. You'll wind up with a knife between your ribs. It's a
dark alley. That's no way to go out. You belong in the light, the spotlight, and I can't get you
under the brightest ones. What do you say? Okay. We just met. You're not wanting to change your
life around because some old geezer told you to. So I'll give up. That doesn't mean giving up for
good. You got room to grow like a tree. I'll keep coaching you along the way. You've got skills as
a trainer. That much I believe. But I'm not really in a position to be worrying about that. Sorry,
but hey, maybe I'll see you around. Okay, my boy. Just steer clear of the dark alley still then,
you hear? No knives in those ribs or bullets for that matter. Are you trying to jinx me? You see
you later, Pockus. Okay. Apparently the Toko credit president's in his office on Tai Boulevard East.
I'll start there. All right, let's go. I'm gonna head down this way. I'm stuck. Oh, oh, oh, what's
oh. Oh, man. These guys. Oh, shit. These guys got weapons. What? Never mind. These guys have
weapons. No, they don't. What? I don't have any weapons. Why did I say that? He's punching the
air. What do I think of the game so far? Jokes aside. I don't know. See me when I after three
hours. Boring. It's not boring. I can't I'm not saying that yet. Okay, so I go in here or why
in the trash? What am I looking at here? What's what is what's here? The front? The door? Oh,
I tried to click on this. I hit a on this like three times. All right, let's get ready first.
Uh, let me save the game. Go to karaoke. No, hold on. Not yet. That bastard. All right,
let's get some exp. I'm not gonna go play blackjack. Let me play the game first. I'm
not gonna go play blackjack. Go play Mahjong. No, I want to play. Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
Leave me alone. Leave me alone. Leave me alone. Oh, my God. I'm sorry, sir. Yeah, good. Well,
you know, let's just do the first mission. Let's do it. I'm ready. Mahjong is more entertaining
than the game. There's a great link. No, no, I have to get to the. Okay, I will link this
because this is funny. This is funny. It's very good. I feel like I've aged that much too.
What's with the huge amount of subs? Forty two community subs from bingo. Bingo Julius
just gave 42 subs. Oh, my God. That's too many subs. Thank you. Thank you, bingo. That's insane.
Oh, these guys are toast.
Worst joke.
All right, it's time to play the game. We had our fun. Now I want to actually do good.
Breaking. So, um, I have how do I activate the rush? I kind of wasn't paying attention to that.
I'll be honest. It is activated. How do I press V? No, no, no, on a controller.
Left on D pad. There it is. Thank you. Any more snacks? What the fuck? All right, here we go,
brother. Oh, that's right. This stances. Right. This game is sick. Oh, I missed the cutscene.
Right in the head. Forced enjoyment. Dude, I'm having so much fun in this game. Sick. Nice. Cool.
Cool. Sick. Sick. It is fun. How do I get health? I'm running out. No way. How'd you make it here?
Snacks, right?
Tell me everything.
All right, this is what I'm talking about.
Oh,
back in the day, one punch was enough to straighten out little shits like you.
What do you mean back in the day? Like when I was a kid? Like when I was like,
how old was I? What the fuck are you talking about?
How long have I known this guy for? He's like in his 50s. Oh, no, not a cigarette.
It's no shame.
You'd listen to this dead air streamer.
Cool.
King of Dead Air. Well, it's a cutscene. Every time I talk over cutscenes, people get so mad at me.
They're like, shut up, you fucking asshole. We're trying to watch the movie.
You can be funny. I'm in a cutscene. I can't. What am I going to do?
Walk up to the TV and like turn it off and turn it on and turn it off and like, no,
like watch the movie. Imagine watching a movie with one of your friends and you're just like,
oh, hey, dude, by the way, like, hey, it'd be funny. What? I guess like, I'm going to stick
my tongue out. You're going to get up and like turn the TV off. I'm going to get like pots and
pans in your kitchen and like you just wait.
No, it's fine.
Are you going to cry? No. What?
All right. So I got a spy on this guy, but like, I'm not going to betray my friend.
That's my beeper. 719348. It's not a number I recognize. Who is it? I don't recognize the
number. It's not his number, but that's got to be Nishiki calling. I'll find a phone and call him
back. It has me worried. I got to find a payphone. I am trying to find a payphone. What are you doing?
Oh, it's blocked. Okay. I was going to say there's a save point right there.
Wait. Oh, it's delinquents. Let's go. Come on. Oh, nice. Be a good dog. Get off. What? Oh,
shit. Why did I swing backwards? I got to spend some money. How much money do I have?
Let me go. Just save it for the debt. No, I want to play. I want to do cool things.
The debt deal. Yeah, I know. I want to like do
slot machines and stuff. Wait, dream machine. How much money do I have? I can't. The debt is
the total collected. Okay. What the office? Okay. What are you doing there?
Hmm. Bingo Julius again. With 18 more subs. Oh my god. 42. That's 52. That's 60.
Community subs today. That's a lot of money. Thank you. Bingo Julius. That's insane.
Okay. That's like a green Elmo phone. I've never seen a green phone before like that.
All right. So can I look at the map? Okay. I need to go buy stuff. Okay. Here we go.
Hey, our food. Okay. Yeah. This place, the place for soba noodles. We're going there.
Maybe I'll grab a bite at Fuji soba. Yes. Soba and hot broth. This house classic
features freshly boiled soba noodles served in a piping hot homemade soup.
That sounds pretty good. Fried pork cutlet bowl. Yeah. Thank you for waiting. Delicious.
I want another one, but a small one. Have you ever been to Japan? I have not. I've always wanted to
go. Let's get the cheap one. I feel like before I die, I want to go to Tokyo. I just want to,
right? There's a lot of places I want to go. Japan sounds cool. I want to go to Europe. I've never
left continental North America, guys. It's down here. I want to see, what's this? Sega high tech
land. Let me in. Let me in. I'm too old to go in. No. What? Other door? What do you mean other door?
This is the door. Left? Wait, I can't go in that door. No, I can't go in any of the doors.
What's over here? I'm going to do the mission. I need to buy healing items. Yeah. I'm going to
go to like the drug store, right? Oh, store. Discount store with many items. Wait, there's
one right here. Convenience store. All right. I'm going to the convenience store. I've got nothing
in my inventory. Grab me a soda. Which one? That one. All right. Hello. Toughness Z comes in handy
when you need a little health boost. Charges up your heat. Stamina X. Charges up your health and
heat a little. That's expensive. Is this kind of like, it's like Final Fantasy. We just buy like
a hundred of these. Okay. Also, I want a spicy chashu ramen. We'll get like two of these,
like three of these. I don't know. What else is here? Seaweed rice ball. What do these do?
Oh, bento lunch. Yeah, I'll take five of these. No, I'll take, no, too many. Steamed bun milk. Yeah,
I'll take three milks. Okay. Wait, what? How come I got, did I get some free? I'm stuck in the
grocery store. My body's too big to go walk down the aisle. Go upgrade. Oh, wait, how do I do that?
Equipment abilities. Russian brawler. Okay. How do I, I have to go find his,
that go to that dude's place, right? Yeah, brawler is a lot of fun. What do you want? You got pocket
tissues. You're just, you're just gonna rob me? In abilities. Okay. All right. Brawler. I got a million
yen. Ooh, throw your entire body behind a vicious kick while running. Yep. Either that or max health.
That wasn't very much. All right, we're going to do kick too. I said while running, you do why
and you do a vicious kick. Anything else I can do? No, two million, two million and two million.
All right. I think I'm ready. Wait. Yeah, let's, I want to test it out. Let's go. Toons. That's
pretty good. That's pretty good. Nice. It's a fall drop kick. Rush is good with boosting for dodges.
Check for rush. Oh, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. It's a different, it's a completely different tree.
Okay. 400. This is power of your regular attacks and heat actions while using rush style. Cool.
Immediate recover or max health. I mean, just go max health and then max health again. I probably
should, I probably should wait. I don't want to just spend all my points and spread it out too
much. I got to pick one. I'm so switching stances. Not fair. Yeah. I said timeout. Oh, he was
switching stances too. Sorry. He said the same thing. Save it. Money's really easy to get later
on. Cool. I'm into it. Go to the shrine. Uh, the shrine. The shrine? I don't see a shrine. It's
yellow. Theater. You just passed it. Well, I don't know what the hell it is. There's a yellow icon.
It's a store. Oh, okay. Oh, so it's right there. It's behind me. Going the right way, right? Yeah.
All right. Yeah. Oh, I remember this part. Oh, I remember this. Yeah. It's me, Bob. Guess what I
have for you. Dragon of Dojima pack. Kumarucho fun pack. Oh, it's just free. Pocket circuit expert
pack. Um, I guess I'll take the dragon of Dojima pack. Oh, it's an outfit. Modified model gun.
Stone of enduring. You only, you're only getting this once. So take care of it. What? Okay. Exchange.
Gotta go fast. Level one. How much, um, what do I have for CP? I have three. Dash for longer.
Recover more quickly. Money magnet. Gather more money from enemies. Kind of like that one. Oh,
that's six. Hmm. I'm going to hold them. I'm going to hold them for now. Okay. Let's go. Let's start
the mission. I got plenty of items. Save the game first. It's important. Go do karaoke first. No,
I'm not going to do karaoke the first. No, I already did karaoke once. Let's do the mission.
Let's go. I will do karaoke. I'll do all the mini game stuff.
Karaoke now.
All right. When I wasn't looking, it kind of sounded like he was ripping a bunch of
tape. He was taping a bunch of shit up on the desk.
Did he ask you to sell out Kazama? He did.
Bastard.
Somebody framed him.
Well, you see, it all started when I went into his office and what if it just plays
that cut scene again, but with a filter on it. They would do that.
I had my hand around my neck. It's three. What?
So I was rubbing my neck. I was rubbing and I went like this.
I am paying attention. Yes, I am. He's just choking himself instead of watching the cut
scene. No, I am paying attention to the cut scene. And this dude is fucking strangling himself.
Do you not like the movie? We can put on like designers,
drive-ins and dives if you want. No, man. I love this fucking movie. It's great.
He's choking himself. I can't. I got to mute.
What the hell?
Well, summarize this cut scene. Okay. Yeah, I can.
So this is the boss. This is one of the bosses.
Guys, I don't even know this person's name. I don't know the main character's name.
What's his name? Kiryu. Kiryu. Fuck, I'm sorry.
We're trying to get rid of the other boss. There's three bosses, four bosses.
We're all fighting over the same place.
I'm watching a foreign film without subtitles because I'm like reading chat too. So I'm not
absorbing any of this. Like if it was English, I would be able to hear a lot of this too. I'm
hanging out with you guys reading chat and I'm just hearing Japanese. That's not good.
No, I'm good. I'm good. We got to watch our asses. Watch ourselves.
Focus on the game for 10 minutes. Okay, I will. I swear to God.
I'm not looking at chat. I'm going to focus for 10 straight minutes.
I'm responsible. What am I responsible for? Let's see.
Okay, Kazama. We don't want him to come back to Kazama.
I'm taking the fall for this.
Oh, man. Okay.
I'm going to care this one myself.
All right. So then I'm not tied to like the Yakuza family, right?
The Yakuza, right? Okay.
I want out.
Let's go. We're going to settle this right now.
They're framing people. They're framing people.
Whoa.
Okay. He's playing PUBG on his phone right now. If I just had it like the sound effects.
I don't have it installed. Stop reading chat. He was lying on the ground with a painful face.
I can pay attention. I can look away for a second. He's like there's no dialogue there.
And now we're framed for the murder of the guy in the beginning. We're out of the family.
Now we're trying to stop these guys from framing people for murders, especially when it's me.
You can't just leave. You can't get out, right? Let's go.
A bad deal in chat? No, I'm ready. I'm ready to complete.
What was the VOD for the last one? Three hours and what? 335. Okay.
We've looked up to you. Won't let us be in Yakuza.
I thought he was like driving. Is he driving? Pay attention. What the fuck? Oh God. I thought
he was like driving the car and just off. He's in his own world. I'm like holy shit dude. What
are you doing? Finally, you say something. We're watching a fucking cut scene.
Every so often, I'm going to take the back of my hand and get you in the chest.
You see that? They wanted to be Yakuza. I'm paying attention.
This next part, man. I can't wait to pay attention to this part.
He's secretly just leveling in Maldraxxus right now.
Yeah, I'm really going to stop treating the cut scenes in this game like I'm in a league
queue. Yeah, whatever. I'm just going to play like fucking Picross for like 12 minutes until
a queue pops. Oh, there's still a lot of subs that I missed too.
We had five from Swiggity Swanky. Thank you. Five from GrillmasterXBBQ1776. Thank you. Ten from
Zurich. Thanks guys. Three subs. Appreciate it. He's here. I remember this part. I remember giving
up like shortly after this part. Yes, I want out of the family. Spell me. Please let me through.
Ah, ah. What a shame. I shouldn't have said that.
It's my favorite stream zone.
My father's favorite TV show.
Derp on a night five.
If it was a story, I'd like to smell it.
Plus two. Plus two. Plus two. Plus two. Plus two. Plus two. That was really funny. Plus two.
You don't even have a lot of money.
You're just saying hello to me with your bare hands. Are you kidding me?
I'm not here to talk to you. Where's the head of the gang?
I'm the one who's in charge of the gang right now.
I'll be careful with the way you talk.
You're a good boy.
I won't bring any money.
I just want to say hello to you.
Hey!
If you want to be a student, go ahead.
The world of Gokudo isn't that bad.
I'm going to get rid of everything now.
I'm still here to listen to the news.
40 minutes until the stream ends.
No! I have to be longer than that.
I cannot stop at the same place.
So you're going to see the boss of the gang?
He came to take your permission.
The answer was no.
Is that so?
Then you're not going to become a servant, are you?
Yakuza is a Scorsese film that is occasionally interrupted by an episode of The Simpsons.
What?
That was pretty great that was great fantastic when we get a clap for that one guy moment
that was pretty that was really good all right it's time to kick somebody's ass
oh you say that not you know what the fuck
oh now you did it now you've done it it's time to activate
hmm it's time to boy it's time to boy I like that table all right let's go 1v30
Oh activate brawl mode brawl activated pick up the couch
illegal books what is an illegal book oh whoops no legal books
oh let's go that person instantly died you yeah that's not you don't defeat in quotes that
person that person is dead stop stop it stop it stop it oh that was the guy that I had that was
the main guy this is dead rising oh my god that would hurt so bad pick up the table give me the
table what else can I grab what else can I grab the TV give me the TV oh I can't do the TV really
money box of nails how would you have a box of nails in this room ow murder somebody with the
nails I think I've lost my opportunity well so for this guy oh it's him what what's going on
let's go get the sofa out of the fucking way oh what's that sorry you missed getting a little
exciting here I think getting a little excitement holy fuck all right should I drink one of those
drinks oh oh who's left what's this toughness oh that's that's that's all right I dropped the
bat why would I put the bat down let's grab him grab him and just smash his head into the boxes
brush he dodged it no you're better than I am we're good who's left who's left who's left who's
left whoa one punch in space dead no brawler me that and get no give me the bat block did
how did I not block that what was it the other guy oh no okay grab the box of nails grab the
box of nails grab the box of nails nails nails nails nails I got the nails I got the nails whoa
did he throw it be waiting for me to eat drink oh yeah let's go okay now let's kill this guy with
the nails all right all right all right nice I killed him but no I didn't not gonna fail QC's
right now Kevin stay down oh that hurts this stool stool is a great weapon by the way you got one
side you got sharp side it's like a hammer hammer is the best weapon if I was in medieval times I'd
use a hammer doesn't matter what kind of hammer I know well you want like one of those iron like
super hammers big ones no no just a regular just Home Depot hammer medieval Home Depot hammer no
you know what I mean they have a medieval section at Home Depot here are the swords the Mesa's
all right give me just stool this guy the head I've missed it it's hard to see back to 300,000
all right just I'm gonna dig this into his head oh my god I'm queuing it up that's awesome what
a cool move no nice nice how's the game so far Jeremy um this part's good that I like this part
block from the other side damn he likes it I like yeah I like the Simpsons episodes all right they
just have peeing right this is gross gross all right I'm gonna smash everybody's head into the
sink that's all I want to do no into the stall put somebody's head in the stall come here into
the toilet come here get him in the sink into the sink oh no I can't like put I can't like put his
mouth into the water it's me again this time I have a knife stool didn't work the plate didn't
work into the urinal into the urinal let's go oh oh fuck that hurts oh my side get up
right get over here good no I can't grab him and do that I'll throw him out the window my
god are you lost all my points come over the window can I throw him out the window can I
actually do that get out the window all right out the window he's almost dead hurry in the urinal
hurry there it is out the window get him oh by the way is this a Simpsons episode or is
this a family guy episode like the chicken keeps coming back and trying to kill me for like 10
straight minutes that drink where are they didn't wash his hands it's the WWE part
gotta get through me first I mean I played this part
it's time to fight versus go go go go go go go go go go go the Gima family lieutenant
Tojo clan that couldn't read it I'm a brawler come on one-on-one let's go oh what's that oh
so hard can't even do anything oh what's that I grab you that I own the family now my family
see what I did to that family guy chicken for the last 20 minutes now oh oh he was warming up he's
just warming up we're good okay he's and I'm gonna get him again get it get it get it get it get it
get it get it get it get it get it get it get it get it oh he's got fire oh shit okay we're good
turn the difficulty up it's not on easy it's not no not only turn difficulty up right now what do
you mean it's too easy it's not easy it's challenging it's challenging combat with some
quick times use different heat actions oh I hold on we'll talk about that later how I got too
confident take take a break hold on I need a drink chucking estus but BM was that okay let
me win fucking come on stop fuck I'm gonna get my ass kicked fuck you I'm switching stances
get him on the ground grab no you dick big finish I have to end it like that yeah that was fun
phase two of ten yeah patriarch of the dojima family
Kazama no
it's not true it's not true not true no don't those lies about me
a coca-cola
Oh
Oh man, it's a total cross, total double cross.
Oh, he's got, yeah, he's got to cut off his, uh, he's got to cut...
No, this is not the Simpsons episode part.
Hmm, as of today, you are expelled from the family.
Thanks, but I just want to let you know, I'm coming for all of you. Eventually.
Oh, thanks for like the tweet explaining the story.
I didn't know anything up till right now.
Perfect, I know exactly what's going on now.
Killer.
Simpsons.
That's pretty good episode.
Stream. Oh my God, stream is gone.
It's over. Oh shit, I forgot.
It's no sorry. I was playing it through the microphone. I was playing it through the microphone.
It doesn't matter. That was me singing that. There's me humming it with my mouth.
Was this like a jazz version? What is this?
This doesn't happen in the Simpsons theme song.
This is not the Simpsons theme song. That's like a completely different version.
Look at the game. Oh, right. All right, we got an umbrella.
Somebody under an umbrella and they're teaching us something.
They've been waiting for us for a long time.
I've been waiting. Yes, I knew it.
Chapter one. 12 million, 12 million yen. Nice.
IMAX battles have opened. Save it.
Chapter two, the real estate broker in the shadows. Cool.
Big windows. I talked about that already.
I don't think you can see everything.
You're just a giant TV show for everybody that looks up.
There's no danger to me.
Mr. Kiryu, please relax.
Tinted? Well, all right.
So sure. Tinted windows. Would you stand naked in front of that window?
No, you wouldn't.
I'll pay you back right away.
Mr. Tachibana.
Yes, please rest assured.
I am a man of my own.
In Kamurocho, I'm asking for real estate.
Real estate? What does that look like to me?
You really don't eat?
What's for dinner?
What do we have?
The right hand is a technique.
It's a way to forgive.
After losing it a few years ago, it hurts when it gets cold.
It's a strange thing.
It doesn't work on the fingertips, and it doesn't work on the painkillers.
I just endure the pain in the middle of the day.
But it's a hassle to put pain on my face, so I quit.
I didn't hear that.
Mr. Kiryu, do you know the word Tojo Kajo?
Tojo?
Tojo.
Tojo Kajo.
Many flowers gather together and become one big flower.
In fact, some of the flowers you know are Tojo Kajo.
What are you talking about?
It's a sunflower.
That's true.
They're beautiful. That's true.
It's a good name to use for a child's kindergarten.
Kazama-san named you sunflower?
You.
You grew up with Nishikiyama-san and your brothers in sunflower.
Another one.
Yumi Sawamura-san, a young lady.
Eventually, you and Nishikiyama-san followed Kazama-san as parents.
Then you entered the world of Jokudo.
And now you're wearing a murder suit.
Because of that, Kazama-san is in danger.
I know what my life was.
I understand that you investigated me.
You have a lot of information.
But why did you investigate me?
What is your purpose?
You don't know, he knows.
No, that's right.
Empty lot.
That bread.
I want that bread right now.
If we get the empty lot, then Kazama's expulsion is guaranteed.
If we don't get rid of your eagerness.
Our information in Kamurocho is a little bit.
If you join hands with me, you can definitely finish the criminal.
Why are you trying to drag me into this?
What is your real purpose?
Give me back my clothes, Tachibana-san.
I'm begging you.
Kobamuto.
Your story is too convenient for me.
At times like this, you have to be careful.
There's no way you can survive.
I see.
It seems you've been looking a little too sweet.
But I believe you'll think about it some day.
At least, can you take this card with you?
I understand.
I'll bring the clothes right away.
Well then, I'll be going.
That's not necessarily true.
I mean, look at Metal Gear Solid 3.
Metal Gear Solid 4.
Wasn't that game like 4 hours of cutscenes before you pressed B to punch anybody?
Look at that series, right?
Alright, so here we are.
Let's save it.
Is the arcade open?
If it is, you know exactly where I'm going.
Alright, so let's take a look at the map.
Alright, so we have Sega High Tech Land and the bowling alley.
I want to go to High Tech Land.
Is this Sega High Tech Land?
No?
Wait, did I?
Okay, yeah, that's it.
Where is it?
Wrong way?
Entrance is on the other side.
Oh.
I don't have time to fight you.
I want to play video games.
Leave me alone.
This is dumb.
No, it's not.
Yes.
Okay, I've never done this before.
Is this fun in here?
Oh my god, yes.
How much is it?
300 yen for three games.
Let's go.
Okay, Move Claw.
That's it right there.
I got it.
And that's a pink one too.
It's rare.
It's worth so much more.
I'll take it.
What's it worth?
Funchan.
Nice.
Alright, cool.
I got two more.
Give me the other pink one.
Nope, I fucked it up.
I might still get it.
It's possible.
I might get it.
Oh, I got to get him.
He's hanging out back there.
I have to get him.
That's a good start.
There it is.
I'll take it home with me.
I'm going to put it on the wall.
That's the one right there.
Scoop him.
Yes.
Oh, it's alright.
I got one.
It's alright.
What else is in here?
Can I play these?
Is this Galaga?
Space Harrier.
100 to play.
Of course I do.
I'll give it a go.
Space Harrier?
Fire.
Select.
Insert.
Credit.
Rapid fire.
Switch screen type.
Okay.
Whatever.
How many coins should I put in?
Controls are reversed.
This is a real Sega game, isn't it?
Oh, dude.
Play Tohoku!
Controls are reversed.
This is a real Sega game, isn't it?
Oh, dude.
Play Tohoku!
You love Tohoku.
Oh, why has he not played it yet?
No, no, no.
Don't play the first one.
Don't play the second one.
There's a third version of the 17th game.
That's the one you should play.
That's the best music.
Don't play the other one.
No, no, no, no, no.
Tohoku 16 version 4.
No, no, no.
Not that one.
Shoot him in the head, right?
I might break through his skin.
Oh, wait.
It's in the head.
I win.
Stage 2.
Let's go.
How many stages are in this game?
One?
It's kind of loud and it hurts my ears.
I'm sorry if it's happening to you too.
It's very painful.
You can't even fucking buy dodges like this one, bro.
You can't even buy dodges like this one.
They're not.
Come on.
Ooh.
How do I know?
I don't know.
How do I get out?
I don't want to play.
Whoa.
What the fuck was that?
Welcome to the family.
Get ready.
Let's go.
Give me up.
M.
How do I quit?
How do I leave?
I want to do that thing where you buy, you put like five quarters into the machine and
you have to leave the arcade.
So you're just like, no, but I can't leave.
There's like five, there's five credits in here, but you have to fucking go.
And your mom's like, get in the car.
We've got to fucking go now.
And it's like, fine.
And you leave and then some kid comes over and it's like, holy shit.
This one's got credits in it.
A bunch of them.
You make somebody's day when you do that.
It's so loud.
I have to stop.
How do I get out?
The back button?
That was fun.
What else is in here?
Welcome to Sega arcade.
What can I do for you?
Change UFO catcher prizes.
I think it needs new prizes.
That's kind of annoying.
What's this?
Can I do this one?
No.
Only two games in here?
What's this bullshit?
Wait a minute.
I have to get the egg.
That's a win.
It is.
I got it.
All right.
We got a lizard.
OK.
Now we're going to get the whatever this is back here.
Perfect.
Get it.
No.
Come on.
Just throw it in there.
Yes.
And the blue one.
That's pretty good.
Get the other lizards.
I got his hat.
Come on.
Just drag him over there.
Yes.
Just go get every prize and then go over to the guy and go, hey, can you refill the prizes?
It's like, how did you glitch this out or like hack this?
Are you selling these?
What are you doing?
All right.
This could be a double.
Possible.
I hit the lip.
Shit.
I can do it.
I just have a handful of prizes.
There's a five-year-old behind me.
That's going to happen again.
It's going to happen again.
Shit.
I'm an idiot.
Oh, yes.
It still worked.
Cleaning out my local.
Whoa.
Oh, I have this actually in my inventory.
OK.
We're going to replace.
I don't know.
One of these.
Just put a health potion in there.
Put it back in the machine.
Yeah.
Why is there booze in this machine?
There's a bottle of vodka in here.
Get his arm.
Yes, I got his arm.
All three lizards are mine.
What a deal.
What's the deal?
Let's see.
Look at this image for a hundred million off your extraordinary debt.
That's too easy.
I mean, that's too easy.
Wrong one?
No.
New deal.
When Mr. Green plays gaming games, total is doubled.
When he plays gambling games, what do you mean?
That's not...
Wrong one again.
Get offer.
Made you look.
There are no offers.
People need to stop spamming links so much these days.
Play Pathologic and Pathologic 2.
Time that person out for an hour.
You got your game shout out.
I'll have an opportunity.
Might as well just try to get everything.
Oh, can I sell these?
What do I do with them?
Go do karaoke?
I will.
Pathologic was one of the most awful games I have ever played.
Jesus.
All right, let's go do some other fun toy stuff.
Can I play this one?
No.
What are some of the toys I can play with?
Hi-tech bowling alley.
Batting practice.
Yep.
Dude, I used to go to the batting cages and just absolutely destroy.
There'd be a 14-year-old next to me.
There'd be like an 18-year-old in the other cage and I'd be in the middle and I would
just be hitting fucking home runs.
I'd be destroying.
I would hit the net.
I would hit the back net in the cages every time.
Getting a high score coming to cool prizes.
I don't care about your prizes.
I care about winning.
I don't want the prize.
I just want to win.
Advanced.
No, no, let's start easy.
Let's go to the one that I would go to, the one that just lobs them so you can just...
You're essentially just chopping wood.
I'm going to just swing as hard as I can and just break this wooden half.
I think I would really love that, by the way.
I probably should have figured out how to play first.
Oh, no.
Do I?
No, I don't.
That's so loud.
Holy fuck, that's horrible.
I got to hold on a minute.
That actually hurt my head.
That was painful.
That's better.
That's very slow.
That was very slow.
I didn't even see it go by.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me just do the training first.
Let me do the training.
How to play.
Press A at the right time.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me just do the training first.
Let me do the training.
How to play.
Press A at the right timing to hit balls, of course.
Okay.
Just ban links.
They are officially banned.
All right, let me get this again.
I don't even hit that that way.
I hit it backwards.
How do I hit the ball behind me?
I'm sitting.
I'm standing sideways.
I'm hitting.
How am I hitting it?
It doesn't make any sense.
Oh, he's a real pull hitter.
It's hard.
The analog is kind of annoying to hold.
Don't worry.
Oh, I can't do it in a video game.
He can't hit the ball in a video game.
See me in real life.
See me in real life when I fucking got a real bat in my hand and I will do, I can do it.
I just watch.
I'll prove it.
I'll do it somewhere.
I'm going to, I'll do a batting cage to him.
And you guys are going to be like, holding it.
I'm going to do it.
Keep in the cage, Mr.
And you guys are going to be like, holy shit.
I take back everything I've ever said about this guy.
That doesn't happen in real life.
Plus, I'm not like standing behind the person actually hitting the ball.
And It's me hitting the ball.
Now that wasn't an out.
That was a ground ball with club kitchen length.
Am I swinging so early?
I gotta go to the advanced course.
That's the problem.
They're going too slow.
is that early? I'm about to go buy me. Fuck this game. I'm not done. I'm not done. I'm not done.
I'm not done. I'm just going to walk up to the cashier. I'm going to pull a wad of hundred dollar
bills out of my hand and just smash it down on the counter and go, just keep the extra. I don't care.
Don't let anybody else in here for an hour. Gone, gone, gone, gone, gone. It's so slow.
Oh, it's gone, gone, gone, gone. Oops.
The advanced one. I will just hold on. I got to load the bases first.
We go load the bases up. Fucking stupid thing. A curve ball doesn't go 60 miles per hour. It goes
like fucking 78. There it is bases loaded. Let's go home run. Let's do it. Fuck you. I didn't see it.
Why do I? OK, another problem is when you when you're playing baseball, I don't like turn my
entire body and look at the sky to try to hit a home run. Fuck out of here. Grand slam. I win.
Double. Let's go home run. No, triple. Oh, go to the casino. I'm doing I like this. I'm having fun
doing this. I'm doing this first. Do the BDSM side quest. How about you do that? Like in your
own free time. There it is. All right. Let's load it up. Go for a home run right now. Let's go.
Fuck it. Oh, what's my record? Oh, shit. You don't have a record. Yes, I do.
Six points. New record. OK, intermediate. Let's do it. Oh, I see. The thing changes.
Well, that's dumb. This is going to do it. Back to back jacks.
Again, get back on this one. Oh, fuck. I wouldn't even look at a ball.
Bullshit. Sorry. We'll do the hard one. Advanced. We're about to pass the the old record.
Oh, there is a home run up top. This will be interesting. Let's see if I can get it.
You have to like look in the sky. This is just not even OK. OK, you have like my eyes are
tracking the home run thing. You can't. I don't have four sets of eyes. I'm looking at the top
of the screen. I'm not even paying attention with the pitchers doing. One out. What?
What the fuck are you talking about? I feel like just like the dad that goes in after the kids are
in there. That was fun, kids. Let me get in there. Dad gets a bat that's way too short for him,
way too light, like a tee ball bat. He just wants to get in there and just rip.
He swings as hard as he can, completely off timing and throws his whole back out.
Hey kids, hey kids, watch this.
Stop leading the shots. Well, how would I? There's no travel time.
There's no travel time. It's only hitscan. Oh, well, what the hell? I'm trying to lead the target.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back. It's gone. A home run.
Who's that guy? That guy back, back, back, back. All I want is one. All right. What's another fun
game I can play here? There's another one. It's 500,000 for the gold rush course. Do I want to play?
Yeah. Oops. What the hell was that? Yeah, let's go. That came in fast. 100,000. Let's go. Go,
go, go. That wasn't even a baseball. What the hell was that? That was a boomerang.
It's a boomerang. All right. The last time I'm going to do this and I'm moving. I'm leaving.
Come on. Yes. All right. This is the crazy one. Got it. That's 150. Let's go. That's 200.
That one just like hit me right in the forehead. I just swung a full swing and it hit me right in
the teeth. Whatever. Fuck this. I'm out. What's this one? Five million for the super gold rush
course. Let's go. Yeah. That's three. That's it. 500,000. All right. Should I leave one more?
See right now, the guy, this guy is going to break out of this. He's going to, first of all, he's,
he's going to run. He's inside of the cage. He's going to run as fast as he can into the door
and open it the wrong way, right? Because he's going to be like, give me the fuck out of here.
He's going to open it wrong. You need to pull it, not push it. And he's going to, fuck. Give me
out. Give me out. Give me out. He's going to open the door and just fucking just run and people in
his way. He's going to fucking shove people out of the way. Just get out of my, please get out of my
fucking way. And I'm going to hold both middle fingers up to this guy and then leave. And I'm
just going to run around screaming, taxi, taxi, taxi, give me a taxi. Like five of them are going
to taxi. Yes. Where would you like to go? Anywhere within a 50 miles out of here.
And I'll pay you double. Where am I? What am I? Where should I go next? Disco, disco, disco. Oh,
there's Mahjong. Disco? Erotic video as well. Okay. I'll play Mahjong. Can I mark it? Oh,
by the way, everybody, we've officially crossed. I've officially been in the game longer. I told
you I was going to be in longer. Here I am. By one minute. What's this place? Now the batting
center. I walk into it. What is that? Where am I? Guess I could hit a few balls. Let me do a mission.
Where's my hideout? Because I kind of want to go there. It's pink dot as the hideout.
It's not unlocked. Oh, okay. It's him. Oh, it is me. Let's go. Random encounter.
Play bingo. Well, maybe in a minute. One, two, three, four, punch. I just kicked him right in
the face. What's the deal with this guy? You attacked me. How would I have a deal when you're
the one that confronts me? You're the one with the deal. Am I going to stream the game awards?
Oh, when are they? Yeah. When are they? That's soon, right? 10th? Yeah, sure. If I can. Definitely.
You're going to get DMCA'd? Will we? Oh, whatever. All this music comes on. It should be fine.
Oh, yeah. I got to tell him what happened.
Tell him you lost six million at the baseball game.
No, you don't tell people that. You don't lead with that.
You keep that to yourself.
I love bingo. It goes like so much fun. It really is. It's so easy. You just have to sit there and
listen and win sometimes. I should head home. Okay. Walk north through the hotel district.
When you start liking bingo, that's how you know you're getting old.
You're old. I mean, I liked it before. I did. What the hell is this? Yeah, you seem to think
you can just walk by me without a word. This dude is huge. I'm not here to show my god.
So this is a shakedown. You should pick your targets better. I don't have a single yen for
chumps like you. Mr. Shakedown? That's this guy's name? What the fuck? Does he just grab you and
take money from your pocket? Oh shit, I just lost $285,000. What? What just happened? You're not
half bad. I'll let you off the hook this time. What? If I'm having trouble with somebody like
you, I need to change my training regimen. Time to bump up the intensity. Should I have shaking
down to do? I'm just Mr. X. Hey, you okay, man? Hey, you just had the misfortune of meeting
Hiroya Egashira. Mr. Shakedown, they call him. Mr. Shakedown? Yeah, he'll go after anybody that
crosses his path, and then he takes everything they have. You seem like you can hold your own
in a fight, but that guy's on a whole different level. If he sets his sights on you, you run for
it. He takes all your money? I wish somebody could come along and beat all that stolen money out of
him. Did he get you? Took my whole holiday bonus. I knew I should have made a beeline to the bank
with it. Next time you're sitting on a stack of cash. Rumor has it he's not the only Mr. Shakedown
and that they aren't just a kumarucho thing. Stay sharp. If you ever go out of town. Oh, great.
If you lose to Mr. Shakedown in battle, he'll take all the money you have. If you can beat Mr.
Shakedown, you reclaim all the money he steals from you. What? Okay, so how do I deposit money?
Oh, I got a tissue. Oh, just throw it away. You don't. You there. Wait, is it him? Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, it's just one guy. This is this is this is not Mr. Shakedown. Spend it on abilities, right?
Yep. Get out of here. You cannot take what you invest. Fuck, I had I had like $12 million.
God damn it. All right, hold on. Let me take a break. I'm gonna get some water. I'm gonna go pee.
I'll be back in like two, three minutes. You're back. Here comes artwork. What do we got?
Do you have the photos? How are they? Right with a gun? More Jojo? No Catboy. Bad ad game.
No Catboy this time. All right, let's let's continue. I head back to the game. So I am
going to tell you guys something that I'm probably only going to stream for like another hour.
At least it was more than four hours. And then I may I'm trying to kind of gauge those who
that weren't here. I want to make sure people know this. I've been getting sick. As of this
kind of past weekend, I started like on like Saturday or so Sunday, I started getting a little
scratchy. And then I'm kind of stuffy. So I took a bunch of precautions. I took a COVID test.
And I want to really just kind of make sure that I kind of err on the side of complete caution here.
So I'm sort of awaiting that. I don't have the I don't know. I don't have the results yet.
So just want to obviously let everybody know that I'm okay. But yeah, that's pretty much it.
Hey gamers. So tomorrow, I'll the next like probably three or four plus days are going to
be sort of erratic. I might stream one day and then two days or one day and then one day, one day off,
one day on. We'll kind of see how it goes. But I'm okay right now. We'll see. Let's go back to the
game. That was cute. Ratatouille. Adorable. There's no camera. Fuck. Okay, good. The light is on like
it's being recorded. Breaks me out for a second. So what can I do with this stuff? Just drink the
milk? That's all it does? Just eat it. Just eat everything. All right, let's go. What was something
else I could do? I'm going to let me do the quest and let me spend this money. So I don't hold on.
Yeah. Before I lose it all gambling. Regular attacks and heat actions. Yes. 30 million,
2 million. A mighty knee from low stance. More health. Oh wait. Reduce the amount of heat loss
when you take damage. That's pretty good. And reduces the heat dropping over time. Probably
this one. Should I do more health? I'm doing this one. So you don't lose a lot of heat when you take
damage. I like it. I like it. Anything else for like 400? Okay. Increase the power of your regular
attacks. Go to the disco. All right. I will go to the disco right now and then I'm going to do the
mission or vice versa. All right. I'm going to do the mission and then I'm going to do the disco.
I'm going to change my clothes. Karaoke. Karaoke. Karaoke. Maybe soon. Maybe. Look at my eye.
I can change clothes in here, right? I can put the clown outfit on. Hold on. Get out of my eye.
Oh damn it. I'm going to laugh every time I see it.
Hey grab me a couple cigarettes out of the fridge.
That's both for you. What about me? What the fuck?
Oh beer.
Weirdly cluttered. The table is, you got a lot of real estate. Not using a whole lot of it.
Thank you so much for not being obnoxious and talking through all the cutscenes.
Thank you so much for not being obnoxious and talking through all the cutscenes like you did
last time. Did I? I think I'm doing that. I'm doing that right now. Fuck. All right. I'll be quiet.
Be quiet.
You can talk? Did this guy not eat? Why are there... What are those bottles over there?
There's like four bottles on the table.
I want to that one's gonna eat
I'll turn it up
There's ramen on the table. Yeah, we're playing poker with Oreos. He's lost every single round
We're not old enough to play with money. So we use chips Oreos sticks and food pieces
Oh
There are beers on the table
They're unopened right
I
Have those same wrinkles on my eyebrows exact same ones
Just look at any picture of my face. I'm straight on
So no
Face cam no, I'm like sick. I'm not gonna put the face. I'm like like pale and dirty and
Like dirty. No, I'm too dirty
Dirty is good. No, it's not
Me
Clean and prepared
Prepared for what I don't know for the day for the world for you for me for everything
Okay. Here's here's our tweet for what just happened
Maybe Nishiki's right and I should accept Tachibana's offer
But I need to I need more to go on before I can trust him. Here we go. There's our lore tweet. I
Should hit the town to see what I can find out about him. Who's laughing. Oh, that's a crow. I just hear like
All right, I'm so I'm just gonna pick that herb up on the ground and use it for help final fantasy laugh
What's the guy that laughs really loudly and um
What's his name? No, not not Tobin Bell. That's the actor from saw. What's his name?
Titus right
Two three four five
Six seven eight nine ten
Gaslight him let's cash light him
We have a disco club disco club disco disco disco disco disco disco
I'm ready for the disco. Let's do it. I'm going to the middle of the day
Is it up top? Where is it?
You thought Christopher Walken and Tobin Bell were the same person
I mean
I don't I guess I can kind of
Sort of see that
But not in their voice. I mean
I don't know
Here you go. I've got I got a million dollars. I'm a millionaire
I can go in here whenever I want
Enjoy your time at the maharaja
Although saw would have probably been a lot more interesting. I guess with Christopher Walken as saw would have been weird
What can I do?
These dance moves
This is like i'm playing in a puddle
Okay, let's go
I request talk to people 50 times
Yeah, let's about the disco
To dance at the disco press buttons and rhythm with a song
Use up down left right left right up down b a start to move your character's avatar to the square
With the next input icon
And then press the corresponding button when it's there
As you move your avatar, you'll see the number of steps it takes. Okay
The more steps you take the more points you will get
The correct input try to take as many steps as you can on your way to the next input
You can't squares marked already stepped on won't be counted again
In the upper middle of the screen is the fever gauge press the left trigger when it's full to trigger dancing fever
New screen with a series of button input will appear press them with the correct timing to boost your score
okay
The voltage gauge at the upper right shows how impressed the audience is with your dancing
It directly affects what rating you get so build up your score to fill the gauge
Get just four levels each level earns you another star towards your final dance rating
I don't know why i'm laughing. It's just funny
There is also a versus mode in which you can compete with another dancer the one with the higher score wins
I guess i'll try
What song do you want?
Friday night
queen of passion
I'm gonna make her mine
I want to take you home
Boy, you know disco queen
Friday night friday night. All right. All right
I'm doing i'll do friday night. Here we go. Ready?
down left right
I don't even have to do anything
Now he's supposed to go
All right, I have to make steps and then
I
I don't understand
What is I don't understand this is not dancing
What the fuck is this?
What kind of dancing mini game is this?
That's not even dancing
I just got booed off the stage. Well, sorry
I have to move the little guy around the screen and press a at the right time
I thought I was going to be moving around the kid like the guy and dancing
You don't know shit about dancing. Oh really i'm gonna link them to gif
Ha ha ha
All right, here we go. I gotta fill as many squares as I can
This I don't like this
Oh, it's too hard to move around that fast
So i'm not even me dancing with me mashing my buttons until I can get to the right spot and press a
Fill as many squares and press a on q
Come on, i'll do one more on hard
Use the d-pad. Yeah, I am
Here we go
Why
I'm gonna quit the game. I'm done. I'm done. It's been four hours. I don't care
And yeah, I quit quit just rip rip the controller up
I'm never playing this again
This is the last time you're ever gonna see disco. I'm never doing it again
Cool, that's all right. I at least I can go to the next level in the ipad game. I don't care dancing mini game
Yeah, give me a break
Who the fuck are you?
It's gonna turn. It's just a haymaker this guy what
What do you want? Hey? Yeah, that's right you the impressive specimen
Yes, you you took you long enough to notice
Come over here. Who are you?
Me i'm hasaki lover of dance and lover of women. Okay, you're annoying
Yes, I agree kiro
All right. Got it later
Wait, wait, hold on
What do you want from me see this dance floor? It's my playground
And i've been watching you dance friend
That's when it hit me. You've got a talent for dancing. That's off the scale
What?
Yeah, there's no fooling me, but I wouldn't mind seeing it up again up close. I challenge you to a battle
But you want to fight me? No a dance battle
All right. I'm doing it. I'm gonna do it one more time
We're gonna dance battle this guy. How can you not know about dance battles?
unbelievable
You're a neanderthal
I think this twit wants to fight me
Okay
Two dancers dancing the same song to see who's better
Both dancers show this stuff the audience reaction determines the winner. All right, I get the picture great
You catch on quick for a caveman
Let's not waste any time then let's hit the floor
You're looking for a drink in your face. What's this? Why are you doing this?
Dancing's awesome because you can get down and boogie anytime
Let's go. All right. I'm gonna be good on this one. I swear to god
I'm gonna be so good on this. You have no idea
Oh, it has to be friday night
All right, buddy
It's time for me to do the thing that I'd say I don't or whatever
Oh, those are your moves those are bad. All right, let's kick his ass metaphorically
What the fuck are you talking about
Fever, I'm sorry
I'm using an xbox controller
And as you all know the xbox controller is wonderful because like when you press one button like up on the xbox controller
It's every fucking button on your entire controller and your keyboard
And it's every it clicks your mouse buttons, too. I still win get push this guy off the stage
Let's tech in this motherfucker and just eliminate him. Just push him off
Virtual fighter whatever the sega game was the same company who cares?
The sega made virtual fighter
They made this game too. That's what I mean
Ha ha ha ha
Virtual fighter five is in yakuza. Is it actually in the game?
That's pretty cool
I haven't danced like this in a long time
All thanks to you
What's wrong with that?
After all, what else can we be we danced wild we danced hot we danced together
Is that how it works?
That's exactly how it works. I knew my eyes weren't deceiving me. You've got legit talent my brother
Maybe maybe you can even take him
Oh me and my big mouth just forget you heard a word brother and nothing to do with you yet
Okay
Oh, hey, I don't think I ever caught your name
Oh, you went with the real name first big mistake. Should have said like dave
Whatever. All right. I have to go. I'll be looking forward to the hitting the dance floor again with you. Who's this?
New character
Boy kiro. He's good
But maybe not quite at my level yet
Oh, i'm getting out of here. Give me out. I don't want to do this again
Hey
Baki
A round of drinks for everybody
Yeah
You heard it here from the dance king. That's me
They start to bring out the bottle service serve every table
Where's the exit?
Where's the exit? I don't know how to get out of here
No, I don't want to get the the whole thing was I didn't want to have to bill. All right, let's go this way
No, this is the bar. Oh shit
Ah
I tried to find the exit and I found the checkout
Okay. Um
Well, yeah, let me find my credit card. Uh
Here you go
Delicious wine
So you like disco dancing? Yeah sort of
Well that dancing makes you thirsty come to me and i'll fix you a drink
Yes, you're a bar. You're a bartender
That's okay sure i'll take a drink
How about another wine shot of wine
Hey, i'll take another one. I'll take a chassis in orange, please
What else you got? What else you got on the list?
uh
Take a gin and lime be good
Come again
I'll take a
What else you got? I'll take you know, i'll try one of everything. This is not what you don't do
This is the i'm guaranteed to puke later tonight
stick with one
If you if you're gonna drink
You don't drink don't drink beer wine hard liquor. No, no, just stay with one thing, please
How many times can I do this
I can't drink any more of these. Oh
Am I wait just getting drunk just untuck your shirt in this game
I don't I he's not drunk
I kind of
This is a video game. Why is the screen not blurry and why is he not stumbling like side to side?
And why is he not gone?
I just want to say that i'm just trying to love you. I have they do that too
How come he's not doing that out loud like voice lines?
Holy shit this all right. I'm good
what
Talk to 50 people
You still haven't found the president of tachibana real estate our boss ain't a patient man and we've been keeping him for
Who are these guys?
It's 8 a.m
Yeah, whatever
What I was just checking the place out
Sorry, i'm skipping this
Go hit one of the businesses. He's bought out or something
Yes, sir
What are you gonna do?
What business has he bought out?
Something go play bingo
I hold on. I want to fight somebody. I want to get a fight
Go to the casino
No, no, that's a bad idea. Where is it though? Just for me to know for future reference
Just for me to know for like later
bar with pool and darts
erotic videos
karaoke bar
Not until later. All right. Well, just let me know for later
right
Is it 12 million?
Holy shit that guy collapsed
That guy was a crumpled up piece of paper
Oh, and here he comes and the award for best pretender on twitch
I would wear it like
that shirt and jacket too probably
Oy, oy, you are an old man
This isn't going to end. Well, are you all right?
No, what's the big guy? What's the big idea?
I'm, so sorry. Watch where you step shit for brains
You're not hurt or anything. Are you asshole?
All right, if that's how you I feel like this is somebody in chat
Like hey asshat like uh, have a good night tonight
You turn around it's right behind you. Um, it's really easy to see behind you fucking idiot
Be having a good day today
Stupid moron
I'm, so sorry. No, I mean i'm in a rush see so please get lost punk ass. This is i'm getting like fucking deja vu
I think he stole from me. Did he like he bumped into me and
Oh, no
Love you dip shit
I know the batting cage is right next to me, but i'm not going in there
Do I even have a goal right now? I think it's just talk to 50 people and entertain myself a bunch of times
This is the what have I not gone in batting practice
the disco club
Karaoke bar. Oh, let's go. I want to go bowling bowling bowling bowling
Thanks, joe joe 288211. Thanks for the
Nice moves
Karaoke karaoke karaoke. Um, hold on. I want to go bowling
Uh, go to the pocket circuit. I want to go bowling
bowling first
What the hell's going on? Shut your hole fat ass and open your wallet. Oh what?
I'm telling you. I can't pay i'm dead broke right now
Don't give me that bullshit tubs
I watched your sorry ass come out of that soap land last night
Wait, what?
Yeah, then you matched you marched your little buddies around from club to club drink until dawn living pretty large for a broke guy, ain't you?
You were spying on me
Goddamn, right. You know how many different lenders you've dicked over pork chop. It's collection day and your ass is getting beat
Email collections agent pretty unusual sounds like a real ball buster, too
Yes, she's terrifying as ever
Pockets what is she a friend of yours? Oh, you got that right?
Sure wouldn't make an enemy of her
But there's miss tatsu the debt collector. She's a legend in yokohama
It's tatsu, huh?
She takes on the jobs that make other collecting boys run away crying and she always
always gets the cash
Her style is bold blunt and brutal
And but to a bulldog's own tenacity
And you get me one big bite boy
You seem awfully familiar with her methods. This uh
This the voice of personal experience
Of course, you got me boy
I was this close to getting my face caved in over a silly little dead a while back
Why am I not surprised?
Hey
Look over there boy
We're about to see what makes our lady miss tatsu so incredible
You think you can get the money out of me? I'd like to see you try
Huh you boys and your tiny toys you think your little butter knife is there it's gonna stop me
Drop the tough fact sugar
So sweet in coffee
Yum yum yum yum yum. I love it in coffee
And I like it on candy
Time to
Tits i've put a dozen dudes in the hospital with this baby
If you have a tear-stained apology ready for me, I'll hear you out
That's my line sugar. Oh
sugar boobs
Except the part about hearing you out since you'll be too dead now make you move
Uh holding a weapon on that woman that's going too far
Uh, you should stop this. Yeah, I should and i'm gonna
No need boy. Just wait
No blinking now boy keep those eyes on miss tatsu in show time
I'll fucking kill you
That's rad
Why
I was kind of fucked up that you did that to that 11 year old spike
Is the girl just crying on the sidewalk right now?
Mr. Why those moves?
Looks like that beatdown gave you a few ideas
Yeah more than a few. Sorry. Yeah
Fantastic boy. Hope you're ready to put him into practice
Huh?
Look over yonder looks like our bad guy here. He's got some friends. Oh shit
Jin kun's getting beat to hell. He paid the tab last night
So what say we pay him back by sucker punching this crazy bitch for him?
You hear that boy those dim bulbs are planning on getting the drop on a little lady from behind
Sounds that way
Lovely crowd. They're a perfect match for the sort of scum that'll pull a knife on a woman
Why don't you give me a little demo of what a man's supposed to be?
And no saying this doesn't involve you this time. Yeah
Yeah, I wouldn't she can clearly defend herself there's a whole pack of them i'm jumping in
Yes, that's my boy keeping chivalry alive and working in a fine bit of training in the process
The hell do you want?
Good
I guess planning a sucker punch that woman in the back. You got an eavesdropping problem
Damn straight. We are is it a robot? It shouldn't be what the robot? That should not be a robot. Why is it a robot?
What it doesn't know hold on a second what that's not what it's supposed to be sounding like let me see
No, what the fuck that's not supposed to sound like that. It's supposed to sound why is it? Why is it? Okay?
There we go. What the fuck it was supposed to be like that. Okay
You think I want that psycho bitch to see me coming
We'll drop her before she can get those claws out
I don't care how tough she is. You don't hit a woman and needing a group to do it. It's just pathetic
You call yourselves men
What the fuck did you say you got a big mouth and a death wish bell yo
We're dropping this guy before we take care of the broad
Oh, is that so?
Switch to beast style
You can switch to be style by pressing right by changing to be style now. Okay, let's try it
Press x while near a large weapon showing a mark to automatically pick it up and swing it. This is called an auto weapon attack
Bash an enemy with an auto weapon attack. Okay
Yeah
Where is it a huge weapon? Where is it?
Oh use x get out of here use x. Oh, that's not a beast weapon
All right, is there anything else bigger
withstand the enemy attacks
Holding lp to guard lets you withstand enemy attacks with the resist guard
You'll take a certain amount of damage, but you are protected against attacks from any direction. That's cool
Okay
Use beast style moves to pulverize the back
Pack of power
Dodge roll now, that's cool
Nice drop kick
I'm so fucking mad
And pick him up by their legs. Oh, that's so awesome
What is this guy all of us beating on him and it's like he doesn't even feel it you want more
No, i'm leaving i'm not leaving till at least I punch that bitch
All right
Well, i've hold on
Well, if it isn't
Porky's little friends. I saw you boys crawling the bar last night
Uh, I must be hearing things because it sounded like you said something about punching
Me out if you're interested. This bitch is ready to go
No, no, no me. I'm just that's just crazy. What kind of man would do that?
And with a group that's pathetic
Right now pick up that sad sack line over there and get the hell out of my sight
I got what I came here for got no use for him now
Yes, ma'am
Mr. Satan. No, it's not
Nothing. Everything that is low is not. Mr. Satan. Is it? It's not everything. It's not. Mr. Satan
This is not. Mr. Satan
This is this is uh, you know, yeah
It's like a hidden camera tv show where they got the person completely blacked out with a silhouette
Yeah, when I uh, you know that the crazy part is when I watched him when we're working at mcdonald's
Yeah, he uh, no, it's even lower. It's like yeah
My identity needs to be taken care of because I watched him
I watched him pee into the coffee machine and it was disgusting and we tried to make him stop
We tried to get rid of him. It's a boss was just crazy. He was just fucking fucked up
Arthur
I want you to know something Arthur. I do believe it me. I don't know what you're saying
I'm not doing this again. No, we're not doing this again. I'd rather do this
What is this bit there is no bit you've already seen it before
It returns it returns. It's time to go back into this bit
If you remember this one from a few months ago go. How do I get back to the game? I need a new trailer
Yeah
It's groundhog day. No, i'm not that we don't repeat material here
Except almost every day we do but you know, whatever
Hmm
Names kiru
Kiru, huh?
I'll remember the name if you've got
Bacchus singing your praises. You've got to be pretty tough. Yes
Yes, this boy is a future champion. Let's take my career on it
Oh, okay. Now i'm seeing what this is you're thinking kiru here is your ticket to a fat stack of cash
Which then you'll use to pay me back so we can get to stay friends
Easy tiger
I told you it'll take a while, but you'll get it back. Oh speaking of favors
Why don't you train the boy here?
Wait, well, this is like a table read for a tv show. I'm not even getting into this
The actor is not even doing the voice. They're doing like the halfway
Table read youtube video
Do I seem like the patient teacher and then they all they all laugh too
After like funny lines, even though they're saying i'm like on a halfway
Now
Ah, don't be like that. We both need him to get stronger
Everyone starts laughing and we're like they all have glasses on too
Every single person at the table has glasses on
We'll be rolling in dough besides. I know you're secretly the doting type
He'll make a champion a hell of a lot faster with you beating him into shape. That means you get paid sooner. Hmm
See win-win
What focus?
What do you think you're doing here, man? Yeah
Negotiating an apprenticeship with miss tatsu for you
Sorry, sorry
Obviously, trust me you train under her. You'll be master of the ring in no time flat
Uh, you're insane. I'm in seriously in hot water right now. I don't have the time to humor your little fantasies
What?
You're at hot water too. My boy
This is great. This is great
Are we talking knife in the ribs here? Because I warned you about that
I'll be lucky if that's all I get and seriously, what's this obsession with me getting stabbed about?
All right chuckle heads. That's enough. Neither of one of you is making a damn bit of sense
Here you walks from stage left into the scene and get swarmed by 25 enemies. Oh shit
But I hear where you're coming from focus ditch the championship talk and just say you care about this kiro kid
If you're worried about him own it
Look, you did me a solid minute ago. What was what's on the floor over there?
Oh, this is trash
The old man is right that my training will make a real man out of you
Hop a cab out to the pier sometime. I'll give you a training space there
You train at the pier
You got it kind of live that i'm holding this paper still
Put down pay me a visit sometime see for yourself. I think you'll get the digs
Everyone looks over at me. What the what do yeah, i've memorized the lines already. I don't need the fucking paper anymore
All you guys that show up like three days before we hurt rehearsal. No, fuck all of you
Focus i've already got a future plan. I'm sorry, but I can't be your champion. What sport are we even talking about boxing?
Not that it matters. I can't
It's a toxic theater kid
I know that doesn't mean i'll stop trying
But I know i'll just stop making a nuisance of myself. I'll give you some spice jump
It's about time for my afternoon drink. Anyway, help me clear my head
Good luck with that. Just don't have too many
Do you think a guy called bakas can't hold his wine?
Ha see you around boy and keep those ribs knife free
Get out of here. Thanks. I'll be careful
I will thank you for hanging out with me
This afternoon didn't expect to get wrapped up in that mess, but at least I didn't come away empty-handed
That is torn on who that is
British bernie sanders. I mean like boris johnson kind of is like sounds like that british bernie
What's going on this is a rough looking crowd
What do I ever do for this guy?
uh
Oi, um
Oi. Oi
I'm so freaking stoked man
Oh rare street show, but you're gonna meet your silvers
Too right those guys are rock and roll boards
Look at this bitching crowd
They drew all these punks without any ads or any nothing at all
crazy, it's crazy
I think this looks like a street documentary voice. It's not documentary voice
They're all boris johnson
It's not nigel thornberry. What?
How do you get boris johnson and nigel thornberry mixed up?
Keep your pants on but I heard the yokomichi silvers are heading for a q and a panel
No effing way. They're famous for never saying a word and letting their music do the talking
I wonder what the hell they're talking about
Sounds like some band's doing an event here
Must be popular with the local punks
hmm
Oops, wait, can you it's coming through twice?
It might no no
theater square
All right, so
Save the game
Oh, there's a quest marker over here quest quest quest
Uh, you didn't see me do that
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Look at these people. Holy cow. What are we going to do?
Oi, hey you
Yikes
Gee whiz pal. I never peed. I didn't peepee my pants. What are you doing chuffing around behind me? You ugly knob
Oh, yeah, sorry
All right, but I should apologize for bumping into you earlier
oh
You're that man
I love so much. Oh everybody fucking hates this
It's giving me energy right now
Uh, sure
Wait a second. Could you possibly be unaware of who I am?
Yeah, uh, are you asking me if we met before if we bumped into each other if we did I don't recognize you
Oh, wait a second then so you really don't know who I am. Oh willikers. What a relief
I'm so sorry. I was rude. Don't not too true. My name's kyo. My stage name is crazy kyo. I'm the vocalist in a band
Let me guess the yoke meet you silvers
Same band these young punks are excited to see aren't you guys some kind of legendary?
yankee band
I'm gonna chat just gave you a hundred dollars to fuck off
What I don't read bits anymore
He's a jerk. The lemmy gave a hundred bucks jerma. I will pay you to never do this voice ever again
Well, you did it before I agreed to that
So now i'm going to read your message in the voice that you didn't want that you paid to stop
He's a scumbag no, thanks. You can't pay me to do anything. I'll never accept money to do something. I'm never requiring
Even hardcore in the slightest
No, as a joke, we tried dressing all punk at a show to our shock
We got pretty popular with the yankee crowd, but now we have to keep up this charade full time
Every time we gained a fan base of wannabe punks and the yoke go meet you silvers became heroes to the rebellious youth of japan
Little style is called yankee now
Okay
There's more to running a band than I thought
So what do you mean by me saving you?
I um actually now I know this game's 80 hours long. I figured it out
I see
I want you to teach me how to be a hardcore hooligan
Teach you to be a yankee
Yes, you see for today's event. We also have to do a live panel
a meet-and-greet for the fans
Every member of the yokimichi silvers myself included are law-abiding choir boys. We've never even shoplifted
If we were to talk in front of the real yankee, they'd realize that we're phonies
Fake punks. Eh now that you mentioned it the way you talk doesn't match how you dress at all
You are a choir boy, right? So if we spoke to our fans, we'd lose all our credibility and popularity in an instant
Or worse, what if they want revenge on us for fooling them?
Okay, but do you have to do this panel thing? Why don't you just skip it?
I don't want to do it either but our agency says we need to hone
Our speaking skills. We want to stay popular. They're making us do this
Are you know when you're in line for the ride at like disney world or universal studios?
And you're just sitting there in line watching the videos
It's like an hour and a half watching the videos in line
And then you get onto the ride and the ride is like three minutes long
And you're like, holy shit. That was fun. And then you kind of get in line for another ride and you watch the videos again
I feel like this is this game
Like i'm in line at the ride and then when we actually fight people
Like I get to be on fucking back to the future for two minutes
So you want me to teach you how to behave like a yankee?
He hates it. No, I don't
I don't
I don't hate this
When did I say I hated the back to the future of ride line experience? I never said that
I just said that's what it reminds me of
You implied it. No, I didn't I said this, you know, you know, you know, this reminds me of
You can teach us. Okay, teach me how to be don't
He hates back to the future. This is not
How much do you like lines then?
in simulator
You heavily implied it
Do you love to watch the theme park videos before the ride?
Yes, I do because it fills me in and I get to see stuff that I've never seen before
That's content. You don't get to see unless you go to the ride
Or I mean maybe like on like the special features of the dvd. They might put it on there
All right, let's do it
Okie dokie
Give me a second, please
Okay
You're back
Sorry to keep you waiting
This is our drummer sleazy tarashi
Hey, i'm tarashi
My stage name is sleazy, but I have no experience with the ladies never even seen a boo
This is our bassist bad boy aku
I'm aku hobbies caring for elders
This is kirusan
Is going to impart the ways of true yankee style hooliganism onto us
Please teach us
Okay
You guys are so polite and proper. I'm starting to wonder if there's anything I can do for you
Oh, no, please don't say that. We're all pretty good guys at heart. So please help us
In your case being pretty good at guys is the problem
I did agree to this. So somehow am I gonna beat this shit out of them?
How can I show you how to be tougher? Maybe you could come up with an opening remark for a little old me
Okay
I want to kick off our panel with authority being hooligans. We shouldn't come across as weak or hesitant
I need a zinger
Dearly beloved we're gathered here today start your engines. Hello, but in english
What opening with hello, but it's in english
English do you really think so?
I mean a hooligan speaking english. Is that is that yankee style?
I think it would be just right for a yankee young rebels fall hard for what's cool and english is the language of rock and roll
Okay
Think about it their hero the vocalist of the yokomichi silver speaks a language. They don't know
They can't help but be impressed by his worldiness
Do I have to keep speaking english afterwards?
That's going to be a challenge. I only know a few greetings
Same goes for them though. If you sound like you know what you're saying you can get away with it
Do we get to watch this?
Rock and roll
What is it? Well the agency told me to tell the fans about how I spend my days off
When i'm not rehearsing or performing
Days off, huh? Makes sense that fans would want to know their heroes live from day to day
How the heroes live?
Terashi, how would you spend a day off?
I make a habit of getting up bright and early so I can make some pancakes after breakfast
I take my darling puppy chibi chan to the park for a mid-morning stroll
And then we have lunch at
Chick cafe to rest our feet on our way home. We do little window shopping after that. I binge on the dramas
I've got this is when I like make my phone
Do a fucking ringtone
And be like, oh, yeah. Yeah. All right. Okay. I gotta I gotta take this see you later guys
You just described a typical girl's day
Oh, sorry
That really made you sound like a fashionable young woman. I was so surprised. I got intense
Uh, I'm so scared
Oh, no, kira-san. You shouldn't shout like that. You made sleazy terashi cry. That's a bit much. Don't you think?
Oh dear sniffle
Should say sorry
Yeah, my bad
It's it's all right. I was just startled. I wasn't expecting it is all
Sniffles, so how about I spend a day off? How should I spend it? How should I do it?
It's kind of sound like butt head right there
One thing's clear. You can't tell the fans how you really spend your free time
No, I guess not. But then what should I say?
What would I be doing instead?
You'd be you'd be hanging with mates
And you just have to say you spend it having fun with your friends
I think all my friends that's kind of ordinary, isn't it? I mean, I already do that pretty regularly
Think about it punks are people too on their days off
Even they would want to spend it with their friends ever notice them squatting together in parking lots
Uh, that's true. I see them loitering around like you say, but are they really friends?
Oh, I used the wrong word
Isn't wrong
They're not friends. It should be mates
Mates actually when you put what people running
You see on your days off you hang out with your mates
Actually you and your mates just shoot the shit with each other say that and you'll be fine
I kind of get it. I'm not sure what that actually means but hanging out with mates sounds totally what hooligans would do
Now, what do you want?
You're a bad boy aku, right? What's the matter?
What should I say?
Uh, you didn't get a topic like tarashi
No
The agency told him to wing it. He's free to talk about whatever
Even though he's practically mute
Bad boy aku even has a backstory locked up in juvenile reformatories from birth bad boy
Aku crushed packs of punks before he even finished preschool
Mmm
Your agency's trying to fit a square peg in a round hole
Man, a few words the crazy backstory. What should he talk about to make him sound hardcore?
Nothing at all
Anything be better if you just stay quiet
Stay silent during the panel wouldn't a discussion without any talking be a disaster
Nope aku was told he's free to talk about whatever he wants. That means he's also free not to talk at all
that's true, but
It would be worse if he were to say the wrong things and wreck his image
From aku's backstory, I think he would seem more hardcore if he kept his mouth shut
Yeah, you put it that way it makes total sense. Okay, we'll do that bad boy aku stay speechless during his part
I can't get over it sure aku. Are you good with that?
Okay. All right
Now we'll go over how you'll run this panel discussion
Yes, please
Oh, here we go
We're almost ready for your panel
I'll be watching from the audience. Let's see how we do
Yes, please watch us we're going to hit this hardcore yankee thing out of the park
We're gonna kick ass and stuff. Mm-hmm
All right, let's see it
Yeah, they are put your hands together for the yoko bichi silvers
Ooh crazy kyo san
Bad boy aku over here. Oh my god. Check out crazy kyo sans original esp guitar smoking red
The man's got the yankee look nailed
Oh, they are popular and they're not talking they do look like real greasers
Sopping wet high rock and roll after school
Tarashi aku hit it boys
That concludes what?
That concludes today's performance by the yoki bichi silvers
Just listening to their songs. I can see why yankee kids across japan look up to crazy kyo's band
We'd like to move on to a special meet and greet panel discussion with the band members
Whoa, no way
Crazy kyo sans actually gonna talk to us. That's mental
I can't fucking wait to hear bad boy aku's voice
Here's where it gets real. They better pull it off
Yo, grease hounds
Hello, everyone rock and roll. We are
yokio michi silvers
Holy shit crazy kyo can can even speak english. That's so bitching. I'm gonna totally get up going mental
My god that totally authentic pronunciation. It drives me wild
I'm shitting bricks over here
I'm fine. Thank you
And you
Yes, the audience loves it using english was a good choice
Awesome. Thank you crazy kyo-san
Next we would like to hear from sleazy tarashi-san and the bad boy aku-san as well
First up sleazy tarashi-san. Here's a question. We got from a fan. How do you usually spend your days off?
Ah, if I get a day off, I mostly hang with my mates and we shoot the shit
Yeah, a guy like tarashi-san must have a lot of mates
Tarashi-san, what do you do with your mates?
um
We uh make pancakes is no
You ruined it. Oh, we don't just stay holed up at home. We go out and uh eat lunch at fancy cafes and stuff. Yeah
Who the fuck is this guy?
Uh, oh
I should have covered more details
Oh, no
I have a bad boy aku-san to say something
Uh, don't say anything
That was it
No way. He just stood there for his whole panel discussion. That's
That's so hardcore
Yeah
Holy crap bad boy aku-san's the coolest. What a rebel. He doesn't play by the rules. Not even his own rules
That's what makes him a bad boy
I'm good. It was the right choice
After all it doesn't take a big talk to make a big man and attitude speaks louder than words
Did I do it?
Here's n were you watching?
Yeah, I saw everything
Good work
Here's n we tried to apply what we learned from you about the ways of the yankee to our panel
Fan response is pretty darn good. I'm kind of shocked. Do I get money for this?
It seemed that way. It was all worth the effort
I think we can keep the yochi
Yokomitsu silver is going without stay of sagging. They're gonna be still we're gonna be fine
Thank you very much
You got a charismatic autobiography
That's the most fun i've ever had speaking in public
Here son. Thanks from now on we're going to keep working hard to expand on what you taught us about the way of the yankee
We'll work on our speaking skills, too
Keep an eye on us
The yoko michi silvers are going places. Just you watch
Yeah, give it your best shot
Do not equip the book. Please do not use the book. Don't use the book. Don't equip the book
Don't do throw the book in the trash. What's going on here?
People sure have all kinds of challenges to face
At least those guys are diligent they should survive the rough road of the entertainment world somehow don't give up guys
Yeah, you shouldn't you got something that you're doing
Keep trying make sure you're having fun doing it. Is it safe point? All right now i'm gonna go bowling
The book is gonna make the combat unplayably hard
Watch out
Who is this guy?
I'll go back to brawler back to brawler
Stop hurting these guys. They attacked me
All right, let's go bowling
I'm into bowling
Use the book use the book
Okay
Hello, how can I help you? I'd like to challenge the staff
500 yen
How many would you like to play? Um free you challenge the staff you get a chicken
well, let me just
Figure out how to do it first
Okay, pull up the position and select ball
And then you can adjust the spin
And then just set power
Okay
All right 12 pounds adjust the power
Press left right before releasing the ball to adjust the spin
Um, yeah, but that was the computer doing that it wasn't me doing that
All right, let's go I want the 12 pound ball no, I want the 16 pound heavy tank
I'm gonna do the thing that I used to do when I went bowling and that's you get the huge wicked fucking heavy ball
And you just roll it really slowly diaper style down the middle of the lane
Well, I didn't I didn't get a chance to do that. Did I?
This is gonna be great
Diaper style is one diaper style is you go between your legs back and then forward
Too much spin too much too much too much too much too much too much
See this why I need to do it first before I challenge any staff member
You mean granny style it's diaper style
And you can do weirdo style, which is you go here
Or you go here you throw it diagonal and you try to get it to spin across the entire lane. We're gonna do it here
That's the best strategy I know what I call it weirdo style
It was a slight curve just a little not very much
All right, I got the hang of it
Let's do a eight pound
That's really slow. We need a very small spin here. It's gonna be very very slow
Almost get a striker. I'm gonna leave
um, okay
Well, how long you gonna stay here for?
No shit. Okay. Hold on. It's gonna take some spin
Twice way too much way too much way way way too much
Bowling till you get a perfect game
All right. Now let's challenge a staff member. I get it
Your bowling form is exquisite
You think so it really is the angle of your bottom when you release the ball is optimal
Would you learn how to do that?
No way, that's amazing
You know how to position your body with the best effect your form. It's really delightful. Ehehe
Oh, i'm sorry. It's just that I kind of have a bowling form fetish
All right, it just went up it went the game went up like two full letter grades
When I see someone with good form, I sort of forget myself
I see. I guess this job's perfect for you then
Yes, I think so, too
My name's emiri
What?
I hope to see you here more often. You have become a regular. Okay
Yeah, maybe I will it was nice to meet you
This could be the beginning of a friendship with emiri
Interacting with her will gradually fill the friendship gauge
You can check the status of this gauge at any time in the pause menu build your friendship with emiri and see what happens
Yep
Me and emir i'm gonna i'm i'm gonna go after me and emiri i'm gonna be like hey you want to go
Hey, you want to go bowling?
Mary, um, this is crazy. But uh
Do you ever want to go bowling sometime?
Would you like to play bowling?
Yes with pleasure. That'll be five hundred dollars
Oh, right, right, right, right
I'm gonna say that's not what I was looking for. Okay
Let's play
Here we go
Okay, what if I destroy her?
Where's my you know, where's my where's my 10 pound? There we go. Where's my 8 pound?
It's gonna be good. That's gonna be good
It's gonna be a strike
If it's not a strike add a million dollars to the debt
Oh my god, I get something for that. I have to
Oh shit tomato, what's up tomato raid? Let's go. What the hell is this strategy?
what
Not a bad strategy
Thanks tomato. Hope you had a good stream. Welcome everybody
You're playing um, why am I so why am I sitting?
Why am I watching her from that far away?
Aren't we together?
Why am I across the entire world?
You're not gonna pick it up. Oh my god, you left one pin
She sucks. How does it? No, she doesn't you got a nine
She's wearing heels
Oh fuck, okay, this is
Hmm
That wasn't funny this is gonna be good right here. I think we strike again
There it is. Oh, yeah, he picked it up. He's all right. He could he picked it up. He picked it up
I feel like the computer just guessed three or four times in a row
All right, so now i'm gonna i'm gonna do the comedy thing that happens in every movie by the way bowling has not appeared in a movie
in like 15 years
But every time it used to
um
Oh shit, i'm sorry. I mean nice almost good. Uh, nice try
Every like 90s movie that was a comedy they'd be a bowling segment
with
Like the person that was bowling would
Something would happen with their hand in the bowling ball and they would get stuck in there and then they would like fly down the entire bowling
uh lane
And hit the pins with their body and shit
How come they haven't made that joke in like 20 years?
Did that happen in too many movies and they were like, no, no, no, no more fly down the lane bowling joke
This is perfect. There it is
more more more more more
When was the last okay, I have homework for you guys
When you're laughing at me doing that, but you just got a gutter ball. Come on
Um, what was the last movie that had person flies down the lane holding the ball in their hand?
Uh, it happens in the avengers. No, it doesn't
It does not happen in the avengers
No, it does not it does not happen in the avengers
No, it doesn't
I
Refuse to believe that
Okay avengers bowling scene
No, there is no bowling scene in the avengers. What are you talking about?
Wait a minute. Is a bowling scene in
No, no
Don't have it right i'm gonna do two. Yeah, here we go. That's a bit
Perfect strike
It happens to thanos
Yeah, the infinity gauntlet gets stuck in the bowling ball
I don't want to take it off though
I need to keep it on
Oh, how wary is it pretending? What do you what?
Let's not be playing
Look at that spin. No, no spin at all
She's pretending she wants she's trying to get me to win
I just want 56 to 22. I win
She's literally throwing
Well, do we get more friendship?
Your bowling form was as good as ever. Yep. Okay, please come again. You want to bowl again?
So I just bowl with her until we're like dating
Hey, it's me again
I think auto needs something. What do you need?
Do you need to go outside?
Okay, uh, i'll be let me i'll be right back i'm gonna let auto outside
No, i'm joking around a lot, but I I do I think the game is fun. I enjoy it. I'll play it again
I'm not done. I don't take that as the streams over. I have to have to bowl a few more times
Uh, i'll be right back
Let me just take auto out
Otto he's like hurry up, please
You need to go outside. Let's go
Did you hear that? He was like, let's go hurry. Do you want to go outside?
Hey, is that what you want?
Yes, I know
Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Boop wine what i'm how you guys doing tonight? You guys doing good?
Didn't even ask you been almost five and a half hours and I didn't I haven't even asked
How are you doing? I hope so. Hope you're doing good. You guys ready? Let's go
Redditor room
Hmm. All right, let's do it again
You and me
Okay, shoot. What if she wins?
It's december
Yeah, it is december, isn't it?
All right eight pounds
I'm gonna try something weird here
It was nice and weird and it worked
All right, can I get three strikes in a row?
Do you think so? I think I can
Not bad to start pretending
Oh shit, okay, this is a game
Okay, I gotta be careful that I don't try to put so much spit on the ball
From here that I just rip it and it goes too high
I like to let it go too late and it goes into the other lane and hits pins down
Oh fuck that's not good. That's not good
Oh, it's I know. Oh my god, he screwed it up. I can't believe I messed it up
14 pounds that's heavy
She's like, yeah, I gotta go back i'm going back down to the six pounder
That's what I did too. You always make that mistake every time you go falling
You're doing an incredibly embarrassing
Roll with a heavy it's too heavy for you
And you go. Yeah, i'm going i'm going down to like the seven pounds. It's too uh, it's too much
It's light spin
very fast
It's gonna be another strike boys and girls
And why don't we do it again? Oh, yeah, this is gonna be awesome looking
This is gonna be like an oddly satisfying video
Oh no
Unsatisfying incredibly. Yeah, very much just go straight ahead
Philly is she on a higher difficulty her thing moves faster
She wouldn't even heavier
Back down to 10. All right, it's because of the ball weight. Oh
It's fun though this we're having fun
We're having fun
That's all that matters as long as we're just having fun
I don't care. I don't give you a gutter ball every time I do too. You're I that's cool. Let's go
Let's do it again
Wait, does it have to stop coming here?
No, please don't say that. We have a special challenge coming up and everything. It's a challenge
Just a little something special for our customers to promote better bowling skills in sexy bowling form
Doesn't sound bad except the last part
What kind of challenge?
That's a secret. You'll see for yourself when the time comes
Hmm when when does it do I can I do it now?
I help you. Uh
Can't do it now
Oh, well, hope to see you again. Yeah
That was fun
Now do karaoke
All right, i'll i'll end it on karaoke
We'll call it a night at karaoke
And then i'm planning on streaming tomorrow
but
Might change depending on how I feel
So
We'll be playing this by the way
I do want to give this game like a good proper like at least 10 to 12 hours at least
All right. I need to like not look at the chat for a second. What am I doing?
He likes it
No, I do
I was just kidding around. I was messed around
All right karaoke
We'll go here. Can I take a cab? Is it faster?
Is there another karaoke bar? All right, i'm gonna take a cab
Oh, you suck at heat moves. I'll get better at it. I promise
I want to go to
The where is it down here? It's kind of right in the middle, isn't it?
I guess I got the equal distance. I don't know why I took the taxi
Am I actually enjoying it this time? Yeah
I think it's fun. I think it's like
It's definitely interesting. It's definitely worth playing
And plus I need to get to the casino because I mean I want to get to the casino part
Am I gonna play minecraft today?
Um, no
Oh, there's a battle
Hold on one sec otto. Do you need to go outside again?
He wants something else. Do you want do you need something else?
What else do you what do what do you need?
Do you want attention?
He's like pay attention to me
What do you need?
You need something else you need more things
What? Okay, i'm gonna we're gonna run around in the we're gonna run around in the other room for a minute
And then i'm gonna maybe you want to what do you want? Let's find out
All right, give me one more second. I'm gonna take care of miss otto. What do you need? Tell me again?
Okay, show me. Uh, i'll be right back. You already see he's like, okay
Yeah, he just started sprinting out of the room when I was like, okay, i'm and he went
What is what do you need?
His tail is just wagging wagging wagging wagging. What do you need? Okay, come show me i'll be right back
Okay, I think he's good now las vegas. He's the giant rat that makes all the rules
All right, let's do some karaoke and then we'll call it a mustache hair
It is pretty mustache hair, isn't it? My first germa fan art, please be nice. It looks great. Well, it's good
Be nice. Of course, we will
Uh, let's go
All right, let's do it
Car door car door car door heat action car door heat action
Car door heat action
Oh my god, that was horrible
Oh
That was heinous
All right karaoke time
Which is right here
What song do you want me to sing in karaoke?
Well, this is it this is the one right this is the domino
All right. I'm gonna yeah, i'll do it. Okay sing
This is it
All right. Here we go
You have to sing it
I don't know the lyrics
Sing it
I have to press x
Oops
Here comes here it comes i'm so excited
I
Can't sing and do this at the same time my brain has one track
I just tried to sing it and I didn't words didn't come out of my mouth
And I didn't press the buttons. I just got locked. I was I was like singing in my head like ah
I actually locked it hard locked. Oh, what a good song
A 90 that's an a minus
Good
I'm the karaoke king do it again
Do it again. Do it again
All right. I'll do all right one more time
Do judgment. I did judgment already
How about times three shine?
Yeah, we're gonna do times three lively interjection. Sure. Oh shit. I didn't even look
Oh, yeah, that's right. I'm the guy that ruins the song in the background
Yeah, i'm the guy that they uh, they escort out by the end of the song
I'm clapping along. I'm clapping along right now
Yeah
Sing along I I can't
Did he go off key? Is he drunk? I'm assuming you're probably drunk if you're sitting. I don't know if you're at a karaoke bar
Like 12 30
How about one more? Oh, wait a minute. Aren't you quite the singer customers like you brighten up my day
I'm singing the bar again will sure I was next rogue of love
Heartbreak mermaid
Lively interjections, I like this one a lot. I like this one a lot
70s love song
I love this song
Oh
Now cry cry cry
Only one mistake. Ah
All right last one
One more for the road. Here we go. Last one rogue of love
Let's go, let's do some screaming
I was like i'm singing over her
Pretty face
Would she be the one
Sir you're the only one in the bar doing that
I know every karaoke night. You gotta wait like two fucking hours to get to go, but just everybody else has to wait, too
Oh, that's not enough
All right, we're gonna do judgment. I'm gonna try to get 98
Just do them all whatever. How come I can't sing some of these? Oh, should I sing it or interjections?
sing, okay
Hold it
That's a hundred percent
Right
I think I just got a hundred percent on that. I didn't mess up one thing. Oh what what did I screw up?
No, that's all right. I got 98 very cool. All right
Uh, that's what i'm gonna call it for tonight
That's fun
It's a good game. It's fun. I like the little quirky storyline stuff little the side stuff
I know I just said the the word that you're not allowed to ever say
Save the game. Oh shit. Good call. So stream be on the lookout for sus tomorrow
because
You know, i'm kind of feeling a little under the weather and I got a covid test
I just kind of need to make sure everything's good to go. Oh my god. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
That's odd. That's too much. That's too much funny
That's a hundred community subs. What are you doing?
That's zap x
zap x
Just gave a hundred community subs
Oh my god, that's too much. That's way too much
Is that the fuck up what holy shit what are these guys saying?
Where these guys even come from I think I couldn't use the phone who's next
Uh, but seriously that's a hundred community subs is to this is that's so much. Thank you. I really appreciate it
But my god, that's an insane amount of subs to give
There we go. All right, it's saved. It's saved up
Thank you, though. Seriously
Uh, I gotta figure out what to do with all these items and stuff. I'll figure that out next time
So tomorrow keep an eye on sus the sus is going to be set for tomorrow somewhere around
I would say
Something like two-ish like two kind of like it was today
but if I if in the morning I get up and you know, obviously
I get some like results back and I need to if I feel sicker or something
I want to be very careful about that too. So
Uh, I did I felt all right today
so I really wanted to like
stream today because I know I streamed like two days ago and then a day before that and then two days before that and
um
If I feel sick if it kind of progresses then i'm not i'm obviously not going to stream and i'm just isolating right now
Until I kind of get the results and figure out what's going on. So
Uh, I feel okay though. I feel all right. I'm good. I'll let you know tomorrow
So tomorrow pre-stream give it give the sus a look and we'll go from there. Thanks everybody for watching as always
There's going to be a lot of community subs. There's a lot of subs tonight. That's going very fast
All right, my first impressions part two
of
Yakuza zero. It's I like it. It's fun. I feel like I just have barely
Started playing the video game
So I want to give it at least one more time at least I want to get I want to do one more
I don't hate it. I don't hate it. What is this?
Oh, this is the this is this is funny Jeremy, right? This is funny. Jeremy. That's a great question
Ask them. They're really they're really angry really
It's sort of million dollars to make your dream come true
I'm doing it. I did it. I said my dreams are going to come true
But it would million dollars. What do you get?
I got a steel business card. I gave me it gave me it gave me one business card. Oh cool
Yeah, i'll uh, i'll see you guys tomorrow
If I don't then obviously we'll probably maybe see the next day or if I take a good day
I don't know a couple days. Maybe we'll see
I'm just playing it by ear at this point. Uh, let's do a raid. Let's see who's streaming right now
Let's see. Who do I want to raid right now?
Who is available again? Uh raiders some of you guys from tomato. Thanks for sticking around
And thank you tomato again
It's so funny looking over in the chat and just like look at the sea of names just like do that one
This person this person this person
Okay. All right. So here's what we're gonna do
Hmm. What am I gonna do? Let me see. Hmm
Here's where you're going. You're gonna go to
Hey, critic critical is not streaming right now. Is he? Oh is he?
Oh
Well
Oh, it's because I wasn't how was I not logged in? That doesn't make any sense
How was I not logged in? Okay. Hold on. All right. Let's go raid out critical. What's he doing?
Watching he's watching tea. What is it?
There's people like this. All right dangerous google. All right. Yeah, I just like clicked on it's true
That was dangerous google search
All right, go say hi to critical and i'll see you guys soon. If I don't see you tomorrow, then i'll see you
You know when I see you
Uh, much love to you all have a great rest of your night. I'm waiting for six hours
Because I mean i'm one of those I need to see it. Come on 10 seconds
10 seconds, but i'm gonna get the intro the outro
five four three
two one
Yeah, all right six. We made it keep an eye on south. I'll see you guys soon. Take care everybody and good night