Alright, this one we're playing is Stay Out of the House, which I'm saving this one for probably
the last one I do today, because this is probably going to send me into another dimension.
Alright, volume. What am I doing about the volume here? How low should I make it?
Is it one of those scenarios where this should be like 20%, like 10%? I currently have it at like
30% right now. We'll see. 7%. Alright, should I keep? What should I do here? Keep it at
turn it off? VHS? CRT off? VHS on? Or everything off? Alright, let's get a poll actually. I feel
like people are... Alright, am I doing filters on or filters off? On or off? Let's see. Alright,
poll. It seems to be on or off. Is it to turn all these filters on or turn at least one or two of
them on? It's literally a two minute poll. Just yes or no. 1999 is kind of scary. Off is winning by
a lot. Okay. Well, not a lot, but keep the CRT on. Off is winning by a pretty large margin now.
Okay, you guys ready? Let's go. Part one, the night shift. Medium. You might not make it out
alive. That's fine. Take the night shift. Yes. Volume is down. Here we go. By the way, I have
not been looking forward to this at all. When I knew this came out, I was pissed because I knew
I was going to have to play it eventually. I'm pissed off for doing this game up. I need to
change the game. Stay out of the house. Here we go. Okay. Want me to pick you up? Yeah, it's too
far to walk. Yeah, pick me up. Yeah, it's too far to walk. As if. I'll be conked out by then.
I'll have a beer for you later. Have fun. Just in time. Hurry up and punch in. I've got a hot day
tonight. Can I play this? Bullshit. You wish. I played this, didn't I? Come on, I've got to go.
Did you sweep the floor at least? It's a different game. Oh, okay. Sorry, dude. I was too busy. Hey,
Rick left Alyssa's side work to do on your shift. Now I've got to get out of here. Oh yeah, one more
thing. I can't find the keys anywhere. The bathrooms are locked up. So go behind the dumpster, I guess.
Have a good date. First part is the same. If my calculations are correct, I'll be running
third base of one hour and 16.32 seconds. Yeah, I played this. The prologue is the same. Oh,
all right. I remember. Yeah, I remember what happens here. This was the worst scare I've ever
had in my entire life, I believe. I remember it. It's the prologue. Should I just skip it then?
Should I just go to the second part? Or just do it and get it over with? Yeah, this was the worst
scare in my entire life. Just do it again. Oh, all right. Fine. All right. Well, you have to do like
tasks, right? Oh my god. I gotta turn the FOV down, I think. I gotta clock in. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
This tasks, right? I have to like sweep the floor and take out the trash. Turn the CRT off. Nice.
Okay, that's fun. All right. Where's the, where's my stuff I gotta do? Don't have to like mop shit
the dumpster out back. Yeah. Do I have to, I can't, how do I get out of here? Is there a key I can't
on the wall or something, right? I just don't remember. Okay. Um, yeah, here it is. Okay.
Do better job on the side work. Make sure to be finished when I come back. Okay. Sweep the floors,
place items that weren't purchased back where they belong and clean the bathrooms. Yeah. Okay.
So the items I have to replace which are not supposed to be in the right and different spot,
right? To move them on the wrong shelf. Let's see what it looks like with this off. That's way better.
I can actually look at this now. Okay. It's the broom. Thank you. Finally, finally, finally. All
right. All right. Uh, the broom is back here somewhere. There it is. All right. Sweep the
floors. They make you do all this because the game just makes you do a bunch of boring stuff
and then it just fucking screams in your face. We've seen this before. Don't spoil the whole
collection. I've already streamed this exact game though. There's a customer come. Hello. Hi. Can you
give me $10 on pump five? Yeah. Thanks. What's it? Can I help you? Can you turn the goddamn pump on?
Sorry, sir. Okay. Sweeping is done. Now I got to put these items back where they belong. So this is
a beer motor oil and chips. Okay. So chips go in the chips aisle, which is, there's a chip here.
Is this chips? Well, this is, it goes in here. Where's the gas go? Oh, okay. Here we go. Yeah.
Extra cases of, yeah. How do I put it in? All right. Put this down. Okay. I'll put it back.
It looks like this is where it goes. Oh, there we go. Okay. Um, so where do I put the beer or the
drink? I would think like right here. Yeah. And then this, this is oil now and motor oil.
Right here somewhere. Yeah. Yeah. Clean the bathrooms. All right. Okay. Here we go. It's
time. Everybody knows what's coming. Here it comes. Here we go. Where's the, it's happening.
Where is it? How do I get out of here? Where's the key? He's going to get scared again. I mean,
probably. I remember. I remember what happens, but I need to just be able to go to the,
to do the dumpster. Where's the key? There's a customer. Hi. Can I help you? Yeah. I just
need some cigarette. Okay. Okay. Which brand? Banshee red with filters. There you go. Thanks.
Oh, Hey, can I use the bathroom? I can't open it. Well, that's weird. Good luck. Thanks for the
money. Okay. Now, what if I get the key? Can't leave the store. I'm going to try so hard to not
have the jumpscare do anything. I'm going to try as hard as I can for all the people that are
trickling in. They're going to be like, what is wrong with this guy? Is he on like drugs? Like,
why did he not even react? I'm going to try to just be like this, try to, no, not going to happen.
All right. Do a poll. When the jumpscare happens, will I do a, any reaction at all? Yes or no?
Let's bet. I'm going to, I'm seriously going to try. I know when the jumpscare happens,
I'm going to desperately try, uh, do a bet. Will I show any emotion during the jumpscare? Yes or no?
That's easy money. Well, let's see, put your money where your mouth is then. I know precisely when
it happens to all in, this is going to be close 20 million versus 12 million points.
Please don't react. I will try. Okay. It's locked in. Um, how do I proceed the game?
It has to be absolutely no reaction. I'm talking about this like that. I'm just going to go like
this. All right. Okay. Like this. Am I missing something here? Am I, am I not pressing a button
to keep this going? I think I have to play the arcade game. All right. It's coming soon.
Yeah, I did play this before. This apparently is the prologue to the new one. So that doesn't
count. That's not, that does not count. That's not what we're talking about. Don't do not pay
anybody up. Don't pay anybody. Nobody gets paid at all. We're not doing that because that's not
what I was talking about. That does not count. That's not the jumpscare. Nope. I didn't say
a jumpscare. I said the jumpscare. No, it doesn't count. That does not count. Dude, I'm dead now.
All right. Where's this key? Here it is. Please pretend like you've never played before. Yeah,
I will. Somebody's coming in. There's a customer. Okay. Hi, you're here all alone. No, no, my
coworkers in the back. What are you getting? Oh, could you help me? I don't remember where the
sodas are. This whole thing looks the same. Every aisle is the same with items on it.
It's hard for me to understand where I am. You ever played a level with cement on it?
I get you, man. I do. Thank you. So what even happens in this game? Wait, oops. Don't tell
them. Nobody tell them. Okay. How do I open this? Read the note. I've already done everything.
I swept the floors. I placed the items where in the end and I just need to clean the bathroom.
But you need the key to do that. Where's the key? Put the volume up. Volume up? It's going to be
probably really loud. I don't know if I want to do that. Volume up. Are you sure about that? Be
aware. This could get loud. What was that sound? Something's here. Okay. That was weird sound.
Okay. I need to find cleaner. Okay. Nothing special. I did not react. That was zero reaction.
Zero. I win. He blinked. Okay. Here we go. Now we're in the game.
You died so someone else could live. That's crucifixion now. Amen. Amen.
You've reacted. Wait, are we playing the game? Turn it up or turn it down? Just be aware of
these games are loud and like adjust your volume accordingly. Seriously. How long have I been out?
Was he not back yet? You in there? You're good. Having some trouble with the door. Hold on.
Oh, I can turn this down. Don't. Coward. I'm just saying the game is loud as fuck and I'm telling
you I'm warning you for real. Lower your volume. Okay. It's a point where it hurts your ears.
I'm going to. Okay. I'm saving everybody. I'm bringing the jumpscares down to like
60% 50%. I'm just telling you. Let me see how loud that is. I'll turn the master volume up.
Actually, I don't want to do. Don't play the game. Seems like someone lost this. What is that doing?
Beginning of this upcoming month, all work and productions conducted at the Crawford mill will
cease to continue due to a lack of business over the past year. The owners unfortunately cannot
afford to keep the mill open and running. Therefore will be condemned and sold to the state. They'll
repurpose the building or demolish it. Okay. His wife will be moving away from Cedarville in hopes
to find a better treatment center close to the city. He sends his deepest apologies to all
employees who have dedicated their time and efforts toward the betterment of the company.
Okay. Creepy dog. Hi dog. What's up? Wow. That's a lot. Something bad is going to happen to the dog.
I already know it and it's going to be so sad and it's going to be, I'm going to be pissed.
Yep. Something bad is going to happen to the dog. Lala. I can't get through this. Okay. So let's
just go and go this way. Is a child a teddy bear glasses? Whose dog is this? This is a briefcase.
God plug it. Hey, hey, hey. Okay. You're not going to give me a goddamn cornfield to go through.
Are you? Dead end. Yeah. God damn it. All right. I can remember that's there. Okay. I just got to
go through it. All right, dog. You and me into the cornfield. Oh, it hurts to do this too. Oh,
what's dog going? Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Where are you going?
Where are you going? What are you eating? Don't eat. Don't eat stuff you find on the ground.
What are you doing? Don't eat stuff on the ground. We're all parishioners. Okay. Assembly of God of
some unfortunately sudden and upcoming changes to our standards of curriculum. Being sad with a
heavy heart, our family of religious followers have turned elsewhere. There are a few who, okay.
They're not following the Bible and it is my understanding that their syllabus is full of
nonsensical gibberish. I don't know who of what they are worshiping, but friends and colleagues
of mine have started to treat me as a stranger. Holy shit. Last night while eating with my family,
a bullet was fired through my kitchen window. It barely missed my head. It has completely
obliterated one of my favorite paintings given to me by one of my choir members. I'll be leaving
town. I do not wish to leave, but feel as if I have no choice. And I'd advise anyone who still
comes to our church to join me towards our new place of hope and prosperity. Thank you for your
kindness and understanding. Stop. Don't, don't eat that. Don't eat that. Where's the dog? Where's
the dog? Come over here. Don't waste it. Keep staying with me, please. This way. I don't think
he wants to come with me. Where's the dog? What should I do? Is there another way to go?
Through the cornfield? There has to be another way to go. Okay. Thank God that was you.
Uh, I'm going this way. Uh, uh, huh? What? Okay. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. Oh shit. Okay.
Good find. What have we? Shirt? What is this? An ID? Weird. What happened here? ID? Our mission,
the Church of Father's Vision. Goal of the Church of Father's Vision is to create a community
abundant with repentance and salvation. We will help you attain a growing relationship between
yourself and the Lord, either at one of our many days of worship in person or via weekly tapes,
which will be delivered to your doorstep. We seek to spread the message of God across the
world to provide the unknowing, ignorant, or those in need with the everlasting life he has
waiting for us all. Our pastor, Dr. James F. Buu, is an authentic server of God since early
childhood, a married man, father, and beloved pastor. He firmly believes in living by Christ
through spreading his gospel and encouraging his neighbors to worship the Lord with him at the
Church of Father's Vision. This is so good. Get off me. Okay. God in his goodness has called on me
to preach to the world. My desire is to please and glorify him. It's happening in my mouth.
And I hope to join hands with the world and live by his word. Okay. Dr. Buu and his wife, Margaret
Buu, hold service at the Church of Father's Vision each Sunday at 1115. Located at this
Georgetown, Kentucky. VHS tapes and more. Okay. The Church of Father's Vision, let us guide you
towards righteousness. Anything else I can grab here? A dress? Check under the car? Did I touch
everything? I think I see everything, right? What are you looking at? I'm just going to leave. I
don't know what way to go. I think I'm going the other way that I just came. I think I came from
this way. Dog check. Yeah, this is the church. Is there any other way I can go? Shit, this is
where the church is. This is nothing here. Is there a direction down here I didn't go? Cement game,
but it's made out of corn instead. True. All right. I don't think I went this way.
I don't like it. The name of this game is stay out of the house.
Why would I go in the house? Where's the dog? I don't know what to do. No, no, no, no, no, no,
don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. No. Where am I? I'm trying to find you. Where is he?
What kind of weird house is this? Why is it? No. Upstairs? Where is he? He is down here. Where?
No. Are you okay? How do I help? Please, please, please, please. How do I help? I need to help.
You okay? No, no. Bad idea. Bad idea. Really bad idea. Bad idea. Bad idea. What?
What? It was a bait. It was bait. It was literally bait. I'm taking these up. That was the soap.
It was bait. It was a Halloween decoration. Should have stayed out of the house, dude.
This is going to suck. My stomach. What did he do? What's this for? This is going to be a granny
game. This is a grandma game. Otherwise I can't do these ones. I can't do grandma games. I pitched
sounds. Is it better? Be quiet. All right. Get me out of here. I think this is like a lamp with
skin. How do I get the fuck out of here? Heal the cage back. Upper back corner. What do I just do?
Turn light on. Fuck you. Oh, fuck you. Don't even. Hold on. Can I do anything over here?
I just filled that with gas? What the fuck is in here? It's a clock. Dude, where should I put it?
Light meter? It's set to nine o'clock. Should I remember that? Okay. Nine o'clock. Toolbox is
locked. Where should I bring this? I don't know. Just turn all the lights on maybe first. There's
another way to go. I'm going to bring that into here. The clock. He hates. What'd you say? I'm
really not. Honestly, I'm really not good at granny likes. Oh, fuck you. Night shift abductors
strikes again. Granny likes. Yeah. So what a granny like is a game where you is a game where
you have to pick up like rope. Bring the rope downstairs to grab that thing. When you grab that
thing, there's bubble gum in it. You take the bubble gum up to the room upstairs and put it
under the sink to plug the hole. Then you can get the water with the cup that you have to find down
in the basement, which you can only get there if you open the door with the key that you find
underneath the bed. I'm not good at granny likes. 34 year old Deborah is the latest victim of the
notorious night shift abductor relocation show video evidence of the same abductor
at multiple locations between Custer County and its surrounding areas.
All six abductions have had very similar circumstances. He was alone in the shift
in the dead of night was confronted by the assailant after a period of observation
when the venue was at a period of little to no business. Okay. Okay. He's mid to late 30s
standing at roughly six four and assumed 250 pounds. Very few other details of the assailant
are known. His identity as well as concealed during the assault via a makeshift burlap mask
and thick seasonal clothing. Okay. Okay. These incidents do not appear to be slowing down
much longer. Are we to expect this to the slow unproductive case to continue?
You better not start. You're going to start moving. Aren't you paperclip? Thank you. Valley
cover versus brand new lock has a preset code, which cannot be changed. We would advise storing
this paper. So, okay. Combination is four question mark 62 or something six two. All right. That's
for the padlock that was in the other room or something. Oh my God. No, or something six two.
Let's brute force it. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. What do I do? What? How do I turn it off?
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Quiet. Shut up. Shut the fuck up. Shut up.
Shut the fuck up. Where do I go? How do I hide from this guy? Oh my God. Under the bed. He's
not here. Screwdriver. Got it. Okay. Screwdriver. Undo the, uh, undo. Okay. This is the thing with
the gas. Where's the room with the gas in it? Fuck you. I hate granny likes. So unscrew it. Um, excuse
me. I have a screwdriver in my hand. Is there, can I save the game? Wood, water, water, as well as
medical tools and treatments. Oh, oh, okay. That's very, very appreciated. I can only save the game
like three times. Yeah, that was loud too, wasn't it? Dude, it's fucking loud. I'm bringing like this
down just like to 90. You know what I mean? It's loud. What? Okay. So I just keep going. The camera?
Blind. What? Blind? What do you mean blind? I missed something. What'd I miss? It's intense.
I'm terrified. What'd I miss? I miss something. Miss something. Oh, it feels like I've been locked
in this house for weeks, but it's only been a few days. I'm losing track of time. I hear wailing
coming from under the house. What is he doing down there? I can't thinking about that. There were
tunnels down there. It looked like they went on forever. I tried to escape, but he caught me with
that damn radar. He locked me back upstairs, but I saw where he keeps the radar. Locked it in the
closet. The combination was five, two, nine, one. Don't forget that number. Jesus. What did it say?
Locked? Do I have a key for this? Yeah. Fucking granny. Can I sneak it? Right. Are they even alive?
What door? Where am I? No, not the fucking house.
Quick, take everything I can. Take the hand. Take the hand. Take the hand. I can't.
Oh, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Fuck. Two days remain. I'm not going to be able to be a granny
like it. I don't. I will. I've never completed a granny like it's never happened. Where am I now?
Dude, what is going on right now? What the fuck? Do I have to stare at this? What's going on? Look
at me. I keep doing this. Ow. I'm so glad I turned it down. Sacrifice. And that's at like 50%. Where
am I now? I'm turning it down even more. Turn it down. Turn it down. Turn it down. Turn it down.
I'm dead. Take the door hinges off. These games are so fucked up. I'm not turning it up. Is it?
Is that actually it? Or is there more? I think I lost the house. So there's a part four. You lost.
Yeah. I got the bad ending. All right. Should I try this one more time? I feel like I'm never
going to beat this. Okay. I'm going to try it again. Turn it back up a little bit. I try one
more time. I usually don't play granny likes. I really don't. Granny likes are cool, but there's
so much intense shit going on that my brain only can focus on the scary parts and I can't figure
out where the bubble gum goes. Yeah. This part. There was another place I could go down too,
wasn't there? Just say survival horror. Well, not every survival horror is a granny like.
I'm going to go back down to where that place where I was before. This way, right? There were
two places to go down. I kind of feel like I want to. No, not this way. All right. I got to stop
looking at chat. I got to pay attention to where the fuck I'm going. All right. This way. Okay.
This time don't wake the grandma. What? What's happening? Why did I? I just, I just moved.
My body just moved all over the place. What am I looking at here? Huh? What? Bandages. That's it,
right? Locked. How do I get the fuck out of here? Am I stuck in here? Can't reach. Grab climbing.
Oh my God, dude. Go for, go forward. Go. So that was what was on the other side. Okay. Don't
go near granny. It's all locked. It's in here. Toilet. Toilet lid. Paperclip. Can I use it? I
think I could use this on locked doors, right? It shows a crowd draining a man's blood. Is it
like a little remote controlled car going around the halls? I think I can hide in here. All right.
I got a hammer. Titanium lock. Okay. I have a couple of, uh, I can pick some locks, right?
Let's try picking a lock. I can't pick this. Okay. We saw this already. You got to use the
paperclip. Okay. I remember doing. Yep. This is, did I do the? Yeah. I already got it. Okay. So now
how do I use the paper clips? Okay. So I can't do anything else up here. What is that? Hit him in
the back of the head with a hammer. I don't know. I can't see him. No, no, no. Don't come in here.
Where is he? I don't know. Is he left or right? Oh, please. I'm going to set it up right here.
Ding dong. Come and fucking get me right here. Come and get me. Come and get me. Hammer. You need
to R1, R1, R1 granny. Am I going to touch this? Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha. Oh my God. Oh,
no. He turned the gas on. I don't think I can swing. This game is so fucking horrible. I just,
I'm too like, I'm too like erratic to play these. And I had, I had, I tried to hit him with the
hammer. I couldn't hit. You need to calm down. All right. I'm going to try to reload the game.
I'm going to try it one more time and I'm going to calm down. I'm going to calm down. Here we go.
I'm going to do it very calmly. I don't do, I can't play granny legs. I told you I installed
granny too. And when I found out that I had to go up the stairs, pick up the hammer or pick up the
wood and go down the stairs, I was like, I held my finger on the button on the iPad and then
press the X button. I can't play granny legs. I can't do it. Rock. Hold on. Wait, can I throw,
I'm going to try to throw a rock at granny's head. Will this work? Did I hit her? How did I drop the
rock on the ground? Oh, I think I, I don't think I can do it. I'm too fucked up. End of the stream
voice. Um, no, no, not yet. I love, okay. I like, I like these games. I like watching people play
these games and know what they're doing. See me. I, I just like walk up to granny and she screams at
me. And then I sprint around in a circle and try to hide under the bed and die. True. Was there
anything even in here? I don't think so. It was a bandage, but like that's going to help. Yeah,
there's nothing, there's nothing here. I remember getting stuck here though. Okay. All right. Oh,
come on. Not even a hard game. What do you have here? What do you, what's this? What do I do? Can
I touch something? Lock? Um, nothing on the ground in here. This is locked. I need to, I can't open
it. She's coming back now. Um, I gotta turn this off somehow. Shit. Cardboard box. Nothing, nothing.
Oh, another vent. Okay. Unscrew it please. Unscrew it. Hot steam. I could die. What the fuck was that?
What? I just, what did I just do? I can't take it off. This is a way to escape. I see this. I'm too
s- I'm, I don't get this part. Can I turn this off with anything? Probably. I gotta go upstairs and
in the bathroom and pick up the gum and bring the gum down here and plug it. Um, I don't, I don't
know. I don't have anything to open this with. What about this? Wait, this is where I just was,
right? Yeah. What did I just hear? Can I just go through this room? Stop. Who's coming? I don't,
I can't go through there. All right. I do have to go upstairs. It was, there was a code that I had,
right? In the closet. Five two something. I just don't know where that is. You stupid motherfucker.
I hate your guts. You suck. I'm done. I can't do it. I'm done. I'm done. I can't do it. I can't do
the granny likes. I can't like run up and down the stairs. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do
it. It's, I, I, I have to, I can't do it. I can't do it. All right. So we're going to, all right.
The code was five two nine one. I don't know what, I don't know where to put it.
Skill issue. Yeah. I just don't, I don't play granny likes. It's a good game. All right. We're
going to play something else. What else we got? We have first one. Do it your way. My way doesn't
work because you have to, if you get spotted, they kill you.