No, my points. What do you mean, fuck off? I- I don't- I can't be- Look, what do you want me to pick?
I- Now, here's the best part about this, I'll tell you before I even get started.
People want me to be late now, so they make fake internet currency money.
Holy shit. I can game this.
What, you're telling me that I could make, like, essentially, potentially, 40 to 50% of you incredibly happy if I show up, like, 15 minutes late?
Holy shit. I'm gonna have to think about this one.
Rigging the system. No, I didn't even know this was- I- Okay, I knew- Let me be very clear.
I knew the gambling thing was going on.
Like, an hour ago, I was like, oh, I think they're gonna do that.
I knew that- I know that's going on. I didn't intend to try to get here on time, but I did.
I just- I happened to be sitting here.
You're a minute late. What? No, I started- No, you- Just because you clicked on the notification a minute after I went live doesn't mean I went live when you clicked it.
Insider trading.
Anyways, how you guys doing? Hope you're doing well.
We're gonna do- I'm gonna make a lot of people really sad and really angry, probably, when I say this, but I'm gonna say it, and here we go.
This is week two, where I have told you that we were gonna play a first-party Nintendo game, and it didn't happen.
Last week was Paper Mario. It got delayed.
And this week was supposed to be Pikmin 2. That got delayed, too.
The plan is to do that- I don't have it yet.
I'll be honest with you. I'm supposed to have it tomorrow or the next day.
Coin game is way better, but that's the best part.
We found out that coin game got a major update.
There's a new arcade, there's a mini golf course, there's eight new games, and there's a survival game.
Survival mode.
And this is one of my favorite games on Steam, so if there's a major update for it, I'm gonna play it.
Also, I have a schedule for you for this week.
Would you like to hear it?
No schedule, Andy, has actual planned things for you this week.
You ready?
Today, coin game, for a little while, whenever we get sick of it.
Tomorrow, in quotes, hopefully, Pikmin 2.
Friday, in quotes, hopefully, Pikmin 2.
And then, week after that, on like, Tuesday?
Wednesday?
Slime Rancher.
There you go.
Look at that.
I'm gonna start Slime Rancher.
That's something everyone wants me to play.
Those are not lies.
No.
They're not lies.
I'm gonna play Slime Rancher next week.
Holy shit.
No way.
I know.
That isn't a schedule.
Yes, it is.
I'm planning out what I'm gonna do for the next week.
Tomorrow, 4 o'clock Pacific, Pikmin 2.
Friday, 4 o'clock Pacific, Pikmin 2.
And then, Wednesday, the 10th, 4 o'clock Pacific, Slime Rancher.
Thursday, Friday, Slime Rancher.
And then...
Oh, you want more of a schedule?
On...
No, I'm not doing that.
That's what forced me to play like Ratatouille.
I'm not doing that.
5.7 million go to Buff Bones and 210 other people that made a bunch of money.
All right.
I didn't even tweet this out.
Give me a second.
Give me one second.
We're back.
All right.
I fell up the stairs.
Yes, I did.
I had to...
Let me ask everybody here.
Do you guys do two steps at a time or one step at a time on a staircase?
Going up.
Going down, it's always one for me.
Going up, it's always two.
But us two-step chads, that comes with a little bit of a problem.
You might miss and go...
Happens a lot.
Or you might not get your footing correct.
And then you hit the part of your knee right where your shin connects to your knee
and it just hurts for the next three days.
What the hell?
Why do I have this many viewers?
What's going on?
What the fuck's happening?
23,000 viewers and then to...
What is happening?
What the fuck?
We got a raid already?
Or is this lag?
I have negative 10,000 viewers?
What?
What just happened?
Oh shit.
What does that even mean?
It was...
Yeah, that was very strange.
Well, whatever.
I'm ready to play.
We're going to play the coin game, as you know.
Hey, all left.
I don't even know what happened.
I didn't see a raid or anything.
All right.
Should I do survival or should I do...
Because this is a new...
What should I do?
It was a raid?
How come I don't see it?
Wait, did the raid...
I missed it?
I don't see it anywhere on any dashboards or anything or any...
Who was it?
Was it actually Ludwig?
Oh shit.
I don't see it anywhere.
Well, that's...
Well, what's up?
Thanks, guys.
Ludwig viewers are always welcome in the Germabite community, of course.
As long as they stay.
As long as they pay.
By the way, let's do survival mode.
Should I do survival?
How do you survive in an arcade?
Raid song.
Let me see if I can get this.
I'm just the annoying guy at the Best Buy that's at the fucking Casio keyboard,
just turning it on and pressing buttons.
I can't do two things at once.
Hey, take a look at this keyboard we have over here.
Yeah, it's a good one.
It's got organs.
It's got every trumpet you could imagine.
It's got an amazing orchestra.
Get out of the way!
Sir, I...
Sir, you're getting hands all over...
I'll take it.
And then you see the price tag and those things are like fucking $4,000.
And then you go, ooh, and you back up like slowly Jim Carrey style.
What were we doing?
Anyways, thanks for the raid.
Thanks, Ludwig.
Welcome, everybody.
Health and energy system in place.
Work odd jobs or scavenge to earn money.
Pawn your prizes to get cash to keep going.
Eat junk food to stay healthy.
That doesn't make any sense.
Keep mom happy by making your nightly curfew.
How many days can you last?
Your problem involves eating junk food and soda to keep your health up.
Work odd jobs around the island.
This sounds like fun.
Or scavenge for junk in the trash to earn money.
Turn on face cam?
No, I can't.
No, I'm not ready for a face cam.
I'm not ready for a face cam.
All right.
What if I...
No, I can't do the thing that everybody copies and pastes.
I have to stop.
If I say I'm not going to do something, I can't do it.
Otherwise, you'll have fuel to put that anywhere.
Are you naked?
No, I'm not naked.
How do I look today?
Actually, I kind of look pretty damn good.
I can keep it on.
Is it delayed?
Wait, is it delayed?
It's very blue.
Well, it won't be in a minute.
How about just really tiny?
I don't want a face cam on.
I'm not a face cam streamer.
You guys already know that.
I only face cam during horror games, VR, and when I have to eat Burger King on stream.
All right.
Let's go.
It's delayed?
It looks like it is.
Why?
It shouldn't be.
All right.
Well, whatever.
I'm going to turn it off randomly.
Prediction started.
What?
Win channel points if you make the correct prediction.
What's the prediction?
What is this?
What are you guys voting on?
Predict with channel...
I can't even see what this is.
Will Jerma...
What is it?
Will Jerma beat Dizzy Bird?
Will Jerma play Dizzy Bird as the first game?
Well, I can't...
I must...
I...
Well, now...
I wasn't supposed to look.
Well, I don't have that information.
All right.
Survival.
Let's go.
This will delete...
Who cares?
I have to eat food out of the trash.
Just live.
I want a refund.
We did it.
We got a refund.
Anybody want any dirt water?
Eddie and the Ticket Eaters.
Why is this delayed?
It is.
What's going on here?
Get your Islandville official merch and support development.
Brought to you by...
All right.
Holy shit, I have a ton of stuff over here.
Wait, why do I have a machine in my house?
New text message.
Press tab.
Oh, I've got an Apple phone.
Welcome to the coin game.
Smartwatch tutorial.
Yeah, Islandville Barry's Pawn Shop.
Gary.
Okay, hold on a minute.
This is a whole new game mode.
I got $2.50.
Can you guys hear this?
Okay, I'm not going to look.
I saw the prediction started.
I'm not going to look at it.
If I look over here, you know I'm cheating.
I can't look over here and chat.
Yeah, I know this is the best game on Steam.
I know it's tab.
This is a map.
Messages menu.
Here it is.
Islandville news.
Barry's Pawn Shop.
I got junk.
You can bring it there.
You can sell it.
Don't forget about your curfew.
Looks like it's 7 15 a.m.
Looking for a babysitter.
The Jones family.
Okay.
Gary.
Golf cart for sale.
Okay.
I need my lawn mode from Barry.
How do I...
Bus stop, right?
Okay, there's the map.
Can I move this around?
How do I like accept a quest?
What do I have?
The coin game.
I can't look at chat.
I didn't see anything, but I'm just going to look over there.
Actually, wait.
What's this?
Soda pop tonic.
Which...
Which one are...
What is it?
I don't know.
That's my Steam name.
Okay.
This is free.
Well, there's sodas in here and shit.
I don't know.
I thought this was a soda pop and tonic machine.
I'm not looking.
I swear to God.
I have no idea what you're predicting.
I have absolutely no idea.
I have no clue.
I'm going to get this, though.
I want to look over there, but I fucking can't do it.
I so badly want to look at you.
Okay, what if there's something wrong with the stream?
What if my bitrate went down or something?
How am I ever going to know?
I need to be able to look over there.
And by the way, when am I going to know when this is over?
I'm not going to know.
What if I just did it?
What if I already did it?
How am I ever going to find out?
And why are we giving these secret slime actions or predictions?
I mean, it's kind of fun, but that is fun.
Keep doing it.
I can't talk to anybody.
This feels weird.
I don't like this.
This feels strange.
I'm just like talking at the monitor.
I'm very alone right now.
Like, I'm very aware of how alone I am in this room
because I can't like look over there and see everybody talking.
What if they're trying to give me advice?
This is freaking me out.
All right.
It stopped.
What happened?
I saw the purple.
Will Jerma beat the first game within five tries?
I didn't know that's what was going on.
I didn't know that's what you guys were doing.
220 million go to hee ha ha ha poo poo.
I can't believe that you can have...
Hee ha ha poo poo poo poo is like a password you use
for a website you know you're going to log into one time
and never fucking open it again.
Well, I can't beat that one.
So, yes, I can.
No, I can't.
I need to survive.
I need to eat food.
I was just off the hook.
Oh, wait, I can watch TV?
When did they add all this?
Oh, shoot.
How do I press the buttons?
Oh, E key.
Get up here.
Get up here and sit down and sit down and watch TV with your friend.
Well, I just starved to death on the couch.
Well, I got to turn this up.
Oh, it is up all the way.
Really?
You guys heard?
Seven, eight, eight, five.
Dirt water.
We love you.
Fairy buys anything.
I fucking hate when you drink a coffee
or anything and that you have the layer of ice,
the ice layer that you can't drink through.
It pisses me off.
Hey there, everyone.
Because now I can't even enjoy that coffee.
I might as well just throw it away.
All right, let's get up.
I want to just look at the new features.
Can I play with the duck?
Same.
Did I brush my teeth?
Yeah, I did.
There's a fish tank, too.
I need to eat something.
Okay, 41 energy, 78 health.
I have $2.50.
How do I get money?
Oh, a flasher on top of the toilet.
Oh, wait, you guys can't see this.
I should probably move this.
There, see?
Now you can see what I'm talking about.
Do I face cam?
Like, fuck face cam.
I don't want to ever use it.
Look at it.
Look what I did.
I just ruined the beginning of the game for you.
50 gun.
All right.
Is this my mother?
F key, inventory.
I just hit my mother in the face with a flashlight.
Put the gun down.
Oh, nice, pizzas.
Okay, I can take these.
This is a Salisbury steak TV dinner.
How much food?
What's my health at?
Dinners must be cooked in the microwave before eating.
Okay.
Does the whole box go in?
This looks actually kind of good.
Oh, it's like the kid cuisines.
I remember those.
Those things were awesome.
What's beeping?
What is beeping?
All right, get that.
Get over here.
Do I have to take it out?
I feel like this is a funny bit part of like a caveman movie.
Like caveman is in the real world now and he's got like time traveled or something.
Right?
How do I turn it on?
Set timer.
Did you see someone?
I missed what you said.
How do I turn it on?
How do I turn on?
It's done?
No, dinners must be cooked in the microwave.
Well, get in there.
Anybody else?
When they cook something in the microwave.
When it's done, you're afraid to like open it up too quickly.
Like two, one, open.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't go near it.
What are you talking about?
Don't go over there.
Wait like at least 10 seconds for the radioactive air to like dissipate.
Right?
That freaks me out.
Doesn't it?
Do you freak you out?
How many of you guys are at zero?
Open up and grab.
Like I feel like this radioactive activity in there.
You want some?
Wait, can we share this?
Oh, I have a plate now.
Okay, cool.
What do I do with the plate?
You're insane.
I'm just saying.
I don't know.
Oh, swan goose.
Can I eat dog food?
All right.
I'm going to put this in my.
I'm going to put all this stuff in my inventory.
This is all food and stuff.
This is a extra stretchy.
I don't know.
Whatever it is.
I'm going to eat them.
Whatever they are.
Fish flakes.
Just eat them.
Okay.
I got plenty of food now.
All right.
Now I'm going to go make money.
I have a ton.
I've got a good.
Oh, I ride the bike.
No, I can't ride the bicycle.
All right.
What have I got?
My map.
Okay.
Somebody needed their lawn mode.
We need to do lawn mode.
Make sure you're eating and drinking.
What kind of text message?
Why'd you hit enter that many times, Ma?
What the fuck are you doing?
Make sure you're eating and drinking enough and don't forget to be home before your curfew
tonight.
Hope you win lots of junk and stuff or whatever the cool kids call it nowadays.
Please don't make nanny bot come looking for you again.
She's really.
She's getting pretty rusty.
Okay.
So that means these ones had stuff to do, too.
Move her babysitter.
We're looking for a babysitter to help us with the little ones.
It's easy work and we will pay well.
If you'd like to help us out and earn some extra money, just come to the front door of
the house on the map closest to the paper route stand.
We are also located on the map as a boot icon close to the newspaper stand boot icon next
to the newspaper stand.
That looks like a boot.
All right.
That is my vehicle.
Ride the bike, please.
I can.
You can ride the bike.
Well, how do I get on it?
I'm wasting too much energy trying to ride the bike.
It's F right click.
What the hell?
All right.
I'm on the bike.
This is like going to make me throw up.
Can I move the camera back?
The handlebars to mount bike W A S D controls the movement and mouse looks around F key
and V key will lean back and forth.
Left shift is bunny hop.
Where am I going?
F key and V key.
Lean back.
Oh, that's OK.
E will exit the bike.
All right.
I need my map.
Where am I going?
E hop.
All right.
I need to do a job.
I can hit by a car.
Do a backflip.
I need to get off the bike.
I need my map.
All right.
We need to take a left.
We're going to go take a left on this road up here.
I'm going to go straight.
Let's make it fast.
Don't laugh at car accidents.
It's too early for you to do that.
I'm just barely getting started.
All right.
Then take a left.
Where do I take a left?
Up here?
Did I pass it already?
I'm good.
That looked a lot bigger on the map, though.
Give me a little bit of credit.
OK.
And then it's down here.
I feel like I'm going faster than thirty five.
All right.
Here's a job.
I can do a job right here.
What is this job?
I got something in my throat.
I'm going to turn the camera off.
I had a kale salad earlier and I think I swallowed a little bit in my lungs.
All right.
Let's go.
So grab.
A paper?
Newspaper delivery.
You can earn some extra money by delivering papers to the good people of Island Village.
Just go to the newspaper van located outside by your house.
Every day, you'll see more snacks of papers to be delivered to all the red mailboxes of
the island.
They're marked as red mailboxes on the minimap.
You get a dollar fifty per paper plus one rubber band.
And if you deliver all the papers to all the boxes, you get a nice bonus.
OK.
Let's go.
Oh, fuck.
I can only hold that many?
Why can I only hold that many?
I can only hold like three fucking newspapers?
Why?
Why are you guys saying gas?
All right.
Red mailboxes.
Let's see.
Is there one over here?
The mic is delayed.
It's not.
It's a red mailbox.
Let's see what's on this street.
OK.
This is not a red mailbox.
I have a red mailbox.
There's two houses on this street are red mailboxes.
Let's go.
It's delayed.
The inventory is full.
God.
Hey, hey.
OK.
This is a...
Is this a mailbox?
Do you need a paper?
Mute.
He's muting.
Please.
There's a delay.
I'm taking a hundred million off the debt.
Not a delay.
It's not a delay.
I'm taking a hundred million back.
Better?
Better, right?
There it is.
Yeah, we're good.
Now I just look...
I'm just darker now.
I'll fix that.
Watch this.
Ready?
Want to see a trick?
If you don't...
If you need extra light on your face and you're like a streamer or a YouTuber or whatever,
you get the expensive ring lights and you get lighting all over you and then you don't
have to do that shit.
Don't have to do that.
If you have more than one monitor, or even if you have one and you're recording, just
open up MS Paint, fuck that guy, open up MS Paint, have a full white background, just
open up a white screen.
I'll show you.
And just like that, I've gave myself much better lighting.
I can do this better.
You just need paint.
You don't even need...
They sell these lights for like fucking a thousand dollars.
Hey, you want to see how to save yourself a thousand fucking dollars?
This is just a white background.
What's up?
Put that on your other monitor, make it nice and big like this.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Yeah, this is just a...
I'm just opening more white backgrounds.
Oh fuck, I broke my mic.
I mean, no, I didn't.
All right, I'm going to open another white background over here.
All right, we're good.
The only thing, now I can't see if any like raids come in.
Whatever, look, it's perfect.
You need to buy expensive lighting.
No, you don't.
I think there's a bug in my room.
It's still delayed.
It's not.
There's no delay.
There ain't a delay.
I can see on my screen.
Oh, red mailbox.
If you have a delay, then it's...
Maybe you have like less than a 1080 or something.
All right, how do I do this?
Red mailbox.
All right, deliver the mail.
Inventory?
Okay.
I only have $4.50.
You're streaming 720p, idiot.
You know, when I get my new computer, I'm not even going to tell you guys I got a new
computer.
And we're going to see if any of you fucking cheeky bastards can tell the difference.
I bet you you won't be able to tell the difference.
Get in there.
What the fuck?
This job sucks.
It says it on Twitch.
Oh, well, whatever.
Oh my God, that's hard.
There's a delay, trust me.
I would like a mod or moderator in the chat right now to speak up here and tell me if
there was a delay on my voice or the game.
I want to see a moderator tell me this.
A moderator.
Fuck.
I couldn't read it.
Let me look at the...
Hold on.
Let me look at the mod discord.
Is there a delay on the stream?
There is.
Yes, there is.
What?
How?
Is this even possible?
It doesn't make any sense.
What is how?
It doesn't...
It's not possible.
I don't have any delays.
What?
This is insane.
How much of a delay?
Look at it.
Red alert.
What?
100 million added.
No.
What?
This doesn't make any sense.
It's very slight.
Oh, we've got a new...
Let me see.
Let me see what this looks like.
Hold on.
I'm fucking confused as hell.
I don't see it on my end.
Don't delay.
There ain't a delay.
I can see on my screen.
Oh, red mailbox.
If you have a delay, then it's your...
Maybe you have like less than a 1080 or so.
Why is that happening?
I don't see that on my end.
Why is it coming through the stream like that?
What the fuck?
I didn't make any sense.
Did I fix it?
Tell me if I fixed it.
Is it fixed?
Hi.
Wait, do I just talk weird?
Do sounds come out of my mouth before my mouth starts moving?
I think that's happening.
Is that how I talk?
Wait, hold on.
Hi.
Sounds are coming up before my mouth opens.
What's up?
What's happening?
Sounds are coming up before my mouth is closed, before my mouth is done closing.
I'm finishing my sentence before my...
I'm finishing the sentence before my mouth closes.
I talk weird.
I said weird and my mouth closed after the D.
That was really weird.
I think I just talk weird.
Snap your fingers.
That was delayed?
That was...
But that...
You guys are freaking me out.
I think he's insane.
Your voice is too fast for your mouth.
The video is delayed.
All right, hold on.
How about this one?
What if I do this?
How's that?
Does that change anything?
What's up?
I made it worse.
I can't fix it.
It must be the shitty webcam.
It's the shitty webcam, guys.
Turn it off.
See, this is what happens when I turn on Facecam.
You guys all have something to fucking complain about now.
Wait, what if I do this?
Hold on.
Ready?
Wait.
Hold on.
I don't want to give you the...
Ready?
Watch.
I'm going to look at this light and I'm going to use my...
I'm going to shoot the light.
No, I need that.
Hold on.
All right.
Ready?
I'm going to go like this.
One.
Two.
Three.
Five.
Six.
Eight.
Nine.
Dead.
Was that queued up?
So it must be my...
The webcam just must suck or I must talk weird.
I think that's what's going on.
I think I just talk weird.
All right, let's go.
It's definitely the webcam.
This thing sucks.
All right.
I got six dollars.
I have to, like, play...
Wear...
Put a mask on instead.
All right.
That does it for...
Was I just running with my arms?
Okay.
Is that one...
All right.
I already delivered to this one.
I have six dollars and fifty cents.
I wish I could look at the map while riding the bike.
Okay.
Taking a left down here and then a left again.
There's a bunch on that street.
I'm playing...
This is a different game mode.
This is survival mode.
This is...
You have to, like, make money before you can play the arcade games.
There's a person on the street, dude.
What the fuck?
All right.
This should be a red mailbox right here.
I knew they were coming too.
I do have a lot of bullshit in my inventory though, don't I?
Eat the food.
I'm going to drink the drink.
All right.
Let's go.
Get it in there.
Am I doing this wrong?
I have to be doing this wrong.
There has to be a way I can, like, move this, right?
I am.
How do I do it then?
Throw it in.
He's zonked.
I think I am doing it right.
Can I tilt it around?
I don't think I can even tilt it.
There's, like, bugs flying around?
What?
Just put it in.
Jesus Christ.
Put it on the side.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
This mailbox sucks.
For a second.
I don't know why.
I thought the bike had gas.
I look for another for sale.
How much?
Is it less than eight dollars?
Probably not.
The smallest thing, the smallest object in the game, the skinniest object in the game
I ran right into.
Try this again.
No.
Why am I doing this so wrong?
You got a link?
Hold on.
Link, link, link.
All right.
Just relax.
I have a scared face and I have a big fucking gross, like, rubber mask neck.
I know.
I understand.
Why is this so difficult to get this done?
I have to be doing this wrong.
Pick it up by the band?
Go slower.
That made me so angry.
I got unreasonably angry.
That's why the face game I don't like having on.
That beep was like, that got me like, that made me fucking angry.
Oh my God.
I only have 20.
What's my curfew?
What time is it right now?
It's 2 p.m.?
All right.
I got time, I think.
This is the last one.
Then I'm going to go play some games.
Because I don't like this.
This is a pain in the ass.
Two by four camera, Andy.
No, I don't, I don't care about webcam.
There it is.
All right.
I got $12.50.
I'm going to go back to the house and then I'm going to have a TV dinner and I'm going
to go play some games.
It's an iPhone camera.
I don't, I don't, what do you need to look at me for?
You don't need to see, why do you need to see my face?
You know what I look like?
All right.
So I need to go right.
And then to home.
Is this an arcade simulator?
This is an arcade game simulator, but I'm in survival mode right now, which I have to
make money.
I think I just lost an elbow.
I have to make money.
We're going to heat up a TV dinner.
Bike is in the garage.
Good.
All right.
Wait, can I sell this stuff?
Can I sell my possessions?
All right.
Let's go inside.
Say hello.
What's the, what's the curfew?
Sell your bike for the money.
I don't know.
I'm not going to do that.
That's transportation.
All right.
Let's get some more food.
And then tomorrow I'm going to go to the arcade.
I need to move up a little bit so you can see my face.
So you can just stare at it.
Chicken finger meal.
Name the goose.
How do I name the goose?
Sell blood.
I'm going to eat this and then I think when's my curfew?
My curfew is probably like 10 o'clock at night.
Grab a soda.
I don't.
Oh, cool.
I lost.
I lost health for that.
All right.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
I'm going to go take my $12 and go play some arcade games.
Is this a bathroom?
What is this?
This is his room.
Mommy's little angel.
That was so cute.
Is this a tanning bed?
Why does the duck have a tanning bed?
All right.
I'm going.
I'm going to the arcade.
I'm going to play some games.
I have 12 bucks.
Where's the new arcade?
I want to see it.
Larry's arcade.
Barry's arcade.
Jerry's arcade.
UFO arcade.
No.
It's the...
I think it's down here.
Nope.
It's the new one.
I just came up with it.
There it is.
One-eyed Billy's arcade.
All right.
So we need to go up.
We need to come out of the house, take a left, and go up.
What about the fridge?
Grandma's home.
Something about the FOV on this bike is I don't like...
I feel like I'm going like this.
Close the fridge.
Grandma is at the house.
She can handle it.
She can close the fridge if it needs to be closed.
Grandma is a robot.
And?
I'm running on one wheel.
Grandma didn't have arms.
She could push her body into it.
Are there...
I think grandma's there.
Was it down there?
No.
Keep going around.
Down here.
It gets visibly angry at the honking.
I know.
I do.
I don't know what it is.
It's like one of those sounds that I just fucking hate.
I can't be late for the birthday party.
One-eyed Billy's.
This is the new shit.
This is new content.
Whoa.
This place is so cool already.
That's making me angry too.
Why?
One-eyed Billy's Adventure and Fun Center.
Pirate arcade, boat pond, pizza, putt-putt golf, shooting gallery.
Oh my.
Good.
Oven-fired pizzas.
It's $7 for a pizza.
I only have $12.
Ice cold pirate punch is $3.
That better be good.
It looks good.
What about over here?
How much is it to play this?
It's $2 to play a game.
Wheel her up.
Win treasure.
How do I play?
Do I have to press...
Get in there.
All right.
Go, go, go, go.
Give us another one.
All right.
You don't want to get it inside of the long slots.
You want to go now.
Like that.
Got it in.
All right.
Good.
Bonus spin.
I just got to get it into one of these.
Ready?
I'm pretty good at these.
You got to go now.
I fucking told you.
I like this one a lot.
This one's fun.
Where are my tickets?
I almost first tried it.
Why am I not winning money?
That's how you get it done.
Bonus spin.
Come on.
Super bonus.
60.
I got 60 tickets.
80 tickets total.
All right.
Let's go.
Put them out.
All right.
Let me get off of this.
How do I move my hand?
Oh, there we go.
All right.
Give me my tickets.
80.
Wait.
What are the other tickets?
Didn't I get 10 before?
Wait.
Do you not get anything if you don't go all the way up?
Losing gets you none.
So what's the...
Really?
What?
All right.
I got 80 tickets.
I love this place.
All right.
Should I get a pizza too?
Out of order?
No.
That one looks so much fun.
Lava mayhem.
How about pick your treasure?
Oh, I remember this shit.
The ball comes and spins around and it's like just...
It's children's roulette.
I remember this.
Oh, I was so addicted to this.
I did white every single fucking time.
Every time.
I didn't pick any of the other colors.
I only did white.
The one with the little sliver.
And maybe once a birthday party would come up and it wouldn't
be me that got it.
I would pick white for like an hour straight.
And then like little Timmy comes over and picks white once and he wins the whole thing.
And I just sit there going, nice job, Tim.
It should have been me.
Go for it.
White only.
I used to play this so much.
I probably sat there during every birthday party in an arcade with these huge bags under
my eyes.
Just sitting there playing it all...
Well, that was blue.
Whatever.
I'm doing it again.
How much money do I have?
Six?
I can do this one more time, right?
White.
Do it.
Give me five thousand tickets right now.
It's in.
Blue looks like it's got the most value.
That's right.
It's blue's come up.
Whatever.
I have zero dollars.
Do it again.
I didn't want to fucking do red.
I wanted to do white.
And I...
It's gonna be white.
Now watch.
Watch this.
I don't have any money left.
Get me the fuck out of here.
How do I...
I can't go in there?
All right.
Ticket redemption center.
Let's go.
Not a restroom.
Okay.
I got 80 tickets now.
What do you got?
Because I can sell the prizes, right?
What do we got?
Can I get you?
Five hundred.
Do you have anything that's...
I guess I'll take the Tootsie Rolls that have been here for 10 years.
I'll take three of them.
Goodbye.
Mini golf.
I need more money.
How much is it?
Insert card.
Is it 50 cents?
Back nine, front nine.
How much does it cost?
This was only five dollars.
All right.
I want to do an easy job.
Wait.
This is probably 50 cents.
50 cents?
They're a dollar.
So I...
I've had this scenario happen before.
You just like...
You just shred this toy.
You just shred this card because you can't even use it.
There's so many cool things.
All right.
I'm gonna go do another job.
This place...
Look it over there.
All right.
I'm gonna come back with like 50 bucks.
See if they accept credit.
All right.
I need to get...
I'm gonna do a job.
Wait.
It's six o'clock.
They accept credit at Chuck E. Cheese.
I mean, they accept credit cards, I think.
Probably.
They have a line of credit at Chuck E. Cheese.
All right.
What's...
There's a job right here.
What is it?
I want to do the babysitting one.
That sounds easy.
Honka S.
What?
I wish I had like a mini map that I could look at.
Do a cool bike ride.
All right.
I'm gonna go do another job.
This place...
Look it over there.
All right.
I'm gonna come back with like 50 bucks.
See if they accept credit.
All right.
I think this is a job.
It is.
Okay.
What does this person want me to do?
I'm here.
I'm ready to babysit the kids.
It's not.
It's not it.
You could walk up to a random house.
I'm here.
I'm ready to babysit the kids.
It's like...
You see this person outside?
Like what the fuck is this person doing?
I need that money.
I gotta get to the arcade.
Babysit.
He looks older too.
He wants to go to the arcade?
So where is this place?
I don't know.
This way?
Call the police.
All right.
Here we go.
This looks like a job.
It is.
All right.
What do you want me to do?
I got a nice car in here.
Hello?
Hey.
I just closed myself in the garage.
I thought that was a doorbell.
It's auto.
How do I pet auto?
Wait.
What?
I just went in this person's garage.
All right.
Well, where's your owner?
This dog is going to bite me.
I think this dog is going to bite me.
I think this dog is trying to bite me.
Stop.
Is the dog biting me?
This sounds like snarls.
Where's the...
I want to...
It's the Brad's lawnmower.
Rab.
Where the fuck is your owner?
Where's my curfew?
Here.
Look.
Oh, so you know...
Is there a sign coming to me?
Oh, there's a lawnmower.
I got it.
Dog.
I'm going to need you to get out of the way.
Move out of the way, please.
Get out of the way, please.
Get out of the way.
He took the lawnmower.
He's mowing our lawn.
OK, dog let me alone.
That's at 730 at night.
It's going to be like one o'clock in the morning.
Hey, you told me to come mow your lawn.
You didn't tell me when I had to.
You didn't give me a time.
Just said, come do it.
I got to speed this up.
Is there a sprint?
Am I even mowing the grass?
I can't see anything.
Mowing the lawn in darkness.
Okay, I swear to god the grass is
growing back.
Am I losing my mind or did that whole entire
this whole thing grow back?
This all grew back!
Did it? Is it just dark?
There are not headlights on this.
Oh, it doesn't? What are you talking about?
This is fun.
Curve view. What time is the curve view?
In two hours. Okay.
Two hours and 45 minutes before I have curve view.
I can finish this lawn.
I probably get a lot of money for this.
Where's my...I have to mow the entire lawn.
I'm going to miss one piece in the
darkness and it's going to drive me insane.
I have to mow their backyard too?
No. See, I'm almost done with this one.
If this is less than like
$50, I'm not doing this ever again.
Go rob the house. I can't rob the house.
Alright, that looks good.
Just have this side and that should be it, right?
I'm running over like they have flowers.
Oh, ransom the dog.
I have two energy. Thank God.
I almost just passed out
on the ground here.
Alright, almost done. We're getting there.
It's close. Get out of the way.
I don't want to run that dog over the lawn more.
That's it? One little patch right here.
Come on, give me a hundred bucks for this.
How much does it cost to have a lawn mowed?
What about a business
charge for that?
Is it like $30? $50?
$50? Depends.
How big the lawn is?
Three bucks to get your lawn mowed?
I don't know. I think you pay yearly.
Oh.
How much do you think it should cost?
I guess it's based on how big the lawn is, right?
If you've got a huge lawn, I would say
how many square footages the lawn is.
There's like still
one little sliver of grass.
I mean, you've got it depends on the size, right?
I mean, if you have a lawn
that's as
if you have a yard or lawn that's this big
just like this.
I mean, that's going to take
less than $5,000.
The backyard too.
Jesus.
Oh my fucking god.
No way.
This is a hundred bucks.
What if I don't finish the job and I have to go home?
Shit, I can't finish this job.
I have to get out of here. I can't finish
put the curtains in an hour.
And I have no food.
I might be able to do it though.
You moron.
What do you want
to do?
I'm going to get it.
I'm going to get it. Here we go.
An hour. I'm good.
I just hope I have enough energy.
I can't fucking see if this isn't grass over here.
Am I mowing their pool?
All right. I think that's good.
Right here. This is the last little
strip right here.
God damn it. I'm not going to finish it.
I'm going to mow this entire
person's lawn for free.
They just have to come out and finish it tomorrow morning.
There's this whole area over here too.
Do I at least get a partial
payout for this?
Use the flashlight? I can.
I can't use them both at the same time.
I have to. I gotta go. I gotta go. I have to leave.
All right. Go, go, go, go. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. I gotta go home.
Where's home? Can I eat fish food?
All right. Straight left.
Straight left. Right?
Vigilante lawnmower.
Fuck. Go.
I feel like I'm playing Stardew Valley.
Where's the bed? Where's the bed? Where's the bed?
Where's the bed? Where's the bed? Where's the bed? Where's the bed? Where's my bed?
Where's my bed?
Where's my bed? Where's my bed? Where's my bed? This is a bathroom.
Where's my bed? Where's the bedroom?
Where's my bedroom?
Where's my bedroom? What is he doing?
It's up the stairs?
Was I cooking him?
Get in bed. Get in bed. Get in bed. Get in bed.
He's cooking himself.
All right. We made it through the first day.
I get it now. I understand how the game is played.
I do want to get one of these though.
Because I can probably sell this stuff.
I can definitely sell this at the pawn shop.
Open the door.
Just open the door.
What do you mean just open the door?
I mean I guess...
Give me a break. Oh, I have
toilet water. My favorite. All right. I have full energy.
Give me a bunch of these.
What do I have?
My inventory. I'm gonna sell this shit.
What do I even do with this stuff? First aid.
Fish flakes.
Gary's food. Okay. Gary's food.
Gary's food must be prepared.
His name is Gary.
On his dinner mat. Okay.
And Gary? What happens if we don't feed Gary?
Close the fridge. No.
Fine. No.
I was about to say, why are you guys freaking out so much?
This doesn't cost any electricity.
This is just like a fake thing.
That's incorrect.
Because what has to happen
when I open this is my graphics card
needs to render
the stuff going on, the particle effects, and the pixels
going on in here. Therefore, using
extra electrical consumption for my
graphics card. Therefore,
adding bills, adding money to my
electric bill. Interesting.
Actually true. No, that is actually
true. I know. I need
a... Let's feed the fish.
Fish flakes.
Oops. Sorry.
It's just a little wet. It's okay.
Oh my god, it's a frenzy.
Okay, we're good.
Coffee.
What am I gonna do? Your shadow is creepy.
Okay, I've got pretty much
full health, full energy. I'm ready to go.
Both of you guys long again.
I don't know. Will it be not?
Maybe it'll be almost completed.
Okay, where the hell does this guy live?
Right here. So I gotta go out, left,
and straight over here. Wait, was it
this one? Was it this one or this one?
It was this one, right?
The one above? Yeah, it was that one.
So we gotta go out, left, right,
up. Got it. We're getting lottery tickets
to the gas station. I have
50 cents, dude. I have
50 cents. I cannot
afford to go buy a lottery ticket right now.
I need to have a bank account worth at least
100 to 200 dollars.
So I can go play at the pirate's village,
whatever it's called. I'm gonna try to jump
this fucking thing. Don't play survival. Switch the
game mode, please. Actually,
I'm having fun. This is stupid,
but it's cool. Hello, dog.
Is it mowed?
I think it's mowed.
No, it is. All right. No, it kept it.
Did it keep all the mowing? I think so.
Shadow is terrifying.
Whatever. It did. Thank God. All right.
Let's get some money here. Going over the concrete
like...
I'm just like shaving it down. I'm like sanding
the concrete. All right, here we go.
Now I can actually see what the hell I'm doing.
I like this.
Wait, people like this?
Would the...
Would the blade like hit the concrete and go like
BOOM and like shoot like 3,000
feet in the air?
Or would it be like...
What the fuck? I had lawnmowers scare
the shit out of me. Lawnmowers scare
the shit out of me. I'm sorry.
You can call me weirdo. Like I told you, like I don't like
ovens. A box that heats up to
500 degrees that sits on your wall. There's
enclosed in the wall. I don't like that.
The gas goes in there and shit. I don't like it. I don't know why.
A lawnmower, then loud,
then right like two and a half feet
in front of me, is a spinning
blade that can chop your bones in half.
I don't know. What if it like comes loose?
It's like fires up like a fucking
Mega Man weapon.
I don't know. I just get the shit out of me. I don't like
a riding mower.
Yeah, but I know. It's still...
That's caveman logic. It doesn't matter.
Look, irrational fears
are called irrational fears
because they are irrational.
I know that's not going to happen.
And now you can't even hear me.
You can't even hear me talking.
There. Alright, how are we doing?
God, I can't wait to go to a pirate school.
What if that place is called?
I missed a spot in the alley.
Let me get over here first.
It's Five Nights at Freddy's or whatever.
Why am I doing chores? Because I'm playing the
new game mode.
It's 50 bucks. That's a good... That's good.
That's 50 bucks.
Alright, I'm going to come back into it tomorrow.
When it grows back. Get off.
Alright, I have 50 dollars now.
Go do babysitting. Alright, where's
babysitting? Oh, okay.
Looking for babysitter with little ones. It's easy work and
pay well. If you'd like to help us out and earn some extra money
just come to the front door of the house on the map
closest to the paper route stand.
Come to the front door of the house on the map
closest to the paper route stand. Which is...
Okay, it's that house right there.
Alright, goodbye, Otto.
It is Otto!
Take the dog. I'm not taking a dog.
Alright, I think it's this house right here.
Babysitting. It is, okay.
Ding dong, I'm here to babysit the kids.
Put boy to bed. Put girl to bed.
Put toys in chest.
I thought it said ocean floor. Clean floor.
Okay, put the kids to bed?
Dear babysitter, please put the kids
to bed. Put their toys in
wood chest. Mop up their mess. We will be
home after the movie. Thanks.
Okay. Put the toys in the chest.
Mop up their mess with a broom. Put the kids
to bed. How do I do that? It's just like
do I... That is pick them up?
Whose room is this?
I can't even go in any of these rooms. Oh, come here.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Alright, get to
bed. Charging.
That's fucking crazy. Okay.
Where's the other kid? Come here.
Put them in the garbage. You are
fucked. Okay. The kids are in bed.
Alright, good night. Have a good
rest, you two. Oops.
I thought the light was on.
I just blinded them.
Goodnight. Alright, now we have to put their toys
in the chest. This is going to be a pain in the ass.
I'm putting the TV on.
I'm going to burn this stuff.
Just light it on fire.
What was that? I heard a smash.
Did you hear that?
I have to defend the house from like a burglar?
Oh, there they are. Okay, cool.
I like that arcade too.
Okay, I was going to fuck if it disappeared.
Turn my gas.
Come on. Alright, just get them over there.
This will just be much quicker if I just go like this.
I hope that's not gone. That's it?
Always in the chest, right?
There's one more? Where is it? Look up.
The fuck is making that smash?
Did I soft lock it? I hope.
No, no, no, no. There's one over here.
Thank god. Alright, we're good. Check on the kids.
Oh shit, you're right.
Something is smashing.
Oh, free food.
I heard it again. Oh, food.
Eat these. Sabotage.
Alright, what is making the smashing sound?
What are you guys doing in here?
Oh, okay. Okay, we'll see.
Oh, if their arm stays up, they're asleep.
I go over and I lift up
their arm, and they
hold it there thinking that they're making their parents
look stupid. Did I ever tell you that story?
I told you that, right? When I was younger,
I shared a bedroom with my brother.
And we would just be messing
around and talking. We would not be going
to sleep at night, right?
The kids would go to bed. So,
my parents would come in and hear us talking.
We weren't sleeping, we were being bad.
And we would go, oh shit! And pretend to be asleep.
So, they would come into the room,
and they would go, oh, looks like
they're asleep in here. Oh, well,
of course they are. Must have heard something.
It could not have been what they were doing.
Well, you know, the best way to tell is,
if their arm stays up, they're asleep.
And they would grab one of our
arms and hold it. And we
thought we were being so smart. We were
just playing the system so much. We would sit
there and go like this. And they'd go, oh,
he's asleep, he's asleep, alright.
And they'd put it back down.
And, oh, okay, yeah.
They're asleep. And then they would
leave. So, over time,
a few years would go by, we got
keen to this trick. So, we would do
the most unbelievable, like,
theater-like flopping
when they would come in and do this again. So,
again, sleep. Oh shit, okay, they're gonna do
that thing. I'm gonna trick them
this time. They'll know I'm asleep because I know that holding
your arm up means you're awake. So,
you do this, like, soccer
flop, right?
Oh, if his arm stays up, he's asleep. And it would just be like,
oh, he's definitely
asleep now. Let's try that again.
He's like, nah, now we got him.
It was fun. Anyways,
if their arm stays up, they're asleep. You're a mom.
Outplayed.
You guys go to bed. Arms up, guys.
And, hey, that's
a fun little thing, right?
If I ever have kids one day, for any reason,
I can't wait, I cannot wait
to do the if their arm stays up, they're asleep
thing. Please, god no, don't ever have
them. Yeah, alright, yeah,
why not? Why, why not?
Why? Look, I know
that there's this misconception that you guys don't think I could
even, like, tie my shoes. And I
can't. But that's besides the point,
it's hard to do. Knots are difficult,
especially when you do the bunny ears and you try to do it
cleanly. It happens a lot.
It's hard to do that. That doesn't mean that I cannot
take care of somebody else. Why are your shoes
right now? I don't have shoes on. I don't
just have, like, a pair of sneakers on
all day. Any dirt in here?
Somebody is breaking something in this house and I don't
I think it's like an animal on the wall.
When he buy, ah, it's not enough.
That's not enough. Leave the fire on?
With the, nobody here?
Okay, so I have 70
dollars. I got food too, that's right.
What else is, what other job can I do? Newspaper delivery,
extra junk, babysitter,
golf cart, I need my lawn
mode, yeah, I think, have I done all the jobs?
Babysitter, lawn mower, newspaper.
Okay, let's go to the pawn shop.
I've located the flashing yellow light
on the main highway. Take the bus stop
to number five and we are right
across the street, okay?
On the highway, we're right across the street.
There it is. Okay, so we gotta go
to turn around and just go
straight, I'm gonna burp. I'm gonna sell a bunch
of shit in my inventory and then we're gonna go back to the pirate
land. Sell all your organs.
Can't do that. Alright, turn around,
straight. Gotta go this way.
Holy shit, jump. There's a German
Easter egg legit. Okay.
Why can I not control the bike? What's
wrong with my body? What happened?
I can't turn left. Oh,
that's weird. Flashing yellow light.
There it is. Flashing yellow light.
The Dan Aykroyd.
Why do I sound like Dan Aykroyd? Go to the flashing
yellow light and find yourself.
That's weird. Why am I doing that?
Flashing yellow light. Where am I going?
Alright, left, straight left.
Gary's gas and go.
Alright, where's the pawn shop? There it is.
That's Stano's doggy bonus.
Whatever that means.
And here's the pawn shop.
Okay, what can I sell?
Barry's high demand items.
Wood bat. Toys.
Swords. Please use the other door.
Thanks. Okay.
Salt rock. Salt rock, light
sword red. Where's the entrance?
What's happening over here? Stop!
Don't move! What the hell? What's happening back here?
These people are on fire.
Why are these people on fire?
Let's kill somebody?
I don't know what's going on. The guy's a bat.
Can I take his bat?
This is a high demand item.
These guys have guns too.
On their car.
These guys are rabid over here.
How do I kill them? Kick his ass.
I'm trying to.
When does he die?
Take the car. I can't.
What are you doing?
I don't know. I'm trying to stop that. You don't have
ammo from the final boss.
They're people.
They started attacking me, didn't they?
They attacked me. They started attacking me.
Yeah, they were attacking me.
Can I take the bat now?
Give me that bat.
I mean, not mine.
Well, make it mine.
I don't think I can kill this guy.
I'm just getting out of here. You can't.
I'm just getting the fuck out of here then.
Use the other door.
Wait. See, this guy's
attacking people on the street.
Just shoot myself?
Please use the other door.
The door? I...
What the fuck?
Okay. Tootsie roll. What's it worth?
Tootsie roll is worth
$303.
What about the kid cuisine?
What would you do for
a crumbled up Mountain Dew can?
50 cents? That's not bad.
I have $74.
On a microwave meal.
Somebody's in there with a
silver ring in front of you.
And then you're just sitting there
behind you. Somebody's like an antique clock.
You're sitting there with like
two or three freezer meals.
What can I get for these?
Well, I guess if they were rare. What if they were like from the...
Okay, what if they were preserved?
Frozen since like 1992
or something. An old kid cuisine.
How much is an old kid cuisine
from 1993 worth today?
Can we look it up? It's probably...
Somebody probably collects the boxes.
Zero. Mm-mm. I don't
think so. PSA 10
kid cuisine. All right. I got $74.
I'm going back to the... I'm going back to play the
games. It's worth $35. That's
still probably... That's like a
probably a thousand percent return.
What were they? Like two or three dollars back in the 90s?
If it was like a hundred bucks?
It's cops.
All right. I'm gonna go and I'm gonna play video games
now because I have
energy drinks. I have
kid cuisines. I have money.
I got $75. I'm going back to that
place, wherever the heck
it is. We are gonna go
back this way.
There's a lot of community subs. It's 25
community subs from Soda Cat.
Thanks for the soda. I don't
know. I'm getting older and I don't
think words just go in and come out. I don't know what that...
I don't know. Thanks for the 25 subs though.
All right. We're gonna go
all the way back here. So we're
gonna turn around and go
behind us. So we're gonna turn around
and go right, right.
We're gonna go that way.
What? I think the soda
song. Sure.
All right.
We're gonna go right this way
and then up the dirt road.
This is close to the house.
Those lyrics sucked. I don't
write lyrics. I'm more of a...
I'm almost an ideas guy.
Imagine being a songwriter
but being an ideas guy
and sitting in like a meeting
going, man, you know, I would love like a song
that was like...
Something like that would be perfect
and it's gonna have a big finish.
At the end. You think you can work with that?
It's like bring your kid to work day.
I think that this should be a song with
a drum beat and
a big horn in the middle
and
this should be a guitar
riff that goes
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
I don't know what you can make the song about
but, I mean, I'm gonna give you that idea
and that idea is not cheap. I'm about to go
into the ocean.
I'm okay. Let's go.
I have $75.
Sonic Adventure 2 theme.
Why do the sun...
That one? Is that the same one?
First try. Got it?
Fuck yeah! Hey, hey, hey!
What's happening? You know what? Those are my tickets on the ground!
Get away from me!
You better not have... Okay.
I'm just kind of like almost... I'm physically removed.
Okay!
Give me these.
I got a thousand tickets now.
Let's go. One more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more.
Jackpot's at 300. I can get it.
Just don't even think about it. Just go get it.
Give me these tickets.
Alright, I'm gonna count these.
These... juggles.
How do you guys think about that one?
You think that was a good play?
I know what you guys want. I know what you're looking for.
I drank two Gatorades
before the stream.
I'll be right back. I have to go pee.
I can't even...
Oh no.
I gotta get out of here. I have to leave right now.
Oh!
Here's a VRB screen. Just watch that and watch that. I'll be back.
I'm gonna take a minute.
That was a huge fucking mistake, but whatever.
You know what I was doing. Whatever, goodbye.
I know what you're looking for.
I drank two Gatorades before the stream.
I know what you guys want. I know what you're looking for.
I know what you're looking for.
God damn it. No.
I had to watch it like twice before I left.
To see if it was a problem.
I didn't turn off the desktop audio though.
That was my mistake.
I'm not... I haven't gone yet.
I got caught watching it
like a few times to see.
Oh my god damn it. Okay, goodbye. I'll be back.
I can't get over it.
I fucked up everything.
I fucking ruined everything.
I'm gonna slowly try to get back to normal here.
I don't know if that's possible, but I'm gonna try.
What's in my pocket? Is that a heal?
Why do I have a heal in my back pocket?
Alright. Let's get back to normal here.
God. Apologize. For what?
For shaking my stomach
full of a Gatorade
into the microphone.
Okay.
You're disgusting. I know I'm not.
I'm just... whatever.
Cam's staying off for five minutes.
I can't be trusted with it on.
I have $56.
What's this one? No bumping or tilting.
This one's only a dollar.
It's got germacolors? Oh shit.
Oh, I get it. Okay, I remember this one.
A version of this.
That's 300. Oh, it's nothing.
I gotta count how long it takes for it to get over there.
300!
Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six.
Seven. Eight.
It takes about eight seconds.
When it comes down here, let's see.
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Five. Six.
Seven. Eight.
Nine. Ten.
We have to do this in two seconds after
it crosses the plane.
Ready? One. Two.
Three. Four.
Five. Six.
Eight.
Nine. Ten.
That's gonna be something. Ready?
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Five. Eight.
Nine.
I'm not clicking on any links.
No links. Zero.
One more. I don't want to spend all my money.
Get that 2500.
Give me something. This one's stupid.
This one's stupid.
Last one.
You have to be too exact on this one.
Stupid. How's that not 50?
Somebody just...
Somebody punching me?
Who's hitting me?
Oh, I have 10 health. Why? Why am I losing health?
Oh, shit.
Is there a microwave in here?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
You have a microwave? I'll take a pizza.
Give me a pizza.
I'll take a pirate pizza, please.
Quickly.
Hurry up! Hurry!
That's only 10 health?
That's it. Only 10% health.
I'll take a pirate punch, too.
I don't know why.
But that just made me want to have a pineapple vodka.
I just did.
Oh, it's called pirate punch.
I want a vodka pineapple.
I don't know why. For no reason.
Just made me want it.
I'm alright for now. I got 39 bucks.
I've got a lot of tickets. We're going for this again.
5000. Come on.
Come on, Gwen. Come on, Gwen.
Oh.
Another 20 subs from Soda Cat.
What the heck are you thinking?
Thank you.
20 more fucking subs.
That's a big hit if it hits.
Oh, no.
Pretend
fake
reaction for people that
don't want one of those.
Oh, shit.
Oh, onion ring.
What?
I'm going to put this down to 25 dollars
if I don't get a white
when I hit 25.
And I'm going to just leave
and I'm going to play something else.
How do I subscribe with Amazon Prime?
I don't know.
Look, I don't blame you for not linking your Amazon
to your Twitch.
That kind of feels like an annoying thing to do.
You have to like authorize.
Click like three or four buttons and shit and like connect it.
That's kind of annoying, isn't it?
I can understand.
Yeah.
I have no response to that.
I guess.
If you feel that way, then like
Sage.
Sad GE.
What is it? Sad GE?
All right. This is the last time I'm doing this.
And then I'm going over there.
No.
Pull out. Take it out.
Get it out.
Do I have more tickets?
I still had more. I had a couple.
I had a lot more.
You're my hater 94, thanks to the five subs.
That's a weird thing to do to somebody you don't like.
I'm going for this one. This is tried and true.
It's tried and true.
I cannot be
stopped with this.
I can't be stopped.
That's 600 on the ground.
More. Again. Now.
Go play mini golf? I will.
After I get this one more time.
I got to get it one more time or I
won't leave.
Okay. Good. I'm ready.
That's another 2,000.
Thank you Izzy for the subs. I missed a lot of subs
from earlier too. Thank you guys.
If you're gifting subs, you're
just dumping money into this channel.
All I can say is thank you.
I hope I spend it well.
Thank you guys. I want to get this one too.
How much is mini golf?
I think I pressed it at the worst possible time. No I didn't.
Thank you. Better GPU.
You know how hard it is to get
a GPU right now?
All right. Back it up.
What other games have I not
seen? I saw these ones.
I love this.
I love this one so much.
It's only a dollar. I can do it.
You have to drop the coin in and try to get it right in the middle.
Did I get it?
Here we go again.
That's 700 fucking tokens.
I got it.
Let's go.
That's 730.
Mini golf. I know.
Face cam on.
I'll give you face cam.
I'll give you face cam for five minutes.
That's it. How many tickets do I have?
I have
3100.
Hold on. Look at this.
Inflatable putter. Starfish. Avocado plush.
Should I get the avocado and
sell it?
The avocado?
Or should I save up for a cupcake?
Even more subs.
And more subs. It was like 30 actually.
Hold it. Just hold it.
But I need money though.
I don't want to go mow a guy's lawn.
I'm going to do the golf
part.
What did we get? Play nine front holes.
Let's do the first
front. What did we get for doing this?
Do I get any money or anything?
Hole one.
Is there a power?
This is pretty cool.
This is fun. It's money if
it's a low score. One.
That's a par two. Alright. Whatever.
The camera. The camera. What about the camera?
I'm going straight back here.
Like this.
Get a good bounce. Good. That's part two.
Old man germa.
Why am I old man?
Part two. Got it. Total needs to be 18.
And then I get money?
Whoa. Oh.
It's one of these.
Get it really slow. Right there.
There it is. Get in there. Oh you
fucking idiot.
Izzy is still giving subs.
What are you doing?
What is that? 60?
It's a par three. It's art.
And soda cat too. I've got to get a hole
in one so you guys can like clip it.
And make me famous.
What the fuck is happening?
That's another 10 subs from Izzy.
What are you doing?
This is too many subs to give in one second.
Oh it's the Sonic the Hedgehog thing.
I love these. Hole in one.
I can still do it. Get scammed.
Why am I getting scammed?
What do you mean get scammed? We are.
Oh. Oh you're the ones
getting scammed.
Well hold on.
How are you getting scammed?
It's not a requirement to spend
any money on this stream.
That's not a scam. I'm dying on
the golf course. Can I get it up there?
Before I die?
Poison golf.
I can't stop to eat by the way.
I have to just finish this now.
Oh my god.
Everybody playing mini golf is really fucking hungry.
And we don't want to finish.
We don't really want to play. We've been here for like 3 hours already.
And it's just like alright everybody just kind of
hit them balls down there once or twice
and pick them up and let's go to the next one.
Classic windmill hole in one guaranteed.
I mean I just have to...
That's just what happens.
This is the last one. I want to wrap it around.
Make him famous.
Hurry up before I starve to death.
Soda pop? Tonic?
That is a good question though.
Are you guys soda?
Are you pop?
Or are you tonic?
Or are you coke?
What is it? Where you are from?
Pop. I say soda.
Soda. That's a soda.
Speaking of a soda, I have to drink one of these or I'm going to die here.
Soda is the one true god.
Pop.
Here's the thing. I kind of wish I said pop.
Pop sounds so much cooler.
That sounds better. But it's a soda for me.
I'm still dying.
I have to go home. First aid.
Oh shit.
That helped.
I need to buy something.
I have $1. What can I do for $1?
What's $1?
I'll try to get this again. This is $6.80. Let's go.
First try. Nail it.
You have an hour to go to bed.
Oh shit I do. You're right.
I do.
I think I'm going to buy the avocado.
Hey, if it isn't the big winner.
Give me the avocado. I want it.
I'm selling this tomorrow.
I have to get out of here.
You have to go to bed. Run.
You're right. I have to get out of here.
Millennial toy. Germa Pluto.
I need to go home.
Where's home? Why am I still holding tickets?
Home is left.
Just go left.
You don't have any time?
That was a pretty cool trick.
I just made all these people shit their pants.
I have to go this way. Right up there.
There's my house.
Don't get hit by a car!
Am I riding on the median?
I'm just riding a bike across an intersection.
You don't even look both ways.
You're just going 20 miles per hour and you just go
Don't get hit by a car!
You pedal across?
Where am I going? Where's my fucking house?
Where's my house? I don't know where the house is.
Where's my house?
It's down behind me?
This feels so wrong.
What the fuck am I going? It's behind me?
Come on! Pedal up!
I can't get off the bike.
Alright!
I'm good. Bedtime.
I guess I'm going to bed. Right now.
Something is not right here.
I have negative one hour.
Speedrun strat?
Kind of.
You want to know the worst part about this whole stupid fucking drink the heal joke?
I don't have a sponsorship with heal.
I never probably will.
I don't know why I keep doing this.
I don't know why that makes me laugh.
I'm just doing it for free.
I don't know why I think that's funny.
It kind of is.
Get sponsored.
Give in.
I just drink these sometimes.
Because I'm a streamer
and I consume a product sometimes
all of a sudden it's just automatically
now I have to be sponsored by that product.
Is this what we do?
I kind of like to drink this drink.
I better get paid to drink it now.
How do I go about doing that by the way?
Excuse me.
Dr. Heal.
It's me German at night five.
I really like drinking those delicious heals.
Pay me money now to drink it.
I'll take it.
What?
Just ask.
Hey.
Can I have some money?
I've showed that on stream once.
If I consume anything in front of a camera
I deserve to be paid for it.
Harold J. Heal.
But really though I'm available for any type of
contractual shit if you want to talk about it.
I'm available for anything like that.
I'll tell you one thing. I ain't tweeting shit.
I ain't going to do a whole stream dedicated.
I drink it on stream.
Why am I giving an ad for myself?
I'm pitching this to no one.
I'm pitching it to the wall.
You simply adopted the brand.
We are the wall.
One of them could be Heal.
I like them.
I think it's pretty good.
But whatever.
I don't have to be paid to say that.
If I was though.
Fuck that.
I never take the sponsorship my whole life.
I've never taken one.
I will take one small check.
Six to seven figures.
For me to have a stream about it though.
That's my pitch to you.
I'm not tweeting about it.
I'm streaming a wink at the camera.
If that's worth six to seven figures to you.
You got my email.
Except you probably don't because I don't respond to my email.
I have not checked my business email in like six fucking years.
I don't have open DMs.
And it's impossible to contact me.
So I guess let's just call this meeting at it's not happening.
Not happening.
Thank you for your time. I appreciate it.
Business email stream.
No. We are not doing that.
I made one like eight years ago thinking it was like
I should give this to people.
And I didn't even use it.
It's funny because I have like this old business email.
Somebody probably has tried
to send me something or contact me.
I haven't even opened it.
Somebody could have given me coordinates to a briefcase
full of like a million dollars in cash
to that like business email.
And I would I don't know I've never opened it.
Where's my bike?
Holy shit that is a scary.
That is a really scary image.
Alright where's the bike?
10, 10, 10, 5, 5, 5.
Jerma zerked on stream.
15 community subs. Thank you.
That's why you wanted me to read them.
SodaCat another 5. Tidy Rolly thanks for 5.
And then Matt. Mattroyous
thanks for the 10.
Alright my bike's over here. Where's the bike?
Come on. Where's my bike? Thanks Matt.
Hey thank you Matt.
Where's the bike? It says it's right here.
I don't see a bike. You see a bike?
Ahhhh. Alright we're selling
that shit. It's up your ass.
Ha ha ha ha. Don't time that person up.
Don't time that person up. Much as I know
we should. Much as I want to.
It's the ha ha ha at the end.
Okay where's the pawn
shop? We gotta go straight down
here. Straight
and then left. Thanks for
the ride. This is where I had to go.
Why did he tail swipe me? What the
fuck was that? What the hell are these people doing?
He just like tail hit
me. He was trying to kill me.
What a
owned. Owned. Owned. Owned. Owned.
Oh my god. Owned.
Oh my god I got you. Owned.
What's in demand?
Assault rock. I'm gonna sneeze
and I'm not doing it on camera.
Holy shit that was
fucking crazy.
It was a rooster.
That was.
Good morning. Good morning. The amount of
good mornings. Good morning.
Oh shit.
Oh my goodness.
Alright what's an avocado worth?
Four fucking dollars.
Four dollars.
Are you kidding me?
That's unbelievable.
That's awful. What does he
want? Let me see the items he wants.
A wood bat.
He wants a wood bat.
I want a bat. What do I get a bat?
Why do I say that like that? Bat.
That makes it sound like dangerous
right? I want to get a bat.
A bat. Hot dog plush.
Assault rock and a light sword.
That guy has a wooden bat
right there. How do I get the bat
from him? I have to
kill this guy. Right?
I have to kill this guy. This guy has to be killed.
I prayed for it.
Put him in the pond with the bat. I don't think I
can do that. I need someone to come down
this road. Here we go.
Can we like GTA this
where you have a pedestrian like accidentally punch
or kick somebody else
or another car and they all freak out and start beating
the shit out of each other? He can't
die. Can I drown him?
Can I drown him?
Put him in the machine. I can't.
I need this
wooden bat but I can't talk to this guy.
Put him in the grape crusher.
Shoot him. Tell the bot. I can't
bring him inside. Put him in a red
mailbox. Hold on. He's
very bad at swinging this at me though.
Press F. Yeah, I can't. It says that's not mine.
Fuck's over there. That's like a weird
shack over there. We're going to investigate that after this.
This is fucking crazy.
I kind of killed this guy.
Drop the bat? He went even higher.
He went even higher. How high can he go?
What? Am I missing him?
I kind of want to get a firework and like shoot it up there.
I'm slowly bringing him back down to earth. Or whatever.
Just leave him. Who cares? I want to go and see what that shack is
over there. See what I'm talking about? See down there? That's like a weird
shack. Let him starve.
Oh, you weren't saying let him starve. You went
and you let him starve in a sad
face. Oh, okay. Well, that's why
texting is hard to do. It's hard to read
what people are talking about when they're texting. I don't like
texting. I like to talk to you. It hurt me.
It's a boomer. It's not a boomer thing.
Do you understand? Okay, when I talk to
somebody, if I'm speaking to them
like this, right? I can just talk
and we can have a conversation. But you know
how hard it is to actually make decent
conversation with just talking
like typing? I found it hard to do
because you'll type something
and then you'll go, oh, no, no, no, delete, delete, delete.
What would I say? I don't know what to do. Are they
going to get that? Let me try something
else. Write another sentence.
I guess that's like, that's okay.
Me saying that, I guess, is where
direct communication like this,
we get it. We know exactly what's going on here.
It's almost like you have to like craft perfect
sentences when you talk to people on the internet
through a text box. Unless, of course, you're here
and you're telling me to
shove a bike up my ass. I mean, you definitely
didn't think too much about writing that, but you did.
But I don't know who you are,
right? If you and I were in a
Discord DM together
and we were hanging out, I'm not sure you would tell me
to shove a bike up my ass. I'm pretty
sure that you'd probably think, you'd be like,
should I write that to him right now?
Should I write this? That's
probably, I don't know if he's going to understand
like LOL, like what?
What the fuck are you talking about?
There is a house back here. Do you have any food?
I'm talking about non-anonymous
texting, like
talking. Pick up your trash. What? Evil.
What? What is over here?
There's probably going to be a secret item in here. There's an invisible
wall. Right. Why is that there?
God damn it. Fly like the other
guy. Oh, the UFO arcade. I got four bucks.
Let's go. Do a noclip. Why can't I drive
one of those? Get the scratch cards at the
gas station. Oh, I forgot about these ones.
These ones are fun. Oh, these ones are really fun.
I love this place. Ski ball.
How is that not powerful enough? Go to
Dizzy Bird. Alright, alright. I will.
I only have three dollars. Alright, survival mode's
fun, but I want to play the games and make money
and make tickets and stuff.
You're in a coma. Wake up.
I'm never going to get a hundred.
I'll never get a hundred. Whatever.
Did I get tickets? No?
No tickets? Oh, there's another ball.
Oh, the plug. I really
hope you hear this. Please wake up. 150
fucking tickets? I just got for what?
I didn't do anything.
Oh my goodness.
Get away from me. Leave me alone.
What are you doing to me?
No, no, no, no, no. I don't want to do. I thought the card
was still. Whatever. That's free tickets.
Don't wake up. Do something funny.
You go into the room where
I'm like in the coma
and a handful of you are just sitting
around the bed. Don't wake up.
And one of you leans into
and goes, do something funny.
I don't think this is going to
work. Do something funny
to like the guy that's like
and then you fart.
Wait, like me lying down and like
I fart and I like go.
What are you talking about?
That's a family guy joke.
You know, I'm sure it is.
OK. I have
my. Let's go.
Oh, OK. I'm I want to do the thing
where I get all the free money.
Where's Dizzy Bird? Where's Dizzy Bird?
I don't think it's in this one.
I think Dizzy Bird's in the other arcade.
Is it upstairs? No, it's not up here.
It's in the other arcade.
They patched it out.
Oh, my God. That was on camera.
That was on camera.
You're out of frame.
Thank God.
All right. I'm going to turn in these tickets.
Two thousand tickets.
You got yourself twenty tickets.
Wait, give me that back.
Four hundred and four.
Dang it. Dang it. Dang it. Dang it.
Wait, is it one of these
worth a lot of money? Minus two.
Do funny joke. No funny joke.
Do funny joke. Funny man.
I don't even buy any sour treats.
I want to go and
I want to play arcade games now.
It's too much. It's hard. I don't have any money.
I don't have any money.
For your teeth, please.
I don't fucking have any.
I can't even take the bus.
Shit, I can't even take the bus. How am I going to get back to my house?
Oh, vehicle reset.
Your bike has been towed to your home garage.
Oh, shit.
Raids coming in. Who's raiding?
Who's raiding? Raid?
We're waiting for a raid?
Oh my
goodness. Raid?
Is there a raid coming in?
Are you guys serious? A raid?
No way.
I'm about to die. I'm dead. I'm about to die.
I can die in this game?
I'm dead. I can't eat it.
The shit's frozen. I can't eat it.
I'm dead. How do you? Wait.
Just go into the fucking beam.
Melted in the beam.
Oh, Andy. Reporter Andy.
Oh, shit. This is funny.
Well, that's survival mode.
That's fun. Actual
real tragedy.
Why am I not seeing raids?
Did somebody raid already?
Did we get a raid? Why is it not popping up for me?
They're here now?
Am I getting baited?
Did we get raided?
We lied. Chat's lying.
Oh. Oh, it's fake. Okay.
Cool. Alright.
I want to just go play the games in there.
Earth Day mode.
Attack of the One Guys. Really?
I'm singing the raid song anyways.
It's still saved here.
Alright. I want to go.
I want to go to the new arcade. I want to play the new games.
That's all I want.
We're going straight up here.
Uh, just go up.
Give me this.
Spit just went everywhere.
No, I'm sorry. You guys got it wrong.
That is the, excuse me.
Quiet.
That noise is the
Wendy's frosty machine.
The stick that comes down and it goes
Fucking relax.
Holy shit.
Mick twist?
Like make him famous.
Make me famous.
Royal flush.
Oh, that's beautiful.
It actually was though.
It was actually really good. It was cool.
It was actually beautiful.
I'm here.
I thought that was the car making that noise.
Okay, I got money.
We're going here immediately.
Okay.
In 10 tries, I'm going to do, let's see.
What's the actual percentage here?
If it's a pie chart,
you've got green makes up about what?
Say 25%.
30%, 25.
20.
So that's like 35, like 40, 50, 60, 70.
Like what would you call this?
Like 10%, 20%.
Maybe 15% for white.
10% for white.
5 to 10%.
12%.
Okay, so theoretically if we do this
100 times,
that should pop up 12 times.
And we're doing a prediction here.
Is this if it will land on
white or not?
I wonder how many people like not go
Will Jerma get it in 10 tries?
Okay.
Will I get white in 10
tries?
So theoretically it should be
between 10 and like 15 attempts
to pop up once.
Why am I waiting? Let's go.
Oh wait, no, no, no. The reason why I'm waiting
is because, yeah, then if you
see the first one, if it lands on the first one,
right, okay. I'm going to get it in 10 tries.
All right.
Close the poll. I'm going to go for it.
How can we?
Do we have to wait? Okay, we can wait.
20,000 on blue.
Imagine if a roulette table was not just red and black.
Imagine if it was red, green,
blue, yellow, white.
I don't think anybody would play this.
And it had the numbers too.
Here we go. Will I get this
in 10 attempts? I'm going to laugh.
It's the first one. M number one is
red, sorry. Red.
M number two.
Oh, blue sucks. Actually, blue
has come up a lot of times. Oh
shit, that was almost there. Red again.
This is easy money to bet against it.
It's, I mean that, yeah,
that is, if you bet
that I was going to hit
white. Remember, you guys have
a, you guys are doing a yes or
no, but your no
has like a 90% chance to
be correct. You know what I mean?
You're like, you're betting against the odds
here, but you're not getting any benefit from it.
If you guys were going to get like
10 to 1 channel points, that would make
sense. But like, if you're
betting that this is not going to happen, you are
going with what will probably happen.
Oh, oh shit, that almost happened.
This is number four.
Not looking good.
Not looking good, that's blue again.
Should have went all in on the other side.
I would have, if it were my channel
points and I had the opportunity to go all in against the
white, I would have absolutely
put it, I would have done it.
I mean, it could still happen. There's no
such thing as a sure thing.
This is six, nope.
Looking pretty bleak. Here comes number
seven. Here we go.
I'm surprised this many people did white.
That was almost 50-50.
That's shocking to me.
I was expecting like 90-10.
There's only two more opportunities.
No, it's
not looking good. It's not
looking good. This is the last chance here.
This is it.
Sorry guys, if you voted for
the white sliver here.
Don't think you're going to make
oh,
that was nine? What do you mean that was nine?
That was ten, right?
That was nine? No, it wasn't.
That was ten, wasn't it? It's one more?
That was eight. No, that was
nine? It was nine?
Oh, what? It was nine?
I thought it was nine. That was nine.
Nine? Are we keeping track?
Is anybody keeping track of this? This is number ten
right now. Look. That was nine.
Okay. You should be. I'm just not.
That was
nine. That was nine.
That's it. Sorry, everybody.
That was
such a sure thing
essentially to win.
Oh, I would have laughed if it went on white.
All right. I got one for you.
Are you ready? You guys ready?
Will it land on
red on the next
spin? Yes or no?
Will red come up
on the next spin? Yes or no?
And 20
community subs from Goikey.
Will it be red?
Yes or no on the next spin?
You're literally playing baby roulette.
Yeah, I know this.
You made me hurt my elbow.
I know this is baby roulette.
Yeah, this is like
I'm the dealer
and you were just playing like
five year old roulette.
But no, but hold on. But the
dealer does not look at everybody and go
Hey, you guys think
it's gonna land on red?
Yeah, well, no. Yeah, they do. Because then you, yeah,
they do. That's exactly what happens.
Because then the person goes, Oh, I don't think so.
I'm gonna put it on black or I'm gonna put it on like
it's double zero. It's nothing.
Will it land on red?
You ready? I can't spin it until it's
over. I'm actually kind of nervous with some of you guys.
All right. You ready? Here we go.
Three, two, one,
go. Oh,
no. That's you just hate to see that.
You hate to see that. You hate
to see that. You actually
hate to see that. That literally
folded over.
Oh, no.
Do it again. Okay.
Will it land
on blue this
spin? What the fuck am I doing here?
I'm doing this one more time.
Will it land on blue
this spin? Is it legal
to do this? Play an
arcade game where people, where we
use a pretend fake currency?
Oh, that's a shit. That is a
shitload of
of that shitload of nos.
Oh, man. That's 20
that's 20 million.
That's five to 20 million right now.
By the way, is this a little, is this too much?
The flashing?
Did I like look away or look up here or something?
Should I look down? Is that too much?
No? Okay.
All right. Is it gonna land on blue? We'll find out.
Three, two,
one, closed?
Did it close? Oh,
sorry, everybody.
Some of you had a chance.
Oh, that's not good. I'm sorry.
I tried. I tried.
There's more shit over here.
Basketball.
Hold on. My, the like flashing gave me
like wicked watery eyes.
All right. I think I'm good. Here we go.
Okay. You get like thrown out for this kind
of behavior. I can do better than that.
I can do better than that. Here we go.
I gotta find the right spot. I'll get it.
Let me find the right spot first.
There? No.
Maybe like here. No. Here.
No. Here. Maybe. Hold on.
Go to the right. One let go.
One let go. One let
go. Stop it! I'm trying to practice!
Yes, I want to play again. Of course I do.
What are you guys voting on?
One let go. One let go.
One, let go. One, let go. One, let go. One, let go. One, let go. One, let go.
This is the spot right here. Don't move. I got it. This is the spot literally right here.
Don't move. Watch this shit. You ready? You ready for this? Check this out. This is going to be a
weird... What happened? What was the prediction? What was it for? Will he get over 50 points
before quitting? How many points do I have? As a gamer, you try to find the extreme exploit
to get it every single fucking time. I'll get it. It's going to be one little spot around here
where I can hold the button down and get a drain every single shot. I'm not trying to do it normally.
I'm trying to win. I already got over 50 points. Yeah, didn't I? It's close. Got it. Y'all just
lost. Y'all just lost. I'm sorry. Holy shit, there's a lot here. That was sick. I told you,
as a gamer, we're very analytical. We take all the situations presented in front of us with the
least, the best possible outcome or the skill. You know what I mean? I'm a gamer like you.
Let me turn my fucking lights on. See? There we go. Oh, ice hockey. I think I've made this joke
before in this reference before, but I hate playing this game because to play this game and have fun,
the person that you are playing against, you both have to have the unwritten rule
that no one's going to smash it into the other person's hand. Because I've played plenty of
times this little like shuffleboard ice hockey with people and they're fucking slamming it as
hard as they can and it like boom hits you right in the finger into the hurts for like a week.
You got to have an understanding that this is just like a joke. It's just fun.
You're not really putting full force behind any of your moves. Unfortunately, some people don't care
and they act like they're like hitting the using the hammer and smashing the test of strength thing.
I hate playing against because you never know who you're going to get. And who you think is somebody
that might you might connect with the unwritten rule there that they hit it as hard as you've
ever seen anybody hit it before. And they are having so much fucking fun. And you just want
to get away from it so bad. After one game, you're like, Oh, that was cool. Let's see what else there
is here. And they want to do it like fucking five times in a row. I don't want to do that.
I don't want to play shuffle ice hockey thing, air hockey, 10 times in a row. You do. Because
you're a fucking psycho. And you just want to hit the thing as hard as you can. And
sure. Um, yeah, I would consider myself pretty I know the arcade very well. You know, I know
you like the air, the feeling of the air in your hand. You're one to talk. I just like the air.
Honestly, I just want to I would just I would like to lie down on this. Does that make me a
fucking weirdo? I would love to just like lie down on my back and lie on this. All the air holes.
That'd be so cool. Why don't they? Why don't they sell these just like old beds?
I would love to be able to do that. If I could be in my house and just lie on my back naked on
one of these. That'd be fucking that'd be like after the shower. Imagine getting out of the shower.
And you just lie on your back on this. That would be like the greatest thing ever.
Especially during like a hot day or something. That'd be so awesome. It'd be like part of my
like morning routine. Why naked so every air hole can like get every like part of you. Otherwise,
if you have I don't know, kicking the shit out of this guy, you can always tell when they're
going to do a huge move because it starts to bounce really slowly back and forth and they go.
If you see your friend's lips do that back up, they're not going to score. They're going to
knock it off the table and it's going to be going to make a scene. You see that fucking back up.
I've seen that face a thousand times. It's this. I know that face and I'm backing the fuck up.
Sour tower. Baby arm. Did I win? Oh shit. I won. How many tickets did I get for that?
Oh my goodness. That's a lot. If you win against these guys, they'll come out and fight you. Wait.
Oh, this is the dude with the bat. Wait, does that mean his bat is not on him? What else is up here?
Oh, I want to go over here. Have I seen the um, I want to see what's over here. Oh, you're in
birthday mode. Yeah. Yeah. I'm in birthday mode. What's up here? Whoa. Oh, this is one of the
endings. This is cool. Feels birthday, man. It does feel birthday, man. I want an ooey gooey bear.
Nice. Did I play all the ones in here? Um, that's under construction. The shooting gallery. Oh,
what did I do with my jaw? Shooting gallery is not done yet. Okay. Hey, want to hear my jaw?
Listen to this. Can you guys see that? My jaw. My jaw's fucked up. I've never showed you that before.
Watch this. You have TMJ. I do. Oh, no. I already beat this one. I think I've seen everything in
here. That means I have to go back to Dizzy Bird. But first, I'm going to order like 10 pizzas for
the for everybody here. Grease bucket coming your way. All right. Let me see him. Sounds good.
I want a pizza so bad. No, I didn't play the lava game. I don't think I can. It's just that
order. I just spend like 80 bucks for one pizza. See if I can get the pizza in the basket.
This voice sounds like a bit from you. Hey there. Hey there. I'll fire a fresh one up for you.
Say, hold on. What can I get for you? Can you hear Otto? He's going,
he just woke up and he's going, all right, I'll get right on that for you.
Otto, what is going on over here? He just rolled around and just started going. Oh, I can do it.
Can I get for you a little bit? One grease bucket. What the heck? It should be
fresh ingredients. Oh, Otto. Oh, you can't see him. He's not on the bed. He is now leaving the room.
He has left the room. Otto has left the building. He's left the room. The lie. No, he's he literally
ran over here. How high can I stack this? How many kids can I do? That's just me. That's my
normal speaking voice. This is, no, no, no, this is not me doing a voice. This is like whenever
something like funny potentially happens on screen, that happens to my voice. Like if I start to laugh
about something or react like harshly while laughing, that's how I talk. That's actually
what it sounds like. Where are all the coins? What do you mean?
Turn with a lava game. It's out of order. Look, it's out of order. It's not ready yet. Why am I
buying this many pizzas? Because I want it to stack up to the lip here. So when I add a next
one after the one that hits the lip, the physics will go yellow well and it'll explode.
One side actually works. Really? Oh, shit. Okay. I'll play it in a minute. We're getting really
close to our yellow well moment. Our laughing out loud moment is so close. It's very, very close.
I can't wait till it goes all the way to the top and then it starts to spread out really quickly
and the game crashes and it goes. Let us bet. Okay, hold on. It's pretty much there.
Okay, you want to bet? Will there be a laugh out loud moment
once five more pizzas are added on top of this? Wait, no, but that's very subjective.
That's incredibly subjective. All right, hold on. How are you going to bet on that?
You can't even bet on anything. Will a pizza hit the floor? Will a pizza hit the floor? Is
that a good one? I don't think any of these work. I'm just going to keep going.
Let's see what happens. They're kind of just folding. It's starting to squish.
It's going to freak the fuck out. It might. It really could. It might freak the fuck out
here in another two or three of them. Especially if I really throw a curveball in and I put a soda
on top. Prediction started. What's the prediction for? I can't. What's the bet?
I can't. I cannot see what the bet is. I have no idea what the bet is.
I need more money. Oh, I saw it. Oh, it's still going. Shit. It's going to despawn. Is it going
to despawn? I hope not. Just keep it in line of sight. I think there's a bug on my head.
I swear to God. Still there. I don't even know what's going on. It's a bug in my hair.
Okay. Back to the pizzas. No. Out of my way. Okay. Don't touch them. They're still going. More.
I hate this scammer. I don't even know what's going on. There it goes.
Let's go put pizzas everywhere. All right. Bye. Get around. Okay. You're evil. Go to the lava
game. Oh, right. Okay. Pizza in one. All right. Lava. Oh shit. It is. It does exist. It do exist.
Oh, M&M's. How do I play? Is the thing for my... Are you sure I can play it? Oh my goodness.
I want 10 coins. Wait, is it a baseball? Oh, it's like a... I have no idea what's going on.
Oh shit. Cool. I have 200 balls. Trying to get them in the middle here. Light for spin.
Oh, get in there. Nice. Just fill up the middle here. Here we go. Right in the middle. All right.
Over this side. There's going to be big money over here. Push these ones down and light the
spin up. There it is. All right. Cool. Spin. 20 extra credits. What's the blue thing over there?
The blue ball. I don't get it. There really is not much to get with the coin pusher. You just
put coins or balls down here and you're just trying to push the stuff off. And they do an
optical illusion. We're right at the bottom here. Right here. Nice. There's an optical illusion,
which a lot of people don't know this. This is... This goes up. So this looks like that.
It actually looks like this. But it's an optical illusion. They have mirrors and shit in there.
So when you push the coins up and they look like they're hanging over the edge, they actually,
they're up on a lip. That's absolute horse shit. I'm not going to look at what this is, but I've
just bet wisely because I have no idea what you're betting on. Okay. If it's like, am I going to say
peepee in the next 10 minutes? Then let's find out. I want that blue ball. Do it again. I want
that blue ball. Oh shit. What's that? Lava? Lava mayhem. Five spins times three. That's 55 times
three. That's a time. All right. Give me a huge one. Oh, that's nothing. That sucks. What about
ice ball? 40 times three. Come on. Let me know something cool. All right. This ball, it's almost
going to go down. This ball. Come on. Give me the big one. Big one. Got it. That's 500 tickets. All
right. What happened? What'd you guys vote on? What'd you guys bet on? It was, it was refunded.
What was it? Wait, we got another. I'm not going to look at this one. I love these machines.
They're so much fun. God. I wanted to just, I want one. You know what? I want one in my house.
It's just relaxing. It's relaxing to like watch the coins push. How much do you, okay. How much is
just like a coin pusher machine? I can't even look at chat because I don't know what you're betting
on, but I can't be that much money, right? Ben just having one of these just like right over here
and I can just sit there and just play it for fun. Just when I'm just hanging out.
I find this to be very relaxing. No bets. What do you mean no bets? I bet they're over. Okay.
What is it? Will German earn more than 500 tickets this skill? Okay. What's the, what's the new one
here? It's 12 grand for a coin pusher. No, it's not. 3,200 tickets. Damn. Those are the results.
Oh, okay. I want to go to the, I want to go to the, I want to say other casino. I was going to say
where the fuck are these, where are these from? I want to go to, I want to do Dizzy Bird. Where's,
where's Dizzy Bird? Gary's Gas. I don't know. Where am I going? All right. I want to go to,
is it the beach? Where's that original one with the Dizzy Bird? Don't act like this is not how
all you guys play GTA. You just look at the line, the purple line,
and you just drive with the purple line on the mini map. You don't even look at the road
because I can just go like a hundred miles per hour and just go like this and just see exactly
where I'm going. Gas, gas, gas. You know, okay. Everybody's saying gas. I thought you were just
saying like gas, like gas, like gas, like gas. I thought you were doing this, like this thing.
Gas. I thought you were doing that. Gas, gas, gas. Oh, cool. What's in here? I really thought
that's what you guys are doing. Where's the gas? Where's, where's, where's, where's, where's my uncle
Jerry's Gas Station? What's back in there? Where's the gas station? Jerry's Gas and Go. Can I make it
there? Where the hell is it? Fill it up. How do I buy gas? Almost blew it up. Use it. Fill up the gas.
Oh, deadly nerve agent. All right. Now we got to go over here this way and we got to go down to
the pier. Where do we go? Where do we go? Where do we go? I want dizzy bird. I don't care about
anything but dizzy bird. I don't know the pier grounds. I have to go to Larry's. I can't even.
Where is it? Leave me alone. There's Larry's. Larry's. I want to get the, I want to get that
music again. That's the Guy Fieri takes a bite out of a hamburger diners drive-ins and dive song.
Where is that? I have to hear it again. Okay, so here we go. He's about to lean in. He's going to
take the bite. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where's that coming from?
Where's it coming from? Where's the music coming from? A house? Where'd it go? I didn't even get
it. I didn't even get it. I didn't get it. It didn't even come out. Oh, there it is. It's,
the shit's stuck. That's a big one up. That one don't open. Where to join? They're flipping
up hot pancakes and comfort food. Why crouching? Still in the car. Welcome to Triple D. Where to
join? No, no, no. He doesn't do that. He's driving around. No, he doesn't do that. He doesn't do that.
Okay, where are we? I need to go to Larry's arcade. This way. Go. Dizzy bird. I know I'm going for it.
You see how itchy my eye is? Let me do that. God, can I catch a break? What's this? What's this?
What's this new badge? Wait, what is this? Predicted yes. Predicted no. Wait, what? Why does everyone
have a badge that says predicted yes or no? I thought it was on sub only for a second. I was
like, what's going on? I don't care about the price. Just exchange the presence for money
so I can get it and I can put it in here. What do you mean no? No, what?
It's green on dizzy bird. First attempt. Why the hell would you vote yes for that?
That's a guaranteed free channel points. Guaranteed. I thought you cared. I tried.
What do you mean I thought I cared? Of course I do. This game's too hard. What the fuck are you
doing? Hey, Jerma, I appreciate you could do Bill Murray. I can't even read what you're writing.
Jerma, can you please do a Bill Murray impression? I'd be very pleased if you did
that impression in case you didn't hear me when I first asked. I'd like you to do a Bill Murray
impression. Okay, I guess I'll be doing Bill Murray for at least a little while. Hey, I don't know
what you're talking about. What are you thinking? Get out of my face. He's a fucking guy. He's like
a guy that speaks with a low tone. I will use my powers to make the machine go green the next time
I use it. Must play dizzy bird. Must play dizzy bird. That's my token. It's out of order. I think
it's out of order. Let's go. I don't think I've ever done this before. I've hit the green once,
but I've never won twice. It's not gonna happen. We're in sub only. Oh, are they getting out of
control? Sub only. I didn't even snap. That hurt. Go all the way up. It needs to be red to go up
there. All right, I need red to go up there. I don't know what you're voting on or predicting
or whatever, but you're probably all gonna lose your money. You're probably all gonna lose your
money. I'm definitely not gonna do the thing that you say I'm gonna do. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go. Shit. What's the battery for? I'll never get the green. It's never gonna happen. Charged and
ready. All right, this is the one to get. This is the easy one. I just don't know. I don't know what
to do. I gotta go up to red for this shit? What? So if it's on the top layer, it's gotta be red.
That's stupid. What's going on? There's a kid stuck in here. I got distracted because there's
a fucking kid stuck in here. Refund. What? I lost. Hey, hey, I don't know what actually scanned.
I'm not paying any attention to your casino gambling betting stream. Here we go. Red. Red,
red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red,
relax. Jesus. I have to, I'm, I'm, I'm done playing it. This is dumb. I'm done. I'm done. I've done,
I've done this stream already. You've already watched it. You watched it like a year ago,
like a year and a half ago. I already did this. Do you really want to see me do this shit again?
Oh, nobody wants to see me do this again. No one wants to see me do this again. Not one person.
I'll do 10 more attempts and then I'm done. After 10 more attempts, I'm done.
Not enough. Not enough. I wouldn't mind if you were a full-time dizzy bird streamer.
That might be the worst fucking stream I could ever think of. Got it. Can you imagine if I just
played dizzy bird every single day? That's like, that would be the world's shittiest stream.
That would be the world's shittiest stream. Hold on. There's people like behind me. There's people
that are crowding me. I have to back up because there's people just literally, I'm going to have
to start moving people out of the way. You little dicks get away from me. You dickheads. And now my
shot got screwed up because there's somebody just pushing into me. No, I don't want to play again
because I'm, what's the platypus's name from that Phineas and Ferb show? Well, he's on the screen
right now, but he's orange. That's, that's it. That's going to be the one. Damn it. Harry the
platypus. Oh, Harry the platypus. It's so nice to see you. That's just me. I've seen that show
before and I don't like it. All right. Bonus is on. It's back there. Oh, I don't, I don't,
I'm kidding. I like the show. Obviously I don't like the show. I don't care what I don't,
I don't watch that show. I've seen like a few episodes randomly. I'm sure it's fine. I'm sure
it's a good show. I've done, I've never, I've seen like three episodes. I don't know. I don't watch
Phineas and fucking Ferb. I don't, I've seen, I've seen like two episodes. I'm sure it's just fine.
I'm sure it's a good show. I'm sure it's funny and engaging. I don't know anything about it.
You're a coward. It is an inga- I don't know anything about the show.
I know, I do know something about the show. They have two kids, one Phineas, one Ferb and Phineas
is the one that talks. Right. And Ferb says like one line an episode. That's why I'm never hearing
that. I don't see, I don't watch the show. Phineas is like, I know what we're going to do today.
Right. And like at the end of the episode, Ferb was like, well, that shit was absolutely ridiculous.
Now, wasn't it? I've seen it before. It's, that's a good show. I would have just got out of my seat
and like sprinted out of the room running saying, please don't hurt me.
Like I'm, my, my pants situation would, that would be bad if I would get in trouble.
I have a pair of, I'm wearing pants. I'm, that's not what I meant. I meant like, I don't want to
get up and like turn and have my like ass in the camera because I know what happened the last time
I turn and like sprinted over into the corner or out of the room. My fucking ass was in the camera
and you all zoomed in on it and made it huge. This person, somebody help this person. I actually have
to stop doing this. I'm done. I've won it twice. I have to stop playing this. But anyways, so you've
got, you've got Phineas and Ferb, but those are the two. And you got Dr. Dufrin Schmitz, right.
It was like the evil. And then you have Perry, Perry the platypus is a secret agent.
Who cares? Why do I have to keep telling? Why do I have to justify that? I know the show.
Oh, and then it goes, just check us out. We're Phineas and Ferb and we're going to make up.
We're going to have a ball. I've seen the show before. It's wrong. It's something like that.
Look, for somebody that's seen two or three episodes of this entire show,
I think I got the idea. I think I get it. He owns the box set. How long you been playing this for?
I don't know. I'm like 15, 20 minutes. His inner complexities of that show. I don't know. I'm sure
there are whatever. I'm sure it's, I'm sure the show is just fine. I'm sure it's a good show.
I don't know anything about it. I went too far. And I said that I didn't like the show as a joke
to try to make everybody go, well, he doesn't like Phineas and Ferb. What is he a fucking dick?
I went a little too far. Backpedal Andy. I so badly just want us to start like yell,
singing the theme song. Is this your sorry video? It's, I'm telling you, it looks like the platypus
and finally I did it. I fucking hate this game. This is a pre-recording. Hey, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe,
master one just wrote at seven 56 Pacific time today that they said it was a pre-recorded stream
and that's not, how would I have been able to do that?
And they're like rocking the fuck out. I'm done. Move on. We've been here for six hours.
Resident sleeper. Why would I record that? That's not even funny.
Resident sleeper. It's not funny. That's like just stupid. You're that one.
Like that was like, that's a good one. I can pull it back here.
The game won't let me leave. This is pathetic. Is this new? Oh, I never won this one. Did I?
Check us out with Phineas and Ferb. We're gonna have a ball. It's stuck in my head now. I think
it's a good song. It's a good show. It's a show that's very engaging to its audience that is a
fan of it. I just love the beef stew. It's the best thing they have here.
Pizza is the best thing that they have in the entire place. It's my favorite.
And they've been cracking this joint since 1932.
It's 1974 and it was made by this guy and it goes all the way to the top, all the way to the top
and we let go now. What drugs are you on right now? Be honest. Zero. Besides coffee.
I don't do drugs. Everybody thinks I go. He must be on drugs. He must be on drugs. I got it. I've
never got that before. It's the first time I've gotten it. How much was, how much is that for?
Why can you see my brain? You can see my, you can see my brain. That was a mid tier one.
How much is four? A thousand fucking tickets. Holy shit. What's the top one for then?
Not enough loot. Oh, you're just weird. Um, I don't know. Do you think I'm weird?
Oh, guess what? So it's a joker. So I, that means I'm the joker. I'm weird.
You mean the Riddler. Yeah. Did he give up on survival? Yeah. It's like kind of too hard.
You're the questioner. The Riddler's sidekick. The pollster. Batman, do you prefer apples or oranges?
Batman, are you a Democrat or a pep? He was, that was Robin. That was very easy. Where's the
fucking Riddler? I don't know. I'm going to give you two options here. Political streamer. What?
The questioner. Question me this Batman. Questioner. He just gives math problems that are really easy
to solve. Oh, Batman. I see you fell right into my trap. Hmm. Interesting. In front of you is a
sheet of paper that has two variables on it. Can you solve for X? No, thank you.
The greedy guesser. Did I win? Why is he so disgusted with himself? No, I'm not. I'm disgusted
with this guy right here because he's always showing himself. I would love it if he would
just stay over there, but he doesn't see, he doesn't want to. Look, he hates me. He always does that.
Dude, relax. Holy, I'm fucking kidding. I'm just winning over and over again, by the way. Oh, no,
I'm not. Dude, relax. I'm honestly really concerned about Jerma's wellbeing. I'm fine. You
don't have to worry about me. I'm fine. I'll get out of my laboratory. I got like two different
potions here and I'm like start dumping them together. Look at this guy. Oh, another coin
game. 10,000 tickets and then I'll see you tomorrow. Sounds like a plan. Don't forget about mini golf.
I played mini golf. I played the first nine holes. Oh, that's right. I guess I could see the other
ones. I went to a job interview and then they asked me what my weaknesses were and I said
everything. I don't think I'm going to get the job. Well, that was your mistake. You didn't
go in full Darth Vader costume. Going like this. You didn't have the full Darth Vader on.
Fallout 76 sucks. That's a weird thing to say randomly. Somebody gave 76 gifted subs. Okay.
Well, thank you for the gifted subs. Appreciate it. That's the worst Darth Vader I've ever heard.
That is not the worst Darth Vader you've ever heard. This is.
That's the worst you've ever heard. Kylo Ren. Was it not bad? I couldn't even hear it.
That was the stunt devil. Just end the stream. I'm fine. Do Homer Simpson. I'm not going to do
Homer Simpson. No, I told you I was never ever ever doing a Simpsons character ever again.
I'm not doing a Simpsons character again. Only in extreme circumstances. This is not an extreme
circumstance. No. Wait. Why would this be? Why is it? This is not an extreme circumstance.
No way. All right. I'm going to count my tickets and then I'm going to. I'll see you tomorrow.
I think we've seen all the new content. I extremely need to hear it. I can't do
Homer Simpson. You're going to get me. I'm telling you. It's his fate. You can't bait me every day.
Last one and then I'm gone. Last one and then I'm out of here. I'm done after this. Put your
cam back on. Coward. Fine. That's fucking rigged. See you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow for
hopefully Pikmin 2. That's the plan. You know what? I'll give it. Coin game. I'm going to have to tell
you. Coin game is awesome because this is what? The fourth coin game. We've gotten four streams
out of coin game. It's like 20 to 30 plus hours of content in this game. It's actually insane.
And they keep adding more things. So that was really fun. I like the new arcade.
Low beans tomorrow. We're doing Pikmin tomorrow. If for some reason I do not have. There's no reason
why I shouldn't have Pikmin. But if for some crazy reason I don't have it tomorrow then we'll figure
something out. Pikmin 2 is the plan though. Probably around the same time around 430 pacific.
I know we've been starting it like later recently but I've been getting up a lot later recently.
Are you going to do Pikmin 1 and 3 afterwards? I don't. I really don't know. It depends how much
I like Pikmin 2. If I love Pikmin 2 then we'll probably do the other ones. We'll see. Thanks for
watching everybody. See you tomorrow. 430 pacific time. Thank you for watching. Good night everybody.
Have a wonderful rest of your night. Thanks for the subs. There was a lot of subs today. There was
a shitload of community subs and I know I didn't get them all. It was a lot. So thank you guys.
I really appreciate it. Thank you. And I think I did I think we had we did have a
there was like 25,000 people here at the very beginning of the stream and I did we get
rated by Ludwig? Did it actually happen? Because if you're here still from Ludwig then
uh thanks a lot. Oh he hosted as Ian. Okay that's cool. I get it. Cool. Well yeah Ludwig's uh Ludwig's
awesome so good to see you guys. And Cake Catboy rated. Yeah I don't know why I couldn't see any
of them. I feel like they like there was like at least two or three that just didn't show up on
any of my dashboards. I don't know why. Well thanks everybody. Whoever did. All right let's
see uh where am I sending you guys today? Where you going? Where are we going? Raid yourself.
Hassan Hassan Hassan Hassan. I saw Hassan uh react to the dump truck ass.
I guess that's a weird feeling for me when somebody just might not even know who I am
and they just look at me in a mirror with like a huge ass. That's lovely. What does that sound
even doing? I gotta like I don't even like follow anybody. People probably think I'm such a fucking
weirdo man. I don't follow anybody on Twitch. I have like two I have like ten five to ten channels
that I follow. Um you're weird it's because you're weird. I'm not even that much of a weird person.
Am I too weird? Am I too weird? All right well all right here we go. We're just gonna fucking go
for it right? We're gonna spread ourselves out there. Let's go raid Hassan. Let's do it. Why not?
I have to follow the channel too. I gotta follow. I gotta follow like a hundred people today.
Raid Jabroni. All right well don't network Andy. This is not a network Andy scenario.
I'm this is not a network Andy scenario. I'm not networking Andy. No I'm not networking Andy.
Have I ever networked networking Andy in 10 years of doing this? I'm not. Go raid Hassan. I'm not
network Andy. We get dog dog god damn it. Okay good night. I'll see you tomorrow. Hey networking
Andy is gonna go to bed now. Now go say hello. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Good night. Good luck.
Take care of yourselves. Don't make me look like shit. I know you guys make people sing
raid songs and stuff but I don't you don't make me look like shit. Yeah I make me look good.
So I could be networking Andy. Yes. Bye.