Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight, gonna be playing as the Soldier with the strange rocket launcher, the buff
banner, and the escape plan, probably my default setup as the Soldier. And before I get into
really anything in this video, I want to talk about something very, very important. It seems
like YouTube hates my channel in recent weeks. Half of my videos are not publishing to you
guys. I put a tweet out last night asking, hey, are you guys even getting my videos in
your sub boxes? And at least 15 people were like, nope. So I guess the only real solution
to this, because it's totally out of my hands, guys, I really wish there was something I
could do, is if you are not getting my videos in your sub box, I'm just gonna put my recent
videos in the description of pretty much all my videos, just so if you happen to catch
one of them, you'll be able to go to the description and go and see the ones that you may have
missed. Now, that's obviously not the ideal solution. I'd like my channel just to work
as intended. But if it's not going to, then that's the only thing I can really think of
for a solution. So in the description of this video, there's gonna be a list of three or
four videos that you may have missed. And if you already saw them, you don't have to
go back and watch them again. It's just these that's just there for the people that may
have missed something. So if you go through that list and you say, wait a second, I didn't
see this face cam fortress video, what the hell, then go ahead and click on it. And you
can go ahead and watch it from there. So again, I am really sorry about this. I wish there
was something I could do, but there just there just isn't. I'm at the mercy of YouTube. But
enough of that, that that's enough depressing talk for one day. Let's get into the video.
Let's talk about the soldier on gorge. I want to give you a couple tips on gorge as
soldier. So the first thing I want to talk about is this right balcony. And most of these
things are going to be on defense, not very many offensive tips for you right now, because
obviously I'm playing on defense. But if you saw right there, when I jumped up on this
right side, I totally negated the rocket jump because there was a small health pack sitting
right here. Now, anytime you jump up here, you're never gonna have to worry about losing
health on your rocket jump. And oh, I'm gonna have like 40 50 less health. Oh, that's not
good. You don't have to worry about that, because you will get that every single time.
Unless this is a big unless unless there is a teleporter sitting right here, and there's
nine people up here all pushing the point, then this is not the best route to go. But
if you see in this gameplay, there's very few people up here, there's only one sniper or
one pyro will be up here at any given time. So this is a fantastic way to wrap around.
And that's what you want to try and do here. When you get up here, when you finally go
around and you kill a couple people, you are going to have a bird's eye view perfect for
soldier, you're going to be on high ground over everybody, which allows you to jump down
if you want, try and do some crazy tactics, try and do a super shot. I don't even know
what a super shot is. But it gives you a lot of options to play around as the soldier.
And speaking of just gorge in general, there's a lot of these little balconies, there's a
lot of these little side balconies, even on the first point, the second point, all in
between, there's a lot of places for you to jump. And I don't mean jump around like
star, where star jumps around like crazy and gets like 90 kills by jumping off walls and
going around. I'm talking just regular, here's a balcony and dares to jump, I jumped up
to the balcony. That's my type of rocket jump. That's my, I can't really do that crazy,
awesome stuff. But there's a lot of these on gorge, a lot of these small balconies,
small cubbies. And it kind of reminds me of a place like gravel pit, where gravel pit
has a couple of small jumps that take you to really, really important places. But only
a couple classes can even get there. People like the scout, the pyro, the soldier and
the demo man are the only ones, well, I guess the medic now has an opportunity if he uses
the quick fix. But they're the only ones with the opportunities to move higher than a normal
jump at any given second. And I really love maps in this game that allow certain opportunities
for different classes. I'm not a big fan of maps where you just kind of pit one team
against the other team. And you just smash together in the middle and that's it. It's
just like a big mess of people in one spot. I like when there's multiple options. I like
when there's a lot of strategy involved. Strategy on a very basic level, not strategy like,
okay, we got to have two scouts over that way. We got to have four medics go that way,
four medic, that's a lot of people. But you know what I mean? I like when things have just
general diversity. I like when things are allowed to be done a million different ways. And that's
why I love Team Fortress. There's a million different ways to play this game. You could
come on and play this game tonight and then play it tomorrow and do something completely
different and you might even learn something. I'm still learning things in this game and
I've been playing since the beta. That's how ridiculous this game really is. But enough
about my love for Team Fortress, let's get back to the Soldier and talk about another
chip that you could do on Gravel Pit. I mean Gorge. So on Gravel, I almost just did it
again. On Gorge, G-O-R-G-E on defense, you're going to notice that the blue team after capping
the first point only has one spawn door to come out of. And look where it is. It's up
on a high rise. So if you can wrap around as the Soldier here, get around, kill a couple
people, you will cause so much fear and so much chaos because you can jump up here in
front of their spawn door. Now I do it once and I jump right back down, but look at all
these people that are like, just running away from me because they are so scared. That's
what you want to try and do. I mean, you don't want to try and do this, make this kind of
a little side mission if you end up doing it. But once you do get back here, just look
at all these people that are in a freak out mode right now. All of them are just thinking,
get this guy out of here. Can we get somebody to kill this Soldier? Can we get him out of
here? Throw him in the dungeon for crying out loud. That will be going through my head.
So it's good to cause some chaos every now and then. Good to freak the other team out.
So then they're looking for you again. Because if you get away, that's the number one thing.
If you can get away after doing this, you are going to make so many people coming out
of the spawn. Just look left, look, where is that? Is that Soldier here? Kind of the
same theory if you were a spy, I guess. But that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And again, there's going
to be a list of three or four videos in the description that you may have missed because
sub boxes are being really messed up and crazy. So if you want to go check those videos out,
they will be there. And every single video I make from now on is going to have the last
three or four videos in the description. I'm going to do this for as long as... Until this
is all fixed, I'm going to be doing it for that long. So thank you guys again for watching
so much. I'll see you guys all soon. And take care, everybody.