Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here, with sort of a different video today. I apologize if I sound a little nervous, because I am.
I just found a wild spee nest on Dustbowl, and this is- they pop up from time to time, but I've got to be really careful here, guys.
This is the middle of mating season. Blue spees and red spees are going to be mating. I've got to be very, very quiet here.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Does he see me?
That would have been very bad.
I don't like how they're reacting to this, though. I don't like how- oh god. Oh god, just run, I've got to get out of here.
Oh no, they're killing each other.
Gee, I'm going to die. I'm going to fucking die here.
I can die here.
I think it's still growing. Your head's big, too.
Is mine big, too?
Yeah, taunt.
It's still growing.
It's not stopping.
Help me. Help me.
It's spee. It's spee.
It's getting bigger.
Oh my god.
You cannot publish me.
It's getting so big, you're taking up almost the whole map.
Your head is upside down, growing, by the way.
What? Why is it backwards? What is going on?
I put a negative value in.
It's just taking up your body.
That is so stupid.
Dude, it is so dumb.
Okay, okay, okay.
Have you ever seen the Super Mario Brothers live action movie?
Yes.
You know, the Goombas in that movie.
It's hard to remember. It's been so long.
You have the cigarette coming out of your neck.
Yeah, you do.
Look at these little fucking peanut heads.