Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here, and welcome to Black Ops 2.
We've been waiting for this game for so long, and it's finally here. I can't wait to talk about it.
I could even sing a song about this game, but I'm not going to. We're going to talk about tips and tricks,
and what I've found in the game so far to be cool, and that sort of shit. So sit back and relax, and let's do it!
So the first tip I can give you is to go right to your menu the second you load the game up,
and get yourself pumped up for Black Ops 2. You want to crank the music as loud as it can possibly go.
And here we go, ladies and gentlemen, Black Ops 2 is in the house! Crank that volume! Let's go, baby!
cheX
Also, you've got to make sure you drink your favourite game fuel. Just like this!
You know I like getting this game. Come on, let me get my game fuel, you fucking piece of shit!
Okay, got him, got him!
This next one is not so big a tip, as it is an absolute necessity.
Necessity you want to get on your final fucking kill game after every single match and
That's it. That's all I got. I think I'm my hallucinating right now
Are you guys seeing bugs on the screen like a shitload of beetles like a thousand of them?
No, my I'm freaking out. I think I drank way too much of that shit man. I'm losing it
Now there's mice all over the floor
There's mice everywhere. Oh
The whole room is on fire right now. This entire room's on fire. There's bugs and beetles
Wait, what are you doing? Yeah, and I'll call a duty black ops 2 came out. You're real excited. Just calm down
You don't have to worry about it. I'm gonna kill you
Burn your body and then eat it every single bit of it. I'm gonna swallow
I'm gonna swallow you whole
Grandpa you all right grandpa. Hey, hey
Hey, what's what is it? You were just staring right through me. Are you all right? You're sweating right now. Oh, I need to get you
Like a cloth. All right. Well, don't get it. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, what is that? What the hell is that?
That's just as a drink as my game if you know, it's not yes
It is I see vodka gin three empty energy drinks and two empty coffees. Are you mixing drinks down here?
What are you doing, man? Just put it down. It's not come on duty black ops 2 only comes out once a year
So come on, whatever. I'll see you later
Also watch you step on the way out because I may have peed. Yep. Oh, yep. Definitely