Hello, how are you? Early stream? Hmm, earlier. Earlier.
I hope everybody had a good 4th of July. That sounded like I just sipped a bunch of whipped cream off.
Well, I don't even care. That's a new me.
I'm not gonna do something that sounds weird and then explain it for five minutes.
No, it's a new me. New me. Yes, you will, probably.
And in pre-stream earlier, somebody was saying,
Oh man, I... What if it happened to the... That like, jacked, like wicked red Jerma.
Man, like what happened to him? I just want to say, welcome 25 to 35. Good luck.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, 25 to 35. Okay. We'll see. New? You're old.
They were just joking? As am I. As am I. Don't worry, we're all joking here.
So today we're playing with Ster. Ster is here.
I don't want to introduce him yet because I want it to be a big surprise when he shows up.
The plan today, Ster was like, hey, this is a game called Hail Card. Looks pretty cool.
I was like, yeah, I'll get it. So I got it.
We also have two other games that we might move to. Maybe not. We'll see.
I didn't mean it in a bad way. No, I know. I'm just kidding around too.
I have a very important question for Ster. Actually, a couple.
Hey, I have a couple questions for you. Oh, yeah.
Question number one, what temperature do you put your thermostat on a hot day?
That's a really complicated variable question. It is. I know it's loaded.
Because in the winter, I was explaining this the other day,
you got to set it at a certain temperature at which the AC triggers,
not the temperature you actually want it.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
So like in the summer, if I turn on the AC and put it at like 78,
it'll trigger and it'll be really cold in here.
But in the winter, if I put it at like 72, that's when it'll, I don't know.
That's what you mean. But you said 78.
Well, I don't think it's actually 78 in here.
That's what I'm saying is that it's like the AC is fighting that the fact
that it's a hundred degrees outside and it's just on.
I would like a like a true thermostat because this thing, I think it's a liar.
You also have the same problem where the room that you are in right now
gets to like a hundred degrees, but then you will go out of that room
and the room that actually has a thermostat in it is like nice and cool.
Yeah. Well, that's the also if you stream in a room, it will be 80 degrees.
There's no way around it.
And those of you that have like your gamer room.
So I put my AC when I'm streaming 73.
Okay. Yeah. I usually try to keep my between 76, 75, 77.
Maybe if I'm not really streaming or anything, I could fill up.
Good answer.
Oh, yeah. Well, like if it was 75 or 78, this room would be 85 degrees to 90.
Regardless of the rest of my apartment would be cold.
Yeah, I put it at 73.
So it like continues to pump cold air in here because otherwise it doesn't care.
I don't exist to my AC. All right.
What about let me ask you this.
What about the I'm seeing a lot of people in chat right now.
And I know a lot of people in my, you know, personal life to like friends
and family members that say that I'm fucking nuts for having my thermostat
at like 77 or 76 because they like what are you talking about?
Like it needs to be in the low 70s or high 60s for me.
And to me that kind of that's kind of like a like like a freezer to me.
Is it to you too?
I don't know.
See, that's where it all comes down.
It might be 60 in the rest of my apartment sometimes,
even though it's set to like 73.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, like I don't get an even distribution.
If you set your thermostat to like if it's a hot day or whatever,
if it's like during summer and you set your thermostat to 68,
I'm not even sure my therm.
I don't think I could even get the temperature to be 70 degrees right now.
If I tried it's just like a hundred hundred and ten degrees out right now.
Hundred five, whatever it is.
I'm not even sure I could actually even happen.
Do you like going out in a hundred and five degree weather?
Actually, I do.
And that's like that makes me a weird thing too.
I if it's a hundred and five out, I want to go outside.
But then when I'm inside, it's got to be really cold.
If it like if it gets to like 80 90 in here, it's disgusting.
Can't handle that.
So but so you like it at like a hundred and ten outside
and you like it at like 70 inside.
Yeah, I need a refugee.
Okay.
Yeah.
So that's refuge.
I need refuge.
Germa.
Are you a lizard?
I like it hot.
I like the hot weather.
I actually enjoy it.
You two are reptiles.
Oh, it's going to be heating up in here.
I hate the heat.
I want to cry if it's hotter than 85.
Just start crying.
The moment it goes from 84 to 85.
You just start like, no, this is too much.
You're sitting there looking at a thermostat like, no, don't please don't.
It's like 84.
No, no, no 85.
But the real feel is 70.
72 to 73 is perfect.
I think.
Do you want to play the game that you want to play here?
It's funny that you phrased it like that.
I mean, because I feel like this is just not going to hold your attention.
And the first thing someone said in my chat was like, can't wait for
Germa to get bored of this in 30 minutes.
So we have two backups.
But here's the thing.
Hold on.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Okay, there's the alright.
I am ready.
You say like, you know what?
On one hand, I appreciate you agreeing to play this.
Yeah.
On the other hand, I wish you'd just say shut up.
That's I don't know.
I'd rather do something else.
Oh, like you said when I invited you to the house flipper thing on Tuesday.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'm going to be here on Tuesday.
I mean, I'll do it.
Well, no, yeah, you can't because now I can't.
Well, I confirmed the list.
I confirmed the list.
You couldn't add plus one to the list.
I could fucking your best man at your wedding.
Do you want I I was just messing around.
But do you actually have you want to do it?
I can know by the end of the day.
I'll be here on Tuesday.
Okay, you're going to do it and you're not here's what I think you're going to do.
It's everyone's timed everyone gets 70 minutes to make a house.
And I know you're going to do 70.
It's not enough time.
Trust me.
We I've tested you're going to get in there.
He's doing full runs to test.
Oh, I have a hole.
You're slow.
You're slow as shit.
How many times did you like stop to explain something when you were building your house?
Yeah, but when you're on a timer, you can't do that.
You got to go.
But here's what I think you're going to do.
I'm going to take your joke from you and I'm going to ruin it.
Okay, you're going to show up.
It's going to be like, all right, everybody get started and everyone's going to be so like, let's go.
I'm hype.
You're going to make a big deal about how hyped you are about this.
You are then going to exit house flipper and go do something else.
And then when your time slot is up, it's just going to be the default house.
It's like that you didn't even do anything.
I'm not going to lie.
That was my first idea.
Yeah, and it's a good idea.
Like I don't want to agree to do this whole thing for this one joke.
And it's the most predictable joke.
He knows I'm going to do but then I came up with joke too.
Still like it's still just like 60 minutes for one joke.
I don't know.
You could if you really want me in this room.
I mean, what is it scored on creativity complexity going to be really biased
because someone told me that you could like import images.
Yes as your wallpaper.
So I just feel like whoever does the drama memes on the wall is going to win.
If why would I I'm going to I'm going to be doing it very seriously.
I'm going to be taking it dead seriously.
It's I don't think you can creativity.
I don't think you can separate yourself.
Like once you enter a room and it's like, oh, this is the auto room
and it's like all dog toys and pictures of auto on the wall.
That person won.
So they didn't win.
They got points for philosophy because that's one of the categories.
Okay.
Yeah, there is creativity complexity structural integrity cleanliness
philosophy and chats grade.
Well, let me ask you this in your own home decor decoration type
strat like your own home.
Yeah, what how is your home decorated?
Do you decorate your home?
Do you go around like all this painting would look great in my Fourier?
I mean sometimes.
Yeah, I think when you get like a new place you kind of look around
and you go, all right, I could see maybe like a painting there
and be like a furniture piece that you do your own design philosophy
when you first I guess when you first move in I don't do this every day.
I don't walk around and go I don't walk around my you know, look at my Reddit
shelf and be like, hmm, what should I add?
I did it.
I did my decoration shelf.
I read it shelf.
You have a Reddit shelf.
It's just that's like the what everybody calls it because they make fun of me
for it.
I have a shelf that has a bunch of like trinkets on it.
Oh, you like framed photographs of all of your favorite comments from Reddit.
No, it's all my favorite stream items.
It's a little like pieces of memorabilia for me to remember like,
oh wait, I remember I did the dollhouse.
There's like the dollhouse the 985 sign.
It's nice to come in and look.
Yeah, I would be all white walls.
No decorations.
The only reason I have anything on my wall is because the camera points at it.
It's like you want me to come in a house flipper and I'm a minimalist.
Hey, the invite is there.
If you if you want to do it, I can get you just said the invite wasn't there
anymore.
But then you told me you had like, okay.
Well, here's the way we got to give the context to everybody listening.
I reached out and hey stir good buddy know each other for like 30 years.
You want to do a house flipper house and your reply was stop talking to me,
which was which was hurtful.
And I figured it was I give you a few days.
And then when I tried again, I said, hey, just want to check it in again.
If you curious if you want to do that house flipper thing, you sent me a gift
of the current the frog drinking the tea and was like, yeah, it was like one.
I don't know.
It was kind of it was kind of hurtful.
Do you know my favorite gift images?
What is it?
And it relates to this.
He doesn't know my favorite gift.
You have a giga Chad is a giga Chad.
No, it's the orangutan trying to nail the nail into the wood, but he's not
actually doing it.
David Attenborough are doing a tumbleweed just went by.
We have to like press play.
All right.
I mean, you're going to like a check out.
I got a laugh.
You got it.
Well, we have a DM open if you want to show it to me.
I could find it.
All right.
It was just if I laugh then you don't have to do a house flipper house.
If I do laugh then you do wait.
They said it wrong.
Which one is more beneficial to you me losing or winning?
I didn't even hear the terms and conditions.
I just said it and I don't remember either.
Let's just play while I'm opening.
I just got it.
You're a don't laugh.
Okay, if I laugh at your gift, I'm I can see it.
It's over there right now.
I'm not going to look though.
If I laugh at this if I genuinely go, okay, that's funny.
Then you don't have to do a house flipper house.
If I do laugh if I don't laugh, you know, I'm just going to look at it.
All right.
That's funny.
It's the best thing on the internet.
It's pretty funny.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's all I love that.
It kind of looks like it loops and he's just trying.
He's been trying for a really long time.
My favorite part is he's got it in his mouth and he kind of like he kind of takes it out.
Okay, you ready?
I don't know.
You have any any more anymore zany things to talk about before we come up with it.
We're ready.
We're okay.
Yeah, it'll it'll it'll come up.
I don't know if you can see the screen.
I'm choosing the destination.
It's like a roguelike.
There's 12 floors to the final boss.
I get to do you give like a TLDR for what is going on.
I haven't played this game before.
My interpretation is that it's slay the spire with friends who play the spire.
You know, you battle the enemies of the gift.
It's quite clear.
Did you not show it on your stream?
I just looked over at your channel.
Let me get it.
Okay.
He doesn't care about the viewer experience.
I guess how do I even doubt?
Well, it's not I don't have this on my computer like you do.
You do because I sent it to you.
But I have to save it and like copy it and then put it over here.
Not I mean, no really.
You can drag it from discord into your OBS window.
I can't it doesn't let me do that.
Don't don't make up stuff reviews.
Okay.
That's it's pretty funny.
It's okay.
You don't have to make a house if you don't want to but wait, what if I want it to then?
Yeah, then I'll give you a time slot.
Wait, there's time slots.
I don't think there's like 12 streamers doing this.
I thought they were all going to be doing it at the same time.
Yeah, but then after you have to give me a tour like you can't do it.
Everyone can't do a tour at the exact same time and you have to like schedule an open house.
Yes, there are 12 people doing this is the game multiplayer.
Like you walk you go to their house.
No, it's going to be discord sharing or through their stream.
You mean there's going to be 13 people.
Well, it depends.
There's still one or two you in the game.
I'm Vince.
I've been in the game the whole time.
I don't we were choosing floor one.
It gives you an option you encounter skeletons and a Smith or a vault where I haven't played this either.
I'm ready stir.
The only reason why people are here is to watch us argue.
So don't worry.
I know but I picked the most complicated game to argue over because you're going to have to like read cards and understand things and mechanics when we really should just be like doing a food podcast.
Yeah, how do I ready up?
I don't know.
I've never played this before.
Do I have to choose a ready button on each floor?
You have a choice between two monsters guarding different locations.
Each hero makes their own choice.
Oh, oh, okay.
Zombie corpse or skeleton.
Would you do left one?
I don't I think maybe it'll even pick whatever a skeleton.
Okay, it shows what we picked above our characters.
All right, let's go.
Yeah.
Wow.
No cam.
If you're good, I'll turn it on.
You have a cam on right now.
I mean, I do.
All right.
So what do we do?
You attack cards drag to the enemy using your mana.
You've never played slay this fire.
I have.
Yeah.
But do we go at the same time?
Is it turns or is it?
I we're going to find out block cards.
Yeah, that just gives you the armor.
Yep.
Tell what a monster is doing by the things above their head.
Yeah, they're intent intent.
Yep.
Just like I played a little bit of Slay This Fire.
Okay.
The circle around us represents melee range and rain.
And okay, I'm done.
I can't I'm done.
Okay, that's it.
That was it.
That's it.
I read it all.
We're good.
I think we go simultaneously.
So like where are you?
I'm on the left.
Oh, we have like, okay.
We have two halves of a screen.
Yeah, and then your manas you got three mana.
I assume at the bottom.
It's a dude.
So I'm going to attack this try to attack people on your side.
Should we just go the same person?
Can you attack the zombie?
Yeah, I don't.
Okay, can you kill that guy?
And then I'm the Ranger then I have one mana to kind of cool
actually.
All right.
So I have to block now and now we in turn this is kind of cool
and then they come get us.
So when they're in the circle here that imagine that it said
when they're in the circle, they count as being in melee range.
Oh, okay.
Special heart icons to read their tooltips special features
only attacks only from near range.
I picked the game with reading man.
I can read I just did source.
When are you going to play sorcery?
You ever going to do that?
I played sorcery one on stream.
It's I'm telling you your chats going to love it.
Just going to love it if you do but every time I play a game
like that my chats like you why do you just play every game
Jerma plays stop saying that to him.
Stop saying that to him.
Stop you're hurting my feelings.
Stop saying that the great game.
They said if you play sorcery, we're done with you.
There's a better playthrough on the internet.
It's not true.
All right, so mighty blow you'll to damage in a medium radius
random monster and radius is okay.
So this will hurt to these two people.
I should probably block right with the mana because I'm going
to be the one taking all these hits.
You're taking a lot of hits you're taking out.
Oh, you're good.
You were taking a minus three fantastic for in the tutorial
level.
I think we got this why have a max amount of shield I can have
as I probably just what the hell just happened.
I just did two shield blocks and it took me down to one shield.
Oh, that's mana.
Oops.
All right, so that's one whoops.
Are you going to hit them ever?
I mean it's I could try hitting them but seems like that's
something that's on your agenda.
Well, your armor doesn't carry over to the next turn.
So you had six armor and they did like two damage to you.
That's Matt.
That's just simple math or Sarah.
Are you turned on your webcam to compete with me?
Yes.
Nice.
You what do you have?
What kind of hair do you have?
What I'm going to swing what kind of hair all right my sides
clear yours isn't my sides clear easy.
No jokes.
This is actually pretty cool.
This is like a cool concept.
No jokes.
That's why we're playing it.
Do we share this or is this for each of us?
I believe it's for each of us.
It's offering me rogue cards and you're getting warrior cards.
I thought you were going to be the wizard to be honest.
I feel like we needed a shield guy.
I took some aoe and I don't know what this gem is to what
a stamina can be added or subtracted by special card.
What does stamina do?
Is that just like the stamina?
I don't know.
I feel like this is going to be hard to use.
I'll get the short sword stamina is mana.
Okay.
Nice.
No sporadu here.
That's fine.
Why does everyone all of a sudden think you're a vampire?
Because we made like a little jokey reference.
Somebody made a picture of me with like powdered face in
like a full Dracula costume.
And then I said I would do it on Halloween.
I would do that exact outfit and you didn't do it.
Well, it's not Halloween yet.
Halloween is on October.
I guess I don't have enough money.
Vault.
Oops.
Okay, those look kind of grayed out.
Okay.
Wait, what are you picking any of these?
Yeah, so you get gems.
I got four gems.
Scoop is given you like, I don't know if we would choose.
I don't know if we have like the same choices.
Yeah, how come there's a refine?
Ooh, okay.
I'm going to write a random card shield block is going to
turn into.
Ooh, this is good for both of us.
That's good for both of us.
That gives you shield as well.
I'll be support.
Okay, get a random artifact of any rarity.
I'll try that you'll free HP after each battle.
You survive.
That's pretty good.
Maybe we shouldn't spend all of our money.
Yeah, I only spent one.
Not all of them cost money.
Cool.
Okay, and then we go down to the next floor and I get it.
That's fun.
What did you get for eight max HP?
That's pretty good.
You should think about a new haircut.
Well, I was in the middle of growing out every single like
piece of hair.
It got pretty long up here.
It was I had a really big beard.
No, it was unbearable in the heat.
It was like 115 at one point in Vegas here last week.
I want to say and I just it just like it had to go.
It was unfucking bearable.
Skeletons weren't that bad.
What is the fucking you've been in Vegas too long.
We're doing like some Elvis shit.
What is this?
What is what you seen Street?
You played Street Fighter.
Yeah, right.
What are you talking about?
You just really got inspired by Marissa.
You thought like I hairstyle looks sick.
I can pull that off.
I don't know what you're describing.
What's going?
What are you talking about?
You ready to go next floor?
I've had this hair for I I used to do e3 presentations
with this hair.
This has been a lot e3 presentation.
Yes for a long time.
Not officially not officially speaking, but you know,
I would everybody it's this is I do this all the time.
Oh, yeah.
I was presenting for my game company that I was a part of.
Oh, yeah, I remember I remember.
We keep teaching new things.
They work over time.
Okay cooperation is key.
Click on your teammates avatar to see their deck and map right.
Click on a spot on the floor to get okay.
Well, we're in a call so we can just yeah, we're not we that's
all irrelevant to me.
I think we actually have to start doing strategy though.
I think that that they that pop-up was hey, you know, you know
how to play the game now.
You need to communicate.
So how do you want to do this?
We got I don't understand.
What was the buff thing that they were talking about?
Yeah, they went away the influences.
I'm going to give us or block.
I think that's a good use of our time here and then I'm going
to deal.
This is going to be three four.
I'm good.
I can take all these hits and I'm going to do a I'm going to
hit these this guy right here.
Actually, I'm going to hit the archer.
That's weird that sometimes when I shoot enemies out of my
out of this like far away this zombie and I don't kill them.
They've returned one damage to me like it's like slay this
fire.
Like, you know, you hit the thing but it feels weird when
you're a range character and they're that far away and he's
a zombie and I can clearly see that he's a zombie.
Was it a ranged zombie like a zombie mage or something?
No, it's like when you hit something they hit you back.
Oh, it's like the boom.
You both did damage.
Okay.
I see.
Yeah, the hearthstone cards bumping.
Yep.
Okay.
Rose a bone in me.
This monster is buffed.
He's got five damage.
This is going to hurt a lot.
I'm about to take 10 damage.
If you die, I can kill me.
I'm shooting him.
God you're about to take five still.
Well, not necessarily true.
Wait, wait.
Oops.
Can you block me?
It doesn't matter.
I can block you.
Yes, and then I can kill this guy.
I'm still going to take one damage though.
Oh, cuz those long-range guys are shooting you know, what
is shake down?
You'll did you just do that?
Yes.
Oh, that's what you are playing.
I get it my gems.
Yeah, better be better be grateful.
Wait, how do I I can't use my blocks on you.
That's that's a you thing.
You can't do it to me.
I'm getting kind of hurt here.
All right, you you're okay.
Yeah, why do they all want to kill you?
I think I'm the tank, right?
I'm going to give us this yourself like a tank.
Let's do that.
I mean I could I do I I deal more damage to things when
they're outside the circles.
So when they're all coming in this circle, I start to
become pretty useless.
So I can kill the range guy.
I guess I can kill the guy right next to me and then
you're kind of on your own.
Yeah, we're good.
We're good.
And take any damage.
I had your stream muted for like two minutes and I
didn't even realize it.
You probably busy with something.
You probably had something else going on.
I can kill this guy and then I'm going to give you
some block and then I'm going to swing my sword at
this one.
Okay, I didn't spend the gems.
It just isn't showing the gems on the UI yet or
while we're in combat.
You asked her if he had a good breakfast.
Did you have a good breakfast?
Did I did I would you have let's compare breakfasts
as that's on I think today I had a what did I have
I had a I just had a sandwich just like a two slices
of bread.
You put meat and cheese in between it tight.
What was this?
What was the meat?
Ham salami Muenster cheese sandwich.
Okay, that's like I would eat that.
Okay, but you're you're about to like embarrass me
with this incredible.
No breakfast you had I had.
I drank full serving of kefir.
It's just like a yogurt drink and then I had some
greens what I don't know when I say it like that.
It sounds like I am kind of trying to be better
than you.
There's the inflection of the green and some greens
because like you didn't say you had green so I was
like trying to make it seem like I was like way
better than you at breakfast.
Hey, I didn't I did not have a balanced breakfast.
I normally wouldn't have that for breakfast and
I'm kind of embarrassed and you're putting me on
the spot.
What a health nut.
I'm really not.
Oh, is it just gambling?
You have a 50% chance to find three gems.
Well, I lost.
I got him.
I'm doing the I'm doing the gem build.
There's a lot of rogue gem cards.
Okay, I can exchange this you'll damage equal to
your block.
Hmm.
I don't like that in a boomerang shield.
I mean why not free free and then I'll do this
and I lost again.
You're poor.
That was like 50 52 50 50s losing them both you
will encounter Templar.
So this is we can upgrade our cards.
All right, so they these these mean very important
thing.
Yeah, the type of enemy you fight and the reward
you want.
What do you have on you?
We choose our own and then the end where it shows
like the three options I think are based on
what we chose.
Okay.
Well, I made it hard because I Templar is going
to fight us.
Okay.
Well, how do you know what Templar is hard Templars
are usually weak because when they go to swing
at you they go wait would God want this and they
hesitate that looks like a hard enemy as 15 health
I got an I got a card.
I got a trump card for that guy.
So right now I'm going to shield block you out.
Let me shield block you first if you're going to
take damage because you'll get it did literally.
I don't know why I did literally nothing.
I'm going to do mighty blow.
What is this new thing here?
What is that above the imp block against three
block from a fix your sideburns there?
They probably all messed up right now.
It's fine though.
I don't care to ignite bombs.
All right.
Well, I'm in a little bit of trouble here.
Oh, you see, okay.
I put a bomb out there.
You see the bomb on the right this thing here.
Yeah, and I have to ignite it and the other Templar
I bombed him you're in danger there pal the first
monster I could kill the one here.
I could do okay.
I could do for damage to the Templar.
I got it.
I'll just okay.
I can't kill this imp but I could kill the yeah,
I'm going to kill this guy and then I will just
do a oh with it not in the circle thought he's
in the circle.
I think when they're on the line that's considered
mid-range or can you remove this charm that you
put on me just go eat a banana.
You'll be all right that does fix it.
Usually I'm going to I was going to attack this
person right next to you.
Thank you.
What did you do?
I kicked him away.
We don't got to kill him this turn or you had
lethal you had to make them did I did I actually
have lethal I can't see your cards.
Why do you have two webcams?
Do you you should get like five of all different
angles of your head.
Did I tell you about the stream that I really
wanted to do and it was I wanted to get like 30
webcams and have them all set for different
timings and stuff and have them delayed at
different times so I could like yell at myself
and fight myself and stuff.
Okay, you go Andy.
Well, I I talked to I talked to Jake about it
community Jake and he was just like I don't
think what you want to do is physically fucking
possible.
I was like, okay, I was like, all right yourself
on a camera.
I was like, whatever if it's not going to work.
It's not going to work.
Here there's also it was it was this was like
kind of COVID was still kind of COVID was like
people were locked down was happening and I
didn't want to because like webcams people doing
a bunch of zoom calls and be needing to buy
webcams and I didn't want to be the guy that
like wiped out the fucking webcam supply during
COVID by buying like 40 of them.
It was like, I don't think I want to do that.
I think that's probably like not a good idea.
Oh, we won.
I could understand that argument if you went to
the grocery store and like bought all of the
food, but these you're talking about webcams.
Yeah, but there was I feel like there was like a
weird price surge with webcams and it was like,
oh, they're like very expensive now because
people are buying them to a ton of people are
buying them.
I was like, I don't I want to be the guy that
has I don't know.
I don't know if I want to do it.
I got like test ones at one point at some point
later.
I got I want to say like six and I tried to
hook them all up and it was like this is fucking
impossible and it just made me frustrated and
I just can the whole thing just delay the single
webcam 30 times.
There is some weird reason why I couldn't do that.
I forget what it was, but I thought of that you
can barely use one webcam.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was a USB thing, right?
Yeah, it was like the amount of USB bus slots
that are on a motherboard like it couldn't do
it or something.
You can you can get a like a USB extension.
Yeah, but I think it's still uses the same bus
lane.
I really think so.
I looked into this and I was like, well fuck.
I can't do this.
I have a I forget what you call him like a graphics
card.
You plug it into that slot and it has USBs on it.
I have one of those like why couldn't you do that?
I wouldn't.
It was something it was something and I think the
only way I would have needed to have like four
motherboards and it's just like this is this this
is turning into like a like a science YouTube video
that I'm not making and I'm not I don't think so.
So you so you gave up I did.
Yeah, some ideas you just kind of move on.
Okay.
Yeah, that's true.
All right.
I'm going to refine this one's good.
Hey maker.
All right.
Hey maker or maim.
Oh, I love my names.
I'm doing a maker and then I'm going to do so I
get both of these.
Oh, I like that.
Wait, what a strain do is that like you can't lose
you lose.
Why you spend your money?
No, my build gained strength from how many gems
I have.
I are in my build German.
Do you want removal on the next rest period?
Do you want new cards new cards?
I want to see the new cards.
Okay, I want to see what's out there in the big wide
world just by 40 PCs.
I agree with that.
I know this one looks hard.
Yeah, you ever seen a snail dude.
Yeah.
So when these firearms fly into the near range,
they explode when they die.
So you got to watch out for that.
I heard us with it last round.
I didn't know I'm going to give this to you and
then I'm going to slash this one.
I'm going to slash this morning.
Yeah, wait, should we kill this thing?
It's in here at the top this thing right here.
Do you have one damage not in close range?
No, oops.
Well, I killed it didn't have to hello.
It was weird.
You look like Anakin from episode 3.
That sounds like a compliment Anakin is one of
the most powerful Jedi's to have ever existed.
Cool.
How come every time I take that test I get Yoda
which is also amazing by the way.
Yoda's pretty sick.
All right, you're just kind of cute five damage.
Does anybody have block on right now?
No, I can't really do anything this round.
You want me to just do here.
It's hard out here.
Can I hit everybody with this?
I thought it would could only hit two people.
That's amazing.
Okay.
Well, I almost just cleared my whole side.
You have a favorite Star Wars character.
I don't know the big one.
Jabba.
Yeah, how about the Hutt is your favorite Star Wars
character.
I'm not I don't know too much about Star Wars,
but I know he's cool.
Mine's Luke.
Lame.
If your answer of your favorite Star Wars
character is like the protagonist.
Lame.
Luke is actually really cool though.
It's not Luke, but I would say Luke is cool.
That's a bad take.
Yeah, that's a pretty shit take stir.
Why because okay, what if the main character
of a show is really really awesome like really
cool and like wow, what a great character.
Let me ask you this.
Have you played Red Dead Redemption 2?
No, what?
Okay.
I played half of the tutorial and I was like,
I don't think I really want to do this.
What no way you've never really good.
Wow.
Okay.
But did you play GTA 5 all the way through you did
didn't know I got to that mission where you had
to start like loading cargo at the shipyard
and I was like, this isn't what I signed up for.
I kind of lost interest in the story.
Oh, I just exploded that you got any armor for me?
I did.
I got rid of it.
But anyways, my point was going to be that Arthur
Morgan is the main character and I think Arthur
Morgan is probably one of the coolest characters
in that whole game.
Like is that is that wrong?
Which one's Arthur Morgan?
Dutch.
I can't do it.
Oh and Red Dead Redemption.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
That was not a great impression, but yeah,
but we're talking about Star Wars.
Yeah, but I'm saying but you said the main character
thinking the main character is the best character
in the series is lame is what you said.
Arthur Morgan is not lame and I think he's the
best character in that game.
No, no, no, no.
I'm talking about Star Wars.
Okay, I'm talking about in general.
Oh, characters are bad.
Okay, everybody settle down reason, but like when
you're talking about Disney Star Wars, like I want
to be the protag Luke.
He's so strong.
They have like no personality.
You really want to you your main your favorite
character is Luke when there's characters like
Jabba the Hutt all the side characters in Star
Wars are cooler than the main protags because
they're not human.
It's always the default anime protag human male
white male hit with the hair.
I did not I did not know you with this strongly
for I thought you meant all I thought you meant
all fucking like media.
Dude any show I've ever seen the main character
so boring.
That's what I thought you like our main character.
I don't like that.
I like the weird side character that was in two
episodes, which is they're still cold.
I have a lot of favorites that are like that.
They're the they're the blank slate that you put
inject yourself into and you you love that guy.
Don't you know?
Well, hold on this thing.
I think silent protagonist.
Yes, I think a silent protagonist you're imprinting
yourself on a silent protagonist.
I think that it has a kiss his sister.
I don't maybe I don't know.
Yeah, no points for that.
I was ironically saying Luke.
I don't think Luke is the coolest character in the franchise.
It's ironic.
I was pulling back.
I was just being ironic.
So is your general Grievous is my favorite character
in all of Star Wars.
Okay, if you want me to give it to you, I do.
Did you pick a card yet?
I'm confused.
Sure.
I picked a card general general Grievous.
There it is.
I think I've told this story to you and multiple times
before that when I was a child in the first grade
Star Wars was really cool.
I'd never seen any of them, but I knew it was cool.
And when I was out shopping with my mom, I saw
a t-shirt with one of the droids on it because that movie
had just come out and I was like I want that so I can fit in
and that's all I know about the Clone Ward bought movies.
Okay, that's kind of cool though.
I don't know anything about general Grievous.
I just know that he's got four lightsabers and he still
can't beat a guy with one.
I'm about to get really heated at that point in episode 3
general Grievous was already very injured.
Not only that he was injured previously before the events
that happened in the prequels very seriously injured.
Okay, hold on.
I got to settle down.
He literally wasn't.
I don't know the lore.
I wish I could debate you more, but I actually haven't seen
it.
You just don't know the lore.
That's okay.
Oh, you're great out.
You're a Star Wars nerd.
I'm not really.
I haven't seen any of the newer things.
Why not?
I don't know because it's just too much of it.
It's like I it's there's just too much.
It's too much.
I don't I don't I don't want I don't there's too many
things to watch.
It's just like I it's like, oh the Mandalorian Mandalorian
and then we got like all these other like Obi-Wan stuff.
And then there's they're making like another movie.
They're making like another TV show and then it's kind of
like the Marvel stuff for me.
It's like my this is too much of it.
It's just I don't even it's like I don't yeah.
Yeah, I you know, I agree.
I would much prefer if they made a Dune movie and it was
like one third of the first book and nothing really happens.
I made this joke like a year or two ago, but I was going
to say like I can't like let me just say it out loud
because it's very good.
I think I made a tweet that I didn't tweet it saved in
drafts.
So, you know, like that as you will it said I can't wait
for phase six of the Marvel Cinematic Universe when it's
a baking competition between Wolverine Cyclops and
Professor X like reality show.
That's pretty damn weird.
Wait, where did I missed a few sentences there?
How did we jump from the what I don't think you were
paying attention to what I was saying, but it's okay.
Okay.
No, I wasn't.
I was thinking about doing wait.
There's a TV series.
You ready there were what a boss fight.
I think we're fighting the Whopper from the Big Mac.
We're fighting the Whopper.
Yeah, I don't think we're there yet.
We have another floor.
All right.
How about the wild hog?
That sounds good.
We're gonna eat a VLT kill curse ghost.
That's a lot.
That is a lot boys.
What do these do attacks only from near range heels itself
at the beginning of monsters turn and it's rotten.
So you have to kill these things that they hurt you.
Okay, the big skeleton the Whopper is the Whopper.
All right spawns a skeleton every time it receives damage.
So don't just go tickling him.
Oh, I thought a lot of skeletons.
I thought you were just saying the Whopper.
This is the actual name of the Whopper.
Oh, I went to McDonald's.
I went to McDonald's.
This is important.
I went to McDonald's and I was so confident like, oh yeah,
McDonald's and I turned to the I turned to the the speaker
and I'm like, hey, how are you?
How are you doing today?
Having a good day?
I'll take one Grimace meal, please.
I was like, dude, that's over.
It's not happening anymore.
And I was like, and I said, oh fuck, I missed Grimace's birthday
and I think he heard me.
I didn't drink the fucking shake.
I don't even know what it tastes like.
I've tried to get it, but I was too late.
I said, oh fuck, I miss Grimace's birthday.
All right.
We're killing the Whopper.
I stun the Whopper.
So what do you want me to do?
I'm going to kill this character.
I mean, I did a lot.
I'm done.
I just took out three flying hogs and end turn.
I had a funny idea too.
You know, over and like drinks the Grimace shake and like, oh
my god, I'm I like died because I drank the shake or whatever
that like the trend is.
Yeah, I was going to take a sip out of the Grimace shake on
camera.
No way.
Yeah.
And then that's crazy.
Stop it.
And then after I took a sip out of it, it was going to cut to
me like lifting weights really well.
It was going to cut to me like relaxing on a couch.
It was going to cut to like I was going to do a lot of great
things were going to happen to me.
I was going to be like, wow, everything's like wonderful today.
I feel like great.
Everything feels amazing.
But I was like, oh, that's meh.
I thought it was all right for a second.
I mean, I would like that if also amongst those things.
It was like you making out with someone in a Grimace costume.
Lifted weights.
Everything's going so well.
Yeah.
Oh, that's like, I don't know what's wrong with everyone
else.
Like Grimace gets me.
Grimace gets me.
Oh, that's funny.
I was going to get like eight full hours of sleep.
But like during that trend, how expensive a Grimace costume
must be.
Yeah, you want to talk about buying the webcams during
when like the all five by 40 webcams.
How expensive was a fucking Grimace costume?
They got wiped out.
They were off of every shelf.
Well, no, I haven't seen a Grimace costume in any of those.
Maybe it wasn't effective, but you have to you know, and
it's got to get delivered.
Then Grimace's birthday is over.
How long can you guys birthday last?
It was I think the whole month of June.
Was it all of June or was it like just two weeks into how
long?
Oh, yeah, my birthday is June.
Hey, my whole birthday is an entire month.
You better give me presents every day.
It was a painful birth.
He's a big guy.
Oh my God.
Are you done with your turn?
Dude, you can't you can't drop a fucking nuke like that
and they don't expect me to take a minute.
All right.
What do we need?
How about how about just a block?
Sounds good.
That sounds good to me.
Hey, you want some card draw?
I'm done with my turn.
I needed that card a while ago.
Did you?
Well, you need to communicate.
I think we're gonna lose.
Wait, don't do anything yet.
Did you get a good card?
Mildly.
Oh, wait.
Okay, deal five additional damage if the monster has block.
Does the whopper have block?
Not yet.
What did you just do?
I got him.
Shit, that was pretty cool.
All right.
Well, I'll kill this guy now.
No, I won't.
You just took all my mana.
Did I?
How I took your mana?
I don't know.
Just go pull up my stream and rewind the VOD to see what you did.
We definitely have had this conversation before but
I can just kill that guy up there.
I'm gonna wait till the whopper has.
Okay, so I can kill a wounded monster with 10 or less HP.
Should we just get wait until the whopper is 10?
Dude, I think we're totally fine.
I don't think it really matters.
Thought they haven't said anything in literally 30 seconds time to leave.
That's what I do.
I'm just gonna keep kicking them.
Yeah, just keep pushing them back.
All right.
I mean, I should have waited till I did that.
I didn't take any damage.
I got 12 armor.
Every time I play an arrow, I get four block.
Is this game fun?
Yeah, actually it's pretty fun.
I like it.
Do you like it?
I like it so far.
We got the whopper.
Destroyed.
I was gonna sing like the Burger King song thing, but no.
No, I'm not doing that.
It's like that would be like dumb.
That would be very silly.
Yeah, it would be.
Keep killing.
That's like wow keyboard turned.
I just like want this because I just think of that.
Okay, gain one stamina for every eighth damage you deal and two stamina.
If the monsters attack leaves you with block.
Okay, so if I have too much block, I'll take I'll take the taunt.
That sounds fine.
You have nine money.
Yeah, what do you want me to do with it?
I just have a lot.
You're I also have like 18 more health than you.
What are you doing?
All heroes get two block at the start of each turn the next battle.
That sounds great.
We're going with this is a boss coming up real.
Wait, wasn't that just the boss?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna do that one.
And then I'm gonna remove that like the heel.
I think this is the boss, right?
Because one floor six the whopper was the boss.
Well, how come we have another boss then?
Okay, maybe we have another one.
Hold on.
Wait, that was a special whopper.
What did that say?
I think well my screen that said was a special whopper that things got
pickles mustard relish onions on it.
That's a special whopper.
Floor five was the whopper.
If we have that we're going against another whopper on floor eight.
We just did the whopper.
Now you got to pick floor six.
Yeah, I have one choice for floor six and it is the whopper.
We either we have different things.
So there's another look at look at my look at see.
Okay, then we got another whopper coming in.
I didn't have a choice of another whopper.
I thought we had the same choices.
Grimishake was the one of the worst milkshakes I've ever had.
I wanted to try it.
I was just late.
I thought you were going to go in there and do McDonald's and ask
for a whopper is where that was going.
That's no that is like that.
That's oh, that is a spectral whopper.
Yeah, that's bigger than the boss whopper.
Where is the whopper?
Oh, right.
Summon.
What is this puffy corpse?
I honestly thought whopper was the punch line.
Um, I don't think there was a punch line.
We just was saying whopper because he said it and we was like,
oh whopper and then we started talking about like McDonald's
Grimishakes.
I still can't get over the fucking comment you made earlier.
It's like fucking up my whole day, by the way.
Okay, I I'm sorry.
I thought it would make your day better.
I mean it was it was a wild comment.
Should I taunt something?
I'm getting I'm taking nine damage at the moment.
You are taking a lot of damage from what I don't know where
it's coming.
Oh the two ranged guys.
Oh all the way like I have to scroll up.
Wait, what there's a big guy up.
Oh, you can actually move the camera.
Yeah, WASD works.
I'm gonna stun him.
That's my turn.
I guess I'm taking six.
Did you have the Grimishake?
No, I did not.
Did you want Grimishake at any point in your life in June?
No, I didn't.
I didn't I legitimately didn't even consider it as an option.
I didn't I saw all the TikToks.
It never triggered in my brain.
Wait, that's a real thing that people can acquire.
Dude, they're blasting me.
I tried to give you some protection, but it didn't really
work.
Why didn't you use a deep breath?
I think that's not for me.
I think I mean, I think that's not for that's only for me.
We're gonna be fine.
I'm gonna be fine.
Yeah.
What about the Hamburglar's birthday?
Yeah, does this mean we're gonna get a birthday for every
McDonald's character?
I mean now now they're gonna do it like that the Hamburglar's
birthday and the meal and the the fries and the is this like
a bunch of characters that all had birthdays.
It's my wife's birthday today.
Happy birthday birthday.
Thank you.
I've been waiting for you to say that you're about to die.
You know, they all want me.
Can you help?
I can do that.
Can you kill one of the like guys trying to shoot me?
No, I have card draw and two damage.
That's all I have.
Your cards suck.
Hamburglar is bad.
He doesn't get a birthday there.
Okay, out of like the the tier list of McDonald's characters
the Hamburglar probably is pretty low.
I would say can you name the tier list of burgers?
What do you mean wrong?
I could you I think I could do some of them.
There's the Hamburglar, there's Grimace and then there's Ronald
McDonald and then there's a girl one.
There's also the fry.
There's like the there's like the nugget crew, right?
Isn't it like a whole chicken nugget crew?
This is not my area of expertise.
I don't the Hamburglar's schtick was like, Hamburglar was
gonna go on screen and go like what does he say?
He says that he has like says two words in a row and it's
like, what is it?
It's like, what is it?
What is it?
Yeah, rabble rabble rabble rabble rabble, right?
And then they would like speed up the footage by like 30%
and they would run around in a circle and anytime the
Hamburglar was in a commercial you could expect a 30 to 40%
fast-forward moment and it was like they do this every time.
I'm gonna kill.
So McDonald's commercials were upsetting to you as a child.
No, I just you think you could have done them better.
Yeah.
Yes, going in my notebook cataloging early German thoughts
and belief systems.
Well, when I was younger, I didn't think that but now
thinking back I could be like, you know what?
I could probably do a pretty good McDonald's commercial
bring back like a weird cartoon shit.
No, why not?
Everyone trying to kill me help I can taunt.
All right, who should I taunt who's doing the most damage?
I'm gonna taunt this one then now that it's okay.
Now it looks good.
We'll give us some block and then that's good.
There you go.
How all right I can get rid of this one on the left don't
attack wait 10 or less, right?
Can you do one damage to the big guy?
Yes.
No.
What that what did you do?
I don't know do it says deal double the amount of damage
is my gems.
I have eight gems and it did for damage.
Bermis has an undertale song in his playlist.
Oh, he never takes more damage than a single hit.
He never takes more than four damage a single hit.
He never takes more for damage.
First of all, is that an official grimace playlist that
you're talking about on Spotify?
Because what what do you mean?
There's a this is there an official birthday playlist.
You can't listen to that.
It's insane.
It's really what a lot.
Wait, how much block do I got enough the perfect amount
you kill that now.
I am out of actions.
Don't play it.
I I'm not playing the grimace playlist right now.
Maybe we'll listen to it tomorrow.
Coward.
They're trying to kill me.
You could deal three damage to him.
Come on.
I'll go.
I actually don't think I can come on.
Yes, I can now.
You only going to take 10 damage.
How much health you have you've 30 health.
You're fine.
Yeah, but it's it like goes away forever.
I'm never going to get this youth back who's got block.
You got this student him wait.
This will be how much would this be?
This will be for one health left.
I was counting.
What were we talking about?
Grimace shake.
You see he drank to do grimace shake and he got the purple on him
regems for that.
That's a good one.
I like this one.
I don't want to remove any cards.
So, okay, Slay the Spire did this too.
We're removing cards always felt like I don't want to take anything away.
Don't don't want to add more.
I don't want to take cards.
You can press back at the bottom left and skip rewards.
I'm not I'm not taking anything either.
Brown.
That's actually really good.
Oh, I'll take that too.
There's a lot of reading going on right now.
You think we're going to get to the final floor?
Maybe index are better than decks bloated with garbage.
That that makes sense.
What's your nighttime routine?
I just go into my bedroom and I go straight on my back like that
close my eyes and I don't move until I fall asleep.
That about sums up for me too.
I take my horse tranquilizer.
I'm out.
Yeah, I really am just iPad.
I hate it.
But so I'll just kind of lie in bed.
Do you do this too?
I just kind of lie like when I'm ready to go to bed.
It's like, all right.
I have my iPad.
I've got like games and like videos and okay, like TV shows.
I'll look at the clock and I'll be like Jesus what the hell is going on?
Like two hours have gone by.
I was supposed to go to bed like three hours ago.
Two hours ago and then I just go put it down and get away from it.
I do not do that.
I take my horse tranquilizer and then I go to bed.
Part of me is starting to understand that this is not a joke.
I am not a phone reader on the toilet like you are.
I'm not a device addicted.
You know, I can I can just let it go.
I feel like I could hear your like lips moving to say idiot.
I could hear it.
I'm not a device addicted.
I could hear like the idiot no judgment in my tone.
If you're going to have to sit on the toilet and read your phone and go to bed and read your phone.
There is no judgment.
But if you want to do that, that's fine.
I guess I'm going to get I'm going to die this round by the way.
You're killing me moment.
Yeah, you should like start playing cards.
I feel like I've been doing a lot for you.
Now it's time to you.
You gained a four block for your turn.
Look how many I don't have what other cards that I have to play.
What have you been selecting every time we go to a ball?
Let me take the hamburger is commercials were not good.
Okay, they sped it up.
They did chase the hamburger burglar around.
Here we go.
All right.
Now.
I'm good.
I got you.
What's priority?
But you're not communicating to any of your cards do stuff like that.
I put this you okay.
Here's my every turn you just go like and then I'm just like, okay, what do we do?
We're supposed to be communicating as a team.
Are we?
We're standing next to each other.
What my turns over here the cards I had defend me.
What do you think I'm doing?
I guess I'm going to swing it this person.
What are you reading on your phone?
What's up?
What's on the iPad?
Are you doing you?
That's when your mobile game time is I actually don't use a device really at
all unless I'm on the toilet or in bed.
I don't use it ever.
You can't follow up that statement by I don't use it ever.
We have to kill this whopper up here by the way, because they just look at
how much shit this I know there's a lot of stuff on your side of the
battlefield.
Yeah, but I have gained two block and like deal for damage.
Okay.
Maybe you should be picking some cards that do things.
Hey.
Oh, yeah.
What about this?
Oh, what's this minus 24?
That's about to kill you.
I think we just is this is a game where you lose and you put like points
into permanent upgrades, right?
I don't think I don't think we could have beaten this.
I mean, I don't want this to be one of those games where you have to lose
to win.
I would like to just kill them.
I think we just die.
I think that's I mean me the first time ever playing it.
Who's killing you?
Who's the who's doing the most damage to you right now?
I hate the problem of throw just throw a stone dude that everybody
is hurting me here.
I actually I actually die still.
No, you don't you're good.
I have actually have to you're right.
It would be flashing emergency colors.
If you were going to die and you guys watch the FNAF trailer after you
I've already done that.
I'm not watching another one.
They're going to come up with like five trailers of the next six months.
I'm not watching them all.
Isn't it kind of crazy though that they're making a five nights movies
just because I played it or your trailers.
I'm not a big fan of trailers, especially when they make like eight
of them and it effectively they just they they take a scene they
take a scene from every single scene in the entire movie and over
the course of like five trailers.
You won't you've almost seen the entire movie.
I watched the trailer.
I was like, okay, so that's how it ends, right?
Like that's the whole plot.
That's everything if you took like the three or four five different
trailers, some of these big franchises do you can take out all the
scenes and be like, well, there's a scene from literally every
single scene in the movie.
You already did this rant, but we're doing it again.
Some people haven't heard it and some people haven't awoken.
You're dying.
I know I am.
Wait, can you kill one enemy this game?
I can I can I can kill this guy and then I can kill this one,
which is this one's doing five.
Good luck because I lose.
No, you don't.
Are you going to save me?
There's got to be a way to save you.
There's simply got to be a way to kill every enemy this time.
There's no way I had the summoner on my side.
You got six health.
I'm about to take 22.
So technically 10.
All right.
I think I think this is over.
They all came with they all walked over to my side.
Death is not the end.
You've fallen in battle.
You can no longer play cards or take other active actions during this
fight.
If your team survives, you'll get rewards as usual.
I wait I can stay if you can do this somehow.
Then we continue.
I don't there's that awful at this game.
Well, hold on.
This is a game that I would never normally really play and it's also the
first time we've ever played it.
Why don't do we not just get any slack at all?
We don't get any slack at all.
No, you're dead weight.
You just took that personally.
Are you some they're all summoning?
This is what I'm telling you.
I was I was telling you there was a summoner on my side and you were
busy talking about grimace was trying to kill him.
Okay, but like to any of your cards do stuff like this.
No, why not?
I don't know because I what happened.
Maybe I should pick some of them.
Yeah, I don't have any of that.
I have gained block and hurt with block.
I am one.
I'm I'm I'm dead by two damage.
No, no, you're a streamer.
You should know how to play every game ever.
All right.
So now what happens we unlocked stuff.
Okay, there we go.
We got a rare voice line.
Oh, you got you got the new spray new artifact.
This is Harley Quinn.
You finished your run your heroes died, but the world mysteriously
reset to the time before they embarked on their quest.
Maybe the next heroes you create will avenge them and break this
cycle with each finished run you unlock new cards and artifacts
for the next heroes to use.
So we get better stuff.
We got one new artifact unlocked basically.
Okay, you want to go again?
Yeah, do you want to go again?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, let's do it.
You want to throw me an invite?
I'll do it again.
I mean, it's not we're not going to be it's not going to be
probably not going to be better than the last time.
Wait, what wants me to make a new character new character?
Can I get a coffee and be back in like two minutes?
I want I need another coffee.
Sure.
You go.
I'll take care of everything.
Well, you just have to invite me to your game.
I'll do the stream.
I'll do everything in the mission.
Oh, no, it's our artifacts are things you start with that
makes more sense.
You'll see and I had to make a new character and that new
character got the artifact.
All right.
I'm going to be and grab another coffee.
I'll be right back.
Okay, don't mute stir.
You haven't been on this channel for a long time.
I'm not muted.
Well, you're about to be thank God.
Yeah, don't mute nice minute.
I have right back.
I am back.
I am back and you are
but I've never met her you are unmuted and let me just
tell you something right now.
You made me laugh so bad.
I was in the middle of I was mid piss and I thought about
the fucking grimace comment again, and I think you actually
hurt me like it hurt.
I was I just sit in the pain.
It's just like I just thought of it.
It's thought of the fucking comment and just like I
I'll it hurt.
That's this stream was a success.
Then I want it like I want you to be in pain from at least
one joke per stream.
I feel like I don't have to do another like it's already
enough.
All right.
We good.
I invited you you got to join.
Oh, there's an invite.
You know, I knew I knew you were going to do that.
You what make a mage.
I feel like you're the one coming in saying I don't
understand these games.
How come you can't give me a break and you're like, okay,
I learned all the warrior cards.
Let me make a mage now, which is probably going to be
more complicated.
Proud of you for choosing the like I'm dumb warrior.
I hit this was randomly generated.
All right.
Should I not be a mage?
You could be anything you want to be.
All right.
Let me see.
There's a lot of characters here.
Okay, hold on.
What's your favorite spell of all the spells lightning?
Absolutely.
What lightning you want for him ball lightning lightning
bolt lightning storm chain lightning.
Why there?
Why because I like lightning moves in games.
I think are fun.
Lightning is erratic lightning is it's like, whoa, it
could do this damage or could do that damage.
It's always kind of all over the place.
I think it's the most fun to play with.
So what are you going to do?
Hold on.
I'm going to do what I know right because like I'm not
I don't want to I got an artifact for the warrior
character a follow-up question.
We haven't talked about it in a while.
Okay.
What is it?
How quickly did you give up on Path of Exile?
No, I didn't know I didn't know I didn't know I played
a lot of peewee because I was kind of preparing for
peewee to you board you stop.
Where did I stop?
I don't act to maybe act three.
I think it's great.
I okay once I figured out what was going on like,
okay, I get it now and I think this is fun.
I think waiting for peewee to is smart.
I think that's what you said to it's a play is apparently
it's going to be longer than people thought but trying
to get the area that I was named some areas in like
Act two or three because I know that you were doing
the bandits and you were confused about the bandits
last.
Yes.
Okay.
Was it right?
It was after that.
It's probably like maybe four or five hours of game
time after that.
So you're not doing a mage.
Oh my God, this coward.
I think about a mage and he crumbles and he folds.
Well, I got an artifact.
Okay, let's play and this is going to make me better.
Yeah, we're going to win.
We're going to lose in the first like three or four
rooms.
Then we're going to play that game that you liked.
Well, you also linked a game.
We're going to have to like flip a coin.
I think is I think we would have more fun in your in
your suggestion.
Okay, but I think I would like to do your suggestion.
We could one day we absolutely could.
All right.
Now we get it.
So let's go.
Oh, I get it.
Yeah.
What do you think of that zombies?
I genuinely do like you.
We I warmed up to it.
Okay.
I mean, it's just that we talked it like we were last
talking about this kind of stuff like two weeks ago
and that's where you were.
So I guess you just stopped.
Oh, I've been busy.
I've been pretty busy at the honest answers.
I've been pretty busy.
I accept.
All right, three damage go which one is attacking this
one here.
You're get all dude.
He's getting it.
Yeah, this guy fucking gets it.
The man's a cool guy yet.
Yeah, I get it.
This man's getting it.
I'm getting it.
You're getting it.
We're all getting it.
I let him hit me by accident.
Wish I could give you my two block and we don't have
to pause every time I play a card and be like so
grimace.
I mean unless you've got another grimace take I see
you unless there's more to the grimace.
I mean, I'm feeling kind of empty inside like what's
the next tick-tock trend like we're like grimace is
over.
It's over.
What now?
I don't know.
I need my dopamine.
No, you have one damage the monster monsters attack
leaves you with walk.
I think it's this one here.
Just I just need damage.
I didn't have any last time.
What does strain do?
If you hover over it, it'll explain it.
I don't know hover over the card with it.
Okay, select one of three rare and legendary artifacts.
I want that I'm liking where this is going for me.
Whoa, keep unspent mana points between turns.
That seems kind of unbelievably good.
I hope I don't you got ice cream.
I hope I don't piss off everybody watching because I'm
not going to use it.
Well, I didn't mean to click that.
That's okay.
You can re-select.
Yeah, we need like upgrades and shit.
Yeah ice cream.
What's your favorite ice cream?
What's your like favorite like top three vanilla?
I never used to be a vanilla or what I feel like I
just awoke and became correct that my whole life.
People were like chocolate chocolate chocolate and
I was like, yeah chocolate.
So I like chocolate and then I kind of just woke up
one day and I was like, you know, okay.
Who I'm going to kill this person right now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, do not shoot
anyone in the in the in the near.
Okay.
How come I don't have something like that?
I don't know why don't you be rid of this guy.
I just deleted my whole hand, but it's okay.
All right.
Okay.
So chocolate vanilla strawberry.
Let's go with like the basics.
Your vanilla is what you would say.
We're talking about just the three basics.
I feel like we talked about this before I whenever we
can recycle content is fine.
Okay, my my go-to grocery store treat when I'm feeling
a little bit sussy is when I go to the ice cream
section at the Hebs in Texas.
They've got all these crazy flavors like all these
weird combos and they're always really really really
really good.
And so I like just try a new one.
I'm a new I'm going to try a new one that was pretty
cool as the staple and then beyond vanilla.
It's like I'm going to get a little bit crazy today
and you kill that other guy on the left.
Here we go.
Look at that.
Okay, so but okay, but strawberry chocolate vanilla
you are now a vanilla ice cream enjoyer.
I would say of the three base flavors.
I think it's strawberry for me with a very important
very important caveat.
It has to be smooth strawberry.
It cannot have strawberry chunks in it.
No, it has to be smooth strawberry ice cream.
No strawberry chunks.
There was one of those crazy sussy ice creams.
I was talking about.
That was a strawberry ice cream with chunks of like
cheesecake in it.
Okay, though.
That's all right.
That's good.
That's fine.
That that was kind of you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah hot for a minute, but just regular strawberry
ice cream.
I don't want strawberry chunks in it my all-time favorite
If we're just talking get away from like the base
flavorings chocolate chip cookie dough is it just
a date nothing compares and nothing ever will compare
to that.
I just don't think I can I have to wonder if I've told
you my chocolate chip cookie dough story.
I don't know.
Did you puke or something?
Did you eat it and puke no is Easter one year they
got the they had these like Easter chocolate chip
cookie like eggs you like unravel the egg and you
it's like just all like that kind of like Oreo
chocolate chip cookie dough thing.
Okay, and then I ate some of them and I got really
sick like really really really sick and then like a
week later the next like in the morning my brother
knowing that I got sick from these Easter eggs and
it was a big deal to me.
He took all of the Oreos out of an entire like
double sleeve of Oreo put all of the double stuff
Oreo into a baseball and just took a big bite out
of it.
Oh you did tell this.
Yeah, that's kind of gross.
Yeah.
Okay.
My bad.
I was a double storyteller.
You can banish me now clean your weapon transform
and upgrade sacrificial lung into what doesn't
set.
What is it transforming into?
It gives you like three options or two or three
options.
Whoo.
I'm going to let's go.
New cards.
Yeah, new artifacts.
That's what oh that's next.
Okay, but what is your we're talking not just base
flavors.
What is your favorite ice cream that could have any
amount of kind of combinations in it, but now
we'll yeah, but we're talking a different tier of
ice cream now like what other ice creams do you
like that aren't just a base flavor.
I think that it was the way I said the strawberry
with the cheesecake in it.
That was some high quality ice cream.
I'm going to drop this over here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You just did something.
Yeah, I just killed everybody on your side.
We're winning this.
This is the run and then check this out.
Nah, I'll let you I'll let you be able to hit
something.
I'm doing it.
God damn it.
I spilled coffee fucking everywhere.
You're taking a lot of damage.
It's just everyone is everywhere and I don't
know what I don't know do about it.
Oh, I have to get it.
It's oh, it's I actually don't even know what to
do right now.
I wish I was there to help you pat you down.
It's all right.
I deserve it for making that.
I feel like this has happened the last like three
times.
It happens all the time all the time every time
because especially especially when I take a sip
of coffee.
I'm like who it's like I need to like relax.
I feel like two years from now.
You're going to be Hector from Breaking Bad with
a ding ding just rolling around waiting for help.
What it's you're progressing quickly.
Just wait till you get to be 37.
It's rough.
All right, man.
This hill is steep hold you right now for real almost
I'm almost dirty tweet.
I'm dirty doing a half as long as didn't get on
the ground.
I don't get on the ground.
There's a pool of coffee underneath my zero key
and that's over.
Say desk like from all of the times you've done this
and it's just going down.
They got I don't know what to do about this.
I don't let's keep gaming.
I think I'm all right.
If there's a pool of coffee underneath the zero on
my numpad and that's going to be a problem and this
is annoying because I like this keyboard.
My keyboard doesn't even have a numpad who uses
a numpad.
I don't want time you use your numpad.
I haven't I'm just saying that's where it is.
All right.
Well, it's no problem.
I hate looking at it though.
And then I'm low.
Now I have to go get a paper towel and turn it into
a little stick and then slide it under and let it
absorb and then pull it out.
And oh my God, what a fucking disaster.
Okay, what are we doing now?
Didn't get on the floor.
So it's our tip the keyboard.
No, it's going to get everywhere.
I'll take the keys out and clean it up later.
Yeah, I can't take all the keycaps off and clean my
keyboard right now.
We're in the middle of a game and I'm streaming with
my friend stir my hands are up and this is the one
time the one time I put like creamer in my coffee.
How is that relevant?
I am deeply like normally be like I Jeremy so bad
Jeremy bad.
Jerma you got to get some credit for like how much
extra stuff you're just dealing with.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you are you talking shit?
I know I'm saying you maybe it's time to ease up on
old German here because like I'm playing the game
and I'm doing well, but I don't I don't have coffee
in my I know like so like if I had all these extra
elements getting in the way who knows where I'd be
but here's the thing Holly just slipped a paper towel
under the door.
Hold on give me one second.
Yes.
Okay, I'm going to be good.
Thank you.
She even gave she gave me q-tips.
Wow.
This is perfect.
That's actually perfect.
I can get it under there and it's like soaking it
all up.
Look see nice.
That's actually a good idea.
Oh, let me this is a little extra here.
This is got 12.
All right.
I'll be ready in a second.
Hold on.
Yeah, no, you're you're thanks dude.
Appreciate the patience and everything.
Appreciate all your patience.
Just like my eyes like big day is really excited to play
Hell card my friend.
Yeah, this big day kind of a big day.
It's kind of a big day.
This was this is what my wife wanted for her birthday.
You're just kind of taking a mess.
I think I'm all right now.
I thought I just ended the stream by pressing like this
button.
That's as good as it's going to get for now.
You know this see this was a good choice turn-based
game.
Oh, I knocked one of the keys off.
Hey,
anybody missing a two isn't going to stink when coffee
dries.
It smells like fucking dog shit.
All right.
That's as good as it's going to get.
I just want to make sure it didn't actually get anywhere
where it's going to be actually like a real problem.
And I don't think that's the case.
I don't know.
You're always making fun of me when I tell you I take
caffeine pills.
Stop doing never never spilled them stop all over my
desk.
Stop doing that.
Stop it.
All right.
There we go.
Oh, but there's going to be a stain on my desk.
All right.
The rest can be done later.
Calm down Hector.
All right.
I'm good.
I took a lot of damage.
Yeah, you are you kill the close guy the near guy.
I can kill the near guy.
And I'm also going to kill the far away one over here
too high.
I got them.
We do got them.
My hands are very sticky and the reason why I say
this is because I usually just drink my coffee black
but I decided I'll put some hazelnut in it and then
I'll spill it all over myself.
That's smart.
I actually really like this card.
I'm going to get it again.
I've got omega aoe in the the near circle like one
when they're getting near I just kill everything.
I think we're going to be aware.
I think this is the one I'm going to heal me gets two
gemstones.
Yeah, I have that too.
That seems very good because it cost one.
Yeah.
So then I just did it for you.
Now you do it for me.
There we go.
We just both gained one gemstone for free.
You're going to heal use.
We got the heal.
I did feel like you need a heal.
I did heal.
That's oh, that's your health after healing.
It is you're at 26.
You're only forehead.
Oh, hey Trevor.
Can you play the original ET on Atari next year for my birthday?
I don't know.
Come on, do it.
You do it.
What else you got going on?
Are you going to do it?
No, I don't know that guy.
All right.
Let's actually pay attention because we got a walk that
we got that's a skill of Zerker.
I'll get that this needs to die 50 health 50 health on this
one 50 health on this one.
Okay.
What do you want to do about this?
I could I could kill I could kill this thing deals one damage.
Yeah, but I think is he a summoner he is giving strength
to all allies to every anything comes in the circle.
I can kill him.
Well, let's kill.
I'm going to kill the flying hog in the circle.
Then I'm going to give you want to give block to you and
then I'll take some block.
Does this carry over to each turn the block it does right?
No, it doesn't you've been playing this game the second
time.
We've done a run kind of a important thing to notice.
Don't you think at the start of the round your armor is
going to immediately come off a fuck you grimace.
All right, we can lay the fire.
We should be able to get rid of these.
Wait, can we I can get rid of like the half of the people
on my side.
Okay.
I can also get rid of those two as well.
It's going to hurt but I can get rid of them.
It's not going to hurt.
Yes, it is.
I know it's not.
Okay.
Now, what are you going to do?
I am going to I'm going to kill this guy and I'm going
to kill this guy.
I'm I still taking nine damage this guy.
Oh, there you go.
And then I can't do anything else with my other cards
are blocked.
Also remember you got that ice cream to keep your energy
between turns.
That's true.
You know, so like don't play too many cards there.
Bucco, I can get rid of these two in front of us.
You want to focus on the big guy.
I'm going to hold as I want to save my man.
Oh, I just got a diamond pickaxe.
Well, well, okay.
What is this?
Is he buffing himself next turn or something?
He's yeah, he's buffing.
It's growing in power.
I mean, I just smoked him.
You what are you doing?
I'm going to smoke this guy.
Smoked new card.
Your swords deal plus two damage.
I like that one.
This one's good, too, but I need to be able to get block
first, but it's definitely this one.
I'm feeling quite good about this one here.
I'm getting an artifact.
That's pretty good.
That's also really good.
I need healing.
I'm taking the blood.
Oh, yeah, get that blood.
I need healing very badly.
No, no.
What is that?
What what are you groaning about?
I'm just looking at cards.
We just moaning.
Oh, that's a good one.
Okay.
Oh, I want the upgrade.
This is a stir game.
Yeah, I could see that I could see this being a stir game.
I did recommend it is my choice a lot of enemies.
Okay, but they're all like stinky pigs.
Okay.
And we got one big guy.
I can get rid of two of these or three of these actually.
Okay.
I'm not going to do that anymore.
Hey, better not.
I can do this.
You're the big guy and not do anything else.
Talon arrow.
I'm feeling a nap creeping up a nap.
Take a nap then.
Oh, I thought you were going to take a nap.
I thought you were so bored.
You were going to know.
It's actually big because I could probably kill all these.
If you can I can they all did.
They all did.
I'm going to kill them all.
Okay.
What the fuck your curtain is cool.
Sorry, I apologize.
That's all I got.
I might as well use it to not take any damage.
No, you shouldn't because you have ice cream.
Oh, you were taking damage.
I was going to take that you were taking damage.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, you're great.
You're great.
That's great.
You're gravy.
You're gravy, dude.
We yeah, we can kill him.
We're so good at this game.
We're incredible.
They didn't make this game no one we were going to play it.
I don't like this one.
I'll take this one black or green olives.
Green olives for the oil black olives for the topping is my
answer.
What was the question on oil olives black or green olives
never either never really?
Yeah.
Oh, that's good.
In a near range before damage in a medium radius.
I actually like that one probably more than at all.
I like the ground breaker.
It's too man of though.
That's a lot.
We got a boss coming up here.
The skeletal zorker deal five damage.
If it kills the monster increase the damage of this card
by five.
Is that permanently or just for the round drive?
I don't know.
It's permanent.
Oh, a new artifact and we off sync that now I have to do
a boss like you just did the boss.
I think that's what's happening.
But how we need to hold on.
That's a lot of that is a lot of damage a lot and I only
have one lock.
I can even do if you see what you can kill before you block
because you got four block guys are dealing three damage
and I can only do I can only do five damage total to
somebody and I can't kill anything.
I guess I could kill and deal damage to things as well.
I can kill the part of this.
All right.
Hold on.
I kill.
Why did I not do more damage?
What the fuck happened?
I well tried.
Okay.
Well now that you killed the ghoul they curse us.
I know that first.
You waited what first you you cursed you you know,
you're good.
You're good.
You're fine.
A delusion card.
You're you're delusional how much you know, we've been
here before like Doki Doki Literature Club.
You just got out of a time machine from this chat in
like 2018.
What do you want me to look at?
This is bad.
I feel like like what there's a lot of shit.
Are they going trouble weird that me as the Ranger can
only kill all of the things if they're in close range.
This hurts a lot.
Okay, your sword steel plus two damage.
This would never happen.
If you were the mage.
Yeah, I mean, okay, but hold on a second.
How the fuck are we supposed to do this?
You got to kill these big ass zombies with the 9 HP.
Okay, they're not dealing all the damage and they got
buffed a lot deal.
I can deal two damage in a medium radius.
I can do five.
Okay, I can do five damage to this guy on the right.
I can't kill it though.
So it's like a waste of me using it.
There's nobody in a cone.
Wait, no, the only thing that's in a cone is this one.
How much damage can you do to the guy on the right?
Talk to me.
These big zombies the big ghoulies the green guys are
hitting both of us.
That's why we're both taking time about damage these
guys here.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, but so how much damage can you do to one of them
right now?
I can do I need to I can I can kill this one.
Wait.
No, I can't.
Can you hit that guy one more time?
I can but because I can kill that one if you could do
one more damage to it.
Okay, we still both take like 20 damage.
I did some major miscalculating.
Yeah, I think I'm dead.
You dead.
Oh, you are dead.
You're dead.
You die right now.
What?
Yeah, I don't I mean, I think it's that we didn't know
these things hit both of us as well.
Like you focused all your damage the first turn on the
thing that cursed you when these guys are double hitting
us and they're getting the damage this this arena is
crazy because he's buffing their damage every turn.
Oh shit.
Death is not the end.
Hold on.
Let's go get apparently they don't have to attack every
turn.
They just were.
Oh, I'm dead.
I guess I could kill.
Who's attacking you nine damage.
I could do five.
No, I could do eight.
You're dead.
Hold on.
I don't know.
I don't think I am.
You're dead there buster.
Are you sure?
I don't think I'm dead.
Kind of dead there buster.
I'm oh wide one fucking health shit.
All right.
This gets hard.
This game is pretty pretty intense.
I think you also got to consider when we're choosing
the vaults and stuff.
What other enemies were making but I'm confused at why
we had to fight two bosses in a row.
Do you think this game is cute?
I think it's good.
I think it's fun, but I am going to suggest we play
that other one which other one the one the one you
liked the one I liked.
Okay.
I feel like that's gonna be very fun.
We played like two hours.
I think we can pivot.
Okay.
No, I'm fine with that.
I like the concept.
I think it's really fun.
Yeah, I'm probably gonna play more of that.
This is a stir game if you by the way, if you want to
see more of hell card stir will be playing it tomorrow.
Okay, apparently I'm playing it tomorrow.
Are you planning on streaming tomorrow or no?
I have no I feel like the last couple of days in a row.
I have like scheduled things and I can't remember what
any of them are at the moment.
I get that I might not be streaming.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I get that though.
Seriously.
Okay.
What was it called bread and Fred bread and Fred?