Okay, so, uh, someone want to link me a good one? What's a good one? This website has a shitload
of them, don't they? There's a lot on here. I haven't even eaten at half of these places.
Well, maybe, actually, maybe I have. Let me get it on screen. Give me a minute. Less than that.
Good old browser. Please capture the window, if you would. That would be nice. Are you not going
to capture my window here? Come on. This is going to be hard to do. Okay. All right. Looks
pretty good. Let me get back on screen here. All right. So, what am I supposed to do about this,
right? I'm supposed to... I drag these up into the front. Fast food. Okay, well, I'm currently
getting a Blue Man Group ad. Let me, like, shrink the screen because it's going to distract me.
There we go. That's better. Oh, you piece of crap. What are you doing? What the fuck are you doing?
I don't care about Blue. I've already seen the Blue Man Group. All right. Here we go. Uh, so,
S is, like, the best I've ever had. D is, like, place sucks, or at least I think it sucks.
Welcome to two months ago. I'm the streamer that's doing it now. Here we go. Uh, Papa John's,
Papa John's is, I think, sucks. It's gross. But I can already, I can put that one out. White Castle
is not good at all. Um, can I be done? Can I just be done? Can all these just be,
like, who cares? Okay. Um, wait, why is there a soda on here? Disqualified.
Cashberg? Cashburger? Rashberg? Like, like, Rashburger. I don't know what this place is.
Disqualified. I don't know what Cashberg is. Sonic? Awful. Subway? Awful. All the way. No,
I can't put everything in D. Everything's gonna be it. Wait, hold on. I'm gonna, hold on,
I'm gonna leave it like this for now. I'm gonna piss off a lot of people with this,
but I don't think, I think Chipotle's not very good. Church's Chicken? I've never eaten it.
Okay. Quiznos was god tier. Absolute god tier. But they, they, like, didn't they close permanently?
I haven't seen a Quiznos in probably, like, fucking 10 years. They're closing them all up.
Keep it a B. Deserves to be there. I haven't eaten a Little Caesars pizza in a long time,
but I remember it was, like, not that great. Domino's? No. Long John Silver's? No. No. Dairy
Queen? You know, you're up at, you're up at C. No, you're at B. McDonald's? B. No. McDonald's? D. No.
No. Jersey Mike's overrated. Jimmy John's overrated. Mo's? Get that up on B tier.
Mo's is way better than Chipotle. I will say that a thousand times.
Elta? Denny's? Denny's can be up here. Five Guys? I don't know if I'd put Five Guys on,
on, like, the Quiznos tier. I might. Maybe. Popeyes? I've never, all right, should I take
off restaurants that I've never eaten before? This is kind of unfair. I've drank an A&W soda
before, isn't that, is that all right? I've never had cashburg before. I'm not even sure
I've ever eaten at Long John Silver's, so it has to come off. Make a new tier for uneaten.
How do I do that? Uh, just make it uneaten. Oh, shit. No, no, no, no. Any of these restaurants new?
Uh oh. Delete this one. There we go. Oh, fuck. What happened? What happened to D? I lost D.
No, no, no, no, no. Un, add, uneaten. Got it. It's there. D. What is going on? D. How do I add
another row? Add row below. There we go. Okay. Uneaten. That's fine. Okay. D. Let's put D where
it was before. What color was D before? Like, like cold? Like cold ass food? Yeah. All right.
Where have I, I gotta, I gotta, where have I not eaten? I've never had, I've never eaten Carl's
Jr. I've never, there's too many things on here. Wendy's goes up here for now. I don't, I've never,
I've never eaten at church. I don't know what okay is. I think this, no, that's, this is Del Taco.
I think I've had this once, but I don't even remember eating it. So I'm gonna, it's as if
I never had it in the first place. Chick-fil-A. I've eaten it a couple times. It was very good.
Is it better than Denny's? Yeah. HBO. Okay. Do I have an HBO prime subscription?
Oh, no, that's Firehouse Subs. Okay. I've had Firehouse Subs before. I would put it in here.
IHOP. I'm only putting IHOP down here because I think I've driven by an IHOP
more times than I've been inside of a McDonald's. That's how I determine if I'm ever, if I'm ever
gonna go there. You literally drive by it and you go, oh, there's an IHOP. Never gonna eat there.
Oh, we're on that, we're on the road again. Oh, oh, I'm hungry. No, I could really go for some
food right now. Something cheap and something that I got, a sit-down place. No, I don't think so.
That's, that's not that I've eaten there before, but I just, I, what is this? Is this Olive Garden?
I don't know what that is. Is it Olive Garden? I just see olive. Culver's. I don't know what that
is. Cash Burger, I've never eaten that. Krispy Kreme. The only experience I have at Krispy Kreme
is when my high school did a thing where you bought them and it was a huge deal and I remember
eating like two or three of them and thinking it was like just okay, I guess. Well, I, the last
time I had a Krispy Kreme donut, I was probably like 16, so I may as well have never even eaten.
Because I can't, I cannot reliably place it anywhere. I've only had it once like 15 years ago.
Dunkin' Donuts? Sucks, but it's, it's all right though. No, I wouldn't, what did I put, what did
I put Dunkin' Donuts up with Denny's? I definitely, no, I wouldn't do that. Krispy Kreme is S tier,
that's fine, but I've never played it before. I had, I've never played that game.
Shits? This place called Sheets? I don't think I want to eat at the place called Shits.
Is that what that place is actually called? It's called Shits. No, it's not. I've never had it. I
don't know. Is it fictional? People are going to be mad about this one too. In-N-Out Burger!
We're all in an, oh, I can't wait to see where he puts In-N-Out. It's going to be like fucking up on
A. It's all right, settle down. It's okay. It's just a hamburger restaurant. Don't worry if it's,
it's going to be fine. Relax. They don't even fucking compare. Is it better than McDonald's?
No, and I have to go through these and I have to do each one in an individual subcategory,
right? So this could be like an A plus down to like an A minus, right? I'll take care of this.
No, I know. I just got to get everything in the right mind zone here. I have not eaten here.
I've eaten here, I think, once. Let me remember. It was definitely better than
like firehouse subs. I think that's accurate. This place only does chicken, right? This is like the
chicken place. Fuck. I had second thoughts about something here. Hold on. You have to add an F
category. Do I really have to have an F? No, having an F category is just, this is where I put places
to get people to unsubscribe the channel. Burger King. Oh, damn. Okay. Hold on a minute. Burger
King goes up here. Does it though? Panda Express sucks. Okay. That's probably the, I don't know
if there's any others that are going to be in. I've been to like four Panda Expresses and each
time it has been, it has been awful. I mean, it's been, I'm not, I'm not saying this as like to be
like the dick or mean or anything. It's been awful every time. It really has. When you're eating
food and the only thing that you can think of is, yeah, I mean, it's, I wouldn't order this again,
but it's, it's, it's edible. It's not, it's edible. Yeah. So is a fucking shoe if you chop it up.
Hold on though. I'm about to bring a lot of people back into, into my corner here.
I don't get it. In fact, I'm doing this. I don't, I'm not a big fan of the way the Starbucks coffee
tastes. I don't really, it's, it's coffee. It's all right. But I don't know if it's like, look,
here's the thing about Dunkin Donuts versus Starbucks. Dunkin Donuts, they're going to screw
your order up all the time. And sometimes you're going to drink out of the cup and you're going to
like get like a burning taste in your mouth and you're going to go like, but it's like three and
a half dollars less expensive than this one. And if you're going to drink this one, you may as well
just go to like the next level up of coffee. Now that's not to say that if you, I mean, there's a
Starbucks everywhere. I drink Starbucks fucking all the time. If there's a Starbucks in the corner,
it's like, all right, well, I'm just going to get a coffee. I'm not saying don't ever, I'm just saying
the differences that it's not that it's not that big of a deal. If you drink Dunkin Donuts over
Starbucks, one of them's quick and fast and cheap. The other one is
fast and I don't know what's the word I'm looking for.
Fast and expensive. They have some good stuff at Starbucks though. Somebody said the refreshers.
Those things are really good. No, but I would rather drink it like another coffee shop than
Starbucks. Okay. Tim Hortons, never had it. Sorry. Sorry to all the Canadians. I've never had it
before. Arby's. Now here's a tough one because Arby's, depending on the day, Arby's is either a
B or an F. I've gone to Arby's before and been like, wow, that was like really delicious.
And I've been there the other half of the time and it was like unedible. I want to throw this
in the trash. So I don't know where to put it. Probably down here. KFC, KFC can go up here.
KFC is just like Kane's 0.4. You know what I mean? Buffalo Wild Wings? My D is going to be
full of stuff. Fatburger. Have I had Fatburger? Maybe once or twice. Maybe. Is it enough to rate
it? I had to change my opinion on that. How is Taco Bell an A? It just is. Pizza Hut. Whoa, whoa,
what? What? What? Everyone's freaking out. The stuffed crust pizza at Pizza Hut. That's my
level here. Is the stuffed crust pizza at Pizza Hut better than anything on the Chipotle menu?
Yes. Is the stuffed crust pizza from Pizza Hut better than anything on the McDonald's menu?
Yes. Better than anything on Jersey Mike's menu? Yes. Better than anything on Jimmy John's menu?
Yes. Better than anything on that menu? Yes. Actually, no. All right, I got it. Yeah,
like the patty melt from Denny's is just better than the stuffed crust pizza at Pizza Hut.
Fuck! Better than In-N-Out though, for sure. Do I have to level? I might have to level up Denny's.
You don't have any pizza places above a C. It's because most of the fucking pizza chain places
suck. No, Denny's is going to be a high C, I think. Let's move it over here. Look, I really
don't want to be like a pizza elitist or a dick or anything, but if you live in an area that has,
look, pizza places, think about if you just type into your phone or like into Google or whatever,
just type in pizza place or pizza nearby, there's more pizza places than there are Starbuckses.
And I'm not talking about like Pizza Hut. I'm talking about like, like Sal's Pizza,
like Pizzeria Regina, like there's so many pizza places that are better than Pizza Hut. There are
so many pizza places that exist that are not chain pizza restaurants, why would you ever eat
at one of the chains? If you live in a city, if you don't have that option, then I completely
understand. Yeah. But if there is another pizza place that's not Domino's, it's probably going
to be better than Domino's. Eat family pizza. That's right. Chain pizza survives off quantity,
not quality. Yeah. And look, Pizza Hut's out here at C. Domino's is, I just don't like Domino's. I
really don't. I like Pizza Hut. I would choose Pizza Hut over a lot of restaurants, like actual
pizza restaurants. I would, by that logic, everything on this list should be lower than
B with all local restaurants at an A or a B. Yeah, I gotta love my local restaurant up here,
Taco Bell. All right, let's keep going. Panera Bread is a C. Panera Bread,
once you eat Panera Bread like three times, the, oh wow, a cheddar broccoli soup and a bread bowl,
like you don't give a shit anymore. You don't, it doesn't matter anymore. It's just like a
soup and a bowl. If it's your first time eating a Panera Bread, it's probably up here. If it's your
fifth time eating a Panera Bread, it's probably like over here. It's not, it loses its flair.
It's still all right though. I still, it's not, it's still good. I don't know what this is.
What is that? I don't know. Popeye's Chicken. Unfortunately, everybody, I have never eaten it.
I've not had it one time. Oh, hold on, I'm losing the, Zaxby's? Never had it. Boston Market,
I think I've had it twice. Maybe not even, and this was like 20 years ago. So the recipe
definitely changed. Fat Burger. I don't remember. I like, it's probably, no, it was all right.
Jack in the Box is, if you're going to go to Jack in the Box, just go to McDonald's.
I've had it a couple of times and it's been like cold and gross and awful. Same thing with
Sonic. Where's Sonic? Make sure Sonic's at F. If it's, my reasoning for Sonic being an F
is because I've had it a few times and every single fucking time it was cold. It took like
30 minutes to come out and was not very good. That's just the way it was. I'm, I'm, I've,
I've eaten the food there. I know Sonic does a bunch of those, he's like weird,
like frat, strawberry cheesecake, banana lime cream drinks that I've never, I've never had one.
No, I'm not a fan. It's a meme restaurant? But what about those funny commercial guys?
Oh yeah, those, there are the two funny commercial guys. All right, so Wawa. I think I've had Wawa
before. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, don't, I'm not gonna look. Is
Wawa like a bowl place where you make your own bowl? Is it like, kind of Asian fusion? It is,
right? Okay, well then I don't think I've ever had it. Steak and Shake. I've had this a few times,
but not enough to like, to make, this is the thing, there's too many things here.
I remember being all right. It was, I remember being at like, okay.
Wada Burger. There's too many like burger places. I've had too many hamburgers.
I don't remember. I think I've had it once. And every one of these places that I've had one time
was just, oh, okay, it's pretty, it's good. But is that like, oh, S tier? No, I don't know, but I'd
see. What was this one? Somebody gave a lot of money. Hold on. KXZ just gave another $50. Thank
you, KXZ. Thank you. 50 bucks disgusting medieval peasant food in local pizza places, A tier or
riot. This is fast food though. We got to at least be fair, but thank you for the fucking 50 bucks.
Why do I have KFC over Wada Burger? Well, I haven't done my complete list yet.
Hey, when am I supposed to get a drink? Little Caesars. It's probably down here. Long John
Silver's. I don't have never hit it. I don't know what this is. Never eaten it. I thought that was
Starbucks too. The rest of these, I don't think I've had at all. Wing Stop. I don't, I've never had
this. What's Ojan? Ojan? I've never had it. What's, I don't know what that is. I don't think I've had
any of these. Look, I don't eat that much fast food. I only eat the fucking S tier ones.
Checkers. No, I've never had it. Checkers. Half of these restaurants are not even physically
available to me my whole life. How am I supposed to go to a Tim Hortons when you have to live in
Canada to drink it? I live in the United States of America. There's no Tim Hortons in America.
There's, there's one in New York. Oh shit. I've gotta get on that plane and go to New York to
drink Tim Hortons. This is what I've eaten. Let me, let me, let me make sure. And I'm gonna put the
uneaten ones in their own category. Places where I probably never will eat. The bottom is places I
will never eat. Places up top is like, you know what? I'll check it out. Might sound like pretty
good to me. Remember, it's in line. So like one, two, this is top to bottom. Cashberg sounds
interesting. I don't, I don't want churches. All right. I'm going to put this up here because
I feel like I've had it. And I remember it, my, my walked by and said, it looked like I want to go
in that place. I don't know. I'm not going to eat here. I don't know anything about it.
Krispy Kreme. But I, would I actually go into a Krispy Kreme donut to buy Krispy Kremes? I feel
like I would only want that if somebody handed it to me and said, Hey, this is a Krispy Kreme donut.
Do you want one? Sure. I guess I'll have one. I'm not eating at shits. No, I would try shits.
Yeah. Just cause it would be like, Oh yeah. I would eat shits. Carl's Jr. No, I don't,
I'm not going to eat. Sorry. I'm not going to eat at Emote Arby's. Um, I think that's all right.
I would eat at this place. I, I, you know, I want, I want Popeyes. I'll try it. That's the next place
I'm going to eat. That's, I don't know if that is, is, is Popeyes even on the west coast? Is it like
even in Las Vegas? Is there one in Las Vegas? I will go to it. Wait, that's, that's Kudobo. That's
Kudobo. Oh, Kudobo is good. All right. Let's put this up here. I didn't know what that was. That's
okay. That's no, that's pretty good. I've had it before. It's good. I've had it. Yeah. All right.
Let's see. What's the worst? That's accurate. Where's Chipotle? Where's Chipotle? Where's Chipotle?
And why is it not down here at D? Where is Chipotle? Oh, it's the first seat. Get out of there.
No, it does not belong there. All right. Let's go, but let's go worst to best here. So definitely
Pan, I just, Pan Express is always, it's so hit or miss. And usually it's a swing and a miss every
time. It just, I'm sorry. It just is. Out of all these restaurants that I think are all right,
that I would eat at, which one would I want to eat at the most or drink at the most?
Holy shit. I don't know if I can do this. Like I'm not going back to Arby's.
You know what I mean? Fool me once. Shame on me. Fool me twice. You can't get fooled again.
Whatever he said, that funny George Bush thing. Um, I don't, I really, really don't like Domino's.
I don't, I think it's bad. Buffalo Wild Wings is all right. They only do one thing that's worth
eating there though. But it is in the title, but sometimes they're not, but I drive by, I hop and
I go, Oh no. It's not Papa John's. Papa John's is all the way at the bottom. This Papa John's just
tastes like a DiGiorno pizza that you made in your own house. Like you do like put the DiGiorno in the
oven and it came out and it was a Papa John's pizza. That's what it tastes like. I don't, I
don't want a like delivery DiGiorno. I want a delivery pizza. Why the fuck is there a Papa John
emote? What? It's not delivery. I know. It's not delivery. No, this is delivery. No, Papa John's,
you bite into the pizza and you take a big bite and every topping and all the cheese and everything
just comes off. That's why. Oh, was this a mushroom, onions and peppers pizza? Let me take a bite of
that. Oh, oops. I'll take my fucking like double dare flag that I'm left with. No, I'm sorry. I've
made my decision. I would drink an A&W root beer right now. In fact, you know what? Let's get this
up here. Just because I just saw that and I was like I want a fresh fucking frosty bug of A&W
that goes up to the level because of that. I don't know why. I just thought this said free wi-fi.
Free wi-fi at Buffalo Wi-Fi Wings? What? That's, that's different. That's not the, that's not
the name of the restaurant. Buffalo Wi-Fi Wings. You get free fucking wi-fi. This is accurate now.
I mean White Castle has the, if I like, if I drove by one of these D restaurants. All right. Ooh,
they made a movie about this. This is, he's a cartoon. Like the other thing is based on
television and fucking movies and video games. This is a cartoon. Buffalo, this is my like,
this is my sign. The Ox. And they made a funny movie about this. All right, there you go.
I got it. That looks good, right? Perfect. Little Caesars is good for the price. Don't
complain about a $5 pizza. Yeah, but, but a $5 pizza is, is not that good. I'm not, I'm just,
this is not about price. This is about like eating and like how much I want to eat there.
But it's $5. Right. But that's, it's not down here. This is, so this is almost a C,
this is almost a D+, C-. To me, this is about like what I would want to eat. Not about like,
oh, hey. I mean, sometimes it's about like spending less money. But I mean, look,
I got like Pizza Hut up here. I got like Wendy's at B tier. It's about, it's not about the cost.
Taco Bell is A for me. It's like a dollar for a taco here. Best thing, oh, I can tell you right
now. And you're solidifying the reason why it's up here. Cheesy gordita crunch with a Doritos,
nacho Doritos taco shell is the reason. If that wasn't on the menu, this is down here.
I swear to fucking God, that menu item brings this from an F to an A. That's the worst menu item.
You and I got some beef now. We have a problem. That's like the best, that's my favorite thing
to ever eat at a fast food restaurant. It's the best thing. It's the fucking best thing in the
world. It's, I want one right now. Cheesy gordita crunch. I will write it down. I'll use my one chat
message for 30 minutes. I'll make sure you get it. Don't do that though. Tweet it out. No,
I can't tweet out food stuff anymore because people think I'm like a monster. It's fucking so
good. All right, we're getting ahead of ourselves here. If I were to do the IHOP no drive through,
I would stop, I would stop the car and I would turn in if it was a little Caesar's.
That would, it's what would happen. Where's D'Angelo's? Now that's a really good question
because D'Angelo's would be up here. Can I just pretend that this is D'Angelo's?
Quiznos doesn't exist anymore. Where's Papa Gino's? Papa Gino's in D'Angelo's. Papa Gino's,
I mean it's like a New England thing, but Papa Gino's is some of the best chain pizza I've ever
had. Papa Gino's is up here or here. Papa Gino's is the best Papa in regards to pizza places.
That's a New England place, yeah. But that's not fair. In-N-Out's a fucking west coast thing. Why
is it on here and not Papa Gino's? D'Angelo's, okay, I'm gonna pretend this is D'Angelo's.
If it's Quiznos, it can stay there, but I'm gonna pretend it's D'Angelo's. I might have to make some
changes though. All right, so we got, this is important because this is like places that,
remember, these, it's not about, not Jersey Mike's is so much better than it. No, no, no, no, no,
but if I'm not gonna stop at, for Jersey Mike's, I'm not gonna like, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If I see those, those golden arches, you might get me to stop because of how hungry I am. I'll
drive by and I'll get just the waft of the dumpster as I'm going through and it'll be really disgusting
and you'll get that like wet trash smell while you're in the drive-through and you're like, oh,
and then you keep going and you realize the reward for your dedication. Two plain McChickens with
mayo and lettuce. Big Mac meal. You can't beat it. It's unbeatable. Can I be honest with you?
Can I be honest with you, right? These three restaurants are the same restaurant.
I don't have, they're the same place. That's why they're together. When I think of like
Whataburger, if I was inside of a steak and shake and you told me it was a Whataburger,
but the sign said fat burger, I'd be like, this is the, this is the same thing. I, this,
this is just a cheeseburger. When you're talking about Shake Shack though, that's how you level
up. We get it. You spin Shake Shack doesn't sponsor anybody. You think Shake Shack needs
to sponsor somebody? The reason why Taco Bell probably sponsors people is because no, no,
nevermind. All right, slow down. These two, they even have the same name. Jimmy John's, Jersey
Mike's. Jersey Jim's like, they're the same fucking restaurant to me. Jim Jersey, Jim John's
Sub Sandwich Mike. Mike, Jim. It's just two, it's like name and then place. Jim, Mike, Jersey,
John. Yeah, fuck that. I feel like these are rivals. These are guys that are across the street from
each other that like prank each other. This is, this is like the, the, the Bob's Burgers made an
entire like storyline about this and it's real. This is just the other restaurant. This is like
the, but no, this is way worse than that because this is the same, the same name. Sandwich Shop
sitcom. Yeah. All right. I'm getting ahead of myself here. That's not fair. Chipotle's at the
very bottom. I'm sorry. It has to go there. I don't like that place and I'm not going to eat there.
I'm not going to stop there. I'm not going to stop at Chipotle. Chipotle is not that, it's,
I'm not going to eat there. They're everywhere. It's next to Starbucks because there's as many
Chipotle's as there are Starbucks and they're usually right in the same fucking mall,
connected at the wall together. But which would I rather go in? I can't, I can't have it up at C.
I understand what, why this would be here. I've had, you know, it's funny. I've had,
I've had one of these, but they're both the same restaurant to me. So I don't know which one it was.
I have no fucking idea. It was a sandwich place and it had somebody's name in it.
It was just, and the signs, they use the same red letters. It's just, I can't have it. I'm sorry.
Why is KFC a C? We're getting there. Hold on. I got to make sure that this is correct.
Denny's is way too high. McDonald's and Denny's are up a little too high, I think.
He just put Burger King in front of In-N-Out. Kim loves In-N-Out. What happened?
Bro, you just, what, what, what was it? Was it loud? Let me listen to it.
Show it to me. What was it? Was it loud noise? Was it that, was it that loud? I'm sorry. I didn't
think it was that loud. Where are my headphones? Was it fucking loud? I just scared the shit out
of your cat. He just put Burger King in front of In-N-Out. It wasn't that loud. Okay, yeah, it was.
It was, it was very loud. I just didn't have my volume turned up. Could you believe what he
fucking did? Did, I saw it. Did you? Wait, what's going on here? Oh, we're fine. But I was saying,
Kim loves In-N-Out. I think, me not so much. I think it's all right. It's definitely better
than Burger King. That's a joke. I'm kidding around. Kim said my list is wrong. My list is not done.
I'm not even close. So hold all criticisms until after it's done. Everybody's talking all this
smack about my list and they have not. What am I doing? Okay. Um, all right. Instinct. Here we go.
Yeah. What did Kim say? Where's Kim's cooking? I can't like put, that's not a fast food restaurant.
Kim making food is not a fast food restaurant. That's not like going driving up to Burger King.
Are you saying that she's her, she's too slow? No. Kim is not a restaurant. He hates it. I
haven't even tasted it. I didn't even taste it. I'm talking about like today. No, whatever.
Cooking's very good. Okay. Let's get back here. This is done. This is done. I feel like I'm playing
chess. My stream is frozen because I'm just sitting here. Okay. C is done. Now importantly,
this is like, I might have to make a few changes here. They give me the fries in the bag and the
fries soak at the bottom of the bag and it gets all oily and shit. They just, oh, I want to fry.
Here you go. Look, I want French fries. I don't want to eat eight potatoes. I don't like those.
I don't like the fries. I don't, I like the shitty plastic fries. I like the ones that are
like dyed yellow, wicked thin shoestring and crispy. I don't like the, I don't like the potato
like you bite into it and it's like eating a baked potato. No, I'm not a big fan.
They look, but I don't like potato wedge type fries. I like the fake gross shitty ones and I
know that that's wrong. I know that this is a wrong opinion, but okay. That's fine. It's also up at B
tier, which means it's really good. So I don't know what the problem is. This is going to be hard.
I've had these both the same amount of times and I thought they were both very good.
They got a sauce. The sauce is better. They got, they have a sauce here. That's better.
Nothing beats Moe's in this list. I just don't remember eating these. I've never had them.
Like I've had them once and I thought they were good, but they were the same burger.
I'm trying to teleport my brain and my memory back to when I ate Whataburger and it was just
the same thing I did when I ate the other, when I ate it steak and shake. It was just
I was sitting in the same chair with the same burger and the same flavor. I don't have any
other memories. I don't have memories for this. They're all the same. I'm looking through like
the VR goggles of like the burger just going like in, you know, that was his mouth. I don't
have any other memories. I don't think Five Guys is better though. It's juicier. One of these was
juicier. I don't remember which one. One of them, one of these was juicier than Five Guys. Cheese
was melted perfectly at one of these places and I don't remember which one it was.
Somebody just came in and said in and out C tier. What the fuck? You know, it's only up there.
It's up a full letter grade because of like it's on stream. You know what I mean? Like
that's like the, that's like the streamer tax here is no, I don't know. It's pretty good, man.
It's a pretty cool, pretty awesome place. See in my mind it's over here, but I can't say that. I
have to say that it's like, okay, I have to say it's good enough. The streamer tax. It's like the
I'm on camera tax. I'm fucking kidding. In and out is here's the thing I don't like about in and out
and we're going to talk. We're going to dial the shit talk up to 11. Anytime you go to in and out
and the burgers are fine. Okay. What do I want to order it in and out? Oh, no, you're doing it wrong.
Don't order anything off this menu. What, what are you talking about? Why? Well, because there's
like 30 fucking secret things to order and they're all way better than the stuff on the menu. Why
don't you just fucking put it on the menu? Oh, uh, animal fries. See what they do is they open up a
thing of thousand Island dressing and they dump it on your fries and they add like bacon bits to
it right out of the cabinet. Fucking cool. All right. That's a straw man. These boys are like
tomato slices. What do they do? They take like tomato slices in like thousand Island dressing
and then you like pick up the fries and it's like, did you just time? I didn't time out Kim.
Wait, why did Kim get banned? Wait, what happened? Why did that happen? I'm just
talking. I'm just taking the piss in and out is fine, but why does it have to be this like
trendy secret menu thing? Just put it on the menu. They have like three or four different burgers
that you can order and none. It's just, it's not a secret. Look, it's not a secret when everybody
knows it. Oh, don't tell anybody about those animal fries that every single fucking customer
orders. Every single customer orders these. Now tell anybody about that secret. It's a secret menu.
Don't tell anybody about those animal style fries. Word might get out. All right. We spent
a lot of time on in and out, but I got a double double animal style is good, but not worth the
15 minute wait. Oh God mute mute the microphone quick. She brought a dog. You want to say hi to
Otto? Hello, Otto. You can't time me out in real life. I didn't even time you out. Okay,
but I don't want to be raised my voice in front of Otto. So what would you change on this? This
entire list is wrong. How, why is this wrong? Look, I don't know. First of all, what would you replace?
Okay, you get one thing to replace. Which one is it? See, I told you, I don't want to raise my voice
in front of Otto. Show dog. No, we only get to see Otto for 10 seconds. All right, so what would you
change? For a second, I thought you just had a Jersey Mike's t-shirt on and I was like, what the
fuck are you thinking? Jersey Mike's. Okay, first of all, why is White Castle there? Put it like
F. White Castle is like a joke restaurant though. White Castle is like a, I thought it said Jersey
Mike's. All right, White Castle has a movie behind it though. It does? Wait, it does?
Harold and the two guys go to White Castle. Oh, I've never watched Harold and Kumar.
Nothing. That's the only reason why it's up here. Otherwise it would be an app.
I'm not going to read that. All right, so we got, look, way would you put In-N-Out on this list?
In-N-Out is fucking better than Panera Bread. Is it though? I mean, it's better than
banana bread and also Panera Bread. Did you say it's better than banana bread?
All right, yeah. Okay, I'll agree. In-N-Out is better than banana bread, but that's not up here.
That's not an option. It's better than Panera. Have you ever even had Firehouse Sub? Have you
ever had a bread bowl soup from Panera? It's better than, you're telling me that an In-N-Out
burger is better than a bread bowl cheddar broccoli soup from In-N-Out, I mean from Panera. Okay,
but like it's all bagged soup. What do you think they get this from?
They think the cow comes in and they're like, oh yeah, bring it in.
No, they all come out of a fucking bag. Otto, what's your favorite restaurant?
Oh, that was so cute that he just said that on camera. I mean, also like why is Taco Bell
like on, wait, okay, so there's an S tier which is Shake Shack and I know that that's true for you.
Same. But like why is, why is Taco Bell an A-list fast food restaurant?
Why wouldn't it be? It's got the cheesy gordita crunch with the nachos,
Doritos, Locos, Taco Bell. Have I ever had a cheesy gordita crunch? Have I ever had that?
I've never had, she's never had the cheesy gordita crunch from Taco Bell and she's wanting to talk
about why it's an A tier. Just saying is, you know, you gotta have, you gotta have a little bit of,
you gotta have some stuff to eat first before you, I mean, and that's why I have the uneaten side.
I mean, I've only ever had from Taco Bell, I mean, we had it a couple of nights ago,
but I ordered the same thing every single time we were going there.
Because Taco Bell is A tier and you find the thing you like at Taco Bell
and you eat it every time. That's giving it a high order. I don't know. That's not, this is not correct.
Is this worth the couch tonight? We're talking about fast food restaurants is not like
oh yeah, I'm on the couch tonight guys. I can't believe I liked the cheesy
gordita crunch better than In-N-Out. Where is my cooking on this list?
Your cooking is all the way up here, up at S, S plus. Okay, but is it better than Shake Shack?
If I could put another category up here that said S plus, I would and it'd be Kim's fucking perfect
cooking. But no, but that would be an insult to your cooking because this is a fast food list
and that would mean that your food would be like in the same realm as a fast food restaurant
and it's not. Is it home cooked? Wait, you don't like Sonic? Wait, you don't like Sonic?
Sonic sucks. How many times have you eaten at Sonic? I'm from the East Coast.
I used to eat Sonic all the time. That's not a quantifiable number of things. Dozens of times.
Okay, so I've had Sonic twice, so it was not good. Both times I had it, it was not very good.
It was very, it was very cold. It was, I got, I got cheesy tater tots and it was, they,
it's almost like they, there was cheesy water tots, what I would have called it. That's a
cheesy water tots. It's like the funny like laugh out loud term that I'm going to use. Wait,
you've never had Popeyes before? No. Oh, so fucking good. That's what I'm saying.
Worst item on the menu is the cheesy tots. Well, they're, that's like in every commercial,
they're like falling down. There's like cheese going all over the place that you didn't get the
chili cheese tots. No, I don't want diarrhea. I'm not going to put, adding, guys, adding chili
to a fast food menu item is giving you like plus 60% chance for diarrhea. Do you get a spicy bum
from chili? Now we're going to cut the mic. Wait, you've never had this before? Why? Why? Nope.
We're back. Okay. So, uh. Wait, you've never had, wait, what is this? What is this right here?
Cash. What is, I don't know what it is. Cashberg. Look, can you see? It looks like Ashburg.
I thought it. From what I can see. It's Smashburger. Oh, the restaurant that we saw. Oh,
Smashburger. It's going up here. We've never even had it before. Wait, the restaurant that we saw
in front of them. Yeah, we've seen it before. Yeah, we've seen it before. We've seen it. I've
driven by it like three times. This, was there one in Boston? No, I think there's one in LA though.
We might have seen it when we were there at first. Everything is a burger. You've never had Carl's
Jr. either? No. I've had Carl's Jr. once. No, this is, look, look, look. You gotta look. This is all,
this is all the uneaten category. So why is Subway on this list? It's F. Did you see the grade?
That's an F. That means it's the worst thing on this list. And that's Panda Palace, right?
This? What is that place? That's Panda Express. Panda Express. It doesn't matter. It's not,
I don't like it. What's this person? What's this little guy right here? That's Caesar.
Oh, that's F. He conquered Rome. And what do you mean F? Caesar's pizza? Why would it be,
this is not F? Have you had it before? Yeah. I've brought an entire box home.
Wait, have you eaten this before? I didn't eat it, but I brought it home and Alan ate it.
Have I eaten this? I think you might have. What did I say? I don't know. We threw it in the garbage
the next day, so I mean. All right. So, all right. All right. So that's little Caesar's apparently.
All right. Can I, can I finish, can I finish my list? No, because it's wrong.
Caesar's is, Caesar's is worse than Panda, Panda Land. Why, why can I not think, I can't get the
name of this place in my brain? Panda Express. Right. Wow. All right. Do we have any coffee
downstairs? What time is it? It's 10 o'clock. I shouldn't be asking for coffee. Do you want some?
All right. I'm going to get a coffee. Okay. Pot of coffee is going on. Where's mine? Oh,
fuck. Okay. There we go. What was that like frame? So I think I have confirmed that was not little
Caesar's. That was a local place. It's going back up. I actually remember the name of the place.
That's kind of a similar name. Why is little, I, I was misled. I have not had it before. I've had it
like twice. I've won it though. I've won it. Then it's uneaten. No, but I have eaten it though.
Back in Massachusetts, I've had it like a bunch, at least twice. What's this, what was this emote?
I'm going to finish my list. Okay. It looks good. It's done. This is my emote list. Wait,
just got here. What the fuck is this? What's, what's wrong with this? That's it. That's done.
Perfect. I was fighting with that the whole time. So let's get this straight. Panda Panda Panda.
Is it Panda Express? Panda Express is the worst restaurant I've ever been to on this list.
Restaurant. No, it's not better. Is it better than Subway? It might be. No,
it's worse than Pizza Hut. Yeah, by about two letter grades. Is it worse than McDonald's? Yeah.
I mean, I've had better experiences from McDonald's. Fuck. Is it? Domstick with my list.
All right. That's good. Any other lists to do? What is this? What is this? File maker,
file maker, file maker. What is this? Wait, why is there a, that's, I think, okay. I thought that
said FileMaker.com. Okay. This is my emotes. I have to write my emotes. Don't make me do this.
Actually, this is going to be pretty easy. Okay. Copy that link. Let's go here and it should just
go, right? Let's go. Okay. I'm just preliminarily getting them out here. A, B, C, D, A, B, C, D.
We need a F tier. No, there's no, there are, there are no F tier emotes. I'm going to say,
I would put, how did you make this? I'm actively right now going through the process that I said
I wanted to go through a long time ago. And that was, I want to go for what emotes I think are the
better ones and which ones are the worst ones. So thank you for, let, let's do it. We're doing
it on stream. All right. Can't, you can't touch those two. This is preliminarily. I like the
top F of the Jupiter better than the bottom half. Let me think. Let me think. Let me think. Let me
think. All right. Hold on. That's correct. I don't need to do any changing here. I would,
I would probably say, look, just because it's used the most doesn't mean I think it is the best.
Still up there. I really do. I kind of like, I like the one guy where it is.
What do I think is the board? Which one is so close to being dropped? The TV has no purpose.
It just doesn't. This, this is no purpose for the TV. Honestly, I've, I like mustard more than I like.
Yeah. Can I, can anybody even do that emote? Anybody here even have the capability to do
that emote? Can I even do that emote? Oh yeah. Speaking of subscription emotes,
Tingy just came in with 10 community subs. Thank you, Tingy. Ten. Count them. Ten community subs
on top of the fucking hundreds at this point, I think. Thank you, Tingy. That's a shitload
of fucking money and I'm surprised that you want to give me that kind of support. Thank you. That
means a lot. There are people that, there are people that can do that in the chat. I'm, I'm,
I'm comfortable with this. Find out whoever did that and ban them. I think, I like this. I don't
do very much. I already know all of my children here. I mean, I have to do this. This has to be
complete. Otherwise it'll, it'll freak me the fuck out. I think that's good. That's, that's pretty
good S and A tier here. Like, I mean, these are, these one, two, three, four, five, six, this,
that's a pretty good, that's pretty good. I would probably go like this though, like that. I think
that's perfect the way it is. I've judged, this is fun to do. I think I'm going to do this again.
Did it really take me an hour to do that McDonald's tier thing? Nobody uses Germapop. That doesn't
mean it's not the best emote on the channel. What tier, what tier would a, a stream tier?
What do you mean? He likes his own face. No, that's up there because that's the first emote I ever
had. And I still think it's the best one. This one, just by sheer volume, that's probably the
most used emote in the whole channel. And I think it's, I think I did a pretty good job on that.
I did a close-up of my face and that's it. Now it's perfect. Now it is. No, now it is. No, it's not.
Now it's perfect. About touching anymore. No, it's perfect the way it is. Perfect the way it is.
Don't need to do anything else. All right, guys. I think that's time to go. I'll see you tomorrow.
Me and Styr are going to do something tomorrow afternoon. I don't know what the hell it is,
but we're going to do something. Some type of multiplayer game. And if not, then look,
we're going to have to figure something out because we both agreed. Hey, let's do something. Let's do
a vid, a stream together. That'd be fun. So something's going to happen tomorrow between
3 and 4 p.m. Pacific time. Thanks for watching. I'll get out of the way now. There's your final
list there. And that's a nice place to call it, I think. I think so. That was Sam and Max Season 3,
Episode 1. We will return to that probably next week because tomorrow is me and Styr doing
something. And then a few days later we'll probably do, I have a couple of ideas.
So you will see Episode 2 sooner than you think. I'm scrolling down the list of bits right now,
and there are a shitload. There are a ton of bits. There are hundreds and hundreds of them.
All trying to bring the score down. Minus two. Oh, there's so many here.
Hahaha. Holy shit. The Google search results for cheesy godita crunch have increased by 300%
in the last hour. Good. I hope you eat one. But let's go back to earlier. Thank you for
joining me on this stream. And if you take it off, maybe we'll see you tomorrow. If not,
we'll see you again soon, maybe. So we had $2.50 from Zake. Thank you, Zake. Thanks for buying food
for my family every day ever since our dad left. You're a good man. I just don't think that eating
only cheesy Cheetos for five months straight is very healthy. Thank you for the $2.50. Appreciate it.
Thank you to Red Ramen for the $10. Ten bucks. Vod boy here. Watch out chat.
Jerma has a real knee slapper coming up. Oh, that's a Vod watcher. I see.
Thank you, Red Ramen. Enjoy the Vod. It's a good one. It's a good one. Hey, back in thanks
for the four dollars. Uh, they say minus two. There are a lot now. Uh, 25 cent bits that have
minus two. It is more than probably 50. 25 cent bits that say minus two.
Minus two. Minus, minus, minus, minus, minus, minus, minus, minus. Somebody did a plus two.
Uh, more minuses. I wonder what this fucking chart would look like. This is one you're gonna,
you're gonna want to look at that one. Somebody's gonna want to chart this one.
Somebody said have fun getting rich, clever streamer. Oh, Espada. Espada Escalata gave
two dollars and fifty cents in the middle of that and they say minus two. More of that. More,
more, more. It then turns into halfway through up here it turns into for a 25 cent minus two
bit messages to 25 cent 750 people subscribe to the channel. My, my weightlifting sub copy pasta.
Like 50 times here. Uh, Espada Escalata thanks for the 250. Chad Germa puts down the minus two
insurrection with videos of him getting ripped but spawns a copy pasta to rival Germacraft. Now
that's a plus two material. There's more, there's more of this. This went on for a while. It was 30
straight minutes of slow mo. Germa lied about Taco Bell. Hello, Germa lied about Taco Bell.
How are you? I put your restaurant at a tier and it was the only one that was there. Congratulations.
Uh, Germa, I just got here. What the fuck happened? I don't even remember. I remember it was,
it was also wrong. That's okay, you can think that. What was that laugh? That was a laugh to rival
Beavis and Butthead. It was all a blur before the tier lists. It kind of was, weirdly enough.
It was. It really was. I don't even remember any of the, I don't remember any of Sam and Max.
Did we play it? Hey, Twunkstee1 thanks for the 250. This is somebody's first Germa stream. Well,
every one of my streams is somebody's first stream. Let's just hope that they come in while
I'm just hanging out having a good time. Hey, Mad at 47 thanks for the 15 dollars. 15 bucks from Mad.
Can you still curl those 35s or are you too old? I can't do it. It's just 21. I'll remember. I like,
I just add, no, I say Twunkstee21. No, I can't do that anymore. I could probably barely do 15 to 20
pounds 10 times on each hand. It's been too long, but I did use the love working out. I felt great,
but thank you for the 15 dollars, Mad. Appreciate it. More 25 set bits that,
I just want to read one. Just checking if you can skip the 30 minute wait time.
You're gonna get so much minus two when this is done. I kind of didn't though. It only happened
for about five seconds. We also had, oh my god, there's so many of these. You did this to yourself.
Is this a scam to make people pay money? How many people made alt accounts to say,
fuck you right now? Jerma's dumb. We are winning. Hey Jerma, when's the next TF2 vid?
That is the one that came through. Uh, plus W plus thanks for the five dollars.
Jerma, thank you for sharing your wonderful personality with the world. I said this before
as my one chat message, but you didn't read it so now I have to say it. I have to pay to say it.
Well thank you for the five dollars, and thank you for listening. Thank you for being here.
Without you there is no me. In a streamer sense. If there wasn't people watching,
I don't think I would have kept doing it. So, works both ways. Thank you. We also see, let's see,
one of these 25 cents that came in is funny. It says, you can't focus on the game because chat is
too slow and engaging. Nice bit extortion. It's just a ruse. When the streamer does a 30 minute
bit for money, Jerma disgust. Viewers dropping, low engagement, sell, sell, sell.
Let me out of the jar, I'm suffocating. Release me. How do I grow up to rule Twitch chat with a
fist of iron like yours? Shave your armpits. Armpit shaving stream. Shave armpits.
These are all 25 cent donations that came in. Somebody says, fuck you. Baskin Robbins mom's
baking cookies ice cream is a mother's day only ice cream. I went into Baskin Robbins and I looked
like a fool. What? No, it's not. No, it's not. It's not, is it? No, it's there. It's there.
Dude, I've looked for that ice cream in six stores. I can't find it. Really? No, it's there. You're
gonna get it. It's definitely not seasonal. Hey, AzzyDreamer, thanks for the five community subs.
Welcome. Thank you. And congratulations to the five lucky contestants that got the community subs.
Thank you. Appreciate it. Thanks for the five subs. Somebody has a question here. Somebody,
this is one of the random just 25 cent like just, it was just flowing in here.
Really not the best place to ask this question, but I'm gonna answer it because it's a strange
place to put this. In the middle of the 25 cent spam, there's somebody that says, I'm looking for
a lost video, Jerma. Where's that Twitter video of a star wasting a bunch of money he won from
You and a Bet on McChickens? I can't find it. I don't, I have no idea what you're talking about.
I don't know what you mean. I don't know. I don't know. I don't recall that Twitter video.
I don't know what that means. I'm sorry. Hey, Demoniccucumber, thanks for the 250.
Why did you empty your Google Play wallet on Twitch bits? I'm sorry, mom. I had to tell my
favorite streamer how much he sucked with them. Thank you for the $10 from, uh, Poopookie? It's
uh, Pookey? Pookey? Pookey? I think. You pick, yup. Just like that Nickelodeon you pick. Get your
toll-free phone out and dial 1-800. You pick Nickelodeon. Press 1 for Doug. Press 2 for
Ren and Stimpy. Press 3 for OurRealMonsters. You pick. Well, what's the... Did I say this like two
weeks ago? I mean, that's a real thing. Well, thank you to the $10 regardless, Pookey. Demoniccucumber,
thanks for the $3. Based on how Twitch searches their chats, you're gonna get your account flagged
for botting because of this stupid bit. Nah, I'll be all right. They got fucking data. All they need
is the data and they have good to go. This is like when each text used to cost money. Us boomers are
used to this. We're calling collect to chat. That's a good one. That's right. I can only do
this twice, so I better make this count. Did you? No, you didn't. And yes, that was the second
message. Maybe it was worth it. Swiggity swanky, thanks to the $5. This all started when you
encouraged chat by noticing the memes. Don't you realize you are an enabler of chat? If you started
going on a tirade about peepee poo poo, chat would go insane. You went off the rails with this one,
big boy. I estimate that this damage you've helped create will last only a few weeks,
so nothing permanent, like hair loss. And they fucking had a... ready? Really? Another gnome
link. Thank you. This is from C4G, thanks to the $5. Hey, Jerma, I think this is the end of the bot.
It had a good weird run and this was a perfect finale for it. Thanks for letting it stick around
for so long. Absolutely, there's a link. Okay, thank you for the $5. I really appreciate that.
Add the bot. Why? The bot doesn't have to go yet. The bot can stay here. The bot's fucking awesome.
It's a great idea. Yeah, maybe after a little while it might, maybe it'll start to derail
streams, but I like the derailment that it does now, so it's okay. Thank you for even contributing
that at all. That was C4G. $5. Thank you. Master Chicken, thanks for the $2.50. There's a link.
Let's click it. Thank you. Jerma, I've been watching you since the first days of TF2 with Star,
and this is the first time I've had money to donate. Just want to say that you've been a
constant positive part of my life. Also, if you don't do the Jerma, where's Waldo? I'll be mildly
upset. I probably will just do that, don't worry. Thank you, Master Chicken. Absolutely. We will do
that. It sounds like a lot of fun. This next one is a $5 donation from somebody. They have
just a link. Let's click it. Nice. And it says, thank you. Thank you. No, let me just click the
next four or five links in a row. Okay. There's no more links after that, so I'm done with clicking
links. E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Thank you for the $2.50. Let's see what this is. It's a link.
Let's click it. E-word. Hold on. What's his name? Hold on. E-word, twerty, word, twerty.
On PC, please. Thank you. Probably. Not. I don't see why not. Probably. Unless, of course,
there's a reason why I wouldn't. Tomorrow, not the next day. Probably not. Not. On legendary mode.
Just kidding. Delete that. Demons V, thanks for the $5. Thank you. Jerma lied about Halo.
He tends to do that. Thank you, though. E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Thank you for that.
Thank you. E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Nailed it. Okay, guess who? Another $2.50 from
E-word, twerty, word, twerty. What is this? E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Thanks for the $5,
Jerma. It's the same clip. Well, it's the same clip twice. I think that maybe they thought they
screwed it up on the first one, but you got it on the first one. Thanks for the $5 total.
Dr. Clay, thanks for the $2.50. I thought this was your voice for a second.
Uh, E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Thank you for the $2.50. And thank you, Dr. Clay.
Jerma lied about Taco Bell thanks for the $3. I have never seen a Panda Express outside of a mall
food court. I know. Uh, Panda, Panda Pal. No, it's Panda, it's, I can't, I cannot say this.
It has to be a different second word every time. Panda Express, Panda Land, Panda Palace, Panda
Time. Like it has to be, I cannot say Express every time, but I really do have to say a very
special thank you to, uh, E-word, twerty, word, twerty. Thank you to KXZ for the 30 bucks.
$30 from KXZ on top of the other huge drops of money from KXZ. Your average Taco Bell meal is
just a biological war crime waiting to happen. What the fuck? Thank you. Taco Bell is good.
One item. Other items on the list? Sure. I've ordered a taco from Taco Bell before,
and it may have well have just been nachos because it was just crushed up lettuce and stale, gross
shell with meat dumped on it. It may have, you probably stepped on it, like stomped on it
before giving it to me. You order a cheesy Gordita Crunch, which I'm going to do right now.
No, I'm not. No, I'm not eating taco. No, I have this rule
where I can't eat fast food more than once every like couple weeks. I can't do that. No.
But thank you KXZ for the huge amount of money. Appreciate it.
Jerma lied about Taco Bell thanks to the 250. Come on man, I was trying to let the
Jerma lied meme die and then you go and rate Taco Bell an A. Uh, Phylactery Lich gave 50 bucks
earlier that I missed, and I'm sorry I missed it, but they said you take this money to Popeyes
and educate yourself. I will. I will go get the biggest bucket of chicken that they sell at Popeyes
and I will eat it off stream. Thank you for the 50 dollars Phylactery.
Really appreciate that. It's a lot of fucking money. Thank you. I have to go get the Cajun fries? Sure.
I'll try them. Hey Dork Cube thanks for the 250. Well now that you've poked the dragon with fast
food discussion, shout out to all the Cook Out and Vojangles fans. You should do a frozen food
tier list next. I might be able to guess who's number one. I would do those. That was fun just
to kind of sit there for an hour. I liked that. That was cool. I had a lot of fun. Kid Cuisine S tier.
Kid Cuisine is definitely F tier. You would probably get more nutrients eating dirt from the
ground. Your father's grass clippings will probably keep you going more than Kid Cuisine will.
Just stir up your father's grass clippings from the lawn and just stir it into water and drink it.
I'm sure that would be probably better for you. That was my childhood you monster? Me too. Hungry
man. All jokes aside, I really don't think I could do a frozen food list because I haven't
eaten them in such a long time. I don't eat frozen like microwavable dinners. I would not be able to
do that list. Should I eat a bunch of them before we do that? Why am I saying like this isn't going
to happen? Hey bake me home thanks for the 250. Take a shower you smell. I might. Oh maybe. I don't
think I do. No I got I got the odor on. I'm fine. But thank you bake me home. Thank you true proxy
for the ten bucks. Thank you Jerm for always giving me the most genuine laughs of all. Have a
thousand bits. I will very graciously take them. Thank you so much true proxy for the ten dollars
one thousand bits. I will gladly take them. Thank you. A watt fridge thanks to the five bucks. The
secret menu exists because they haven't changed their actual menu since the day they opened
and it's sort of a key part of their business model. Same how their prices barely change year
to year. Yeah but at what point does does the actual menu be trumped by the secret menu?
When when your menu of the secret menu is bigger than the actual menu
don't you think you should like switch them around? Uh thank you milkshake for the three
dollars. In and out is S tier. In and out is S tier. In and out is S tier. In and out is S tier.
In and out is S tier. I you guys thought I was making that up when I was like screeching and like
like wringing. I told you you're not allowed to say in and out is bad. That's why it has the
streamer text that I'm on camera streamer text of it being in the like high somewhere in seas.
In and out is all right. It is. I would eat in and out if somebody said let's go to in and out.
I'd be like yeah fucking that sounds pretty good. Man I would also skydive if I had I could build
up enough like the courage to do that too right? Kidding it's all right it's just a hamburger.
Jeremiah Shake Shack is overrated. You've never had it before. You've never had it before. And by
the way Shake Shack has a better chicken sandwich than most restaurants that specialize in chicken
sandwiches. They got a twofer. Better chicken sandwiches than most of the chicken sandwich
restaurants. Better burgers than the burger restaurants. Come on try it if you have it's
available. All right you know you got me there. You got me there. Shake Shack the the fries at
Shake Shack are dog shit. Yeah still S tier though because they spend so much time with
so much effort crafting such incredible quality sandwiches that something has to get left behind.
And do you really care if the fries aren't that great? All right the fries from Five Guys and the
fries from Shake Shack. It's the afterthought. You just don't order the fries then. Just get two
sandwiches. Fries aren't good for you anyways. It's just starch and oil. You don't you shouldn't
even order them anyways. Get two get a chicken sandwich and get a hamburger. What are the best
fries? That's actually pretty easy. The best french fries you can possibly get from a fast food
restaurant McDonald's right when they come out. If they're fresh McDonald's fresh fries are better.
Burger King is pretty close if they're fresh. Burger King fries are really close if they're
fresh. I would say Burger King's are the best but here's the issue Burger King's fries are never
fresh. That's like a one in 100 chance and unless you're feeling pretty lucky I wouldn't do it.
You get the fresh Burger King fries though. Hard to beat. Wendy's fries. Wendy's fries are good.
I think I would put them they're pretty standard. Should we go back to the list and do fries only?
Do a fry test. I would do that. That sounds like a good idea. I'm gonna do a fry taste test. I'm
gonna get fries from Shake Shack, McDonald's, Burger King, Wendy's, In-N-Out. Popeyes has fries.
Interesting. They won't be fresh? Yeah they will. Thank you. Jerma lied about Taco Bell for the 250th.
Do you ever accidentally call your streamer friends by their twitch channels? That's all
they called. I don't call them anything else. I know Star as Star. That's what I say to them
in actual in real life. Talix is a Talix. Talix. The only reason why I call Kim Kim is because Kim
is her username. You know what I'm saying? Try the other um Incredible Orb. Hey that's Orb. Hey
Orb! Hey Orb! Orb! Orb! I don't call him by his first name. Boo yeah. Boo is just boo.
Boo. That is how it happens usually. Demons V thanks to the five dollars. Appreciate the five
dollars. You called Nova James before. Isn't that what people call them? It's usually by like what
like people call you in your community is what I usually go by. It's actually easier to remember
people's handles than it is to remember their names. Interestingly enough because they could
be like a hundred Johns but you know there's only one. Excommunicado three right? That's the
that's the only person with that name. You could be like one of 20 Dan's or Dave's that I know
or you could be the Strangler 49444. That's just who you are. Hey uh RTM thanks for the five dollars.
Just want to say thank you for bringing some laughter and joy to me in an otherwise shitty
day. We had to put my father's dog down today and I've not been taking it well. Watching the stream
and reading chat has helped me so thank you. I'm terribly sorry to hear that. Losing an animal is
tough. It sucks. I really hope that that dog was able to live a nice good long life
and if it was for other circumstances then hopefully the time that the dog did have was
full of love. So I'm really sorry to hear that. Thank you for the five dollars and by all means
absolutely we are very very happy to take your mind off it. Sorry to hear that.
Thank you for the five dollars. We also had a ten dollars come in from Azzy Dreamer on top of the
I believe community subs that came in as well from Azzy. Thanks for all you do Jerma. I've watched
you since TF2 days and watching on YouTube helped me through so much of my darkest times in my life
have a good one. You as well. You have a good one too. Thanks for watching for that long. Yesterday
uh reminiscing and watching some old videos and watching maybe mention TF2 I really do like miss
that stuff. You you almost like you plant yourself back five six seven eight years ago. It's like oh
this was fucking a ton of fun but then I think about now and this shit's a ton of fucking fun too
five ten years from now I'll be looking back to this stuff going oh that was a great time.
That was a lot of fun. Remember when we did that? Well that was great. That was so cool.
So it works always sort of in perpetuity when you look backwards.
So thank you for the ten bucks. Thanks for sticking around for that long and I hope to
see you around more. Hopefully you stick around even longer because there's so much more going on
to do. Thank you though. Let's get the community subs. There were a lot of them today
on top of the all of the bit donations that came through and of course the regular resubs and the
new subs people that just didn't get a community sub. Community subs come through so often now
that it's almost like they're taking a huge huge portion of actual subbed people to the channel.
So that's thank you for that. Whoever whoever you are whenever you do it that's some of you
guys are responsible for tens, dozens, hundreds of people on the channel. So really appreciate it.
Why don't we show all those names now? Here are tonight's subs. Thank you. Somebody says it's
gonna be weird when I've been watching Jerma since I was 12 and be like 30 in 10 years.
Now you know that that works both ways right? That means I'll be 44. Don't really want to think
about that. I don't even want to think about 35 because I've mentioned this before but I'm at
that stage right now where I don't get to pick the 18 to 34 drop down box anymore. One more year
and I've got to do the thing I have never done and that's pick the one 35 to 55.
There are a couple more bits to do. We have Internet Jorge
for the $15 from Internet Jorge. Take my offering so that us peasants may never suffer your wrath
again. Wrath. If I was a seven deadly sin what would I be? Pride. I don't think so. Sloth?
No, I'm sorry. Pride. Lust. Greed. Envy. Pride. Lust. Wrath. Greed. Envy. Gluttony.
Pride. Lust. Pride. Pride. Lust. Rage. Greed. No, Pride. Lust. Wrath. Greed. Gluttony. Envy.
What's the other one? Pride. Lust. Gluttony. Greed. Sloth. Envy.
Who am I missing? I have to write them down. Wrath. Pride. Sloth. Greed. Gluttony. Greed.
Wrath. Pride. Sloth. Greed. Wrath. Pride. Lust. Envy. Is that seven?
Wrath. Pride. Sloth. Greed. Gluttony. Lust. Envy. What's the- Wrath. Pride. Sloth. Greed.
Gluttony. Lust. Envy. That's six. No, it's not. Is that seven? Okay. Which one would I be?
The eighth sin. But what I was trying to say, somebody said short. Oh yeah. Wrath. Pride. Sloth.
Greed. Gluttony. Lust. Envy. Short. Funny. I think I would be a combination of- I don't think I have
any of these things. How come there's no seven awesome sins? You know? Like, how come- why is
it- why is there not like a holy equivalent to this? What is it? The Ten Commandments, right?
Instead of the seven deadly sins, where are like the seven things- cool things to do?
Oops, I tried to hit enter to like do another one. The seven virtues. Okay, wait. Seven virtues. What
are they? Let's see if- okay. Chastity. Temperance. Charity. Diligence. Patience. Kindness.
And humility. Where's like Jack? Temperance. Charity. Diligence. Patience. Do a tier list
of the sins and the virtues. No, not tonight. Maybe we'll do it again. Maybe we'll do it again
another night. Books of the Bible tier list. What are you- you trying to get me like a reservation
downstairs? Easy. Oh, we had one final bit coming from Mitchell, thanks to five dollars.
Hey, Yerma, thanks for the awesome stream tonight. Five guys being below Taco Bell is a crime against
humanity, but uh, whatever. I waited 20 minutes into the 30 minute slow-mo to ask you to play
Freedom Force 1 and 2, but the message still managed to immediately disappear. I think you'd
love them. I think I have Freedom Force. Didn't I play Freedom Force? Well, that was Freedom Fighters.
Freedom Force. What's the final tally? I don't know. I- I- the bot got uh, eaten alive.
Truly a minus one thousand stream. What did I do today? We did episode one of
season three of Sam and Max, and then I spent way too long deliberating over a fast food tier list.
But uh, thank you everybody for watching. See you tomorrow. The plan is Star and I are going to do
something. I don't know. We'll see. Plans change, but that's what's supposed to happen.
See you tomorrow at the normal time somewhere around three to four p.m. Pacific. See you tomorrow.
Have a great one.