Yeah, I found a- oh my god, there's four, like, police helicopters here. There's so many RPGs.
Oh, Ster, what are you doing?
I, like, drove up there. You're already gone.
I'm climbing up the top of this, like, construction beam.
I'll fly this over to you so you can get the weapons.
I just gotta be able to fly without crashing into-
Oh, wow.
It's a long way up.
They're so confused, they, like, can't get over- they, like, don't know what to do.
They're just, like, all down there.
Some of these guys are just walking around in circles.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
What have I done?
What'd you do?
Run?
Oh!
Oh, no!
Don't fall down the hole!
What?
What just happened there?
You dropped- you dropped, like, a bomb behind me and it blew me down the hole!
Oh, no!
What? What?
All I heard was, oops, that's not good.
And all of a sudden I just fly forward and my body rolls into the freaking hole.
It went down the tube?
Yeah, I rolled- like, I was, like, a piece of, like, hair going down a bathroom sink.
Oh, no!
Dude, some dealership just, like, made out, like, a bandit.
All these poor ladies do legs.
They really all are the same car.
Hey, look, everybody has, like, a Saturn.
Maybe run her over.
Holy cow.
Yeah, I need assault now. I'm one shot.
I'm out of ammo in my assault rifle.
I can't believe that helicopter- what is this helicopter doing?
What is this guy doing?
Wow, what an idiot.
There he is!
I just saw him.
I'm all by myself.
This is a helicopter graveyard.
This is, like, 30 helicopters here.
Whoa! Oh, my God!
Oh, my-
30 helicopters here.
Yeah!
Oh, my God!
I just, like, elbowed it.
Oh, it's still there on my screen.
I'm keeping this one.
Here we go.
It's time to obey the rules of the road.
Starting now.
We are now law-abiding citizens.
Is there, like, a speed limit button?
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Police officer.
Oh, that guy just passed us.
Yeah, what was that all about?
It was a police officer.
You're supposed to pull to the right.
Oh, excuse me!
All right, I'm going to be-
My right blinker is on.
I'm going to be taking a right-hand turn here.
I broke your right taillight by accident.
Hey, look at this guy.
Hey, you need to calm down, buddy.
He's taking a left-
His left blinker is on.
He's in the middle of the road.
Look at this guy's head.
Oh my god.
What is this cop doing?
What?
I'm not absorbing this.
Does anybody have a star?
I may have three stars by accident.
You have three stars?
Oh, this cop is right next to me.
He's going to pull down.
I'm still obeying the rules, not my problem.
Drive safely.
He's in my car.
This guy's passing-
I'm trying to let him pass.
Oh, boo, it's in your car.
It's a red light.
It's green, it's green.
We have to get them away from you.
It's a red light, boo. I don't think we can go yet.
It's green, it's green.
It's a shotgun!
Get out of here.
Oh my god.
It's so bossy.
She's trying to drive safely.
Alright, Steph, I'm going to be taking a left-hand turn here.
I'm taking fire on my vehicle.
My car! Look how scratched it is.
Oh no.
The cop, man.
He's like pulling up alongside.
Oh, it's green.
Go left.
Oh no, there's a one-way.
There's a one-way back up.
There's a one-way.
They're pushing us sideways.
That's a one-way.
I think boo turned all the way around.
I saw that.
No, no, no. No one noticed.
Alright, actually, can we pull over for a second, guys?
I kind of want a hot dog.
I'm kind of hungry.
There's no vendor there.
Is it closed?
What?
What happened there?
Disconnected from live.
Too bad there's no vendor here.
My car!