Is it $359? Pretty cool. What's up?
Clap, clap. One time on time Andy.
One time on time Andy. Did I add that?
How are you guys doing? Hope you're doing well.
Uh, just let me make a tweet and we can get started. Give me one sec.
Okay. Neanderthal is playing the power wash simulator.
I saw that. Yeah. Does it suck?
Is it a shitty game? Or is it good?
Gonna have to get a little review here.
Are you going to try the don't starve mod? Wait, what?
Why did you have sub only mode on you fucking? What?
What are you talking about? Yesterday?
What? I can't turn on sub only? I already explained it.
Did that person wait of 24 hours to say that?
That must have been in your text box.
You ever text somebody and you just kind of give up halfway through?
Like three or four days go by and you like open up your
that person's message and you go, oh fuck, I was going to write this. Enter.
You must've just done that. Yes, I did.
Did you? That's so funny. No, no way.
Do you have like a tab open?
Jerma, please. Jerma, please sing me a song, please.
No, not everybody gets a song.
On time, Andy, a billion off the debt.
That would be pretty cool, actually.
I should have done it.
God damn it. Yesterday, I should have said,
hey, today, by the way, if I get exactly 359 live, it's a billion off the debt.
Oh, well. Missed my opportunity.
No deal? Well, that's all right.
Today, we're going to finish Hitman 3 today.
I have, I think, two more missions, but one more real mission.
And then like a finale or something, from my understanding.
You're late.
Shitman 3. Sing the Hitman 3 song.
It's all about songs with you guys, isn't it?
It's all about songs.
Everything has a song now.
Jerma, sing the tooth brushing song.
Well, that's a very important one
because you need to brush your teeth for two minutes.
So, I mean, I would do that one for you.
Let me get the lyrics for it.
So use this for when you're brushing your teeth, okay?
Here we go. Brush.
Start it now. It has to last two minutes.
Very important that you listen to this while you brush.
Brush, brushy, brush, brushy, brush, brush.
Brushy, brush them up and down.
Brushy, brush, brush them round and round.
To keep teeth healthy, here's the truth.
You gotta brush each and every single tooth.
The teeth in the back get a lot of wear.
So don't forget to wash back there.
Brush, brushy, brush, brushy, brush, brush, brush your teeth.
Keep them looking clean and neat.
Brush, brushy, brush, brush, brush, brush.
Brush your teeth every day and night.
Now your toothpaste may taste good
when you've got it in your mouth.
Elmo, that's not right.
That doesn't, that's, toothpaste sucks.
But you should never swallow it.
You gotta spit it out.
Go on and spit.
We'll wait it out.
Brush your teeth.
Keep them looking clean and bright.
Brush, brushy, brush, brush.
That's all right.
Brush, brush, brush every day and night.
Now if your parents heard, here's what you've gotta do.
Let them get your toothbrush
so they can brushy brush your teeth.
Great job.
Looks like you're almost done.
What?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Now spit.
That song's terrible.
That's like Elmo's teeth brushing song.
That song sucks.
Anyways, get your, wait, if your parents hear you,
get them to brush your teeth for you?
That's the end of the song, Elmo.
That's at the third, that's the final third of the song.
Two minutes.
Elmo, you have the parent line be the first two lines.
You just plagiarized Sesame Street.
Yeah, what, let's go.
Plagiarize.
I didn't plagiarize Sesame Street.
I just told you I was reading you something from Sesame Street.
I mean, I was giving you the source.
That's the source.
Plagiarizing means I pretended that I just made that song up
and I didn't take it from Elmo.
Today, oh no, yesterday, okay.
All right, so here we go.
We're in the final of real level of Hitman.
If you, you know what?
You know what?
Let's just, for the people that weren't here yesterday,
like let's, what am I, just skip till I get to,
no, we're gonna just restart the level
so people can know what's going on.
Here you go.
I want you to know what happened.
We're gonna just start it from the beginning.
Everything's planned, everything's good.
Yep, that's perfect.
And let's go.
Give us a recap.
We're meeting Diana.
You know, 47, this is Diana.
We're meeting her at a ledge
because there's a bad guy that's trying to kill us both.
So now we're meeting in an undisclosed location
so we can try to kill that guy and get him
because he's trying to get us.
And I just explained power is a thing.
There you go.
Power is a thing and some people grab it.
Some people miss their opportunity to grab it
and some people reach for it their whole life
but it's a thing that you can get.
There you go.
And for those of you that weren't here yesterday,
I'm gonna go ahead and do the exact same job I did last night.
I just killed Diana with one shot.
I killed her.
She's still alive.
Well, that person's dead instead.
I think I can still do it.
All right, but if you weren't here yesterday,
we're gonna start with that one.
All right, so it doesn't matter.
No, wait, no, you wanna see the beginning.
No, don't replan the mission.
It took so many.
Oh, fuck, this dude's out of material.
No, I just started.
Give me a second.
Hold on, what's going on here?
We've got a link.
Oh, is this a link spam day today?
What the fuck?
This is a fucking paragraph, dude.
This is like an essay.
Hold on.
I'm gonna read this.
Um, what the hell?
Okay, so, um, okay.
Jeremy, this is your principal from Clown High speaking,
Principal Bubbles.
Hi, Principal Bubbles.
I've been watching your Hitman 3 streams
and I've been very underwhelmed.
Okay, I know you can do better than zero stars every mission,
so I want to cut you a deal.
For this next mission, the score you get at the end
in the detailed score tab
is how much I would like to remove from your debt
times 100.
However, you kill one innocent man
and get even one point of a negative score.
The money you receive is null
and instead we will add to your debt
the amount that was penalized also times 100.
Loading a save if you have to is fine,
but no blatant save's coming.
We trust that you'll be a good person, Mr. Albertson.
You always were the best in the clown class.
If you accept,
you can also choose to double or triple the rewards
and penalties from the bet.
We believe in you,
valedictorian of the clown class of 2004.
Thank you, Principal Bubbles.
And I really wish I didn't get suspended that time
that I squirted the water in your face
with the flour on my blouse.
But, and I, everyone laughed at that but you,
and I got suspended.
So, I mean, you're gonna cut me a deal here, that's fine.
Is that a deal?
All right, I have to be very, very honest with everybody here.
This is, this is the truth, the absolute truth.
I've played every single Hitman, all of them.
Contracts, Blood Money, Hitman 1, Hitman 2,
the Hitman Absolution,
the new reimagining of this last trilogy here,
Hitman, Hitman 2, Hitman 3 here.
I have, I don't think ever, not one time ever,
in two decades, gotten more than zero stars on a mission.
I've gotten more than, I've never gotten more than zero
in two decades of playing this game, this franchise.
I don't even know how to properly play this game.
I don't even understand it.
So, that's a very bad deal for me to take, very bad.
I don't know if I can do it.
You're talking about a one in a million chance
that I will get this right.
I've played every single one of these
and I end up having to like throw a guy over a balcony
or like shoot some lady because she was in the way.
It's gonna happen.
It's not easy for me.
Should I do it?
But okay, what, times 100?
All right, let me ask you a question.
Can I do, can I get a save file
where I save and I can go to that save
and just like fucking throw a grenade?
Like, can I do that?
Like, can I take it out of my system
or do I have to just do it from now on
and do good on the mission?
Like, can I have like a comedy save file
and then like the regular save file?
No, it's from now on.
You get a comedy save, okay?
So, I get one comedy save.
All jokes are allowed.
This seems very elaborate.
We need to have a consensus here.
You have to say it's a comedy save.
So, like if I say this is a comedy save
I'm making right now, I can throw a grenade at somebody.
Do we have a, I'm allowed one comedy save
for this whole mission.
Okay, yes.
Yes, one comedy save.
Unfunny stream.
Wait, I just started.
Come on, dude.
What the fuck?
I haven't even started.
I'm like blocking out a deal.
Like, cause now, here's the thing.
Now a lot of you guys are concerned now
because now I'm not gonna just throw grenades at people.
I'm not gonna throw people to balconies
and I'm not gonna like trap somebody
like in like the kitchen and throw plates at them.
Now you're like, oh shit, this is the gaming.
He's gonna be like gaming on this stream.
Only 13% of the people from the census
even wanted this in the first place.
I'm going for it.
Let's go.
I accept the agreement.
I get one comedy save.
And the rest is I have to play Hitman.
I'm gonna make, I'm gonna do the best I possibly fucking can.
And that's how times 100 at the end
is the hardest I'm ever gonna try in a video game.
All right, does it go, can I get it?
Let me get something out of my, should I?
Is it not starting now?
Is it starting now?
Is it starting right now?
But wait, this doesn't count as a comedy save, right?
Put that away.
Not right now.
Not right, can I start right now?
Not yet.
Doesn't start yet.
When does it start?
When can I, when does it actually start?
It starts right now.
Okay, right now.
All right, all right, all right.
I want to throw off so bad.
I want to push her over the edge so bad.
You got my message.
I have one comedy save.
I have to make it count.
Put the face cam on or no deal.
That doesn't-
I'm not the only one who's been busy, 47.
Okay, we already saw that.
You need, there has to be a face cam for this.
Why?
You know, I don't have to prove I'm looking at the screen.
Why do I have to prove that I'm looking at the screen for?
Or it's pre-recorded?
Don't get out of here.
Okay, fine.
Or you could be doing a walkthrough.
Okay, it's times a hundred, right?
All right, I'm going to try really fucking hard.
Eliminate Tamara.
Eliminate Dawn Archibald.
Do not eliminate Diana Burnwood
unless you make a comedy save file right now.
Too early.
Let's go.
Put the guy with the camera.
This is not a comedy save.
All right.
Slot one is regular save.
Slot two-
Can I have three comedy saves, please?
Can I please have three comedy save files?
Three-
One is not enough.
Three.
Okay.
Why are you asking?
It's your stream.
Right.
That's right.
I get three comedy-
Okay.
I get three comedy save files.
This is regular save file.
This is comedy save slot.
I get three.
Oh, damn it.
Like, okay.
You know what?
Soldier 76.
Right now, like, the visor came down,
and it's like,
Soldier 76, I got you in my sights.
And it's like-
Everybody's lighting up,
and I'm just like, which one?
Who do I-
I need to-
I gotta throw that guy in the front of the car.
I'm seeing so many-
I wanna, like, just-
I don't know what to do.
The person's smoking a cigarette.
Like, I wanna throw a cigarette at them.
Cell phone.
Smack cell phone out of his hand.
Walk through-
Just barrel through the crowd.
Shoulders.
Okay.
You know what?
I can, like, pretend I'm doing it.
I didn't do anything.
Okay.
Visitors.
Here we go.
I'm gonna start to pay attention,
because I need to-
I need to get a good score.
Okay.
You know-
Can I disguise as one of those guys?
Eliminate them-
But where are they?
Inside there, up there.
Oh, I wanna get in front of the-
I wanna pretend like I'm the singer of the band.
This is not gonna deduct points.
I can still do things like that.
Okay, I don't understand.
I did not understand any of that.
I'm sorry.
What about in here?
Do not eliminate Diana Burnwood.
Well, that's so easy.
She's-
Oh, she's coming to the party.
She's gonna stand.
She's-
Hey there.
Can I dance with her?
May I have this dance?
Oh, okay.
Are we gonna work together?
Oh, I know.
Excuse me.
May I-
May I button?
Excuse me.
How can I tell-
No, I'm gonna cue.
Is this-
Okay.
Is that me?
I'm gonna disguise as that guy.
I would laugh so hard if she just turned to me when I pressed F1,
like her head just turns and she's like,
47, we have a new lead.
Okay.
Well, cool.
Oh, if I push her over the edge, it won't kill her, but it'll be funny.
Imagine just like a somersault over the railing.
This is a-
This is a gamer save, by the way.
I want to make that really clear.
This is-
They're playing music really loudly.
All right, what do we got?
Let's see.
Mission stories.
Eyes on the target, over the top, or the tour.
I want to do the tour.
The guy they were talking about is over here.
Turn down the music.
Better?
Turn it up.
All right, wait, wine bottle.
Let me get the wine bottle.
It's not illegal, right?
Oh my god, I can bottle somebody.
Me?
That's like me, but British.
All right, go sign in.
AKA get bottled in the bathroom, and then get your costume taken.
Wait.
The whole time I'm staring at them.
Oh, we can't get them to say that again.
We can't get them to say that again.
Too bad.
Skies yourself is Corvo Black.
Here we go.
Remember, this is a gamer save.
Don't kill anybody, that's important.
Kill them all, kill them.
I don't understand a 50-50 chance of getting caught.
I mean, you do realize the risk here, boss.
Brought the workers around.
Who would send me in this world?
Why does this chat suck so much?
I didn't say it, you did.
But if I'm going to be one of these heralds.
I didn't say that.
Oh, QR code.
Scan it with my camera.
What is that?
Cool.
Nero Yates features a spectacular dining patio
on top of their winemaking facility.
Cool.
We hate one guy.
What?
This is rude.
What's rude?
This is a terrible link.
I keep seeing terrible link.
I need to...
Okay, this guy's about to be alone.
Okay, this is important.
I don't want to fuck this up.
He's coming over here.
He is alone.
He's alone.
Diana.
Diana, just like scream really loud right now.
And when everyone runs over be like,
oh, I'm sorry, there was a bug on my face.
Give me a hand here.
Hey, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it.
I didn't save scum.
That's not a safe scum.
That was me completely...
I couldn't do it.
Fuck!
Why is he mad at me?
I can't do it.
There's another opportunity right here.
If he turns around, I have to kill him.
Fuck!
I can't kill that guy.
Ahh!
Okay, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
It's impossible.
I can't play it man like this.
It's literally impossible.
It's invo-
It's impossible to play a game like this.
It's impossible.
I lose.
Somebody should call an exorcist.
Cancel the deal.
Cancel it.
Alright, this is this.
Cancel the deal.
I can't do it.
Cancel it.
Cancel the deal right now.
It's not gonna happen.
I guarantee it won't happen.
The deal is off.
Just not gonna fucking happen.
Load the save.
I'm not li-
I can't save scum.
And right there, I would have had to kill like four people.
Add a dollar to the debt.
It's dead.
Okay, well, you know what?
That's fine.
That's minus 50,000 points.
I don't even care.
The deal is off.
You know what?
You have this.
You can add-
You can add 50,000 dollars for every minute that we had that deal going before I canceled it.
Why?
That's not that much.
That's like two million.
How much is that?
It's 1.5 million.
I said 50,000 for every minute.
It's been like-
It's been like two minutes.
Twelve minutes.
What's this guy-
What's-
Why is-
What happened to this guy?
Why are you puking?
Why did I do that?
Who's searching?
Okay, we're gonna go up.
Let's get-
Let's take the tour.
That guy tripped.
Actual maniac.
Again, I will say it again for all the people that were not here a few days ago.
Playing GTA V but following all the rules and the traffic signals
is how Hitman is supposed to be played.
I can't do that.
If I'm driving the car in GTA and this is like-
I'm just gonna get out of the car and I'm gonna punch someone.
And then I'm gonna get back in the car and go back to normal and do the mission.
Body f-
He's naked.
Let's go start the tour.
Dream is actually not ironically fucked.
Dream.
Ooh, this is beautiful.
How was my day?
It was pretty good.
How was yours?
Your 1080 is dying.
Don't hold your breath.
Don't worry.
I'm getting a new computer.
Vidal is a true believer.
It's just this shit's hard to get right now.
He's loyal to the cops.
Must be why he chose her to show Burnwood-
Sorry, that like fucks with me in real life.
All right, here we go.
Let's join the other guests.
Here comes the tour.
Here.
You two must be Burnwood and Vidal.
And you must be Yates' garbage man.
Sorry, but I didn't catch your name.
This is Corvo Black, Tamara.
It's me.
I see a regular.
I only work with the best.
Well, we're all here it seems.
Except for our guide, the chief winemaker.
Looks like we're stuck here until someone fetches him.
Mr. Black, I'm looking in your direction.
Hold on.
I'll track him down.
Where is he?
We try and bring him back in one piece.
Infiltrate the grape fields?
That was a bit rude.
Yes.
Infiltrate the grape fields.
Why didn't I just say go get the guy?
Okay.
We're supposed to be on the tour.
What the fuck is this?
Oh dear.
Okay.
Oh my god!
All right, I'm fine.
I got a coin here.
No, don't look over here.
Look over there.
Into the barrel?
Okay.
Hang out right here.
Puncture.
Doi doi doi.
I'm like a bird.
You just do certain calls, I'll call back.
I love Malbec.
Three grapes.
Excuse me.
Dave scum.
The deal is off.
It doesn't matter.
There's no way I was going to do that.
You knew that was not going to happen.
It just wasn't.
It just that was that was not possibly going to happen.
Wait, what?
Why is he not investigating?
Is it a wood chipper?
What is that?
I'm not going to grind this guy's body up, right?
What?
You what?
Why?
You can what?
Oh, here it is.
The skies.
I'm going to do the same exact thing I did last time.
You guys walk by.
Ready?
Check this out.
Two guards walk by.
I can't believe I ground that guy up.
Where are the two guards?
There they are.
Oh, I thought if I went the other way it'd be safer.
Read the objective.
Discard yourself as a winery worker.
Not the winery worker.
A winery worker.
Not this winery worker.
Not that winery worker.
A winery.
Well, it doesn't matter.
He's the one with the fucking blue thing on it.
I'm taking him.
Acquire a grape picking knife.
Thread him.
No, I'm not going to shred this guy.
So that's so much money.
That's so much money from Freddy Dredd.
Freddy Dredd giving just millions of community subs at this point.
I'm a thousandth.
Thanks, Freddy.
That's 69 community subs.
Holy shit.
All right.
I need a knife.
Thank you.
That's people have given a shitload of money.
I...
Thanks, guys.
I don't even know what to do.
I don't know what to say.
This is so much money.
Does it give somebody?
You guys, a bunch of you.
Our benefactors.
All right.
I need a grape picking knife.
Oh, this guy.
These guys can see through my disguise.
Holy shit.
I just accidentally did this correctly.
Harvest three ripe Malbec grape vines.
Oh my God.
Is he crying?
What?
Yes.
Orders confirmed.
I will.
Just like the blue.
Okay.
Harvest three Malbec grapes.
Are these Malbec grapes?
No.
Oh, they are.
Okay.
These are big.
Harvest two ripe Malbec grapes.
Why would I have to sneak around doing this?
I think I have to distract this guy.
Here's the mission agent 985.
No.
Anisoto.
Why don't you just open this thing up and pick some grapes out of here?
I need there.
Is that one right there?
All right.
This one.
They look like beehives.
All right.
Here we go.
Ready?
What was that over there?
Oh, easy, easy, easy.
I don't know what to turn that on.
There's one this way.
Investigating distraction.
Good.
There's one right here.
Wait.
Is anybody looking this way?
Nope.
Okay.
What about this way?
Nope.
Go.
Last one.
Thank you.
Deliver the grapes to the chef.
Sure thing.
I heard.
I don't know why.
The grape chef.
We're going to give it to the grape chef.
This is why I don't do face cam because I end up going like this.
You know what they need to make?
They need to make a device that you put around your neck
to make it so you can't move your neck forward.
Would you guys get one of those if it was like a posture neck thing?
That like it was like a thing around your neck
and there was like a thing here that like went.
I know you just saw my fucking armpit hair and it's too long.
His armpit hair is way too long.
Does he do any manscaping?
All the time, but not recently because I've been busy.
So anyways, I've got a thing around the neck
that connects to the back of the chair.
So it's like because I always go like this and one is like that's all right.
That's that's just a chain.
No, I don't want that.
The gamer posture.
The gamer posture corrector is just like a a fucking like neck brace.
That whole like a chain.
If you would get so excited or like a big kill or something.
If you're sitting there like playing like fucking Fortnite.
Just like come on, come on, come on, come on, one more.
Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill, come on, come on.
Oh, right, right.
Okay.
Victory Royale.
I did it.
Wait, so I gotta save it.
Game leash.
I have to hand it to him.
Fine.
Are we going to try it?
Is he's going to squish it in his hands like into this cup and I'm going to try it?
That's a 10.
What if you had to go to the bathroom?
Do you have like the key right here?
Disguise yourself as Corvo Black.
I have the keys and there's just the key to this thing sitting here.
What if I drop it on the ground?
What if it's just like, okay, that was awesome.
I got two Victory Royales in a row.
Let me just get that key.
No, let me just get my phone.
My phone.
Oh boy, that's the phone on the ground.
I don't want to start screaming in that.
Well, I don't have access to my hands.
Why am I like strapped to the chair?
So not only do I have like the gamer like nerd neck preventer,
I also apparently have my arms taped to the chair.
I don't know why that's why.
Why am I like reaching like this to try to get the phone?
If you're going to see me do this, just in case somebody does, I'm saving it right here.
Okay, good.
I'm now trespassing.
All right, because I'm a different person.
Top the fence.
We're good.
Oh my god, German.
Look what Neanderthal is playing.
Oh yeah, I saw.
Power wash simulator.
I wonder if it's the game of the year.
All right, let's save it here.
I feel like I'm going to have a lot of opportunity to just be stupid.
This is not even a guy I have to kill.
This is not even the target.
Every time I hear Diana talk, I just think she's not here.
I just hear, I just hear like she's in a beer piece.
The production floor.
Graves are processed.
We insist on the steaming every grape by hand, which means that during harvest season,
the grapes do tend to pile up.
Plenty of sauce.
Is this how it actually works?
Our equipment is a state of the art.
Industrial sized freezer unit.
They bring the, I thought, I thought they just like froze them.
I can't pretend with that one.
I know how wine, I know how wine is made.
I can't like, I can't like make a fucking stupid bit how I like don't know what they do.
I know what they do.
They crush them and they squish them.
I can't pretend like, oh, they freeze them and then they put them in like the squisher.
I'm not going to even go down that road today.
Farm farming like question marks.
Oh, cool.
The McDonald's play place bar.
I love this.
Hold on.
Using our grape presser for the longer secondary stage of fermentation.
Ask questions.
Okay.
Yes.
Are they allowed, are we allowed to taste the grapes during the production process?
Wait.
What was it?
Wait, is it a squisher?
Yeah.
Press it.
Press the button right now.
Let's see if I can Indiana Jones get out of this in time.
Okay, cool.
Wait, what do you unlock safety mechanism?
Wait, I can squish them.
Who has a key?
Save, save, save.
Oh, I think he's just.
I need a key.
Oh, somebody pressed the button and squished her.
You have a lock pick.
It's why it's grayed out.
Who has the key?
One of these guys have a key.
I can't believe you would stand in this for more than one second.
I would, I would never even stand in it.
I'll take a picture.
The thing that that is designed to only fucking squish and crush things.
You're going to stand underneath that for a fucking tourist photo.
What are you talking about?
Wait, hold on.
We got to go up here.
Put the lock pick in your hand.
Wait, I have a key hacker.
Does that do anything?
Somebody said Willy Wonka joke incoming.
Did you just spoil a potential joke that I was going to make?
And I didn't even know I was going to make it until right now.
What the fuck, man?
Oh, come on.
Unbelievable.
Augustus, you're getting too close.
I love chocolate.
I was going to do that.
That was a wrong person.
That was Diana.
Why did you ruin that for me?
You've ruined that for me.
I didn't know that's what this was.
And I was about to, I could have done like an Augustus bit
where I dumped Augustus in there.
Well, not dumped.
I don't.
But like, I get that pretend like Augustus gets stuck in the pipe.
Down from there.
Don't do it, Diana.
Diana, don't do it.
Almost.
That was very close.
Standing on it with high heels.
Yeah.
I can't dump her in here?
Okay, but wait.
What happens when she doesn't come back to the door?
Cassie had diarrhea.
She had to leave.
There's a third option.
I'm just gonna say it.
That's what all of us are thinking.
If this was on Steam, this wouldn't happen.
Because it didn't.
It did happen.
This is on the fucking Nintendo Store.
This wouldn't happen.
I didn't just pick my nose.
I went like this.
That's the worst one.
Okay, error.
Unable to load the requested menu.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna...
Here's another thing all of us are thinking.
Unable to load the requested menu.
Please retry the quest or contact Hitman support if this is a problem.
How many people are looking at those emails coming in?
Contact Hitman support about how I lost connection.
There's an inbox somewhere with like 40,000 unread emails saying,
hey, my server doesn't work.
Call them.
It's not a number.
It's like a support email.
Can I not even load the game now?
What the heck?
The bar is loading.
You can't see it, but it's going very slow.
Somebody said, the game stinks.
I'm just gonna hard reset.
I hope I don't lose save.
Do a hard destroy.
Good thing it cloud synced the game files.
What mods should you get for Oblivion?
Um, are you...
Never mind.
I am required to play online,
but you are not required to make sure it works.
Yes.
Let's go!
Don't do it again.
I'm gonna be very upset if it does it again.
Thank God.
All right, so...
There's a third option.
I want to see it.
What is the comedy part of the stream?
Well, stay tuned.
Stay tuned when we do the next, um, like, mouse trap.
We'll push him in.
Can I have this?
All right.
I want to see the, uh, the last one.
It was the third one.
Where's this last one?
How would he hear me from all the way over here?
We've never heard 47 raise his voice.
Has he ever screamed?
I mean, all right.
Come on.
Like, give me a break.
Really?
Like, what can you tell me about the grape crusher?
Well, it crushes things.
Hold on.
Does it kind of crush anything?
You're gonna see me do this, though.
Had any workplace accidents?
Well, fall into the bath and get crushed to a pulp.
You'd have to be a bona fide idiot.
Waste of space if you ask me.
Yes, well, fortunately, we have had none of that.
So if there's no further questions...
He's gonna put on some music?
What about that guy?
That's fucking disgusting.
What happened to your calling?
I should call.
Something about work.
What happened?
Hey, what happened to the calling?
Looks like a little deep red.
A little deeper than usual.
You know what's the funniest part about that?
I throw in a wrench.
Everybody screams.
I throw a person in there who screams and makes way more noise.
Nobody gives a shit.
Have to be a bona fide idiot.
That was fucking awesome.
Remember, this is fucked up.
It's a hit man.
You kill people and you grind them up and you throw them off the ocean and shit.
This is not Yoshi's Woolly World.
This is Hitman.
You grind people up and do it into like a meat grinder.
Oh, I just tried to close the door on him.
Well, this motherfucker's right here.
Can I like throw that guy in the meat grinder?
Is he in the barrel?
To make sure the wine is good, he stays in there?
He is what makes it so delicious?
The secure wine fridge next to the barrel room contains the vineyard's most precious wines,
but the access doors which are made from ballistic glass can only be unlocked
from a terminal in the upstairs security room.
Oh, it's not a real barrel.
Ah, Ms. Burnwood.
Don Yates.
Pleased to meet you.
You come very highly recommended.
As chief of the heralds, let me be the first to say welcome aboard.
Why, thank you, Mr. Yates.
Rest assured that I will be following your every lead very closely.
Say, that reminds me.
We're about to have a little herald get together up the house.
We are.
Modest toast to celebrate my forthcoming inauguration is constant.
You are, of course, most welcome.
I believe you shall make a fine.
I believe?
Take the black.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Capital, right this way.
Into the...
Why don't you take a break, Corvo?
We're done here for now, I think.
Oh, but don't go too far.
I may still need your services later.
I'll be closer than you think.
Oh, almost forgotten.
What is it?
Please nip down to the wine cellar and tell Mr. Flowers, the sommelier,
to prep the 1945 grand paladin and bring it up to the house.
That's code.
For our special occasion.
1945 grand paladin.
That's like a bazooka.
Make sure to get the bazooka ready to fire it when they start to come into the front door.
What's going on?
Intel.
There he is.
Okay.
Intel.
Mr. Flowers, Mr. Yates wants the 1945 grand paladin brought up to the house.
I have my orders.
Special occasion.
You have to follow.
Have the ghosts of Jesus, John Lennon, and Eva Perrone unexpectedly come for dinner?
What could possibly be so special?
Above your clearance, Flowers.
Just fetch it already.
Fine.
What's the passcode again?
Last year of World War II.
If you have to look it up, shame on you.
Last year of...1945? 1946?
Yates has invited the heralds to a small gathering in his wine cellar,
celebration of his upcoming inauguration as the new constant.
Likely, Yates wants to make a good impression with his future team,
but he hadn't expected the team to include Diana Burnwood.
That's me.
Disguise yourself as a sommelier.
How do I get in there?
Wait.
Security camera.
Can I take a photo of it?
Can I open this somehow?
Shoot the glass.
I'm not gonna shoot the fucking glass.
Punch the glass.
Can I go in here?
Turn the tap.
Tap on the glass.
No, that's not gonna work.
Can I do something with this?
Can I open it like this?
No.
Nothing I can do about this.
Is there a place I can go?
Maybe I should just like...
Hold on.
Maybe I should just tap on the glass.
What's the worst that could happen?
I like drop a bottle and they come and say, what's wrong?
I'm gonna tap on the glass.
That's a bomb!
I thought that was a coin.
I thought it was a coin.
Oops.
Let me take a piss.
I'll be right back.
Goku?
Well, let me ask you a question, Goku.
I can't do it.
I just ate food.
I can't.
Hold on.
Well, I can't believe it, Goku.
No, I just had like a piece of beef jerky.
So like it's kind of still going down.
I can't do it.
I need full empty throat to be able to do that.
I kind of sound like a little different.
It's because like the idea...
I had two beef jerky sticks and they're still going down.
I need full complete empty pathway.
I'm like crying.
Reality.
Cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry.
Can I just like cry on stream with like a full cam
and just wait for somebody to be like, what's going on?
Just get like water droplets like to wet my fingers
and like make sure like tears are coming down.
Just sit there and be going, sure.
That's like kind of fucked up.
I don't want to do that.
What happened?
Oh, okay.
1709.
Shave your head.
I'm not...
No, I have it for now and it's staying here until it's gone.
All right.
I don't want to be on camera.
Hold on.
Let me do the thing where I sit down at the computer
and I like go like this.
Okay.
I have really like watery eyes just in general.
So if you notice, I go like this a lot.
And like so if I get like shot from this direction,
and I'm like kind of doing hard blinks with my eyes
because they're watery.
Like that's why I didn't see that guy.
A lot of people when you go like, oh, how did you not see that?
I probably went like this.
I was probably looking this way and I went...
And somebody showed up right there, right there.
And I didn't see them and they disappeared.
I have really watery eyes.
I just have very...
All right.
I need to go upstairs.
What's this?
I'm not trespassing.
I'm like I'm allowed to be here.
Anything in this room I can...
Oh, wait.
This poison.
Binary worker's key.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
And a tier one access dongle.
Just sitting out here.
Key to unlock doors and machinery on the winery production floor.
Cool.
PLT sandwich.
What did he just do?
Poison that?
I guess I could disguise as one of these guys.
Use, sell.
Should I disguise as one of them?
Maybe I'll need the outfit.
I just added some sugar.
I gotta distract him.
I could go for some mate right now.
Somebody said that.
Mate?
Mate.
Okay.
Let's distract.
Let's distract them both.
What?
I'm just looking back here.
I'm all right.
I appreciate your concern.
You messed up your spine?
Gamer neck.
I'm all right.
Oh, you don't like that either.
I mean, I'm trying to pause it at the...
I'm trying to...
I'm doing that every time.
And I thought it might get old at this point.
But it hasn't.
I don't...
You know what I mean?
It still is like funny to me.
I mean, I could do that.
This is just...
This is tried and true.
Here's the tried...
Wait, I have grapes.
Yeah.
This is tried and true.
I'm gonna go with tried and true.
This is how I play.
I throw something to cause a distraction.
And then they both turn around.
They both go over there.
And then I'm gonna poison.
Like, yep.
It's a pretty cool Halloween drink.
In fact, I'm 95% certain that...
That was...
It was in the Doc...
What?
Doctor Dreadful commercial.
I have bubbling disgusting bruise.
Yeah.
And I drank it.
You can even eat brains in my Dr. Dreadful kid science kit.
You know, I wanted to do Dr. Dreadful on stream.
But holy shit, it's rare as absolute fuck.
They don't make that shit really anymore.
And it's hard to find.
Wait, get him now.
Get him right now.
Get him now.
No, I wanted to choke him.
I wanted to choke him.
I wanted to choke...
Did anybody hear that?
No, good.
Where can I put him when no one's gonna see him?
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Okay.
All right.
Where can I put him that no one will see him?
There's a guy right here.
Oh, come on.
Just grind this guy.
You tell me you want me to drag this guy all the way to the grape crusher and crush him.
He's gonna be on camera.
Oh, shit.
I need to be quiet.
I need to do it tactically.
God damn it.
Fine.
I'll do it fucking tactically.
Just kill a guy near the grinder.
Let me try this one more time.
Isn't the grinder really far away?
Grinder is not close.
It's very far away.
It's over there.
Now, hold on.
It's the fucking video camera.
Oh, it's this guy.
Whatever.
Who is looking at this?
You're ignoring the link.
Yeah, I am.
I am ignoring the link.
You're right.
And I'm gonna continue to do so.
Third time's the charm.
If I don't get it this time, I'm just gonna move on.
I have to distract everybody somehow.
Come on out here.
Okay.
I have my special save point right here.
Put him down.
Give me a coin.
All right.
That's like a fuse cell.
Let me like throw it or something.
I have like a bottle.
Let's throw the bottle over here.
He's dead.
I got him.
Just pretend I ground him up in the grape grinder.
Does Jerma look down at his keys?
It's killing me.
Yes.
Just grind up everybody.
I think I want to do like a crazy guy run
where everybody gets put in the meat grinder.
I have a save over there, right?
All right.
I do.
Not right now, but eventually.
When I finish this mission, I want to go back to that save file.
I want to just put like 50 people into the grinder.
I want to put the whole...
I want to put the entire mission in the grinder.
I want to put every enemy into the meat grinder.
Oh, that's going to take a long time.
All right.
I need to go down this way to disguise as the sommelier.
And links.
Maybe.
Disable the security.
Enable alarm, temperature controls, ventilator...
All right.
Disable security doors.
Go down.
Down, down, down, down.
Go down, down, down, down.
Hurry.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm trespassing.
I'm a security guard.
And we look pretty good for 53.
That's how old my dad is.
Thanks.
I'm going to need these.
Why do I feel like these have paints?
The Endo Yates Pinot Noir.
Inspired by wines from the Au Valley.
Medium bodied and fruit forward with an aroma of cherries and raspberry.
Not their most popular.
This one's not good.
I don't...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't throw the Malbec.
You throw the Pinot out of here.
You hold on to the Malbec.
Now disable the lasers.
Can I hide this guy somewhere?
Oh, shit.
They're coming back.
I thought this was a disguise as water.
All right.
Nine...
Was it 1945?
1946?
1945.
Can't even read this.
Wait, this is like the...
This is the super bottle.
All right.
Put them both in here.
Right?
We're going to hide these guys.
I don't think anybody comes in here.
I need that.
Drop the shotgun.
The zombie here has a shotgun.
Does it matter if the zombie here has a shotgun?
Does it?
Fine.
What else is illegal?
I mean, this is illegal, but whatever.
All right, let's go.
1945 Grand Paladin.
Chat, shut the fuck up about the pistol.
What?
I'm going to get searched.
Oh, I can't wait till we pour the...
Wait, he's going to know.
Doesn't he know his own sommelier?
Ah, you're a lot bald.
Balder than you were five to ten minutes ago.
And you have a different voice.
And you're jacked.
I told you that was going to happen.
Come on.
Right.
I told you this shit was going to happen.
Go get the pistol.
I'm about to get patted down.
What?
Why did I not kill this guy?
You both just did like a dance routine.
All right, I guess I'll hide it in the trash.
I guess I'll hide it in a trash can.
Like I passed a reflex save.
Passed a reflex save.
Oh, well, the good thing is the trash can here.
Won't this explode?
I can't place that.
I can't put this down.
I have to put...
I have to throw it somewhere where no one's going to touch it.
I have to put it somewhere where no one is going to walk by it.
It's proximity.
I know, but I can't have it on me.
Gently place an item down.
You can.
Yeah, but somebody's going to walk by here.
It's fucking armed.
Okay.
Just pat me down for the love of God.
Whatever.
Let's go.
What does the word proximity mean?
It means near.
When you go near it.
Around.
In an area.
I know.
But what am I supposed to do with it?
If it arms if I put it on the ground?
No matter what I do.
And it's illegal!
So here's the deal, Flowers.
Here's the deal.
The boss is having a powwow with some employees, and discretion is the name of the game.
I'm sure you figured that out already, you being a scholar and all.
Don't discuss, disclose, or hell even contemplate what goes down.
Just set your mind to wool-gathering mode.
You think you can do that for me, Flowers?
Worry not, Mr. Cortezar.
I'm the very soul of discretion.
Good man.
Just waiting for someone to walk over there.
1080 is struggling, MonkaS.
It is.
I don't know why we're looking clear in an enclosed building.
Why am I eye twitching?
I'll place the wine on the table.
I'll pour it.
Deca-
Pardon me, your majesty.
It's considered the heralds the unspoken heroes of Providence.
He ain't okay.
I need to poison this.
I have to poison the wine.
I need to poison the wine.
I need to poison-
I need to poison the wine!
Wait a minute.
I have always-
Ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Flowers, our resident sommelier.
Flowers.
I believe he has brought us something-
Oh shit!
Quite special.
Hello sir, how's your wine?
Do you want to-
I have to educate us, Mr. Flowers.
No, no, put the shitty one on the table.
Put the shitty one on the table.
I'm gonna put the really shitty one on the table.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not the good one.
I'm gonna put the terrible one on the table.
That everybody hates.
Which one was it?
It was their, uh-
Was it the-
It was the Pinot, right?
Was the Pinot the one that they don't like?
It's the blue one, yep.
Nobody likes the Pinot.
Whatever, just-
Don't go over there and look.
Good, frisk me.
Don't go over there and look at anything, please.
Go.
No, don't walk over there.
I want that ax-
So bad, you have no idea.
So here's the deal, Flower.
It's illegal, I can't.
You being a scholar and all.
Don't discuss, disclose, or help-
Okay, where's the Pinot?
Even contemplate what goes down.
Just set your mind to-
This is the shitty one.
They're all gonna be like-
Pfft, ugh!
You can do that for me, Flowers.
To court as our very soul of discretion.
Good man.
And then smash the other one on the table.
Spill it.
We're gonna do like the Mr. Bean routine.
Where he like breaks the expensive bottle of alcohol or something.
Everyone like is staring at him.
Go on, place the wine on the table.
All right, I have to do the Mr. Bean routine.
I do.
Do not save over that one, stupid idiot.
Here we go.
Hello.
Wait a minute, I need-
I need this to play a few times.
It was so fucking loud, it hurt.
I need- I need to play this.
I need to get this recorded.
Will this pick up through here?
I need to get this saved.
Because I can't- I can't alt-tab and click it.
How do we try to pull that through?
Can I pull that through?
Take your own laugh track.
Dominic, I could.
That's just a roomful of weird people.
No, that's a roomful-
No, no, that doesn't work.
That doesn't work.
That doesn't work out.
That's a roomful of weird people.
I have to-
I gotta give this 30 more seconds to figure this out.
How am I gonna do this?
Fuck, I need a soundboard.
I need a laugh track soundboard
that I can put on this fucking thing.
Wait, I think I got it.
Where's my XLR?
Sampler!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I think I got it.
It's not gonna work.
Sampler enabled.
Nah, I can't alt-tab.
It will-
I can't-
I have to like load it into-
It had to have already been prepared,
which it wasn't.
Scary fucking eyes.
Just do the-
Just do the laughs already.
You will need some boos too.
If I do this,
you let me know if it pulls through here.
Let me just do-
Let me try something really quick.
I'm gonna give this a minute.
I think it's worth it.
Routing.
Here we go.
If I do this-
Broadcast mix needs to be this.
Got it.
Here we go.
It was too long, wait.
Really?
No, what the fuck?
Why?
One minute-
Hello?
What the fuck?
Why won't it save it?
Hold on, I have an idea.
I think I have to make a noise.
Boons.
It will-
It won't do it, nevermind.
Let's go.
Decrease-
I'm so-
I'm so upset.
The brain to the body and limbs of our-
I'm upset.
I had to like have that prepared like two hours ago.
All right.
What's the shitty one?
This one.
Great organization.
Hey there!
Hey!
What's wrong with you, man?
Ah, ladies and gentlemen.
The ten-
Mr. Flowers.
Our resident sommelier.
i believe he has brought us something quite special perhaps you will educate us mr flowers
present as the sommelier this is the 1945 grand five bottles in existence people are gonna hate
it is legendary like your inventory unicorn the year was hot mine's super concentrated
what are you talking thanks to hail and frost what i actually put the right one in what the
production was small be 300 bottles you have to the vineyard was bombed during the closing
days of world war ii only a single crate survived it is said to have amazingly complex aromas with
long god damn it man i was trying to break them on the table well now i know i can do that
okay everybody relax everybody relax everybody relax nobody gets up if i act like a psycho and
just break like 10 bottles on the table body and limbs of our great organization ah ladies and
gentlemen mr flowers our resident sommelier i believe he has brought us something
quite special perhaps you will educate us mr flowers this is the 1945 grand one of only five
bottles in existence the vintage is legendary is that the proverbial unicorn wine the year was
wine super concentrated thanks to hail and frost the production was small only 300 ever produced
when the vineyard was bombed
it's playing it's like just playing chicken i i'm trying to get them just all on the table
but sometimes the curse would just to somebody's head
all right last time i'm gonna fucking do this i promise i want it to be covered in
fucking glass and wine and shit throw the good one throw the good one throw the good one
all right did i put it down i put it down on the table already this is the 1945 only five bottles
in existence
the production was small only 300 bottles were ever produced the vineyard was bombed during the
closing days of world war two only a single crate survived it is said to have amazingly
perfect long savory layers of fruit and spice flavor and enjoy wonderful thank you mr flowers
feel free to stick around in case our guests have questions this wine was gifted to me by the ark
society an acknowledgement of my firm legal services and by the way uh this is where they
come from these grapes
we are but a few and yet together we are unstoppable because we stand united my friends
loyalty is everything which is why we cannot allow traders into our ranks
ah yes here it comes this woman has waste bloody war on us more than a dozen heralds and operatives
your colleagues and clients my friend ken morgan not to mention the partners themselves is he gonna
press a doctor evil button and one something to fly back benefactors no mistake this woman's hands
are soaked in blood our blood and arthur edwards the new supreme head of providence is handing her
the keys to the kingdom now does that seem right to you my friends does that sound like loyalty
oh i agree yes perhaps edwards you fucking weirdo when he sees it perhaps oh you want
to see a magic drink come on over here i'm gonna make this pencil disappear i dare say i am in the
lead don you're lying of course which only proves my point you're gonna be trusted miss burnwood
this woman will be our downfall that is unless we take matters into our own hands
you are heralds sworn to protect providence against all threats including inside ones
i have devised a plan together we can make it work but you have to decide now my friends
are you with me i think you jumped the gun a little
you didn't wait for the cheese to come out that's when you should have
i don't know i scored miss burnwood to my office hey that's my friend you fucking asshole don't
fuck with me all my friends ever i have to watch the whole thing again sorry i just flew off the
handle there oh shit we have to watch the whole thing sorry wait saved it did it actually just
save right there oh auto saved they knew you would do it i scored miss burnwood i can't help it
i can't fucking do it this is like you give i can't play hitman normally i never would be able to
i scored miss burnwood to my up it's like if a pigeon could play video games
why him because he was the closest i scored miss burnwood to my up move it let's go
i'm warning you yes this will not go your way it's not going to go the way that you think
yes yes yes i agree yes a toast then in her honor
savor the taste because you never will again and let me remind you we are in this together one
goes down we all go down here's to loyalty uh that sounds like a house of cards that's usually not
the way things should be run get them hey there sorry time limit remember flowers you never saw
that's a good one holy shit nice all right let me in they don't even care that i'm gonna unlock
this door they don't even care that i'm doing this all right where's where's diana you're supposed
to poison them all he's your target kill him glass him glass him throw him germa the target
i have to get to diana wait i have 10 minutes to kill him yes what are they searching for no
save diana get to diana oh will you shit new costume let's go come here come here come here
all right come here come here come here you know what it's okay that's what you have the saves
coming for that's why you do what you do last light him please germa you have to focus you can't
focus for more than five minutes you're a muppet i can't take it anymore only half of what you said
was true and i'd be and i'm i'm hidden in here right what is over what is that cheers that's
just i gotta get rid of this guy bring on the germa muppet if you're looking for top 10 hitman
gameplay this is the channel to watch don't leave stay here don't leave my channel i'm gonna do very
well don't click the x stay and name another channel you'll see that name another channel
you'll see that you just you're not going to i just have to be honest like you're not gonna
find a channel that can do that not one channel will be able to do what i just did all right we're
gonna go up save it all right how much time do i have six minutes all right i'm i'm gonna i can
go in here now let's go up to diana i need a staircase over here i have got plenty of time
to get to diana and again i have to i have to reference the census here literally 13 percent
of people that were censor sized they don't want to see me play the game the normal way we have a
sensor sizer i'm uncensored we'll come down and look at it already that guy's not gonna look
behind right don't look behind you don't look behind you he's looking behind him stay there
kill him he's seeing your face i don't care he's not getting up i have he's not as long as he
doesn't get up in five minutes i'll be fine what about the umbrella that's a good call hi i made
it take out the top floor guards okay one more guy over here holy shit that was close hills
lethal poison oh you're outside okay the house is haunted poison the glass of red wine with a
lethal point with a lethal poison he's gonna sit there and he's gonna drink out of it probably
all right i'm here diana i was beginning to worry where are you no listen up 47 yates will be here
shortly he'll have his thug cortisol do his dirty work but he won't pass up on the chance for a good
gloat and a monologue so private space kill room exactly we won't get another shot at this
now sit down and blend in when i provide a distraction you just be ready to move
fuck distract him go distract him distract him you have to distract him distract him distract this
guy distract him don't go over the fucking railing don't pimp over the railing don't roll off stay
there hold on where how hold on i got so distracted this it was just right here right 1758 right here
why did you just stand there because i knew i was gonna reload and just do it again you didn't need
to do that i thought you were slick buddy what a surprise did you fuck it all up all right poison
what am i gonna poison there's only one guy to kill then they come up let me deal with this first
was uh should i poison the glass kill him with the chandelier i could kill i could is the poison
release the ladder what why does this guy have like a booby-trapped house
a poisoned glass there's a battle axe on the wall hold on let me wait a minute calendar on a 2021
calendar in the eighth house our date has been circled with the world's crystal anniversary
scribbled alongside kill him with the calendar all right now i i got a minute here i can i'm
just gonna drop the chandelier on him like hit me in one right poison the glass i'm just gonna
poison the wine here this is definitely you poison this battle axe battle axe you use the battle axe
you're gonna get the fucking battle axe no get the battle axe go into the attic into the attic
attic attic attic what's up here oh my god there's a sniper rifle here cannon balls
wait can i shoot a cannon at him bag of gunpowder broadsword where's the cannon i can shoot at him
just no scope him with the rifle we're gonna have to kill this guy a few different ways where's the
cannon out in front of the house there's a cannon holy shit there's a cannon right there all right
i'm gonna go arm the cannon i'm gonna shoot him with a cannon when he comes over here
and i is this gonna work nice thinking dude yeah let me see can i even do this i drop down not
loaded not loaded yes it is load gunpowder um so i are they gonna know it's me i'm gonna be sitting
here holding a string ready to pull the cannon when he walks up i'm thinking i know i did it
okay well let's let's go i'm gonna talk to diana and i'm gonna run back out there and we shoot him
with a fucking cannon i was beginning to worry kill room
corva what pick up your damn phone
just tell me one thing before we part ways why me why you why would edwards trust
i blew it with the cannon so i'm gonna just do whatever i'm gonna do this
wait does he maybe he tries to escape in his car wait what if he tries to run away in his car
i was beginning to worry hide the body no listen up 47 yates will be here shortly
don't have his thug quarters i'll do his dirty work pass up on the chance for a good move so
private space kill room decal exactly we won't get another shot at this sit down
when i provide a distraction you just be ready to move is that everybody okay here he comes i'm
gonna save it right here sit down and blend in i'm holding i'm just sitting like holding a gun
make a little hand shot first we discussed staged accident courtesan will bring the package
get it done oh fuck i'm blowing it i saved it come on just connect to the internet for the
love of god miss bern you rolled out the red carpet just for me you shouldn't have so confident
even in defeat i suppose you're not used to danger always safe behind your screens
just tell me one thing before we part way why me why i would edwards trust you
it will keep me wait is diana dead oh she is now oh well done 47
better get rid of the body won't be long before they come looking when you're done
meet me on the dance floor why are you alive why are you oh he's still alive that's impossible
that's literally impossible right in the fucking head no stop moving around what happened no way
that's impossible that's this is not possible damn it fucking get it right there you're dead
how did i get the last time fucking moving i shot her directly in the fucking head
his mouse pad is seven feet long you rolled out the red carpet just for me okay but what does
she do you shouldn't have so confident even in defeat what should i do you're always safe behind
your dpi don't tell me what to do just tell me one thing before we why me why why trust you
it will keep me awake at night tonight enter full i get up four times to piss as it is
oh it's simple really edwards is proud he considers himself the cleverest man alive
and yet we tricked him on aisle of scale and it's eating him up he needs to win full unequivocal
victory my recruitment was just the feather in his cap by the way you write about one thing
it was me stabbing the stomach yeah i'm all stabbing the stomach right in the stomach got him
what are you gonna say now turns out this woman what are you gonna say now if it's any consolation
don what are you doing you asshole stand there shoot her and i will make it my mission to tear
down providence brick finish it well done 47 better get rid of the body won't be long before
they come looking brick by brick when you're done meet me on the dance floor oh and dress
appropriate i will dress appropriately i'm gonna i'm gonna shoot her with the cannon i have to
she's already down there how'd she get down there that fast disguise yourself appropriately i think
i am already aren't i sniper i might not disguise appropriately oh i need his suit got it and that's
another sniper he was it was fucking waiting for me on the roof that shit's not happening
how do i get down i'm supposed to get out of here out the front door can't like drop why can i not
drop down leave i i can't drop down was somebody down there on the computer you have to drop the
sniper rifle drop the sniper rifle oh fuck okay is that what's going on did i kill him that's the
same lawyer from the other level all right i'm up getting out getting out oh no it's okay all right
that's okay this moon walked off the roof oh i got the shortcut to a back door okay i'm not
trespassing anymore i'm done can you let me in course i believe good anakin good i can't
but i want to use the cannon oh this is where we dance this is where we dance local boomer can't
find exit i'm right here diana look what i swiped don't i hate this you're just taking me out of the
game you're taking me out of my immersion i want to break my own immersion okay i want to be playing
hitman put a chef costume on and like throw the wine bottle at the guy's head while i play a laugh
track let me do my own immersion breaking i don't want you to do it for me all right let's resist
the temptation i know it's done now that's cold 47 what the fuck are you i why edwards finds you
hold seven he is untraceable and he never lets you forget it he is cocky and that will be his
downfall what's the plan too many eyes meet me at the olive grove at sunset one last tango 47
maybe at the old have gotten 47 32 000 xp doesn't matter i got i got a zero at least i'm leveling
up i let me ask you a question though okay without the non-target kill penalty of being 50 000
what is a decent mission score for a hitman level what is it 150k is good 100k is good
100k 60k plus 100k okay so what did i get 34 000 50k is decent 100k is great okay
if the game minimum is all right oh i got like a hot heat gun started the vineyard started the
parking lot the boat house the bathroom okay cool all right i'm gonna turn cam off this is
this is like one of the final cutscenes right this is the last level this is it this is the
final level of the game what play is diana that'd be kind of cool but how did you know
your deal that kind of power always comes with a price what's yours i think you know
oh yeah it was a setup i am sorry this is a necessary evil have you done the heat gun
transfers by touch see edwards learns by his mistakes 47 and as you've clearly demonstrated
brute force is futile it had to be me it was the only way to get this class my family i know what
you did after all these years i finally know sorry you didn't have a choice i did providence
used you but i'm no better all i saw was a blank slate a weapon to wield this is when i put my
hand up and start shaking my fist and the crowd starts screaming hulk hogan starts to get on one
knee the ultimate warriors just towering over him the power he gains it shaking his fist back
and forth bye agent you're telling me to shut up you care about the you care about the storyline
here we just saw it this is important we care about feet what you guys are crazy this is
untouchable briefing for untouchable but is this going to be like a weird i'm in a dream sequence
don't forget about the wine crusher save file i won't are you still here still clinging on
to your self-image agent 47 the apex predator always hiding behind the headlines i remember
this this is the first game was perfection its own justification or a willful distraction
i remember this level built contract by contract to shield you from the uncomfortable truth
i remember this level you're exactly the tool they bred you to be i remember this level
i remember that one i remember that guy i remember that dj i remember that lady how could you
possibly function on your own you never even had a name until i gave you one that's him burnwood
never ceases to surprise me you really are a most singular individual and to think she wanted me to
put you down lucky for you i never throw away anything useful prepare the serum forgetting's
not so bad you've done it before you may see it all in me a bad dream what's he doing is he still
looking at us i'm afraid so poor sap just won't accept his days are done perhaps i should take
him out to the woods and set him free oh it's a classic he was a loyal tool but everything goes
the way of the horse and cart eventually must be me up there are you the toxins are playing into
your fears don't let them why is this guy my opium on go to get your head straight she wants
me dead she has every right to after what we did but that's not what is really going on she chose
power in the end she was just like them no she found a way to turn edwards own cleverness against
him the rest is up to you i don't know how you do know diana once you dispose of edwards i will
dismantle providence from the top down it will finally be over all you have to do is embrace the
past i'm diana's son no i'm not i killed everybody in her whole family okay how did you come to that
conclusion eliminate arthur edwards providence members may be eliminated really well i wanted
to come in here like cough but we have tools all right i'm gonna really freak this guy out watch
this ready this is impossible right why is the guy so slow yeah he's cleaning it they actually
clean it i'm awake by the way look at that key card now by the way all providence members can
be eliminated would you look at that face cam face cam where is arthur oh open after no blend
in as a doctor for you this thing has combined tuning okay right now the serum it rains long
and short term memory banks wholesale but in a couple of cycles we'll be able to isolate the
effect individual memories imagine if you could pluck out childhood traumas ugly breakups combat
jim carrey movie about this
salmon i don't know blank slater zine the ether serum a technical report on ether's new memory
repressing neural inhibitor serum the formula is reverse engineered and enhanced by a much
older prototype created at the institute for human betterment in romania in the 1980s an
antidote produced at ether's rnd site in johannesburg was stolen by lucas gray during his
assault on the facility i don't care jim was it it always starts like this gps microwaves duct tape
this serum will eventually improve lives i've got to believe that tell that to the poor sob in the
rear car he's a providence members when i want to forget something i rely on my good old pal
mr al khal there's a providence members in there they need to die right oh fuck they're coming this
way oh my god out get out out out out out out i don't know the button i don't know what it is
1979 crowbar this kid just just this kid just picked up a crowbar it just picked up a fucking
crowbar oh my god hey i just want to let everybody in here know this kid just picked up a crowbar
you're a fucking providence member where the crowbar go did it break on his head
wait what it broke on his head well whatever i can't leave i need that crowbar well shit
i don't know it's gonna break we need to find a catchy name for it for when we go commercial
figure this thing has commercial applications who'd want to have their minds wiped not wiped
obviously but that's mind wiping okay right now the serum erases 1979
do a fart sound sure we're on a train i mean i i have to get rid of i have to throw them out
very important this serum will eventually improve
huh where you're gonna go run that way no the other way run the other way run the other way
run the other way run i wish you could see wait i want that uh should i disguise as a doctor or
disguise as him probably him right it's a security guard now where the hell are we going mall cop
okay i gotta hang on the ledge this seems dangerous this is dangerous what the fuck just
happened what's going on what's going on right now walking on the this is a little bizarre
i guess i'm gonna keep going no what was this i climbed that can i get like am i gonna get hit
the head by like a fucking highway sign okay rt dude oh that i that just blew by my head
that went that was very close what is going on in there at least valve valve is there a valve i can
get where's this valve valve in here right unlock cabinet what the fuck oh i okay turn it on i haven't
saved it in like five seconds big mistake there's a shitload of people in here first drop a grenade
can't get hit by it you cannot get hit by those that should have hit me right in the fucking
groin you cannot get hit by these i took that right in the stomach does it will it kill me
i don't think you can die by this you're freezing i'm freezing to death that's what's killing me
that's that's what kills me the hell am i you would have been split in half i know
i would be in the stratosphere right now just skip it i don't even need to fight those guys
why would i fight them all right wait a minute a can of soda we've got that's it just a can of
soda can't jump over this he's freezing fuck get in the ether corporation bought this train
for sample backup storage but since the bombing of there aren't guys asleep in jehannesburg
they're refitting the cars as a mobile field lab this used to be some kind of cage shoot them
you have a gun shoot them missile launch control center no no that's not giving me a bad rating
appears to have been the hq of janus old war spy master apparently his crust was on the front car
before no it won't it won't well no it's not gonna give me a bad rating how does this guy not hear
that i got a body on the ground i'm moving in holy crap holy crap all right let me let me
investigate a little hold on confidence elite guard or thing and there's a fucking tactical
shotgun right here oh man oh man tactical shotgun playing cards in here wait so it is
i'm i a can of soda i almost had a santa coda a santa coda go pick up the soap pick up the soap
pick up the soap go back and kill the other guys i was too late they're so far back nothing wait
this is a secret door locked from the other side huh gentlemen how are we i mean am i just gonna
do am i just there's a muffin here pretty cool okay save the game oh it's been auto saving isn't
it i don't have i could i can't unlock the door who had keys which one of you guys had keys on them
somebody had a key not you not you who had a key all the way back on the table
didn't me all the way back on the table what did i miss it where is it it's not highlighting
look it's tiny the thing is a fucking tiny little thing oh shit fuse box now we're gonna work it in
at night time in the dark don't miss that key can i like pull somebody out of here snap his neck
all right let's go oh so i got oh sure why not this is fun say what i'm gonna pick that up
out of bullets he's a helmet on okay i got him all right let's go why do i feel like this train is a
mile long this this train is huge another key just hanging out so didn't i pick one up it's not that
key okay rusty old nail all right get get get out get out get out get out get out get me out get me
out get me out in the window climb in the window please in the window in the window in the window
we're good rusty a tetanus weapon i try it looks the same behind the bar i'm gonna stab somebody in
the neck romania from zagreb to irkutsk isn't that risky what border inspections they use a system of
decommissioned rail lines and pay the local governments to look the other way it's been
like that since the cold war hey commando hold up how can i use it don't try anything stupid sir
i can't use it
target is fist fighting let's shoot him you know what i'm just i'm just gonna run what's the point
i'm just like wait i'm already disguised as this person let me say finally finally finally
finally five wait this is what i was supposed to do i'm i thought i was supposed to be sneaky
oh my god okay holy shit i thought i was supposed to be sneaky i'm picking up like
frag grenades unlimited ammo free guns walk from the other side when i get over there
yeah come on okay go all right i'm just i'm gonna shoot people i guess rusty nail finally
finally finally finally wait that's a it didn't explode hey uh oh here comes this is sometimes
how i feel i feel when i'm like call of duty you just know there's like five people and you're
just gonna go like hello that gun all right take take take take take take take take take take
take everything take all the ammo all the guns everything take take take take take take take
take take take take take take take take take all right reload take take take take take take take
take left someone alive what who who crusty crowbar okay i'm gonna use i'm much better i'm
much better i'm good with the pistol i'm much better with the pistol i really am
that's i'm dead serious guys aiming a fucking gun don't shoot me in the head don't shoot me in the
head don't shoot me in the head
ah my eyes shoot him shoot what snap his fucking neck quick
clean oh a new jacket stop these agents wait are these bad guys this is not somebody doing this
right i'm supposed to do this right yeah eliminated five xp okay what is it he's gone
wait is there a key you say what a shot i need somebody to tell uh the all right i missed just
you're gonna stay alive at least someone has to stay alive that person's not gonna stay at that i
just killed that person oh it's you 47 it's really nice to see you again i guess you made it all the
way to the front of the train i'm gonna give you a choice i don't suppose there's any point calling
for help seems i brought this on myself well played miss burnwood do you really think she'll
be able to resist all that power this is not how people work she rejects the power not the
responsibility a noble idea but i thought there was another 47 over there trying to kill me
i trust you already know what this is why not simply take it embrace who you were always
meant to be that never again well i had to try go on then do your thing at least i die knowing
who i am should i give him the super serum yeah let's sure what are you doing
no this is what it means to lose everything you're making a mistake it's mine to make
what is that what does that thing do forgive me i seem to have uh what were we talking about don't
worry we were done i just get the good ending can't wait till he goes like yes yes yes
credits roll nightmare fuel completed new deal i don't want to see a new deal it looks like new
deal reload the last save file and kill one person only and one billion is wiped from the dead new
deal finish the game twice oh give me off screen it's been a long time agent 47 that's not who i
am anymore the name is the name's greg it's greg 47 v o r t i e z e v e n i choose this path because
i can there will always be people like them so there will always be people like us no one is
untouchable it's good to be back oh all right the smile hitman 3 cool very cool button masher
whoa i got 94 000 points that's the best i've ever had that's 100k somebody's 100k was good
that's the first time i've ever had more than zero points holy shit whoa i got three stars
no recordings no body's bond and the objective complete nice out of the lab cool okay cool that
was cool what happens now it's the same thing it's the same thing is it new deal same thing
inject yourself with the serum just take the serum grind xp take the serum myself oh wait hold on can
let's stop the train just wait hold it and wait hold the serum and wait second thoughts perhaps
we understand each other after all i have to wait 47 seconds he was haunted by his humanity freedom
from choice is also freedom everything is so much simpler in black and white thank you my friend i
will take care of you now all will be well wake up wake up my friend it's the dawn of a new day
and you have things to do how does that change how does that change the ending that's the that's it
you just wake up on a weird bed that was the start of hitman 1 what that's the start of hitman 1
so wait is that is that the true ending yeah i have played all of them i haven't played hitman 1
since i was probably like 17 like 18 or something it's been a long time i can prove that i played
the original hitman 1 because remember the mansion level with the that lady ran up the stairs it was
a mansion and it would be uh they they were they were speaking they weren't speaking english what
were they saying they ran up the stairs and like you you have to shoot the lady going upstairs
that's absolution no it's not no no no no no that's all the games that's most hitman games well a
lady running up the stairs not speaking english and you push her down the stairs i mean i guess
you could do that in all of them some i but i mean this is the whatever all right well i'm just
going to grind up a bunch of people now never touch this fucking franchise again well guess
what it's over they're not making any more hitman games the trilogy of assassination
is over you're never going to see me play this again until hitman
how do i get her to move i'll get her she's like freaking out just walk in there please
walk in walk in walk in walk in diana diana walk in
shoot her in push her i couldn't push her just shoot her
interesting are those cooling sockets they are indeed
the cooling system allows us to fine tune the entire process temperature humidity levels didn't
go up it's quite simple from the state of the yard why make you how did i get her to go up
go behind her when you shoot she'll back away from you just stand still don't move i kind of
blocked her right was i blocking her so stand still interesting are those cooling sockets they
are indeed so you will insist him allows us to fine tune the entire process temperature humidity
levels etc our goal here push button yeah i couldn't push her when she was standing up there
okay do i have to let me try to stand over there and we're just fucking around now the stream is
pretty much over we're just messing we're just hanging up we're never gonna get it how did i
get it again it's like a way i think i have to if i move like over here maybe she'll i'll block
her and she'll move up there are those cooling sockets save it like right here so i can reload it
like a thousand times they are indeed signora cooling system allows us to fine tune the entire
process don't know it doesn't work i got lucky and i blew it you ruined it i didn't move the
last time i tried it system allows us to fine tune the entire process temperature humidity levels
didn't work the last time when i stood still
i didn't move the last time i reloaded it what are you talking about ron's dead
cooling system allows us to fine tune the entire process
temperature humidity levels etc oh well
our goal here at pineda yates it's quite simple from the state of the art winemaking facility
to our carefully nurtured gravestock handpicked with loving care we look what
i'm gonna add some special ingredients okay i'll add some extra wine
a little bit of that a little bit of uh a little bit of metal
large fermentation tanks constructed from solid french oak and each contain up to 500 gallons of
interesting are those cooling something they are indeed
ah yes their large fermentation tanks are constructed from solid french oak i think this
could use a little bit of spice i gotta go stand up here okay here we go it's time to do the thing
i wanted to do the whole time you threw that good for you all right here's what we're gonna do um
just let everybody know the stream is the stream is over i'm gonna i'm gonna kill everybody in the
room we're gonna grind everybody in the room just to let everybody know that's what's happening
now that's what's going on humidity levels etc our goal here at pineda yates it's quite simple
from the state of the art might as well start at the top here just broke her neck i'm turning
he shoot it out of my fucking head all right i scratchy ass beard that just threw me off
get the keys under the squisher let me i want to do this i'm this is what i want to do i'm just
gonna go for it like fucking you can't kill diana you can knock her out watch bionicle with joe
biden i can't i that's not possible fuck get everybody in here it just blew up the bottle
okay i'm gonna grind up everybody i'm sorry but fucking stupid game
very cool i love it come down here
temperature humidity levels etc stupid dumb fucking dumb fucking idiot stupid
fucking goddamn fucking game new strategy stupid fucking goddamn fucking stupid fucking game
fucking goddamn fucking idiot bro it's okay to put the catboy costume on here we go this is it
this is the one oh shit i can't save it all right and on the bad spot ketchup factory behind the
scenes do i have to do everybody in the whole that was really loud do i have to do everybody
in the level i mean that this is i don't know i don't know if i should do everybody does it have
to be everyone yes of course but what if i can't get every single person over what they said to
despawn i'm over here i'm over here what's the bad guy put them on this put them on the ground
and then activate the smasher holy shit that's a way better idea i'll just wait i'm gonna save it
we'll crush like 100 people in the ground in the in the crusher holy shit what a good idea
yeah that's an that's an incredible idea yeah let's go can i do this first
all right we're gonna do this first pretty up here hey please play pikmin i mean i could i
not right now wait maybe some other day right now i'm not gonna play it right now
i'm in the middle of doing something what do bodies can you have on screen at once
yeah the 1080 is really gonna start to struggle here he's got no reaction right now i'm just
trying to get this going you need a 3080 start doing it already um hold on we need to have
patience for this trust me the payoff will probably be worth it especially when we squish them
telling us to have patience hydraulic press them okay i'm gonna save it i'm gonna save it here i
can't even i can't save it till i'm not let me oh you okay i'm not am i still compromised
searching can't save it hold on not yet we want pikmin there we go all right let we're gonna do a
small we're gonna do a small batch first and see i just i'm curious as to uh why is that kind of
flows on i don't think i want to do this anymore this is like this is like
fucked up i don't think somebody said honey i had a long day of crossing people
at work today now smush them okay we're gonna um we're gonna move over to the other thing now
sorry honey the grind can be really tiresome crush them at once i'm gonna try that and we'll
see what but we need to put at least this is gonna take so long to get everybody into the smusher
it'll be worth it i don't where's the key forklift please forklift please
you need the key is it on the table what a laugh track on when i smush everybody
that guy just get up oh no you where are these people coming from table in the other room
that's a key oh no where's it put on the laugh track i i don't know if i want to put i don't
know it's like this is like fucked up this is i think this is too fucked up i think this is
too fucked up i'm this might be like too fucked up this is fucked up do it put a laugh track on
and do it it was your idea yeah it was this was my idea pretend this is a mr bean bit
this is charlie chaplin level humor charlie chaplin didn't crush like 50 people in a smusher
what are you talking about the ritz brothers did it they did not smush a bunch of people all right
well this guy stay down do the seinfeld theme i'm jerry i i actually i press the smusher button
and then it just crushes them all and it's like
george what are you doing george what are you thinking
i got i i bumped into it i'm not gonna smoke all of my cell phone
do you want to see and i'm the fucking i'm the fucked up guy that's like smushing the people
but somebody wrote leave a head outside the area so it smushes their head off but i'm the it's me
i'm the guy that's the crazy one all right only the people that are left in this room are going
in there that's a great idea i'm not no i just i was just curious to see if the game's engine
could handle this that i'm just testing the game's engine right now i'm not i don't think this is
cool i'm testing the video game engine i'm gonna see what how much particle spawns can happen i
don't i'm serious isn't this a tour guide he can go put him in smush him i can't even look
i can't look anymore smush him
there's no mercy here what do you mean put him in the juicer i'm oh my god i'm just don't look
just don't look all right i'm done remember they're pixels smush smush smush smush and then
needs to be a laugh track i okay i'm gonna smush him oops looks like i accidentally pushed the
button oh this is it i've been a really fun i would have why did it not do anything
skeleton she skeletor is the baby i took from rando princess adora what why did that auto play
i can't i can't alt tab and play just loop it how do i loop it how do you loop a youtube video
head out oh right click it loop i can't i can't turn it on i mean there's something in the way
it can't be an object in the way
wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait no run this way run the other way run this way
so i'm done it's over i'm told jerry no no we squished the people we squished the people
in the in the wine factory we're done i'm not no no forklift it's over now you're insane that
shit's done that's wicked fucked up no we're not going to chase people around and push them
into the squisher and squish their bodies with a laugh track i want to go in by myself
so the sooner you lose your morals the sooner it'll be easy no there you don't there there's
okay my line is was that skeletor what does that skeletor my line is smushing people like look
there i'm there's being squished i'm not walking around and like forcing people into the things
that's that's no help them make red wine nice day it's just a game germa do it no i can't do it
no that's that's too much absolutely smushed on red wine play the seinfeld theme on loop
go kill the tour guide no you monsters these people are still filming put him in a smusher
run sir here this is a rerun though snap the hey come look at this cool crusher that i found
pikmin waiting room pikmin well you're still going on about that all right that's it i'm done
we we did our we did our like insane grind up the people stuff as many people in the smusher
as possible and there's probably more you could do but i i know uh no this is not just going to
be like a mutilate bodies stream it's it's fun to do for a second but no no i'm not just going
to sit there and find other ways to smush more bodies but why not this is exactly what it's been
the whole time i've played no there's a difference between like putting somebody in the smusher to
smush them and then like grabbing as many humans as possible and smushing everybody on the level
forklift i keep seeing forklift oh hey that's what it's been a lot of fun
no i'm not forklifting anybody no i i need to put i need to i can't be this corruptible
i can't be uncorruptible i have to be uncorruptible you have to take a stand somewhere
no that's it i'll see you guys uh what are we what are we doing next i feel like there's not
much okay what else can i do now after i've smushed all the people right
in hitman at least you know how about this one i was looking for an opportunity to play
people are going to freak out over this paper mario what do you think now should i do super
paper mario thousand year door or regular paper mario mm thousand year door maybe i should do a
poll what do you think maybe i'll maybe i'll pull it let's get a poll going paper mario which one
we'll start that in a couple days in like two three days i've never played any of them by the way
i played regular uh nintendo 64 paper mario for three four hours or is it more than three
no okay well here we go what do you think oh we're not i'm not forklifting like a hundred people no
we've reached right at the peak of of psycho stream i don't want to cross the line into like
horrible stream we thought we were already dancing on that line stop using straw pole you
fucking boomer why not what's wrong with straw pole it looks like thousand year door is winning
by a very large margin a huge margin is thousand year door really that much more better of a game
than the first two i know that they're kind of there you can play either any one of them right
they're all good okay all right uh emulator earl omega low well i have a wee what was thousand
year door on was it on gamecube it was on the game all right cool all right we'll do thousand
we'll start thousand year door um on what's today's date we will start thousand year door on friday
that's what we're gonna do i will get a copy of it then i'll make it work i've been looking for
an opportunity to play it too so that's a good opportunity i'm gonna do yakuza that's a really
good question soon take a champ it's all yours you earned it to germa best streamer ever oh
that's debatable but thank you yeah that's gonna be it i'm gonna call it here i just wanted to
finish it man i'll see you guys in a few days we'll play paper mario thousand year door thanks
for watching as always have a good rest of your night as always take care of yourselves go uh
go relax a little you know you may have already been relaxing well who knows there's a music oh
do a raid yeah we we will raid today we will raid see who is live at the moment who is currently
live
raid yourself uh i'll dump you guys on joel tonight sure why not playing madness madness
i'm not gonna take a dump on a i'm not gonna dump pasta sauce sauce on a pasta that would be
too much too much pasta sauce you don't need that much you just need a little bit
center the credits oh shit did i move it i think i moved it i did yeah i moved it you're right
holy shit how did you even pick that up how did you pick that up thanks for the support everybody
thanks for the subs uh this channel sees a lot of them i just can't fucking believe it thank you
and i'll see you again in a few days take care of yourselves have a wonderful rest of your night
i'll see you guys soon see you in a few days good night goodbye take care