Okay, ladies and germs ladies and gentlemen, I'm your new warden. My name is Jerma. How you doing? Good to meet you
I want you maggots to do one very important thing for me when the cell doors open
I want you to turn around and face your door. Do not move do not make any sudden movement
So you will be shot on command
Take a few but get back in there spoon take a few more steps back in. Thank you
You are not out here cherry frenzy you have three seconds to comply three two one you are now dead
Okay tease what I want you to do here
I want you to do a very special thing for me want everybody to crouch walk over to where I'm standing right now and jumping
All right, which one are you are there? I am the one jumping right now if you can see
Okay, any funny business
Should be 2142 you were gonna be the first to go down if you keep that mouth open
We are gonna play a game of Simon says I saw a tea go around that other side
I want one of my associates to go around tea went around the side. He did. He's not coming for it. What is going on?
All right, so we're gonna play Simon says there is a team missing over on the left I want one of my so she
I can stay stay on here stay on here. No one's gonna be moving
Is somebody in a freaking helicopter over there?
All right, no, no, no, no, we're gonna keep order here
We're gonna keep order Simon says we're gonna look at those look at me look at me
If you are not looking at me right now, you're gonna get shot in three seconds three two one
Oh, you are not looking at me, sir. What what?
Me we don't know which ones you know, I don't know who I am. I'm the one that's in the front everybody. Okay
All right, so Simon says jump
Very good Simon says jump again crouch walk to me. Oh, you are wrong
Simon says crouch and then stand back up. All right Simon says jump
Simon says to turn around and face the other way. Go ahead. Go ahead and turn back now
You saw me a lot
Come on turn back around face me. I said somebody turn back around and face me for crying out loud
Simon says turn around face me. All right now jump. All right, you guys you guys are good
So now what we're gonna do here is we're gonna do first reaction last reaction
If you don't know what that is the first person to do what I say is gonna get shot
When I say first red stop hitting that goddamn button
We're gonna play first reaction last reaction, are you ready? Hey get back on red
Oh, by the way, Simon says the Simon says is over. Okay, how's that?
So first reaction jump Oh
Last reaction crouch. Oh
Did we lose somebody that just fell down
I'm sorry about that. It won't not happen again. Fuck this one
All right, so we got three of you left last reaction stand back up
All right, we got only got two of you left now, what are we gonna do with the two of yous?
Give them a gun and tell them to fight each other
All right, let's let's love we're gonna give both these two boys a gun and they're gonna fight each other to the death
We're gonna start them at different sides of the map. So I want if you hit that button again
Are you ready?
Here we go
No, don't kill me, please
Terrorists versus terrorists go for it
Friendly fire is not currently on
Hi, my name is German. Don't kill me. Don't shoot me in face, please
All right
Well, okay, well there was a friendly fire on that's my mistake
We do last request right?
Kill them he's got a gun now and
Yeah, do you how can you do like a last request you can do it right is that how it works is that mod in the game
All right, so now this is what's gonna happen for you. Oh, here we go. Okay. All right. You want a knife fight with me with the master
All right, let's do it. Where is he?
All right, come on. Come on. Come on mother. Come on
You can't take out the war I'm the damn one for a reason
Oh, yeah, that was the best warden