Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here. And today, well, you haven't seen me in a while, and I know that's because I've been doing a lot of stuff, I've been getting into art class, and I've been taking yoga lessons and all that shit.
So that's why you haven't seen me lately. But I'm coming right back at you with this DayZ gameplay, and I've been playing this game for the last three weeks or so.
And something to remember, something of note. I've died every single fucking time I've ever played this game, so I don't have any ghillie suits or any sniper rifles or anything like that.
But I live on the edge. I live dangerously, as you see right here, walking on the main road. What if somebody comes over there, Grandpa, and tries to shoot you? Well, I'll knock his fucking teeth out. That's what's gonna happen.
Please don't kill me! Please don't kill me! I can't, I'm so scared! I don't know what to do! I don't even have a weapon, I might as well just stand still while somebody kills me!
You see, the real reason why you play this game is so you can roleplay. So let's start that right now.
This tower has stood here for over a thousand years! And it's the rusty nails of eons of centuries of rust. And this was owned by the great Catherine of England.
You know, that's not working. Let's just keep moving.
I am currently on my way. Hey, Geoffrey! Geoffrey, I need to talk to you. Where are you, lad?
I'm currently bleeding profusely from the face, and I need some bandages. I need some help here.
Is everybody even listening to me?
Hey, hey, look, let's work together. Come here, buddy. Come here. Just run with me this way. You got a mic?
Okay, so you have successfully brought the entire town behind us. That's fantastic. I'm happy about this.
So, um, where are you from? I know this might be a bad time right now, but can you give me like three guns or something?
Shoot, get that guy. Shoot this guy. What are you doing? Shoot him! Oh, hey, what the-
And God said unto him, Eggo waffles are the best breakfast, and if you don't believe that, then you will be shot in the face.
Gentlemen in the back, excuse me, we cannot have people standing during church. Please take a seat in the left or right septicles, and we will continue.
Explain this game to me again.
Well, the whole point, you're not supposed to just run in and just run into people. You gotta find stuff, you gotta do-
No, but, I mean, how do I tell people? Is this ridiculous?
Well, the point of the game is not just you have to go explore, you have to get into out alliances.
No, I mean, no, I think this game is a little deeper than that. I think what this game at the core is going into the kitchen and finding a piece of bread,
and then putting some bologna and some cheese on it, and then coming back into this room and handing me the sandwich, and then I eat it, and I would like you if you did that.
What if I lie down? Maybe they play dead like a bear.
Wow, it actually worked.
No, it didn't, no, it didn't.
So yeah, what you just witnessed right there was pretty much the happenings of every time I play DayZ.
If you have any tips, I will gladly take them, because I suck and I can't do anything, and nobody talks to me, nobody fucking responds to me when I try to talk to them.
But besides all that, have a good day everybody. Make sure you eat your cereal, your breakfast, and your Captain Crunch or whatever you're eating, and see you later. Goodbye.