I'm going for the shotgun. Shotgun is where it's at. I did not know what Francis was going to say. He was like, man, Zoe is pissed. I thought he was going to say, man, Zoe is hot. Quite the opposite.
Alright, let's do this thing. Very careful, they can spawn now. Yeah, they're usually on that roof up there. Yeah, they are. There's a smoker up there.
You got one. There you go. Oh, Rigatoni. Oh, Rigatoni. Rigatoni. Oh, there's a hunter coming down right now. Hunter on the move. Thank you very much. And a smoker on Rigatoni.
Oh, hunter on me, hunter on me. Alright, let's go, let's go. They're all down at this boomer. Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh god, it's alright. They're all down. We have 20 seconds just to move. Just move.
Okie dokie. Reload, dammit. They got a respawn time. Oh, they have a spitter behind us. Or in front of us, I'm not sure. How? How is that possible? I have no idea.
Do they have like a set respawn delay? Or is it on like a... It's like 20 seconds. Yeah, it's like 20 seconds, I think. Okay. That's a nasty time delay. Let's move on out of here.
I think it's like, if they have a full team, then it takes longer. But if there's only like two on their team, it's only like a 10 second delay so they can get more infected. Oh crap, oh crap, crap. Where's the spitter up top?
I don't know. Spitter on the roof. Spitter on the roof. Fiddler on the roof. Yep. Alright, so far so good. So far so good.
Here's an axe and... Oh, give me that auto shotty. I'll take that. Oh god, jockey on me and rigatoni's getting plastered right now.
Wait, somebody just got... Oh my god. Oh, he's talking in the... Oh, he can talk. We can hear him. Oh no. Oh, I see him. Oh, nice. Oh, what's he doing?
He can heal. Let's have him heal up. Oh god, I got you. Oh, rigatoni's got... Oh, I'm on fire now. Oh god. I'm just healing. Oh my god, we're getting dominated. Oh god.
Thank you. Alright, we gotta keep moving, keep moving. I definitely don't overreact.
Hey, overreacting is okay, left for dead, because it's scary. Oh, is that a spitter back in here? There's a hunter right there coming up to try and get...
He's not dead. The hunter's still back there. He is still back there. Keep your eye out for boomers. There hasn't been a boomer in a while, so keep your eye out.
You know what? I'm gonna throw this behind us. Oh my god, I'm busy trying to blight a fire and I can't even... Oh, what an idiot.
I hear a hunter, I can't see anything. Oh my god, that was a good charge.
Oh man, all at once. Are we dead right now? I'm coming, Jerma. Save me! Kill that charger!
Alright, we're good. We're alright. What a real shame about my aim. Oh, the son of a bitch is still stomping me.
It's no problem. We're good. We're good, we're good.
I need a boo, let me get those pills. Sure thing, honey.
Oh, come back to me. Boo, boo, boo. Oh, what? What? Come on, Rigatoni. There's a jockey over here, too.
Jockey on me, jockey on me. Oh my god. Our teammates are killing the shit out of me.
We gotta get out of this area. Oh my god, they just respawned me.
There's a charger. Oh no, it's not a charger. Just a very fast common infected.
Let's do this thing. We gotta get out of this area. Like, right when I get up, run. Just start running the other way.
Give them pills, give them pills, boo. Just right click on me with those pills.
That's what I'm talking about. Let's get the hell out of here. Is it through here? Pills. Auto. Okay, let's go.
Let's get out of here. There's a Rigatoni. There's a Rigatoni right there. Dead.
Rigatoni is behind us. I don't think he's playing, to be honest.
Is he just like AFK? No, we can't leave him.
Alright, if you revive him and he stands still, we're just gonna run.
Oh no, no. He's still alive. Yeah, he's standing still. God damn it.
Just go, just go. Leave him, leave him. Goodbye Rigatoni. He'll be fine.
Oh, Gordon Bennett. It's alright, we're good, we're good.
Incendiary ammo. Oh lord. We, we, we're good. Okay.
Just some ammo. Oh, I'm smoked. Cheers. He's still up on that rock.
Oh, boomer in here, boomer in here, and a hunter, and a hunter.
I got you. I'm just gonna crouch. Don't stand in the spit, don't stand in the spit.
I can't see anything. Oh, a hunter on me, a hunter on me kicking my ass.
Oh, I'm getting owned. Can I get him? Yep.
Oh, they don't have these hazmat suits on.
Oh, we gotta pick up that, pick up that boomer bile.
Pick up this incendiary ammo, we gotta keep moving. Let's run.
Yay. Just ammo in general is nice.
Alright, this is, we're like just getting to like the point.
Wow, we're just, yeah, this is gonna, this is the friggin' tank.
Oh no. Oh no, I can't, we can't, we just like jumped down.
Oh no. Oh lord. Oh, this is it, this is game over.
Game over. This isn't even a disaster.
We just got our asses kicked, like big time.
Just getting smoked.
So thank you everybody so much for watching, I really do appreciate it.
And if you want more Left 4 Dead, let me know.
Just testing the waters a little bit with these two uploads.
Just seeing how you guys like it, if you guys want to see more.
So yeah, I'll see you guys all next time, and take care everybody.