Hello, how are you doing? I'm doing an experiment today where I'm gonna try to say
less than 5,000 words. So that's 22 so far, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27. I have a count on the screen,
an 8, 29, 30, 31. Why am I doing? I'm just, I'm not doing that. Hey everybody, welcome,
we're gonna play Space Channel 5, the original one. You're gonna watch me open the package.
We're gonna do an unboxing video of Space Channel 5. Total word or unique words? You know what?
I wonder. I wonder how many unique words I say per stream. You ever think about that? How many
unique words you say a day? Not uh, or the, and, is, maybe. I think I'm gonna do it one day
and just see just how terrible my vocabulary really is. And another interesting thing to do
would be what's the most repeated word? Obviously things like the, the, and, or, is.
I don't think count. They watch it be ass. That would be very surprising. Did I play this
yesterday? Uh, no, this is Space Channel. We did um, Hypno Space Outlaw last uh, yesterday.
Yeah, last night. It was a long stream to go just about nine hours to get through it,
the whole thing. It was a good game, really fun, really interesting concept.
But playing Space Channel 5 today, this is the last, by the way,
we're gonna, this is gonna be our farewell to the Dreamcast. Unless something else comes up
down the road, this is the farewell song of the Sega Dreamcast. Oh, by the way,
this is the last stream ever. Uh, how's my migraine? It's okay. I'm doing better. I'm doing
fine. I've been trying to hydrate, keep my fluids up. If there was an issue, it would have been
an issue yesterday and it wasn't. You need a season finale. No, don't you understand how
this SHIB TV show works? We're still in season one. It's just been 800 episodes. This is a
TV show. I don't know what, no, no, okay, hold on. What could, how many seasons has
German 985 been? I wonder. It's, you know, if it really was actual seasons, it's probably been at
least five or six. I gotta be careful though, because once you get to 10 seasons of a TV show,
that's where it all goes down and it's like not funny anymore. It's not interesting anymore.
The characters all suck. The writers are scrambling to come up with new content. So
what about, what about season six? I got about four more seasons worth of shit before
people start to hate me. That's how it works. Too late. How do you know that people don't
already hate you? Yeah, but you know what I mean. Anyways, let's go ahead and open this.
I don't like this at all, but I'm going to do it. Let me get the intro off.
The funniest part about what I'm about to do right now is, that was weird. When I first
showed this, what, like a week ago or so, two weeks ago, it was like four days ago.
I don't remember. My brain is beefed. I got beef brain. Here is Space Channel 5 in the
original liquid case. This is the original liquid casing, and it's got a hologram.
Look at this. Look at how cool this is. I said I didn't want to open this,
because it's an artifact. And somebody on Reddit, like a hundred years from now,
there's going to be a whole subreddit dedicated to this. Like r slash oh no,
right? It's going to be like 150 years in the future. And I'm going to be on the front page,
because this shit's going to be worth like 2,500 bucks. Those of you saying buy it on
Steam, this is a different game. This is the original game. Space Channel 5 part two is on
Steam. This one is not. You can only get this on Dreamcast. So we're playing the
original one. You can't get this anywhere else, unless you get an emulator or something.
But I got original fucking hardware. Those of you that didn't know. Okay, here we go.
This is the unboxing of an original liquid cased Space Channel 5 Dreamcast video game.
It's desynced. No it isn't. Don't do it. I'm not desynced. I'm good. It is. It
shouldn't be. How desynced is it? Don't do it. It belongs in a museum. Stream something else.
Don't do this. Please don't do this. I'm going to get the emulator one. I'm going to get the
emulator version. This is new. This is brand new. Don't touch it. I should be wearing gloves.
This is the official rules. Play to win. Register at Sega. Let's take a look at that disc.
Who gives a fuck? You ready? This is brand new. Going to be clicked out of the receiver
here. Ready? Take a look at this. Take a look at that pristine fucking cut. You can look
see everything. It's a mirror. That's unbelievable. Where's the corner of my desk?
Right here. There it is. Let's get some scratches on it. It's a fucking joke guys. Look.
It's pristine. Let's get it in there. Space Channel 5 part one. The original. It only
costed us $2,500 150 years from now. It's being damaged by UV light. What? What the
hell are you talking about? You look like Bradley Cooper. That's the biggest compliment
I've ever received. I don't think I agree with you. Isn't that nice MTV commercial from 1996?
Right before Beavis and Butt-Head would come on. Space Channel 5. There it is.
Original hardware. Not Space Channel 5 part two. This is the first one.
If you don't know how this game works, just you'll see. Light. This is very bright.
Hold on. Let me turn this down. Light. It's the UV light from the disc. Hold on.
Disc is already damaged. It's been ruined already.
It's a little better. I'm going to keep that up just in case I need to keep it going there.
Let's start a new game. Why? Do we need to do tutorial? Do you know how to play this?
I act like I've never played this before. You have a pirated copy.
Let's go to the options. Device options. Sound options. Player's status. Character profile.
This looks awful. Why does this look so awful? Maybe if I make it bigger, it'll look better.
We're going to have a nice, relaxing, crazy taxi day.
Well, here's the plan. Space Channel 5 is less than a couple hours long.
So if I get through this in an hour or two, then there's a couple options on the table.
We might just go back to PictoPix for a few hours. I'm not against that.
There's a Samurai top-down game that I might want to try playing. Who knows?
Let's just go. This takes place in 2489.
No, but this is the prequel. Forget about everything you know about the first one that
we played. I believe that is Ulala.
Did you just call the first game a prequel? I did because we already played the second one.
80, 2199. Somewhere outside Earth. This is a crunchy game, but it's okay.
Welcome to Spaceport. 6 45 p.m. Yeah, it's pretty crusty.
Why couldn't the aliens just develop 480p? They were too busy dancing.
Hey, watch out for the vape rings. Yeah, no, I just made that joke. I'm sorry.
Aliens. That's the first song. Guaranteed.
James Bond? No. To save the world by dancing and chewing.
The Swingin' Report Show. This game is very ugly. Well, because this one is the one for
Dreamcast. The other one was HD remaster. This didn't get an HD remake. For some reason,
they only did an HD remaster of the second game. And apparently the VR game.
This is bright. Again, bright. I got it.
I got it. Put the contrast down quick.
Quick. Here we go. A button. When they say chew.
Oh, this is off. Oh, boys and girls, this is off. It's because it's being captured through
a device. And I'm seeing it delayed, I think. Uh oh. That's not good. That's not good.
This is bad. It's delayed through the capture device. This is fucking bad. What do I do about
this? I have to compensate for the lag. Is it before or after? I don't know. What's the
input lag? Okay, left. Okay, I think I'm figuring out the compensation.
It's like a half second before. Fuck.
Oh, this is not good. It's not going to be possible. I don't think it's possible to play this
while capturing it. But why? Why is that delayed? Oh, I've ripped off the protective coding
for this. Just hold on. I'll figure it out. Webcam capture? No, no, it's, it's, it's,
it's, it, I can't do webcam capture. It's still going through the device. Oh my god,
I just lost 2500 bucks. No, you know, it's not, it's not going through to the screen.
It's coming through the device to come up into my monitor. Oh, man, it's just, ah.
Sometimes I get it and sometimes I don't.
You know what it also might be? It also might be the controller too. It might, you know,
it might not be input lag. It might be inputs on the controller not being registered.
I don't have a new control. This is an original hardware Dreamcast controller.
Guys, you watched me do this like a month ago without any problems at all.
What? I did this like three weeks ago without an issue.
I played the second game and I got 100% on this level. Oh, god. All right, no more. I
beam when they say Q. Ready? Oh, I had to do that so early. Stay tuned.
Did you hear the click before it happened? Some of you did. I'm at the control tower.
According to my sources, the space rescue party's mission has gone horribly wrong
and they've been captured. Do a controller cam. Watch your footy. Let's shoot.
I can't believe you're so bad at that game. That's bait. I'm not going to take that bait.
I'm not taking that bait. I'm going to get.
I was looking forward to this too. What happened here?
Oh, I was really looking forward to this. Am I playing this on a CRTV? No, I'm capturing
this through a HDMI upscaler through an Elgato capture card. Just go emulate it. Just plug it
into the TV and record. I can't plug it into the TV. The Dreamcast does not have an HDMI.
The Dreamcast only has RCA inputs, which you have to convert to play on a monitor
that's not 15 years old. God damn it. Go buy an adapter. What? That's what it's plugged into.
That's what it's plugged into. It's plugged into an adapter. That's how it's no way I
can put it on the screen. Oh, this sucks. Emulate. I'd have to like set that up. That's
not even fucking ready. Let me try compensating one more time. A poor craftsman blames his tools.
What happens? A poor craftsman blames his tools. But what happens if the saw that they give you
is not actually a saw? What if they give you a fucking wrench and you're supposed to cut the
piece of wood? What are you supposed to do? You're going to fucking just hit the wrench until
it explodes? Shit. Shit. Craftsman blames his tool. Yeah, it's not a tool.
I might be able to get through the whole game in 7%. I have to adapt. It seems so erotic.
I am pudding. That's my report on channel 42. Don't worry. I'll take you out. Let's dance.
Up, down, shoot, shoot, shoot. Up, down, up, shoot, shoot, up, down.
That's so unprecedented. Left, shoot, up, down, shoot, up, shoot, shoot,
shoot, shoot, shoot. No match for me. Play the Steam version. I'm going to say this
one more time. I'm going to say this one last time. One final time. This is a different video
game. This is not the same video game that's on Steam. The one on Steam is the second one.
This is the first one. You can only get the first one. You can only get the first one on
Dreamcast. That's what this one is. Shoot, shoot, shoot. Up, shoot, shoot.
Shoot, shoot, shoot. Up, down, shoot, shoot, shoot. Up, left, shoot, up.
I was so off and it ended up working somehow. Down, down, down, shoot. I'm figuring out the
competition. Beat her. Retreat. I'm not taking the bait about how bad I am. This guy's
terrible at guitar. Yeah, shit Craspin blames his tools. Roger. And even better Craspin
complains his shit load about how bad the tools are and then does a spectacular job.
Kick, kick. Here we go. Shoot, shoot, shoot. Stay tuned. Nice shooting. Go get the one on
Steam. Oh, you guys are fucking with me. I've made it to the launch pad. What's this?
Was that supposed to happen? Something's up. I'm feeling kind of... No, start over. Do it
again. I got it now. I think I figured it out. It's a little bit after what I'm supposed
to do, but not really. It's like weirdly before. I don't know. I'm trying to figure
it out. I'm doing that again. I'm not getting 8%. Is the A button broken? I don't think so.
Okay, here we go. Just pretend the whole... Okay, but first of all... Hey guys. Well,
look at how fucking angry that face looks. Hey guys, welcome to the stream. I'm gonna
play Space Channel 5 tonight. This is the one that's not on Steam. It's only available
for Dream. I'm getting angry now. Is this turning into Mario Tennis? No, it's not.
...to investigating reports that aliens have invaded and are forcing people to dance.
All lines are clear, Oola. Let's see what you're made of. Let's go.
All right, no more 10%. Stream starts now. Well... I've encountered aliens on the main
floor, and they've taken hostages. The aliens moves. Press the buttons with the rhythm.
Let's dance. No boings. No boings. They say cue. Cue, cue, cue. No boings. I got it.
I figured it out. Sometimes when it gets fast, it gets weird. I'm okay with that though.
That's fine. No more boings. Too fast, too weird. Look out. They're gonna jump out at you.
Use the A button beam on the aliens. Aliens. All right, bring them in.
Cue, cue, cue. I'm never gonna be able to play a...
I'm doing okay. It's weird, but I got it. What are they doing?
This is the equivalent of T-posing. What's going on? The music's still going.
No. She's blinking. This is fucking terrifying. You ruined the disc. I didn't do anything.
It's brand new. Wait, let me try something. This might be blue. I'm sorry. It's blue.
No, god. Poor craftsman blames his tools. Not the non-existent workbench.
God damn it. I have to do that again. Oh, it's all right. It's okay. Everything's
gonna be just fine. This is gonna be a two-hour stream for this game. Not anymore.
I didn't expect this to happen. Well, I got two backup games in case there's more
problems. I am going to get this to work. Maybe this is why they didn't remaster it.
All right, people that... All right, Lodz, the next person that says to play it on
Steam, I want you to ban them for 33 years. Every year that I spend a life.
Don't actually do that.
Play it on good old games? No. Arrest them. This is just a space bike awaiting us.
Okay, if it doesn't crash, then I should be fine. Let's go.
Disprocessing my input. Okay, when I press a button, I hear...
This is what I hear. I hear, left, chew, chew, chew, up, chew, chew. And then I press,
left, chew, chew, chew, up, chew, chew, chew. Listen, do you hear the fucking bird in here?
My data's getting stolen. All right, no crash.
Nice. Got it. Am I gonna play Sekiro? I'll be playing Sekiro day one. Not at
midnight, but first day comes up. Get the PS2 version. Okay, see you in a week.
Use the A button. I'm good. I'm good. Here we go. Stay tuned.
Ditto is better than Peepo dance. That's it. That's debatable. All right, we're at 14%.
I'm at the control tower. According to my sources, the space rescue party's mission
has gone horribly wrong and they've been captured too. What? Peepo dance?
Perfect. Perfect. He's still got it. He's still got it, even though he's compensating.
For your height, there he is.
Is that Michael? Space Michael when? He's showing up in a minute, just relax.
Is that on? Is that on? Is that? There it is. Is that on key?
All right, Bart's here.
Shoot. Shoot. Shoot. Up. Shoot. Shoot. Shoot. Better than I thought.
Better than I thought. Right. Left. Right. Shoot. Shoot. Shoot. Up. See ya. Goodbye.
One, two. What happened to that guy? Oh, it's that dance. Charlie Brown.
Roger. Oh no, them say shoot.
Can you change this channel? It sucks. We're about to change the channel. Here comes a sneak peek at the next channel.
Funky? Is this Michael? Michael Jackson? Maybe?
Is that a robot? I can't tell. But let's see what it's made of.
Nope. This is the boss, I think. Or one of them.
Hypnotized robot invader.
I kind of want hearts.
Dancing my hardest. Dance with me!
Woof!
That was tricky. Tricky!
Stop screaming. What the fuck am I doing?
Is it still alive?
Check it out. There's something coming out of its mouth.
This is going to get hard.
It's the Rockettes.
I forgot! I forgot again.
Dammit.
Got that one, though. I can adapt.
Yeah, this is Rhythm Simon Says. The second one is on Steam.
I shouldn't have even said that.
Because people are going to start making fun of me about it now.
I tried.
It's the A button.
They were right. Somebody said that like 20 minutes ago.
The A button's all messed up.
My controller's broken.
There it is. Minimum view. Overall view.
Expected view.
There it's 99%. 30 plus 28.
28. 15. That's 2. 3. 4. 5. 6.
100!
228% or something.
Just play on an emulator. I'm good.
I figured it out.
Only 12 minutes in the game.
And we've been streaming for 48 minutes.
Hey, I just got here. Why this? I'm going to read it.
The emulator would have more input lag. Probably.
Give me your excuses.
What's the next plan?
We lost our battle because
our tactics were too straightforward.
But we've come up with a new plan.
Powered us with elegance.
We've prepared this dancing robot for our next battle.
Who's the robot? Let's see.
Why are you savage these past weeks?
It's because of Seaman.
What?
I medically induced Seaman rage.
Cowardice with elegance is a perfect way to describe you 90% of the time.
Level 2. In the corridor.
I'm not even going to give it a response.
I like that color scheme.
What is going on? This is like Nickelodeon furniture. This is weird.
Is this the robot?
Just walked onto the set of Rocko's Modern Life.
Again. Why?
What the fuck? I swear to God.
This doesn't make sense.
Sega got sued over this game.
How? I didn't... I don't...
Okay. There's no way you get that wrong.
Up, down, up, down, up.
No, you didn't do down.
What? This is really fucking...
Aren't you glad you opened the sealed artifact?
Yeah.
Oh no, our ratings.
Quiet.
Maybe I should... I'm taking the microphone out.
Maybe it's using data.
The background is decent.
The background is also decent.
Let me see if this fixes it.
Let's see who that does.
Embarrassing.
I think each area has its own style of input lag.
Maybe. I don't think so, though.
How do you get the first...
I'm gonna do it.
What the...
Is this Space Michael?
My name is...
Is this Jaguar?
What are you doing?
I'm about to fucking turn this off.
This is unbearable.
Okay, how does that happen?
Chew, chew, chew, chew, chew.
Boing.
I'm so... I'm so soft right now, I really am.
You have to set the daylight savings time.
Ahead an hour, though.
The second experience was so great.
I don't want to have a bad taste in my mouth
I'm trying to pull this through the new
current technology.
It's the Waltz robot again.
Oh, yeah.
I gotta do some rescuing.
The game is fucking broken.
Are you sure?
No, we're good.
This is what's supposed to happen.
This is probably... Are you sure this is not where it's supposed to be?
It's impossible.
It's im...
I opened the fucking seal, I bought the dreamcast, I bought the game.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, god damn it.
Alright, come on, I can do this.
It's a little... It's crispy, it's crunchy, it's fine.
Is something wrong with the disc? It's brand new.
I don't know.
Chat says you bought a bootleg.
That's impossible.
It was sealed in the pristine condition.
A background?
What's happening?
The boring was on cue with the music.
What the fuck happened?
Okay.
If it was cheap and sealed, it was a bootleg.
This is not a bootleg.
No. No it is not.
It's not a bootleg.
This game is not meant to be this fucked.
It's definitely a bootleg that got shrink-wrapped.
Hold on.
No, it's got original packaging.
Did they boot... How do you bootleg this?
No, I don't believe that.
How do you bootleg...
This is like original Sega Dreamcast packaging.
They didn't print this?
They didn't print this.
Look at this.
Okay.
For all you scholars in the chat, how do you prove this?
How do you prove that?
It's really easy to do this.
No, this is not a...
The disc isn't broken.
The disc is not broken.
It was brand new.
I didn't get...
Reset the console?
Hold on.
This is important.
Why would you buy...
The artifact and the history...
Is it Dreamcast?
We haven't had a problem with it so far.
Hold on. Just give me a second.
There's no way this is a bootleg.
The shit is printed into the disc.
It's not like there's a piece of paper on it
I can peel off.
No, there's no scratches or anything.
Show the disc? Yeah, I opened it on stream.
I showed it.
Let's restart this.
Chat is bullshitting you.
You can't fake the hologram.
I just reset the console.
Let's see if we get the same problem.
Before, there was...
Brand new factory.
Hello, Cosmic Kitties.
This is Ulala's report show.
Tonight, I'm reporting from the luxury spacecraft G.
The aliens seem to be stirring up a dance crisis.
I'm in the cockpit.
Sorry to spring this on you, but you got some
aliens up here.
That's like the exact same thing that I bought.
I didn't buy from here exactly, but...
That is a bootleg.
Hold on a second.
I didn't buy it from eBay.
I'm gonna beat this. I don't care if it's a bootleg or not.
I'm gonna complete it.
I'm gonna see the credits.
Up, down, up, down, up, down, up, down.
No, no, no!
It's all over the place.
Do I cut my losses now and just fucking
throw this thing in the garbage?
Or what? I don't wanna do that.
I'm so annoyed right now.
I'm gonna sour my opinion on the game
if I keep going. Eh, that's true.
I think it's a combination of
old hardware, trying to take
and process inputs, combined
with being pulled through a
converter into a capture card.
And not on a CRT TV.
I think this
is a real copy.
I do.
Well, there was another option. I was gonna play this
top-down samurai game.
And then maybe PictoPix.
Yeah, it would.
That's the weird thing.
It's almost like the game is reading
the disk and causing
me not to be able to put inputs. It's weird.
Alright, what am I gonna win?
Spin the wheel! There it
goes, Vanna! Yeah, what's it gonna land
on? Oh!
Oh, you just went past the $20,000,
Jerma! Here it comes!
Come on! Not bankrupt! Not bankrupt!
Oh, it's at
5,000's okay. 5,000's okay.
Oh, top-down samurai game. You won.
Yeah, I'm gonna just move on.
In a sour and old experience.
That's obviously something's not right.
So I'm not gonna pretend like this is not
an issue with it. Because, I don't know.
Sorry, everybody. Everybody
thought this was gonna be Space Channel 5 and so did I
and it's a great game. It's great
that it went on Steam, we beat it, and it
was fantastic.
We're gonna play the top-down samurai
game now. Sorry, everybody.
Gonna change the title, we're gonna move
on. I'm very sad.
Let me change this.
This game looks very fun, though.
It looks interesting. I'm not
even sure it's on the Switch directory.
No, it's not.
Games and demos, apparently.
Let me close this out.
I'm so sad right now. I really wanted
to do Space Channel, but
it's okay. Look, it can't be
it can't happen every time, right?
Hold on, let me turn it off.
Kenshi? No, no, no, no
Kenshi. I want to play this game. This game looks
really fun. I'm gonna BRB the screen
here for a second. It's not even big enough.
Here we go. I already have it ready.
I had it just in case something
was gonna happen, and here we are.
I'm literally buying Kenshi right now. Well, you should. It's a great
game. Steam.
Okay, here it comes. Hopefully it's not too loud.
I'm gonna mute it just in case
it is. I gotta put a
controller in. Why is it an empty
yogurt cup here?
When did I eat this?
What even is this plugged into?
I mean, that was...