What's up? Good afternoon. Yeah, it's a surprise. Surprise, I'm live today. I know I originally, you know what, if you're a watcher of this stream, what you should do is you should check the sus, right? And then what you should do is come back, come back the next day and check it again. I feel like I've reversed the stream schedule the last three weeks every single week. This is this is like the third or fourth reverse delay.
Uh, in a row, check it once an hour more like and the next day and the next day and the next day. All right. Yeah, originally I was going to stream today. A couple days ago we talked. Oh, yeah, I'll be live on Wednesday with more Breath of the Wild. But it's my birthday. Not today. And there may have been some birthday plans. I was like, you know what, maybe I'll just come back on Friday. But birthday plans have shifted. So I'm available.
Available today. Not going to be available tomorrow. Tomorrow, the next day. We'll go today. I'm here. I'm ready. Hey, he's available. But yeah, let's play some more Breath of the Wild. Happy birthday. Well, thank you. I appreciate it. Thirty seven. Thirty seven. And I can still do this. I can still do this. You didn't see what I did, but it was cool. My hands moved so fast. It's his bones cracking. I also wanted to play Breath of the Wild.
For my birthday. So that's where we are. He's still got it. Yeah, still to this day. Yeah, early, early start today. In mod chat, we have a gameplay thing chat wanted to tell you about.
Oh, OK. Yep. Uh huh. The shield surfing. Jump and tap the parry button and you can slide around. OK. I'm all right with backseat tips. I'm not OK with you telling me.
Uh, who Ganon is, right? I don't want to know who Ganon is to the last cut scene. You're thirty seven. What the fuck? Dude, I know. I'm sorry that you're big. I'm sorry you're figuring this out now. No, I'm not. I'm not like twenty six. No, I'm thirty seven.
Ganon is Ganondorf. You're almost forty. Yeah, whatever. Whatever. I'm closer to fifty. Yeah. Dude, can you please be younger? That's I don't think that that's not how it works. Do you think twenty six is young? No. What do you mean? What? I'm that old now. All I said was I see I started YouTube when I was twenty six. That's what I'm saying. I started YouTube when I was twenty six.
Twenty five. Whatever it was. I've never really been doing this for twelve years. Almost. Wow. Twenty six is young. Yeah, it is. Thirty seven is young, too. I'm still a young man. I'm still a young man. I'm not forty yet. You know, I am. I'm fighting until that four zero shows up. You know what I mean? On my thirty ninth birthday. No, the night before my fortieth birthday, I am going to be
in a full Super Mario pajama onesie, and I'm going to eat popsicles and like and popcorn and watch fucking TV shows all day. I'm literally going to. And then I'm throwing all those pajamas away when I turn forty. I'm going to have an absolute pajama blowout on the night of my fortieth birthday, and I'm just going to burn them all. And it's going to replace my whole closet, going to replace with suits in life crisis. Thirty nine year old behavior.
Yeah, what am I going to do with all of my Super Mario pajamas? Fucking finally a good title. What would be finally a good title? I guess I forgot I played the game, by the way. It's going to take me a few minutes. There it is. Breath of the wild. OK, so the jump is that this is attack. It's you hold buttons. All right, fine. Yeah, I'm still a young man. Yeah, not until forty. People are living longer anyways. You're using you. Why do you still have a mop? Thanks for reminding me.
All right. So what was the last thing we did? Check the map. Oh, that's a good idea. All right. So we're going here. This is locked memories. We have to go do.
Impa told us that there was some crazy shit going on down here. I can have a birthday hat on because it's not my birthday. You can't read. I can read. Can we see more of your beautiful face?
It's here. What do you want me to like pull my skin back? What do you mean? Let's see more. This is I'm in front of you right now.
Your head is cropped. It's yeah, but that's what do you mean? Yeah, my head is cropped because that's how it works. That's what a face cam is, guys. You understand the word face cam.
It's not body full body cam. It's not all of my upper body and like my face cam. It's a camera for your face to be in the corner. And that's precisely what I'm doing. That's how it's going to stay. Let's go.
All right. So I need to go from here to here. I'm excited to play this game. I'm telling you, I'm actually excited about it. Is it fall damage? I would have died. Of course there is. All right. Let's glide.
Two headphones in for this. Welcome back to Breath of the Wild. We're going to explore this part of the map. We see your neck. That's an easy way to go across the whole game. This game is potentially hundreds of hours. I'm so excited. Made it with time to spare. Come on.
The person is saying help? I'm coming. I want a reward. I'm coming. I want a reward. I'm coming. I want a reward. I'm coming. I can't say it. You know what I mean? I'm coming. I want a reward. I know that's kind of fucked up to say. This person dead? No, you're all right. I saved you.
Wait, stop. They never fight fair. They always lurk and wait to ambush us. What a bunch of cowards. Seems like every time I go out hunting for arty truffles, I'm taking my life in my hands. Time to stop floofing around here.
Let's get back to the hunt for the hardy truffles. I mean, I don't have a weapon. I'm right behind me. What is she scared? You scared of this? Oh, shit. He's attacking another another citizen. You all right. All right. Let's keep going.
Somewhere this way. Yeah. Yeah. What's this town? It's very bright. This is a bright town. Can I go in? Can I just go in? Can I just go in? You can. You can go in buildings in this game.
I got to get it out of my system. OK. Make their beds. Dude, you need to keep that shit in. Keep it in. No. Do you want to know what keeping it in means for me? If I had to keep it all in after like an hour, I'd be like this.
It would be insane. I would explode. Oh, I can dye my clothing.
Now, should I change that? Wait, can I change the Nintendo Switch colors like Xbox? This is worth 20 bucks for me. OK, chain. Choose a color. What? You're wearing clothes that you can't dye. That's unfair. I want to make the shirt green.
No, I need different clothes. I'm getting one hit by random enemies. I need armor and shit, right? I'm getting one hit killed by the random goofballs outside. Please be all red. No, it's not worth 20 bucks.
Buy armor in this village. How much money do I even have? I only have $37. Why would I have no money? Checking everyone out today, too. The check-in just never stops. Never stay to the Tanpu Inn. No, you're not staying there then. I'm supposed to check out everyone who comes into town.
That's weird. Dollars? Sorry. Rupees. My 37 rupees. Sorry, I didn't say what it is. It's whatever bucks. Dollars. Money. How much money do I have? Do I have to say how many rupees do I have? You know what it is. You know what it is. That's like calling everything gold. That's fine. How many gold coins do I have?
Grandpa, it's rupees, but you don't turn the game off. Any beauties or suspicious folks? What are you talking about? Go stay at the inn. You're not immersed? Yes, I am. I have so many side quests. I have to get overwhelmed with how many things there are to do.
First things first. The most important thing that I want to do right now is go to the shrine because that's what I like. My favorite part. Where is it? This way. It might be underwater. There it is. Out of my fucking way. There it is.
Oh, man. Oh, come on, dude. I was about to say something funny. I was going to say something funny. Yeah, it was going to be wicked funny. Oh, it's because I forgot. All right. If I fall off this and drown, I'm going to be very upset. No, I'm good. I glitched it out.
Would I have a breakfast? Yogurt. I had a yogurt. It was good. Was it Greek yogurt? Yes. Shut the fuck up. Yeah, it was. What's wrong? Wait. Oh, I thought I was going to just walk in. It's not goat milk. Greek yogurt is not goat milk. Shut the fuck up. It can be. No, it's not. Greek yogurt is not made from goat cheese. Shut the fuck up.
I'm not. I'm just kidding. God. God. All right. Where's ball? Greek yogurt is not goat milk. Why did I think I could reach that? It's your fault for distracting me with your goat cheese. OK, I need to eat something before I die in here. Oh, emote only is on. Right. So I don't get spoiled. OK, I've got. What about magnet? I do anything, move anything, throw anything, twist anything. Doesn't look like it. So what about stasis?
Hey, where's the ball? I think it's over here. Oh, OK. Well, move. Oh, you're not going to gyroscope me right now, right? Will he beat the dungeon before 1 p.m.? Yeah, I of course I will get it. Get it right. Check it out. I'm telling you right now. You should be voting for me to win. Yeah, almost.
Oh, shit. Wait a minute, can I? I can probably just launch it over there. What time is it? All right. No, I'm going to do it the right way. Oh, you piece of shit. Yeah, there you go. Before 1 p.m. done. What's going on? Oh, wait. I can make this jump now if I tilt it down. Oh, that's just a chest. That's just a treasure chest. I thought that was a button that I thought that was the end of the maze. Oh, my goodness. Right. I have to get it down here. OK, I thought that was a button. I thought I was going to drop a separate ball. I don't know. What time is it?
I still don't think you should vote against me. I still don't think you should have voted against me because I figured that part out. That's the most important thing to figure out. So watch this. Yeah, I saw. I saw the person. Yeah, I saw it.
Yeah. You don't think I've read what people say sometimes about me? Somebody told me, well, maybe indirectly. I don't know. I heard that watching me play this was like watching an early human learn how to use tools for the first time. It's kind of rude, I think. Fuck.
All right. All right. Oh, yeah. How's it for a fucking tool? Huh? Take that early human. Fuck you. God damn it. All right. I got seven minutes. I'm fine. Yeah. What the fuck?
Oh, my goodness. All right. I got to get it. Let's do it right. What time is it? I got plenty of time. Believers, you win. This doesn't count as you know what I mean? This doesn't count. I already beat it.
I actually I thought this was a button. Frenic Bow. Cool. Target distant enemies. So it's got long range. Pretty cool. All right. I think I just have to die, right? Yeah. All right. You can take it out of your mode only. I won. Hold on. No, this is OK, right? Yes, it's fine. Am I OK? Oh, yeah. All the all the believers. Yep. Believers win. Believers win. Yep. Believers give them the give them the win. Believers won. Believers win. Very cool. Spirit orb. So cool.
So cool. All right. So now I'm going to go do the quest. That was annoying. I like watching you discover day one speed run strats. OK. So besides that regular mission, I go into the pond. I'm going to look around the filthy pond. Yes. All right. I'm going to go check out the filthy pond.
I just take something off. Wait, what did I just take off? Yeah, I want to just be able to know what that is. I was on the map. That's because it's not a stamp. Oh, my God. I'm the buttons. Oh, my God. I just wish A and B were flipped.
What were this person's any stuff? No stuff in here. There's no stuff. You can't steal anything. So what's the point of having houses you can walk into? I'm just just just in a game play and just purely a game play setting.
What's the point of having houses if you can't steal like jewels from their chest? You can't sleep in the bed. You can't steal plates off the counter. What the heck? Oh, it's probably one of those. No. Heads up.
OK, what's down here? Anything cool in the pond? Oh, anything cool in the pond? No. There's got to be something cool near the pond, right?
Arp. Anything of interest here? It was just a rusty sword. Whoa, wait, something interesting. What is this? Pray? You don't say you can hear my voice. Yes.
She trapped me in this stone statue long, long ago. Villagers here call me the horn statue and don't even bother to wipe away the bird droppings.
One would think years upon years of such treatment would have made me mend my ways. Does an audio desync? I'll fix it.
I've only been biding my time for the moment someone who can hear me appears, someone such as you. But I've said enough. Now then, shall we strike a bargain?
And stay that way. No further action on your part is required. Wait, that was mine. What? Um, excuse me. What just happened? Um, do I get that back?
That's not good. Ha ha ha ha. My touch is as subtle as ever. Note how I took that essence from you without leaving a mark. What? That's not fair.
So wait, this thing just eats hearts? How do I get that back? All right, hold on. This isn't audio desync. Let me fix it. So you're saying when I go one, two, three, one, two, three, there is a delay.
There is? Okay. Is it on me to the gameplay or is the game audio is desynced? It's not my voice. Okay. The game audio itself is doing it. Hmm. Let me see.
The game audio has desynced from the game video. That's interesting. That's weird. Uh, let me see if I can fix it. So, okay. Are you? Is it happening late?
Like what? Do you hear the sound first and then I move it? Or do you hear the sound late? This one guy? Game visual is happening late. Hold on. If I can fix it, I will.
Let's ready? Check this out. Just check this out. Hold on. How's this? Perfect. So what? The horn statue took one of your containers. Well, what the fuck?
Give it back. Did you think I deceived you? Parish the thought. I hope that ours will be a long and profitable relationship. So which will it be?
As I may have mentioned once or twice, I'm a dealer in life and power. I can provide a valuable service to you. I take heart containers or stamina vessels from you and then for a price return whichever of the two you like.
Oh, it's just if you want to. Okay. So if you want to put more points into stamina, you can. It's a respect. All right. Well, I don't want to do that. In fact, I probably should do heart again.
Next level up. Okay. Money and life are always one to me. If you're ready to begin, then first you must sell me either type of essence for 100 rupees. And then when you want to buy an essence back, it's 120 rupees.
Okay. Well, I'm not going to fuck up my build, so we're never going to talk ever again. Good day. Nice to meet you. We will never speak again.
Idiot fucking morning. All right. That's cool. That was that's what was over here. I'm going to mark this. We mark it as I don't know what's like a good point of interest. This should be I don't know.
This is going to be but this means boss right skull to me is bad boss, not NPC. Maybe this like, oh, it's a leaf star. Maybe a star is probably a good idea. Yeah, that's a good one.
Okay, cool. Got that. What else is there to look at? I think I can just go do the quest, right? Are they quests in this game or are they missions? Are they quests? Go get a quest? Was it a objective mission? What's it called?
All right, I'm going to sell some. Maybe I can get some new armor. Oh, look at this. 250. Yeah, I want I want armor armor. Yeah. How much is this total? 180 250. That's 350 like 400.
Five. I like I was going to drop 700 dollars on the table and just walk away with this. I'm just going to go. I don't I'm not doing math. Just just keep it and leave. Well, I wouldn't have to do the math. They would.
Whoops. All right. So who do I sell to? Why do you look like John from Garfield? What can I actually sell? I don't really have much to sell. Do you like food? Whoa, look at this is worth a lot. All my my gourmet dishes will get a lot of money. I'm just gonna sell everything. Oh, and I can. Sorry about those sapphires.
Nobody knows what that is. Maybe one person doesn't. That's all I care about. Is it literally all I care about? All right. What about the amber? I'm going to sell some of these fish too. Who cares? Sell all. You're going to find tons of it anyways. Tons of amber. Are you sure? Sell all the gems. You're never going to use them. Really? I feel like that was a mistake. OK, sell it all. No, I don't. I'm not selling it all. I want this armor. There it is. Got it. I want the whole set. 200. Thank you.
Please. I'm begging you. Sort your items there. They're exactly where I want them. Wait, I don't think I want this because this helmet is good, right? This is a climbing helmet. Yeah, I'm not. I'm keeping this. I have the Nintendo Switch shirt underneath it. No, you look like a dork. No, I don't. All right. I finally have armor. Does this weigh? Does it weight in the game? Do I have to worry about? Oh, you're going to be fat rolling or something. Die the armor now. Oh, cool dad. That'd be cool. There's no way. OK. Was the person that was dying stuff?
There you are. All right. Right in front of me. To the right. Oh, dude. Oh, sick goat milk. No. All right. So what can I do? Let's die. Would you like to get back to square one? What do you mean square one?
Shouldn't I be Link? I can pretend I have the Switch shirt on or anything. Didn't they make a Legend of Zelda game where there were four links and they were each different? One was pink. One was green. One was blue.
And it was kind of like a movie with all the emotions with the mad one. What was it called? Inside, right? The Four Swords. OK, so who was like the funny, goofy, like goofy one, right?
Because I want one of them was like sleepy. One of them was like grumpy. Which one of the links was the funny, goofy one? Is that Mike?
Is this not happening in the Four Swords? Wasn't it like, oh, one was like a sleepy one. One was grumpy. One was kind of like I'm thinking of the seven dwarves. But they did that, didn't they?
That's not a thing in Four Swords. They didn't do like a red is angry. Blue is tired. Yellow is crazy or kooky. They didn't do that. That's Hyrule Warriors.
Somebody said, dude, you're thinking of parody animations. What? All right, well, I'm going to be light blue. Wait, five ingredients.
Have you ever done a sober stream? I was thinking about it. Is it worth? Are these things worth it? I feel like I need these. I don't care. Whatever.
I'm thinking of Zelda, the Four Swords adventures on the GameCube. No, somebody said it's real. No, wait, we're talking about the mod chat.
The mod chat saying you guys are on crack. It's real. It's in the Four Swords. The game is real, but I don't think they have personalities like that, did they?
They were depicted as acting differently. Yeah, one of them was sleepy. One of them was hungry.
One of them was dashing and one of them was vixen and whatever it was. The manga had flat out different personalities. Red was shy.
Purple was a cool guy. I told you I knew it. Why are you talking about the reindeer? I knew I did. I knew I had this right.
What happened to the quest that was here? Oh, I switched it. Okay. All right, let's see. I want to do Treasure Twilight Relic.
That seems kind of fun. Strange mask. What does EX mean? Ancient horse. Oh, this is DLC. Oh, all the side quest DLC.
Destroy Ganon. Free the Divine Beast. There are four. The Divine Beast. Okay. Yeah, this one here. I look cool now.
The game came out in 2004. I knew I wasn't crazy. Where's your horse? I don't use the horse in this game. It's too hard to control.
You need a better horse. I'll find one. I need to level up. How far away is this? This is not that far. There's a purple cow.
Wait, they'll all pay. What do you want? Don't act so clueless. Although fine, you seem harmless enough. Forgive me.
I've just been on edge with all these monsters running around. They come up from Hateno Beach to steal my sheep.
If someone doesn't do something, I won't have any left. Let's go do that right now. It's right here. That's far away. No, too far. That's too far.
That's way too far. That's way too far away. No, no, I'm not doing that. It's not too far if you had a horse. I'll get to the horse later.
That's a two-second walk. Can I actually make this without... I think I can, yeah. The map is not that big. It seems like it's pretty big.
I think I'm just gonna make it. There we go. Okay, you are all the way out here. You are all the way out here.
What do these Minecraft signs say? Ancient tech lab. Enter at your own risk. It's bigger than Skyrim?
I don't really know the scale of Skyrim because I don't really like it. All right, here we go.
If the flame is blue, the furnace is hot. Don't touch it. Good morning. This is Hateno Ancient Tech Lab.
Do you have some business with the director? Yes, I do. The director's in the back. Terribly busy person, that one. Please try to keep it brief.
Good morning. I imagine you've never seen so many books in one place. Pretty incredible, isn't it? I mean, it's actually not that many.
We've gathered all of Hyrule's known literature on ancient civilizations here.
So the actual number of books, well, is that the thing on your waist? Is that a Sheikah?
There's no mistaking it. That's a real Sheikah Slate, isn't it? Never actually seen one in person.
If you could just show me the runes on it, I'd be most appreciative. Stasis, Magnesis, the remote bomb, and Rionis.
And what else? Let's see. Oh, that's it. But, hmm, strange. Doesn't seem like you have the basic runes.
Why are they not there? Oh, where are my manners? I nearly forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Simon. You are Link, right? You know my name. Lady Impa caught me up to speed.
You see, we were told a young man holding a Sheikah Slate will appear and you must do all you can to help.
You'll be the hope that awakens from the slumber of restoration. His name will be Link. What's your name?
It's not my name. My name's Fred. Director, listen. Ms. Director, this is the real Sheikah Slate.
No, that's right. I haven't introduced our director. Ms. Pura happens to be right over there.
Ms. Pura is the world's foremost authority on ancient Hyrule culture.
Wait, that was... Okay. Check it. I have the utmost respect for Ms. Pura and all she's accomplished.
I'm honored to be her assistant. On that note, Link, you see the director may look like a young girl,
but, well, maybe it's not my place to be telling you these things. You should talk to Ms. Pura herself.
Don't spill the beans. Do you guys have any money? I'm just looking for money.
Can I, like, reshuffle the books or whatever? Like, I just want some money.
The director of this laboratory is not Simon. It's me. Snapity snap.
Anyway, Linky.
Well, no matter. I'm just happy you're still in one piece.
What's with that look? You still remember me, right?
I don't remember.
Don't, sorry.
It's a charming quirk, isn't it?
I'm not gonna go read it. I don't care.
Anyway, enough about that. Back to the topic at hand.
After a hundred years, here you are. Here to defeat Calamity Ganon, who is growing in strength with every passing moment.
And to rescue our beloved princess, Zelda, that is, if you've got the courage to try.
And to help the one true hero, I, the one and only Pura, will restore the basic functions missing from the Sheikah Slate.
So, cool. Do it.
I knew you were gonna say that. Alright, then. First, I need you to run an errand for me.
What's that look on your face? Well, I'm fine. That's actually what I came here to do.
I did not. You're pretty considerate.
But then I suppose that's because you're actually over a hundred years old.
Let me explain what this errand entails.
You know, the unlit furnace on the wall just outside this laboratory.
Could you please bring the blue flame from the ancient furnace in town?
Oh, and also use it to light our furnace.
I thought I said don't touch it.
This sweet little guidance stone will start working once you do that, allowing us to restore your missing runes.
Okay. Okay, then. I'm counting on you for that.
Alright, let's go get it. I'm going right now.
I'm gonna go as fast as I fucking possibly can.
Alright. If I ain't back in 30 minutes, it's free.
You can get a motorcycle?
I'm just finding the urge so much to just go like...
Let's do a really loud annoying sheep sound.
It was eating me inside.
You know, I've done that once before.
I don't know. I hope I'm not, like, putting in fake memories.
But didn't I do that on stream once?
And people flipped out. People were pissed.
People were like, don't fucking do that again.
Like, that was not funny. It actually was annoying.
I swear to God that happened.
How do I pick it up?
Alright, I got it. Does this count?
Make it a SBA torch?
I don't think I even have a torch.
Oh, I do. Okay.
Wait. This thing?
Oh, this is gonna be annoying.
It's gonna be worth it.
Just run. If I can't sprint, it blows out if I sprint.
God damn it. Hold it up, man.
I could have done that.
I could have held that up.
It's two feet of water, man.
I have a better idea.
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you.
What's the next one?
Is there one up there?
Is that one all the way up there?
What's the next one?
Just go find it. Alright.
How long does this last?
Oh, I see one right there.
What's going on?
What the fuck is happening?
What is happening? Why is this fire?
Why am I on fire?
What?
Okay, I need to just walk with it.
I'm just walking.
Put the bow away. I'm just walking.
Just walk with the torch.
Is this gonna blow out?
Does this blow out
if I run all the way up there? It's gonna be annoying.
Everyone's gonna laugh at me, but I'm losing my mind.
If anybody laughs at me for this,
I'm gonna ban you from my community.
Okay?
You're gonna get banned from my community if you don't.
I don't know.
Look, I redid it.
What a strangely colored fire.
It's almost like an anglerfish's lure.
Okay. Alright.
I'm back. No, I'm not.
Wait, where the hell am I going?
Wait, I gotta go so far?
Oh my god, I have to go all the fucking way up.
What do you mean, wrong way?
Oh my god, this is gonna be annoying.
There's no weird glitch that I can go like,
like, sk-sk-sket-sket-sket
grrrrrrrrrrrr
and fly like 100 miles per hour that way.
I actually have to walk.
I have to walk?
There is, but you're not skilled enough.
Wow, that's too bad.
It's not that far, it's fine.
I actually might not make this.
Don't go out, don't go out, don't go out.
Don't blow out, don't do it.
Yes, we're good.
Okay. Now, you want me to light right here?
Travel gate. Oh cool. All right, so now you're gonna give me my runes
How do you feel about pride spam? I've never had it. I was like, I've never eaten it. Okay, take a look over there
There we go
Cool. Cool. So what does this do?
Basic runes. What'd I say? I said nah to what? Oh, I thought it was okay
Give me a I didn't I just wanted to say nah, I wanted to do it. I just turned around
I was just gonna put the thing in there
She hates you. All right, what do I get camera? Well, you just unlock the camera app new iOS update
Camera. Oh the ancient runes the ancient runes
magnetism cryos
thesis
Stasis and camera app the ancient roots
What do I do with all this?
Creatures an iPhone 3 camera. Okay camera. I would definitely have to take a picture, right? Can you do selfie?
Okay, no, no delete that. Oh my god. I hate this. All right, this is funny. Okay picture save an album. Sure
All right, that's gonna I that's gonna actually be fun. That's the most expressive link has ever been in a game
Okay, let me see. Hmm. Who's this beautiful young creature? I'm deleting that immediately. I guess that's my cue
Sorry, I kind of lost it there. I wasn't on purpose
Hmm, and it's not just a pretty girl in these images. These are also some old landscape photos
So when somebody else's camera, I knew Princess Zelda had made frequent use of the camera feature what I have somebody else's photos
Wait, what it's a hand-me-down phone. They're your old photos
Okay, check in with Impa. She knows more about Princess Zelda than I ever did. Oh, yeah
There's just one more thing I need from you
You don't have to worry about this until after you see info
But I want you to bring me back some ancient materials
Bring them to either me or to Robbie. Okay ancient materials
I thought that wasn't enough room. How do I put the put it away? Whatever put it away
Travelers bow. All right, cool. So I got the camera. All right, let's go to the beach
So this is the what the person took. Okay, what is this a picture of?
Is this the same tree five times? Well, you went to Disney on a slow day
Holy shit, how the no people in these photos can you imagine getting a shot like this at Disney? Damn. All right
Oh, right. Okay. Now, let's play the video game the beach, right? It's Geo guesser. Look at that
I'm gonna land right on top. Oh, wait, that's trying right there. Go back back back back back back back back back back back
I want to go to that one too
Trying right there. I'm going to that one and I'm gonna drop down to that one. Perfect. That's not that far, right?
I need a I need a horse. I need a better horse than Frank
Frank Frank kind of stinks guys Frank kind of stinks
Zelda took these be nice. I'm just saying Frank kind of stinks whenever I try to maneuver around with Frank
I you can't turn how many photos am I allowed to have on my camera? By the way, I get rid of this shit
I only have 48 photos. Why would I keep just shitty photos? They have to be I want to be good
This is a little strange, but whatever I don't think I should be able to run up this mountain
But I'm here. I am is raining. Oh, come on
Take you make sure you save a slot to take a selfie with Ganon at the end of the game
Make sure you take a selfie with Ganon. Yep. That's true
No
I need to say 48 images so I can just be in front of Ganon and
Just go like this and just go snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap snap and a 50 fucking
pictures that's such bullshit. I
Would if it wasn't raining, I'd be fine
Yeah, I'd be fine God. Where is he going?
Wing all right look there's there's like 17,000 people here you understand that the collective leave you all say the same thing
Just the way that world works. I can hear it. I can sense it
Two or three thousand people at the same exact time just said the same sentence, so it's been manifested
I heard it my god. This is actually really far away. Whatever. Oh
Crunchies all right from here. You know what you're gonna. Go for it. You got you have to go for it right change my mind
Cave with uh minerals in it weather forecast in the bottom right oh, that's interesting
Wait keep old picture. Well. I don't know I want to keep everything how many times is he gonna swing all right?
Get up and use the soldiers claim or love of God crush his head
Okay, I'm ready with power explain it to him
Please somebody with power explain it to him quarry, please all right this
Mineral you can take pictures for specific items in the compendium yeah
That's in addition to the 48 other photos every item an enemy can have a photo attached. They don't take space
Okay, I get it so you're saying that if I go like this and take a picture of the luminous stone deposit
That this is okay. This is not a photo now, but it says four look at this bullshit. It's up here
It's both you can delete it. Oh
It's copied over oh
Oh, that's okay. I get it cool. Let's go luminous stones
All right, that's probably worth a lot of money. I know they're worth something cuz chat freaked out when they saw it
Don't proceed
Thank you bang okay. Oh, you can see the mountain in the background. That's cool
I should don't want to be fighting with this right this mistake. Oh bat wings can I
What can I do can I do anything with the light bugs?
Can you make apple pie I mean I won't eat it, but I'll make it
If we're gonna talk about shitty food takes right I've gone over the I don't like apple pie routine right
It is that one well that one's in the middle of the ocean. It's not a routine
Well hold on let me let me back up a little let me back up so
Apple pie is fine if there's vanilla ice cream on top if there's vanilla ice cream. That's on top
It's good, and it's I will eat it
Just a slice of apple pie without anything else. I don't like it. It's just I don't like it
It doesn't taste bad, but I didn't needs vanilla ice cream on it like cat just gave birth
Well while we were watching what the fuck really?
Yeah, where did you get this horse this hold on? I can I that Frank?
That looks like Frank doesn't it where do I end up?
I have a set of armor on and I'm dying in one hit give me that shrine
You got to upgrade the armor
Can you actually up that actually can you upgrade the armor cuz that would be a huge deal you can okay?
That's really cool. What's what's your problem?
What is your problem?
Are you gonna go over here and do that to this camp?
What are you just in a rage?
All right, let's go
Fucking run don't go that far
Holy shit this so they do so much damage. Oh my god. Just get over there. Why do they kill again one hit?
No, no, no, no, no
Run run run. I need to eat some apples
That guy just fucked everybody over. I wish you a and B were flipped
Rock back up no
It's a skill issue. I'll show you a skill issue. I'm gonna take care of this right now. What's sneak?
Okay, I'm throwing a bomb into the eyeball. I don't care
That's not really hurting them by the way, all right, I'm taking out the guardian sword for fuck's sake
Okay, I'm doing this wrong. I everyone's gonna make fun of me
Everyone's gonna make fun of me cuz I'm doing this wrong and I okay. I gotta take this slow
I gotta take this slow and I gotta just relax. I'm under leveled because look at look where I am
Look all right. I'm so under leveled. I should not I'm supposed to be over here in the fucking
Rico
Cliffs, where are they? I don't I'm not supposed to be over here. How do you how do you sneak? How do you sneak?
How do you sneak L3? Yeah, watch this. I'm dropping a grenade in this thing. What are they hearing?
No, don't come out of the cave. Why are they coming out?
You heard me through the concrete
God
Okay, are we okay?
Happen now die already. All right. Here we go. It's up. Remember me. That didn't hurt them
I can't hurt this guy that does not hurt at all
Which had arrows right now
The taunting me yeah, they're all you're all doing a fortnight dance. Yeah, you're all in a party. I solo queued
I'm sick of solo queuing shoot the lantern. That was a bad voice crack as well. Yeah
Where's the lantern? I mean shoot that lantern up there. You got it, bro
This didn't do anything that guy helped me more than the lantern
Fucking keyboard turning by the way. I need to make that faster
Okay, how am I gonna kill these guys? Oh
Check this shit out. These guys are fucking dead now. That's gonna be one down, right? Yep. Oh, you're throwing rocks
Shit, okay. Hold on
They're almost dead now. They can't take damage from this really I don't think
Don't know what I was gonna say. Hope he doesn't get up here. All right eat something. Oh
Got him got him Knights broadsword only one more one more left. No weapon Andy. No weapon Andy. I win. Thank God. Oh
Internet problems starting again. Now that we're okay. We'll see this is another Knights broadsword
This thing's almost broken
But I want to throw it at somebody so I'm gonna get rid of the this yeah, this thing's a piece of shit
Why don't I still have this?
All right, what's in here? This is a pretty tough encounter. That's it. I mean, that's okay
This is a regular spear. Should I just get rid of the guardian sword? You can hit really fast with a spear
That's literally one of the best weapons in the whole game. Really? Yeah, I don't need this thing anymore
So I'm gonna save this for a little bit. I have some pretty good weapons. I need more inventory slots. Yeah, I do
I really do desperately another one of these
God
Get rid of this I guess but this thing's not as good
1520 just think fast
This thing's fast. What if I need a fast weapon? These are these are slow
Yeah, the boomerang is sucks. Get rid of it. All right, I'll get rid of the boomerang
Okay, it's a boomerang. I forgot. That's cool though. Let me do that one more time
Cool yeah, these night swords are 26 damage. Have you guys ever thrown a boomerang in real life?
They actually it's actually kind of hard. They just okay. I have been out in
In a big open field, right?
Whipping just throwing a boomerang as hard as I can and this shit just goes straight
It doesn't come around it doesn't do anything if you throw a boomerang for real every time I've ever thrown one
It just kind of goes there and falls down. It doesn't go all the way around
I feel like it'd be terrifying. Can you imagine that coming back?
How do you prepare for that it's just like oh shit, it's gonna hit me in the head
How do you catch a boomerang? It's just did did did did did did did it's gonna literally get you in the head
It's gonna kill you. You got to throw it, right?
I would imagine throwing that and you just see it but hit man briefcase glitching back towards you. No, dude
I'm turning around I'm sprinting. I'm not gonna get hit by that
That's terrifying. No way
Okay. All right the beach
Wait, did I pick up the sword? Look at that 26 26 26. I got a lot of damage now. I'll go. Let's go with this
It's the worst one. Oh, there's a shrine. I forgot about the shrine. You're right with it. It's up all the way up, right?
Yep, they really do come back if you throw them, right? It's scary. Yeah, I don't want to do that
Yeah, can you do anything with the bull? You can ride the bull. No, you can't
Well, it's gone. Why are you tan? I don't think I'm tan
I'm not tan. You can ride anything. That's awesome
All right. I finally made it
We're doing that shrine then we're doing that shrine and then I'll go do the main quest
There's shrine over there. You saw that right over there
Yeah, I don't get it. It's okay
It's gonna do this and then it's gonna remember this is how it works
It does this for like 30 40 minutes and then doesn't happen again for the rest of the day
Just happen. I don't get it. It was just weird doesn't matter if it's 2 o'clock in the afternoon noon 10 o'clock at night
Just the way it is. What's on your right? Why do you keep looking on your right?
Okay on my right I have
So I have thing that tells me how many frames I drop right there on this monitor
I have mod chat and then I also have the stream preview is up that way
So like well not the stream preview but the device that's I'm streaming with
So I'm usually look from look if you see me looking over here. I'm looking at what's the stream health or?
Mod chat if I'm looking over here. I'm reading you your chat
Um, you know, I got a whole battle station here. Okay, so let's go. What's this puzzle?
computer police play celery man
Did you do that? Yeah, dude, it ends the same music
This thing is broken already
So this doesn't fucking hurt no, don't take a picture
I'm dead instantly. Okay, I gotta probably parry it. It's a parry, right? It's definitely a parry. It's a boom
So parry is how do you do parry? You have to be I have the shield equipped
How do I put this in? How do I put okay, and then it's this in r1
Listen, how do you how do you parry? I have a shield out and is it how do you parry computer?
Please should play please place a celery man, please. Hey
Oh
You broke my shit
Barely hurting this thing
Can you I can't parry that I just have to fight this is not worth it to be honest
Okay, so when it goes like
You're gonna I dodged it you saw me jump in the air I fucking dodged that I actually did
Everything is breaking against this person
Flurry rush incoming
Do that didn't fucking even hurt him
I'm just breaking all my weapons on this
This is actually terrible. I'm gonna break all my weapons. Everything's gonna break
Every weapon I'm gonna I all this cool stuff
Use the best weapons. I feel like as if this is bad
I
Was gonna say what the fuck was that
Where's my flurry rush? Excuse me. I
Thought you had to interrupt it. I thought I had to land on top of them to interrupt it
All right. I got it. We'll be good. I got it. Now. I got it. Now. This is it
This is the one that usually works your bed and play too much Dark Souls. I pressed our three to lock on
Flurry rush incoming. Oh my goodness. Oh
Well, what does this do this is stealth boost jump and open the parachute now don't do it again
I
Am not getting one hit killed just eat the gross food and puke. I don't care. Go ahead. Do it again. Do it again
That's not I you have to be directly on top of this fucking head do it again you piece of crap
But this is different. Am I safe behind this?
I'm safe behind this right? They'd know there's no way I'm gonna be I'm gonna lie behind this right my dad
Shoot it in the face
Okay, um, do I have any more food? I'm fucked. Just eat the snails dude. I don't understand
I think I'm dead. I
Didn't know when he was gonna fire. I didn't know. I didn't know when he was gonna shoot it
Fuck. Okay. I get it now. It's over this time. You're so bad. It hurts
I have never fought these things. This is the first time I've fought one of these. Of course
I don't know what the hell I'm doing
How am I supposed to know I don't have the knowledge of beating this before
I don't know if the laser does that
The knowledge of beating this before I don't know if the laser does
And I should have flurried right there and you know it
Why is that not working that was a perfect
Junk it's backwards not sideways. Wait, you can only do it when it's backwards only a backflip does that I wait only a backflip
What I thought it was just you if you dodged it either side
I thought it was like doesn't didn't matter as long as you got a perfect dodge
It's only on backwards
With a horizontal attack because there's no iframes
You gotta be fucking kidding me. All right, so I did I thought it didn't I didn't think it mattered
I did. All right. I didn't know I thought those iframes
Okay, I got it holy shit ancient battle axe plus what
guardian shield plus
No way. No put this away. I'm never I'm literally never using these until the last boss fight something else in here, too
Whoa better not be no, I don't want to do that. I want to throw the bow. Let's drop it. This game's fun
I like it. That was a challenge. It was it took me a minute to figure it out, but I got it
Um, this is fun. I think that's my second one got a shrine right down here
By the way shrine down here before I get out of here is something else. I should look up
Check out up here. It's kind of sits alone on the mountain top here. What is this tonoko island?
I think that's where I'm going. I
Think that's actually where I'm going right now. Yeah, it definitely is. Oh, all right
Hmm. I want that trying
Saving on stamina
Oh
Okay
Cool. There's a boat here. I
Use this this just look cool. Oh, there's a cares coconuts or anything. There are coconuts what?
Do this coconuts
Trying time use the leaf. I
Can use the leaf move the boat. All right, let's go
Combat trial. Oh god another one of these is the same. It's another one of those guardian things. Okay, it's the same thing
Just do it again. I just have to do it again
You just you have an extra weapon. That's fine. I'm gonna run out of weapons. I think this is bad
What if I run out of weapons? Can I hurt don't I just blew up one of the things? Oh my god
Every button in my brain is remapped to dark souls. Our one is attack our
Prussian our three is dodge. I mean is it lock on I have dark souls brain. It's genuinely dark souls brain
Should I use this thing? I just like fuck this guy up. Yeah
Pretty good
I'm gonna scream as loud as I fucking can I thought that was gonna be vertical use that why I'm gonna help at all. I
I
Pressed left. I'm pressing left and dodge. Why am I jumping backwards controller sucks?
Dude, I hate the joy con. I'm doing my YouTube angry voice is doing pretty good, right?
I'm not trying to jump backwards. Why does it keep doing that? I swear to god. This is drift
It's now it's not the drift use the pro controller
I why I don't want to buy something else and use it because they didn't package the better controller in
I'm not gonna buy the pro controller for the switch two of them. You're doing a Kubrick's dare every time you play
Sitting there like this. See if I can beat this guy with the Kubrick's dare. I
Don't know what that means. Oh god run. It's it is
What it's broken. It's broken. Oh
Shit, that's bad
He's not even a half way
I
Space to bullshit. What's the face to bullshit? Same thing, but it's a weirder. Oh
Nice miss you idiot
I'm so paranoid about missing that
What was that what happened what the
Oh
There we go, oh my god, he's doing that thing
What's the strategy here?
What's the strategy here? Shoot his I just run in a circle. Just run in a circle
Period I'm not gonna parry this. I don't have the
Skill for that Harry or run around I'm gonna run around
Oh
Man that's pretty good one
Ancient battle axe super double plus 60 damage a fucking swing guardian sword double plus 40 damage a swing ancient core
Very valuable to researchers. Oh
That's cool. All right. Hold on. Look at that. I got a full set of diamond gear. I got the diamond pickaxe
I got the diamond sword. I got the diamond hoe even I'm loaded save that core
Do not cook it don't sell it. Don't eat it. Why would I eat the core you can eat it? Don't cook that
Don't the mods are I'm getting a lot of mod help here
I was told do not cook that or sell that okay, you've been eating gears. Ooh
Really? What's the defense on this? This is good. Oh
Hell yeah, I got the climbing gear. This is really I can sell this now. All right, cool. That's way better
It's only one defense less and I get the climbing ability
I'm gonna call me a shit eater
Who said that I'm not I'm not gonna I don't know they're in here somewhere if you get the full climbing set you go
Much faster starting to understand this game now starting to get it. No, I get it. I get it
I get it these little challenge shrines with with cool items in them. I get it. It's like my favorite part of the game so far
Who's that?
Okay, I want to get on the boat saying I can get on the boat and do this, right?
Wouldn't this work when it goes this way?
Wouldn't it that's when
This is how it would work the air would be moving this way, right? Oh
It has to go to
Okay, all right. I'm thinking of like a jet propulsion
I was like I'm gonna aim this way and go air that way so we go this way like an octopus swims
All right, why oh over the island let's go
Over the island, let's go
Under the boat get up both of you just fucking die. They drop anything good. Ooh
Dragon bone bow
Two ingredients. Okay, cool. What do I have? That's a piece of shit. Probably one of these can't drop it
Don't go don't go go go go. Wait, wait, wait. Don't fly away. There's a chest in the ocean
I'm fucking dead. I
Completely forgot about fucking death and well, no, I'm fine. I'm right here. We're good
I thought I was gonna get teleported somewhere. That was such an overreaction. I
Pick it up. How do I get this? How do I haul that up? There Ramit? How do I pick this thing up?
How do you pick it up?
How do I get this chest Oh
Okay, I get it. I don't act like you figured that out immediately people for hiding Santa Claus
All the people doing Santa Claus is an evil to save the day
All right, so I'm gonna check out this island this game's fun
It's really not that much movement I just get picked up a porgy I
Feel like I could just swim there faster
Right, all right, I'm done
Hey, hey, hey, check it out. Yes 50 purple rupees. Oh, no. Okay
What's that even Tide Island was that
That's a place for a ball
Okay, hold on to you who has traveled to this island I
Present you with a challenge in your travels. You've relied on the equipment you found along the way
Here you must cast this equipment aside and face this trial with only your wits and whatever you can scavenge
Offer up the orbs to the three altars on this island only then will I acknowledge your skill and return your items
Okay, am I stuck here?
What do I have to do?
What was the goal just survive on the island for a day? Did you take my food? Oh
Shit, you took my food. Oh
Okay, well
Good friend
Cool wait, I need to bring this rock around cuz I've hit somebody with it there's fire over there
Okay. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on a second. Can I cook on this?
Oh
Did the tree kill me
All right. No, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. All right. Oh, yeah
Now you're all in fucking trouble
Okay, I'm gonna cook some food here. All right. What do I got to work with replenishes your stamina when cooked in a dish
Increases defense just cook them individually, right? Why can I not cook on this? It'll still count, right?
These will be like cooked crabs, right? Yep. Okay
How much health does that give? Okay, good
I'm going to cook all this. No, no, no, no, don't you chill out. You don't get the buff what I needed the health
Whatever. I'm good. I'm good
That's just effectively gonna break the fucking sword
Yep apples and shit in here
Volt fruit is that a watermelon? Cool. Okay rusty shield. I'll take it wait
All right. Now, let's go
I have to explore this island and find I forget what it was but I find the three shrines or something, right?
Put it out. Put it out. Put it out gummy bears. What was that?
Nothing just attacked me. Oh, that's kind of sad. All right
Looking for shrines
Oh stop
Oh, no, what is that?
He's got the ball on his neck. Wait a minute
Can I sneak onto him and like steal it? No put it away put this way put this way put it out
I definitely like sneak up behind him and like undo it and take it right?
I have a bow
Oh
What is that? I just got something cool
24 damn. Okay, so I I don't I don't think I can kill this guy
The bow dropped out though
Because it looks like something attached
It's connected to something it's attached to something
Get in the eye get in the eye. Oh, no, no, no. No, I was trying to climb the tree
Wait, what's wrong with him?
What's going on? Why is he burning?
It hurt
Wait, what's he
They're throwing rocks at him
Stop taking trees down
jumped into his asshole
God damn it
Fuck. Oh, I got all my stuff back. I don't think I can do this right now. Should I try it again?
What if I don't go talk to that thing?
What if I just okay? I got an idea. What if i'm just on the island watch this
I'm not gonna go talk to that. I'm gonna go on the island
I'm gonna go up to him with my guardian axe and i'm gonna chop his fucking head off
Watch this
Never mind. All right off of the orbs to the three altars on this island. So there's an orb on
That trolls neck
First of all, let's collect the items from before
And crabs and shit. Okay. Yep
Yep
Okay
What else is on this island? That's not that
Chest down here
Jesus stop it
Five arrows that doesn't help me really at all right now
Okay, so I know that that's it's over there
What the fuck was that? Oh
What?
bananas
There's an axe right there
what
So grab on to the
Where did I go? I'm trying to grab on to the branch the tree
God damn it
Oh my god game over. I don't know. I'm not supposed to be here
I'm supposed to be here in like 30 fucking hours. I'm not supposed to be on this island
I'm not supposed to be here. You can do this. Yes, you can you can do it
Well, first things first, let me eat the food that I have so because I know it's gonna go away
Shit, I don't have any more of my special drink
They're all it's a but this is a puzzle man. You can survive you can do it
I'm gonna try this dude. Don't worry. This game is like rices. There's no wrong way to eat it
There are wrong ways to eat rices
I don't buy this like oh what I do is I put my tongue and push it through
And I take the middle out with my tongue and then I eat that no just eat it normally
There's a wrong way to eat a rices. Let's just eat it
What I do is I I I bite one half and then I put the other half in my pocket for two days
No, just eat the fucking Reese's
eat it
What was that?
Where did they come from? I don't understand where they came from
Holly said i'll make you a brain juice if you want
Um, hmm
Should I have a brain juice?
I think I should
You already finished your first brain juice. Yes, I did. I did have my first brain juice of the of the afternoon
That's like a brain juice. Sounds good
All right, i'm gonna do what I did before here's what I did before
I
Attacked this camp and I got a bunch of equipment
So I gotta get the equipment
The problem is I got really lucky last time because I threw the just get in just get into it quick before they get their items
Okay. All right. We're good
All this shit is now mine. There's a chest here, too. This wasn't here last time. Where did this come from?
Oh, no, that was okay. Yeah, that was
All right. Now let's do this
You shoot me with something i'm gonna be pissed. Okay, what is gonna heal me the most over the apples?
Okay. All right. So I have a little bit of equipment. I'm good to go
There's fish over here and i'm gonna get all of them
These will I can cook these
I didn't get one. Are you kidding me?
I'm gonna drown
I'm gonna fucking drown
The ground is right there link. Just put your feet down
Give me the fish. You can't even swim over here. Okay, this is chest in the ground. It's chest in the ground right here
You better not kill me god
Fuck off
Don't just run just run run run run
Okay, that's where the sleeping giant is right
We're good. All right, there's some weird shit going on over here
Can you see me oh my goodness, what do I do here this um
What are these lightning orb things? Ooh hearty durian. I'm gonna eat one of those right now. The lightning bolts are alive
Uh, oh my god eat shit. Oh my god. He hurts when he stings
Okay, I need to heal again not this time you're going over the edge buddy
See you later punk. All right safe
That was pretty terrifying
Ooh, there's a seared steak
Can I cook on here?
I don't think so. All right
Electricity demon over here
Okay
Yep ball goes here
Oh, dude, you are fucking lost of trouble now
Oh, i'm gonna i'm gonna roll this over his head when he sleeps
He missed put this down, please
Wait, wait, wait. Oh my god. He's coming the long way. He's coming the long way
I can't believe that just missed
Come on, dude
These don't even hurt
Fucking do it already. I can do it to it, but I can't mine up close enough if I stop time
Will it like to wrap will it choke him?
or something right
Magnet
No, I can cook here shit
I'm out of here. I have time to look under the rocks
I think he went back to sleep up there. Okay. So what do I do about this guy something up here?
Finally I got a bow. All right, there's no arrows. Why didn't I pick? No, I didn't
I'll figure it out later. I'll come back later. It's fine. I'm not supposed to do everything
Nobody in the chat blames you
No, I know
We're good
I'll come back later
That's part of the game
I'm fine. I'm not like mad or anything
Uh, all right. So what's the actual quest nine?
All right this one. Oh, wait, what about should I do one of the divine beasts? Where do I do that?
Oh my god
Okay, so the closest one is here
Is it too early? Is it too early to make my way over here and do one of these?
I gotta go this way
You can do it
All right, that's right. Let me get a stamp so I can see where i'm going
I'm gonna head that way. Where's my horse?
I actually need my horse. I need a horse for something, right?
I can sell a lot of shit
Let me just prepare
Hold on. I gotta get I gotta get my brain juice. Actually i'm gonna i'm gonna take a piss too. I'll be back in like two minutes
Yeah, no, thank you
No, this is good. This is great
Yeah, I just have to pretend to like this fucking shitty game still
Thank you
No, it tastes good
Unmute. Hey, what's up? Uh, i'm back everybody just uh, ready i'm excited
I've done that stupid routine so many times. Come on, you're not gonna fall for it for like the tenth time
Are you I do it all the time?
It's I do it so much that it's probably
You can probably tell at this point. All right, can I get confirmed from the gaming andes?
That I can sell these opals
I can sell these
Luminous stones and shit. I I can just get rid of these. I don't need them right now. It's just money
Keep one of each. Okay, i'm gonna keep more than one of each
I don't think I really need the money like that bad
What else what can I even buy with this?
Is there something I I could buy?
Maybe what about a bunch of arrows? How can you play from a library?
What do you mean? Yeah, i'm gonna get arrows but there's also stuff here too, okay, this is milk ingredient in soups
mushrooms
Truffles, oh people were talking about truffles eggs
rice, okay
Should I get some milk?
All right. I'll get some milk. Oh
three
Why are we talking about a library?
Should I should I get milk eggs and like can I make a cake or something?
all right, so if I do milk eggs and
flour or
I wonder oh arrows. Here we go
Bomb arrows. All right. I'm gonna buy a shit load of arrows
All right
10 bomb arrows i'll take uh, yeah, let's go
Get sugar milk eggs and wheat will that work?
Who sells sugar that's rice
Well, i'm kind of out of money anyways
Ah, this is a weapon shop
Oh, no, it's a oh, no, no, no. All right. You need wheat cane sugar goat butter and an apple
Make apple pie
First has a quest wasn't I supposed to go to the beach for somebody and I forgot completely
All right. Should I do that?
Okay, there's probably a treasure on the mountain
Mysterious place. All right add it to the list
Are you reading?
Um, but i'm sneezing
And very shortly
Take one picture of everything
Is what i'm being told
Everything like even the grass
What does it not know why is it still saying question mark?
Okay, this is donkey over here donkey. Okay. Let me make a uh, you need that. Yes, I do take it
I'll explain to the villagers you eat your fill. All right. Let me cook some stuff. What do we got?
I know I have at least a few things to make
All right snail. Okay steak fish steak
Milk and eggs steak and fruit steak and apple was pretty good. Right steak and salt. Okay
steak salt more than one salt milk steak should I do it milk and
Truffle truffle oil five times salt. That's enough fire. Um, why is it enough? How do I get you need a light?
Why would there not be any light source or anything over here? You can use flint
How do I use it strike it with a metallic weapon to generate a spark?
It has to just be on the ground. Okay steak and a bunch of salt
Fucking waste of ingredients. Why did somebody tell me to do that? That was such a stupid thing to do
All right. How about this?
Cooking this into a meal unlocks the potential of these nutrients. Can I do fish and honey?
Try just cook them individually
Should these always be cooked individually don't mix effects. Okay, so but if I go like this with one fish
It's gonna be one heart
Or will it be better?
That's two. Okay. So then two fish would be four hearts, right? And i'll put a mushroom in there. Why not?
Okay, honey and
All right. How about this another fish? Okay when it's cooked into a dish it increases your attack power
So let's do that another mushroom. We can't do two right fish honey and apples
Will this be good? Don't mix stats. So this is
Stamina this is also stamina. This is just fine
It says nuts and then this is
Attack power so I don't want to do that. Okay defense
Stamina, so this would be huge. Let's try this. Whoa
That's cool
So let's this is stealth. So this is a stealth
Any more stealth any more stealth food heart recovery?
Maximum hearts. This is just eggs. I'll put some wheat in there, too
Stealth boost sneaky fried egg and rice. Maybe let's just make a few of these
right and then
Attack power more add salt to and more eggs. I have eggs don't I double salt double wheat
Add some bacon in it and an apple. Nice. Okay. I'm gonna have a lot of good food
Okay, egg milk salt wheat fish. This is defense. It's gonna be huge five minutes of defense
So we said cook an individual truffle make a creamy mushroom risotto. Oh, wow. Holy shit
Why wouldn't I just only do this? Are you kidding me? That's insane full recovery
And two spirit hearts. What about this shit grease your heart recovery when you use this as an ingredient
All right, so let's do two of these some milk an egg and another another glass of milk. Let's have let's make a uh,
Let's pick up a coconut stew. Wait, hold on
Let's not put some salt in it. No, no salt. This is gonna be like a cake milk fruit and egg. It's gonna be like a
stew
And I made an omelet. Okay, what does this do? All right, whatever. I'll just do this
Very good. Now i'm ready. Look at all the food I have now. I mean some of the stuff is gross, but that's fine
I have so much stuff now. Thank god
Okay
Now that i'm prepared that way it's time to move to the divine beast
Press please sort it press y to sort it didn't do anything. Is it by rarity or something? Go level up. Oh
Do I have four? I think I only have three. What about the beach quest?
Shit, yeah. All right, i'll do the beach quest fine. I'll do the beach quest
Let's go preparation is the most important thing in breath of the wild. That's what i've been told
Packed buffs are great for bosses or tough enemy camps
Also, you're doing way too much healing for your current hp look smaller dishes. You're not wasting ingredients. Oh, that's right. I didn't think about that
Yeah, one of those is it heals 10 hearts
That's a little too much. I think
Can you see me a lullaby? Yeah, I think so. I think I could give singing a lullaby
what
We're floating all the way there that's somebody just said that's the final straw
What are you talking about?
Uh-oh, I have not been paying. Oh, I gotta do this
It worked
All right, dude, that's the last straw
Come out of here
Okay, so let's do it
I'm ready. I got some good weapons. Maybe I should eat one of the stamina foods
What are they fighting? Why are you fighting me? What are they doing? I'm trying to save them
Holy shit that hurt
Oh my god, your reach is insane. Ooh
What the fuck enhanced?
Lizzle spear. Okay. So now what do I got? I gotta get rid of some of this shit
I'll use it. Spears are really good. This one seems really good. Okay
I still have so much trouble judging how far this goes. I don't even think about it
Oh my god, that's fucking such a what a youtuber seriously like honest to god
Don't fucking die because you're a youtuber
Got it. Okay
So now
I believe
How do I get them to come back?
Well, i'll deal with them in a second. Can I like move them?
Oh nice good bolt fruit again
Uh-huh grabs. All right. So what do I do with the sheep?
How do you get the sheep to move something else to do that freaked out? It's okay. Wait this meat
Oh man meat
What's the
Where's the marker going? Wait, did I do it? Did I do it? Did I do it? Oh
Okay, what's where's this one? That's up here
All right. I'm gonna go back and turn this all in
Will you please go back and talk to her?
Well, that's
Definitely what I should be doing
Travel I need a new horse so bad. I need a horse so bad. What's the shirt?
Andy martin
Whatever
Yeah, i'm wearing my whatever shirt
All right. So what do you what do you need?
Something good. What what's what am I doing here?
ancient material
Three ancient screws to power up your sensor
ancient shaft power up your remote bombs
ancient cores
Oh, man. All right. I have all that stuff
Yeah, let's do it. Okay
Definitely remote bomb. I use that all the time. I'm I use bombs all the time a lot. I'm a big bomb
Um delta bomb fan dude. She installed root on your phone
Okay
So what's another good one?
Um, how many
Is this what you do with this stuff or is there other things you can do with the ancient materials?
Stasis or the sensor just do them all if I can there are other things. Okay
All the stasis I use stasis pretty frequently. I don't have it. Oh
How about the sensor?
Yeah, let's do it. Oh talk to the sheep owner. Yeah, i'm just getting this out of the way. This is um
I like games like this because I feel like I haven't done anything but I feel like i've done a lot
I feel like I have not done a single thing yet
But somehow I am okay if your sensor has been augmented to search for things other than shrines
It reacts when you are close to the thing you have set it to look for so you can make it look for other stuff
Okay, cool
You can now search for anything you take a picture of that's why you're taking the photos. Oh
That's actually really helpful. All right
The sheikah sensor plus I really want to see it
Take a look picture of a sun shroom with the camera
Okay, i'm pressing b
But it's you have to hit x b is universal back. I did get one. Okay using that in the rain
Yeah, that's probably a bad idea
Okay, give me three sun shrooms. So
All right. So here we are
The album we're looking for that's these are not pictures of the bow is they're pictures of me
Okay, so target with sensor searching for sun shrooms. Okay
So that's gonna blink when i'm near a sun shroom now very interesting
Yep, the one back here
sun shroom
All right. So then now just have to look for him
Oh
That's I like that feature a lot. That's cool
Is there another one over here? Go to that light go to that beam go to that beam. What is it?
It could be rare now go get it. I thought that was a marker that I put down
I thought that was one of those beacon things
When I looked on the map, I was like wait a minute. I didn't put that down
I have a gold one on the map
This ends at 5 a.m. Dude, hurry up
What?
Lighting is ooh, there's um, was it unobtainium? Whatever it is
Frank it's not like the uh
What's the other force from the other games?
You have to be within the same zone or something. I think frank is dead really
That would be kind of sad
All right. So what is this?
Is it doesn't work?
Star fragment mysterious stone fragment that fell from the sky looks like it would fetch a good price
But you may be able to use it in a certain recipe
All right. Nice
So now what what do I want to go from here? Probably fast travel back to here. Oh, I need the shrooms, right?
I wipe this out. I need to go back to the village and I have to talk to
Yeah, hold on cook it
What if you cook the star? Do you make a black hole in high rule kingdom and ever get sucked into it?
Okay, I need to find a couple more shrooms
apparently a few nearby
They're probably down here
Really?
Where are these mushrooms that what do you mean nearby? They're not nearby
What the fuck are these things? Oh, hey there
All right. I got three, right? That's what you needed. I got a lizard iron shroom and a bunch of these too
Okay, I got a lot of these. I thought this is live. How much is enough of any given material like 10 20
Finding new objective. It's never enough 25. I think that's good enough to turn this in
Can you just watch funny videos instead of playing this dude? Can I can just like watch some funny videos?
Ooh, that was worth it. I think i've got some news that should be music to your ears
Found a way to help you search for new objects using the sheikah sensor plus
Uh show excitement
Okay, I was doing some research. I felt there were some pictures of the past left on the guidance stone
You add those pictures
To the compendium you can search where did you went over this?
Oh
Didn't we already go over this drop one of those and take a photo. That's a great idea
What are we doing?
Doesn't sherman know that he has to eat a bug since he made 10 dark souls references
That was never set in stone
I have to eat a bug. What bug?
When did I I didn't make 10 dark souls references?
You name me 10 dark souls references and i'll believe you. Okay
Please be a centipede
God damn it. No enough. Is this the sus guy? Yeah. Yeah
I should probably not have these
mushrooms anymore, right? Although
Okay, let me do this
Where's the truffle watch this? So somebody said you could do this
Truffle now I can find truffles, which that's pretty cool. That's a good idea
All right. Well, I definitely don't want it to be that so
Uh, let's do it. How about I change it back to shrines you need to on the map? Okay
All right. There we go. Cool
Uh, I gotta talk to the lady at the town, right? You look like a truffle. Sorry. I wasn't looking I came back
I'm ready for my reward your eternal reward
All right. Uh, are you the one who took care of those monsters? It's me
Maybe he did it not much of a reward. But hey, it's light that accounts. Oh fresh milk 10 milk
I feel like that's pretty good. Uh reward. All right, what else do I got? All right, i'm gonna go this way
Maybe I should go to kakariko village kakariko village get a horse and go up. That's what i'm gonna do
Do you play elden ring?
You're like a four month sub. I think you would you definitely know that already frank is on the map
Oh, wait, no elden ring came out in february. Wow. Why does it feel like it came out like three months ago?
February march april may june july august september. That's seven months ice. I'm corrected. I'm sorry
I don't know. I let me pull that back. Wait frank is on the map. Wait frank is here
What hold on that was wicked rude. Yeah, that was pretty rude. Yeah, i'm just like oh you should know
You need to you should know that I streamed that
That was dumb
If you were a four month sub and you maybe you have only been here for five or six months
Maybe you don't even know I played elden ring like one of my favorite games ever made except for uh radan
Like the worst bite ever in the whole series
All right. What where are you?
How is frank not hearing me?
That by the way, i'm i'm i played pre-patch
pre-patch radan
Don't ever forget that
Is frank just free like out just free?
Don't replace frank we need to find frank
Frank
What are you doing over here?
Why is frank over here?
Yeah
No, no, don't go don't go. All right. Where's the stable frank? I'm sorry. I'm just gonna i'm gonna
This horse is better
It has three. Um
Yes
I'm keeping this one for now. Where's the stable? I wanted to go up. Where's the stable frank?
Will just still be here. Okay, isn't it right next to me somewhere?
Oh, there it is
Yeah, this horse has three yes
Um, what are you doing?
Oh
The horses control so strangely
wait
All right, you're smart you're very smart don't run too far
Oh, that thing's a piece of shit. Never mind better than this
Take a picture of the chest
Oh
That's cool. I feel you. Cool. All right, let me go back to the stable. Wait
Is uh, aren't there like ancient screws and shit? Yeah, there is we're gonna go
We're gonna leave now
All right, we're safe
This game's beautiful, isn't it? It is. Yeah, it looks great. Okay. I want this horse. This horse is stronger
It's a little bigger
Yep
Oh, look at that three two and two much better
Let's go so now i'm ready i'm gonna teleport to here
The horse comes with me, right?
No, I want to take the horse, too
Yeah, I gotta talk to impa. Okay impa would have the answer right? All right, let's go talk to impa. Where's prank?
Frank too does not hear me. So I can't have a horse. I can't fast travel and then have a horse
Let's go on in the review. By the way, we need to run around but you seem just fine
Locked memento is complete
Now then let me see
Yeah, this is the camera that zelda used a hundred years ago
Could be that if you visit locations within those pictures, you'll be able to restore some of your lost memories
So it's like the elden ring paintings
cool
Okay
Have I been to one of them be properly equipped?
I won't fail. That was the tenth reference
That was an elden ring reference. That was not dark souls reference
kid
What do you got? It's the same thing
Okay, so you found the fairy fountain
Oh, wait, I know what that is
Oh, let's go. Let's do it
Should I just fuck up the quest because of them new clothes cute outfits
cute outfits
Oh
You have a sheikah slate on your hip
Wait a sheikah slate
Isn't that like an incredible thing that only incredible people can have?
Hold on. Just looking for a cute outfit
I don't want it. I have climbing gear
Oh shit, i'm losing them
Mask is op. Oh, maybe i'll get it later. I'm not going anywhere
Grain juice is pretty good. Yeah, I know where it is
Okay. Yeah, I know where it is. It's where the uh, the big lady is right?
That's a good pick too. Isn't there something she can do?
Enhance your clothing
Wow
Take a look. Wait a minute climb climbers bandana
And some rush rooms make this better
Choo-choo jelly soldiers armor
Okay
All right. I need rush rooms and I can upgrade my climbing gear
Cool. I need a picture of a rush room. Do I have rush rooms?
I think I have a picture. Well, not a picture. I think I have one in my inventory
Don't I?
Do I have a single rush room? I don't think so
Where do you get rush rooms?
I cooked them all. Yeah, but they're on the sides of cliffs, aren't they?
Usually they stick it out of a cliff
We can find one right here
It's the purple ones on the clips. I'll check that after this guy
Maybe this guy will give me some uh rush room
Here's the picture
That's it. It's beautiful, but I thought it would be more sacred and elegant
How is that not elegant and sacred? Is there a place you've been seeking?
Oh, I know where that is. All right big mountain east of this way. I know that place
There's a big mountain east of this village. It's called mount
Leneiru at the base of mount leneiru on the west side of najra snowfield lies that gate
base of mount leneiru west side of najra we're gonna mark it west of the
najra snowfield
so like here i'm gonna put a pin here and it's gonna be a
Um, go check this shit up. It's up from there. I'll figure it out. All right, I need to find
Some rush rooms. Let's check the clips
Because if i'm right here, I might as well try to upgrade this
No rush rooms
I don't see any
Oops, I distinctly remember there was a ton
Somewhere else. I remember just passing by them and not picking them up. I was like, nah, I don't need them
Put them on your sensor. I don't have a picture of them. Oh i'm doing that
Look at this
It's a great find. Look at all that money
Cool. All right
Here we go
Trine trine
And then i'm gonna open that thingy
What's wrong?
Hold on
There's a little thing here wooden bow rusty claymore
Sucks super fairy
Oh, okay
Soldier's broadsword. I feel like I have some crap to get rid of
Yeah, I do
This thing was better
Tortures are easy to find. Yeah, they are but I feel like I need one and I don't have one sometimes
back there
Okay, is this swamp or can I stand in this?
Where am I even going? All right. So I do want to go this way. This is kind of the direction I want to be going
All right trying time. I love the shrines. There's so much fun
shrine time
Why do we do that? Has anybody figured that out? Is there a reason why?
Anytime you stretch or if you're lying in bed or if you're just you have to make this horrible noise
why
When I get up in the morning, it doesn't happen every time either. It's just like I don't I don't know why
It's never been explained
And you freeze your whole body locks up
Why do we lock up and scream?
I'm not the only person that does this right?
Yeah, when you guys get up in the morning, do you lock up and scream?
Yes. Yeah, everybody does right that's emote only you can't tell me shit. All right, so that's obviously not what you do climb
World's most simple task. Okay, cool. Great. Now what?
Um, all right, so i've got stasis. Okay, check this out. I think I know what to do. What's that?
That it you have to do it. It's two more times. Oh fuck dude. I got the bowl already
um
wait
Okay, so I gotta put the button down hold on
That's what you do. You just gotta scoop it up like a reverse claw machine. I know what i'm doing
Let me know that's what that's exactly what you're supposed to do. I'm just too slow watch this ready
I didn't I wanted to i'll get it right here
That's definitely what you do. That's definitely it's just the stupid thing
I need to get this in the right spot. Come on. Check this out. I got it ready
So if I come straight up from here
I want to get the ball
No, I had it. I I just did it. I just did it. I just did it
But this thing was too fucking wiggly. I just did it. I just did it guys. I just did it
I'm doing it that way. I don't I just did it I fucking win
That's it. I got it. I win. Did you lose your points? I did it. You could have just left a ball on top
Right. Thank god, that's over
Let's make me sneeze that wasn't even that bad. It wasn't even that bad. There's another one right over here
I do have four orbs. I think I need to do health. I'm getting one hit killed way too often way too often
What the heck is that thing? Oh my god, it burped. Where was that other? Uh shrine there it is
Get out of there
I'm doing the shrine. Here's my plan
I'm doing the shrine here and then i'm gonna wrap around here to do the divine beast. That's my plan
How do you what do you turn in the spirit orbs again? I forget
Who does that?
Make sure you get this tower too. Yeah, i'm gonna get that tower
and
All right the route i'm gonna go
Straight that way get the tower get the shrine
And then i'm gonna bang a right
that way
Get this tower
And get that tower. How do I take out the binoculars to mark again?
I can do with the camera, right?
How do I do this? It's l3
Right stick. Okay. Yeah, thank you
Okay. All right
Cool. Let's go the statue and uh kakariko. Okay
How long are you gonna be live for? Um
I don't know. I'm gonna have a set plan
an hour or two
Where's your horse? I know I just don't have one. Did I just call a bunch of bulls?
What did the horse call do that?
Why did I just call that?
Why are they all freaking out?
That was a word smoke here. What's this?
It's a new ingredient
I'm so dumb
Oh, what's this?
Arm-o-ran
There yeah, is there a chest here usually there is right? Oh nice arrows
Kind of running out of weapons
Oh the cleave that was perfect. Okay, that was challenging
Something good night's halberd. I'll take it
spiked boko spear
and
Onto the shrine
Zapturum make sure to take a picture of the weapons
Take photos
Oh you there
Over here over here. Oh, I just been calling on you. So suddenly
I am lido a proud member of the distinguished zora
Are you a real hylian? I had no choice but to call upon you
Will you spare me a moment of your time?
Sure
See that tower the one atop that mountain. Yeah, I need you to go upstream of zora river
Which runs along the north side of that tower to inogo bridge
I can see it in your eyes. You're asking yourself why
Reasonable question for a stranger frosted by a passing zora in such a manner
But I must assure you this venture will be profitable for you as well
See prince cedan of zora is in desperate search of a strong hylian
And as a loyal request from the prince himself, it's safe to assume a generous reward is in the cards
I'm asking you go meet prince cedan at inogo bridge along the zora river just upstream from here
You're getting robbed
Okay
That's fine
That's not wait. Do I I can I don't have to accept it?
Or just know that it's there
zidon
Uh, not good green nut. Um, do I have to land in here or maybe what do I have to burn it or something?
Fire right? Yeah, I remember seeing that spoiler from last time. I was live
That sucks, i'm sorry, man
Okay, so I need fire
This fire over there
Question is can I bring it this way?
Is this like a giant torch?
This thing right here
Oh, I have flint
Dude, I can stand in this why do you drown in that I can stand up. Hello
This doesn't work
What about my arrow? Wait, hold on. Yeah, that doesn't start a fire. Hold on. I'll be right back
Does this work? You need wood and flint. What the fuck?
Wood and flint. I almost got no more left. Okay, bro. Your dark uga is showing
Dark uga this is a bug in my hair. Oh boy. They're done. Are they done?
They can burn or whatever. This is worse than a regular apple regular apple is better. No, it's not it's not
I thought it was one heart. No, that's not what I said. I I mean I like regular apples in real life
I don't like baked apples. I like old apples. You guys misunderstood me. I want more weapons and armor and stuff
Let's trial speed of light. I got it. Okay now it's only the second. Mm-hmm. Right now that shit floods
It seems I don't know where to go
This elevator goes up but this barrel
Goes down
Hmm. All right. Um
It's definitely something out here. What if I block this and do anything?
What's the point of this?
Oh, thank god ice cold. Do I have to like fill the barrel with water so it makes sense, right? Make it heavier
It's not what you do. I probably have to spin this thing back but
Can I?
Interesting. Why would I want to do that though?
Why would I want to stop that? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know but let me go over here. Okay, if I go like this
Oh the water
Water. Uh-huh. But so I put the water fill the tank with water
Fill the thing with water. Okay now
Now
Okay, so I have to get this plan is to get this back over there
And then get over there myself
Freeze time on that thing
All right. I know what to do
This could be wrong, but whatever let's try it
Get this back over there. Okay now
I'm gonna do this
What if I do that maybe that's stupid this could be stupid but we'll find out
I can't freeze time on this. So, all right, I'm gonna freeze time on you
Spin it
Go
All right. Got it. Wasn't that bad. Is this for a spirit orb? Very cool spirit orb
Five. Yep
Cool. All right. Now I'm gonna activate the tower
And oh I have the seeds too, don't I? I got four of those. The time freeze didn't do anything
You didn't even notice the extra chest
Yeah, whatever
There's some unobtanium over here though link. You are an awful swimmer. Give me a break really i'm gonna drown in here
No, i'm not. Where is it? What a waste. That's such a waste
Nah, i'll just die. Whatever just die
Go ahead and die
Yep, I can't make that i'm gonna jump. I'm just gonna jump from off the shrine
Go from up here. All right ice functions. You're right. I forgot I had ice
I keep forgetting you can use this stuff outside of the shrines in my brain. It's a shrine power
Get the unobtanium and then head over here
Let's get the shit out of me
Cool, let's go sledgehammer is damaged. Where do you get? I have not found another sledgehammer. All right, it's broken
But how do you get another sledgehammer?
Oh
I could have taken a picture of it post the lead pic. There's a bunch about okay. All right stay
Through to this mission here. That's what i'm going after. Why is it getting so dark?
Step right up and buy them. I find bananas. They're available. They're so yellow they make you yell. Oh, okay
I'll buy some sure a hundred dollars
That'll take your life what you just love when the fucking lock-on turns around and looks at the shrine behind you
Got something to say
mighty bananas
vicious sickle and
oh
$15 never mind. I like the halberds. They're really that the reach is awesome shrine. Ooh, really? Let's go
It was 99 bananas. I think it was just a mighty banana
uh one
I don't think it was more than one
All right vantage point interesting camp that I don't want to go into
Ooh, I keep seeing these around but that's right. Get out of the way. Get out of the way
Oh cool, where's that shrine I wasn't make it I don't see the shrine that was blinking
Said it was right over here
Only this had a mountain
Find out other mountain peak. Yeah, okay here it is
I'm not I don't want to kill the fog
What about shield surfing how do you do you parry
There it is
Oh rush rooms. Take a picture. I already have a picture. That one's better. All right, that was down here, right?
Okay, I didn't know that you could get that hurt doing that. I guess that was pretty brutal
I thought I was safe. I guess
But no, I was not
Wait, who are you?
Big hearty radish greatest vegetable on earth
Oh, how wonderful you are a hylian. Yes
Oh, it's my lucky day
Oh, I apologize for calling you out. So suddenly I am torfu of zora
I've been searching for a hylian like you for a very long time
My home zora's domain is in terrible danger. That's why prince
How do you say it?
zydon
Prince zydon sent me in search of a strong hylian warrior
Prince zydon is waiting at that bridge over there
Would you please talk to the prince and perhaps save us all
zydon
Sedon Sedon
So I don't know how to say it man. I don't play zelda
How do you say it?
Sedon
zydon
Like Poseidon like Poseidon
side
Haven't I been saying that?
Combat trial. Oh
All right. I'm taking some food here. This is defense. This is attack boost. I'm going with this
Let's go computer play celery man. Well that attack up is fucking incredible
I'm making so many more of those
What did I miss?
Why did it miss? It shouldn't have missed
It shouldn't have missed
Uh computer, can I see a nude tamed please?
That is not safe for work
Your wife is calling. She says it's an emergency
I'm doing the dodge and it's not happening. Give me the attack food. Where is it?
Do it. Oh
We don't know what that is
A guardian shield. You know, I know what that is guardian sword
Oh, yep
Tons of uh, blankets. Nice. I don't didn't already have a guardian shield. I do right?
Guard oh the guardian shield plus. Okay
and a chest
That's really good
And an orb. I might be able to get two levels up
soon
They're great for sliding
Orb count. Oh, it said six
Yeah, i'm blocking it that one guy is wrong. Don't do that. They break instantly
Oh, okay. Can you please do the get out of here? Get out of here. Come on. Get out of here. Yeah, sure for you
It's your birthday
uh
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Yeah, get out get out of here. Come on. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out of here. Get out of here
Get out of here
Hey
Hello there
It was this is that person's birthday
Yeah, it's this
Yeah, it was that person's birthday. So happy birthday
What the fuck is that that's hoover the talking seal
All right. I'm doing that
That's what that's from yes
Yeah, that I didn't that's not me doing that. I mean, it's me doing an impression of that
Why did you have that ready? Uh a mod posted in mod chat?
They were prepared
Don't mean um side
Oh
I'm so bad at the game that I missed the opportunity to get uh dark souls
Get out get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here
What I just shoot
Hey, hey
Oh there
What a weird animal it's fine fine
I'm i'm just gonna be left with awesome equipment and then i'm gonna have to start going down the list
Oh stop
Does it have to be raining permanently right now? I feel like it's been raining the whole time i've been streaming
You're weird if I call you weird. That means you're weird weird
Don't be stupid. Wait, hold on this stuff important
You're gonna end up with 999 jellies
Why did I die? What did I what did I stub my toe on the ground? And what was that about?
Forever is it still raining?
It's still raining
Even with the climbing outfit on
Okay
Oh giant dinosaur bones, they just throw a rock at me
Who did that?
You dick you dick. Who is it?
What the hell is that?
Whoa, what did I just do?
These are explosive arrows. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
What was that thing?
Ice rod waves of freezing air
Does it break?
I don't want to put that on
Holy shit. Okay. This is awesome. Very cool. All right
Most of the tower
Chest or anything. Can I break these with the club or does it have to be a hammer?
Damn it bombs will do it in bobs do it too. Cool
Uh, some lucky person is gonna like find that and get rich and that's fine. I don't care
interesting
Press for a moment. Have I given a rating? It's uh,
Um, I don't know it's definitely a
it's way higher than an eight because i'm
Realizing the amount of things you can actually do
It's very comfy
Okay
I know people are gonna be mad that i'm gonna say this
but
All right, whatever i'm gonna say
This is a comfy elden ring. It's not I didn't say easier
It's not oh, this is like a kid's game. No, no, no
It's just a comp. It's just a comfier elden ring
I don't I mean, yeah, maybe i've been a little stressed during some of the encounters but for the most part i'm not
um
I'm not stressed the fuck out like I am everywhere in elden ring
When I die in this I just kind of laugh it off and I just climb the mountain again
You don't really get penalized for losing like you do in the prom software games, obviously
Like i'll ski off the mountain and fall down and die
Because it doesn't matter i'm not gonna lose 50 000 souls or something
Or forget how I I not even get back to that area again
Elden ring for non-clout chasers
No, what do you think clout chasers?
Why is the elden ring for clout chasers?
I can't believe it
Excuse me. Have you talked to uh syden yet? He's down there
Yep, I order prince syden of zora's domain. I'm searching for a hylian
Found you go to the bridge and okay, they're really pushing this into my face
They are shoving this down my throat right now. They're just like push. It's like they're just like hey
Go go go go
There's a guy syden there. He is
Go to syden go he's up there. Oh, by the way, i'm gonna go find him
So I mean what what?
I said they're pushing it down. They're jumping it in my throat. That's saying
That's a saying
Okay, I just typed it
Don't google that
You could find yourself in a little bit of trouble
I I just oh that oh god
I got a warning. It was like are you sure?
I'm like what it means. Oh fucking jesus christ
Oh my god
The legend of zelda prince syden. What did I google? I just never mind it. Just forget it
Forget everything. Don't forget everything
Oh
Push this guy off you can't there's no there's no collision
I'm having a little bit of trouble. Is that it's prince syden down here
Found him say hey there young one up top above you
What's up syden?
He's googling pardon the entrance. I I don't have to tell you what I typed in
I was hoping perhaps you'd have a moment to talk people question marked by use of that phrase
And I was like, what are you talking about? So I typed it in
And I just I was like, okay, wait
What why is it what everybody wanted me to come see syden?
I am syden the zora prince
What is your name?
People really like syden
Okay
Have we ever met this person?
I mean in the other
Uh zelda games
Is prince syden a character that's in the other games?
That's me
I am a zora prince after all I have an eye for talent that is unparalleled
Yes exquisite
I've been searching for someone like you for a long while a man like you link who carries himself with power
Right now zora's domain is in grave danger because of the massive rainfall coming from divine beast varuta. Okay, that explains it
Please promise you will help us. We need your strength warrior. Won't you please come to zora's domain?
Sure now zora's domain will be saved for certain no time to waste. Hurry up and head over
Because of the rain the cliffs are too wet to climb I figured that out earlier
To reach the domain you will need to go straight along this path
As a hylian, I know you are unable to swim up
As such the path to the domain may be difficult
You likely have a tough fight in store. There are monsters up ahead that attack with electricity
Don't give up. I believe in you
Oh, that's right. I have something that I'd like to give you
small trinket
electro elixir
Cool grants of mid-level resistance to electricity
Everybody loves this person. Everybody loves it
Sidon, but who's my favorite character?
I need to know who my favorite character. All right, so we're gonna go to we're gonna do this, but not yet
What did I just what the hell is this hero's path mode? Wait, is this showing?
Is this showing where I've been like these frivolous? What?
What what happened here?
What happened here? I don't know what I did over here press a
What killed me? Uh-huh
Wasn't that the first area?
I teleported to this
How many times did you guys die in this first like
Level one starter zone
What was going on here? This is not accurate. This is not accurate
What happened?
What did I do was I fucking drunk?
Was I high?
What happened? Oh, that's the stone guy, right? How do you die in kakariko village? It's impossible
God damn it, man. Oh my god
Okay, so I teleported back to there back to the same spot. Why did I teleport back here? What are you doing?
Here we are. Why did I teleport three times the same place? That's a cool. I like that feature a lot
That's so fun. Go fight that guy now. Oh my should I go get revenge? I'm getting revenge
I got bomb arrows. This guy is in deep shit. I don't have any hammers. Do I actually need a hammer?
All right, where is this dude?
Right here, right? Where is he brian brian?
Where is he who's over here? Right? If you beat the game in under 200 hours, we could watch the whole thing
Really?
Will I beat this game and lock this monster? What the hell is that thing? Oh my god. I have an idea
Why are these not exploding? It's a bomb arrow
What because it's raining?
I'm kind of more curious about the huge dragon eel serpent thing that was just flying around over here. Where'd it go?
Whoa
What is that? Holy shit. Okay. I'm gonna get a good pic of this focus it
Oh look, he's like landing into my hand. Probably shouldn't fight this you're right there
No, no stay on task task task stay on task stay on task
I'm gonna go over there and I'm gonna get the things gonna kill me i'm gonna breathe fire
It's gonna kill me and i'm gonna die in one hit. I need to fight that thing when I have 20 hearts
So we're over here by the okay scouts hill i'm gonna go there and i'm gonna find the rock person
See if i'm strong enough
Over here right here, right? Yeah, he's right here. Okay, let's use
Um, just let me use the spy club first him right here. No, this is him right here
No, yep. Okay. This is him. Why is it glowing now? It wasn't glowing before
Like get out
What's that? Yeah. Oh, yeah
Lock on cameras in every video game suck. What's that? Yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah roger that sore loser
Kind of hurt i'm just gonna do
I'm only gonna use bombs. Why would I do anything else?
They're effective incredibly effective. Oh that hurt. Whoa, he dropped something. I don't have any arrows shit
Actually, you know what? I don't want to die in one hit. I might be able to take three hits still need an apple hit marker
Oh my god, don't blow me up
Come on, come on
It's downhill bullshit. It's really spurring everything up
There's a glancing glow i'm fine
It's glancing glow. I'm okay
Yeah, I get he's I get
Yeah, get it back. I you know what i'm saying? He's on the downhill track
Oh my god
I'm fine
This fucking thing too, why is he doing this?
I win
What did you drop?
topaz
opal amber
Oh
I got it. We're rich. Wait people weren't betting again people were betting on me
Am I alive? Am I okay? What was that?
Do I get out of here? What does that mean?
ah
Don't get on higher ground. What am I thinking duck?
Put the metal away, dude
Metal in a lightning storm. That's really what it was
So what all the uh, uh, uh, I really am just a walking conductor, aren't I? I get it. I feel
Accomplished maybe not the smartest way the g4 rated the stream. Did I miss that?
You hear from g4? What's going on? I didn't even see it
Uh-uh
Um, but wait, don't I have the what did I get a topaz?
So I killed the boss
It took me like 10 straight minutes to do that and after the boss dies
I pick up all the items and then get struck by lightning because i'm
The tin man. I have a bunch of pots and pans on me and I die instantly and then it didn't save
I have to do it again
You got killed by an act of god
Dude, I have to do that again
um
Okay. Well
I'm I'm not i'm not doing that again
Chatter is upset about the vet. Do I have the topaz? I don't see it anywhere
No times one
No
Sapphire
No, it didn't save
Well shit. Okay. Well, I beat it and I know it's there but i'm gonna mark it like right here because i'll come back and do it again
I'll just come back and kill it at like level 50. Okay. Well now I need to change this stamp
to
What is what is npc again leaf? I don't remember spend the orbs. You need more hearts. Yeah. All right
I can let me go to
Let me do two more shrines so I can do a double turn in that's what i'm doing
It's in here
Anything uh fucked up anything fucked up in here?
I don't see anything here
I'm just going this way
All right, i'm biting my lip and I don't want you to see it's so bad right now. All right
I have to stop stop ryan. I'll find one up here. Damn it relax your eyebrows
Um, I just have deep set eyes. My eyes are always in kind of like a brow
Whatever it is called. This is gonna be fucking secrets up here gonna be secrets up here, right furrowed brow. That's right
All right. So what's up here? Interesting. Come on, dude. Really? I don't have a single arrow. You gotta be shitting me
And I still get the item I can probably get the torch too where to go that went way over
Ah
Look at that. Would you look at that shrine?
Oh, i'll get this tower
Oh, i'm almost out of terrible weapons. Oh, no, i'm not done. I got this one. No get down
Anything over here fishing harpoon cool zora spear. I want to throw this I miss
uh
Sidance already to the boomerang. I can't care. I uh, it's cool, but I don't think I want it. I'll try it
But
I'm just checking around the sides. You never know. It's two week rift. Are you playing slime rancher tomorrow? No
I'm doing birthday stuff tomorrow. I'll be back on saturday. We're gonna do
Uh slime rancher 2 on saturday and then probably back to breath of the wild on sunday
You gotta do a birthday stream. No, i'm not doing a birthday stream a lot of enemies here a lot of enemies here
Thank god long enough for me to find some. Okay, so take off unequip literally everything, right? How do I unequip everything?
I take off all I because uh the lightning shit i'm not holding anything. I'm just naked
I'm not gonna get struck by lightning, right?
I won't get struck by lightning if i'm naked
I hope that's accurate
Clothes are fine
And wooden weapons are fine. I don't think I have anything that's wood. There's the harpoon. I mean this is metal at the end
No, just climbing
These metal
Take them off take them off. Okay, we're good clothes do not matter ants are safe clothes don't matter
Well, um, I made it up here
Pants are safe. All right, here's the plan two more shrines. I'm gonna do the omega turn in level up twice
And then probably call it there
I got one shrine marked. Oh if it's sparking in the menu, it's unsafe. That's interesting. Okay
Good to know let's take a quick look
You can't say omega when it's not omega gaming weekend
That's true
No, you're right. Okay, that one's marked
Any others from here I could be able to see a lot. Um
Not that I can see from here. I think that's the only one
I think that actually is the only one
Yeah
Really? Damn. What about here?
Is that
Rubble or something or is that a monster?
I'm marking it whatever it is
All right. Well, let's go
I can't get struck by lightning in the air, but i'm just ready to get struck
Look at the menu. Oh
Okay
So these are safe
Cool, they do a little twinkle
I'm too lazy to go pick that up pretty good snapshot. Oh you ducked. Did you just go like this?
You just put his arms in like I don't know
Go I need to heal I have tons of food. I really haven't been taking that much damage
I die instantly. I don't take damage and die. You're talking about that one, right?
Yes, you are
What's this little uh
An encampment or something. What is this?
Where's my bow?
Oh, I unequipped it because I freaked out, right?
I can't turn
Got him
Okay. What is this? Oh stables, isn't it? Horse horse horse horse? I already have a horse. Oh my god
I hit the horse in the head. I'm sorry
Hello, this thing's gonna be free
Yeah, go on. You're good
Where's my where's my horse?
No, I don't want to register this one. Uh, I'd like to take my horse, please
Uh frank
I want frank
Two, please
Okay. All right, let's move
All right. It's been real. See you later frank two. Bye
We got to hang out for
eight seconds
I'll have seven orbs after this. I need eight. Oh, thanks g4 for the ride g4 tv. Appreciate it
And you guys are still here combat or puzzle. That's a different door
It's not a combat trial. I think it's a puzzle metal doors open the way
Okay, what are you doing here?
All right, ooh
He put only a yeah, I think that bow is not good five damage rival is bow. No, thanks
You can stay in there
Okay. Well, I can't grab that
I don't know try to rocket jump figured it was worth the shot can't grab that from here
Hmm
Okay
Um, I guess
Okay, I think I understand it now
Yeah, I didn't know they could fall
Okay, I
Oh my god, whatever
I'm trying to block it
Who seven orbs seven? Yep seven get the other treasure now
Uh, the thing sucked it was like a traveler's bow. There's a third chest where
Where there's an other treasure hidden here? There's a fake wall. It's in the wall that you stared at like a moron
I wasn't paying attention to what the wall looked like. I was trying to do the puzzle
The wall that you were staring at like a moron
Okay, not in here
I
Just die just kill this thing
I'm gonna go this thing sucks
Oh my god, did I really just get this okay
I'll take a free guardian spear
All right. So where's this thing that I was looking at like a moron?
There's a hidden wall that I was looking at
Look at the walls
Use magnetic and look at the walls. I yeah, I didn't sorry. I didn't see this
I wasn't paying attention to the the I know I didn't see it. No, I
No, I didn't that's 300 rupees though. That's pretty good. You did look at it
You just didn't notice it and then in brackets like a moron
Like a moron. He's pretending for content
Hey, gotta get that 300 hour breath of the wild playthrough
Okay, so I want one more shrine. I don't am I gonna be able to find one over here?
I'm gonna say this way. I bet this one over here bring frank to
All right
To why am I sitting on this like a weirdo?
Oh
But he just oh, okay
I thought I thought frank to just mood
Why can't I walk up the walls I don't want to go on the road
This isn't sky room
moron
like a moron
Fine
Where's it at this way this way?
Uh, all right. There it is
Well, then let's go the long way down here
You can make that jump. I know it's not sky room, but it's come on
No, no, i'm not doing it. All right, fine. I'll do it
Where to go? All right, come on down. It seems frank who isn't able to come. Okay fine
I don't know sometimes there's a little uh, the little forest creatures. All right
This is the last shrine we're doing tonight, then i'm gonna go level up twice
And then uh, i'm gonna like half hour. You need to have you need ancient horse here. That's cool
Combat trial or a puzzle trial
I know this is a combat trial. I got plenty of good weapons. This should be I should be able to do this pretty easily
Minor test of strength. Okay, i'll be fine. At least I hope so
I shouldn't use a fishing harpoon though. Use this thing
Why won't you dodge sideways dodge sideways finally what the heck is happening
Uh-oh
You do this thing out of here guardian sword and another guardian shield
Yep, can't carry any more shields. Yes, I can. It's the same thing. I'll get rid of this one then
Uh
Yep. Yeah, wait 16 and eight. Uh, whatever keep the wood one. I thought this one was 18. Okay 16
All right
so all the
guardian shield plus
Okay, cool. Where's your nintendo shirt? I had it on for like four hours
It was just getting really sweaty and hot so I just take it off boomerang. I don't want that
Oh better than the this
Cool, okay. Now I need to go back to the village
And i'm gonna level up stamina twice
Is that bad? Or should I do health twice? I feel like I need the hearts. I'm gonna do uh hearts twice
Yeah
Only a four
Yeah, I gotta stop. Yeah. Yeah. I'm a four health Andy. I know it's bad
Maybe I won't get one hit killed by the regular enemies anymore if I had six hearts
We scream
So i'm good
I'm gonna go back to uh, where's that? Where do I need to go here? Where's that thing?
Shrine island
All towns have a statue. Okay. Well, i'll just go back to next to impa two hearts
Oh, i'm gonna bet that yeah the seed guy too. I'll do that as well
Just cleaning up some loose ends
All right, so saying right
next to impa's house
Which is here right on a heart container i'm doing too very good do it again
All right. That's feels pretty good. Now. I want to go back to
I marked you on the map right here, right? Okay. I'll just walk here. He's not there anymore upgrade your armor
Oh, that's right
That's right. That's right. That's right. All right, we're gonna go there first still there
So i'm gonna upgrade my chest piece first. He still might be there. Okay, welcome back enhance away. Let's go
All right, so the chest piece it goes from three to five
Or I could do the helmet
Three to five three to five is the same thing
Maybe the armor
I feel like the helmet
Because if I find a much better chest piece, I could still keep the helmet on
i'm doing it
Thank you five armor nice set of clothes that have all been enhanced twice can have a bonus
But you have to wear the whole thing
I mean i'm wearing the pants
I mean, why not?
How hard is it? I feel like these materials are not hard to get so i'm just gonna do it
Just in case at least a level one stuff
Very cool. Okay. Now I did
Upgraded my gear
That was step one of two now i'm going over here
To see if that guy's there to do inventory slots
Then i'm gonna wrap it up
This doesn't do this
I don't know what to do with this
The ball somewhere
You can do this again next stream. I will do this again on sunday plan is to do
Uh slime rancher 2 comes into early access tomorrow
So i'll do that on saturday
And we'll help back into breath of the wild on sunday and then after that we'll see
We will see
You actually want to keep playing this
Yeah, I mean if you guys like watching it then why not i'm having a good time if you like it
If you want me to continue and you want me to beat it
Then i'll just keep playing it
Yeah, definitely
All right. Where are you?
Yeah, you're still there
All right. I got five of these
All right
I
another weapon stash
I go through weapons. So crazy
and then maybe
field
What about splatoon 3 i'll do that too at some point
Wait, what bring some to korok forest?
Uh, whatever
Okay. Well, at least I did that
See you later speaking to see you later. I'll see you later
North of here all the Hylia river and continue north. Okay
Yeah, i'll see you later the next couple days i'm gonna do some birthday stuff
I appreciate uh, everyone hanging out though
Maybe we'll see you again
a couple days
Slime rancher 2 going into early. I don't know how much content will be in slime rancher 2 is early access
So I will find out but i'll see you later. Thanks for watching
Save your game. I will do it right now officially saved
Okay, they were a shitload of subs today
This is 25 pages of subs. Are you kidding me? Oh my god. Well, thank you
I'll have a good birthday. I'm just i'm just gonna it's gonna be chill our prime subs included in the credits
I think all subs are any sub that comes through during the time the stream is live. I think is there
Yeah, there was some big gifted subs, too
Yeah, i'm sure probably some of you saw the news about twitch's changing how they monetizing partners. Let me just be very clear
Um, I ain't fucking running ads. It's just not happening
So
We'll see however that plays out
I mean, I I obviously have opinions on it and you know, one of the major ones is
I don't want to be forced to run ads because in my mind a ton of people are already paying
Essentially a premium to the stream
So I don't oh, yeah, thanks for your essentially kind of like netflix like subscription
Here's a shitload of ads every day. I don't want to do that. So i'm i'm not going to
Um, if I am forced to run ads on this platform, I will leave this platform
100%
so
I'm not going to be forced to run ads
Now here's the thing ads do play pre-rolls play and I don't really have that much control over that
I do have control over if one essentially runs while you're sitting here and I don't want to do that
I don't want to run ads
You've seen ads on big streams before sometimes to fill dead air
sometimes part of a
Obligation but regardless of of how they're changing subscription revenue. I'm not going to run ads. Let's run an ad right now
Ads aren't that bad ads aren't that bad
They really aren't in the grand scheme of things if it depends on how many you run
But I don't want to be forced to do them the thing about ads, especially on twitch. They're pretty intrusive
For a few reasons one if they happen automatically we could be in the middle of doing something
And you're just gone for two to three straight fucking minutes. It takes over the whole screen. You don't even
What if you missed something interesting like one of eight or like one of four or one of three?
Whatever it is now running ads on a brb is something that okay
Yeah, that may maybe that would make sense
But I don't want to be forced to run ads if you're contractually obligated to run ads
Yeah, that's not the case right now, but I don't want that to be the case and if it does become the case
I'll just leave I mean that I really do the phrase ads aren't that bad as a weak mindset
You're okay with what happened losing imperfection
Uh, is that a meme? What is that?
Oh, it's the ninja thing, okay
But I just want to be clear about that because I know that a lot of people might be saying oh shit
Which is changing how money and
He's gonna quote have to make up the money. No, I don't give a fuck. No, I don't care
If you I want people to have the best viewing experience if I can
I'm not gonna just run ads if I have to i'll just i'll literally stream
I'll literally make fucking videos again or something. I don't know
Yeah, I don't know I i'm not gonna make any statements about
I have some ideas of maybe I would want to change platforms or something, right? That's not what this is for
a lot of these
Changes are not even happening till like the what the middle of next year
So there's lots of time to figure out what I would want to do
and
if
Which changes a lot of their policies to make it so you have to run ads or something. It's like, I don't know
I'd rather just
Stream off like youtube and not have to do that if I didn't have to and let me maybe make videos again
I don't know
I really don't know
But i'm trying to be transparent with everybody right now
Um, and that's me being transparent
We got about uh, 10 months before this is even a question to even figure out
So don't worry. It's not like oh, all right. Well
That's
See you on see on youtube tomorrow. No
Uh, this is like a year away before a major decision like that will have to get made
But i'm going
I'm gonna be where I think is the best viewing experience for people here
Regardless of how much money I would or would not be making or would or would be losing but whatever
We'll see
But uh, have a great night. I'm gonna go do birthday stuff
Have a great night guys
Take care of yourselves
Oh, yeah, there is a trombone game, isn't there?
I keep people I see people play the trombone game. What is it fun?
Should I do it?
Yes, please. Okay
It sucks
It looks fun. All right. Good night guys. See you soon
Take care of yourselves
Goodbye. See you saturday