We're gonna, I'm gonna open Viscera. Viscera got a new level. Really? Okay, so, uh,
Amid Evil, we are probably gonna, we're gonna stop here from Amid Evil. We're gonna move on
to Viscera Cleanup, but I like this game. You will probably end up seeing this game again.
Nah, Viscera, um, Viscera's pretty fun, but I don't think, I fucked it up. I said the wrong game.
I was trying to do like, nevermind, fuck it, I just said the wrong thing. I was gonna say, like,
it's, like, pretend it's been like two weeks, and like, I'm never playing this game again.
I said the wrong game. Just pretend like I made something funny happen. I was trying to get the
music queued up, too. Oh well. All right, we're gonna play Viscera Cleanup Detail. Merry Christmas,
everybody. What, what's the new level called? I already did the Christmas level. Do I even
have this game installed? I do. Is it just on the base, Viscera Cleanup Detail? Or is, do I have to
buy it? Do I actually have to buy it? What's it called? Here, just put the BRB on for you.
Is it, it's like DLC? Oh, okay. Would it be on a DLC? House of Horror the Vulcan Affair.
I've already, I've done this. Is it a separate video game, not DLC?
Is it not called Visceral Cubes? Have you done the Vulcan Affair? I don't even remember.
Have I? What is the Vulcan Affair? They're just debating you. All right, well, fuck it,
we'll just open up, we'll open up one of them. I'm the god of so excited for the stream.
Uh, I don't think I've done the Vulcan Affair. How big is this one? It's spy themed? This is the
newest one. All right, well, fuck it, whatever, I'll try it. Your account already owns this game.
Oh, how? What? I don't have it listed here. I don't own this. You already own this game.
What? It's not in my library. Viscera Cleanup Detail, Santa's Rampage, and then Shadow Warrior.
I don't have this. It's just DLC on the base game. Let's just open it. Should I launch 64-bit or
play, just play it normally? I haven't played this in a long time. I don't remember. All right,
let's go. Hey, and the title doesn't even need to change. That could, that still makes sense.
All right, hold on. Switch game, DLC. The Vulcan Affair. I don't even own this. All right, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, FOV 90, windowed mode. Nope. 1920 by 1080, windowed mode, turn it off.
Okay, gamma, 0.75, FOV 90, view bob, get it out of here. Dynamic shadows, sure.
Environmental shadows, I guess. Sure, motion blur, get it out of here. Bloom, who wants that?
Light shafts, nobody wants those either. Anti-aliasing, times two. Antroscopic filtering,
four. Ambient occlusion, get that out of here. It's ugly. Expensive particles, sure. Okay. Oh,
I think it crashed. Did it? Yeah. Too many expensive particles. I don't know where to get it. Hold on.
All right, there it is. Start assignment. It's a little, it's kind of loud.
Audio, sound, master down to 50, effects, music, ambient, that's whatever, that's fine.
Start. I would like to play solo. Save file, game type, clean up, work site, the Vulcan Affair,
okay. Game rules, I know how this works. Disable the sniffer, time limit, footprint limit, unlimited,
that's fine. All right, let's go, let's go, let's go. Am I going to be in the YouTube rewind? No.
Why would I be in the YouTube rewind? Okay, company vids you welcome to this
dump or whatever, right? It's a, oh, wait, wait, wait. Your mission, should you choose to accept it?
Well, you have no choice but to accept it or face severe disciplinary measures, understood.
Now then, this sprawling facility and various accessible areas are to be rendered clean and
rehabitable. As always, once decontaminated and cleared, you are to ignore and forget any details
regarding the incident. The multitude of nations that may or may not be connected with the events
would just clean up. Finally, considering the nature of the operations and work,
it's advisable to proceed with caution. Certain devices and systems may remain operable.
Well, that's a 10 million DPI. Okay, all right, so those of you who don't know how to play Vista
Cleanup Detail, it goes like this, and then you clean up stuff. I need to remember how to play.
All right, I need to track down a few things here. What's the, what room do I want to go to first?
Oh, right, put on music. This is new music, right? That's going to get my entire channel deleted.
No, that was, oh, that was all right. It's too loud, though. All right, so I need to find, where's the
broom? All right, this is a guy. Pick him up with the incinerator. Find the incinerator first. That's
most important. Okay, okay, okay. What's this? Warehousing. This shit don't work. What's this?
What's this? No, this is the particle exploder.
Oops. Uh, these are flares. It's a better broom. Now, that's where I put the USB drives.
Cool. So, where is the darks in here? Shit, this is so far away. Where's the incinerator?
Oh, god, this place is huge. All right, so this is where you get the buckets.
That's locked. Does this work? First floor. What about the sharks? Hold on. Oh, that's easy.
All right, wait, is this where you throw stuff away? Did they eat anything? Okay, did that,
okay, cool. Wait, I don't want to walk. What's in here? All right, let me, um, okay, I need a
buckets and shit. Buckets, buckets, buckets, buckets, and all right. Dude, Dr. Evil OST.
There is no, Dr. Evil OST. Is that even what you said? No, you said Dr. Phil OST. Right, okay.
That music sucks. I need my trash bag. Give me my trash bag. There it is.
Now, people get mad if I break this. Okay, we got some trash over here from the Home Depot OST.
I'm desperately trying to grab this. Isn't there a way to grab this a different way?
Depot theme. Hurry up. Home Depot theme. Now, I'll get you guys talking about the trash.
Very cool. All right, give me the mop. Do guns work? That'd be cool if they did. No. Okay,
just get rid of everything. Will they delete everything? So they can't be killed.
They're not gonna die, right? I need to clean that. I'll be up here, right?
One room at a time. This room first. I gotta bring, um, I need to fucking memorize where the
water comes out from. Give me this one. Go two at a time. Okay. When's he gonna do it?
When's he gonna do it? When's he gonna spill it? Here comes the first spill.
Fighting my tongue. I can't believe he's gonna do it. All right, corner to corner. Let's go.
What's over here that's dirty? This place is a clean. This is a clean. There it is. You got
what you wanted. You got what you wanted. There it is. You got it. Done. I did it.
Congratulations, everybody. Job well done, all of you. Okay, now next game. That's what I wanted.
All right, next. Next, do next thing. This one doesn't feel as messy as the other ones.
It just seems a little, it just seems bigger. Am I missing? Do I have to go down floors and shit?
Oh, that's gonna be hell. Let's put all the trash over here.
Fill joke has been filled. Time for the next game.
Great. No, this is where we're staying and this is where we're ending. Play Dark Souls 3. I already
did. A lot. What qualifies as trash? Is that chair trash? Four game stream. I've never done that
before. What's the most games that you've seen on stream in one stream? Three? Two? Probably two or
three. Three, yeah. Go in the water. Why would I go in the water? That's death.
Isn't that gonna kill me? Yeah, no, this chair is junk. Look at this thing. Get rid of it. Why is
it still there? Good. Nice work. Nice work. Dr. Revo Lo St. Anything important? Trash. What's the
dirtiest level in this whole game? Anybody know? What's like the bloodiest, dirtiest level? How did
I knock that over? I wasn't even near it. Like, honestly, next level spill joke. I wasn't even
there. It fell behind me. How do you flip things around quickly? R? E? T? How do you do it? There's
nothing in water in it. Trash. Okay, how are we looking? Not bad. I gotta make sure it's all done
before moving on. No, I'm not doing face cam. There's no reason for face cam.
No, you know, I'm not doing it. No, I refuse. No, no, no. Eat that guy. Bring my trash receptacle
over here, please. One by one. I wish that... Can I just sweep these into the... Can I do that?
Can I do that? Yes, I can. That's it. I'm just painting. No, that's... Just do it. Just do it.
What do we got? This thing is filthy. Is it time to dump? Just very soon here it will be.
Time to dump, yeah. Yeah, it's time to dump. There's too much shit in here.
Good. Dumping. I know. I'm gonna mop it all up later. I should have done this first.
Face cam fortress. That's an old one. Are these open? I don't think they are.
Should you store your teeth? No, no, I don't like my teeth lately. Not lately.
That means they're clean, but they're not... They're not sparkling clean, and I don't like that.
I have to go back. I gotta get a cleaning or something. I think they're green. They're like
dark green. They're a clean green, but they're not... They're not like sparkling white, you know?
Yeah. How long has it been since what? How long since what been? All right,
now let's get the mop in here because everything's cleared out, right?
Nothing else on the ground, right? I don't care about this. Dr. Moreau. Oh, okay. Somebody
screenshot that and read it later. These are both locked. Can I just pick up the whole thing?
Here, watch ready. That didn't work the way that I wanted it to, but what if we're throwing this
away anyway? Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Almost there. Looks all right. Bring a couple buckets.
Can I dunk my feet in there if I step in anything? I didn't fuck this up last time, so...
Baldi's Basics? I've never even played that game and I know what that is. How do I know that? Why do
I know that? I've never even seen anybody play that game. Why do I know that? It's only because of the
in this song. That's what I'm thinking about that. All right, we're almost done. This fucking level
was easy. Fuck. No, it's the FOV. It's not balling up. Whatever. Easy. Yeah, there's this up there.
Why do I know this? I shouldn't know this. I've never fucking played this and I've never seen it.
I've seen the intro screen. What? I know this. Did I play this in my sleep?
And there's another character that goes like, hey, I... Did I? No, I didn't. I did not stream this game.
No, I did not. Give me a clip. I don't believe you. No fucking way. You did. No, I didn't. I know I
did not. Okay, just bring them. Wake up. I don't want to wake up. I want to stay here. So, this is
just part one of like 10, right? In this level. Look at the clip. Nobody linked anything.
I'm getting... I'm getting gaslit by my own community. I know I didn't play it.
Why'd you leave the keys on the table? You made the video. What the fuck are you talking about?
Hold on. Wait, I need to save this because what if it breaks? Oh, shit. Look it. I have stuff.
Five and a half hours? What is this? I made this video. I'm going to play the whole song.
No, I'm not. I don't want to. I don't want to listen to that. I mean, it's a great song. It
just is. But I don't want to play the whole thing. And that just messed up my framerate. Sing the
lyrics. I need water. Oh, I keep thinking. That stream was fucking ridiculous.
I wake up screaming sometimes because of that stream.
No, no, it's not real. Oh, it was. That stream killed me. Me too. All right. Only a couple more
pieces of fresh. And that's it. And I beat it. It was pretty cool. It's pretty good level.
Nice and clean. I have some cigarettes. Looks good. Looks good. This one looks good.
Good. Good. Good. It's a dirty monitor. Get in there. This is the longest YouTube video.
What do you mean? What are you talking about? YouTube video? Monitor lizard? I don't know
you guys talking about an S tier animal. S tier, yeah. Monitor lizard is an S tier animal. We
already know that. I've already done the tier list. All right. Is this clean? It sure is.
All right. What's wrong? What's today's date? Uh, December 3rd. See, I do know some things.
Cheating view the scanner. Part of the game. This looks pretty good. I would call this clean.
Would you? I didn't have to put a cheat code in to get this into the game. Wait, there's something
else here. Where is it? Bucket. Maybe it is the bucket. Is it? Is it? No, it's not the bucket.
Look right here. Oh, well you can't clean them all. That room's done. Is it above?
I don't see anything above. All right. The bucket's out of here. It was the bucket. Yeah.
We're good. Room clean. Don't spill. Okay. Now let's just get rid of this.
How are we looking over here? This room is pretty normal. There's an elevator to go down.
There's an elevator to go down. There's an elevator to go down. That runs off the tongue.
Really fun. Should I go down? Let me check these other floors. All right. Current floor.
One, two. Let's go take a look. Let's go to two. Am I on two?
Am I on two? Let's go down. Not there. This isn't even that messy though. That's not that messy.
What is this? Is it? Is my? Is this massage chairs? Am I activating their massage chairs?
Okay, it's dropping. Oh yeah. All right. Cool. So just put all trash here.
Jump in. Nope. I'm testing the theory. See where it goes. It goes. It's going into the
shark pit. I know where it's going. I can put them in there. I have one of those squares too.
Yeah, I don't even. Just get all trash ready. They have to be in the gray squares. Whatever.
It's okay. I'll do it in a minute. Just get it on a square. Coffee cup. Just get it on a square.
Hats and shit. Just throw it away. Good. Wait, is this chair of music playing out of it?
That easy. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna push broom this stuff.
It's dirty. I know, but I'm gonna mop later. So it goes under the hole. That's not far enough.
Oh, it's a big brain, big brain place. Thank you. Big brain school. Nice.
Oh, these are going to have to be picked up individually. This is fine. Uh, drop this guy
down. See you. I want to watch though. All right. This is starting to look all right. Just need to
mop eventually. I got a broom. Wait, hold on. This one does jump. Please. I am.
This one does jump. Please. I am.
Oh, hello. It's me Baldy. I am restoring Valia. I don't, I didn't play it. I don't fucking know why.
All these basics. I started with hand simulator and you guys told me I can't believe you're
playing the YouTuber game, but for some reason you'd like me to play all these basics.
I want you to say that into the mirror. I'm pretty cleansed.
I like how the trash receptacles are just really right here. This is great.
We got it. All right. Now I need to get, uh, some water up here. Where's this music coming from?
Seriously. Use gun. You can't use gun. It's gonna be so much fun. It really is.
I would put this up there with like ocarina of time.
And you have to say ocarina of time. Otherwise your list is invalid. The best games ever made.
Am I ever going to play that monkey game again? No, no, I'm not.
No ancient. What's it called? Ancient ancestors. No, you will not see that game again.
I do. I do not think so.
I'm here. Uh, a lot of these random. I get that with a broom.
Drop them. I think I brought a bucket up here. Where the fuck does he live? It's four o'clock
in the morning. I live in the center of Pacific Ocean. I'm on it's currently on a submarine.
Where's the water? Water bucket. There it is. All right. We're going to work out,
bring the bucket in here. What are you dumb? We're on the sub cam.
You guys do realize that's the next step for IRL streaming, right? All right. Uh, we've,
we've been, I've been to every location on earth. Now I'm going to stream myself getting into a
space shuttle and going to the moon or Mars. I don't want to go to Mars. I'm going to stream
the whole journey. It did that in the sixties already. Yeah, but, but it wasn't,
but it wasn't my favorite streamer. So whatever. I got to go more buckets. I am on floor one.
I know you're going to hate me for this, but I'm going to bring like three up there.
Somebody's getting the chat. I can already read their comment is going to say in all capitals,
just fucking do it normally. God, I know I've already read it. I can see it already. See,
not a problem. Bounce there. I'll do it. Fuck it normally.
I keep, we're going to have to put our own OST on again. Oh, Paul, they space it.
Where am I? That's the whole song. That's the, I thought it was more longer than this.
Home Depot theme, the Home Depot theme song. You guys, this is real. Oh, it's this thing.
Let's save it. We're doing that's power. Home Depot. Now I know what you mean. This is all,
this song is too. It's like eight seconds. This song is six, not even one, two, three,
it's three seconds long. It's not even a song. It's just the end of the commercial after the
guy says it. It's so stupid. It's growing on you. You can't be copyrighted if it's only three
seconds long. Oh, it's because I'm hearing this music too. I can't, I can't fucking do this anymore.
This is actually terrible. I mean, it's fine for a like 15 second ad for the Superbowl,
but not right now. I have to stop this. Lowe's doesn't have one. That's unfortunate. How about
Allstate? How it's made. We've done that already. How about we need cleaning music. Music to clean
too. This doesn't have to be like a playlist. Catchy songs to clean your room. One hour of
cleaning music. Okay. Oh, so some like dumb teenager made that. Some teenager made that
and that's fine. It's cool. Let's see what they have on their playlist. Cool. What's next?
Okay. What's the next one?
We should start now. Wait, is this Coldplay? Okay. What's the next one? I think this is,
uh, this one doesn't have a list. What's the next one?
I guess the search. That one didn't have a song. And not a bad playlist. Some of those. I don't
know what any of these are actually. Why would I type this? I, like I said before,
this stream was an extra stream for the week. And I can, you can tell that I just typed in,
um, I typed in piano key mashing. Like I was going to put that on. Nobody's made a video.
I'm trying to find one. Okay. If you type in piano key mashing, nobody has like,
uh, why are you kidding me? How has nobody done this? This like 600 trillion videos on YouTube,
not one person made one. That's unbelievable to me. Hitting every key on piano. What is this?
Fast piano key hitting. I could do that faster. I know I can. This is the fastest in the world.
I can do faster than this. You guys know I can do that faster than this Guinness world record
fastest hitting the piano keys in a minute. I could beat this. No, I can't believe nobody
has a video where they just hit a bunch of keys and it's like a 15 minute long video. How you
guys got one? I found one. Did you actually find one? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Funny. All right. Who gives a shit? Wait, no, that's not it. That's not whatever. I'm done.
Just give me something normal to play. This took five seconds to find. What did you type in? No.
Yeah. Oh, the stinky video. I'm not, I don't trust you guys ever again. What is this? I can't put on
like this music. This is the cartoon music. Okay. I'm done. I'm actually done. What I'm going for
this one. This would be best background music. That's all I need. This is just stress relief
music. Sounds good to me. I gotta like continue playing the video game guys. That's not even
trash. Oh, you're a video game streamer now. Yes. I don't know what happened there. I know
it's a push from it still. Like what happened? Drop it. The best thing is I can drop these
too, right? Yes, I can get rid of them. Just press every button for God sakes.
Am I walking this around? Still have one bucket. That's clean. This is the same music that you
played when you died. Is it? It is. Dude, I scrawled a long way. I scrawled pretty fucking
far. That's so stupid. This is the music I played when I died. Fuck me. God damn it.
Okay, I can do a little bit more. I can do a little bit more cleanup. I have to use the device,
the shooter. This one's unlocked. Well, this is a mess. This is a mess. Just break a world record
on stream. Do you know how hard that is to do? People train for months doing the same thing
every day. And you want me to break a world record that I don't even know what record I'm
going to break on stream. Just now. God, do it already.
5G noises. You want to play 5G noises? Fine. You guys are in trouble. You guys,
you guys are on restriction right now. Okay. This thing's actually called chilling and relaxing
to 60 cycle hump. 12 hours of power line, power line noise.
This is what I feel like. I feel like it feels like cell tower sounds. Do they actually make
sounds? No, I don't think they do. Let's keep going. Don't, don't, don't, don't let it go.
Okay. Bring this one over here. Cool. No, I'm not playing it. I'm not playing it. You're making
that up in your head. There's no, I don't have any video on right now. You're making it up.
It's you. It's you. You think you hear it, but it's not there. That's just the air conditioner
in this room. Okay. Let me Dr. Phil. Dr. Phil. Sorry. Maybe some other day. Let's get this over
here. Play background crowd noises. Like at a bar. How about, um, crowd noises? Yeah, that's fine.
Internet cafe. That's right. This is not the same one though. Do a Twitch con panel?
You mean like right now? Yes. It's not Twitch con anymore. It hasn't been for a long time.
I need to dunk this in the water without knocking anything over.
Oh, fuck. Okay. Do a head start on next year's Twitch con panel. You're going to do
I'm not going to do a Twitch con panel. What the hell would I even tell you guys or anybody
dance? So if I, if I was on a Twitch con panel, what do you, what do Twitch con panels talk about?
I've never been to one. Weren't you there? I mean, I was at Twitch con. I never been to a
Twitch con panel. I had a Twitch con panel and I just had like a dummy on the stage and I was in
a doctor's outfit and I was just doing open heart surgery to the dummy. And the, the name of the
panel would be, I made a mistake, but I have to do this anyways. You know, I made a scheduling
mistake, but, but this guy needs a new heart. You know what I mean? So that's what I'm doing.
I just have like 10 people all in scrubs, just like openly are these operating and then randomly
answer Q and A questions about Twitch. That just, you know, like the people come up with a
microphone. So how did you get your start? Uh, on Twitch? Well, uh, hold on just a second. Yep. I
need a, can we close that one please? See that up. Yep. Thank you. Well, I, uh, I funny thing,
I played team fortress too. And I made comedy video. You have to do that now. I, do you don't,
do you think that they're going, I would ever be allowed to do something like that?
That's the type of scenario where you tell somebody that idea and then they go, oh, yeah. Whoa. Super,
super cool. Interesting idea. Let me, uh, let me throw some lines out and yeah, cool though.
Cool idea. And then they, you don't, they never talk to you again. That's how that works.
Those aren't Twitch panels reserved for, but do you have to actually talk about something?
I feel like they wouldn't want me just to make a mockery of Twitch panels, right? I don't think
they would want, I don't think they would want me to do that. Oh, just, just copy, just copy pen
and teller. And I have a panel where it's, what's the name of their show? Like fool us.
And I get up there and I'm like, welcome to a magician. I just bring like magicians on to like
fool me. I have to try to figure out what they did. Yeah. They filmed that show in Vegas and bring
in a, just bring in a bunch of really expensive looking fake cameras and hire 10 people to be
fake production staff. Like this is a real show that's on television, but all the cameras aren't
even real. Like it's, it's nothing about it is real at all. People are going to come into the,
into the panel, into the hall and they're going to look around and be like, holy shit,
there's like fucking 10 cameras. There's like a guy on a crane that he's sitting like Steven
Spielberg style sitting in the crane camera seat. The camera is made out of plastic. It's not real.
Crane is also plastic. Well, I think that would be kind of dangerous. So that would not be the case.
And have 250 actors be the audience and have one person actually in there that signed up for the
panel. And people are like treating it like it's a real thing. You know, actually would be kind of
funny is to have a panel, but to actually do that. I have a bunch of people that are hired to be
there to just talk you up and say how awesome you are and ask a bunch of questions and then
never really talk about it. But like somehow it comes out that those were all fake paid people
to be there. I would just look so bad and so fucked up. I would, it would just look really awful.
That's impractical jokers type shit. Yeah. Do a Reddit AMA. I do a Reddit AMA, but it's not even
me doing the AMA. It's not even me. And like halfway or like 75% of the way through that AMA,
my channel goes live and I'm sleeping in my bed. And then the stream turns off after like
two to three minutes. Nope, that ain't me talking. Two to three hours? Oh, I don't think I could do
that. Or have an AMA, but have like 10 accounts pretending to be me. One of them is the real one
and we're all answering questions. One of those accounts is real, but you don't know which one.
Everything looks good, except for this window that needs to be broken. Never mind.
That's the EQ stream, but in reverse. I would call this room clean except for this one.
There might be a couple of, uh, oh wait. Nope. Nevermind. I gotta get rid of all these bullet
holes. Here comes spade tornado. Oh, progress is being, uh, progress is being made on the
Minecraft stream by the way. That still should be, should be good to go for the 15th.
I mean, depending on how long it takes the, uh, the devs to put it all together,
I will have a better answer soon, but looking like it's going to happen. It will, this will
probably happen at least in December, but we're still shooting for the 15th. So that should be
fun. No, no, no, no. Not like the actual devs of Minecraft, like the people that are making
the server for all this to go down and all the plugins and everything.
Get them all in one go, get them all in one go, get them all in one go. Come on, do it.
I left one behind. Leaving one behind is fine. Leaving 12 behind is not. Hey, that's me. Who?
Me. All right, watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it. This is going to be the worst room in real
life. Yeah, it's made out of strands of hair. All right, that's good enough for now. Make a joke.
What are you talking about? Make a joke. I'm not a woody doll. You pull the back, you pull my string
and I just say something. There's buttons under here. I want to press them. How do I press these
buttons? How do you crouch? What does that do? What the hell does that do? Shit, 5G dude, 5G.
Are you ready for 5G? Which one is this? This one? Okay, it's that one. Press it, press this button.
I can't press this now? This only works one time. Are you kidding me? Crouch, control, C, space,
caps lock, shift. What is crouch? Control, C, V, F, C, control. There is no crouch.
In the evening, in the event of my escape, I will bring Puddlesworth with me. I expect all of you
to attend to his requirements. You left your ring. That's a big ass ring. Caution. Caution. Submarine.
See, I told you I live here. Did you get out? It's clean. Re-chat, re-chat, re-chat. It's a collar.
Yeah, I know. Look, here's the cat right there. There. See?
Get on there. Fucking thing's not fucking working. Fucking stupid, fucking dumb,
fucking dumb, fucking stupid, fucking thing. This room is clean. Take a look. It's like nothing
ever happened in here except for these two blood stains. Pick them up. Fine. The bullet holes.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d. I know. Remember dead bodies up here? New viewer here. This guy's pretty cool.
Hey, thanks. Welcome. Welcome to the channel. How come there's no Twitch preview for when
somebody's new? Instead of a pre-roll ad, if you've never clicked on this channel before,
instead of a 30-second pre-roll ad, why don't you get like a, hey, my name's German on A5.
Welcome to the channel. And like a cut-up of a highlight and stuff.
Crazy things happen here all the time. 5G! The 5G, it hurts!
But I also do real talks. And then it cuts to another one. And I'm talking about like real shit.
I also, I also have a hernia. Why would I put that in my trailer?
Just in case you didn't know, I have a hernia. Okay. All right. What, why do I have to know that?
Oh, my rib cage is all fucked up. Just let it vent, chat. That is the lore.
I can't wait to, I don't even care if you guys don't want to see it. I'm going to make it in
front of the green screen channel trailer. And who remembers this one? Hi, German985 here. You
might know me as the Shpee Guy. Cut to like, Shpee, Shpee, like you've seen me say it like five times.
But I'm so much more than that. Just last week, I broke the world record. I'm the current world
record holder for clicking a single mouse button more times than anyone in five seconds. And then
I whip my hand up over my mouth to kind of lean in, whisper and be like, try to beat that one.
I'm also the only person that's slapped themselves in the face very hard, not on purpose.
In fact, it's probably, I'm probably more known for that than the carnival I did. And I'm going
to look right into the camera and be real fucking sad. All right. It's clean. We're good. And then
it's going to, the best part about if you could actually have that is I have to fucking,
don't make me do this. It's just make people think they're getting an ad on the stream.
Is that against term service? It's just in the middle of my stream, just fucking boom, play,
just like have a pretend like ad banner on it and like have a play over the video.
So it's like, you're actually getting an ad on my stream, but it's just, it's pumped in.
Imagine having an ad play on your stream. It's your own stream. And it's talking about,
Hey, you should like stick around. And it's like, it's like six minutes.
And then it cuts back and I don't fucking say anything. I'm just, I,
I, as if I continued playing where I left off, where I, you know, six minutes in the game has
gone by. Oh, you guys got an ad. All right. Hold onto that one. You might see it. All right. I'm
done up here. Everything's clean. You have this rocket ship. That's just a YouTube. Yeah. I know.
Press the button. This button. Press the button. All right. Next, next room. Wait,
Twitch staff is in here. What, who, who, who on Twitch staff is in here?
I should just make a bunch of fucking fake commercial shit. What was that?
Hey, commercials for like grills and shit that I, that I apparently am endorsing that I,
that aren't real staff is here because you said you were taking a dump on your desk.
Fuck. Oh,
like too much headquarters. You get, you get, you get a, a lead. It says, Hey, uh,
just made somebody stick around there for a while. This guy said he was going to take a dump on his
desk. You just sit in there with the stream open, just with your hand, I'll be mild, just like,
okay, what the fuck is this guy doing? Your hand is hovering over the like turn off stream.
Okay. What else do I have to do? Let's go. I gotta go up a floor.
Your ribs are breaking. Streamer, streamer removed from Twitch for threatening to take dump on desk.
Oh, that's fucking so stupid.
Career over. Please jump in the shark pit. All right, I'll do it for you. I'm going to do it for you.
My friend. It's me. I'm back. Ooh, good. I gotta go up a floor.
I'm going to get calls to the principal's office. Like a DM on like Twitter or something.
Did you Twitch staff Andrew or something? Hey, you got time to chat.
Uh, what's up? Hey, so, uh, we're going down. We're going to go three.
All right. This is not bad. Door control. Enter code. Now here's the really fun thing.
Not even fun. All right. So, oh, didn't DM from which staff? Oh, no, no. Oh, boy.
Hey, what's up? I'm sorry. I'm sorry about talking about shitting on my desk. I'll never happen again.
I promise that was really fucked up. Hey, dude, just want to say congratulations on your for your
partner. Right. Right. Okay. Thanks. But now that you said, what are you talking about?
Nothing. I didn't. Don't worry. I just, I'm, you know, Mr. Comedy Man. That's what I do.
Hold on. Somebody's linked me a clip. Oh, don't click that. It's probably a virus.
You know, it's not important. Just get them on the elevator. Who cares?
Who cares how they're on the elevator? Just get them in. Get another message back. Yeah,
I've reviewed this clip. I don't know what to say about this. Bring it all.
All of it. All of it. All of it. It's in here.
Uh, okay. Do I open these? Say it. Say what? What would you say if you were really,
really sort of tense and scared and there's a fucked up moment that's about maybe about to happen?
What would you say?
I'm just picking stuff up and moving it. Launch aborted. One second remaining. All right. I
can't do this yet. I need the code. What's the code? Just give it to me. I just want to tell
me what it is. I'll sit here all day. I don't care how long this takes. I'm waiting for someone to
put the real one in. Why would I ever think that would be real? I mean, it's been in the chat so
many times that how am I supposed to know that that's not how am I supposed to know that?
They are random. What makes a different sound? It was on the cat's collar. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Thank you. Where's the elevator? How do I get out of here? Am I stuck in here?
No, there it is. Right. I fucking barricaded myself. Where is it? Two
cats collar. This is not even right. Screen blinks green when you do a right number.
Oh, I'm already here. Let me see. Is it on the cat's collar? Mr. Cuddlesworth.
Right. Is it on the back? Oh, how is this not spilled? These two have not spilled.
That's almost impossible. I sneeze next to one of these and they break and they fall over.
It does a green. It blinks green. Wait. All right. Hold on. The second number is three.
Second number and fifth number are three. Third number is seven. Fourth number is seven.
Something. Wait, what? First number is eight. First number is eight. Three. No.
Eight. Three. Eight. Three. Seven. Eight. Three. Seven. Three. Nope. Eight. Three. Eight. Seven.
Three. Three. Eight. Seven. No, it's eight. Three. Seven. Seven. Eight. Three. Seven. Seven. Eight.
No. Eight. Three. Eight. Three. Seven. Seven. Three. Now what? Seven. What's on lock? What did I do?
Oh, shit. Can I launch this? Death Ray is ready. Fire the weapon in Yellowstone.
Okay. Where's the button to go? Fire the missile. How do you fire the missile?
Do I have to throw a match in here? Launch the missile. What do you think I'm trying to look for? A way to launch it.
Man. All the way from the ground floor. Okay. Well, I want to launch this shit. Let's go.
All right. It's locked. Where the hell am I? What is all I'm going to do? This map is huge.
There it is. All right. Here's the way to... How do I get this open?
German. I dot dot dot. What? Oh, no. All right. Two. Two is the first number.
This is... Holy shit. Do you see how long this code is? I have to write this down. Oh, my fucking
God. I gotta write it down. Two is the first number. Two. Four. No. There's four in here.
There's a backspace. Yeah. Two. One. Two. Four. Two. Three. Two. Five. Two. Six. Two. Seven. Eight. Two.
One. You know. Two. Three. Two. Eight. Three. Four. Five. Eight. Six. Seven. Nine. Zero. One. Two.
What? Three. Okay. Three. One. Okay. Almost. Okay. One more. Pay attention. I wasn't paying
attention. I wasn't paying attention. It's not what I want. I wasn't paying attention. What was
that number? Two. What? Two. Eight. Two. Eight. Three. Three. Five. Three. Guys, I don't... Two.
Eight. Three. Three. Five. Three. Seven. Nine. What's the last number? Six. Seven. Eight.
What's that? What's the last number? What's the last number? Four. Am I gonna miss the explosion?
Wait. Map. It's so big. This is a huge map. This is so big. I'm not gonna be... I'm not doing this
whole thing on stream. No. Nope. It's not gonna happen. You're not meant to do it in one day.
Yeah, I know. Frogman? Whoa. I'm interested. What's this? I would get so lost in here.
I already am. Giant laser? Holy shit. Okay. So there's two target acquired.
That's cool. Recharging. Wait. Can I move it around? I lived on the moon. I'm sorry.
I think I did it. You have 24 hours until it hits the earth. I'm supposed to be cleaning.
This is too expansive. It's too expansive. I want to launch this, though. How do I open this thing?
That's the wrong one. So it's this one. How do I get you open? There's gotta be a way to get this
open, right? This way? Baldi's waiting room. You're never going to see Baldi's basics on this stream.
I need to explain to you why. Can I just like... Wait a minute. What are the tools? A beacon.
Well, I don't think we can launch the thing because I don't know how to open the door.
You either play Doki Doki Literature Club or you play Baldi. There are no alternatives.
No. All right. Let's just pretend this is the room that I cleaned and this is the one that
is the one that matters right now. Look at how clean it is, right? I don't have the broom anymore.
All right. I have to take care of this. This is a lot of bullshit. I need to go back down to...
What was still needs to be cleaned up here? There's a whole spot over here. What is going
on? Yeah. This spot here. God damn it. I need buckets. Okay. Bucket and bring three.
I need to ascend. To where? I don't need to ascend. Jump in and out of the pool real quick.
I already did that. You missed it. I'm bored. Dual voice. Just give me a minute. I'm down.
Stream's over. I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. So tomorrow,
tomorrow, what is planned is Joel and I are going to be potentially... We're going to be starting
Halo Reach. We're going to do Halo Reach today, but we rescheduled for tomorrow.
And then I played Hand Simulator and everybody... If you weren't here earlier,
rewind to that part of the VOD. Everybody thought it was so fucking funny. So good.
They're not watering these. This is a razor.
Joel's going to ignore you and just play Baldi's Basics. Don't even kid.
But yeah, so I decided instead of just postponing streaming till tomorrow, we're going to... We
decided to play a triple game today. Stream is just an extra one. I'm going to go three
days in a row from here on out after this. I'm assuming Halo Reach will be maybe a full stream
or two. I don't know what the plans are. We'll see. And then we're going to play Tools Up.
We're going to see if we can get that to work with the second, third, fourth day.
Play Hand Simulator tomorrow. I already got what I wanted out of it.
But no more Hand Simulator. I already said it was the worst game of the decade.
And I kind of regret saying that because that's definitely not true. I know it's not true.
But I said it and I need to retract that statement because that's definitely not true.
Of the decade. All right. Yeah, I'll call... No, not yet. I want to clean this house.
Just... I want to do this part. I'm almost done. Well, okay. It's a base, not a house.
Why does this shit not work? Five more minutes, mom. Five more minutes. Five more minutes.
Oh, let's just bring them up there. Baldi, Baldi, Baldi. One day I will just turn on Baldi's Basics
and I'm not going to tell you when. It'll just happen one day. You'll just see it one day.
That's a lie. That's a lie. That's a lie. Can't be a lie if it hasn't happened yet.
All right. So if I told you that I was going to play Baldi's Basics and then
six years went by and I played it, is that a lie? No, I played it. I didn't say I was going to play
it tomorrow. Can I clean this in here? You actually can. Wow. Technically. Yeah. Halo
Reach should be fun. By the way, for those of you that don't know, I have never played
one solitary minute of Halo. I told you Halo 2 is the only one I've ever played
and I played the multiplayer across like four TVs once or twice in college.
I've never played one second of any of the campaigns. So we'll find out. That's not a lie.
That is not a lie. I've never played Halo. I mean, so I've lied. No, I never had an Xbox.
I didn't have a regular Xbox and I got an Xbox 360 late into the game and just didn't play them.
We played Halo 2. It's a multiplayer. Maybe for 45 seconds in two or three lives when I drove a
car into a wall and like threw a grenade at somebody. But okay, what constitutes playing
the game? Okay is. Oh, I played Halo 2, but I really didn't though. I can't even name you one
gun. I guess I physically pressed the button on it once and then I've watched somebody play for
15 minutes. So you played it. Yes. Physically I have sat in front of the screen and played
Halo 2 multiplayer for a minute or two minutes tops. So you played it. I guess I've played it.
Literally competitive Halo. I love how somebody's doing that joke for me right now and I didn't even
plan it. All right. All right. I'll see you guys later. I'm gonna call it here. This was a real
wild one. And Medieval is actually pretty fun. So you may actually see me complete that game.
You actually might because it was pretty fun. I did enjoy it. Thanks for watching the secret.
I don't even have a secret. I tweeted about it and I told everybody I streamed today.
Uh, thanks for the coming to the extra stream this week.
See you tomorrow for Halo Reach Cooperative Multiplayer Campaign with Joel. Thanks for
watching guys. You made a video on Halo. I'm not going to click another Rick roll. Jump in.
My computer crashed. I just have a bloody screen. Yeah, there's just blood on the screen.
All right. Actually, good night guys. I'll see you tomorrow. I'm looking forward to Halo. I've
heard a lot of things about Halo. I've heard, dude, Halo is, is just, it's like the best. You
have to play it. You're going to love it. I hope so. And when they all release, I'm going to be
playing all of them. I mean, I can't necessarily guarantee I'm going to co-op every single one of
them, but we'll see. Hey, Bob Boy. What's going on, Bob Boy? Thanks for the five subs. Richard
Nixon's still a top sub gifter. Thank you. But let's go back. Let's do the bits. I'll see you
guys tomorrow. Thanks for hanging out earlier, earlier, about six, what six hours ago. Yes.
Hey, uh, hey, turret hugger. Thanks for the 500 bits. That face when hernia. Poor Jeremy show
love. Appreciate it. Thank you. I'll be okay though. I'll be good to go. We'll continue to
work on it and see what happens. Appreciate it. Oh, so thank you to swiggity swanky for 250
bits. They say hand simulator. What is this? Let's find out. You ma'am, get your hands in there.
Like open this up and get your hands in there and just start feeling around. I want you, you. Oh,
wait, this is me talking about how I want, I told ma'am, get your hands. Yeah. Look at how old this
is. Get your hands in there and just start feeling around. I want you. All right. This is two years
ago. This is me describing what I wanted the doctor to do. I wanted to do exploratory surgery on me.
Yeah, that was, that was two years ago. Jesus. Time flies when you have a hernia. Thank you,
Zeke for the 250. Your streams have been a soundtrack to many long lonely nights of studying.
Cheers for that. Still waiting for the cooking stream. Hopefully it's worth the wait when you
see it eventually. We'll see. Hey, Jason, thanks for the 500 bits. Hey, German, today marks the
one year since I first started watching you. Today's also the same day since the green screen
movie night. Ever since then, I was hooked on your content and never missed a stream. Not only have
you helped me through so many tough times, but most importantly, you've helped us. Whether it's
being called short or saying, look at me, you never cease to make us laugh. I'm so grateful to
have discovered such a great guy. Keep on keeping on. Thank you. I really appreciate it, Jason.
I'm glad you stuck around. Hope you continue to do so. Thanks again. Hey, Marvish McGally,
thanks for the 250. I look forward to the stream with Joel, especially after we recently reacted
to rat movies on stream. Not sure if you saw that. It was quite wholesome. Yeah, we'll see. The one
thing I'm concerned about is ping tomorrow. We're going to have to see how the connection is from,
you know, across the world. Might be interesting. But yeah, that's, Joel's a funny guy.
Let's see how the stream is tomorrow. It's not, it won't be too bad. Let's hope so.
Because remember, I'm Pacific. So West Coast to, I wonder how far the travel time is. But thank you,
Marvish McGally. Appreciate it. Thank you, Gnarly, for the 250. My friend got me to play Hand
Simulator. I've never raged more at a game in my entire life. I've beaten every Soulsborne and I
actively play League of Legends and yet fucking Hand Meme Game is what breaks me. Fuck this game.
Fun stream. You know the thing about that game? I would have sat there until I got it. Until I got
it, I would have done it. But I had, I had to stop. I had to just pull the plug. Even if I wasn't
streaming, I would have sat there for like six hours trying to put the clip into the handgun.
I know I would have. You didn't though, you said it. I put it, I put the clip into the gun and I
fired the gun. I didn't, there's, I didn't shoot at anything. I didn't hit any targets.
That's okay. Thank you, Final Fantasy, for the 300 bits. They say nice. Thank you. Martin had
a meme. Thanks for the thousand bits. 10 bucks. Appreciate that. Jerma, you should have, you should
have just admitted to the gun range owner that this was your first time. Lying about your experience
is never right. Now you're gonna have to make up excuses like, I swear this doesn't usually happen.
I guess I'm just nervous. Thank you, Snarobosis, for the 10 community subs earlier. Don't think
we saw it. I think I was in the middle of doing a chill stream where I get very angry at a game
that I then call the worst game of the decade. Chilling out, just hanging out. Chill stream today.
Extra chill stream. Thank you though for the 10 community subs. Appreciate it.
And thank you, Martin had a meme again for the thousand bits. CAD, BTV. What's going on CAD?
A thousand bits here from CAD. What a game. It gives you a gun, makes you want to shoot yourself,
and then doesn't let you. All right, no. Hey, Jerma95 AMA. How's it going? I could get a large
number 10 with fries, please. No. Did you ever play Halo? When's the next Kenshi stream?
Kenshi was an incredible experience and I'd love to stream it again. However, when you do multiple
streams in a row like that, it can get pretty tiring. A lot of people in chat were tired of it
too, but seeing how warm of a response the videos on the second channel got, I'll probably play it
again at some point. It's supposed to be fun to return to it at some point. Just like I return
every Tuesday to get a $5 waffle meal at Burger King. What was that sketch you had 100% confidence
in that didn't execute as expected? The infamous slap myself in the face joke was supposed to end
with me turning around and leaving the room, with my arm whipping around, with my body turning to
follow, but I timed it wrong while looking at my second monitor. I suppose that went better than
expected, much like the $12 or 99 family bundle deal they have at Burger King. That's three
cheeseburgers, three small fries, and three waffles for under $13.
Thoughts on the new Crispy Pretzel Chicken Fries? Did Burger King Crispy Crunchy Pretzel outside
tender juicy white meat chicken inside new Crispy Pretzel Chicken Fries?
That stream was a mess. I don't condone the things I said while I was live. It was really
out of character. I don't think you'll be seeing me streaming with him again. Sorry. What?
Have you ever tried coffee marinated chicken stuffed with Cheetos before?
Oh, look at you. It's the same fucking coffee Cheetos chicken joke again. Well played. Look,
everyone. We have a fucking comedy genius over here. Jesus Christ, you subhuman. Okay.
Can't think of anything. This is not me. This is not me. This is me. This is somebody. This is me
pretending that this is somebody pretending to be me. Why are you a massive compulsive liar?
If you're looking to throw hands, I'd be willing to meet you at next year's
winner buys the other a $3 10 piece nugget. Okay. I can't. Okay. Oh my fucking God damn it.
All right. That's it. That's it. That's it. All right. Abort, abort, abort, abort, abort, abort.
I'm not, there's no AMAs going on. There's no AMAs going on. There's no AMAs.
It's your AMA. It's not my AMA. Why? This guy, this is a PR nightmare for me. Yes. This is going to
pop up like 10 times. I have no control over this. No, no. What? What? Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute. A real AMA. You have to prove it's a real AMA. Don't,
I have to tweet out a picture of me holding up a sign that's pointing to it going like,
Reddit AMA. Uh, January 10th, 2020. Right? That's how you know it's real. So it doesn't matter.
Fucking damn it. Okay. Let's keep going. Let's keep going. PR nightmare.
Anyways, thank you. Really appreciate it. Large 27. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Dermot, please for the love of all that is holy, stop for your health and mine. I can't take it
anymore. I'm about to die and combust into a million pieces of dirt. Please stop. Oh my god,
stop. I was playing hand simulator and like, nobody liked it. Thanks. Hey, uh, hip moose. We
didn't see this five community subs from hip moose. Oh man. Thank you hip moose. Sad Vega,
thanks for 300 bits. I suffer from a condition where I get a lot of information and I suffer
from it year round. I take a thousand milligram capsules of turmeric to help manage it. It helps
a lot, but as a heads up, it's going to dehydrate the hell out of you, which means expect constipation
if you don't drink tons of H2O. Yeah. Uh, what's probably going to end up happening here is I'm
going to do, I'm going to do some, maybe try to do some supplements and stuff, but I'm probably
going to start to go see a physical therapist because I know that there are some things to help,
um, kind of unlock your joints a little bit, different stretches, different physical therapy
you can do to help with this issue. Cause like I said before, it really does feel like
I almost just need somebody to like press down and twist and then pull up and then twist and it'll
be like, and I'll go back to normal. But I know that, I mean, that's just kind of how it feels.
But even sometimes when I like, if I, if I lean back and I pull back a little, I can feel inside
of my chest around to my back, like it's like, so that's what I get for shoplifting. That's what
you get for stopping lifting. Oh, that's what you get for not lifting anymore. Well, it's actually
a very good thing. I don't like lift any weights anymore. So I'll probably do some physical therapy,
see if we can move some shit around, see if I can do some stretches, try to loosen up
these apparently inflamed joints. And yeah, I know that I've been told,
the doctor told me you might get like a shot of cortisone, cortisol, whatever steroid into the
bone, into your, that's not, that's not good for you though. I've heard that that's really not good
for you. We'll see what they say. I'd like to try physical therapy first. I've had that in my back
and it's the second worst pain I've ever felt. Damn it. Oh well. Is the pain in your back or
is it on your stomach? It's my whole entire core. So it starts right in the middle of my sternum,
right in my breastbone and then goes out inside that area around my ribs. And then it's all around
the back of my ribs too, my whole back. Mostly, most pain is on like the right side of my back
into the center of my chest. This has been about a year and a half of dealing with it.
And something that I didn't really talk that much about because it was just like,
ah, what is it? What would I, what is there even to talk about?
So it's just like a, just constant, just there always, but this last six months or so, I've
been really pushing hard, hard, hard, hammered hard to really try to figure out what the fuck
is even going on with my body. And I, over the last, yeah, like six, seven, eight months straight,
I've been trying to figure out what the fuck it is. And maybe one piece of that puzzle is the
hernia, which is what I had, that's what I have. But the doctor also says it's probably both.
His skeleton is hatching. But hey, we get it. When's the ball de-stream?
There's still blood all over my screen, by the way.
We get it. Oh my God. You guys are ruthless. I, yeah, I've got this like fucking medical
problem that's like really been bothering me for like two years. Where's Baldi?
Oh, it's something about it's like funny though. It kind of is to me. It's all good. Hey, thanks a
lot, Frody and Weapon for the 256. It's hard to hear about the hernia and ribs. I'm sure you don't
need to hear it from me, but take it easy. If you need to, I'm sure you'll overcome it.
Yeah, from all the things I've heard about, if it is costochondritis, is that some, it's some,
for some people, it's around for like a few years and then it just disappears. Oh yeah,
it's inflammation in your ribs, joint pain and joint problems inside your ribs. Oh, by the way,
it's not, it's gone now. It's been four years and now it's just not there anymore. What? What the
hell? What are you talking? What? Your body just balks it out. Check and make sure it's not a heart
thing. No, we've, we've eliminated every major organ in my body. At this point, I've had enough
blood tests and scopes and it's not anything going. I don't, it's, it would be shocking to me if this
was an organ problem. You need those. I know. Did you have an x-ray? Yes, I've had an MRI
and an x-ray of two different places and they confirmed a few things and there we go.
You want to look at, look at your x-rays on stream. Now that would probably be the strangest thing
that you would ever see on Twitch. Has no one's ever done that? Like you want x-ray of my spine?
What, you want to pretend to know what I'm looking at? No, I'm not going to do that.
That's super naked. That is naked 3.0. Put it up on your Reddit. Yeah, just make like a post.
Hey guys, here's the result. Here's all my MRIs. What's wrong with me?
I'm not doing that. That is strange. That's strange. That's really strange. I can't do that.
I can't do that. That's too fucked up for me. It's like, oh, here's like your x-rays of his back
and spine and shit. It's like, I don't know. No, no, no. I, you, I don't want you guys to see,
I don't want you guys to see me naked. I don't want you guys to see me times three naked.
Then my dream would just come true. But yeah, I have, I've got turmeric tea. I'm going to be
doing that. Drinking turmeric tea, probably taking some turmeric, try to eat more of an
anti-inflammatory diet. That's hard to fucking do though. Like no dairy, no processed meats,
no nothing fried, no gluten, no wheat. That's so no hydrogenated oils. If you live in 2019,
it's actually really hard to avoid all of those things. Because half of the shit that you ever
eat is just cooked in some kind of pressed oil. This is olive oil, which is, that's not inflammatory
or whatever. Just go vegan. I could never do it. I could never go vegetarian or vegan. I just,
I could not do it. I couldn't do it. I'd go crazy after like a, like a month. I'd lose my mind.
I'd turn into like Gollum. I love certain foods and certain meats so much. I could not,
I just would not be able to do it. Who's this? Hey Reddit, hey Jeremy, here are my MRI scans.
If you're a brand new viewer and you're brand new to that sub Reddit,
I'm, and you think that's me or something, you're gonna be, it's like, I, I, this person's like
freaking me out. But anyways, uh, thank you SadVega for the 300 bits. Thank you Freuding Weapon for
the 256. And thank you Gnarly for the 250. I had a hernia removed from my stomach when I was like six
or seven. I don't remember anything, but the dream I had when I went under, I was on a steel bed in
an empty room and a metal claw dug into my stomach and pulled my hernia out. It was a scary and
painful dream, but I got a dual popsicle afterwards. So easy, 10 out of 10. Oh my God. Thank you. Please
go out with my grandpa for the 500 bits. Hey Jeremy, just want to thank you for saving my
relationship. Uh, me and my girlfriend have had some hard times together and I didn't think our
relationship would last till we discovered the erotic, it's, um, it's hard to not, it's hard to
say this. Erotic, uh, no. No. Rat movie RP and since then our relationship is going strong.
Thank you. She's a giant rat. Okay. Shitty Viewbot, thanks for the 400 bits. Seems good. Hey,
Jerma, since this is the week of co-op and you might need some game recommendations, might as
well just pay day one and two. Uh, you decide whether you want to play or not and I hope your
hernia gets better. Me too. Um, well I know for the next day or two it's going to be Halo Reach.
After the stream tomorrow I think we'll probably just come to a consensus if we're just going to
do it the next stream. Maybe, uh, Joel and I will be like, oh that was fun, that was cool, but
maybe we don't want to finish it together. Maybe I would just, if he wasn't into it doing it again,
I would just do the rest. Something like that. We'll find out. And then there's another co-op
game that's already lined up. If that doesn't work though, then we'll probably look for something
else. Thank you. For the 400 bits. Uh, P flavor, thanks for the 300 bits. Jerma, I keep missing
your streams so stop streaming when I can't watch. Also here's your 6% Jerma tax. Sorry it's late,
please don't hurt my family. You say, you say this every time. Don't, this is like two or three of
you that have the same end to your messages. Hey, the coldest fridge, thanks for the 500 bits. Hi
Jerma, you told me that you would say happy birthday to me on stream three years ago,
but you never did. What? I just like put the phone in the back and put it, like throw it down there
and just have it. No, that's fucking weird. That's a good reverse surveillance video.
All right. Good night, everybody. Coldest bridge. Thanks for the $1.
Well, thanks for the $2 actually. Jerma, can I get a happy birthday message?
Uh, December 6th, like Nicholas. I'm going to have to start doing like, all right, I remember that.
December 6th? What's going on on the 6th? I don't know. Remind me. Siri, remind me in six days
to say happy birthday to the coldest fridge. Saved it. Got it. Thanks for the $3 coldest fridge.
That's one, two, three in a row. Okay, for real, thank you for the coolest beans stream.
Right. And that's three years ago. So in three days, it's your, it's your birthday again.
I've got another chance. I didn't mean I was going to say happy birthday to you
on your 25th birthday. I was talking about happy birthday on your 28th birthday. Remind me.
Siri, make a note here. Remind me on December 6th to say happy birthday to the coldest fridge.
Got it. There it is. Thanks for the 500 bits. Appreciate it. Stinky beaver. Thanks for the $2.50,
6% tax. Frank West and TK for a Jerma Rumble. Why is everything 6%? Why do I, why do I have to
take 6% of your money? What? Is that the number that we agreed upon somehow? 6% tax? I said that?
Oh, not a bad number. Hey, uh, Firo Swee. Thanks for the 400 bits. Dude, Jerma, thank you for
streaming on my birthday. Happy birthday. We've got one right now. It's Firo's birthday. Happy
birthday, Firo. Hope you had a good one. Happy birthday. Uh, Midna says, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey, Jerma, I don't usually watch full streams due to my work schedule and only heard about
your medical procedure through SUS last week. Hope everything went well and you're feeling
better. Thanks for streaming. Yeah, I'm doing all right. I'm at the stage right now where I'm,
the, the light at the end of the tunnel is starting to open and I'm going, I can see through that.
I can see it. The beams kind of just hit me right in the eye and it's like, oh, oh, oh,
oh, it's so bright. And I'm, I'm going, I'm walking towards it. No, that's not a good,
that's a bad analogy. That means that, that means I'm dead. That's a terrible, no, no, the light at
the end. Don't go into the light, Jeremy. Don't go into the light. Go the other way. Open the door
that you came through. Uh, go away from the light. Right. Uh, I'm getting to the end of the road
here. That also is not a great analogy. Okay. I know what might be wrong with me. They're done.
So therefore, hopefully the next couple of months solutions start to be put in place as to this
fucking dumb mystery illness. So I kind of have some answers now. There you go. That's better than
don't walk towards the light. But yeah, I'm fine. Don't worry. I'm fine. It's not a significant
enough problem to really affect my day to day life. It's just kind of there. And I always know
it's there and it's just irritating, but it's not, it doesn't necessarily affect too much of my
actual day to day to day life. It just kind of hurts sometimes. It's just kind of, it just,
like, it just hurts a little. Not enough to really, you know, it just hurts a little. That's it.
Am I colorblind? I don't think so. But I appreciate it. Thank you. Hey, Flugboy,
thanks for the 250. You know how long I've been in this community. I thought I had seen everything
and I'm sure you've seen it by now, but someone put the fucking picture of you crying on their
credit card. I love this community with all my heart and they never cease to amaze me.
All right. But here's the thing. They, you have to hand that to the cashier. The cashier doesn't
know who I am. So I am almost taken completely out of that equation. That's the thing between
you and that cashier. They don't know me. And if they do, that you just surprised us the surprise
of the century. Somebody just leaked it. Okay. What the fuck, man? That's so fucking ridiculous.
Dunkin' Donuts. How does it look? Here's some Dunkin' Donuts because you have good news. You
can upload custom photos on Dunkin' Donuts gift cards. It's here. You guys are fucking,
you guys are fucking hilarious. But what's that person that you give it to?
Because you're epic. That's how I read that. Here's some Dunkin' Donuts. Because you're
epic. That's how I see it. Now, you know, put it in a greeting card now. You know those cards
that you open and they just talk. Put that, get that sound bite into a greeting card.
Put the Dunkin' Donuts card in there. And when it's opened, it plays that really shitty low
bitrate quality audio. I mean, you have my permission. We are almost at the end.
Let's get the credits rolling as they do. Let's move the scene over to here. Let's roll the
credits. Thanks for watching. Thanks for the subs. Holy shit. That's a lot of subs. I was gone for
about four days. So look at all these racked up subs. You guys are fucking awesome. Thank you.
Thanks for the support. Thanks for streaming. Thank you for streaming, guys. I really loved
that hand simulator stream. It was great. No, thank you for real. All of you. Let's head back
to the bits. Let's finish them up. Flugboy, thanks for the 250. You know how long I've been
in this community. I've seen everything and I'm sure you've seen it by now, but somebody put the
fucking picture of you crying on their credit card. I love this community with all my heart and
they never cease to amaze me. What? Somebody put it on the what somebody put my that image on
a what do you mean that image? You have a link? Hey, mad. Thanks for the 1500 bits mad. No, I'm
not kidding. Thank you, mad. Thanks for the 1500 bits. So it was my birthday on Thanksgiving,
which had a good meal. So here's your obligatory 10%. It was 6% must have gotten that incorrect.
Please let me out of your basement, Mr. Comedy Man. It's getting dark in here. Okay.
Okay. Oh, he spelled it. M-O-N-K-U-H. Monka S with two S's. Uh, phylactery. I missed
5000 bits from phylactery. Thanks for the $50 phylactery. Again, again, again, again, again,
50, 50, 50, 100, 100, 100, 100, 100, 100. Thank you. And you say $50 for playing spill joke the game.
Love you, Jeremy. That level was huge. I didn't think it was gonna be that big.
It was 500 last time. Yeah. Yeah, it was. And who could forget Bob Boy? Bob Boy 61. I mean,
out of out of the potentially just thousands and thousands and thousands of community members,
Bob Boy 61 has got to be up there at least in like the top in the top like fucking
two to 300,000 people. Thank you, Bob Boy for the five subs. Appreciate it. You rank us. He's
picking favorites now. Yeah, he's in the top like two to three. How many people actually think,
watch this channel? I have no idea. How many people follow this channel? Two what?
250 something, 270. How many, how many followers are on this channel?
Well, I can't, I'm too, I'm too lazy to click over here apparently. How many followers do I have?
265,000 followers. Okay. So yeah, I, Bob Boy's definitely in somewhere in the top like 300,000.
That's a flex. How's that? What do you mean? How's that flex? Do a tier list of all your viewers,
all everyone that's followed. That would take probably five years to do that. If I did it
every single stream and it would never be finished because people would know that the stream was
happening and they would continue to make new accounts and follow. I would in the first week
of doing that stream, I would probably get 10,000 new followers. It would never end. You guys are
all up at, hold on. I don't want, wait a minute. I don't want you to think, you know, I don't want
you. Well, you, everyone, everyone's asked here. I don't know if I could say that. What about the
person that came in here and they may be followed the channel. They called me like a idiot like two
days ago. Is that person on S tier? This is not you making the tier list. This is me making the
tier list. Everyone except him. Yeah. Everybody except that person. Who is it though? I don't know.
M-O-N-K-U-H space B-S-S. I don't know. Who is it? Thank you back in for the 300 bits. Hi,
Jerma. Thanks for streaming as always. I'm losing, uh, I'm losing cognition more and more,
but hopefully my upcoming appointment should help maybe. Anyways, I hope you and Chad have a
wonderful day. Thanks for the 300 bits back in. Let's send some love and energy over to back in.
Thanks for the 300 bits. Hope you have a wonderful day. Take care. Thank you so much for the 300
bits. Send some Jerma hearts over to back in please. There we go. That's what I like to see.
That's what I like to see. Also, thank you to snoozingcopter for the 250. Hey, Jerma,
missed the beginning of the streams. I haven't heard the medical updates yet. Hope you're all
right. However, I wanted to say something else. You've been robbed. Oh no, there's more. There's
more. There's more. There's more. Any stories that you could share? I, I've, no, I've never
been robbed before. They said my girlfriend recently got her phone snatched out of her hands.
Holy shit, that's horrible. Currently seeing if they can access the cameras.
But it was a real shock. Some people are unbelievable. Also play Disco Elcium. Do it.
I just started it and I swear to god this game is made for you. Um, no, well, I've never been,
I've never been robbed. Like somebody comes up to you and says, hey,
give me your money or something. That's never happened. But Disco Elcium. I, I, maybe. That's
been kind of just sitting there. I feel like Disco Elcium is going to be dusk. I'm not going
to play it for like a year and then I'll play it and it'll be one of my favorite games I played
the whole year. That's kind of what happened with dusk. So that just count on it. Count on it. Hey,
Bobo Durago. Thanks for the 500 bits they say. Sup Jerma, I'm playing Apex Legends right now.
I absolutely love the game. Have you ever played it? I have not. Also nice stream and also my
username is pronounced Bobo Durango. Please say it. There's no N. It's, it's, it's Bobo Durago.
What have I done? What do you mean? What have I done? What did I do? What did I do?
Okay. Everyone's like, Oh my God. He said, like, okay, do you understand saying names out loud
that I, that I, I have many panic attacks when it's like, wait, he said it. He, he said the thing.
What did I say? What happened? Where? What did I do? It's like every like seven names or every
like 10 names is that one like panic attack moment where it's like, did somebody just phonetically
make me say something horrible? No, no, no, right? No, no, no. Okay. No. But no, I've never played
Apex. I'm not really into the BR thing was never my cup of tea. I heard, I heard that it was fun
if you liked BRs. But then I heard that it was not fun anymore. You won PUBG mobile on stream.
Yeah, but I only played PUBG mobile for like two weeks and then I just deleted it and never played
it again. But hey, KXE, thanks for the $20, 2000 bits from KXE. No message. Thank you.
Thanks for the 2000 bits. Uh, Squimpist, thanks for the 250. Hey Jermbo, just wanted to say,
I know chronic illnesses, pains. They're no joke. And I'm sorry about the bozos in chat who are mean
about it. Living with these things can be tough, but you're tougher. Godspeed. Yeah, but here's the
thing. It's not. I've had an annoying chronic illness for like more than 10 years. I, I kind
of know what to expect. I've had irritable bowel disease. It's just for, I don't know how long. I
was like a, I was a junior senior in college when I first had to start, started having the problems.
But that's, that's what 10, 12, 12 plus years ago, something like that. So, you know, I, it's, it's,
it is what it is. It is what it is. I'm just going to keep just, uh, kicking at it. You know what I
mean? Till I start to get some answers and some real solutions, right? Which those should be
starting very soon. Hey SaranRaps, thank you for the 300 bits. Hey Jerma, thanks for streaming despite
your health problems. Is the game Rain World on your radar? Rain World? Uh, what is Rain World?
Not Rim, not Rim World, right? I know Rain World. What is this game? This looks pretty cool.
Wow, are you like a little fox or something? Wayne's World? No. I'll punch that into Steam
after the stream, see what it looks like. It's very cute, very hard. But I mean, I, on stream,
I completed after only, on hard. So I think I'll be all right. It'd make a good what do I do stream
game. That's cool. Hey Gondolin, thanks for the 250. Hey Chumer, Chad plus Boomer, will you do a
video game award stream with your villain hair? Nah, I'll probably have a haircut by then. I'll
have a haircut by then. Thank you Gondolin, appreciate it. Thank you Saturn for the 500 bits.
Hey Jerma, it's inspiring that you have these health issues, like IBS, hernias, and back
problems, but you still get up and entertain us where others may not even get out of bed.
Much love. Here's the thing though. This is one of the, this is probably in the top one, two,
or three things that I care about in the whole world. I have to. It's, I care so much about
doing this. I have so much fun. This is so interesting to me that I, I would, I would
rather be doing this than something, anything else. You know what I mean?
And it's, it's not, don't get me wrong. It's not a scenario where I'm getting up and like forcing
myself to turn a stream on and I'm not healthy or happy or anything. No, that's not the case at all.
If that was the case, I just wouldn't do it. I just wouldn't turn the stream on,
which I've done many times, many, many, many times. I've pushed a stream, delayed a stream,
said, you know what? No, we're going to, we're going to do like three days, like Tuesday,
Wednesday, Thursday, instead of what I said, I would, you know, I'm not feeling it today.
I do it all the time. So do not worry about that at all. It's not, I'm not in a position right now
where it's a major, major, major issue or anything. It's just a minor problem that's going to take.
Here's the thing. It's some, it's a minor problem. That's going to take some potential major changes
for me to fix. Right. Then that's what you get. That's what you do. But I do appreciate it.
Appreciate the concern. Do not worry. Thank you produces. Thank you produces San for the 500 bits.
Want to thank you for making me laugh so much. This time when I have, there's times where I haven't
laughed so hard. Oh, sorry about that. I got like a bubble in my throat. Okay. Uh, there's time where
I haven't laughed so hard in my life. Thanks to you. It's been really making my days that much
better considering where I am now. Uh, kind of lost and drifting at the moment, trying to find
my place. But these laughs are well worth making me know the world is still turning.
And also the burger king has the whopper junior, which has the same great taste as the regular
whopper for a dollar 50, except it's fucking tiny. It's a small sandwich. Okay. It's, uh, it's a
whopper junior is, um, just, uh, Wendy's bacon, uh, Wendy's junior bacon. What the fuck? What's the,
what's the thing called with the huge bunch of lettuce on it? And they've got rid of the lettuce.
They changed it recently. It's just a tomato now. What's called the junior bacon cheeseburger
from Wendy's. I like, did they change the recipe or something? Cause I remember it had lettuce on
it and I didn't get lettuce last time. Wendy's is not kosher. Is any fast is, is McDonald's and
Burger King kosher? I don't think it is. No, McDonald's is not kosher. And what do you mean
kosher McDonald's and Burger King? There are rats. I can't even say that out loud because I don't
want to get like sued. Uh, there are rats in rat movie too. It's a fun movie. Only two or three
more to do. We've got, uh, shades fen, shades fen for two 50. Hey German, watching your VR stream
videos lately and didn't remember just how funny they were. You're going to do more VR before
half-life Alex. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Also ever since the, uh, I'm Jeremy Lammy and Parappa streams
have been massively hooked on the OST, especially the Jeremy Lammy one can never thank you enough
for all the laughs and introduced me to such an awesome music. Can't wait to see what you have in
store for us during December. I'll put these kids to sleep. Will you? Yes. There will be a, another
VR stream before a half-life Alex and by I'll probably just do, it'll be one of those scenarios
where, uh, is this even playing? Why is the music stopped? Okay. That was weird. Uh, it'll be a
scenario where we'll do like another five, 10 games over the course of a week. So yeah, I,
absolutely. And I will be, and I will be one of the, every single streamer on the website
that's doing half-life Alex at launch. Yes, they will. But thank you. Also, this is, uh, from
uh, Flugboy. It's a Twitter link and it's, it's the Dunkin Donuts gift card. This has 17,000 likes
and has been retweeted five fucking thousand times. I thought this was just like a few dozen of you
thought this was funny. What? What the fuck? Link the tweet. Uh, this five, I can't even get like
5,000 retweets on anything. Oh my God. It's cause you don't tweet. Yeah, I know. I know. I know. I
know. But when I do, when I do, that's so funny. And then the other tweet is the, the debit card,
the credit card. So I think somebody linked the picture already, but am I going to do Boneworks?
Yeah. If I'm going to do Boneworks, I need the new controllers though. I have to get those
index controllers. The game was made for it. When you do go viral, it's the mom baking cookies
of the drawstring tweets. Going viral. I'm going, Hey mom, I'm going viral. If you get the index
controls before Christmas, you get Alex for free. Is this really, that's a pretty good deal.
All right guys, we'll see you tomorrow. Joel and I are going to try to attempt to play, uh,
Halo Reach co-op. What did I just do? That's the wrong thing. It's this one. So see you tomorrow.
If something comes up for some reason, then we'll probably figure something else out.
Flugboy, thanks for the 250 right at the end here. I know I didn't add a caption that last one,
but I'm sure that you know what those links are by now. I hope you have a good rest of your night.
Wish me luck on my finals. Please. I really need it. Good luck on your finals. Hopefully you studied.
Hopefully you get that information we walked in. Thanks for the 250. Good luck on your finals,
Flugboy. Oh, Jerma real quick before you go, be ready for Reach not to work because it has
peer-to-peer connections. Well, that's bad. We're going to test it to make sure it does work.
And if it doesn't, then we'll figure something out. It is, you know what? You are right. It is
day one launch day of a brand new video game in 2019. It's guaranteed to not fucking work
as intended for at least six or seven days. Technically day two. You're right.
Halo brand new video game. Well, you know what I mean? Like a brand new launch.
That's been, it's a brand new, it's a launch of a game that has a lot of multiplayer connections.
We'll see. See you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves. Thanks for joining me on the
hand simulator. I'm medieval and visceral clean of detail. Triple stream. That's right. You got
three streams in one today. Stream three separate streams in one stream. Now I don't granted.
It was the first, the first hour and 40 minutes. Uh, for a lot of you was like having your teeth
pulled without novocaine, but it was fun. The streams, not even cannon. That's right. The
streams, not cannon. This is an expanded universe stream because I wasn't even going to scream
today, but I was like, you know what? Fuck it. Let's go. Let's play hand simulator and piss off
an entire community. That sounds like a good idea. Good night guys. See you tomorrow. Have a
wonderful rest of your night. Take care. Somebody said, didn't even try a hand simulator multiplayer.
They were burning my house down. I had to leave. Maybe I'll play it again in multiplayer.
Maybe you'll see it again. Fuck it. We'll do it. Halo reach. Let's go play with Joel. Yeah,
that's what's happening. Do you remember when me and Joel did the gamer challenge?
We made the gamer challenge like a year ago. Let's go. Gamer challenge activated. They're
going to be co-op game. Let's go. What time? Somewhere. Oh, let me see. I actually have it.
This also be correct, but just for you to know, be the first to know.
A year in the, it's a year in the works. It'll be, so because we're working
around both of our like streaming schedule, streaming times, it's going to be somewhere
around four PST. Joel doesn't have a schedule. Neither do I. So when you have two non-schedules
run into each other, you got to pick a time here. 4 p.m pacific state tomorrow. Good night. Take care.