Hello. Welcome, welcome, welcome. Hope you're having a good afternoon, everybody.
I'm having a pretty good afternoon. Show yourself. Nah. Nah. He's early?
Well, the schedule changed a little bit today. It's gonna be during like 4 or 5 p.m. Pacific.
Change of plans, as you see. Apparently Joel is having PC problems. He got some new audio
equipment and he's walking up on them. So he's like, I'm just gonna troubleshoot it and I'm like,
go for it. Computers suck. Oh, I understand. PC gaming. When you set up your setup, he hates OBS.
What was he using before? Xsplit or something? Here comes the substitute teacher's voice.
Good morning, welcome class. I'm your substitute teacher. Today we're gonna learn how to do math
problems. Okay, thank you. All right, so what we're gonna do instead is something I've wanted
to do for a while and it should be interesting. Interesting as in it could go very, very, very
poorly very quickly or I'm gonna beat the whole damn game. I'm gonna play Diablo 2, straight up
Vanilla Diablo 2. Hardcore and you guys decide every single thing. You pick class, you pick the
stat points and you pick the skill points. So you're already dead. You are already dead. Yes.
Something like that. Oh, that's a terrible idea. I actually was freaking out about this because
I brought this up to be like a month or two ago and somebody in the chat said, dude, you're gonna
die to corpse fire. And I'm like, don't fucking say that. Don't say that because I might and it's
if you know, you know. When corpse fire dies, it's like eight minutes into the game. There is a
chance that the computer will hang for three seconds and he's going to explode and you'll die.
It happens. I have to be very careful but I'm going to leave most decisions up to you. Now
you will not have the decision of choosing weapons and items because if you give me a complete and
total dickhead build and make me use a club as a source verse or something like I'm I mean,
I'm going to pick the items. I'm not just going to be naked and shit like this is not going to happen
but it should be fun. I also found out something interesting today that I didn't know because why
would I know this? My Diablo II account is banned from Battle.net for some particular reason. I don't
know why. I can't. I'm apparently been shadow banned. I didn't do anything. I don't know when
this happened. I haven't played Diablo II in at least a couple of years but apparently I did
something wrong. I'm not sure what it was and here's the worst part about that. Diablo II is
in a funny position right now on Battle.net where I can't buy another copy. I can't. To get a new
CD key I can't purchase another copy. Maybe it was a mod? I don't know. I can buy a copy for a friend
so I'm gonna have to eventually if I want to play online buy a copy for a friend send it to
their email and then tell them to give me the CD key. What? Why would you buy again?
Well what am I supposed to do? Call Blizzard support? Hey uh I don't know what happened like
four years ago. I have no idea but I think I've been shadow banned on Diablo II. What are they
gonna do? They don't give a shit about Diablo II anymore. You know I would assume if they could
just delete Diablo II off the store they would. I'm not gonna call Blizzard. But anyways so I was
under the assumption that I might be able to get a little help if I needed it. No I have to do this
alone for the best maybe. I was thinking maybe oh fuck this is gonna be impossible for me to do this
alone. Hey I know some of you guys have D2 get on like just kill kill on Dario for me whatever
it's for the stream. I can't do that now I have to do it all myself. Without further ado we are
we are gonna get started. Please do me a quick favor. I need to make sure that you guys can
click on the screen. So uh oh just realized something very important. It'll be tricky it's
gonna take a little finagling. I just realized that I can't can't can't. All right how do you
in Windows 10 how do you pin a window to not be minimized? Anybody know is there like a shortcut?
Because every time I click off the screen the window drops. Is there a way to just pin a window
so it never uh never it gets minimized? You have to do it in the task manager? All I have is close
window. Oh that's complicated. Is it? Make it windowed? It is windowed but I it's I have
it doesn't matter every time I minimize the window. You know every time I minimize the
window then no no no look I'll just show you in real time. I'll just show you in real time.
So for instance here is Diablo 2 right? But here's my cursor if I click off the window at all
bye bye here's my desktop. How do I do that? How do I keep that there? How do I keep it from doing
that? How do I keep it there? Pretty sick background I know. But to turn on click map
so I have to click out of the window. You know what I'm saying? There's got to be a way. What is
this background? All right we're not ready yet hold on. The boomer wallpaper? No it's a default
basic wallpaper sorry. All right where is it? I have to download a program? Do I have to download
more programs for this? I think it'll be fine. I just have to like make the window maximized again
when I turn on click maps. So anytime click maps turns on just wait like five seconds before you
click anything. I know that's asking a lot. It's an 800 by 600 boomer wallpaper. This isn't a joke
background. Do you know how hard it is to find? I got three monitors and it's hard it's kind of
hard to find one that doesn't hurt my eyes because you get it you get attacked from all angles.
Three just three monitors only three omega low. Only what do you mean only three? That's a ton.
Like I'm under attack from my right screen because it's just there. What do I need? Who needs more
than three monitors? What do you need it for? I'm not like watching tv on something. Maybe I mean
that'd be kind of fun actually. All right we're gonna test see if this works. Let me just see
what happens. Here is Diablo 2. Remember what happens if I die in hardcore? I die when you die
when you die you're dead. There it is. Okay so let me make sure the click maps works.
Otherwise that would be bad wouldn't it? Yeah you're gonna get the mountains every
every like every time there's a decision that needs to be made you're gonna get these beautiful
mountains. All right does click maps actually even work? It does. Well this is just a test.
Any people clicking? It's me on the right. Look at that it's pretty good actually.
You have scuffed maps. Well the reason why I have scuffed maps is because it's actually easier to
the bubbles to not run into each other. All right but this is not the this is not the choice. This
is just us hanging out for a second. Fire I want you to be fire be fire. Just so you guys know
I really am actually looking to you to not ruin this whole thing and I know you give I'm giving
this to thousands of people. So this is not this is not it. Hold on take a look at those mountains
for a second. This is and fine if you want to have a 200 strength source for that has a melee
for a move. I mean I'll try to work with it but just know if I kill the last boss with this shitty
character I think that I think I deserve something there. I think I deserve at least a little bit of
credit. Don't do melee it's shit. Well all right this is not up to me. Are you ready to pick the
class? Here we go. Pick the class. I'll go over them just in case people don't know. I mean Diablo
it's been a while. Diablo II is an old fucking game. Amazon. Bows. Spears. Ranged mostly. Javelins.
Assassin. Traps. Bombs. Martial arts. Mostly melee with a little bit of electricity involved.
Necromancer. The meme character. Diablo II if you don't know has this thing where you can have like
a hundred companions on the screen. This is the summoner. You can have like
85 fucking people running around with you. Okay cool. It kind of sucks though. So just let you know.
Barbarian. Melee. Very easy. Or you could put 20 points into potion. Potion find.
And that'll be completely useless. That sounds fun. Melee. Paladin.
That's all you need to know. That's all. That's literally it. Sorceress.
Magic. Casting. Bells. Fire. Lightning. Ice. And druid. Summoning. A little bit of summoning.
Also shapeshifting. Bears. Turning into a wolf. You guys know? You guys get your ideas? This is it.
Majority rules here. Whoever has the most percentage. And by the way if you click,
if you click on fire or exit your vote is useless. We're not doing it again. Don't start yet. I'll
tell you when. Look at those mountains. These mountains are fucking beautiful. Here we go.
I don't know. Use window capture? That doesn't work. Okay. That seems like a lot of people
want to do Necromancer. You're on an old version of Diablo. I'm on 1.14d and I have the glide
wrapper installed. I shouldn't be doing this but it is. And there's not much I can do about it
at the moment. All right. Looks like we're doing Necromancer. Which I'll work with it.
Wait. Why do you guys want to do this? You really want to do this? This is going to be so,
this is going to be the most boring playthrough ever. I'm not going to. All right. This is also
important. No. We're doing another vote. We're doing. No. No. Are we? I don't. Okay. Listen.
Listen. Listen. Important. I won't. I can't kill bosses. I know what you're going to do.
I know exactly. I know what you guys are going to do. I can't kill bosses.
It's literally this will be unbeatable. I'm going to have to hit the bosses with like a wand.
Or a stick. Like six or seven hundred times. And run back into a portal. All right. Fine. Fine.
Fine. Fine. God damn it. Fine. All right. Let's go. Veto it. Veto it. I can't. Why did I say that
in the beginning? By the way, this is the worst thing you could do. Actually it's not. So you
just got baited. Congratulations guys. Yep. Let's go. Check out those mountains for a sec.
Okay. Barbarian actually would be the worst thing in the world if you did Barbarian potion
finding. I literally don't want to have moves. Or a melee sorceress with like eight hundred
strength. Completely worthless. I can work with this. Maybe I should pick the stats because
otherwise this is going to be fucking impossible. No. Not Sans. Of course somebody's going to say
Sans. Unbelievable. I am actually fucking mad about that. I am actually upset about this. Tommy
Pickles? How about Tommy Pickles? Makes no sense. Tommy Pickles does not make any sense.
Chucky? Chucky the Necromancer? Okay. I like that. Here we go. Diablo II hardcore
as a Necromancer. Good luck. No. Too late. It's a bad name. It's too late. You guys. This guy's
going to last five minutes. It's a bad name. And okay. Chucky's a bad name but Sans is a good name.
Tommy Lee Bones. Sans. Tommy Lee Bones. That's very elaborate. I like Tommy Lee Bones.
And it fits. Tommy Lee Bones. Warning. Once a hardcore character dies it cannot be played
again. Are you sure you wish to make a hardcore character? Yes. Here we go. Good day. You guys
hear it? Greetings stranger. I'm not surprised to see your kind here. Many adventurers have traveled
this way since the recent troubles began. No doubt you've heard about the tragedy that
befell the town of Tristram. Just look at these mountains for a second. Some say the Diablo
walks the world again. I don't know if I believe that but I did travel this route a few weeks ago.
It was headed east to the mountain pass guarded by the rogue monastery. Maybe it's nothing but
evil seems to have trailed in his wake. I didn't skip anything. You'll see shortly after the
wanderer went through. As everybody knows the fucking story, do we really have to do this?
And strange creatures began ravaging the countryside. Until it's safer outside the
camp and the gates are reopened, I'll remain here with my caravan. I hope to leave for Loot
Ghulain before the shadow that fell over Tristram consumes us all. If you're still alive then I'll
take you along. Mute the game audio. You've never played Diablo 2 ever? Holy shit. You're in for a
tramy. She can tell you more. Okay so I'm a necromancer. We don't need the help on there.
I already know how to play the game. Right now as you can see I've got my inventory. I've got a wand
which is plus one to raise skeletons so I can have a skeleton. None of this matters. I'm dead in
fucking five minutes. Like this I'm gonna lose. No I get rid of the wand. What do you mean get rid
of the fucking wand? What are you talking about? Why would I get rid of the wand? See this is why
I'm so glad I have you have nothing to do with the items I can equip. Here's your stash. I'm so I
can't wait. I love this game so much. Just like you played D3. Drop wand. I know I can't. I do
have to do this though. So you uh reanimate a skeletal warrior from a target corpse. If something
dies you can bring it back to life as a skeleton. Right now I have one total skeleton. It'll have
20 health. 2020. One to two damage. Drop the wand. Chat picks everything. To an extent though.
No I'm not dropping the fucking wand. I'm not dropping the wand. I can't summon. I can't.
What are you talking about? You can't punch things. The necromancer and the level one.
Cain's title. No that's true.
Drop it. I'm not dropping. I'm not dropping the wand. You're not going to convince me.
No this is hardcore man. I don't want to die to corpse pyre. If I die to corpse pyre then I'm
not going to stream for a week. Like I'll just turn the stream off. I'll get out of here. No way.
Like that's too embarrassing.
I implore you stranger please help us find a way to lift this terrible curse on this town.
There is a place of great evil. There is a place of great evil in the wilderness.
Kasha's rogue scouts have informed me that a cave nearby is filled with shadowy creatures
and horrors from beyond the grave. Predicted it. Yeah I've only done what you're seeing right now.
Probably realistically five to six hundred times.
If you are sincere about helping us you can find the dark labyrinth and destroy the foul beasts.
Be the great eye watch over you. All right so Diablo 2 works like this. You get six quests in
each zone. There are one two three four five zones. That's six no just five. He doesn't even know his
own game. So the six quests in every zone. This is the first one. Look for the den in the wilderness
outside the rogue's camp. We're going to change a couple things just to make sure
because I don't like that. I don't like that at all. We're going to go into the options. We're
going to go into the mini map controls. We're doing the small map. I'm going to fade everything.
So then we just keep it on the screen there in the top left. Now we got a mini map.
You click to move in this game which is interesting. Click to move in this game.
All right let's go. Let us pick the options. Options. We're going to find the den of evil
guys. Are you ready? Beware. I'm so ready. Pre-recorded stream. That would be funny.
Go get a stone of Jordan. Just wait till you see the drops in this game.
I'm so nervous. I can't like walk around. So I got posters down here obviously. You click on
things to attack. We got one skeleton. This held us up there. Actually I actually don't mind this.
Hold alt to see everything. Turn the game down. Is it loud now? How's that? Better? Is that a
little more bearable? All right looking for the bloodmore. Now we're in the bloodmore.
Your video buffered. We're talking about buffered. It's Goldilocks too much. The game works just like
I don't know why. Why do I feel like I need to describe Diablo to you guys? It's every single
human. Even those that don't play video games know this game. Every human. I literally don't.
Do I need to explain Diablo too? Do I? All right here we go. You guys are going to have some
choices here and you're gonna have to pick. That's the ultimate rumor. That's an air rumor.
That's a fucking that's flying like over the house. That's okay. We're good. The way that
skills work in Diablo is every time you level up you get a skill point. Each one of these can have
up to 20 points each. Summoning spells. Poison and bone. Curses. As you can see. You have a lot of
choices. Each one of these can hold 20 points. If I were you. If I was watching this stream right
now I would go open up a Diablo 2 skill calculator. Find out what you'd like to pick. You can't you
know you can't choose. If you guys choose nothing. If all of you guys click on like the the X.
Then I get to choose. Run on 3D audio. I can't turn that. That feature like doesn't exist anymore.
All right I need some items. We're gonna find the little cave. We're looking for a little cave.
It's a little and by the way I'm gonna level up soon. You guys will have an opportunity to fucking
me. It's all right. Imagine min maxing every playthrough lol. Yeah it's Diablo man. You gotta
be careful. He's listening to the he's listening to this in 2D.
I can't fucking believe this is not gonna work. You know how many times I've tried
to do okay you can only play as a summoning necromancer if you have like four friends to carry
you. Oh shit. Look at that. You wanna see? Show all items. Show all items. All right look.
Low quality leather armor. That's a fucking pogchamp right there. I've never seen one.
There's your belt. Your belt can only hold four potions at the moment.
And these potions are not instant. You have to eventually end up spamming these.
This is the first ding. All right guys. Let me get to. Here's the thing. I can't just like stand still
because this is hardcore. I'll die. Just wait a minute. We'll do this. Give me a second. All
right. Is this safe? Is it safe? I think. Okay. We'll do the skill point first. So the first thing
you need to do is you have to pick a category. So it's gonna be category first. Okay. Once you
pick that category don't select anything. You're picking a category first. Is this uh yeah this is
LOD. Don't touch anything. I'm gonna show you the focus of mountains for a second. Okay please
choose a category. Right. I click this one. I choose skeleton. I like skeleton. He looks cool.
All right. Point number one is gonna go into summoning spells. It just is. It's too much.
All right. I'm gonna show you a cool fucking mountain for a second. Okay. Where do you want
me to put the point? There's only one place it can go. You can only put it. There's only one place
it can go. I can't touch this yet. Gee. I fucking wonder where it's gonna go guys.
Well. Okay. I wanted to raise skeleton. Now I got two. Pretty cool. All right. Now.
Dude. I gotta figure out how to keep this fucking thing. All right. The stat points thing. This is
gonna be hard because this is so important. Like it's so important. If there's somebody watching
right now that's played this game and I know this is probably up high in the categories on Twitch
right now. You're about to see something that's gonna make you fucking just curl up into your
chair and I know and I can't fix it. Nothing I can do about it. By the way this is for all five
points. We're not gonna sit here and do each individual point. One at a time. This stream
isn't gonna be all day. The stream is never gonna turn off. Every single point has to be voted on
but what about the mountains? All right. This is for two at a time. Two at a time. Two points at
a time. Where's it going? I'm not even sure it's it's far away enough. Make sure you're clicking on
the right spot. Thank you. It might be too far away. I might just have to. I might have to decide
these. I might have to decide these is too. Wait. Hold on. Mountain. Wait. Zoom it in. I got no.
Hold on. I gotta like. Zooming in this guy. Look at those mountains. Hold on. I can't zoom in. I
can't zoom in this. I can't. All five. This is for all five points. Do not do an
individual mountain voting. No. Just okay. I'm gonna take a screenshot and I'm gonna zoom the
fuck in. That's a good idea. All right. Screenshot. Print screen. I didn't think this one. All right.
I got a print screen. Take a look at those mountains. All right. Hold on. Give me one second.
Give me one second. Give me give me give me one second. So this will be this will be much easier.
In fact, yeah, this is going to be so much easier. It becomes the longest stream of 2020 or the
shortest one. I'm not sure yet. We'll find out eventually. Okay. Hold on one sec.
Hey, you guys will be able to see them both. That. Okay. I just wish I could keep the window up. I
don't know why it's doing that. I have it in windowed mode. I cannot play this game online.
My account is banned for no I for no reason. I didn't fucking do anything. All right. Let's save
this. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. All right. Here we go. So now I can just do this. This would be much
easier. Do I do this for each individual skill tree too? So we could just go bang bang. I got a
good idea. Hold on. Okay. I got a good idea. This is gonna be a good idea. No, don't do that.
No, that's a good idea. I mean, this is the fucking window. Shit's gonna be all over the place.
All right. Just get, you know, here like the stream hadn't even started yet. Just fucking hold
on. I'll be right back. All right. I believe I'm ready to start doing this. Okay. For a second,
I just had a panic attack because I realized that this is this has been minimized the whole
fucking time and I I've just been like I could be dead right now. Okay. Hold on. That just like
scared the shit out of me. All right. Let me just get these loaded up. All right. Just hold on a
second. The stream's starting to just a minute. Pick which way you want five points to go. Go for
it. Nice JPGE. Yeah, I know. I know. Trust me. Strength. Okay. Of course. We did it. Hooray.
This will, once we work the kinks out, this is gonna be a lot of fun. Well, good for you guys,
I guess. All right. Okay. Five points in strength. Pay no attention to these.
I'm just getting them ready. Don't click on any of these yet. Don't pay any attention to these.
These are just putting my my getting my pages ready. Mountains? No, we're gonna we're trying
to minimize the amount of mountains we have to have. Put that on there. I know it's gonna be all
stretched out, but you have to just it's gonna be easier for you to click. Sounds good. Everything
should be good to go, right? Now, very important. Okay. Sorry, guys. I didn't realize this is gonna
be as much as a pain in the ass as this actually is. All because I can't fucking get off my
minimization. Don't get mad. I'm good. This is called this is this is poison and bone.
Which one is this one? This is versus. Okay. What the fuck is this one? I promise we'll actually
do something in a minute. Blame Blizzard for literally not giving a shit about the games
they made 15 years ago, unless they can resell them for $40. Oh, hey, we had some community
subs. We had 20 community subs from Zap X. Z half X. And hold on. Wait, hold on. A bunch of money
came in. Thanks for the 20 subs. Thanks for the 50 fucking dollars from AB Joe. Give me one moment.
Well, I gotta get this stuff going. Kind of against the clock here trying to get this to work.
All right. Now I just have to add it to the stream deck. Okay. This is it. We're just like,
just look at the screen for a minute. Blizzard. Fuck your old games unless you can 15 years later
sell them for $50. I'm gonna call this one bone right now. I wonder how many sad people buy because
they sell it on on battle.net. They sell this shit on battle.net. I wonder how many disappointed
people go to buy this and then go, wow, this is fucking like not even remotely close to being what
it should be in 2020. All right. There's the bone. This is all for a purpose. Trust me. I promise.
It's a curse. Uh huh. Last one. I promise. Summon. Here we go. Imagine there having to be third
party mods to have the game run in a fucking window correctly. Blizzard entertainment.
Tis ain't the same, is it? And summon. All right. Here we go. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm actually ready
to fucking do this. If I'm dead, I'm gonna fucking be so bad. All right. We finally crossed the
threshold where I can do this. Sorry for the 500 people that left. Blame Blizzard. Always.
Here we go. I'll be shocked if I get past fucking Act 1. How have I not found the Den of Evil yet?
I'm gonna blame the dumb idiot streamer. You could. You could, but don't. Holy shit. Everyone
came back. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What? Hold on. Like 700 people left and they all just came back
instantly. Like they all came back at the same time. They were all just like, all right,
I'll come back in like 20 minutes. I'll get this shit figured out. Hey, what's going on guys?
Not a big deal. Don't worry. Everything's good to go. We are. I got two skeletons.
I'm gonna have to use a sword. Where's the Den of Evil? It never takes me this long. I've played
this game 2,000 times. Where's the Den of Evil? Wait, do I have a stamina? I'm already, I already
had a stamina. I didn't lose already. Your health has to go to zero to lose. Give me vitality next
time, please guys. For the love of God. No. Use the bow. I don't have any arrows. This is the
longest I think it's ever. This is the type of RNG you get where if I was speed running this game,
I would just smash my fingers on the desk and then quit. What is it? A car door? Yeah,
I smashed my fingers at my car door on my desk. Ah, there it is. Help. Damn it. Why aren't you
saying it? Help. Help me. Help me. Help. Help. Help me. Got it. All right. We have to kill every
single monster in Den of Evil. Oh God. No, I died. Within this place. That's good.
I think I got my two skeletons there. I got a dagger. Field? No, pet build would be.
I can't believe we're actually doing this. This is actually bullshit. This is gonna be so bad.
All right. Hold on. What did I get? Ooh, two sockets. Yeah. Yeah. One to three. Good for. No.
You're a summoner in hardcore by myself.
This early in the game, I mean, you get carried as a summoner to late game.
I'm not gonna be able to beat the first one. I'm actually kind of glad you guys are doing the
main and putting points into strength because I'm gonna have to hit the fucking first possible
wouldn't stick until the end. All right. Do I have any? I'm actually paranoid.
It's so loud too. Why is this so loud? Come on.
Amulet. I just let you guys know the way it's white is the lowest quality. Actually,
gray could be technically damaged. Blue is magic to standard. Yellow is rare. And then gold is
unique. Not legendary. You could call it legendary if you want. I know we leveled up. Just hold on.
We know how Diablo work, but I do you. I got like 10 people that's fucking 5,000 people here.
Yeah. Look it up. Just look up Diablo 2 rules and there's like a whole list. You can read them.
Be careful. There's a little mini boss in here. I got to heal.
Diablo 2 rules. It's great. Yeah. All right. You got to kill. Where's the shaman?
And you have to identify shit in this game. Actually, let's identify this. Hey,
plus two to strength. That's you guys are doing that already. Might as well just keep it going.
Is there even any skills that the necromancer has? Two to seven. I lose a skeleton though.
No, not worth it. I'm too scared to lose another skeleton. All right. Time to level up. So
here we go. Where are we going? Actually, I'm going to do it like this.
So you guys don't have to end up. You guys never have to see the mountains again.
I don't want you guys have to see the mountains again. All right. What are we doing?
That's first. Thank God. The mountains are the best bit of a stream. No, I don't. That's like
jarring. Are we actually going to put points into vitality for the love of God?
Thank you. Seriously. Thank you. You're not going to regret this. All right. Thank you. No energy.
Well, that's not that important right now. Very cool. Thanks guys. Back to it. Here we go.
So, um, yes, good work. All right. Now for the skill, the skill point where what, first of all,
you got to, maybe you got to pick a category. So why is this all fucked up? Hold on a second.
Should be spread across the whole thing. No, what? Lock this in place for the love of God.
I don't want you to see the goddamn mountains. I don't want you to see the mountains.
Okay. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. All right. I know this is real
ugly. You ready? Where are we going? Why is it doing this? Stop doing. Oh my God. I hate Blizzard.
He said it. Oh my God. He said it. He said it in this very moment. What is happening? Why is this?
What do you, am I going crazy? Okay. Am I going crazy? Why does this keep doing this?
Okay. Fucking Blizzard entertainment. Can you believe it? Where are we going? Why can I not
see this? I didn't spend the point. All right. We're going summoning. Good. Now where? Now what
do you want me to do? It only took an hour. And then for me to say that I hate Blizzard for this
to work. We can only go, all right. We can't even go anywhere for this. I can show you what these
things do if you want. All right. Three skeletons. Let's go.
Skeleton squad moving on. How many, how many more we have?
Funny. Am I allowed to click on shrines? Yes. All right. So at three points,
he's still the same amount of health. Better attack and defense. So that's good.
I feel like we're going to walk into a fire and I should hopefully get some good items.
Players at eight. Players at eight. Did I do that? Players, how about players?
No, that's, I'm going to die. That's like the quickest way for me to get destroyed. Four.
That's cheating. That's reverse cheating. That's seven times the difficulty.
You're going to get more experience. All right. No, no. All right. We'll do four.
Players set to four. That's more experience. What if I die though? All right. I might,
I might revert this. I'm kind of scared about this. How many, what if I, how many? Okay. It hurts.
It's power leveling. Lakers set to four. Yeah. It's simulating four people in the game.
There he is. There he is. There he is. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no. Don't, don't,
don't fuck this up. You guys get in there and you, that's corpse fire. He's fucking scary.
He has electricity. He, he, he just fucking one hit killed that guy.
He explodes when he dies and it's going to kill me. I'm, I'm going to, it's going to kill me.
It's going to kill me. I'm already panicking for no reason. How much health does he have?
All right. Get him. Get him. You have the AFK build on. I, this is actually not that big of a
deal. He's going to watch this. Ready? Watch all three of these. Wait, does he not have that move?
Oh shit. He doesn't have that move in normal. Okay. Well, we're fine. Level up again.
There is one more monster left. What are you doing? Skeletons are you doing? You're going
off on skeletons here. Where's this last one? That's what we got a ha ha copy pasta. Oh,
well cut it out. You're a monster. They're an underrated type of, I've never seen this before.
I've got a bunch of dog shit we got to throw away. I'm going to kill one more monster. We're going
to, we're going to get this down so I can actually, I swear to God, people only call my phone when the
stream is turned off. Nobody fucking calls me at any second of the day, unless it's, I'm live.
All right. Where's this last monster? They're trying to network with you.
Why would you do? No, not like when I'm, not when I'm working. You stream for eight hours though.
Yeah. But I start the stream around the same time, like between like, you know, two in the
afternoon, three in the afternoon, four in the afternoon, five in the afternoon. Sometimes one
in the afternoon. You know, it's a big window. You're right. I got to find this last monster.
Where's this? Oh, wait. Get all this gold. I got fucking banned from battling that. Like I'm, I'm
not happy with Blizzard at the moment. I'm like actually annoyed by this.
Press completed. I didn't do anything. Greetings. You have cleansed the den of evil.
So if we're doing the den of evil, we get a skill point. You've earned my trust and may yet
restore my faith and humanity. What is training in the skill of your choice? Thank you.
All right. So, uh, again, we're, uh, we're, where would you guys like to go?
That's so ugly, but it has to be like this. I don't, I refuse to show you the mountains.
Where we go? Okay. Summoning. We got 2000 clicks already. Show the available skill pass. Yeah,
I'll do that too. I think I know where everyone wants to go. I want to go to summoning. Very cool.
So from here, uh, I wonder what you want to do. Uh, yeah. So we're going to put it in skeleton
build. Fucking dumb ass boring chat. I didn't say that. Oh yeah. Skeletons.
It's all right. It's okay. We're going to be good. All right. We're going to put it into skeletons.
Let's take a look at what these points actually do first. So, uh, as you can see here are the
paths. So you probably should have seen that first. Okay. Let's actually, let's go over this first.
Let's go over this first. We've opened up some stuff. All right. So you
spray listed. We're going to do it again. Ray skeleton skeleton mastery is what you can do as
well. Cause this path has gone over this way. Uh, it's a passive increases the life and damage of
Ray skeletons. So you just make them better, more better, more better at level 12. We can go down
to skeleton mage at level six. We can do clay gone more better poison and bone. What is available is
bone armor, which is just a shield of bone that absorbs and shit. It's pretty good. It absorbs 20
damage. As you see, I have 59 health, which that's pretty great actually teeth, which I can explain
as just, it goes around, around, around, around, around, around. That's all. That's seriously what
it is. There's no other way for me to describe this. Uh, it's just a damaging spell. It shoots
little, uh, little goo balls out curses. Uh, necromancer can cast curses on people that do
various things like for instance, uh, amplify damage increases the, uh, physical damage that
they take. They take a hundred percent more damage from all physical attacks. Number 20 points can
go into all of these. The reason why I'm doing this is because you see the screenshots we have
and I have to remember, uh, we'll go over it before we do it, obviously, but for instance, curses,
like that's what we have available, but it's going to be grayed out, but you see the path,
right? All right. So with that knowledge and knowing what we can do, we'll do another,
we'll do one more. Here we go. It's, it's race. It was race. Okay. Now we have another,
we have another point. Where's it going? It's not like a category. You got to pick a category for
all right. Okay. Does it count if you pick the category and then you pick the skeletons?
You're already just going to skeleton. It's already been decided. Like I can't even,
it's just going to the skeleton. It's supposed to be category first and that's just not it. All
right. Okay. We're making a huge minus two joke. I'm not me. Uh, by the way, we still only have
four skeletons, three skeletons, six stats, five points. Why am I so boring? What? Whatever.
Whatever you say. All right. We're going vitality. Thanks for vitality. Appreciate it.
Thanks for the vitality. Stupid chat. It's stupid over what the stats do. I will.
That's not a bad idea. Strength is just melee damage and able to wear heavy armor. You can wear
heavier shit. Dexterity is attack rating, which is how often you will hit something and your
defense rating. So, I mean, kind of useless for a necromancer. Vitality is health and stamina.
Stamina becomes absolutely useless. It doesn't matter anymore after like 50 points
and energy is mana. So this is health and mana. Kill NPCs. Stop going around like slashing.
All right. Let's keep going. I need to do this. Let's sell some stuff. Kill NPCs. All right. I
got to let's identify this brain. It's pretty pogchamp right there. Pretty cool. I can't use
this. This is a sorceress only. I need to get a book too. What do I have? 90? Oh, I'm not going
to use a bow. I got to, I have to identify, I got to identify this shit. You can reset your skills
once per difficulty, right? Is that correct? I don't have enough. Was it 360? What?
What? 350 or 360? 360. I want to identify this because it'll be worth more.
How the fuck do I not have to bring your 60? All right. There we go. Now I can sell this for 840.
You have to identify every single magic item. Now we got money. Town portal scrolls. This book allows
you to travel back and forth from town. It's pretty useful. It's pretty good shit. Don't get
the identified book. Kane does it for free. Well, I needed, Kane's not here yet. Not in town.
I'm doing this with money. All right. We're looking good. Intend you. Let's do players,
players six. I'm going hard. Yeah, we don't have Kane yet. We get Kane later.
All right. So the next quest after completing this, which will be completed, we have one here.
Everybody skipped this. I know you're here to challenge the evil that's driven us from our
ancestral house. My rogue scouts have just reported an abomination in the monastery graveyard.
Apparently, you support Satan and worship him on screen. Blood Raven, one of our finest captains
in the battle against Diablo at Tristram. Here comes 30 minutes slow mode. Now you'll find her
in the monastery graveyard, raising our dead as zombies. We gotta go get Blood Raven.
Defilement. 30 minutes slow mode. You want another reason to leave
at a player when you add a skeleton. All right. So we're going to go out.
How far? How close was the dinner people? I think it was pretty far away.
30 minute bone mode. I can't have four skeletons. You guys need to read up on the lore. Look,
it's fun. I can't believe there's five points in Ray's skeleton right now. Okay. The next point
in Ray's skeleton, we'll get a fourth skeleton and they're just going to die because they're weak.
They're fucking worthless. He hates them. Skeletons are cool. That can be pretty cool. All right. So
how far away were we? Where I get it? Let's get a good indicator. So we got to go to the coal
plains with the Blood Raven in the burial grounds next to the coal plains. In the world of Diablo
two, every single thing is connected to itself. So a lot more is connected to the coal plains,
which is connected to the stony field, which is connected to the passage to go to the dark wood,
which is connected. Everything is in a row and everything is sort of, kind of, sort of randomly
generated. Beware. The evil is strong ahead. It's like seven different patterns. All right.
We got a waypoint. First waypoint of the game. I can't believe it's taking an hour to do this.
Fuck. God damn it. Hey, stamina shrine. That means I can run forever. All right. How many
plays are it? Okay. Be careful. I have a hard time. This might be too hard.
Oh, chip emerald. Armor plus three dexterity. Okay. Let's go drop it. It's a bad item.
I'm just going to use it. Bad. They're taking too long. I have to drop the difficulty.
Name the skeletons. I can't. The gloves just go on automatically. They just get
reanimated anyway. Well, I mean, look at the EXP bar.
All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I got to drop it. Four of us are whacking on the same guy.
I'll take it to player support.
I can do one more skeleton. That's a skill shrine, by the way.
All right. We're moving to burial ground. I have to be careful. I really do have to take
this slow because you can't just die in a second, but we're going to go find it.
All right. Don't just run. Don't fucking run. Oh, that's bad. That's unsafe.
I hate skeletons. There's one inside of you. That's actually fine.
Okay. I have five skeletons. Don't I count? Technically. Burial grounds. What do you think?
Dense and legless pill. Why do you guys keep showing that?
That's good. It's very, very good.
Burial grounds. Stony field. God damn it. No, that's wrong. We don't want to go this way yet.
I'm sure he said worse. I don't have. I said worse.
I'm not even sure why that would be the worst thing I've ever said in my whole life.
Okay. This is stupid. I'll just run up. All right. Okay. This is bad. Very bad. Very bad.
Very bad. I have no stamina. Do I have stamina potions? Okay. This is where it ends.
Is there a champion in there? Oh, my skeleton. Okay. This is a battle. I have to be very careful.
I'm going to level up from this.
Red orb, the health. Yes. Red orb is health and blue orb is mana.
This is the slowest way to play this game. This is the absolute slug way to play Diablo 2.
Just stand around and hit each other in the face with rocks. It would be more. All right. Here we
go. Necromancer gameplay. Here we go. You ready? Skill. Take a look at what we've got available.
Summoning. Poison and bone. Remember, we've got like, and this shield. Curses. That's available
up here. Amplify damage. Also, raised skeleton is available and so is skeleton mastery. Please,
if you could pick a category. Pick a category now. Is it going to end real quick? Okay. We're
already here. So what skill would you like? Remember, the one to the left is available.
Skeleton mastery is available. Holy shit. Really? Okay. Okay. Skeleton mastery is really bad.
I mean, yeah. Well, no, I mean, it could be. Now we make the bone boy strong.
Thank you for voting. We'll put that into skeleton mastery. Please choose where the five step.
Fucking God damn it. I showed the goddamn fucking mountains. I'm actually pissed about that. All
right. Where are we going? By the way, keep in mind, those are not what the points are right
now. That's just because Blizzard entertainment sucks and I can't capture the window. You know
what I've said that like three times now. Who cares? Vitality again. Oh, hypers. We like mountains.
We like mountains. Hype. So I can just click. Yeah. You've become part of the vote. We're
doing vitality. Thanks for voting for vitality. It's very useful. All right. Vitality. Bang, bang,
bang. We're not 30 vitality, which is okay. That's pretty good. We now 81 health. Skeleton mastery.
So our skeletons are going to have plus eight life plus two damage. Pretty good. Okay. Now they're
just stronger. We still only have three though. Actually, they are lost. Good decision. Nice job.
Okay.
I can't wait to do the equivalent for grinding for vials in Bloodborne.
When everybody dies and there's like 30 people on the screen and I have to go grind for skeletons
for fucking 15 minutes. That's going to be, that's going to be a lot of fun.
Wait, that's champion. Champion. Anybody with a net that has a name like that.
Of course, they're doing much better. You're doing all right.
All right. Come over here. Bite this thing. Is it like electricity? He's immune to fire.
All right. Gang up on it. Explode. Does this guy explode? I don't know. He might.
Okay. He does. Thank God I moved away.
Okay. That's going to kill me. I'm going to die from that. Guaranteed. I guarantee it.
Skeletons don't suck. I do. Fresh skeletons. Oh yeah. We had big money coming too like a few
times. We had 10 communities up some Super Bruce right now. Thank you, Bruce. We also had enough
5,000 bits from phylactery and AG Joe. Thank you both of you. Jesus. I fucking love skeletons.
Make sure we go over in detail those at the end of the stream.
Thank you guys. Seriously. I probably missed more too. I was too busy yelling at the ceiling.
All right. We need to find the barrel. We're going for a boss.
I'm still on single digit skeletons. What a rookie.
Not even possible to do what you're describing. All right. Is this better?
I lose a point in skeleton, but I'll be able to kill things. Two to four, three to six. I'm going
to lose. All right. I lose a point in the skeleton. No. Okay. Fine. For health. This thing's broken.
Fuck it. Let's put this to take that. I'm running out of room here. Four to nine throw damage.
Do I have her head on three? Same thing. All right. Let's go. Is this guy streaming Diablo?
Is this guy watching skeletons play Diablo 2 while he streams Diablo 2? All right. Careful.
He's a champion. They're harder.
Uh, yes, that is kind of what's happening.
This is one handed. No, I can't. I can't do well. All right. We've got to level up. We're not going
to use it yet. All right. We came from this was flabby over here. We came from this way, right?
Oh yeah. Looking for the burial grounds. Every single, they're all in the edges.
Essentially, if you follow the road on here, you see, you'll eventually find something to put a
face cam on a skeleton. This is a random dungeon. I don't want to go in there. In fact, let's just,
let's find this shit while I have the stamina potion. I can run forever as long as I over there.
I want to get swarmed by a bunch of fucking people. Dying here is bad. If I don't make it
through act one, then I got to think of some kind of punishment because that come on. I have to do
act one burial grounds. Got it. Okay. All right. If I do not, if I die before act one is over,
I will do a, I will do a mountain stream or like at least five minutes with like calm music in
the background. Who cares? That's what it was. What does that punishment? All right. Hold on.
Let me go back. Town portals work the same way they do in the other Diablo games.
Got to kill blood raven. Greetings. Let's sell all this shit. One, sell, sell, sell.
This is a, I need a belt. I can only hold four potions at a time. Do you have a belt? Who has
a belt I can buy? Why did I just fucking identify that? All right. Give me a couple of these.
All right. I need a belt. Otherwise I'm just going to hold on to these potions in my inventory.
Belt or strength mountain stream promise. Well, I have to beat act one. I sold the last one. What
am I stupid? A thousand dollars. All right. This is 200 bucks. So now I get another slot here, but
still have town portals pair. All right. I'm ready. All right. Let's take a look at what we
have available. I'm level. All right. So I just, I am level six. We have unlocked and we have
obviously raised skeleton, skeleton mastery. We also now have clay golem rates of golem from the
earth to fight at your side. It's just another little buddy. 60 attack, a hundred defense
with a hundred life, two to five damage and a 20% attack bonus. And it slows enemies just to give
you an indicator of what that means. So attack 95 and 95 and 50 health. And they do three to four
damage. There's a difference. We've also unlocked poison dagger. That's poison to your dagger attacks.
I don't have a dagger, but it will make me do a lot more damage. If need be. We have unlocked
that. We still have teeth. We've also unlocked another curse dim vision creates a group of
the curse is a group of monsters reducing their vision radius. I'm not, I have no comment on that
because that's, um, this, I am not going to give you a comment because I don't want to influence
anybody's opinion. So, uh, what category would you guys like to go to? Sure. Okay. Now in this
category, remember you have the top three are available. Clay golem, skeleton mastery and
skeletons. We're going back to somebody. Where here would you like to go? He's an influencer.
Okay. All right. We've got it. We've this, we've got, we've now we've got it. Now we've got it.
Now we've got some actual, you know, people actually have to think about this shit. Now
you're assembling the squad, more skeletons, goblins. Well, it's a golem, not a goblin.
Golem, not golem. What did I, I'm stupid. All right. Whoa. What just happened? Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What is going on? Okay. All right.
Something. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do it again. Something fucked up just happened there. Do it again. Something's fishy there.
What is happening? What are you, wait, why, why is this possible right now? There's no 10,000
people didn't click. One vote per viewer. Start click map. All right. Now we got it. Now it's
actually working. Somebody was cheating. Yeah. There were, there were some, this is
the, do it in mastery. Um, we'll do it. I don't know. Do it. Why would you click bought a Diablo
two stream? Cause you really want more skeletons on the screen. I don't know what the fuck to do
here because this is, I mean, technically, technically there's a winner. Okay. Three,
two, one. Thank you for voting. Please choose the stat points. Five are going in.
Now all of a sudden everybody wants strength, huh? Now magically, randomly people decide that
that's what they want. You did vitality twice. It's good. Okay. Attack raises skeletons. All
right. All right. All right. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Easy on those mountains for a second.
Follow and then worst possible thing you could fucking do. Would you like to see our new friend?
He's perfect. Okay. Keep going. Now we have to fight the boss. Everything looks good.
Everything looks good. It's not a skeleton. No, it's not, but I have town portals, right?
All right. It's time to get blood raven. Everybody good. Let's go. Too many empty graves.
You made it. This is a poop monster. No, it's a clay monster. It says it in the title of the
guy's stream. Here we go. Go. There she is. All right. I can actually die from this like very,
very, very easily. He's absorbing so much damage. He's just a skeleton with extra step.
Dude, we're just fine. This is fine. Good on my friends. Say that now. Nobody even died.
All right. Get in there. Let's go. It's around. It's around. Circle, circle, circle, circle,
surround. Get her. Come on. Get her. Don't let her get away. Get the dagger, please.
I'm going to be here for a while. Three, two, one. I can't use this, but it's pretty cool.
There's a dagger. Nice job, guys. You did a good job. Our first bearer of the game,
40 strength required. Don't take that as an opportunity. Don't take that as an opportunity.
Charms just have to be in your inventory and they get whatever is the bonus that's on it. So I
plus the root of strength. As long as it's in my inventory, I get it. 5% chance to cast level one
amplify damage on striking. More damage to demons. More attack rating, which means you hit
more often against demons. Fire damage and 4% life stolen per hit. Cool.
We also get a, we're doing the blood rating quest. We get a companion. Kyle. Kyle. Kyle's back.
Respect stranger and the allegiance of the rogues. I have placed several of my best warriors at your
disposal. Mod her. Uh, she needs a bow. It is clear that we are facing difficult to comprehend,
let alone combat. There is only one Haradrim Sage in the most arcane history and law who could
advise us. You must go to Tristram and find him. We know. All right. We've got to go through the
dark wood. There's a tree. This is where it gets a little, this is where the game actually gets a
little bit more difficult, especially when we go to Tristram. Uh, this is her inventory.
Give her something. Let's go get a bow. Good day. Even if it sucks, doesn't matter as long
you just have one. Uh, $177. Take it. And manna. Do I have anything that has a socket in it?
Let's just stash it for now. I'm not going to sell this. Hold on. Maybe I just should sell it.
This is just giving you guys incentives that are going to make me have 40 strength.
Control click on an item. What are you talking about? I can't use that. You can't use that.
Need to be level five to use this piece of shit. What? All right. Let's go, uh, get Deckard Cain.
The level two companion. Oh, that's the problem. That's a huge problem.
Good day. I have three portals. That should be enough. Everyone's good to go. Let's move.
So we need to go through our memory serves me correctly here. We got to go to stony field
and then through the underground passage, right? What are the underground passages of the dark
wood? Yeah. Turn your face came up and play ads. I don't think I'm going to do that. That
doesn't sound like something that I would want to do. I'm good so far. Let's move. Use this.
What level two piece of this? All right. You can use this. I'll put that to good use.
Every act has a different companion by the way. And we're not even going to care.
I have 50 companions anyways, or maybe not. What's this? Germacraft. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? Why did I, why did I need to see this? What's the point in me seeing?
It's me holding a diamond pickaxe.
All right. All of me. The real test is if I can, I kill and are you'll coming up here in a little
bit. I got excited for the club because I just kept seeing me using it as was this an armor
and manna. Yeah. I mean this shit. Look at that. Just go up like and fucking sick. Wait,
you can wear this. Can you? Yes, you can. I wasn't even dying. This is actually going pretty well.
And Dario poison is going to one shot your minions. Yes, that's true. This is going to,
it's actually going to be probably a fucking nightmare. It's going to be an absolute
nightmare. We shall see how this goes. With that too, can't you?
And you're safe now. Going good. Do not die to recognize you.
Okay. That's why I killed fucking Diablo with this shit.
I would need to go down and then up. That's what I wanted.
It gets past. Storm. What's it? Storm wing with demon or enchanted. All right. Just let my
friends die here. Skeleton's op like half of exile.
Oh, it depends on what you mean by that because the answer is no, but it could be yes.
Out game. Yeah. Why is it doing this?
Runs us so loud. I'm crying. Yeah. I don't know why it's doing that.
That music's fucking awesome in this game. All right, let's go. I'm going to make my
run for it here. This is, this is a little ballsy, but you know, okay.
That's too, a little too ballsy potentially.
Where's that at? Level two. I don't want level two though. I want the dark wood.
Oh, don't go that way. Don't be a fool. I know, I know, I know, I know. But if I have the
stamina potion though, if I have the stamina shrine, then just go for it.
You know, you can run faster than everybody else. Oh, his CD key is banned. Yeah, I know. That's
what I'm saying. Why? I didn't do anything. That could have been real bad. Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run. Keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Holy shit. Okay. This is bad. This is very fucking bad. I, I, this is a, why did I do this?
All right. Now I'm good. Holy shit. Help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help.
I can't die right now. I don't want to do a mountain stream for 10 minutes. Where's everybody?
Oh shit. That's it. Okay. All right. All right. Oh my God. I'm going to die.
Oh my God. People are dying. We're good. We're okay. We're okay. We've used homeward bone.
Everything's going to be just fine. Where's, where are my skeletons? All right. Just stay
over there for a second. Why am I already full? I gotta get out of this. Uh, it's probably right
up here. My boots are broken. That's too ballsy. Stop. Part of me is actually kind of glad this is
happening like this because otherwise this would be, it would be, I'd be all alone in here.
I don't want that. Good, good, good, good, good. Good work. Although this is dead end.
Don't die. I'm almost out of stamina. Oh, this is a bad idea. Oh, this is a bad idea. What am I
doing? What do I do? I gotta slow down, slow down, slow down, top order. Get out, get out, get out,
get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out,
get out of the game. Get out, get out. I need health, health, health right now. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay. I almost just died. That was actually, yeah. Cause if that's it, if I'm dead, I can't really
seriously have to be careful. No, leave, like actually leave over here. Okay. What is it on
player count? Like six. I should probably turn that off and help. Is that it's on four or I'm
gonna set it to three. I got body blocked by everybody standing around that. I got bothered
like my own, my own friends. All right, let's pick something. 2000 playthroughs and he has to
play on three. I didn't make any of these decisions. This 30 points in strength right now as a necro.
Do you want to stay like that? What do you want me to do about that? That's what I'm saying. When
people come to this dream and they see like, Oh, Diablo two sick. Wow. There's people watching
this. I love Diablo two. What's this idiot doing? Somebody help him. Please help him.
All right. What are we doing for, uh, you know what to do? Well, actually take a look where here's
what we have raised skeleton, like golem. You can do another point in the clay. Golem will increase
the health and everything, make them better. Poison and bone. Same ones are available. Poison, dagger,
teeth, bone armor. This is survivability. This is me actually being able to do anything else
besides stand around and hit with a stick. And we also have dim vision and amplify damage.
Seeing what they do. Okay. Here we go. Where are we going? I'm going to keep quiet.
I don't want to influence anything. Why does this keep happening? And again, all right,
I have the check box set for only allow one click per user. But if I reset the poll, I have to do
that. Okay. Here we go. Here it is again. You need an updated screenshot. I might as well just open
up like a webpage and just show it on there. I'm closing it in 10 seconds. Poison and bone it is.
Okay. Uh, remember I'll show you again what we have available here. Teeth, bone armor, poison,
dagger. That is what's currently available right now. God damn it. Whatever. All right. What do you
want? It's up to you. Nice background. Whatever. Hey, uh, Jeremiah, I don't mean to backseat,
but this is not a good build. Really? Damn. I, I thought this was going to be really good.
I thought I was going to be able to get the first boss. All right. Let's do teeth. Good choice.
Not really. Cause I have no mana. How the hell am I going to cast this? Uh, two teeth come out.
It does two to four damage now. Here we go. Here are my current stats right now.
Just to make sure you guys see that what the image you're going to see is a little outdated.
Okay. Take a step using the F keys. You have to. All right. All right. Not bad decisions so far.
Not bad. Could be way worse. Energy sucks. All right. All right. Five points of going
in energy. Let's go. Thanks everybody. We repair and okay. So this is a day. This is a very dangerous
portal, right? This is that this portal will kill me. I have to be careful. I'm going to make a
portal immediately when going through this portal and you're going to, we're going to do something
to cast teeth at people. Let's do it. Three, two, one, go.
Dude fog. What's the level up again? Wait, why am I going to, why am I leveling up so fast?
Wait, what? What's happened? How did I level up so fast? Cheating? Am I? I don't think so.
Are we doing skeleton doll life? This is how you got banned. I was so pissed off when I saw that.
Oh, and I can't even get another CD key. That's the worst part. I have to buy the game and send
it to somebody else. But then they have to open it and give me their CD key. Make a new account.
Yeah. I would have to make a brand new account on battle net to buy Diablo two again. This is
going really well. I'm going to make a prediction. I'm going to beat and Ariel is the first major
boss of the game. By the way, we're going to get a first unique in the game. You should be excited
about that. It's going to be very hectic. I'm going to be very scared. It's okay because I'll
have a couple of friends, large acts, 35 strength. Can use it. I do more damage just by swinging
because I have so much strength. Okay. So this is, this is why this is so dumb. So you pick teeth,
which is fine, but I do more damage by swinging because I have 30 strength.
Okay. So I may as well put on that two handed weapon. You know what I mean? At this point,
it's sort of a lost cause. We're going to have multiple points. Your hit rate is 10%.
That's yeah, that's right. All right. Dark wood. Here we are.
Uh, get this out of here. I don't want this. Now we're looking for the tree.
Get away from me. Somebody with electricity in it. Somebody with electricity. Electricity,
the worst thing in the whole game. Who has electricity? Who has electricity on them?
I don't see anybody in there with electricity, but why did that come up? Who has it? Yep.
There's somebody in there that has it. I see them. Oh my God. Okay. Run. One skeleton. That's not
good. We're good. We're good. Don't get hit by the lightning. I got to kill. This is shaman
somewhere. There you are. It's too stressful. Why did I want to do this? This is too stressful.
It really is. Especially when you get a little bit later here.
I have to kill the guys with the staff. Help me skeleton. All right. He's one dead.
Where's my golem? All right. My golem is he's doing a good job. He's currently surrounded.
What? Where? Okay. Where's another shaman dead? There you are. Oh, you motherfuckers. This is
ridiculous. Oh my God. This is a mess. This is an actual mess. I have to leave and level up again,
I think. Yep. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. No. What? Yeah. Actually
put a safe teleporter down here. Okay. Do I have any money? Get rid of this. No saw. Wait.
22 attack rating. Should just put it in. Who cares? All right. I need load up potions.
How many do I have? I get some more. Okay. What level are we now? We are level eight. We have
opened up a couple of new things because you put a point to teeth. One point is in teeth right now.
It just increases the amount of teeth and the amount of damage. Armor as well. There's corpse
explosion. Cast on the corpse of a slain monster. It explodes damaging nearby enemy.
Okay. Pretty good. Poison dagger. That's what's available in poison and bone. We have still the
same curses available. Amplify and envision and we still have the same summoning ability.
Do not get new ones until level 12. Roll over so you can see what would happen if I put a
point into these. Okay. All right. So you've seen it. Please choose a category if you would.
He thinks anyone cares. That's kind of the point of the stream is to have people pick something
crazy for a hardcore. He thinks anyone cares. Oh, don't be so mean. Why are you being so mean?
Kind of torn, but it looks like summoning. Okay. Good. Oh, we're still in summoning. So
you only have three choices here. Two into play golem. Another one into, you only have three
options. Go ahead and pick one. Well, that's a hundred percent. This will make four skeletons.
He's going to start crying. Well, that's, there's no coming back from this 76% one another skeleton.
This will be a level of six points into skeleton, which will get us to four skeletons. There's now
time to choose some. Well, I'll show you here. Here's where the stats currently stand. 30, 25,
30, 30, 30, 25, 30, 30. Those are where the stats are right now.
Where am I going? Yeah. I've never done anything like this before in this game. So this is kind
of an interesting, I mean, I guess I can hit things harder. Does that, well, I'll be able to
wear some really, really heavy armor. Thanks for voting everybody. That'll bring us to
to 35 strength. Can I, uh, one, look at, okay. One to 27 damage. That is so terrible.
All right. Let's bring, let's resurrect Kyle. All right. We need to, how many, how many,
what do I have for, all right. I only, let me get some more portals. I only have one.
Okay. I feel safe now. Fresh. I can get four skeletons. Can I resurrect anybody here? No.
All right. Let's go. Three, two, one. Let's go. Fuck. Oh my God. Don't do it. The champion's
almost dead. Get in there. What are you doing? Get in there. He's just standing around. Get in
the fight. She's still alive. First she's in here somewhere. She dead. I don't know. Just kill the
doctors. Yeah. She's right there. The blue one. Oh, okay. I can't even walk over there.
Don't please kill her. Kill demon lightning enchantment. The worst die. I leveled up again.
Nice. Good work. It is hard leather armor here. God damn it. I didn't mean to do that. 15 to
strength. What's it got? 21 defense. I'd rather have that than the health. You see what, okay.
Go ahead. If I put on the huge ax, I lose a skeleton. That's true.
Keep that in mind. Do bugleberry right now or riot. I'm not going to do that. Okay. You do have
another point to put in. Let's go ahead and do this first. I mean, if you look, if you're going to
make me do this, then I have, look at two to five, two to 40. That's it. This is good, but I lost a
skeleton. Here's what's available. The same ones from last time. Obviously corpse explosion, teeth,
bone armor, skeleton, which we lost it because we had plus one from the wand and also one and one
in skeleton mastery and in clay foam. Please choose the category if you would. I appreciate it.
We lost a friend. Bring back friend. Yeah. Use that skill point and compensate.
I'm actually going to be pretty useful though. Okay. Well, what do you want to up? You have,
you could, you could do skeleton mastery, clay golem, or replace the skeleton that we just
lost. Remember you're going to get clapped in the dirt before end areal. I don't think so. Okay.
Four skeletons. This is what they currently have for a bonus. We are level nine. Let's go.
How slow is this? It's pretty slow, but I feel like it's going to be kind of good.
Oh, look at the tree. It's too many people. I'm one hit killing everything though.
So it's not terrible. He's not picking up the gold. I'm trying to stay alive.
Actually not that bad. Swole man, sir. Oh, she leveled up. Grand charm. Give me
running around with a two handed sword as an answer.
All right. Let's do one. We need to find the, uh, the tree. And when I find the tree,
it's instantly run away from the tree because it's, you're guaranteed to die. If you do not
run instantly away from the tree, the tree is scary. Yes, it is hard. No, I don't want it.
Tree fist is going to kill them. Don't say that because it's potentially accurate.
It's so scary when you find the tree because they just sprint at you. All right. That's good.
Six to life. What do I have right now? Is it strength? No, keep the strength on.
Trying to pay attention to him. He's still, he was like a week ago, but he's still recovering.
Show us that. I don't see at least a thousand cog champs right now. I will turn the stream off.
I'm going to count. Hey, good. Nice work. I knew you guys could do it.
Ooh, they're terrible. 10% fast, one to dexterity, cold. At least it's cold resistant.
Better than what I had on. I have six cold resist. Holy fuck. That's a lot of pogs.
All right. Give me the gold. People are yelling at me, but I'll pick it up the gold. And yes,
I know. I agree. I need it. I'm going to put another, uh, I was on the, I just did another
hog. I don't know why. If Kyle stuff, no, I'm going to dump Kyle pretty soon here.
Large acts. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. What do I have? Um, this shit's
he hates Kyle. No, I don't level up. This actually might make and Ariel easier because I can
actually swing and I'm going to do damage. This might be, I'm not, I'm not scared at the moment.
I will be in a little bit though. Play point. Thank God. All right. Give me a second. It's all
part of the plan. Trust chat. Well, it's hard to do that. Right. I still have, uh, no sockets.
Right. When I get the cube, you can eventually combine these, but they're going to be worthless
in about 40 minutes. How many keys do I have? I have too many mana potions. Why do I even have
these? Absolutely useless. Dude, two minutes of gameplay, 10 minutes of leveling up. Yeah,
you know it. Let's go. All right. Well, we got this. We got you with same choices. Same choices
are available. We still have four skeletons, skeleton masteries available. Golem is available.
We still have corpse explosion, which is available. Bone armor, poison dagger is still curses
available. Here's what will happen if you put a point into this. Damage goes up by a little bit.
It also happens here. Increases life and damage of raised skeletons and revived creatures.
And then amplify damages is incredible, but it's not my choice. Okay. Go ahead and pick.
These will start slowing down as we level up though. Don't worry. As always, it looks like
we're going to skeleton. Are we? Or do I just assume the worst? Okay. Well, we're on the right
page. Uh, which one? All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Corpse explosion, resident sleeper, skeleton
population explosion, pog champ. It is going into skeleton mastery. Uh, what about stats?
Strength, dexterity, vitality, energy, which one?
Getting smarter. They're getting smarter. That's good. No, I'm not. Yes, you are. Don't downplay
yourself. You just pick the one you did is good. So we're doing skeleton mastery, which will go up
from life 8%. It's just doubling their life eventually damage. So now let's see what they
do with three to five damage and they have 60 health, six to seven damage, and they have 68
health. So now they're going to be pretty good, not terrible play. And then everything else looks
good. Let's go. Dude, pod three minutes to gameplay. Here it comes. Magic find is really good,
but I'll keep the strength on. Oh shit. Watch out. He's a chump. Let's kill him.
Best opportunity to get prayers and uniques is from named enemies. Right.
Dude, fucking residence sleeper gameplay. What is this shit? I want to see level it up.
Where's the tree? I think it's right over here. Damage shrine. Good. Very useful. Let's go. Don't
get overwhelmed. Three, three, three, three, three. Still no tree. This house is burning, but
free. I would take that skill shrine, but I don't want it because I wouldn't be able to run.
Where the hell is it? I got the waypoint. What's the over under on me? Screaming when tree
fist appears. Ah, it depends. How does the game lag and does he instantly teleport next to me?
Is that what happens? Probably this way. Depends on who sees who first. Yes, it does. All right.
Slow down. I need my skeleton. There he is. There he is. Okay. All right. There he is. There he is.
I didn't scream. I didn't scream. He's not even that bad. He's fine. I'm good. He walked right
into the okay. He just got destroyed. That wouldn't even scared. That was easy. There's the tree.
This tree shines with inner spirits. What did he drop? Anything good? I am overburdened.
Free defense. That sucks. And I'll keep that on you. You wear this.
There's a scroll. Look at all these potions I have. What a waste of space.
Waste of space. These are I'm going to sell some shit. All right. Now we're going to go to Stony
Field and go to Tristram and hopefully not lose. Hey, are you winning? Are you winning?
You must find the cairn stones and touch them in the order that I have written.
Yes, we do. Go to the cairn stones in the Stony Field. Touch the stones in the order of the scroll.
What was the thing everyone was saying? Will? Well, there was at least a few people that said
will he get past Rakaneshu. This is the real test, I think. Coming up right now. All right.
Let's get rid of some of this shit. Like get out of here. Put the magic find on instead. Sure.
Okay. Stash some of this shit. Do I keep this stuff on? Eh, it's fine. Okay. Now we have to
go to the Stony Field, which is further back. Pole Plane, Stony Field. I think I already did.
I found it. Didn't I already before? Yeah, it's right down here. Look at that. We're already
ready to go. Wrong. Did I do the Countess? I did not. I may skip the Countess and go right for
Endereal. I know that's a terrible idea, but sometimes you got to go for the hard play.
Look at the Stony Field. Oh, EXP Shrine. Kill. Come on. You get like triple the amount of
experience. How do I have no stamina? Doesn't make any sense. Kill something quick, please.
I gotta get back on the road. These Countess skip people equals skipping levels. Yeah. I mean,
the end of Act 1 is actually pretty hard. Is this Stony Field or is this Burial Grounds?
Is that Burial Grounds? It's Burial Grounds. All right. It's up there.
Oh, I got Stand Stills with my stupid ass stamina can refill. Why don't you stack stamina potions?
Because I forgot that we have 40 points in strength. I forgot. Go, go, go, go, go.
Tristram, pause the game. I have to go. There is no pause in Diablo. Yes, there is. What?
Oh, I'm not playing online, right? Yeah, there is. Pause the game. Not yet. We're not going to.
Our first break is coming soon. After I go through Tristram, we'll do our first break.
I'm in it for the long haul tonight, guys. I want to see just how far I can get
before reliably turning the stream off and being safe. Pause. What about my pizza roll?
You'll be OK. Look for the stones. You'll know when I find the stones when you see a blue guy.
We're looking for the blue guy. Give me that. I'd rather have that right now.
Who cares about the experience? I'll get it. Stones, stones. Found it. OK. OK. Run, run, run, run.
All right. Let's go. I'll leave it to Shirley. We'll take this out.
Any shamas over here? There he is. Go get him. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
Why is Teeth selected? Why is Teeth selected? Why is he chasing me? Nice. All right. Turn it on.
What about Griswold, though? He's scary. Good Tristram. 21, 21. Sucks. All right.
All that's left of proud Tristram are ghosts and ashes. We have four skeletons.
Let's go. Take it slow. There's no reason to do this fast. Holy shit. OK. We'll run.
He can do amplify damage to you. So I gotta be careful. Like that. No. Actually, I did that.
Oh, that's right. This thing has a 5% chance to amplify damage. For God's sake.
Die. Run. Run away. He didn't drop anything. He dropped shit. All right. We're good. Keep going.
Dammit, a potion. Get it. OK. This is where we get Wirt's leg.
My goal is to kill the shamas. That's all I'm going to do. OK. He's left. Right here. Champions.
There's Wirt. I do a lot of damage to this thing. It's actually kind of good. All right. Here we go.
Where's Wirt? Where is he? Right here. Two to eight. One to 27. I could. All right. I might
actually use this. I might just put like three gems in it. Go get Deckard Cain. He's in here,
surrounded by people. Help. Help. Deckard Cain. Move quickly. And that's barbarian. Wrong person.
Say the rest. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. We got two levels up.
Am I level 10? Level 12. Wow. We're moving right along. Level 12. Are you kidding me?
This is fucking easy. The game's not even fucking hard. All right. Let's get out. I got a lot of
damage. We made it. Here he is. Hello. As a token of my gratitude, I will identify items for you at
no charge. Regrettably, I could do nothing to. I could do nothing to prevent the disaster which
devastated Tristram. It would appear that our greatest fears have come to pass. Diablo,
the Lord of Terror, has once again been set loose upon the world. Our greatest fear has
come to pass. Chat has made an acromancer with 40 strength. As you know, some time ago, Diablo
was straining against Tristram. He might as well just go home. Let one of the adults take over.
Yet as the weeks passed, our hero became increasingly aloof.
He kept his distance from the rest of the townsfolk and. There's no way you can beat Diablo
with that shit, Bill. Perhaps his ordeal had been so disturbing that he simply could not put it out
of his mind. Okay, fine. Stay awhile and listen. Hey, I ate some food and you're still alive. Good
job. Yeah, we're doing fine. You have risked your life. Oh yeah, you get a ring doing this
and then it always just sucks. Nice magic damage reduced by one.
There's probably more nutritional value inside that ring from a box of lucky charms. You know
what I'm trying to say. All right, let's sell. Have we got what levels up to do? And then we're
going, we're going for it. We're going for our Dario. Fuck it. I'm going, we're going right for
it. This is where it gets hard. I have a keyboard's leg. Uh, it's time to gamble. He's getting too
confident. It's fine. Hey, good day to you. I'm good. I'd never have to lay my eyes on one of
your kind. You didn't even do it. Yes. A gambling is you don't know what it is, but it could be a
rare. I have $5,000. What do I need to replace? Uh, this is this shit. You can give me something
better than this belt. Should I try to get a better belt? I still have gloves. These gloves
are so bad gloves. All right. That was bad. Heavy armor. Yeah. I can wear it. Can I,
I think I can wear it. Sword. I go for sword or club rings. The rings are 63,000 Goldie
new armor. Yeah. Let's, let's see if we can get some armor. All right. Chain mail 18,000.
All right. Here we go. I don't have enough money. This shit just drops on the ground.
Does he hate the music that I should be turned off? Oh, I want this. All right. That's better.
Now I'll have more slots. Seven life, three mana. Let's go. See that was worth it. All right. I'm
done. I'm done, done, done, done, done, done. Put this shit in here. My favorite part about this
game is organizing gems. It's just somehow satisfying to me. I've got potions. I need
another row. Yeah. I'm going to just buy like two or three. Wait, I'm just, I'm buying back the ones
I sold. What the fuck is going on? All right. So we have 10 stat points to put in. Where do you
want me to put 10 stat points? We're doing well. 10 points. Where do you want them? Take a look.
Is that what it looks like? Mountains? Any mountains? Hey Otto, what are you doing over there?
Any mountain fans in here? All right. 10 points are going to strength. I'm going to be the heaviest
acrobat ever. Okay. What about, we have two points. Let's take a look at what we have
and some new stuff though. So check it out. First, let's do this. That was painful to do.
So we have a couple of new things here. Again, we have, here's what happens with Ray's skeleton.
We have skeleton mastery still. We do not get a fifth skeleton. Play Golem. We've Golem mastery
has unlocked. Enhances speed and life of your Golems. More health and more attack and they
walk faster. Or skeleton mage. Just like regular skeleton, it revives a, this adds to your skeleton
pool and it's a mage, not melee. It shoots ice, fire, lightning, et cetera. They're a lot weaker,
but they still get skeleton mastery. Still get a bonus from this.
You can't do anything here because no one's picking anything here. This all remains the same.
Poison Dagger, teeth, bone armor is the same. Curses has not been clicked on once, so we can't
go further down. But if you did, this weaken, which makes everybody that you touch with this do 33%
less damage. It's Iron Maiden, which when they do damage, it hurts themselves. It's a thorns.
So they do 200% damage returned back at them. Terror just makes people run away.
Nobody wants to do curses, apparently. So, and now that you see these, you know what they do.
Where would you like to go? This is for the first point, by the way. Please pick the category.
People are already clicking it. Hey, hey you. Hey you little, hey you little dork.
All right. Okay. We're on skeletons. We're on summoning spells already and that's where you
want to go. Which one? Skeleton mage is. So that's the first point. Where would you like the second
point? What a category. Or we just do it again. I guess we already know. I guess we already know.
Hey dude, great necro build. This actually is not even that different than just making a
summoning build anyway, so not too big of a problem. Okay. We're doing another point into
skeleton mage. See, a lot of you guys think you're doing some crazy weird impossible build,
but you're just going to make it hard for me to beat bosses, and then I have to figure it out on
my own. So we've got skeletal mage. One. Skeletal. Uh oh. We have to be level 13 for this one. Uh oh.
Pick something else. Now you could save points too. You don't have to spend them until you figure
out what you want to do. You don't have to spend them right now. We can do curses. Okay.
Don't influence us. I'm just saying, you don't have to spend your points until maybe you figure
out what you want to do. You don't have to spend every point. All right. So just to refresh your
memory because this is an inaccurate list. Very currently available curses. Invision and amplify
damage. Everything takes a hundred percent more damage or make them so they can't see very well.
Any mountain fans in the area? Curses equal lame. Well, it depends how you use them.
This actually will be very, very good. Okay. Good choice. And I mean that, actually, I don't mean
that as a joke. That's actually a really good thing to have with summoning build. Put on the bar. I've
got a couple things to put on the bar. So we're going to do F1, F3, F4. Okay. We have a skeletal
mage. Now we can summon, which is a different button. I'm also going to go P. So let's take
a quick little break for the first time. I'll be right back and we'll continue.
Okay. Sorry about that. Take care of Otto. Make sure he was doing okay.
All right. We've selected everything, right? I'm going to keep an eye on him. He's my special boy.
All right. All right. What was on tap here? I don't remember.
I'm Dario. Greetings. When I fled the monastery, my enchanted smithing hammer. If you can retrieve
it for me, I'll use its magic to strengthen your equipment. Okay. So it's so odd seeing this as a
fucking necromancer. Oh, we did that one. We could do this, but nah, we don't need it.
This is on the way. Idiot streamer sucks at Diablo. We got to get...
I need... Okay. We got to go from here to here. It's going to be quite a journey.
Do all quests with an angry face. We don't need... I'll go back and do them.
I'm looking for the... What is it called? The black marsh? That's the one. Oh, a ring.
Yeah. Light radius and attack rating. That's good. Why are there so many skeletons? Well, because
chat wants to have chat on screen.
There's going to be a bunch of them. Somebody redeemed a wing.
Hey, no, they didn't. Not right now. Did they? Did they? Oh, it was fucking fake. God damn it.
I need to... I need a way to track that on my own screen. Seriously.
I have to... I guess I gotta track that. Otherwise people will just keep doing that forever.
All right. With me, with me, with me, with me, with me. Black marsh. We're making a run for it.
Read the chat. But when there's 5,000 people in the chat room.
Somebody redeems a wink and one second goes by. It might be off the screen. I need a way to keep
track of it. Oh, look, there's another one. Oh, really? No way. Come on, run on the edge.
No, there was no real wink. I would have saw it. It'll show up on my dashboard. Is that for real?
Where? Reward requests? Is that it? Okay. Reward request is currently on. I don't see anything.
Don't ever alt tab during a hardcore game. Seriously, I'm gonna... I wonder if he's gonna
die to Andariel. No, no, no. I'm gonna alt tab and die to a one random person hitting me.
All right. It's up there. I didn't bring very many of these. I only got one.
I'm gonna go buy more of those. I'm gonna spend like all my money on it. Great. At least I have
an army protecting me. Yeah, that's true. But if I go too far ahead of the army and they don't
teleport quick enough, I'm gonna die. I have to go Black Marsh, right? Yes. Now, you really should
get the waypoint, but the only waypoint that matters is Catacombs level two. But this is
hardcore and you can't just die. So I'm gonna just hold on. I'm gonna relax for a second.
Ooh, that's pretty good. Lightning and Poison Resist. Block rate, 35% chance to block. Oh,
I can't really use it. When's the Paladin Scepter? I gotta use that. Wait, that's a Necromancer only
item. No plus to skills, so it's absolutely worthless. I keep going. Is that a waypoint?
Oh, you leveled up. Remember, there's a bug on your camera. Oh, oh, fucking ew.
Hey, look, the waypoint. All right, outer cloister. I think it's over. Kill the bug, kill the bug,
kill the bug. No, this bug's gonna live. You guys ever do that? You guys ever have a bug in your
house? Like a spider or something? And it's in a spot where, you know, it's probably not gonna
bother you. And you just go, all right, man, you can stay, you get to live. You stay there.
You can just hang out up there, but don't do any encroachment. The further you come out with that
web, the more chance there is that I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking get rid of it. All right, that's
this is the lightning lightning lightning lightning. Careful. Oh, fucking people are dying.
I'm so, oh, that's good. That's really good. Come on, plus the skills, plus the skills,
plus two to corpse explosion, plus one to weaken. All right, but I lose my actual damage. Hold on,
I'll look at that later. We're gonna get into the scales. I'm gonna kill people around you.
Why am I doing such a little damage to you? All right, speaking of damage, I gotta be doing
that way more often. Amplified damage, two to forty damage is a hell of a range. Yeah, and it is.
It is. Portal shrine, great portal. I'll take it.
But range damage really can kill you without, I guess, look at everybody with my true friend.
Love the bone squad we got going on right now. The ever increasing, what I got, six people.
I do feel a lot safer having six friends. Yeah, I can't play it online, but I can play with my
pretend friends here. All right, monastery gate. This place has the stale demons about it.
Sucks. I can't carry anymore. Oh, wait. All right, give her this.
Talk it. Who cares about the man? This dude's been playing since the beta. Yeah, dude.
This shit actually does get dangerous in here. This is like one of the first parts of the game
that you can actually get truly, truly, truly. A lot of tiny little corridors,
a lot of random people that just run through. Let's just stay alive. That's all it's about.
I do have to keep reminding myself that this is hardcore. Can't just have to be careful.
Okay, there's a demon up there. We still got all of our friends, right? Yep. All right. Move.
Move up. Move up. Let's move. Move. Move up. Is this being revived by?
Where is he? All right. I just was going to say, oh, thank God I got that in case I die.
That's not how this works. Easy. Hold up. We're going to hold off on leveling up for a minute.
I want to keep getting in. Hey, just in case I die, I'll be able to run back.
No, you won't, because that's where the game ends.
The butcher, too, might kill me. No, I have to get through three sacks.
Otherwise, what the hell? Lost my mage.
When are you going to do Sea Man 2? Is this Sea Man 2? Wait, isn't that one Japanese only?
And then only come out in Japan? Play it out. There's no English version of it.
You know where I really think I'm going to have a huge problem? The Arcane Sanctuary.
That's the worst place in the whole game. If you don't play the Arcane Sanctuary with at least
four people, life sucks. Okay, easy. The barracks. I'm just running around sniping the Shaman.
What? What the fuck? How did I take that much damage?
You weren't here earlier. My account is fucking damaged. I want them to go in first.
I hate these little doors. Back up, back up, back up, back up. This is the worst,
because you can just open a door and get hit three times and die. Are we good? 22 gold, 23 gold.
Looking for the jail level one. Okay, back up.
All right. Yeah, I'm starting to get a little clenched. Just a little. All it takes is one
person. We got some, that's a lot of money. Hold on a second. I got to do something about this.
What about one guy? A lot of potions left. Sell the miners. This is such a weird build.
I have way more potions than I need. Why are all these rejuvenation potions dropping?
I don't remember this being a thing. It feels weird and new. Why are there so many rejuvenation
potions? This over here. I'm going to store this. Use them for the cube. That is right. All right,
what we got for skill points here? We've unlocked Iron Maiden. I'm just saying. We've unlocked it.
Here are the, we have summoning spells. We still have the same amount.
And then here's the poison bone. One point in teeth. Don't worry, it's not useless or anything.
All right, where are we going? He's got one tooth. It's like we're staying in the summoning tree.
Everyone's got one good can opening tooth. All right, well, what are we doing in here?
And by the way, if you put another point into golem, it does not give you two golems.
It just makes your one golem much better. I want to make sure everyone's aware of that.
Germa one golem. Second skeletal mage. It's golem. I know, but ever since I was like 15
playing this game, I just, I say golem. I know. All right, that's the thanks for voting. That's,
there's no way anything's coming back from that. And what about stats? Is it bogus voting or am I
unable to vote because of mobile? I don't think extensions work on mobile. I think that's probably
what's going on. Some do. Yeah. Vitality. Still no points in decks, but that's a,
actually that's, that's probably going to be a bad thing. It is this many points in strength already.
Vitality. Thanks for voting. With this many points. Yeah. All right, we're going to get a
second skeleton mage. Cool. And what was it? Vitality, right? Yeah. 26 dexterity.
All right. Five points. If I was a barbarian or something or no, this is a terrible build,
whoever you are. Okay. Make sure I've got everybody. One, two, three, four. So I got seven
companions. So it's going to start to get messy very quickly. It's almost broken. All right.
Yell up on the mini map. You see a, okay, something's in here. The only way to play hardcore
the guy who watches. Ooh, skullcap. All of them's in there. Everyone's alive still. So this is okay.
I want to check that skullcap. Everyone's still alive. We're fine. Let's take a look.
Better six to energy. That's pretty useful. And lightning resist. Yeah. Put it on. It's better.
Straight up. All right. Stay with me. What level am I? I'm 13. Potentially a little underleveled
for what is happening in the next section here. But, you know, sometimes you got to go for it.
I know you're 13. Yeah. You have to grind. I haven't had too much of a problem yet.
Once, if this starts to become a problem, this is still on player's set of four.
Yeah, it's at least three or four. If this becomes a problem, then I will grind.
Is that a ring? Almost. It's playing hardcore and Diablo foolish if you've never played it before.
Uh, yes. It's so easy to accidentally die in these games by just some random explosion
or some random champion enemy that's going to be once you die.
Okay. Speaking of kind of an insane room, uh, people are dying.
People are getting cream. What is, what is cream and everybody? Oh my God. People are dead.
Get up here. Up, up, up, back out, back up, back up. Golem's dead. No, it's not the Smith.
Okay. I'm sorry. I just get this shit at everybody. That was a mistake.
I forgot that what that did. There's something in here. What is in here? That's causing so much
damage. They're all down the corner. Oh, this is, oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God.
This is where it ends. This is where it ends. All right. Maybe it's time to grind. There's like five
champions down there in the corner. I can't see everybody. Okay. Okay. This is bad. This is bad.
Let them come to us. All right. Just, all right, Larry, it's just me and you. I got to move. We
have to leave. I got to get out. Okay. Now we have to do the fun thing called be a necromancer. Uh,
we're going to go out to the blood more and we're going to get a full party again.
That's a wink. There is no wink. No, there's no, I, I can look, I can see it now. Yes, there is. No,
there isn't. I'm looking right now. It was a scam. I like identifying on the fly. Even it's a waste
of money. I know. Okay. All right. Let's, uh, get some new friends. Oh, gamble. I might in a second
and repair. Yep. Refilling shrine. Just do it. That almost was very bad.
Just give me some, I need to just build my army back up before I go back in the door for them to
instantly die. Is that seriously the only body that's around here? How can that be the only body?
There's going to be a German wink market correction soon. Probably. All right. Den of evil. I was in
there already. We just do two more things. Come on. Manor recharge station. Yeah, there's that. We
have our Golem and now we have, see one more of these. In fact, I used them. That's all right.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. Everything's fine. I almost had a panic attack. In fact,
this is better because then I can, I can, yeah, this is fine. I didn't repair. I will, I will,
I will. After I get through these dickheads up here, we got to go slow and I got to run in the
room. No, we have to have the, the Golem has to go in the room first. I ain't going in there first.
Where is it? The shithouse has to go in there first. There they are. All right. Get them. Get in.
Everybody in. Everybody get in. Kill. Holy fuck. There's still a lot of people in there.
We good? Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. Kill this guy. Good. Overwhelm them. Overwhelm.
Golem's doing a good job. Nice. Everyone's fine. All right. Kill him. He's pounding him right.
All right. Nice job. That was almost a disaster. Almost a disaster. A second time.
What have we got? Almost level up. Everyone's okay. We continue. Found it. Yeah. Level one.
Safe. The slow torture of caged starvation. Okay. I'm going to, where's, uh, is that really in such
a stupid place that I can't click on it? Did I really do that to myself? The order welcomes you.
I'm going to go gamble too. I'm not going to repair. It's a lot of money.
Try to get some heavy armor. Well, this chain gloves, which are probably better than what I
have. How much? It's too expensive. Couldn't be much worse. I'm all right. It's not terrible.
I have more defense now. Does he know that it's not pronounced? It's pronounced dual. It's not dual
weld. Yeah. I know it's wield. Dual wield. Dual weld is easier for me to say. Dual welding. Dual
welding. Dual welding. Dual wielding. All right. We're just going to level up. I think that's good.
Let's go back in. I'm prepared. Dual weld. Golem. Bad. All right. Place your bets actually.
I want to know real opinions. Do you guys think I'm going to beat Andariel?
Do you think I'm going to? How do we figure this out? How do we do like an actual
figure this out test? Heavy gloves. There it is.
Are you okay? Like, hold on. I'll actually have to pause again.
I'm going to help him. He needs like a blanket. Hold on. He has this, uh,
you got a cone. We got him one of the soft cones, you know, things so he doesn't get his stitches.
So, but he can kind of get stuck. Then when the, when the cone, because it's a soft cone,
it can press down and he's like, eh, I need to help him sometimes. That was a real wink.
It really was. That was actually, okay. That actual, yeah, you're right. It did. You're right.
Here. Thanks a lot. The prophecy has been fulfilled. How are we doing? Dude, fucking,
I can't wait to kill Andariel first try.
Losing. Stay back. Too bad that's not a weapon. It's Paladin only. So I guess I could save it.
Hold on. Six. So many potions. Do they like up the amount of potions you can have?
I swear to God, the last time I played this, there wasn't this many potions available.
Don't keep picking those. Bring jail level two. All right. Easy. Easy. Easy.
Skill shrine. I might be able to get more skeletons with that. Six, four and a third. Yeah. A third.
Okay. Almost at the inner cloister. Almost at a major boss of the game.
Close there. There are so many potions because the game is trying to drop enough of the three
players you have. You're a hacker. I guess that's true. Get antidote potions. I know. I know. I've
played the video game. I know Andariel's got poisoned and you have to be careful
because it'll kill you. That's gonna be I'm gonna be so terrified.
You guys want to know something about this? Here's a true story. I have never once and I truly mean
ever over the course of thousands and thousands and thousands of hours across Diablo one through
Diablo three. Thousands. Thousands of hours. I've never played one single character on hardcore.
This is the first time you're ever going to see this. Never taken a shower. I have never ever
taken a shower. Hardcore to me was always too stressful because there's so many ways to die
in these games that especially when you get onto a higher difficulty like nightmare of hell,
you can die in one one hit just from something across the room. I hated it. I hated taking showers.
What level am I? 14? Not bad. You guys going first. Thank god you guys selected amplify damage.
Come on. Get in there. Get in there. Let's go. What the hell are you doing? Dude 14? What? Are
you serious? Yeah. I'm dead. Am I wearing a bathing suit? Why would I be wearing a bathing suit?
Will somebody kill somebody over here, please? I can't even see who's over here. This thing's
gonna explode. I think these explode, right? Do eight players or riot? No, I'm on four right now.
Do you have level two? Come on. No, it's not over there. It's down here.
Here's 99. I mean, if I do players eight, I'll level up faster, but
it's too dangerous. That's way too dangerous. Level two. This game is 20 fucking years old.
Very old. I'm gonna get dangerous. No, no, I can't let it end like that. I'm gonna put it on eight
players and die. And then I'm gonna sit there and go, why did I? What's the point of that?
What? To make myself look cool? Attack rating 15 to 10. Yeah, that's better. Poison resist.
I need poison resist. The good thing about this is about this hardcore run. If this character dies,
you're not going to care about losing them. Yeah, that's that's pretty good way to put it.
That's not that's not a bad way to look at it. Don't put eight until after and aerial. Yeah.
Plus, I might get some really good items from an aerial. Hopefully, hopefully I get at least
one or two unique. That's the real goal here. When you see that first that the gold text drop.
Oh, it's like I wonder what that's going to be. Be careful.
All right. Stone skin demon. Amplify that damage. Just stay over there. Try to get a set. Well,
once I get the waypoint, I can do an aerial run and just try to get a couple of cool items
before I get killed and active. I'm still alive. All right. Hang up on
no. Give me some. Give me anything. Stuttered leather. Hold on.
No, go back and sell. Look at all this crap.
They had to. They did something weird with these potions.
They actually did patch this. This is a lot. They patched it on Otto's birthday. Oh, that's nice of
them. It's even in the stash. Nothing. All right. Six and six. That's fine. Jail level two. Oh,
OK. What happened? Good. I don't know why, but that I got the same reaction for that. That if
my character died in hardcore, I don't know why I thought something happened.
I'm going to be able to level up twice here. Probably better than pausing the game for like
five, 10 minutes. Hey, Vaude, Jerma is going to die soon. What's your prediction? Yeah,
I mean, you've got to get what you can't say. You've got to get prediction after that.
Right. You can't just say soon. When? Give us time. When? 15 minutes from right now.
So it's with three hours and 32 minutes into the stream. So in three hours and 47 minutes.
OK, we'll see. As long as they have an army, I might be OK. He just opened the door by himself.
You've got to let dad open the doors. Don't open doors for no reason.
I have to be in control of that. Once we get to the interclusters, I'm going to start to
kill. This game is actually kind of scary. Yeah, a little three. What is that? Resist fire. Sure.
I'll take it. It makes me take 75 percent less damage than fire. I think. Although I've never
really known what that does. I've been promising the green screen since November. What's the hold
up? Those of you that don't know, I have costochondritis, which means I can't move around that
much. And until I find a solution for that problem, I cannot jump around and fly around
and do the things that I want to do in front of that green screen. I'm I got hold on. I got to
apply damage on me. So it might include a few things. I might have to have surgery on a hernia
and I might have to get an injection of steroids. But pretty much the only way you treat it.
Unfortunately, this is going to be really bad. So I have to focus here.
Oh, don't kill me. Why can't you guys be fired? All right. So the guy that said this is going to
end in 12 minutes, how dare you spawn these enemies here? Go in, like physically go in the door.
Get in there. Somebody go in. Go inside. All right. Kill. Fight. Mage. Mage. Mage.
Why do you get to have amplified damage, too? It's not fair.
All right. Slowly, but surely get in here. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Where's my goal? Oh, I need somebody.
I need somebody. I need somebody. I need somebody. I need somebody. Back up. Any corpses?
No, you got it. You got to get in there, man. You got to get in there.
Come with me. You got to get in here. Get in there. He's coming to us. He's coming to us.
Look at his health. Inside of the gate. In the gate. Get in the gate. You're just getting hit for
free. Thank you. At least somebody has a brain. Get in. What if he explodes? All right. I'm ready.
I'm ready with another golem. It's too scary to do this on my own. He just low-key called them dumb.
Well, yeah. He's kind of dumb. He's going to explode into cold. I know it. I'm staying all
the way back here. Did I low-key say it or did I just say it? Come on. One more. Hit him. Yep.
Okay. I knew that was going to happen. Nice work, you two. You did it. Okay. I've got to kill like
two more things and level up. No corpses over here. Promote that golem to iron. I probably will. Well,
actually, no, I won't because it's not my decision. Don't let me influence you.
I'm going to have two levels up here.
Second level up. I don't want them to... If they're ice, they explode. That's terrible because I can't
turn them into corpses after that. These characters ruin the purity of the bone.
Cool. Level up. I will. I will. I will. I'm going to put this down.
I just want to get to jail level three. Got everybody? Yes. Jail up here. All right. Don't
even fight that. That's just... That's just death. I think it might be in here.
I knew it was down here. Jail level three. All right. Time to level up. We've got two
levels up. I'm going to put 10 points in. Where should we put our 10 points? Time for you guys
to make a good decision here. We got 10. You're looking a bit low. I'm talking about coffee,
Cheetos, and what? I'm actually not sure where that is being clicked. No, no, no. That's terrible.
That's the worst thing I could put 10 points in right now. It actually is the worst. You need hit
chance. Imagine putting one point in dexterity. Get influenced. Hey, get influenced. Get influenced.
10, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Done. Vitality. 10 points in. What? Done. Look at that. 39%. Thanks a lot,
guys. Ah, I feel so much safer. All right. We have two points to put in, but we have
essentially some new shit to look at here. Ray Skeleton. Skeleton Mastery. Make it better
skeleton. Make Clay Golem a little better or make it plus 20% health. Skeletal Mage is a third
skeleton permanently. We don't have enough to go down yet. That one point in teeth is just so,
it's haunting me. Or we have, again, amplify damage. Also keep in mind putting a second
point in amplify damage does not make it do more. It's always 100%. It just makes the radius bigger
so you don't have to cast. It gives you a much huge wide area and duration. All of them. So,
Iron Maiden is, I believe Iron Maiden does go up. Explosion is here. Still have not picked anything
in this really, besides some of you just making a joke a few hours ago. And then again, take a look
at what you have available for summoning. All right. Where do you guys want to go?
Summoning looks like not a bad choice. Where would you like to go inside of that?
Summoning memes are so 2019. We have another point to put in, so this is the first one. What
about the second one? We'll take a look what it looks like afterwards. All right, here we go.
Skeleton Mage. Some of you want to do a better golem, which I don't disagree with you. Not a
bad choice. What are you going to do with the 43% of these guys? Trying to put a, well,
third Skeleton Mage is good too. I'm fucking into this. I'm beating Andariel first try.
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. All
right. All right. Let's go. Third Skeleton Mage. We have enough. By the way, keep in mind.
This is going to make them stronger defense-wise, but it's not going to add another Mage. See,
take a look. Take a look and see what it does. Make sure you're certain of what you want to do.
Residence Sleeper actually making a real build. But are they though? You know what I mean? I mean,
it could be kind of. All right. You see, you know, you know what's available. I don't have to show
you again. I will very much implore you to open up a Diablo two skill calculator and go to
Necromancer. You can take a look on your own time, you know, so I don't know if we can,
you can be certain of what you want. No, no, no, no. All right. Jesus. Just give me a suggestion.
What the fuck? All right. Where are we going? I would do that. Why would I do that? I just click
on X. Okay. Summoning it is. Silence. Summoning it is. What are we doing in summoning?
Real build. Real build. What is this real build? I wanted to do 20 points into dim vision. Why?
No, he's going to kill Andariel. You had an opportunity and you didn't take it.
I actually completely I have to apologize to you guys. I was under the impression that you
were going to put one point into skeletons and then 20 points into skeleton mastery.
I thought you were going to do 20 points into teeth. I you know, you've got you guys are
actually working pretty well right now. Let's get all the mastery. I don't want to give you
any ideas, but we're already going on a build here. Okay. All mastery. Let's go. Which as you see,
life is at 100. This is an attack bonus. Take a look at the attack. It's at 20.
So he's at 80 and 100. Let's do a bang. So he's got 120 health. The attack is a little bit better.
He's just going to live a lot longer. He walks a lot faster too. You're doing cuck at build.
This is literally the build I did in middle school.
Yeah. And guess what? It's fun to look at, but you'll see when we get to a boss,
it's only me. Well, who knows? They may have patched it. Here we go. Jail level three. Let's
do it. Thanks for voting. You guys won't even give me bone armor. If I'm going to be melee
necromancer, like you at least give me some defense.
Am I running faster? What? I feel like I'm faster. Kind of a suboptimal build. I would say.
Yeah. It's very suboptimal, but that's just the way it is. Now we get a champion down here.
Getting harder to kill things. Oh, that's right. I do it. I do another mage.
We got eight friends. Yeah. The Golem lasted a lot longer. Golem's name should be play.
Yeah. Well, the thing about the Golems in this game is if you beef them up,
they will survive at bosses and they will. It is just, it is just you watching somebody else play
the game. Just hypothetical. If you put, if you guys put like 20 points into the Golem shit,
we're going to be watching somebody else and watch somebody play a video game.
I will be the camera pointing at the Golem. Come on, Drew crew. Why can't he just be dead
in 10 seconds? So we can play Nancy Drew. That's not, that's not going to happen.
If I were to die in 10 seconds, we would have played a paperclip empire,
but whatever that thing was called, true, true, true. If we got a new crew, look at this crew.
You don't like this crew skeleton crew calcium crew. Come on. Milk mob battle.
Let's get so hectic. You don't even know who's on your team.
Once there's 10 skeletons, 15 skeletons and five different, it's just hard going on.
I got an item. I have like good items or what? Cool items. I haven't seen one.
Bones are made of solidified milk. This is where I die. Game over. This is game over. I lose.
Holy fuck. That was terrifying. Everybody in the bones equal frozen milk.
Yeah. I got to buy the portal. If I'm playing on hardcore, I got to find portal to something.
I'll just stand there and open up the inventory. All right. That's,
that's a lesson I need to learn right now. All right. I'm binding, uh, F five town portal.
Okay. Good to know.
They all run at you like that. I see that Adam Sandler got snubbed for best actor. I did.
It's a joke. I was actually getting a little nervous. I just heard the, uh,
blacksmith's voice line and gotten nervous. What did he say? He said, I will crush your bones to
dust. Something like that. I'm scared now. Don't open. What a room. Bad room.
We're doing a real life. Don't get stuck in there. Don't get stuck in there. I don't know.
Come on. Stay alive. I'm just the coach. Just a football coach.
He's lightning or what? Diamond. I'll take it. It's a teleporter.
Okay. Old enchanted. Are you seriously going to give me Paladin shields? Why? Give me anything
else. It sucks. That sucks. It's okay. It's all right. Diablo two. I was just paraphrasing.
That wasn't actually me actually doing. It wasn't paraphrasing. Found it.
All right. Inner cloister. Time to get scared. I'm so glad I'm not a potion find barbarian. This
would not have lasted very long. This would have been horrible. It might be going a little faster
if I was source first or something, but even still, I think that would be horrible as well.
This is just stupid and shitty enough to last long enough to have fun. Thanks for that.
It's because you are one. I am one. What? All right. This is kind of funny.
This is kind of funny. I'm going to put this on screen.
That's fun. This stream was worth it just for that.
Oh, whatever. I just want to do this. I think this is fun.
Plus two to the artist. All right. Here we go.
Uh, where's the waypoint? It's like right here somewhere. Isn't it?
Plus two to the artist. Minus two to me. I didn't say anything. Can't you just give
plus two to the artist? Why do I have to get a minus? That seems kind of unfair.
Inner cloister. There it is. All right. Time to get scared.
Seriously. Actually scared because this is the part with the
monastery barracks. I have a lot of friends over here. Is there no max level?
Uh, there is no max level. Wait, is it outer cloister? Wait, where is it?
I didn't know it's outer cloister. Isn't it? Yeah. It's the barracks. Okay.
Well, I'm going to do this because I want the, I want to be able to do the thing.
I'm free to die. I hope not.
Barracks. Okay. Yeah. I wasn't here before. All right. Uh, uh, I hate this. I hate hardcore.
I do any one of these doors. I'm just going to hear the voice line. It's going to get
the shit out of me. He's going to sprint at me. He's going to hit me once. I'm going to
hurt us. Here it is. I'm trying to get around. All right. Golem, tank them.
Still alive, right? I'm so paranoid. We bring this back to, uh, Charsey.
Things actually pretty good. I bring it back to Charsey and then we can
imbue any weapon in the game as long as it's white. We can make it magic. Good to see. Oh,
thanks so much for returning the Herodric Malice. I will now imbue one of your items
with magical powers. Thank you. Well, the idea here is you do not just do this for no reason.
You find something that's really high quality and you bring it, but you don't just want to
throw one. Oh, yeah. A random pair of socks. No, no, that would be terrible. So that would be
waste. Almost level up. It is certain that we face the demon queen, Andariel, who has corrupted the
rogue sisterhood and defiled their ancestral monastery. This does not bode well for us,
my friend. Yep, yep, yep. Kill Andariel. Find Andariel's lair in the depths of the monastery
catacombs. We are there. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Let's go.
I'm ready. We need to get the catacombs level two waypoint so I can farm for items if I want to.
Do not ever, under any circumstances, play Diablo 2 and not get the last waypoint. It would be a
mistake. Don't do it. I know some of you just want to run through, but we have to get that waypoint.
Worst mistake of my entire life. Oh my god, he's...
I would be so scared if I was doing this with anything else. Oh, there's a lot of people in
here. Slow, slow. Good thing I was... We got our first... Boys and girls, we got our first unique.
And a jewel. Oh, yes. Don't die. That's a unique over there. Uniques in this game are not like
Diablo 3. They're actually cool. It's not just like 700 strength, 700 intelligence, 750
health. No, they're actually cool. What is it? Oh my god. Our first fucking legendary.
I want to identify right now, but that's a mistake. 700 IQ glove. Player of the room,
don't be an idiot. Don't be a fucking idiot. No reason to put myself in danger.
Who's reviving? Where are you? Where's the shaman? Where's the shaman?
Okay, that's a champion.
Thank you, Coke Gaming.
It's so funny how that just became a thing randomly overnight. It really did. All right,
let's see. Heavy gloves. Pretty fucking good. Blood fist. 10% increased attack speed,
40 health, 10 defense, plus five to minimum damage. Let's see what this does when I put them on.
Look at the health. Ready? 150, 190, 30% faster hit recovery, which is huge. 40 health is huge.
Yep. Nice. Seems kind of bad. For a random, just normal act one, that's pretty good.
Big in my head. Bullshit gloves. Let's go to the catacomb.
You're not going to beat act two. Well, there's a way I'll beat act two. And that is I know it's
going to be me versus Doriel. Right? So I just have to grind until I have like 80 cold resistance.
It's just the only way. What about the maggot lair? Oh, man. I forgot about the maggot lair.
That might be the run ender. All right. Catacombs. It sucks. It's a really shitty jewel.
Like you're going to make it to the maggot lair. I think I'll make it to the maggot lair. I mean,
unless something really bad happens now. And we're going to find my screaming tomorrow. Yeah.
Another jewel. Doriel is going to kill 100%. I don't know. It's going to be tough.
This is better than what I have on. Nine to 15, one to 27. But I'm out of, I'm out of, um,
town portals. That's horrible. Okay. I can't go back to town. Don't they be paying attention to
that stuff? Stay back. I'm running dumb. If I identify that's not what I want, it's whatever
it means they're going to drop. Come on, scroll. Scroll the town portal. I can't be a rat man.
Are they alive? How am I overburdened? Oh, all right. Is this better? If I put, all right,
if I just put a bunch of dumb shit in here, three to four fire damage, can I make this better?
15, 16, 18. Fire resist and cast. No. Does Darryl have fire? No, it's poison. Is it poison and fire?
It might be. Town portal. There it is. Yes, poison. Okay. It sells junk. Junk, junk, junk, junk, junk.
This shit is junk too. Yeah. It's taking up too much space. Get the hell out of here.
It really is. It's taking up too much space. This guy's a psycho. What did I do? This guy's a psycho.
14,000. Should I gamble? Maybe. Yeah, we'll level up. I'm going to need to do it every time.
All right. I need, I'm looking for, I need armor. All right. What's the worst thing I possibly,
what's the worst thing I have on me? These boots suck. Three. This belt sucks. Everything kind of
sucks. The boots are probably the worst though. What do you need? I don't need gloves anymore for
a while. Claymore. Boots. Boots. Geed, come on. Better belt. It's going to be another slot.
Where are the boots? Anything. Geed, come on. Here we go. Heavy boots. They're still awful.
Why level four of all the things? I'm so focused on this game. You won't notice. Yes, I do.
All right. Chain boots. Bad. I can do this like one more time. I don't want to completely
broke our chain boots. Come on. Rare. Well, that didn't work out. Here are the points at this point.
Where am I putting these stats? Take a look. Okay, here we go. What does dexterity do? It makes you
hit more. It increases your attack rating and technically your defense, but it makes it so
you hit more. Your hit percent chance goes up. Did you die and restart? Why are your stats so bad?
It's not a question for me. Okay, we're doing dexterity. See, defense. Average chance that
Dark Shaman will hit you 40%. When this goes up again, it's not going to go up again, is it?
90. Still at 40%. So bad. Only 27 mana. I have 80 mana, but if...
It's chance your hit and chance to hit things. All right. When's the next level of... 18 isn't
going to get more stuff. So at 18, Blood Golem will make an appearance. You do skeleton mastery, which
will... Skeleton life, damage, improve missile damage. It essentially just makes everybody better.
More health on Golem. Attack bonus gets to 40%. Health goes up by a lot because this is synergizing,
obviously, with mastery. They're not quite have... Not enough to do another mage and not another melee.
Eventually though, maybe. Make the skeletons better. Point anywhere here. Absorbs 20 damage.
As you see, that's pretty useful, but you haven't put one point in it yet. So, like, thanks. Or a
curse. And you've seen this already before. Dimvision, Iron Maiden. Choose wisely the category
you'd like to put a point into. Poison Dagger is the meta. It's not your choice. It's your
choice collectively. He wants bad choices to make it more interesting. How does giving me a shield
that absorbs a bunch of health, a bunch of damage, me trying to meme you guys? I'm trying to live.
I want to see the end of Act 1. All right. Summoning skill. No, we're not choosing categories
anymore. If he dies in Act 1, we get a 10 minute mountain stream. Yes, that is still on the table.
Skeleton Mastery. To be put to level 3, which will increase the life 24 through missile damage.
Yeah, I mean, hey, let's see. 6 to 7. And there doesn't say how much damage they do, but 6 to 7
with health at 168. So let's see. 8 to 10 now and 76 health. Better defense. They just better out
all around. Okay. Have what I need, right? I just want to say you betrayed the Drew crew. I'm gonna
be honest. Well, we're, we're milk mob now. Sorry. I do feel a little stronger.
I think they're a little stronger. I got everybody, right? So fucking mad. I'm so fucking mad. I'm so
fucking mad. I'm so fucking mad. I'm so fucking bad. I don't know what to tell you. Drew crew
have their time and they continue to have time. But it's not just only about the Drew crew. It's
about other crews making an appearance, being able to have fun.
Watch out for that explosion. It's gonna happen. Kill it. Oh, oh, crystal sword. All right. That's
better. 7 to 24. 1 to 2. Take a look at that. All right. I get corpse explosion now, at least
temporarily. 20 to 44 damage. I'm good with that. And let's get corpse explosion on. I don't know.
Let's say I'm not cute. I got to redo this bar. I'm going to get F1 is going to be skeleton.
No, no, no. F1 is no. F1 amplify. F2 corpse explosion. F3 weaken. No. Yeah. And then F4,
F5, F6. So these are my offense moves. And then here my, yeah. So F4, F5, F6. I can also scroll
too, but it kind of is hard to do. Miss things very easily. All right. Now I have corpse
explosion so I can do this. This just became possible to beat this. As long as I never take
this weapon off. Find portal again. Shit. Right. Okay. F7. Please, Jeremiah, please. Bind your
portal. Level two. Where is it? I feel like I'm missing somebody. Am I? No. There have been
exactly 5,200 people here for the last hour. That's kind of crazy jerk. That's a dagger. Yep.
But I can't do corpse explosion that much because I don't want to lose bodies
for somebody. It's tricky. Not up in the top right corner. I mean, it's probably going to be lower
left. That's where I think it is. Easy. I like the sword. It adds to my attack rating pretty well.
Let's try. Almost. There's a little too. Do not let me leave here without the waypoint.
If you see me go down. Oh, we're going to go. No, I have to get the waypoint.
This is a waste of time. Corpse explosion is a broken skill. Yes, it is. Yes. Nice volume.
It is pretty good. You turn up my volume, please. Yeah. Sorry about that. I'll be over in five
minutes. I know you don't want to get out of bed. You want anything else? This way.
Never seen this build on forums before. Look at that. Look at how good it is. Overuse it.
Unlimited power. Who says that? Who says it? I just want to know if you know who says that.
Oh, if my game were to crash right now, would it? It's not like I lagged and I died, right?
It would just save the game where I am. I think so.
Not bad. I'm going to push this up. I think build, man. Stop teasing me.
I'm going to come in handy here. Don't waste it.
Shit, this crap is everywhere, dude. How long have I been screaming now? Four hours? Four and a half
hours? Something like that? Come on, waypoint. Bro, please. Flare Act 1 already. I knew somebody
was going to say that. I knew it when I said, oh, you know, four and a half hours. I was waiting
for the four and a half hours and you still want to kill Dario. Look at me. Get with the program.
Dude, get through Act 1 already. What the fuck, man? You're really starting to piss me off.
Sorry. I am a good level, though. 16? 16? You really want to be somewhere around level 20 for
Act 2. Like 15 to 20 is where you want to be. Usually. I hate these spiders.
I've got to kill this motherfucker down here. OK, no, no, no, no, no. Run, run, run, run away.
There's a lot of people there. This is my first time playing Diablo 2. Yeah, I know.
I'm just trying to get a feel for it. Where is this waypoint?
We're going to do Diablo 3. No, no, I don't want to play D3. Careful. Three SOJs in chat.
Stones of Jordan were, it really was crazy how that was just the currency of the game.
I told you guys that I got scammed out of a pre-patch worm skull before, right?
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got scammed. Yeah, because I don't know. I was an idiot.
Is he dead? How strong is this thing? Is Diablo 2 worth paying $20 for? Well,
he missed the first part of the stream. Instead of a lot of bad things.
Level up. We cannot kill this. I'm afraid to go in there. Kill that thing right there.
Things lightning chanted. I will die if I go in here. Kill it. Come on. I know you can.
Get a couple more people in there. Get in there. All right, easy.
I can't cast. Here we go. I can't go in here. Oh, it's too bad if I do. You're in such a shitty
spot. Come out of that spot. No, don't just go in. What are you, dumb? There's no corpses?
I'll be back. Stay there. Stay there. How much health does he have? Let's get too much health.
All right. We have to kill some stuff. Run. I found it. But I can't leave. I'm so useless without
the army. Oh, there he is. He's already got his health back. Oh, you've got to be fucking
kidding me. He regens. How am I going to kill this? Shoot teeth at him? No, that's the best
way to do it. I want to go in there and just smash him. Just wait it out. Look at, he's
regening more faster than I can kill. He's regening faster than I can kill him.
Try to pull out the teeth. I'm going teeth. Let's do it. Not ideal. Not ideal. I have to,
how much am I lighting at? 10. No, it's dead. I'm going to die. What do I do? Did I hit him
once? No, that's death. See, look at the one little of those bolts. No, no, no. This is
hardcore, guys. You can't make a stupid mistake like that. He's going to follow us around,
but that's fine. I'm going to get an army. No bodies anywhere. No bodies. We have to find one.
There. You can't wait to see this boomer is going to get owned. That's what you think,
but it's probably not going to happen. I'm going to be very careful.
I know how dangerous this is. I'm going to be very, very, very careful.
Okay. On the way point. We're fine. I need to kill this spider. All right. This is enough.
This is enough. Let's go. Come on, boys. Where are you at? Where are you at? You're hanging out
over here somewhere. Where is he? In here? Get him. Get him. Get him. God damn it. Come on.
He's melting. My golem. Every time. Kill. Holy shit. I thought the game crashed and I was about
to scream. Don't let him run. Kill him. He's almost dead. Well, that wasn't worth it. Oh, well.
Give me a skeleton. How many times this German says, get him. This stream. Oh, probably a lot.
Get him. Get him, guys. Get him. Get him. Get him. Yeah. All right. Let's get lucky and find
level four immediately and then fight the major boss of the video game. I need more. Easy. Easy.
Don't go. Don't just go on running in. This is bad. This is bad. Get him. This is bad. Get him.
Get him, guys. This is bad. Get him. I don't feel safe without a full crew.
And why would I? It's the only thing that this point's in. God damn it. How about over here?
Up left. Get him and resurrect him. Shattering these guys alive because one of these magicians
has the free. Kill it. Don't blow it up. Good. All right. Now I need two more mages. Undead,
extra strong. Don't let him turn around. Kill it. Get it. Kill it. Get it. Kill it. Well, team,
back to being confident again. Feel good. It's like a zit on my face. It's coming up.
Where did that come from? You know when your face is normal and then 10 minutes later,
there's just a zit on your face. Why does that happen? I hate that. Nothing in here.
Where is level four? That's stress. Yeah, probably.
Superior studded leather. We can turn that into something if I really want to.
Do I want to? I don't know. Should I put, should I imbue that?
No? You don't think so? I know I can come back here and do it.
I think I don't have to fight anything.
Oh, I can give that to Kyle. Oh, lots of money. I don't like how they're dying. They're dying
to regular enemies, which I don't like. I really don't like that at all. Level up. I will. Before
we fight Andariel. Don't worry. I just want to get there first. I'm so sorry. I just punched
in the face. Oh, let's go up this way. Level up. Re-level up. Re. These guys suck.
I've explored the entire left side and you tell me it's not over here.
What did I say? Blizzard sucks. The first like 30 minutes of this stream. Anger. It's true though.
I think Coolz will show. Please. I just want to do it. It's taken me five hours to kill Andariel.
Come on. I can't have it cross five hours. I know we've spent like 40 minutes picking abilities.
Come on. It's right here. And then we're going to make a safe point. Everyone's alive. There it is.
Catacombs level four. Kill Andariel. Oh, thank God. Okay. Easy. Tricky room.
Tricky room. Tricky room. Tricky room. I'm scared. I hate hardcore. I don't like hardcore. It's too
stressful. Okay. I got to go in here with a full team. All right. I got to hold enchanted. I got
to run up before he does anything. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. How? What? Oh, right. All
right. Go back to time. We're going to get the archer with the bow. Hold on. Isn't she like level
three? Well, that was a stupid thing to do. You can die instantly. Level seven. I've been leveling
Kyle. Why would I? I want the act three companion. Should I imbue this? It's hardcore.
You know what I'm saying? It's hardcore. I got to take the opportunity. Superior studded leather.
Just imbue it and make it a rare. I can't just hold on to it. What if I die?
Save it? There's better armor at Charsey. Is there a new loser? Jesus Christ.
Okay. Right. Get rid of the Dirk.
He dies. He dies. Yep. It all build it up to this moment. I need antidote potions.
Okay. How much are they? They're expensive. It might be overkill, but it's not. Trust me.
We're going to be such a coward. What am I doing? Is stack when you drink. What are you talking about?
You really don't need to do this. Yes, I do. Yes, I do. If I get poisoned, I'm going to die.
So I have to instantly just take it off and I'm going to make the portal in a place where I can
just run the fuck away. You can't die from poison. No, but I can die from a swing to my head.
That's a coward strat. This is hardcore, man. All right. Gamble. I want at least studded leather.
This is hardcore and I'm alone. I have my pretend friends here. You don't have to be. No,
I mean for today, I do because I was shadow banned from battle net. I have to make a new
account and buy the game again. We've went over this. All right. So studded leather. No,
I'm not going to buy this from Charsey. You can't rely on multiplayer. No, I can't.
I got to accomplish it. Got to achieve it on my own. Studded leather. Come on. Let's see it.
Ooh. Ooh. Come on. All right. What am I putting points into? That's what we got so far. 50
vitality, 48 strength, 32 dexterity, 36 energy. You get banned for a 20 year old game. Did he die
once? If I die once, the character's gone. Did you use map hacks? No. The only thing I've ever used
was the Glide wrapper. Is that illegal? I don't know. What are we doing though? Wait, it is.
Wait, the Glide wrapper is illegal. And that's why I got banned. It's just to make it so you
can see the 3D shit. No, is that you for real? I don't believe that for a second.
All right, we're doing vitality. All the Glide wrapper does is just make it so you can
actually see the X in the 3D stuff and everything, right? That was so disappointing when I saw that
though. All right, let's do skill. Let's take a look. Again, here we are. So you can see
these are fake just to make sure you understand they're fake. Next level, we open up some stuff
down here. Now it looks like we can... I don't know. It's up to you. Poison dagger, bone armor.
We still have iron maiden. Weaken. Up to you. Pick the category. Hold on. It screwed up.
Blizzard fucking sucks. All right, you know when you say something you know you're like,
I probably just don't say it. Who cares? Me angrily saying Blizzard sucks four hours ago is like,
oh well. Whatever. Oh well. Oh well. They're a 40 streamer without sponsors.
I don't think I'm going to get invited to the next Overwatch mixer. No. Uh oh.
Okay, poison and bone. Cool. What do you want? Pick something good.
You pick teeth right now. Why would you pick teeth right now?
Are you trying to fucking kill me? Yes, but don't answer that.
Yeah, you're giving me bone armor. Good. Good. That's just 20 extra health permanently.
Nice job. Thank you. Thank you so much guys. I'm going to show you some of the other category
stuff down here just so people that don't know what the hell is going on they can
make a more informed decision. So bone armor receives plus 15 absorption
from bone wall and bone prison. Here's bone wall. Bone wall just makes a gigantic annoying wall
of bone. It's a way to block stuff off. One and one. And then bone prison can hold anything.
Creates a barrier of fossilized bone around your target so it just traps them. Bone wall is great
in the maggot layer. It can help a lot. But watch, look at how cool this is.
Now that just stays on forever until it comes off. I'm gonna make it f8.
All right, no more fucking around. No more dicking around. Let's see if I can kill the
first boss in the game with what you guys have presented. All right.
Get rid of the shamans. Don't get too overwhelmed. Look at that bone armor. It's helping so much.
I feel safe. Okay. All right. Let's go. Not yet. Not yet. No. Hold on. I want to make sure I've
never- I want to make sure I'm in full health. We're good? Okay. I think we're good. Here we go.
I'm actually kind of nervous. I've never done this before. Everyone, have you poured a two
liter in your friends humidifier? What the fuck are you talking about? I didn't do that.
Uh, interesting though. I wonder, is it in a humidifier? A two liter of what? Of like sprite?
What would happen if you did that? That's so stupid. I just took damage because of that.
All right. Let's go. Here we go. On Dariel. No more, no more sitting around. Let's go.
Everybody in. This is shamans. Holder yet. That's good. Any more shamans over this way?
Kill that shaman right there. Oh God. I was dead. Everybody's dead. Everybody's dead. Everybody's
dead. Everybody's dead. Run. Run, run, run, run, run. Back to town. Greetings. You didn't even use
an antidote? No, man. I don't want to get killed. I don't want to take one punch and die. It's- I
need- Okay. We need corpses. Everybody stand still. Stay, stay, stay. Okay. Where is she?
All right. Everybody get- Pull it, pull it, pull it, pull it. Pull her in here. All right. Get her,
get her. What's going on? She instantly killed everybody. Get me out of here. Get me out of here.
Okay. I'm fine. Let's refill the potions. All right. Somebody just wrote
Hey. Fuck. It's all right. It's okay. All right. All right. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. We're not doing that. I'm going in with a full army. I'm not going to get killed.
Let's just go to the dark woods and get people. I'm not going in with just my clay buddy. That
would be absolute death. Just do not use a town portal under any circumstances. I need bodies.
It's just me and you. I can't wait to see what items we get. I'm so excited,
but nervous at the same time. Let's go get blood vials. Oh, stamina shrine.
You guys just kill. I'm not going to hit anything. I don't want to break it.
Don't use a town portal. I'm being an idiot. Same deal. Then I'm going to swarm her.
I'm going to go for it again. All right. Let's go. Follow me. You got the throwback. You ate a
bunch of Oreos and threw up in your mother's bed. I drank a bunch of... I drank a bunch and
puked in a friend's bed with brothers. I don't think that's the same story. I don't think those
two things are connected. All right. Give me some mana potions. No, I don't need them. All right.
Good. All right. Here we go. Back in. I have... I still have town portal. Oh, fucking God damn it.
Why? It's so... All right. Here we go. One, two, three. Get in.
Okay. Wait. She's almost dead. She's almost dead. She's almost dead. I'm fine. I don't... Am I?
I've never done this before. I don't know what... Save. Fuck around.
She's hitting me. She's hitting me. Yeah. I did it. Wait. Kane will do this for free.
This is a great victory indeed. Loot the chamber? Yeah, I will.
Many more battles await. I will accompany you on your journey.
Finally. You know what assistance I can. Remember, Diablo is still out there,
seeking something in the desert. On your way to loot Golane. And Dario's death brings about
renewed life for us all. Yes. Now we talk to Warif, but not yet. Finally, we may rejoice.
We were dead. We can never repay. In time, we're able to rebuild our order. Skipping quests.
He must just be watching a video.
What can I do for you?
All right. Let's get these identified and see if there's anything worth using.
6 to 23. No. So there's only... No. 9 to 22. No. No.
Got a regular ruby. That's pretty good. All that shitty items. Well,
uh, not necessarily because, I mean, I guess I could, uh, I might just do it again.
I might just kill on Dario again. What you need. At least you got a normal ruby. That actually
will come in handy. If I get a weapon with a socket, that's just 20 plus extra damage.
That's pretty great, actually. Is that better? No. All right, let's go to Act 2.
The caravan is prepared. Good evening.
Shall we? Oh, hey, you want to watch a cut scene? I didn't lose the chamber. Oh, sorry.
We traveled east over the mountains and into the vast deserts of broken lands. Sorry.
As the days passed, my companion told me of himself that he had once been a great warrior
and that a dark and secret burden gnawed heavily upon him. We traveled for an eternity
across that arid wasteland. How long, I couldn't say. And oh, a dark cloud seemed to follow us
just over the horizon. Yeah, the cut scene still goes on. Finally, the journey ended. We climbed
the last bridge. The shining jewel sea beyond. We made camp that last night. It looks like
Kenshi. Perhaps it was the warm desert wind or the sound of the ocean, but for the first time
in many weeks, I slept. However, the dreams returned, but these were clearly not my own.
I beheld the vision of a great man, the mage. You were there too, Tyrael. I remember
seeing you in my dream. His brethren had cornered a great demon in Baal, the lord of destruction,
had been set loose upon the world. They attempted to imprison the demon within a sacred stone.
Yet when the rinse failed, Tal Rasha selflessly volunteered to contain the demon within himself,
completing the prison. He instructed his brethren to bind him with soul within.
How long is this? This is pretty long. I'm not even sure why we're watching this.
This is my brother. Sleep now. We set out with the dawn.
The next morning, we walked over the hill toward
Lutgulain. I had no idea then of the horrors that were in store for me there. Greetings, honored
traveler. I am Jeren, lord of Lutgulain, and I bid you welcome to my fair port city. I'm glad to
know that once again caravans are free to travel through the western pass. We've been having some
problems though. We're here, Akdu. It all began when a dark wanderer came this way,
looking for the tomb of Tal Rasha. No one knows exactly where Tal Rasha,
keeper of Baal, is entombed, but it is certain to be far out in the desert. Thank God the skeleton
came with you. Now my people whisper tales of the dead rising from their tombs and horrible creatures
lurking amongst the moonlit dunes. Not explained. Okay, it's you raising the dead. How do I know I
could trust you? I can trust you. Welcome to my shop. Better potions now. I'm bringing him money.
This skeleton needs to calm the fuck down. He's fine. He's just out of bath. That's why he's
doing this. All right, so the first thing you do here is obviously you gotta take the townspeople
of Lutgulain, trust you. You gotta clear out the sewers. I've heard that you are responsible for
banishing Andariel back to the burning head press stranger. Only noobs do every quest? For which
you're up against, my friend. You ought to look over my inventory of items. All right, the portal
is still there. That's right. I can go loot still. Okay, do the sewers. The sewers actually can kind
of suck. The enemies are not easy. Yeah, let's just go. Let's go loot the chamber. Yeah, it's still
here. Ah, we can still do it. All right, let's go to the back. Kill the cow? I can't do that till
the owl is dead, right? Or is that only after Act 1? I don't remember. It's been so long.
Just do the cow level? Can I do it? Can I? No, I can't do it yet. Okay, he's killed Bael. Yeah.
All right, was there anything back here? Nothing was even back here. But I did get companions,
though. You have so much gold. Yeah, I don't mind having that much gold on me because
it's not if I... Oh, if I die, I'm gonna lose it. No, I'll be fine. Yeah, we're good. Please pick up
the gold. I beg you. You just did. Okay, let us do the sewers. Remember, say Bael. Bael. Where's
Atama? They're being attacked and harassed by enemies underneath the sewers. It's your job to
take care of them. There's the guy to gamble with. How much money do I have? I don't have that much
money at all. Watch me just die here. Easy. Don't get too cocky. Fire resistance? Not very good.
Not very good. Did we just get... Did two raids come in at the same exact time? Wait, what?
A double raid? Was this intentional or is this unintentional?
A box box came in with a huge raid and so did XFSN Saber. That's pretty crazy. Welcome, guys.
Hope both of you had a good stream. It's on slow-mo follower only. Oh, well, that's not good.
All right, turn it off. Back in demons instead. If you're wondering what you're doing, why are you
playing Diablo 2? It's 2020. What are you doing? And it's vanilla Diablo 2. I don't know. I just
felt like doing it. This is hardcore and Chad is picking every stat and skill and they picked
the class too. So blame them for the 48 strength and 32 dex I have. But welcome. Thanks, guys.
They're free. Push them back. What do you mean no, we aren't? I could have just died right there.
You almost just killed me, guys. You almost just fucking killed me. All right, that's a lot of
arrows. I actually... That's a lot of enemies and a lot of arrows. I don't think this is going to
last very much longer. I'll be completely honest. Hey, I'm new here. What kind of streamer are you?
No, you know, I like to dabble in fucking all kinds of fun stuff. You know,
Nintendo, Mega Man fan. I just love Mega Man.
Why is it so loud? Is it still that loud? Even after turning down to almost a zero? After all
this, turn up my voice like that. Is that better? Can you hear me now? Hello? Hi. How are you?
Can you hear me? Yes. Now I'm too loud. Well, what is this? A thousand times better than what
I have on right now. Yeah. We get a skill point for this too, by the way. I can't believe I'm
fucking swinging at people with a weapon. I still can't believe I'm doing this.
Where is everybody? Get over here. Where is everybody? Are you body blocked? Get over here.
Look at the level two. Oh no, I can hear the game.
Where do I go? Down here? I forgot about the bone armor. Well, I've died. Look at how I'm so spread
out with skills. I don't, yes, I forgot about the bone armor. There's a point in teeth guys.
I forgot. I'm sorry. Just wait till we get the cube. I think we're doing all right. Let's go.
I forgot my name was Tommy Lee Bones. Who came up with that? Does he got x or enchanted? Get away
from him. Does he explode? No. I always think people explode, but you have to. You have to be
so careful. All right. This is a stalemate. This is a stalemate. That's better. I can't hurt anybody.
Can't hurt anything. This is where it all collapses. They're starting to win. This is,
yep, this is where it collapses. Any healing potions too? God damn it.
Yeah, we can level up. Where'd your potions go? I've been using them. All right, stat points. What
do you think? Here's your look. You need another tooth. No, one is fine. One tooth is fine. Pretty
split. Strength, vitality. Guys, energy is useless. Well, that's sort of accurate in a way.
All right, close it in 10 seconds. All right. Oh, we're getting indecisive. What is going on?
What the fuck is going on? Why is this so fucked up again? It's fixed. Sorry, I'm clicking a million
times a second. Use a straw pole? Yeah, but I have to make a new straw pole for every new stat point.
All right, that's good. Vitality. That's a lot of vitality. In fact, that might be too much.
I don't know. All right, let's take a look at we have unlocked some new things. We've got a bone
wall. Bone armor still. We're in the bone category here. Keep in mind, if I put one point into this,
it's going to make this increase by plus 15 absorption. Just letting you know. Just gonna
put it out there in case anybody was curious. You cannot have more than one golem out at a time.
Keep that in mind. This is blood golem. It's a golem that shares with you the life it steals
and damage it receives, right? Okay, so this is we share health and I forgot. I forgot about this one.
It converts 86% damage to life and we also share damage. That's the thing. In the curse category,
we can't even go down past iron maiden. You can do lifesteal and of course, we still have points
into mastery and free skeleton. Whatever it is you guys want to do. Pick a category, please.
You didn't, you don't mention the teeth. No, I said don't do teeth. Well, hold on a minute here.
Just because you guys pick it doesn't mean I have to use it. You understand that, right?
If you guys select blood golem, I don't have to summon them. What do you mean wrong? You guys
could put 20 points into blood golem and I won't summon them once. No, but we can waste 20 levels
in it. Okay, well, here we go. Summoning. What am I doing? Why would I use blood golem on hardcore?
You want to see what it does? Because we want to get to fire golem. Yeah, all right. I will,
you know, let me show you guys the other golems too. Blood golem, iron golem transforms a metallic
item into a golem that gains the properties of the item and it also has thorns. So you have to
throw an item on the ground and then at the very bottom is fire golem. It's a golem that converts
the damage it receives from fire into life and it's just a beast. You only have one golem out at a
time. Reef people's drops with iron golem. Well, that's if you are a sicko. So blood golem gives
life to every golem, as you see. Play golem is attack rating, fire golem is damage to every
single one. But you picked blood golem, so I'm going to do it. He does look actually pretty
cool though. Let's see what he looks like. Gross. He just doesn't have any skin. Pizza golem. Spaghetti
sauce golem. All right, let's move. I didn't go that far, did I? Go get him. Can I heal him somehow?
I need more. He's kind of taking it pretty well. I'm still getting my ass kicked though.
When's he going to die already? I might be okay for a little while. Everyone's here. This was
supposed to be a disaster stream, but here we are. A rune. Yeah, you didn't think I was going to do
okay. Well, to be fair, you guys did pick. Not pick 20 points into dim vision.
We went over this. Yes, yes, yes. Get emotionally invested. Wait, is this so you can just pull the
rug from underneath me? All right, no town portals. That's great. Good job. Could have made him play
assassin. Yeah, I didn't say it in the beginning of the stream, but I hate assassin. I'm so bad
with assassin. I don't like the move sets. I hate it. I'm so glad you guys didn't pick assassin.
I would have died in the blood more. Yeah, I got to get the act two mercenary.
All right, everybody stuff in there. Stuff in the hallway. Picking up minor plots.
Stop. I know. I pick up everything. Oh, he's dead. Get in there. Oh, I got clay. Clay's back.
Oh, right, right, right. Because it's not. I'm going to change to blood.
You used blood going on one time. No, he's back. He's back. See? You got a full team.
Picking up minor potion. Now you got it in my head.
I feel like this is going to start to move a little more smoothly, though, because we're not.
I think you guys have an idea of what you're doing and what you want to do.
I think we might start rolling here. Almost to the boss. This boss sucks, if I remember.
He just resurrects everybody over and over again. And there's like 100 people in the room.
Once you see the quest marker pop up, that's when you have to freak out and make a portal.
Damn skeleton. Yeah. Make it so he can't do anything. Those are the plays.
And do I get a streamer's choice? Skill point? No. Really? Come on. No. All right. Fine. You
you can't have that as your title then. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, you're right. You're right.
Nobody getting hit by that. You can do it for a wink. I'm trying. I do more damage.
That morning's already good. Hmm. No. Get rid of this too. Fucking problem on the ground. Who
cares? Where is this guy? Show show my skill point. You know, you do. I know I could just pick it.
Right. I mean, it'll break every rule, but I can do it. You're still alive. Yeah. Oh, it has to be
down here. There's no other options. It's always the worst thing in these games when you look at
every single possible avenue and it's the one tiny little spot that you didn't go down.
Right here. This little sliver. Don't die. Wink. Did a wink come through? All right. I need to.
It's not even it. Where is the where is the right place? Top left? No. The fuck lower left.
I think it's the only place it's not. I think it's down here. Am I correct? Oh, yep. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I'm going to get 10. Hold on. Wait, I can't. I don't want to die.
I'm going to revive them first before you do. Apologize. What? I didn't do anything.
There we go. Weaken. See how much of an area that is. All right. Get him. He's got a lot of health.
Book of skill and scale mail.
I love that sound. That's pretty good. 17 health. Two mana after each kill.
Free skill point. Hey, that strength is coming in handy somehow. I might just put life in it.
Oh, I can't leave. Roderick scroll. This tells you where the cube is. The Roderick cube.
Get that socketed sword. Superior crystal. Seven to 24. Five to 15. Wait, hold on. Let's go examine
this. Imbue it. What level is it? 43. Five to 15. If I imbue it, it's probably just going to turn into
this. I can't imbue it. I'm going to only imbue white items, right? Here we go. Wait until hell
to imbue anything. Do you think I'm going to make it to hell with this character?
You're putting a lot of faith in me. You couldn't do it? Gotta get there first.
Open the chamber's hidden door. They're nearly losing one to the thievery of a rogue sorcerer.
They divided Aldrich's staves into two parts. Wooden shaft. Yep. Get the shaft. Get the head.
Get the cube. Played the game before. His name's not Dylan. All right. Here's where we get weird
because should I? Should I? I could add eight to 12 fire damage in this. That's kind of good.
That makes it better than this. And I could add five to eight. This could be like 30 or 40 damage.
It's fire damage, man. Save it for a better weapon. Yeah, but these gems just suck anyways.
I'm going to get the cube and I can start making stuff. Yeah, that's true. Hold on. Let's
organize this. Stop moving the gems. What? What? It's not by color. It's by quantity. Quantity.
Outward. Red is fire. Yellow is lightning. Blue is cold. White is undead. Green is poison. And
purple is attack rating. And then there's light steel, which is good. Very good.
And then you have these ruins. You can make ruin words. Very, very, very powerful. But we're not
going to do that any then. No. Or potentially ever. Good day. Need potions. And give me max out the
scrolls. I want 20. Just do 20 and 20. I know Cain does it all, but I want to be able to do it on the fly.
All right. So now we return to Atma for rewards. Makes it so it's less expensive to do everything.
Isn't she in here? Where is she? Where is Atma? Down here. They say that the taste of vengeance
is bittersweet. Yep. Press completed. Now we have to go. This is kind of a painful part of the game
because you have to go run around the giant wasteland.
Yeah. The rocky waste. You have to run around and it can be really kind of a pain in the ass.
And all the bugs have electricity. They're already painful.
Oh, we just have to move. We're going to walk around. Get a mercenary. I will. I'm going to
come back to town. We're going to have two points to burn. All of Act 2 suck. I mean,
Act 4 is probably my favorite. Act 4 and Act 5 are awesome. Just because Act 4 is such a mess.
It's just hundreds of enemies. It's just a giant open world with a ton of enemies.
Yeah. I would say Act 3 is worse than Act 2. Hold enchanted run. There it is. Level up.
Really want to be somewhere around 20 here. 20 to 25. Is it dead? Kill it. What does Eldoron do?
76% damage to undead. I mean, you could have an undead killing weapon if you have a sick slot
weapon. That'd be pretty cool. I almost just did these out of just habit and I almost, people
almost just freaked out. All right. We've got two skill points to put in. Well, you can take a look
what we have and to refresh your memory. If you want to just see it again, you kind of know how
this all works at this point. Bone wall, poison dagger, teeth, bone armor. I don't really care
about curses in this chat, I don't think. Okay. Let's pick something. Pick a category. Very clear
at the moment. Okay. It is. Fun deal. What skill? Fun not found. Fun not found. Do bone wall. Well,
convince your fellow chatters to select bone wall. That's, you gotta, you gotta do that.
Another point is going into blood golem. Please pick a category for the second skill point. Okay.
Some of you want curses. I feel bad for you guys because I don't think you're ever going to get
what you want. I'm not sure you guys are ever going to get what you want. Poison and bone.
I think I know where you're going. Could be wrong though.
We want teeth. We want teeth. I've actually tried to make teeth work before. You can kind of make
it work. It's really stupid though. All right. Bone ball. We do stats yet? We did not. All right.
So we got bone wall and blood golem too. All right. Want to see what bone wall looks like?
Kind of cool looking. Tell me. Jesus. Please be unique. Skeletons are dying guys. Skeletons
are not lasting very long. I repeat. Skeletons are not lasting very long. I repeat. Skeletons.
I told you we need to buff them you danguses. I'm just, I'm just going to put it out there.
If you're going to have skeletons, the game is getting progressively more help, more damage on
enemy. You can't just go spend it where you can't just blow it on bone walls. All right. Let's do
stats. Who does he think he is? Do you have a name? Strength or energy or vitality?
Bad influencer. He's a bad influencer. He's a bad influencer. All right. Strength. Thanks for ruining
the game. Again, appreciate it. Look at all these abilities. It's just all over the place.
I have to redo this. I'm never going to do weaken. Amplified damage is always going to be done.
Okay. F1 is bone armor. F2 amplify. F3 bone wall. F4 blood golem. F5 skeleton. F6 skeletal mage.
That's a little bit better. Okay. Let's go. All right. Where are we at?
We're going to be in the far hills of the cube. I want the cube so I can mess with the
recipes. It's a lot of fun. Can you wink at me in person? That just doesn't. All right. The
marshmallow wall does not do very much here. I don't even know why I'm going to. Why would I
use that? All right. It's cube hunting time. I got to get it. Where would I go? All right.
Rocky waste. We need the far hills. All right. All's the dead under the dry hills. Okay. Up
this way. I'm going to move. Don't run into people. That's the cast rate. No. Actually,
I probably should use bone wall here. Oh, dry hills. There it is.
Okay, mage. Blowing mage. Should have got the cast rate. I'm summoning necromancer though. I'm
not going to need it. At last. I need them to be strong so we can fight the boss. I need to be
strong. This is up to the... For the halls of the dead. Find it. Find it. Dude, this dude chugged
that entire bottle. Yeah. Why do I think that's so funny? I played a ton of Diablo 3. Now you're
making me get Diablo 2. Diablo 2 is a fantastic game. It's been an incredible experience. It's
one of the best games ever. It's one of the best games ever. Found it. Halls of the dead.
Let's make a little spot here. We don't have any more mages so let's get them. Sapphire.
I've burnt an embarrassing amount of time in these games.
It's truly, truly so much time. I don't remember much from when I was 16 except for
playing Diablo 2 when I got out of school. Every day. Every single day. And even
out of high school and college every day. Oh, this is a bad room. I gotta get in here. I gotta help
too many people. He's really gonna get trapped in these rooms. I gotta kill the guy resurrecting.
Get over here. Oh, hit this. I have no dexterity. Right. I forgot. How are we doing? Just one
mage. How the fuck does this build for the late game? On a scale of... We're gonna hit a wall
when I get to the boss of this act. It's really gonna determine if this is gonna be even humanly
possible. No good items. It's annoying. I really wish I had more skeletons. I wish that I had more
skeletons and they were stronger. You know, I mean if we're gonna put six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve points into skeletons. I really, you know, just wish they were just a tad
stronger than they are now. Bonewall school don't get me wrong. You guys are indecisive. Fucking
boomers. All right. Decks and teeth. Got it. Uh oh, uh oh, uh oh, uh oh, uh oh, uh oh, uh oh,
don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot.
There's a fucking, there's a trillion people in this room. I gotta go around the corners.
Kill him. Okay, we're good. I hit him. Okay, we're good. Use bone wall.
Oh, what? I already have a bone wall. It's standing around swinging its stuff.
Move to level two. All right, now's my opportunity. Good. I gotta wrap a run. What is it? How many
players is it set to? Four? Come here. Only one unique this whole game so far. Yeah,
an unusual bro. I have one. It's really good. Arguably one of the reasons why I'm doing okay.
Ah, because it's just a dump of health. A ton more hit recovery, which is a huge deal in this game.
Hit recovery will kill you more than anything else. I remember pre-expansion never getting
it unique. Yeah, it happened. It did happen. Once you start playing on Nightmare in Hell,
though, they drop all of the plays, especially from the bosses. A boss will drop a unique
or a set at least one out of every, especially if you have magic find. Magic find is so important
in this game. Why am I talking like I'm going to be able to do this? Once we get to Nightmare in
Hell, I'm going to have 200% magic find. That's not happening. I'll be lucky to get the axe free.
You're underestimating the bones. It is good. Looking for the cube in here somewhere.
He's getting class jealous. He's getting class jealous. This is bad. If I was a sorceress right
now, I would melt this whole room in one second. It would just be like everything would just die.
That wouldn't be very interesting. If I had Nova right now, I would just walk in a room,
right click three times and run to the next room. It'd be great.
No, I do, which is why I'm playing it. I could have said at the beginning of the stream,
no, no, no, no. I don't want to do skeletons. No, stop. Stop. No, I'm done. Hey, we're still here.
We kind of did. Why am I so good at beatboxing? I'm not really.
I can just go like this and this and this. Pretty much it. Resist fire.
I just got a taste in my mouth. What was it? I just sensed a flavor of some sort. I'm trying
to figure out what it was. I just smelt it and tasted something. It was like a chard. What is
that something? I just got like this random memory of a flavor and it was like a charred
kind of meat flavor, but it's not meat. What was it? I don't know. It's freaking me out.
What is it? It's like a smoke, like a smoky flavor. Very charred though. Turn off the stove.
Oh shit. It's been on all day. Hey, waypoint. Now I can run my friends through the whole game
in less than 40 minutes. Oh, but I can't play online because I was banned from battle. Oh,
I had a dream about the stream actually. So I had a dream that so I got this wallet.
No, this is the dream happening. Okay. So I got this wallet recently and I actually really like it.
It's great. It's this shiny metal small like travel wallet, right? It's my dreams happening
right now. It's called the ridge. It's actually a great wallet. It's fantastic. It's really good.
I had a dream last night that I was sponsored by this company that makes this wallet. I don't
know why. For some reason. And I was nervously doing a presentation for it while the chat and
there were like 30,000 people here for some reason. And it was just a wall, a spam of like,
I'm fucking out of here. Unsubbing loser. You piece of shit. Fuck you. Fucking loser. How dare
you? And it was like, no, no, people weren't joking. It was like last stream. I'll have a go to
just a wall of just, everyone was so mad. And I'm sitting there going like, and as you see the,
and I kept looking over and going, no, if fuck anyone hates this, but like I haven't
been doing it. And as you can see, you can fit like 10 credit cards in here. And
I was getting so nervous. It was a sponsored dream. Yeah.
I don't have any friends. Where'd they all go? They'll hide. Give me the cube so I can get out
of here. He thinks we hate him in his dreams. You know, I think dream you, the dream you,
at least I'm going to give you some benefit of the doubt here. Dream you guys. It just came out of
nowhere. I didn't say, Hey guys, like tomorrow's going to be a sponsored segment or Hey guys,
this is going to be a stream tomorrow. Hey guys, this is company. No, I, it was just, I turned on
my webcam and started going and was stone faced just doing an ad. That wasn't a joke. So it was
just like, what are you, what is this Jeremy? My face was like kind of red. The wallhuts are great.
They really are. I love it. This is pretty scummy. It seems like we were right.
No, but it wasn't, it wasn't even stuff like, Oh, unsubbed. I'm out of here. It was real mean,
horrible shit. It wasn't just like, Oh, unsubbed. Oh, hello. Well, you know,
have a hands. Where is the cube? Where is the cube? I'm getting so unlucky. You wonder why this
has been six hours into act one, act two, whatever. It's because I keep my RNG so bad. I can't get,
I think this is it. At least we're going to have the cube though. What should I have for dinner?
Any food suggestions in the chat here? Only good ones, please. No, not pizza. No, no. Japanese
salmon. Oh, I don't really have any food. Stir fry. That's not bad. Sounds pretty good.
I wonder what that flavor was though. I don't remember. This is still not the cube room.
How have I not found the cube yet? I have no idea. Oh, the cube. I already found the cube. It's in
the room down here. What am I? Did I not see it? How did I not see this? Cube. Okay. There it is.
The Herodric cube. You have quite a treasure there in that Herodric cube. You have, you have
quite a treasure there. You have, I'm trying, I'll get it. You have quite a treasure there in that
Herodric cube. You ready? And go. More. Blood Sapphire. Hey, he's available. He's available.
He's, yes, I'm available. Any more? Nope. That's it. What am I holding onto this for?
These rings are terrible. Salad. Let's get rid of this thing. Just taking up space.
Okay. Prepare. Save the money. You can convert three rings into an amulet. Yeah, that's true. But
no, no. All right, let's go. Time to find. Oh, the maggot lair. The best place in the game.
Best place in the game. Damn it. I think that's so hard.
Oh, God. God damn it. Somebody watched my stream for like 60 hours. I have to turn on my camera
and go like this. God damn it. It's like such a, so hard to do that apparently. Stony tomb. All
right. Fire Wastes. I'm making pretty good time in act two. Would act one take like six hours? We're
like, we're almost like halfway through act two and it's been like 40 minutes. Shit. Stamina.
He didn't spend a half an hour allocating stats. Well, you, you got, but you guys had to do that.
You guys had to know the tree. Now you guys know the tree.
You know kind of the direction you want to take the character and we can, we can move forward.
You're blaming us. Yes. Yeah. Every time I hear the ring drop, I just, I want, I want it to be
unique. So bad. These little ships are the worst. Has he died yet? Nope. I have not.
Arctic binding plus 40 cold. Hey, and guess who that's for. Guess who that's going to be great
for. The boss of this 30 defense and 40% cold resist. Take a look at this shit. It's almost 60.
Oh, I lose a slot, but it's all right. Almost 60%. Good. Resident sleeper. Wake up, wake up,
man. Wake up, bro. Wake up. All right. Don't stand still in hardcore. What are you dumb?
I need more mages for that. Wake me up when we're at a hundred strength.
Where's my pancake? Why am I, how am I responsible for getting new pancakes?
You got to take care of your own pancakes. How is it? It's not that bad. It's like nine 30.
Oh, there's a nephron. It's two 20. Ah, right, right, right. I live on the other side of the world.
Um, well, in six and a half hours, we'll see what we're at in like 30 minutes.
What do you guys think? You guys, you guys want a conclusion to this? I mean,
I feel like we kind of have to see the conclusion. You got to keep going until you die. I need
far away. So I think it's far away. It's connected to dry hill. Don't get off until you die. Well,
that's probably not going to happen. We get back up here. How are you even still alive?
Because chat accidentally made a character that wasn't completely useless.
We knew what we were doing. Yeah, that's why I'm still alive. But I don't think 14 or 15
points in teeth would get us this far. It just wouldn't. It would not have happened.
Yes, it would have. Ridge wallets are real. Yeah, I have one. I know. But I didn't,
that wasn't part of the dream. Part of the dream was not that the wallets weren't real.
Stupid ass. Get out of here. We've got their ridge wallets in my spaghetti.
No, we've gone. I only talk about products that are actually useful. JetBlue, a useful product.
Ridge wallet, a very useful actual product that you should probably get if you need a wallet.
I have nothing to do with them. I just know because I use them. It's my last time being here.
Stamina is killing me. Admit to the joke. Show the wallet on the camera. I mean, I do really
want me to go get my ridge wallet and show you. I mean, it's it's not much to see. It's just a
wallet. No. Yeah, but I've got like, I got like credit cards and my license in there and shit.
I'm not doing that. I'll just, I can just take, I'll take them out. There we go. Far away.
Actually not a terrible charm. Pretty good charm actually for right now. Champion in there. Watch
it. They get melted. Jesus. Oh, it's because this guy's here. Oh, a jewel. It's out though.
It's lying about the wallet. Oh, I own one. I'll get it in a minute. Well, when we take break two,
that's the last break of the night. I will get the ridge wallet and I will show you the wallet.
See, picky bugs. Yes, lots of bugs. This is why this part sucks because there's so many random
enemies everywhere. I'm close to the maggot there though. Oh, the zombie head. You're right. This
could be plus to something good. Okay. All right. Well, now thank you for telling me to go get that
one guy because this is plus two to raise skeleton. One to clay golem and one to bone wolf. I lose
corpse explosion and weaken. Don't care. I didn't use them anyways. Go. How many can I have now?
That's it with eight points. Oh, the next point is five.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I forgot about the bugs.
Swarm and shit. Yeah, they're killing everything. Oh, fuck off. You ridge wallet.
I got, I'm going back down. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to get it. I'm going to go get it.
Hold on. I also want to get the, an act two up here. It's higher. We're about to kill Kyle,
by the way. All right. Defensive. We want offensive, defensive or combat. That's the aura.
Probably defense. I want a level 19, 19 defense. Doesn't exist. Offense, level 19 offense. All
right. Yeah. What are the different auras? Combat is probably better. Combat's like blessing a might,
whatever it is. Combat aura is healing. It's the regen aura. Probably, probably not a bad idea.
Let us pick it when you piss. Defense is just pure defense and offense is I think attack bar,
right? All right. Let us pick. Yeah. I'm going to go pee. I'll let you guys pick and I'll come back.
I'll make the pole. Wait one second. Straw pole. Bring the wallet back. I will. And we can,
um, we'll play for like another 30, 40 minutes and see how everyone's feeling.
But it's, it's going to start to get late. Okay. Vote on this and I'll be back in about two or three
minutes. See you in a minute. Guys, the wall is not real. I fucking made it up. Or did I?
This is the wallet right here. There it is. Look at how thin this is. This opens to store cards.
You can slide, I believe up to 20 cards in here and looks like an SSD. There's all kinds of styles.
With this thing. Oh, you got your little, you can see the little thumb thing here.
If you get cards in here, you just, you just push, slide them when you want out, slide it right back
in. It's easy. Cast strap on the back. Secure. Ridge wallet. Pick one up. Maybe. If you feel
like getting a new wallet. Bye. They're really good. They're very good. They're secure. They're,
they fit into pants. You can actually put this into like a jacket pocket.
If you get, you put your essentials in here. It's light. It's got a nice click to it. It's,
it's very sturdy. Never coming back. I'm never coming back. Well, all right. What did you guys
pick? Offense. Apparently it's offense. All right. Uh, look for 1119 offense. And there we go.
Uh, or, what was his offense? Ilzan. The Nari. Or, uh, Vic Yat. Vic Yat. Life 270 versus
270, 155. Are they the same? Vic Yat? Who's Kyle? All right. You want, you want Vic? Okay. Uh,
who's Kyle? You'll see. Kyle's about to die. The mercenary will replace your current one.
Kyle is dead. There he is. Look at how much better. Level 19 damage. All right. We got to
deck you out. We got to deck you out with some stuff. We got to pick some kills. All right. We
need a spear. Seven to 18, seven to seven. Required 50 decks. Eight to 28. That's not bad.
Seven. That's cheap too. All right. Get rid of this. Where's Kane? Kane, come here.
Good day. Uh, Phylactery Lich. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. $50 they say. Derm of the Ridge is
fucking $75. It's quality. It's a quality product. This thing's made out of fucking steel. You can
get the same thing for $15. This thing's made out of fucking steel, guys. Does it protect against
card skimming? What a great question. What a great question. Seriously. It does. It has RFID blocking
inside of it. There you go. Blocks RFID. It doesn't do you taxes. It's also got an integrated
expandable track. Followed section of the wallet's pure metal plates. The T design of the track
secures cards from the bottom as well as the sides, so nothing accidentally falls out of the
bottom of the wallet. It'll snugly hold one card or expand to hold numerous cards. The track is
made out of a robust elastic material that has undergone several strength tests. It can expand
to hold up to 15 cards, and when the cards are removed, it will contract to hold a single card
securely with the most pure of fucking iron and aluminum metal and steel. And it's pure steel.
15 cards. Your actual, your local Walmart little compact wallet cannot hold 15 fucking cards
securely. Sorry. I'm sorry. That's completely incorrect. It was a sneaky way to do an ad.
Ad block isn't working. I like it. I like it. Nobody gave me. I like these things.
I like this thing. I like it. I like it. Next, you're going to send me like a review of that.
I can't piss in my Berkey. Okay. All right. Fine. That's fine. Whatever. Things made out of solid
fucking like carbon steel or something. I don't know. The Berkey, it's my water filter and
everybody made fun of me because I said it sucked, but they, you can clean, you literally take food
dye out of water. All right. I'm not even going to get started on that. What do you bring so I have?
Yeah. Oh, the water filter. Yeah. Let me go get the water filter. Let me go and pick up this clunky,
huge, hard to move around thing and bring it into this office. It quotes your office in the quotes.
Of course. Of course. I'm not going to go get a Berkey filter and filter as I'm no, I'm not doing
that. No, no. It's you know how hard that is to move over here. This thing's huge. It holds like
two gallons of water. What you get, what you want me to go get the Berkey filter and pour
chocolate milk in it and see what happens. I'm not going to do that. Find the YouTube channel
that already did. All right. Let's go pick some stats, please. If you could. Oh, there's still
time. Water filter stream. Why would that be cool? It would be me just drinking water. It would be
drinking water. What would, what's the, you want me to bring the Berkey up here and filter water
through it and then drink the water. Do you want me to tell you how it tastes? Yes. Doing a water
review for milk and coffee in it. I'm not going to ruin my water filter. No, it's that you want
to talk about expensive. It was expensive. It was like a hundred something dollars for the,
that is just thirsty. All right. We're putting this into decks. No. What have I, which one?
Come on, get a pick one. Just buy a new one. I'm, but what happened if you filtered Gatorade? I
don't know. I don't know. It would get clogged up and it would just be a waste. Let's find out.
It's not, this is not going to be as interesting as you guys think it is.
All right. We're doing vitality. What about skill point? Category, please. That's a worst stream of
the new decade. I guess I did build a bird house on stream. That's true. Yeah. I built a bird house.
I could filter fucking Gatorade. What a waste of time that's going to be. And then tell you
what happens. A hundred percent of you. All right. So what, what do you want me to click?
What do you want me to do? Oh, you want the fifth skeleton. Would you look at you guys picking
things that will help us through our journey? And then Bugleberry drinks it. And then he has
to give a review. Robust flavor, pure crystal water. All right. Let's get the next skeleton.
Thanks for voting vitality. 65 vitality. Kind of good to 15. All right. The,
we have five skeletons now. Finally, it only took a million years. This is a good charm.
Recovery and lightning resistance is very important. I'm going to save the rings.
No, because I'm going to, I don't need to tell you a fucking reason for everything that I do.
I have to tell you a reason for everything to explain everything I have to do. Wait,
how are you still alive? This is how I'll show you a few ways that this could have been a disaster.
This, if you, you could have just put every single point into this and I would have no
moves. Okay. Same with here. You could have put every point into bone wall. You could have put
every point into terror. I would simply have to run around and scream while I find a way to kill
them. I mean, even bone prison is some of these are bad. You could have put all your points into
golem mastery and put one point in clay golem and that's it. And then max out like skeletal mage
and it would have ruined everything. I don't give ideas. I'm just telling you,
you guys are doing a pretty good job. Everyone look at chat. I am. You think I'm not?
All right. We're looking for, let's get our new friend out here. We get five skeletons now.
The plan though is once you get more than 15, how was I going to say community subs?
When you get more than 15 community subs, you will start overwhelming. You will get,
that's when it's a, it's a battle. That's how you know, you've made it. How are you guys doing?
Are you guys doing good? You guys chilling? I'm just chilling. Oh, superior zombie head,
leave it. I've been looking for the maggot lair so I can hate my life. I want to keep playing.
You know, I really, I want to keep playing, but it's going to get, it's getting late.
Do this again tomorrow. Um, I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow.
The reason why we did this today is because Bill was having computer problems today.
I was like, you know what? I thought about doing this a while ago and I'm going to just do it now.
I don't know what his schedule is like over the next couple of days, but we're probably going to
do keep talking. Nobody explodes. If not tomorrow, then the next day, we have that tomorrow,
the next day, whenever over the next few days, we just got to figure it out when his computer is
good to go to the filter screen tomorrow. Joel's streaming right now. Well, then that, that means,
that means he, that means he must've figured it out. Do a water filter test, test different water
filters. What a weird stream. Water filter test where I break down how, what the flavor of the
different water filters is. Pure, Brita, Ferkey. I mean, you're talking about as expensive jokes.
I mean, what am I going to do with them all? I guess I could donate them. What do you,
I don't know what I would do with them all. Did I not find them the maggot layer yet?
No, no. I mean, I'm, no, I'm talking about, guys, I'm not going to put anything like
fucked up in these filters. Let's see what happens when we filter orange juice. It's
going to come out as orange juice. It's just going to taste gross. How do you know? I don't know. I
don't know. I actually don't know the answer to this question. Where's this, where is it?
Where's the maggot layer under the far oasis? Come on, right here somewhere. You need to figure
this out. You have to be a scientist. Anybody see a little hole in the ground? No, I can't pee in
the Berkey. You do realize that if I, if I pee in the Berkey, I'm going to get banned from Twitch.
Even if I do this off camera, I'm gone. I'm, I'm gone. Let's go. I'm gone. Durma985,
so obsessed with proving to his loyal audience that the Berkey filter is legit,
he's in water filter on stream and drinks it to prove a point and then gets permanently suspended
from Twitch.tv and his partner status revoked. All right, where the hell is this place? It would be
infamous. Yes, sure. Oh, I hate running so slow. Dude, you would be a fucking legend. I don't give
a shit about being the guy that eat in the Berkey. Do you think I care more about that or being able
to like continue to stream and hang out and have fun and continue doing what I'm doing?
What do you think is more important to me right now? Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on a minute. You're telling me that I can be the guy that pisses in a water filter and drinks
it. Everybody remembers me and laughs at that crazy thing I did. Oh, I lost all my partner status.
And eventually after that, I lose everything, every cent I own. The only reason why people
even talk about it is to laugh at me. Or I could have just played Diablo 2 and enjoyed myself.
No, good thing I pissed in that thing and one person every six months remembers me for 15
seconds. Yeah, it was me. It was me. Oh, man, those were the days. Grandpa, grandpa. Yeah,
grandpa. Wait, you're you're pissing Perry. Yeah, that's me. Wow. No way. Are you serious?
Yeah. I've seen so many top texts, bottom texts about you.
Wow, I can't believe that's so crazy. We were talking about you the other day for 15 seconds
and then didn't bring you up for like a year. Yeah, I lost out on like $7 million.
$7 million. Wow, cool. Cool, grandpa. Yeah, we saw you. We saw you in this funny meme compilation
video. I had 20 million views. Yeah, I don't get any of that money. I don't get any of that. Oh,
but you but people saw it. Yeah, they did. Oh, wait, you don't know. No, haven't seen a dime of
that one. Just pissing Perry. Son, do your grandfather a favor and go get him his favorite
Berkey. And grandson goes and gets it. He's like, Oh, this thing sticks. What's in there?
Yes. I've learned to love it. In fact, it was crazy because right after that stream,
I could never drink regular water again. All I could drink was filtered piss. So delicious.
Okay, I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. The grandson has the youtuber voice because
the grandson is probably a youtuber. Found it. Two decks. Get out of here. Here it comes. Here comes
the end of here comes the end of the character. No, no, no, no, it's gonna be fine. This place
sucks notoriously. Let's just be real. We're getting arguments about stuff. Yeah, pissing
Perry over here. I can't he couldn't even figure out how to keep his channel going.
You don't even have 5000 subs on YouTube, you little shit. You know how many subs I had before
the great pissing of 2020? More than you'll ever have in your life, kid. And what I don't know is
he recorded that. The whole thing. And he uploaded it to his YouTube channel. And it got 20 million
views. And then he makes five videos after that. Talking about it and laughing about it. So all
of his YouTube friends, all of them, are making reaction videos to this. We're talking like six
to 700 million views across like 50 different channels. Pissing Perry just sits in his fucking
rocking chair. Doesn't see a dime. Doesn't see a dime. Get over here, everybody. Come on.
Don't get stuck. If anyone's gonna get stuck, it's gonna be one of you. No. Come on, Vic. He's okay.
He's doing all right. He's actually pretty good. Who thought this was gonna end here?
You were wrong. We're good. How many people we got? We got many more. All right, we got
eight, nine, we got 10 companions. It's not gonna end here. It just sucks because it takes forever.
This is why if I was a sorceress, I could just right click and do frozen orb and just walk forward.
Tell us more about how you love. When did I say I love doing that?
All right, I'm not gonna get justification for why I can pee into a Berkey on stream.
No, I don't know who did it. I don't know who drank pee already. I'm no, hey, hey, you know,
this guy drank pee already. That's okay. That's fine. Oh, good for you. Good for whoever that
was. I'm not gonna drink piss on stream. You're trying to somehow justify me being able to drink
pee on this stream. No, no, no, no, no, no. Are you serious? Are we actually talking about that?
You can't be serious. Bear Grylls did it. He didn't even use a filter. Yes, he did. He buried it into
the ground. He peed in the ground and buried it and then the soil sucked up the fucking
ammonia that's in the piss. He was clean and whatever. I don't know. I saw like a,
I've watched that like a year. All right, we're gonna have to have important people up here. Put
people in front. This isn't gonna take forever. That's fine. Just stuff everybody up here. Come
on. Push through. He's thought about this already. No, Bear Grylls peed into the ground. He dug a
hole and he peed into it and he waited like three days or something. And then when he opened up the
hole, the pee was clean. Something like that happened. Something like that happened. I don't
know. Something weird like that. What was it? I'm telling you. It was like there was pee in the
ground and it was like he buried it. And on the third day his piss rose. Nothing like that happened.
What? That was one episode. Yes, I know. Why do people think I'm crazy? I swear to God this happened.
Jett is so dumb is what somebody said. No, he did not do that. He did not pee.
He did not pee up. He's such a shitty survival technique.
Imagine telling somebody to just sit down in the air. No, that's not how you survive.
That didn't happen. All right, we need. Where's my blood going? Get in there. Get in there and cause
a mayhem. You need to cause a mayhem. Turn around. What are you getting? See the person behind you?
Spaghetti. Turn around Mr. Spaghetti. All right, now you're in the way. What year is this? I knew
that was going to piss so many people off. I knew that was going to just piss like a thousand people
off. The second they heard the gay was just like, no, shut up. Dream is dehydrated.
Don't worry. I'll take care of that in a minute. 17 max stamina. Nice, man. Pretty cool. Nice.
Actually, I'm starting to lose my mind. Whatever. It's the maggot layer. It does it to you.
You are making me want some water though. What's your guys favorite water?
Favorite like bottle of water. Am I a rich asshole if I say Fiji? No, a lot of people are saying it.
A lot of people are saying it. No, a lot of people are saying it. I saw like at least a
hundred people say it. Guys, Fiji is filtered with rocks. It naturally gets filtered over the
sediment of the rocks. Now you're going to tell me that's fake too. Don't die. You're going to be
in front of me. No, I'm not talking about every day. I'm talking about just like sometimes.
Sometimes I'll see it and I go, you know what? That sounds good. This isn't every day.
Drink smart water then. I don't think you want to say that. I think you just angered a lot of
people. I don't know what it is but for some reason if you don't drink water out of your tap
and you say, I like this. Careful. Like if you don't turn your bathtub on and turn your head
over and drink out of the bathtub apparently you're a crazy person. Are you guys drinking out of a
garden hose? Yeah, seriously. No, you know, I don't drink tap water. It has fluorine in it. I don't
want that. No, I clicked an ad one time and it told me that I don't want fluorine. I was like,
all right. I don't want that. I stopped buying it. Stop drinking it. This place sucks. It really
does. Will somebody get up there? I'm so glad I have these mages. I need potions. All right.
15. Just stick it in there. Whatever. Not a bad thing. I mean L runes, they drop like rain.
It'd be fine. Yeah, just whatever. I'm going to do it. That's 15 plus. There's more defense
and light radius. It's fine. I did level up but I have to get to the end of this. I bet that's
damaged. My tap water is hard water and it's awful tasting. Yes, I agree. Vegas has really hard water.
It smells like rust. You got hard water too. Yeah, that's why this filter exists. You don't
want to, you know, I don't, I don't want to drink rust. German misses the East Coast.
I'm not sure I necessarily would have wanted to drink that much tap water in Massachusetts either.
I don't think Massachusetts has very good water. I'm pretty sure it ranks kind of low.
I'm pretty sure tap water in Boston is really not that great.
Go dig a hole if you want clean water. I need more mages. Here we go. Here comes the fun part
where we sit here while a hundred flies get stuck in the wall. Is anybody even up there?
All right, I'm going to put you up here. Get in there. Fight. Nice aim play. It's at this point
that I will agree with you. These guys are immune to physical damage. That's why. I've got a guy
immune to physical. That sucks. The mages have to kill this guy. Oh, he loved that one.
Come on, mages. Get him. All right. I made it through. All right. All right. Okay. Okay.
Let's get some more mages. All right. Kill moonbiting. Jesus. I get two hits.
I got to sell. Hey, I can make one. And four to seven cold damage. Oh, man. Nice.
That's three rings, right? To make an amulet. Yes, it is. Filter tier list. How does that even work?
It's like five. I got to get a bunch of these. I am starting to run out of mana. All right. Let
me get through the maggot layer and then we can do points. Yeah. Level three is probably up here.
Yeah. If I was a sorceress and I had teleport, you know, I really just wish I was a sorceress,
to be honest. Who had a sword? Oh, fuck. You're right. Well, you're not. So yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Not as good. Not as good. Kind of sucks. If you had teleport, you would teleport into death.
Also kind of true. It is. Yeah, I would teleport into a bunch of enemies and die.
Link vessel notice. I saw the tier list. David, I do tier list all the time.
I'm not going to do it right now. Come on. Just get me to the next level.
Claw of Fire for Temple is actually going to be painful. It's not in here either. Shit.
Let me in. Let me in. What tier is hose water? Of all the tap water, hose water is probably up
pretty high. I would say. There's something about taking a hose that's turned on and tilting it so
it makes that arcing fountain and just putting your mouth up and they really can't be beat. I
would put that pretty high on the list. Hose water is dangerous. Why? Hose water can kill you.
Does bacteria and mold in it. What's with all the Debbie Downers? I have a Berkey.
Berkey suck. Not even real. I love drinking out of a hose on a hot summer day. It's going to kill
you. Bananas are my favorite fruit. Radioactive gross. I got this ridge wallet. Oh shit. Too
expensive. It is. But still, an honest shill. No, I was a shill in my dream, but I was not
a shill in real life for that. Hold on a second. Am I getting told? How many, let's be honest,
how many of you guys do vape? How many of you guys have a jewel in your pocket right now?
I know a lot of you do. I know you can get pneumonia from fucking vaping. You know that,
right? Fake news. I stopped, okay? Good. Everyone thinks his fan base is all Zoomers. Well,
considering how many of you guys didn't know the game I was playing until about two hours ago,
yeah, sometimes. Don't run forward here. This is bad. This is a boss in here.
It's the 1999 Zoomers. Are you a Zoomer if you're 1999? What's the cutoff here?
I thought it was like 97 or something. Like 96. What's the cutoff here? Yeah, it's 97, isn't it?
96 is probably the cutoff. You guys get such an interesting
childhood. Think of all the stuff that's been developed in the last 15 years. I mean, we went
from, I went from like the regular Nintendo to cell phones, but the cell phones were kind of shitty.
You know what I'm saying? We got iPhones. We got like, I was going to say Google Stadia,
but that would be not, that's not a very good, that's not a very good thing to say for a tech,
but I don't know why I was going to say Stadia. You know, we've got cell phones. We've got Stadia
now. Like, that's such a big deal. No, Google, this is a long play for Google, guys. I know
Google makes a product and then pretends it doesn't exist like two years later, but really
there, I'm going to die. Fine. They are waiting for when the internet is a hundred times better
than it is now, but they can be the first people that has the streaming video game console
in 30 years. We've heard this before. We've heard you say this before. Yeah, but not everyone was
here. This could be completely different audience. All right, this is it. Get everybody in here.
Respawn everybody. Get up here. He ran into things to say. Listen, I never run into things to say.
I can talk all day. We know, we know. He kind of ruined my thing. I was going to not talk for like
five minutes. He spent an hour talking about expensive water. It's expensive water. Sorry,
the term is airport water. Airport water. Come on. Why do you drink at the airport?
Okay, watch out. All right. Low and slow, low and slow, low and slow. Like a pot roast. Good.
Oh man, there's so many people in here. All right. I need more
Mano. Big mommy bug. That's right. Eggs everywhere and shit. This is why this place sucks.
Ring. Come on, give me something better than that. If I didn't have all these people,
can you imagine this is solo, right? Imagine if 40 or 50 things were shooting at me at the same time.
All right, immune to cold and all of my majors are cold. So that's good.
Done. Staff of Kings. I remember when I first played this game with friends a long time ago.
I mean, it's not a terrible, very fast attack speed. It's two-handed, but I remember a friend
of mine used this. They had this equipped for a very long time and they didn't realize
they were running around with this thing on. And I had to try to tell them that that's not what it,
you don't use this thing. It's part of a, it's the thing is though, it's really pretty good.
Look at how fast the swings for a two-hander. That's really great. But they used it for a long
time and they couldn't figure out how to get out of act two. Why not use it because you have to
get rid of it to get out of act two and quotes his friend and that person. Oh, let's make a,
let's make an amulet. That's funny that you can use it at all. You can use the hammer too from act
one. Can we take a pee break? You can take a pee break when I level up again, cause it'll be about
five straight minutes of us picking stuff. So you'll have that opportunity very soon.
Old resist is more important than magic fine right now. Cause it's burial 59 old resist.
All right. We're almost there. Almost at Daryl. Please. I have to go so bad. We'll just,
just go. It's okay. You guys are good. All right. Now we need the, uh, the head, which is in the,
the, it's a little bit further out. It's the last one. Did I get the far always this waypoint?
I don't remember. I did not. I think we're going to ask them. All right. We're going to go through,
we got to do, we got to do some running here. You can go now. You could actually go now.
We got running to do our ways and we're looking for Valley of the snakes. Don't make any plus
two jokes while I'm away. All right. I won't. All right. See you in a minute.
Hey, thanks for the, thanks for the three. Thanks for the free stock market bump.
What's with the strange darkness? Must find the valley of the snakes. Plus two omega lulam
dying. What have you were? What have you were though? Like what have you were?
What if you were laughing so hard? All right. Don't be a dickhead.
All right. I got to ask this dude bedtime. That's pretty early. I'm just, I just want to,
I'm just playing it. I just love this game. We're going on eight hours. I know, but I mean,
it might not be everybody's cup of tea right now, but I mean, I really do love this game.
It's just so funny. I'm glad you guys got to participate.
Should enjoy what you're playing. Yeah. So, so this, the rest of the week for like the next
five days in a row, only this. All right. Thanks. Yeah. Cool. Thanks. Thanks for permission. Yes.
It's taken a lot longer to kill things though. That's sort of, that's starting to concern me a
little, just a little getting a small amount of concern and how long it's taking me to kill
anyone. You got two levels up. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Oh, there's an ancient tunnel here.
There could be a chest. Who cares? Oh, can I go up? Yes. This is still on hardcore.
I've not given up on that one yet. It's the price for a wink at 75,000 channel points.
Alley of the snakes. Come on. I'm going to sneak. Don't kill me by a trap. That would be,
that would be, I'm going to sneeze. I can't pay attention. I'm going to sneeze.
I promise that was real. All right. Where the hell am I? I don't have any anecdotes.
Kill something. Will somebody die? Somebody die to the wink. Thanks for the free wink.
Yeah. You go. I'm devaluing the winks by accidentally giving up free winks. That's not good.
Alley of the snakes. I don't want to influence the vote or anything, but I'm going to say this as a,
I'm going to say the first letter of each word that I'm trying to tell you.
I W L I Y E 2 P I S M. That's his wifi password. It's DaVinci code. Shit. Where's this loss?
No, where's the valley of the snakes? I need it. I need it. I need it. I need it. I need it. I need
it. I want to filter some water and also review the filters on stream and then maybe pee in the
filters. Not quite. Not, not really that close. Try again and then maybe drink the filters.
Where's this? I need a valley. I thought it was up here. I'm wrong. That was not it.
Honestly, that was so long ago. I didn't even know what it was. I lived my life in dog years, guys.
Like one year is seven years for a dog. It's kind of the same way. Like one minute is like 45 minutes
for me in my brain. Wait, six sockets. Let's go. Actually, these sell for a lot. I can gamble.
Valley of the snakes. Looking for valley of the snake. Just want to find it.
Oh God. Don't let this be the end. Don't let this be the end. Don't let this be the end. Don't
let this be the end. Yeah, these sell for, look at how much these sell for. Let's go gamble.
Just tuned in. Is it the end? No, not yet. I'm, I'm still all right. I'm still chilling.
The stream has been chill enough where it's not like I'm like exhausted right now. I still got my
guy. Yeah, we'll level up too. Some gambling. I need, what's the worst thing I have? I need boots.
Boots in an offhand or something. Boots. These boots are so bad. These are like level three.
Level three boots. I could probably get a better weapon too. They're better. Not by very much,
but they are. Ooh. Magic find is crazy good in this game. Once you cross one to 200% magic find,
rares, sets, and uniques drop all the fucking time. I'll wear them. I'll put a better helm.
Yeah. Try to get a helmet. Here we go. Two sockets. 22, 25. Hold resist.
I could put some stuff in. There's two sockets in here. Do you want to try for something else?
Maybe a weapon. This thing's level six. Oh, it's gotta be one-handed. One-handed. Three to 19.
What are you guys talking about? My job after streaming? What do you mean? I don't like turn
off the stream and go to work. What? Wait, is he going to go to his job that led to today?
He's not relatable. What do you mean I'm not relatable? 12. All right. No more. All right,
that's it. These all suck. Last one. Terrible. Terrible. Let's go. All right. I got 10 points
to put in. Where do you want me to put them? Take a look at what we have so far. Remember,
strength is damage and gear. Dexterity is attack rating, hit chance, defense, health, stamina,
just mana. That's all it does. He got fired. No, I've actually never been fired from a job in my life
because it never happened. All right. Where do you want to put 10 points? Take a look. Which one?
You're going to get fired from streaming if I pee in a filter on stream.
So yeah, we'll make it one out of one. All right. So it seems like now we're actively trying to
fuck up the whole thing. Okay. I mean, this is what if you guys want to do, but I'm an engineering
school. What are you talking about? Engineering school. All right. Five, four, three, two, one.
Dexterity. It is 10 points into dexterity. I might as well pick up a bow if you're going to do that
shit. You're not having enough meltdown, so it's all has to go into dex. Aye, aye, aye. All right.
Take a look. This is what we've got so far. Remember, blue means it's being, there's plus
skills on it. So if you like, what the fuck is that blue, dude? We have two points to spend.
There are two points that we can spend. I don't want to influence the vote at all, but you know,
we have poison of bone. Here are the curses. You know where they are. Bone wall. It already has two
points in it. All right. Where do you want to go? First point. Pick a category on the right. Bone
wall. You already fucked up his dex. Yes, they did. Okay. Summoning. Hmm. Better skeletons.
Skeleton mastery. Is that where you guys are going? Okay. What about point number two?
What about point number two? Please pick a category on the right if you want to pick a new
one. You know, I'm sorry I just hit you in the mouth. Don't get mad at me. I guess you don't
want to pick a category. We'll just choose, okay. Nobody wants to pick a new category. They want to
stay right here. So we're going double skeleton mastery. Okay. All right. I may have done it a
little differently, you know, if it were me playing. For me playing. But you know, going from,
you know, increasing life and damage. Let's say for instance, 13 to 14 damage.
16 to 17. Bank again. Skeleton mastery again. 19 to 20 damage. And they'll live longer. They
have higher defense. I mean, it's not a terrible play. I don't think. This is the same build you
were going to make anyways. No, it is not. Some of this is all wrong. We don't know. We don't know.
We don't know anything about the game. Okay. Cool. Tell us what you would like so we can avoid it.
Well, I said skeleton mastery was better. And everybody clicked it. We want to have what's up
to you. Hey, how do I oceans are all right. Snakes. Holy shit. What happened here? Oh, right,
right, right, right. Okay. Yeah, I panicked and left. I forgot about this.
I forgot about this. Oh, heal him, heal him, heal him. You can drop a potion on companions
and heal them. I just didn't do it to Kyle because I didn't care because he was like level five.
We were fighting with level 15 enemies. So it was not even worth doing that.
Still no Valley. Is that a little spot up there? Did I miss a spot up here? Am I crazy? Yep. It's
actually probably right over here. You missed a spot. Alt tab and turn off your computer.
One of these days, somebody is going to say something like that and I'm just going to do it.
But no, no skeletons are dying. Please. I'm stuck here. What happened? What do you mean?
He's stuck here. How is it possible to be stuck in that chair? Did you, are you like,
are you like bare ass sitting on a wet piece of ice? What happened? There it is. There it is.
There it is. Found it. Found it. Found it. Found it. Yeah. I miss Frank. Yeah. We don't have any
dead rising friends. How would we just, I just played that like a month or two ago.
We don't have any dead rising friends. Friends. Is that what I said? I'm going to beat Darryl
first try and then I'm going to alt tab my computer. Ooh. I think that this is a quick one.
It's just right on level two. Oh no. I feel the arcane sanctuary forgot. We can't just skip that
part. Arcane sanctuary is so bad. Look at five, three. Yeah. Look at this. Look at how much these
guys are staying alive now. There's so much beef here. We can increase their potential by 40%
overnight. Overnight. Easy. All right. Everyone get in there. All right. Here comes the battle.
What's my hit chance on these guys? I'm curious. 95%. Okay. That seems way higher than I thought
it was. No level two in here. Bone mage gang. I think it's pretty much all bone. All bone gang.
Not just mages. There's random hell. Tonight I'm going to sleep. Well, maybe we'll see it tomorrow
or the next day or whenever. Have a good sleep. Period. Two hit a sword. Hold on.
It's 17. Two sockets. Crash. Plus two to weaken. No, crash. It's in there. First kill it.
Worth using? No. It's probably right here. I always hate when it's right next to the door.
I have to train them around. I'm going to get stuck on somebody.
Hmm. It could have ended very badly. How do I hate gold? Um, no. Ask him. Deflect him.
Sometimes there's so many people in them. Get in. Get in. Why does your mouth taste like blood?
Because you bit your lip. You're chewing too fast and you're trying to eat your food too quickly.
Slow down. The drank from the 5G garden hose. All right. Level two is very quick. Right here.
No, it's not. I thought it was right around the corner. It's not. How long is the stream going to
be? Um, I don't know. I don't know. Probably not that much longer. I don't think. Probably not
much longer. But I, I, I got addicted to Diablo 2. Which I kind of knew this was going to happen.
Let's go. Right to the end. Oh, is it not over here? Seems impossible. It's right on there.
Again, see, look at this. Look at the RNG I'm getting here. It's in the one spot again
that I didn't look. The one place. He's not going to be able to play D2 online with us.
Um, well, not with this character, but, and I don't, yeah. What does a Vic have for armor?
Actually, I don't think anything. Actually nothing. So, um, just here. Put this on.
The skeletons are us. Yeah. Think of it that way. I still seriously can't believe I got fucking banned
from this game. I don't think I've ever been banned from my whole life. All right. Be careful
here. This is, this is danger. I've never been banned from a fucking video game ever. I never
had any problems. I got banned from Diablo 2. All right. Okay. This is actually slow down.
They can run up on you real quick. This place on any, on a higher difficulty than normal,
it's hell. It's so bad. I've been spawn camped in this room on hell and had to restart the game
like more than three or four times. Isn't this game hell though? I mean, yeah. There he is.
Bang skin. Get. We've completed the staff. Here's the amulet. The amulet.
Amulet of Kings. Ten life, ten mana poison resistance.
I thought we were going to turn into the staff anyways.
Time to die. Die. Time to die. Die. How do I do that? When is it again?
Time to die. Time to die. Die. Time to die. Help. Help me. Help. Help me. This is for you.
Where is it? Run. Help. There it is. Help me. Help me. Help. Me. Me.
I know all the voice lines from samurai warriors to empires. All right. The horodric staff.
Excellent. You have horodric staff.
I can now go to the castle. The castle? The palace castle.
Let's get some actual armor and weapons for this guy. How about a trident? Trident? Yeah.
And a regular shitty helmet. And that's fine.
3096. That's pretty good, actually. We're going to talk to
Brogdan. The potions are fine. This path of exile is similar to this. I would say very.
The path of exile is a little newer. This is pretty dated. It still does very, very well.
Still holds up very well. Somebody said they bet 50 channel points that I die to the arcane dudes.
Researching the old records. Trying to find the location of Tal Rasha's tomb. Only 50?
I may have a good lead for you. Great Viserai Summoner. Yeah. I'm going to go to the.
Build a summoner. Find a. I hate this part. Look in the arc. Look for the arcane sanctuary
within the palace. I do have a lot of friends, though. Builds to join me within the safety of
the palace. All was fine until one night. All right. Get the staff into Tal Rasha's tomb.
Find Tal Rasha's tomb. Here we go. Who do you hate more, Vinny or Joel?
You know you just love when you get RNG like this one. Level two. Let's go.
Why do I have to hate someone? Is there a reason why I have to hate someone?
It's the part of the game where I become kind of useless. I'm not going to be able to hurt anything.
I don't have any moves, but I do have friends that can hurt for me.
Is it down here? I think the red dead stream when he just showed up. Yeah, that was funny.
There it is again. Nice. Quickly doing this. Good because arcane sanctuary is a pain in the ass.
So I'm glad to get this out of the way. I need one more mage. The whole team is here now.
Oh, Vinny is here. I wish that red dead stream worked better, but it's always good to play
games with you, Jeremo. What's going on, Vinny? Good to see you. Look at this. We're getting such
good random roles. Vinny, I'd love to play Diablo 2 with you, but I'm not sure if you're here,
but I've been shadow banned from Diablo 2 for a reason I can't figure out why.
I have to buy, I have to have a new account. It's weird. Yeah, I don't know. Who knows?
He got reported for GlideWrapper. I went off. I went off. I talked a little bit about Blizzard
earlier, but if I actually got banned for trying to get their game to run, like get out of here.
No, don't want to go that way. I'm so starved of stamina. So bad. I streamed this last year
and I still love it. I was not banned. However, I'm glad I'm glad to hear you weren't banned.
I usually play this game once every couple of years. Once every two or three years,
I'll just turn this on and do act one and then uninstall it. It happens like every couple of
years. I don't think there's ever a time where I was like, you know, I'm going to install a
level 99 cheats. I think so. It's just kind of what you do with this game. If anyone's
been keeping track, I think that's like the 12th or 15th composite rare bow in a row.
Can I get anything else? That'd be happy. Act one is the ugliest environment.
I would say act three is probably uglier than act one. Act three has a couple of places that
have just and they spread out weirdly. Speedrun time. Let's go. This better not kill me. This
better not kill me. This better not kill me. This better not kill me. Okay. Don't open that
door. Don't open that door. Vic, don't open that door. Look how smart you are. I'm so glad that
you're smarter than the pizza because the pizza just opens every single door. All right. I'll open
the door now. Now that we're all here. Can I even open this door? You can't even open this door.
Wait. Yes, you can. What? I couldn't do it before.
This is an honest, this is a mistake to do. I found it. It's right there. It's right there.
Okay. I got to go up and then left. Make sure you have stamina for this shit.
Ah, almost got it. You almost got it. That was close. It was real close. Quick do another one.
All right. Get in on our way to the arcane sanctuary. I hope I don't die here.
You know, if I wanted to, I could just completely game this stream
and I can turn the stream off whenever I want. Oh shit. I died in arcane sanctuary. Well,
hardcore. See, that's it. See you later. I'm not going to do that though.
Just going, just going. It's right here. Arcane sanctuary. Here we go. Find the journal.
I wish I had time to study this bizarre dimension.
So if you don't know about arcane sanctuary, all this place works is you have four directions.
Usually you play this with four people or at least four or five people. Sometimes if you have eight,
that's great because you go in groups of two. It sucks because I'm alone. I got to do it in groups
of one and you pick a direction and you go all the way. It takes about 15 to 20 plus minutes per
direction. You might hit a dead end and only one of them is correct. Which way do I go?
And now we wait. Let us vote. What the fuck? Chat picks everything. What the fuck?
It's all good. You would have picked this way anyways. I got to go back to town.
Can't can do that for free, Jeremy. What the fuck are you doing? Not a bad helmet.
One of the decks are already terrible. Four to mana, get out of here. I need mana potions.
Yeah, you don't.
Jeremy is ignoring his viewers. Did you put the cube in your stash? Yeah, what? What? I don't like
it in here. I don't like the way it looks in here. It's free inventory space. I know, but I don't
like it in here. I remember back in the day, perfect skulls went for a lot. Let's do some stats.
You can see what we have so far. Five points going in what? Please decide.
Yeah, perfect. Have you had 20, 30 perfect skulls? They were pretty good currency. Yeah,
I'll show you the bones. I remember when FDR was president. All right, vitality. Good choice.
We also need a skill point here. So have we unlocked anything new? Not yet. No. Same deal.
We're almost at 10 points in Ray's skeleton. A bunch of random points in blood golem and
mastery. Just to give you a look at the category. And we are actually, we're going to kill Dariel
and I'm going to turn off the stream. It's going to be over after that. We're at eight and a half
hours. It's a long time. I'm not, I'm not aiming for another 13 hour stream today. All right,
we're in the same category. What do you want? What are you guys doing? What are you guys doing?
Uh, guys, guys. Okay. Strike three and I pick a strike three and I'm going to pick a skill.
This is strike three. Here it comes. You already picked summoning spells. You already, you guys
already picked the category. What is happening right now? We want to change category. Broken?
There are 320 votes so far. We want different category. We want new category, different
category, different category. Well, you picked it already. No, new category now. We want,
we want blood. I'm going to give you guys one more chance. If you really want to change categories,
this is your only opportunity. Otherwise, I'm picking something. All right, fine. Jesus.
Poison and bone. We're here. See? We made it. What do you want? Okay. Sure. Sure. Okay. So good.
Cool. I'm about to pick something. This isn't us, Jerma. This is bots. We're already here. You
don't, we're already in summoning spells. Someone else is doing this. He doesn't know. What would I
know? No, this isn't bots. Bots wouldn't do this. Okay. All right. All right. That's it. All right.
The stream's over. That's it. Pick something. Pick something. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, pick
something. Go, go, go, go, go, go, pick something. Pick, pick, pick, pick, pick, pick, pick, pick,
go, go, go, go, go. Delta mage. Thanks for picking. Nice work. It only took you
six straight minutes to figure that out. I don't need two more points to get another mage to get
to four. I'm trying to artificially inflate, you know, how long the stream is. I see. I know
what you guys are doing. Back to the sanctuary. Am I going to play this again? I'll be honest.
I don't think this is going to last this long. So I mean, I'm still alive. I'm still alive. Although
I can probably give that 60. All right. Yeah. I'm going to give this to, uh, nice. Good. All right.
Let's get lucky here and have this be the right one. The first try. That's why you're doing the
TVs. What's going on on TV? All I can do is sit back here and just cast amplified damage and just
wait for them to die. I don't, I don't see it. I don't see it. In fact, I actually don't really
know what an ender dragon looks like. Five skeletons. There's four. What does the ender
dragon look like? I feel like I know what it looks like, but I don't at the same time.
Arcane sanctuary is also a place you cannot just run through. I wish it weren't the case,
but you have to actually play this because the corridors are three squares wide.
And we find the correct tomb of pal Russia. And then we kill durial and turn the stream off.
I'm just here to watch you die. Well, that would be a long nine hours. Wouldn't it just die to
durial. He sucks though. Durial socks. He just, it's a tiny little area. I don't know what the
hell I'm going to do. You know, I'm going to have to go in and here's the, his plan. The plan is
bring an absolute shitload amount of mana potions into the dungeon
and have durial just fight my blood golem. It's going to take like 30 minutes to kill him,
but that's the only thing I can do. You're really supposed to one hit kill you. No, he's not. I,
look at, I have 49 cold resist. I'll just stack it. Yeah. I'll just bone wall myself into a corner
and let the blood go. I just keep respawning the blood golem with like a hundred potions.
I'm going to fill every slot in my inventory with potions. Stop pretending. This isn't hard.
What have I done? What did I do wrong? I'm playing a summoning necromancer. What are you talking
about? What more am I supposed to do right now? What more am I supposed to do right now? I have
just a bunch of people. I can't do anything. Folks explosion is summoning building. Um, I just,
I don't have it. This is all I have. This is all I have to work with.
I mean, it wouldn't be chat picks everything. If I go, you know, let me sneak a corpse explosion
in here. That sounds good. I got lucky. I actually just got lucky. First try. Get them, get up the
stairs and get them. All right. If I, this is pinwheel. If I die to the summer, that's a
literally dying to pinwheel. Kill them. Somebody hit them with anything. All right. We're good.
It was oops. I just skipped everything. All right. We did it. Canyon of the Magi.
That didn't take 20 minutes. I was like, I'm really lucky. I didn't have to go through all
the portal shit. You don't know how annoying that could possibly have been.
Did you know the mage, the summoner is the mage from Diablo one? Yeah.
Faith will strengthen the courageous heart. I feel no pity for that would be summoner.
His terrible ambition for demonic power was pretty skilled. And you know, I already got it with,
uh, random and slayer. The reason why you have to go through all that is because there are a bunch
of dungeons that all have symbols in front of them. And this is the correct symbol. It's the only one
that has burial in it. Can't wait. I really hope I don't die here, but it would be a nine hour
fucking stream to just die to the act two boss. This is why hardcore sucks. All right. Do I have
any? Okay. 24 health in a helmet. Old resist. I don't have a shield. What do I have right now
for cold resistance? 49. That's not bad. Normal. That's okay. Let's go. But I played Diablo one.
Oh, Diablo one doesn't hold up for me like Diablo two does. It's still a good game,
but I can replay Diablo two many times. Make sure you bring the staff. Yep. I got it. Uh,
what do I put in here? I'm seeing what help in there. Okay. I'll get more rupees. I did it. It's
already done. Okay. Now I need a shitload of mana potions. Why can't you pop in this game
and don't you lose all your items? Remember people used to do, that was a scam that existed
back in the day. It was, Oh man, let me show you how to dupe. They said if you put the items that
you wanted on your character and you filled your body with potions like three times and died. Yeah.
And eventually if you die like three times with a full belt, full potions and everything and no
slots for anything, your character popped and all your items landed on the ground.
It was a lot of Diablo scams. Another scam in particular was the switcheroo. So there's only,
I think, three or four different pieces of art for Diablo twos, rings and amulets and weapons
and swords and stuff. So what would happen is somebody would, you had to check a box and that
other person had to check a box to be able to have a transaction go through. You both had a trade
window and somebody, let's say this was the stone of Jordan, one of the most sought after rings in
the whole game. And it would have this art because they all have the same art. They'd put it in.
Yeah, I want two worm skulls. You're like, okay. Yeah, sure. Here's my worm skull. Here it is.
And then I would check the box and they would go, Oh, hold on a second. I need some inventory
space. And they would get back and they do this bullshit. They'd walk over and pretend to go to
the fucking stash. And then they come back and they say, Okay, hey, and they'd go put it in the
window, check the box. And then you would put your thing in the window, check the box. And it was like,
Oh, no. Oh, and it was one of these. And this shit worked all the time. Why would you trade?
I don't know, because you don't, you don't. It's a scam. Scam. That's like saying, Oh, hey, dude,
when, when Microsoft calls you and tells you that the IRS is looking for $50 in iTunes gift cards,
what just, why do you do that? The scams work, man. This is how he was banned. No, this is shit
that happened like 20 years ago. I didn't do this shit. I was, I, it happened to me once.
I was like 14. I got scammed out of a pre patch worm skull. I told you guys that that thing was
worth a shit load. And I remember just DMing this person over and over again, telling them
that my brother gave it to me. That was a gift from my brother. I got scammed. Yeah, it was horrible.
And I say like me and my brother don't talk anymore. And that was like one of the things
that me and my brother did. And I, we love Diablo. We don't talk anymore. And sometimes he logs on
and like we play and that's his worm skull. And the guy was like, fuck off. And what I was saying was
total horse shit. But still, what a dick. I'm not even sure there was a report button in the game,
guys. See nowadays, when you play like League of Legends and somebody tells you to like, to go,
like, fuck you, buddy. You like report. Somebody sees it. And then that person gets into, I don't
think that even was possible. You could do the ring scam a hundred times. And it was just like,
that's the ring scam guy. There he is. He joined another server. I think you actually had to email
support. But I think there was a thing that said that you're not going to get your items back.
Uh, be careful. It worked though. All right. What was I doing? This. Prepare. Let's go kill
Duriel and then we'll turn off this ring. I'm ready. What's the symbol look like again? Circle
with the smiley underneath. Okay. All right. I hit the way point. I had a way point. What
am I doing? What the hell am I over here? He doesn't need a ring. He needs another ring.
All right. Is it weird that I don't give a shit because that ring is like plus one to maximum
damage or something. I'll find a better one. Probably right now. We aren't fighting anything.
Let's go. I know the symbol. Not the one. Not the one. There's a circle above it. Not the one.
Why do you keep ignoring gold? Because once you get to act four, act five, the gold is meaningless
in this game. Once you get to like nightmare act one, gold has no value. Don't die to this.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
important. I got to. Okay. We need some skeletons and shit. I almost just walked in here with
nothing. Horrible. All right. Leveled up. Good for you. Don't run on this. Oh, there's a well.
Cranked on the well. Uh, wrong. Is there one more down here? I don't think so. Yes, there is.
Wrong. Uh, wrong. Right. There it is. Boss time. Because this is a pretty big apex of the stream
here. I want to know how many people have any confidence in me beating this. Let's see. Am I
going to beat Duriel? I'm actually curious. Yes. Yes. Yeah. All right. Actually we're getting a
lot of yeses. Okay. No more levels up. Oh boy. Easy. 75%. All right. Thanks for the confidence
boost. It's going to be very boring and you'll beat him and pretend it's hype. Oh, I turned off
hype trains by the way. You probably noticing why you haven't seen them. I turned mine off too.
Yeah, it's just, uh, this is going to be incredibly disappointing if he was. Um, yes,
it will be because that would be, it would be nine hours of a total waste of fucking time
because I can't log on to this character again. Let me in. What are you going to put in that
wallet now? What do you mean? Cause I turned off hype trains. I mean, it's, it's a, this is a tricky
zone. Oh, it's an, it's an interesting idea. It's just, even when you put it hard to do,
it still happens. And it's sort of just a game of focus on the game. All right. All right. All
right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're going to have to do that. We're going to have to focus on the game.
Otherwise I'm going to die before getting to even to the holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit.
Ring mail. That's a couple of greens. This is Arctic Arctic. Oh, it's angelic. Oh,
these little normal difficulty, shitty sets. I'll give it to you. I don't know what you have on.
Oh, scary room, scary room. No, no, Vic. He's dead. What the fuck is even in here doing that?
What the hell is in here? Nothing. Nothing. A whole lot of nothing. I'll get them back
before I did Daryl. Don't worry. I'm going to keep them alive. You're going to die to a chest trap.
You probably, that's why I'm not kicking over any chests. Cause that's bad. I don't want to die to
a chest trap. Kind of feel naked with a Vic. That aura was actually pretty key. All right.
Everybody get in here. Oh, oh my God. Oh my God. It's itching my eye. Hardcore is a horror,
especially in Act 2. Cause Act 2's light radius sucks. So you'll just open up one of these doors
and there's 40 people standing behind it, just waiting to kill you. And half of them shoot
lightning out of the rest. That's fun. Act 3 is not going to be any better. No, it won't.
They're doing all right. I think it's safe to get in here now and go for a kill myself.
Nothing. Anything dropped. Nothing good. Can't carry anymore. Anyway, bone wand. Let's take a look.
Uh, one to teeth. He's
laws. I have to go back to stay back when they die. Replace them. Five,
a number looking for a room with an, there's an orifice. Probably not this way, but let's go.
This is so bad. Jesus. I can't walk in here. How did you get back? Where are they coming from?
Where are they coming from? Back to town. Back to town. Tell this shit.
Oh, a man of potions. The ring. It's not whatever. All right. Let's go get our buddy back.
Good evening. $3,000 to bring you back. Come on. Stay alive. All right. Vic being here now.
We're going to be doing just fine. Everybody get in here and go and go.
Okay. How's everybody doing? Oh, party. I got to keep an eye on Vic's health because he's probably
the most important person here. You see this Vic shows up and it's just instant kills for people.
Another wink. What? That one hurt. Another stupid room where we just stuff in Vic. Get in there.
The only person here worth anything. All right. I'm going to get in there.
Now I'm going to go snipe the guy back here. Where am I going? Probably to the right.
All right. Let's go. Come on. We're almost there. Can't get lazy on hardcore either.
As long as Vic is in there. Hey, wink. Yeah, I can see the channel. I'm going in. Three, two, one.
Good. Yes, we are. Hang on. Right. Stay with me. Don't attack the one person over there.
I'll be idiots. I got to get back. I'm just replenishing. Good.
This is summoning Necro right here. This isn't what it's all about.
You just don't do anything. Well, if you're at a party with a summoning Necro, it's great
because all the minions just eat every hit and you just create just a smash on people.
My almost done. Poison Nova Necro is fun too. Yeah. Because you just run in a room,
right click and then run away and just let everything die. You have to do every synergy
though or you're useless in hell. I can sell this. Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Vic, careful. Nice. How many players do I have to sit on? Still four.
I just leveled up. Maybe the Spear is better. Two to 24. No. Old Resist though. Here. Is this
better than 32 to 92? That's better. Yeah. All right. Well, I'm going to just check over here.
Just I want to look. It might be right here. Oh, God damn it. This place is huge. This place is
enormous. Too many people. Sweat check. Not really. Take a hit. One hit would be pretty deadly here.
This game is a God damn mess. Oh, Eisenhearts. Another shitty one. Eisenhearts case 107 with
magic damage reduced by two. It's just, unless you get it, this is bad. What do you have on?
I mean, this is just better. Where's Tal Roshas? You don't get that till like nightmare
or hell. I think that only drops in hell. Balloons going down. I might actually get to level up one
more time before Durial. That'd be nice. LOD improves the game significantly. Yes, it does.
At this point, I think that I'm not sure I'd want to play just regular Diablo 2
without LOD. Too much better. Too many improvements. So many more items. So many
more runes. As much as the charm system is kind of dumb, it's still there and it's kind of
interesting to find stuff that works with your character. Can this be a yearly thing?
Hold on. I love this game. So I'm going to take very much to convince me to play it.
I just want to see if it was possible for me to get into the first.
As you guys know, I'm not going to play games like hardcore. I play them just kind of to do them.
Don't go down that high by yourself. What are you thinking? I'm about to make a full circle.
Here comes the full circle. Sneak around. Don't go too far. Where am I? 23. That's exactly where
I wanted to be for Durial. Right about 24, 25 is when you should be kind of going through.
I would say Act 3, you really want to... What would you guys say? It doesn't get played in
25, 30 for Act 3? Something like that. I've got to be close. This is getting ridiculous. Come on.
How big is this? This build puts us at about level 15. Well, I mean, there are points in
Bonewall. And there's a point in Teeth, a point in Bonewall. I don't even check yet.
What else is there? Points in Blood Golem? Golem Mastery? There's at least five points here that
are not being utilized well. You guys got to think about what the hell you want to do.
Those are well spent points. We can agree to disagree on them. What about a Snow Golem?
I don't think they exist, but that would be cool. An Ice Golem? Someone who lives and breathes this
game. This is painful. This is what happens when you give 5,000 people or 6,000 people earlier
power to choose a character in a World of Warcraft. Wrong franchise. We're down 4K now.
Yes, we are. It's also midnight Pacific. It's also very, very late. I'm actually surprised
this many people are still here. So thanks for sticking around. Hope you like it. I'm having fun.
All right. There's only one place. Again, look what happened. Every single place uncovered except
the one spot where it is again. And again, please don't beat the boss. I'm done. I'm done after this.
There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is. Don't get stuck. EU wait. No, I'm done.
Whatever happens here, this is the end of the stream. I'm either going to die to Durial or
we're going to have beaten Act 2 and we can keep going another time probably. I really hope I don't
die though, because this would be, that would be sad. I'm not even here. What is tomorrow's
stream going to be? Well, I got to talk to Joel because I know he said that he wanted to keep
talking, but I couldn't do it today. So we're either going to do that tomorrow or the next day.
Let me stop for a second and catch my breath. Where's the one place I didn't go?
Where the hell is it? Off left?
Do I know about the dupe glitch? It's not a scam. Well, I want to do this legit. If I'm going to
beat Diablo hardcore, I want to be for real. I don't want to, I don't want to dupe like
50 million gold or something up there. It's here. It's here. I found it. It's here.
Crime I dupe glitch. It's not a scam. I promise. Just stand on the outside of the Rogan camp and
drop your best item on the ground. Oh, sorry. I'm a sorceress with telekinesis and I'm just
going to pick it up. See, if you're outside the camp, this is for security. So I don't get it.
I know all the tricks. Yeah, drop. You guys remember that too? Yeah, I do. I remember just
being in the Rogan camp with eight people that are strangers. I don't know why the fuck we did
this. We were psychos. I don't know what was wrong with us, but everybody would stand around
and you would just run to this because no one's paying attention. You don't tell anybody this.
And you just drop one of the best items of the whole game. Pick it back up quick. You just,
oh, hey, there's like 10 people there. I don't know. I'm strangers to fucking all of you.
I'm going to drop the best weapon in the entire game over here, like a hundred feet away and wait
till somebody runs over and pick it up. And sometimes somebody would get it. And at that
point you just exit in a quick game. You're not getting it back. But it always was so fucked up
when you did that right next to somebody and they just missed it. Now this game was taken
dead seriously back in the day. It's 15, 20 plus years ago, guys. If somebody were to get a
grandfather two handed great sword without even trying, and it was a great role that took hundreds
of fucking hundreds and hundreds of hours to find that just rolling dice. Now imagine if it was right
in front of you and you had an opportunity, it was this far away and you didn't get it. That shit
happened all the time. People look crazy. I'm not even over here. This is the biggest dungeon
I've ever seen in my whole life. Why is this dungeon so huge? Why is this so big? I don't
remember being this big. There it is. He missed. Is it always this big? Maybe. Okay. I needed to
make a town run. Parents of hate level two on hell says hi. Yeah. That area is such a blur to me
though because I have like the 300 magic fine sorceress and you just want one one one one one
level three one one one one static static static static Nova Nova Nova. Give me my items. Do it
again. You do it like a hundred times in a day. All right. I need to get this actually situated.
We need, uh, what is it for rejuvenation post institutions? It is three of each, right?
Oh, is this even necessary? Not. I don't, I don't, I don't need like a full stack inventory of
potions. Just mana. Put this in the stash. I'll figure it out later. Okay. Here we go. Kim subbed?
Did she really? Kim, thanks for the sub. But did somebody, oh, somebody gifted her a sub. Okay.
Hey, Spleen. Thanks for gifting him a sub. All right. So remember the plan here
is to spam potions with the inventory open and just make sure I keep my Golem and Vic alive.
That's the plan. How many town porters do I have? Plenty. Okay. I'm ready. Level up. Yeah. Yeah.
Level level level level level level. Yes. Yes. Yes. Stop. Stop. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I don't know.
All right. Hold on. Do I need this many potions? No, but I've died to Durial dozens of times on
normal running around in a circle. So yeah, I kind of, maybe I do. Big stat. Five points.
All good things must come to an end. If you can win here against Durial, you can beat Vale
without dying once to the ancients. That's going to be tricky. Vitality. And pick a skill.
The ancients are actually a joke for Skelemancer. Are they really? I'm not sure I've ever played
a summoner all the way that far. I usually just get bored and give up because you just
watch 20 people fight on the screen. I'm always like, yeah, I'm done. And then I make a paladin
or something. What is corpse explosion is under poison and bone. Yeah. I have amplified damage
already. The burning souls in act four that one shot you. Yeah. Hopefully we'll have some decent
items by then if that happens. Okay. You guys want to go poison and bone? Is it because somebody
came in and said that they had 5,000 hours in the game and now you're embarrassed that you didn't
pick the best spell in the game? Is that what's going on? Okay. No, no, no. You pick something
from here. You pick something from here. Yeah. I'm not going back to summoning. You've already
made your choice. You pick something from here. I'm not going back. Corpse explosion. Which one is
corpse explosion? Why? This is not going to do anything for Dariel. No, no, we're not going.
We're not doing the back and forth like back and forth. Are we going to go summoning? No,
just kidding. All right. Corpse explosion. It is. I know there's at least 8% of you. They're
clicking on teeth, but corpse explosion was vitality and corpse explosion. And you guys,
didn't you guys wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We've leveled up. We've leveled up. And you guys
didn't even know you could. We've leveled up. We've leveled up. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We, we're going to revote because I didn't show you.
Iron golem is available. And so is summon resist. This gives resist all elements to all of your
summoned creatures. Or iron golem transform a weapon or item into a golem. And it has thorns.
Or you could do bone wall. You've already put one here. Can I interest you in dim vision?
Do that again. Where do you want to go? Okay. That was very quick.
Iron golem is a fancy way to save a robot. All right. We're staying in.
Durial doesn't do elemental damage. Durial does a lot of cold damage. What are we doing?
Ooh, he's going to be tight. New golem or resist? He swings for physical. He has a frost aura.
Everything's going to get one shot anyways, including me. 40% of Durial's damage is cold.
That's what I thought too. Okay. Are you ready? I'm calling it. We're doing summon resist.
It was vitality, right? Summon resist, 28% to all elements. And then it was vitality.
Well, this is the shot. Take it. What was it? It was, it was, no, it was vitality. Was it? No,
it was. It was. I remember. All right. Here we go. Blood golem on cue. Page open. No,
that's too distracting. Oh, get in. Get him. Holy shit. He's dead. Okay. Golem, get him.
Please drop the potion on the ground. Oh, that was something. I don't have a chance.
Well, hold on. Let me, let's. You think I can fight him one-on-one? I have to go one-on-one.
Is he going to one-hit kill me? He's not going to one-hit kill me, right?
All right. I don't. Is this doing anything? This is going to take forever. If I drop below
50% health, I'm running. I'm just spamming potions. Get him. Double team him.
Thaw, thaw, thaw. I'm in the corner. I'm in the corner. TP out of here. TP. This isn't
doing anything. I need skill. All right. All right. Here's the plan. I'm going to load the
fuck up on everything. I'm going to go in. I'm just going to spam him for a little bit. That's the
plan. If we actually, that's not a bad place to be because we're all going to be stuffed in the
same area. And maybe I'll take aggro. I need aggro for this to work. Hopefully he attacks me first.
I'd love any enemies on the ground. Didn't that kill? All right. Let's go back to tall of the
tomb. I just put on, should I just go get like a kite shield? Yeah. Let's go get the mercenary too.
Oh, also, by the way, I think he regenerates HP. Yes, he does. I need to just. Oh, these don't do
anything. This is a waste of time as a total waste of time. I need healing potions. Bonewall
is not going to do anything. I lose two points in Ray Skeleton though. If I just put on a shield.
I have 85 cold resist. From what? That's what thawing potion does. How long does that last?
I didn't even know if that's what that did. I thought it just instantly took cold off.
Oh, right. Okay. Well, they are worth it then.
Okay. Let's go to the waypoint and get a full army. He played Diablo 2 for 20 years and you
don't know what the items do. I've never purchased a thawing potion in my whole life ever playing this
game. There was never a reason for me to. I just didn't ever. All right. Let's get the team back
together. Aren't you guys glad you put a point in teeth? All right. We got the team back. Let's get
up. Five skeletons, three mages. Let's go get our mercenary back. And then there were 10 and I make
11. If I can get in there and tank this, hopefully we can do it. All right. You good? You good. You
got some pretty decent things. I have 12. All right. You ready? Three, two, one. Action. I'm
tanking them. I'm tanking them. Somebody pull aggro. Somebody pull aggro on me. Somebody pull
aggro. Am I going to die? All right. He's dead. We got him. We got him. We got him. Kill him.
Yeah. That wasn't that bad. That was fine. I'm scared for no reason. That was scared for no
reason. That wasn't even that bad. That was not even hard. That was not even that bad.
And seal. Hopefully this is good. Well, uh, let's one to golem mastery.
Read a bone sphere. It causes a monster to flee. Bone sphere is pretty good, but it's,
I, I, this character's, this character's all over the place. I can't even use
bone sphere. Step on the maggots. Does the one have a faster cast rate?
Also light radius. I have too much strength to have this be worth it.
Uh, there comes a loud cut scene, but this is going to be horrible if I keep doing this on
nightmare. Oh hell. I did expect you earlier. I am the archangel Tyrael. I came here to prevent
Diablo from freeing his brother Bale, but I have failed. Now terror and destruction roam free
throughout your world. Diablo's got a pretty good story. Diablo's got a good story.
Eastern capital of invincible, but their aims are, it is certain that they must be stopped at all
costs. This is stupid. And the energies that tie me to this world are diminishing. Okay.
Sorry. You feel that way to prevent the three brothers from reuniting the sea and search for
Diablo and Bale in chorus. Time is running out. Time is running out for all of us.
All right, let's go back 13 to 24 fire damage and a stolen loss of attack rating. Better than this,
right? Hmm. Slow attack speed. Can't can do this for free. The archangel Tyrael was the one who
gave the soul stones. Yep. This is terrible news. Bale is in possession of one of them.
Let us choose your weapons and that would be an absolute disaster.
I just, that wouldn't go over very well. I was going to act three and then we can do
uh, end of the string. Let's go. Please show stats and stuff. I will. I will show you exactly what
people have decided to do. Greetings. I'm the chief captain of this ship here. Jaren tells me
I play act three real, real quick. Um, no, I'm going to kill and Ariel one more time.
Just YouTube this cut scene. It's fucking, it's pretty good. Greetings.
Welcome to Karaz traveler. If you come willingly to this ancient city anymore,
I hope you brought your wits with you for sanity is in short supply here.
The Fisto is running rampant on here. This is lore. Yeah, but it's, it's 20 year old lore.
It's 20 year old lore. So I just want to speed this up because I, it is getting late.
Okay. We'll go over a full, what happened in Diablo two.
The potion guy has a lot of money. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. Let's go kill on Dario. I'm going to try to do as fast I can. Why would you want to,
why would you want to watch act three? Good question. All right, let's go.
Why does it look so weird? All right, let's go quick quickly. Wait, if you play the game on
single player, does it, can you act, can, is this, do I need to see this for the rest of the,
really? I went the wrong way. Uh, usually if you reset a game, doesn't it? Uh, I thought that it
reset the dungeon too. You have to exit the entire game. Oh, so this is, I'm not, Dario's
not going to be down here. That's only on D-Net if you close the game. So is Dario not going to be
down here? He is going to be. Oh, well that makes this way easier. Holy shit. All right. Wow. I
thought that was going to take a lot longer. So you can just farm the fuck out of bosses on single
player. All right. Get in there. There's also no lag either. So even though his shadow band from
battle net for some reason, uh, actually not that concerned about it because when you play it on old
D-Net, sometimes the game would just hang for five straight seconds and that happened all the damn
time. It was this weird, like half second lag on everything you did. So actually I'm kind of glad
I am playing it on here. Change to eight players. Not a bad idea. All right, we're good. You guys
would like to see the original loot box, but no further than what I'm doing right now. This is
free. Oh shit. She just killed my friend and we're gonna get, ah, too bad. Too bad. 21.
It's a junk. Do we get one more time? Oh, okay. One more time. Do one more time. One more time.
That's it. One more time. That's, that's actually it. One more time. That's it. That'd be 30 times
done. And that's it. And I'm not doing act three. No, it's 10 fucking hours. No, I'm not.
We're going to call it. All right, let's go. I want to open another loot box. I just want to get one
more unique. You know what I mean? I swear to God, this is the last time. This is not happening.
Actually true. Not happening. Not going to happen. Just, I figured it was going to take me like at
least 20 minutes to get over here. I didn't realize I could keep doing this until we reset
difficulty. That's awesome. You said I've been Lord of the Rings. No, this is different though,
because with the Lord of the Rings stream, I wasn't planning on streaming the next day.
I'm streaming today. I'm streaming today. So I'm done after this. All right, let's go.
You've got kids to take care of. It's not too bad. We're good. Don't get fucking, I can still get
trapped and killed. He used just waking up now. This is it. We're going to get a decent
unique right here. It'll carry me all the way through act three and then we can beat normal.
Hell. Hold on. There's an extra strong here.
Soul sludge. You're going to sneeze. I just got slapped in the face while I sneeze.
No, it's like, don't sneeze. Don't do it. Somebody just fucking cracked me.
Get in there. Kill. Oh, don't, don't fucking come after me. Don't fucking come after me.
Unique. Fuck. Fuck. All right. I'm out. Save. Just leave. See you tomorrow or later today,
whatever you want to call it. That was a lot of fun. I did not think I was going to get that far.
I thought that we were going to get destroyed. I thought I was going to make it through the first
two hours of the game, but it turns out still going. That's pretty good. We'll have to continue
that. So before we play that again, I'm going to try to do a better way to have you guys interact
with that instead of having weird images pop up on the screen. Good old fashioned coward strategies.
They work every time. Have you ever tried hardcore? That's not, that's the first time
I've ever played hardcore in any of the Diablo games. Never done it, but I thought it was great.
That was fun. Was it fun to stream? Yeah. I mean, games like this are easy to stream because,
I mean, yeah, it's hardcore and I don't want to die, but the menial minute to minute is we can
just talk about whatever, just chill and just do whatever. Nice change of pace. Game was just
playing itself, but let's, let's do the bits. I'm going to go through these fairly quickly
for obvious reasons, because it's getting very, very late. I'm not going to do it super duper,
insanely fast to the point where I blow through everyone's donations, but fast enough where we go
bing, bing, bing. And then tomorrow, I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow.
I have to talk to Joel. We'll see if tomorrow's going to be keep talking or it could be the next
day after that. I will let you know before the stream starts tomorrow. You will know.
All right, let's go. We had a thousand bits from acidic vengeance. They say for your Diablo 2
unban fund. Still can't believe that. I'm crazy. And I found that out 20 minutes before the stream
started. Oh, well, got like a scratchy voice today too. I don't know what's going on.
You can drink plenty of water. Weird. Thanks for the thousand bits. Potion dweller, thanks for the
250. Congrats on duping chat into one giving you necromancer, two giving you summons instead of
worthless curses. You may actually win this without dying now. Chat, I'm very disappointed
in you for not going throw barbarian. So many classes and so many combinations would have been so
terrible for this. Yes, potion find barbarian would have been the absolute worst thing possible.
I wouldn't have any moves. I would have to default click on people. This sucked.
A B Joe gave five thousand bits earlier. We, I think we said we talked about it, but they said
here's a pad, there's a paste bin here. It's a dream. Holy shit. This is long. I got a dream for
you. Let's see. Let me, this is very long. What happened? What did you eat before this dream?
Okay, I'm going to go through this because this is actually interesting to me.
I had a very odd dream the other night. This might be kind of long, but please bear with me.
It was evening and I had come home early. You had set up some sort of obstacle course at the
beach with all sorts of odd challenges. You're at the beginning of the obstacle course, ushering
people in with a big grin. When I tried to initiate a conversation, you ignored me.
I decided to carry on. There are many obstacles in your course. One of them, you had to drive an
actual train down some cartoon tracks at speeds that would in no way allow that train to remain
on said tracks. And in another, you literally just had to bend down and grab an empty can of
Monster Ultra with sunglasses drawn on paper taped to them and hand one over to Gabe Newell,
also wearing sunglasses who was apparently running that segment. After that, you had to slide up a
water slide to the top, which was about 50 feet tall and had to jump into the ocean to get back
down because landing in water doesn't give you fall damage. There were other people there also
attempting to complete your obstacle course, although I don't remember much about them other
than the fact that they were there. I was going through a, these dreams are becoming creative
writing exercises. Sorry, stop for a second. Where are we? Where were we? I went, I was going
through, okay, a jungle section, jungle gym section that you would find at one of those old McDonald's
play places. And I saw the kid in front of me go through a clear thin plastic roof above me
that had air holes poked in it. I asked him how he did that. And he asked me if I had the right
version. I said, I didn't know. He told me that I needed the right version of the map to continue
this section of the challenges. That was the way through. I had no idea what he was talking about.
So I did the only thing that came to mind and cut through the plastic with a serrated pocket knife
I had on my person, telling the kid to be careful as he was still there, even handing it over at
some point, telling him where to cut as he couldn't see what he was cutting because we were on different
versions of the say of the game. After that, I had run into another obstacle later down the line
and the same kid showed up and asked me which power up I had chosen at the station at the beginning
of the obstacle course that you had manned. I said I didn't have one. He said you need to choose one
to complete the obstacle course. He then T posed over a pit of mud that was in our way. Not sure
what to do next. I decided that I was going to probably like going around probably wouldn't hurt
anyone but as soon as I did a bunch of germa sun surrounded me and forced me back on the path and
people behind me booed until I tried jumping over it only to fall to my death. It was at this moment
that I had awoken in my bed in a cold sweat. I keep a dream journal so I wrote this down as soon
as I could and looking back on it now I think it looks like I had a stroke or something.
Looking forward to my second go-around hopefully next time I can get past the mud pit.
Fake dream feels weird.
Dreams are so fucked up you never know. It could be completely real. That sounds pretty
that could be accurate. Keeping a dream journal is the most fun things you can do. Well you heard
the dream about the tigers in the plane and shit like that. The only reason I even remember that
happened is because I wrote it down. So yeah I didn't did this this wild shit happens. Snarbosis
thanks for the 10 community subs. 20 from Zap. We caught Zaps I remember that. We didn't see
Snarbosis. Thanks both of you. Friedl Schlitz. Thanks for the 250. Can you tell me to stop
procrastinating and go do my homework. Oh yes get out go go get out of here go. What are you
doing still here? Oh wait this is like eight hours ago. I hope you did it. I hope you did.
Futanari thanks for the 1500 bits. Yay mountain stream. Potion dweller thanks for the 250. I
apologize to chat as it's clear they wanted to keep you alive. Now that's out of the way you
owe to yourself to try Path of Exile. I've played Path of Exile before. I do not like it. The reason
I do not like it is I do not like the camera. I think the camera I don't like it's kind of close
and too high. It's one of the only pet peeves I have of the whole game. I do not like the camera
in Path of Exile. That's it. I've tried to play it two or three times now. Sad camera noises.
Remember you just said a porn term. What? I don't know. How am I supposed to know what porn terms
are? Okay whatever whatever. All right fine fine sure. All right. Havgon thanks for the 250. Hey
Mr. Albertson. Chat keeps telling me to watch the streamer called German985. The stream is bland
and his fans only like him because they have Stockholm syndrome. Watch this other streamer
called BF Bugleberry instead. He only does 11 minute streams. Now that the joke is over I think
you should watch Jojo at some point. Also watch Redline. We had a long conversation about Jojo.
Listen to my voice right now. This is kind of fucked up. Why? I know you just heard like an
explosion or like a gunshot in my room. That was a battery. Nine hours? No it was like this before
too. It was like this like six or seven hours ago. It's my throat. I can I can feel it. I don't know
why. Oh yeah we talked about Jojo already. My anime for 2020 is what was it? Ping pong. Yeah
that's what it was. Ping pong. We deliberated for a while. Incendiary thanks for the 10 community
subs. Appreciate it. 10 subs. A lot of money. People drop five and ten subs in this channel.
Dozens of times a stream. Just 10, 10, 10, 10, 5, 5, 5, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 20, 20, 20.
You guys are really fucking generous. Thank you. Cell juniors thanks for the 500 bits. Sending
love and support to all trans people in chat. Very good. Thanks for the 500 bits. I appreciate it.
All the love. Thanks for the 500 bits. Espada Escalada 250 doing this for the channel points.
What do you mean channel points? 250? What do you get? You get channel points for giving bits?
Is that how some of you guys have gotten to 75,000 so fast?
Holy shit. I didn't know that. Once a month. Oh okay. Oh that's cool. Phylactery gave $50 and
they said Germ of the Ridge is fucking $75. But Phylactery thank you for almost buying me a second
one. I need a second one. This time I'm gonna get the the chrome one. I like that one. I was
gonna get that one. There's another link. Where? Oh there wasn't. Oh my fucking god somebody actually
did. You guys getting this shit so fast. What a shitty fucking thing for channel points.
I'm realizing this now. What a bad thing for channel points. We will continue.
Hey but thank you Phylactery for the 5,000 bits. $50. Phylactery gives money. An insane amount of
money. Almost every single stream. Every single fucking time. Thanks Phylactery again. And always.
Appreciate it.
No. It'd be a pan-seared salmon. Pan-seared salmon with lemon and oil. Good.
How would I drink oil?
Bananas are all I eat now. All day. Every day. 365 days a year. I eat sleep and breathe bananas.
Thanks again. You've changed my life forever. You learned that eating bananas is all you have to do?
Don't eat too many. You'll get radioactive. Deadly SP. Thanks for the 1,500 bits. $15.
Jeremy it's me Alex Cora. Why the hell haven't you answered my calls? Things aren't good Jeremy. I
had to step down because of you. You said no one was going to find out. You said it was going to
work out. The commissioner thinks I'm the one who came up with this. But I'm going to tell the truth.
I'm going to tell the whole world that you, German985, were the one who came up with the
sign stealing. Even your buddy Chat can't stop me. You won't. I gotta go out of this. Half the people
in this chat don't know what you're talking about. I do. Zeroni thanks for the $10,000 bits. Jeremy
it's Andrew from Ridge Wallet. We're having trouble with the corporate account so we're disbursing your
first payment in bits. The whole team is looking forward to your next endorsement. Thanks for the
$10. It is like a nice wallet. It's clean. It's sleek. I know there's a buzzword for when you
bought something that was expensive but I really do like these and I've used stuff like this before.
I've used a wallet that was supposed to be a little tiny little steel wallet before
and I think it was a piece of shit. This thing is not a piece of shit. Clean. It's nice. High grade
steel. Hey oh wait wait wait wait wait. Those of you that have been to Las Vegas that took me up
on my go-to hash house of gogo in the link and get the blue cheese burger. I know at least six or
seven people have done that over the last year and what did they come back and say? What did they come
back and say? Oh that that was the best that was the best thing I've ever eaten in my life. So I'm
not bullshitting here. This is a good wallet. You can trust me. Trust me. Blue cheese is gross. I'm
sorry. You don't have to apologize for being incorrect. You just have to be feel ashamed
in what you said was wrong. Thank you too. Oh we had another one. Mr. Mr. Goido thanks for the
$2.50. I had a dream that Jerma drank his own piss on stream haha. Oh my god why are there so many
of these today? Look how annoyed I look. Hey it's been 10 hours. We just crossed 10 hours.
Uh let's get the credits on screen. I have no idea what's gonna happen tomorrow.
Hopefully I wake up. I should. Money changed this guy. He used to be so fucking nicer. He was so
much cooler. He didn't have ridge wallets. He didn't drink Fiji water. He didn't buy original
hardware to play his Wii games on. I don't even remember the last time that I heard him sneeze.
Come on. Come on. Damn it. Oh that would have been funny. It would have been funny. It seems
it's coming on. It's okay. That would have been fun. Uh let's get the credits rolling. Like I said
before thanks for all the subs everybody. That dream is really fucked up. Old Jerma would have
sneezed. Yeah we'll see what we do tomorrow. I gotta um let me look. If me and Joel don't do
anything tomorrow and we do it the next day it's not much good shit over here. There's so much
good stuff over here. I don't even know what to choose. There's so many good games. Deadly creatures
for the Wii. We play the fucking scorpion. I don't know. We'll see. We'll figure it out.
Uh but anyway the credits are supposed to be on. What the hell am I doing? Is tomorrow gonna be
more D2? Uh we'll probably take a break from it. This was a long session here. So uh 10 hours of
Diablo 2. I don't want to have Diablo 2 exhaustion. We will probably do Diablo 2 again um at some
point this weekend probably. Why are the credits not rolling? What time's the stream gonna be
tomorrow? Well I have to eat. I'm probably not gonna get to bed till about uh I'm probably not
gonna get to bed till about three. So I don't think this is gonna be like a 1 pm or a 12 pm stream
tomorrow. So I gotta talk to Joel too. Is Joel is uh is he streaming? Streaming right now? Okay.
I wonder if he said anything on Discord. Let me just check. It's not rolling. I'm getting
set. There they are. And they're incredibly fast. Glory. All right uh let's see. Anything on Discord
from Joel? Thanks again everybody. Seriously. Another long one. But this was long because I
was kind of addicted to the game. Uh last thing that we said was. Let me see. We said uh I just
have my computer upgraded. I have a ton of issues. All right so we'll see. I'll be around the next
few days. All right yeah we'll let me just hit him a line. I'm gonna say I'm gonna be around
tomorrow the next day whatever's better for you. And then we'll go from there. Uh bits just came
in right now. Or a couple minutes ago. It was uh Flugboy. What's going on Flugboy? Thanks for the
thousand bits. Ten dollars right at the end here. They say hey Jerma gonna drop you some moderately
sized bits tonight. It's always kind of weird to me that I've been watching you for this long and
it's always wonderful to see new people. I agree. I love seeing new people. It was this huge Destiny
puzzle that came out recently and it brought literally the entire community's heads together
and it kind of reminds me of the hive mind that is chat that pulls together to just poke some fun
of you. It's really amazing. Keep up everything you do. It's always nice to talk to you. That's
part of the fun. Thanks a lot Flugboy. That's part of the fun though. The splendor of the piss Birky.
All right good night guys. I'll see you tomorrow. Whether we do uh keep talking or something else.
I'll be around tomorrow afternoon. Once uh I figure out what's going on,
this stuff will be updated accordingly and I'll see you tomorrow or later today.
Good night guys. Take care. See you soon.