Yeah, Megaton, I know. I know, this is the town. Seven years ago, I would have been,
well, what's this town? You blow it up, or you don't blow it up. I know, I can't wait.
Hey, Dr. Church, I really appreciate it. Thank you for healing me. Have a good day, and may
the Force be with you, as they say in Fallout 3, and maybe may the Force be with you. Take
it all, take it all, take all of it. Take literally everything on his fucking desk,
take his drinks, take his whiskey, take his fan. Give me that, give me everything, take all, take
it all. Activate the terminal and fucking just fuck up his computer too. I seriously can't help
myself. Why would I need utensils? What? Oh shit, they sent me to take their fucking silverware and
plates and stuff. I gotta get out of here. I'm sorry. Give me the fuck too. I'm such a fucking
kleptomaniac. I have to take everything. I'm sorry. Give me this light. Give me that book.
Open up. I don't even know what's in the fridge. Give me all of it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please
don't kill me. How are the noodles? Are the noodles any good? They're pretty good. What?
No, I was trying to eat the noodles. I wasn't trying to steal the noodles. Are you serious?
Do I have to pay for them? Can I get a drink around here?
I'd like to report someone.
Okay, you've been very helpful. Thank you. Okay, how do I put my gun away? There we go.
See, I'm no threat. I'm threatless. You guys just on me, huh? The guy told me to come in here.
I don't understand. Wow, that's a lot of stuff. That's a lot of stuff. That's a lot of things I
can do. Activate the vat system. Right in the head. Did bullets even come out of the gun?
What? Wow. Wow. Wow. Way too many. Way too many. Fuck it. We're going for it. It broke. It broke.
They broke it. They shot it out of my hands and it broke. Why are they fighting? Why are they fighting?
Who told them to do this? Did I? It's the lady. All right, one guy is just watching this shit.
Kick his ass. Come on, Dr. Lee. And your winner by knockout, Dr. Lee. And your prize is to watch
this guy fucking die. We gotta be smart about this. We gotta move. We gotta move quickly
because they're after us. So let's go. I don't want any dilly-dallying. Hurry up.
Assault. Assault. This guy's assaulting me. What does she have for a weapon right now?
Is it a flashlight? Watch out for the barrel. She just rocked the guy.
You sadistic murderer. Your co-workers. Because I shot somebody with a gun.
Fear. Somebody just like blew up over here. Oh boy. They're like evil farmers. Are you serious,
guys? What the fuck was that? What are you guys doing? Okay, two very important questions from
what just happened right there. Number one, why are you running at a guy in power armor
with a baseball bat? And what teleported through space-time in the sky? A spaceship from outer
space landed right in front of him and a big green alien jumped out and started eating people.
And what did our hero do, you wonder? He came up with the most cleverest of clever plans.
Sticky look. If we're gonna go through this journey together, you're gonna need to shut up. What?
Once upon a time, there was this dog. His name was Holy Toledo and he was really powerful.
And one day, these giant super mutants attacked him and tried carrying him off.
And what did our hero do, you wonder? He... That was a great story. That's the town right there.
I just gotta hit the remote detonator, blow the town up, and I get my cut from you two clowns?
Okay. Well, I guess I probably should have told you this before. That I'm a fucking double agent!
Okay. You are just looking all over for me. No need to hide. It'll all be over soon.
I'm not gonna come out of stealth. I'm not an idiot. When you turn up,
you're dead. I didn't know they could even have rocket launchers.
Level up! I don't know. I'm not really lost. I don't really want to report anybody. Yeah,
River City is run by a council. Yeah. Oh, there we go. Okay. Yeah, I think there might be ants in
my room. Bye. Hey, can you check it out for me? Thank God I found somebody because I seriously
have no idea, like, who I was even supposed to talk to about this. Yeah, so, I mean, I think I
might have left some food out. That might be what happened. We did have a party here last weekend.
I know we're supposed to report on all of our parties, so I'm just letting you know.
And there was, like, maybe eight people here. But I'm sorry, I don't...