All right, so let's see. I got fucking wiped out. Do Family Feud? All right, that sounds like fun.
The one for the Xbox? Please no. What? Well, maybe we'll save that for Connect.
Play something new? I did that today. Do more Ancestors? I don't think I'll ever play that game
again. If I'm completely honest. What should we do? Let's see. What are my final thoughts?
Final thoughts on Ancestors? It was, okay, there's a lot going on in the game. They kind of dark
souls you and you're supposed to figure it out, but at the same time they tell you a bunch of
stuff to do. And then on top of that, it's kind of hard to even play it in the first place.
That it's a cool idea, but execution wise, I mean, it was just kind of all over the place.
Talk to Transformer? Yeah, you know, let's do that. Let's just talk to Transformer for like an hour or
two. Not that long. Maybe if they patch it, they may, I don't know. It just, for every interesting
idea that game had, there was something that was equally just stupid. That I just, I was like,
what the hell? Why is this even here? That's my real opinion. All right, let's, let's do some,
let's do some fucking voice work. What do you say? For every good idea, there was a tiger. Yeah,
but even if I was supposed to stay up in the trees, a ton of that game is down on the ground.
You know, you're going to drink water. You can't get water from a tree. I've got to go pick up
fucking sticks and stones. I didn't even know about the whole like evolve through the times.
I thought that the, I don't even need, we don't even need to talk about it. It was a very fun
idea. Very cool stuff. I just, I just don't think you'll see me playing that game again.
Interesting concept though. Interesting concept. Okay. So I'm going to get this on. Let me turn,
let me, am I like fucking ugly for a webcam? Let's see. Let's see. Let's see how fucking weird I
look. What's wrong with the camera? Well, it'd be nice if it was plugged in. Why is this not
plugged in? That makes no fucking sense. 800,000 years of evolution. All right, let's take a look.
This is bright as fucking hell. Jesus. All right, I'm going to put on Talk to Transformer and talk
to it because that's what you do. Hello. Oh, wait a minute. You got, I got to turn off the
desync here. All right. Carve out the responses that I will. I'm just going to do this for like
an hour. Do tier lists? Um, I feel like that'll take a while. I think I only really want to
stream for like another 30, 40 minutes, but I didn't want to just end right there. Did I kill
anything yet? No, I didn't kill one thing in the game. Oh no, actually that's not true. All of my
monkeys died. So I technically did kill them. I guess in a technical sense. Okay. 18 of them
to be exact. Yeah. All right. I think I've gotten over it. Let's open it up. Here we go.
I'm going to cover up the responses. Well, not all that. To make it so you can't see.
So in case something fucking bad comes through, we can just get rid of it.
Like that. So for instance, let's just curious to see what I make sure nobody can see what's
going on down here. It's taking a while. Okay. So you can't see it. Only I can. So that's just
made that up. Let's go with, oh, I gotta change the name of the game too. I can see everything.
No, you can't. Chilling with transformer. Put it into IRL because that's what we're just doing.
Hanging out. There we go. Not playing that game anymore. Let's go. I've said, let's go like five
times. All right. How about this? Okay. This is, this one is just kind of, just kind of good for
you to know. Balloons tower defense is what you should play. However, if you do decide to do play
tower defense, you will want to focus your energy on a few things. Leveling. The following guide
will show you what you should be doing at the start of your level. Make sure to take into
account when using the first upgrade that you should be spending some of those extra points
on if you'd like to spam kill. Keep this guide as a guide, not to tell you how to level up
your character, but more to give you some pointers. Level 10. Level 19. Level 27. Level 34.
Level 39. Level 44. Level 47. Not very many tips on how to play. Once the required level,
once there's the required level and you've got the level up, you've really the time to get to grips
with the rest of the game to spend some time with the gameplay mechanics before we get into actual
gameplay. There are some things you'll want to do early on as a beginner while the basic abilities
aren't particularly fun. That's it. Those are pretty solid balloons tower defense tips. Okay,
I need some music too. Get some tunes on. Okay, let's try this one. What's this website called?
This is TalkToTransformer.com. You punch in a sentence or a word and it'll make a full
fucked up randomized AI story for you. This is going to be really loud so let me turn it down.
Okay, so let's get the music going. I'm going to get off cam for this because
people are reading in here. Please be quiet. I'm serious. As they were thinking, the people who
were supposed to be reading in the room at that time fell silent. The people who seemed to have
been in there for some time, the children, the staff, and the people of the academy,
all of them felt as if they were in a kind of trance just like they had when they were sleeping,
not knowing what to do. What did I do? Why were they all asleep like that? I guess I must have
been quite noisy the entire time. I just have to make it a calm, serene atmosphere so that the
people inside can do their business safely. The place I was thinking of was the study room
where the disciples of this academy lived, but how many children could I hold in my arms?
Even if I tried to, I couldn't bring more than one at a time. When I thought about it, I realized
that with a total of four, I could not have more than four people. With a troubled expression,
I approached the people inside. More than an ape-children armor. Oh my god. And then what?
Who knows? Let's see. There you go. With a troubled expression, I approached the people inside the...
Hold on. Okay. I'm going to try this one. With a troubled expression, I approached the people
inside the carriage and told them to put the clothes off. Are you tired? Yes. While I spoke,
Anne, who was standing in the back, started to dress herself. She was holding her arms
with an embarrassed expression. Anyways, it's fine. You just ignore this and go back.
Why are you treating me like this? Don't you agree? I'll be going, so you just have to ignore it for
now. I thought of a good plan that made use of Anne's good mood and headed to the next carriage.
I told Anika to stay where I am, and she returned. I'll be going back immediately,
and then I'll be leaving once again. By the way, Sirius Kun. Can we let that cat in the carriage
since he has a strange appearance? Sirius Kun. I don't... I don't have... I have nothing to say
about that one. Let me move this a little because it's kind of screwed up. There we go.
Okay, by the way, Sirius... We'll do this one too. By the way, Sirius Kun, can we let that cat in the
carriage since he has a strange appearance? He is... Keep going. Let us play balloons. By the way,
Sirius Kun, can we let that cat in the carriage since he has a strange appearance? He is also
not a human. I also need to look into the cat. Yeah, let's have him. It's okay because it is
dangerous, so I don't want to worry you. I looked at the surroundings and looked at Sirius Kun.
I had a feeling that it would become a problem since the cat is going to get eaten if Sirius
Kun and that cat continue to fight against each other, but I don't have an idea in regards to a
strategy yet. It might be better to show a different side of Sirius Kun and leave it be. Well,
I wanted to make him feel the fear of this cat. I wonder if maybe he can feel a little bit of fear
at that moment. After all, I am the one that is the prey here. Well, I'll see you soon, Sirius Kun.
Leave it. This is just... I don't... Okay, this is... Garfield versus German NA5 in a steel cage,
the main event of the night pitted the two best female wrestlers and the winner of this one would
go on to win the WWE Women's Championship at SummerSlam. The show wasn't great, but I'm sure
the real reason Fox decided to stage it in a gym was just to look good. Hope you guys enjoy this.
Feel free to leave comments on the video and let us know what you think of it in the forum. Fox.
Okay, this one's gonna be funny.
I was on the forums last night and I heard about that WWE main event,
so I had to watch it on loop last night so I could post up a list of the names that were
called up or put up. So who's the best of the lot? In no particular order. Here's a breakdown.
CM Punk won the Raw main event with a steel chair hammer pile driver finish over Batista
in one hour and seven minutes. He followed that up with a drop kick on Batista off the top rope,
dropping the champion to the mat again. Batista came back for three and that's where things got
weird. I'm still waiting to hear from WWE and if I have a response I'll give it to you.
For now if you're upset that Batista got that far, take a deep breath and take another walk
down the hallway. Tom Brady versus Clayton Custer versus CM Punk versus Barry Smith.
That was a pretty fun match, but what really stood out was the action on the outside.
Tom Brady
who is Barry Smith. I watched it on loop last night to be able to write it down.
Okay, let's get, ladies and gentlemen, here we go. Tom Brady versus Clayton Custer versus CM Punk
versus Barry Smith tonight at 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time,
8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern
time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m.
Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, at 8 o'clock Eastern time.
Put your TiVo on for 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 o'clock Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time,
8 o'clock Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern
time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern
time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.m. Eastern time, 8 a.
Brand Bay Brewing's Bourbon Barrel-Aged Imperial IPA. Brand Bay Brewing's Double IPA. Let's try that one. Brand Bay Brewing's Bourbon Barrel-Aged Imperial IPA.
This one's like, I don't know. Hold on. Is this a real place? Okay, here we go. Brand Bay Brewing's Bourbon Barrel-Aged Imperial IPA.
Brand Bay Brewing's Bourbon Barrel-Aged Imperial IPA, pictured above, is a dry-hopped imperial IPA that's a massive addition to the brewery's lineup.
And it is now available at liquor stores around Austin. We visited the distillery early in June and drank it in all its pungent golden glory.
We caught up with Brand Bay CEO Sean Colony via email to talk about this beer, what was going on at the distillery, and how it fits in as a major addition to the brewery's lineup.
We've had a few beers from the brewery previously, but this one was by far my favorite. What was the process of coming up with such a flavorful and unique beer?
In order to create the bourbon barrel-aged imperial IPA, we had to create a beer that was as unique and special as the barrel.
It was so hard to find a beer that had that dry-hopped nature to it. Our original plan was to pair our bourbon with a special citrus hop called Cascade or Magnum.
Interesting, that's it. This is...I'm just gonna do it.
Having some trouble in the realms? You guys make up a large portion of the server population and we want to help you improve your gaming experience as well.
Here's an in-depth guide on how to fix a few minor problems.
The following list is just a very small list, with the caveat that the fixes listed herein aren't for every problem, but are all effective as a temporary fix for most people.
It's very important that you verify that your desired improvement can be achieved by simply adding a character or two to that server for a couple of minutes.
And in particular, that this does not cause a lag spike, freezes, or other performance issues.
If you're having issues with any of these, don't hesitate to leave a message. It'll help us to do our best to fix it.
Multiplayer errors.
If a character that you had set to offline is back online but after a brief time has passed, such as while another person is playing or logging out and back, you find that the other person has joined your game.
And then, nothing. Let's try. That image, hold on.
What the fuck? Wait, this is...this doesn't make any fucking sense.
Filling my mouth with way too much peanut butter. Filling my mouth with way too much peanut butter, I decided to do something crazy.
To my surprise, I managed to stop and write a paragraph.
I'd have a very bad day. If you want to stop and write a paragraph, you could use the pen and paper version on this exercise by clicking here.
Note that the pen and paper version is very basic, so if you want to be completely in control, you should use a pen and paper renewable device.
We'll start by writing a list of numbers on a piece of paper until we reach our goal.
After completing the list of numbers on paper, I made a commitment to do another paragraph.
The only way to get a straight answer in mathematics, I decided, was to write a paragraph and stop at that point.
It's not a new concept, but a math teacher, Mark Jacobson, explains that it's essential to know if you're on track.
I can't do it this time, though. I have to stop when I reach four, because it's infinity.
If I was doing the exercise now, I would feel a little peanut butter in my mouth.
Let them tell you a story. I like that phrase. Let them tell you a really horrible story, not me. Let them tell you.
What? This is fucking ridiculous.
So I'm going to go through this one slowly. Just just. OK.
I'm just going to read it. I'm only 16 and I was the last in my family to get married.
So imagine that. Imagine me. Imagine you get married to a man that just killed his whole family and the rest of your family gets on their knees begging you to take their daughter.
Why not? He'll ask you. Well, there's only one solution. Why not? Oh, they're all dead now. That's all I got.
I just went into the water and I drowned. It was the worst day of my life. What the fuck is this?
Now, tell me a good tell me a fun story. This is not even this is just stupid.
It's about mocha butter. Yeah, delicious. Oh, yeah. I love mocha butter. Mocha butter is delicious. That's it.
OK, here we go. Tell me a story, Grandpa. Who were you? I'm a student.
Well, I saw somebody get down on that leg and say, I'm a student. That's my son. That's my grandson.
And he just went, Oh, yeah. Who else would want that? He's right. He's a student. He's my son.
And then you get back to these kids and you're like, Oh, that's really nice to hear that he cares.
And you don't actually care. But it's like you see that you have some influence whether you realize this or not on the kids you spent a lot of time with.
And there's this whole thing where you actually care and you actually helped him out and try to help him be a good parent.
I remember this from my own kid. She was a good kid. And she has sweet little face and a little cute laugh.
Every time I spoke with her, she would smile and say hi. And I would get up and walk around her in a circle.
Okay, Grandpa. Time for bed, right? It's like 630 p.m.
That's right. Good night.
Grandpa is sleepwalking again because I'm sleeping in the same spot every single night.
I wonder if I'll get all and die. I got the feeling that he actually isn't the only one with that mentality.
The last time I checked the entire Mountain Dew is my favorite campaign was started by some kids in South Korea.
I wonder if he'd be all right with being dead. I wonder if people who think like this ever find ways to make ends meet.
Thanks to Nana-sama for the link. Reply or report the post.
I got the feeling he actually isn't the only one with that mentality.
The last time I checked the entire Mountain Dew is my favorite campaign was started by some kids in South Korea.
I wonder if he'd be all right with being dead.
I wonder if he'd be all right with being dead. Is that like an old man and then somebody talking about the old man?
Oh, God.
I can't. I can't. I can't do this one. I'm gonna, but just bear with me.
Mountain Dew is my favorite. I do have a small amount of dessert, half teaspoon in the fridge, but it is not as nice and soft.
It makes about 15 teaspoons of powder.
Five grams powdered cinnamon, one medium cinnamon stick, one vanilla bean, one teaspoon ground cinnamon, one half teaspoon ground cloves,
one teaspoon ground ginger, one fourth teaspoon ground nutmeg, half teaspoon ground cloves, the dry ingredients this time now,
one cinnamon stick, one teaspoon ground cinnamon, half teaspoon ground cloves, one teaspoon ground ginger,
one fourth teaspoon ground nutmeg, half teaspoon ground cloves, that's all you need.
And the liquids now, one banana, two cups water, I recommend a double boiler.
Sorry, I have something in my throat.
Two cups brown sugar, half teaspoon ground cloves, half teaspoon ground ginger,
one fourth teaspoon ground nutmeg, half teaspoon ground cloves, two egg whites, one cup of sugar.
My favorite is one egg white plus half teaspoon of salt.
Now for the sugar based ingredients, of course.
One cup white sugar, one third cup water, three tablespoons sugar, one tablespoon molasses, one tablespoon ground cinnamon,
two teaspoons ground ginger, half teaspoons of something else.
I have listed on the liquids of banana.
One banana and five cups of sandwich.
No one would eat that.
Make it? Alright, I'm going to make this.
I'm copying this.
Oh my god, the fucking five cups of powdered cinnamon.
Only makes 15 teaspoons.
Yeah, what, do you bake it? Do you cook it down?
Okay, here we go.
Oh no, here we go again.
The secret recipe for my famous pancakes, which make a spectacular addition to any sandwich,
and one of my favorite quick and easy breakfast items, in addition to the chicken.
The other ingredients are two to one eggs, two to one, two tablespoons of butter,
two tablespoons of balsamic vinegar.
You would not put balsamic vinegar in pancakes.
Alright, I'm going to try this again.
The secret recipe for my favorite pancakes, which make a spectacular addition to sandwiches,
and one of my favorite quick and easy breakfast items, in addition to the chicken.
The other ingredients are two to one eggs, two to half tablespoons of butter,
two tablespoons of balsamic vinegar, two teaspoons of white wine, one tablespoon of gravy.
Okay, I need some other music. That music is making me laugh. That's better.
Welcome back. How are you? Good to see you again.
Welcome back to Anthony's Kitchen.
Today we've got a very special show for you,
because I'm going to tell you something my mother passed down to me.
It's the secret recipe that my family has for pancakes.
That's right, the little dollops, the little delicious dollops that my mother used to call them.
By the way, these make a spectacular addition to sandwiches,
and are one of my favorite quick and easy breakfast items.
In addition to the chicken, the other ingredients you'll need are two to one eggs,
two to half tablespoons of butter, two tablespoons of balsamic vinegar,
two teaspoons of white wine, one tablespoon of grated parmesan cheese,
half teaspoon of kosher salt, one teaspoon of nutmeg,
half a teaspoon of ginger for a little bit of a kick,
two teaspoons of minced garlic. I thought I was going to sneeze.
I'm sorry, folks. One teaspoon of oregano, two teaspoons of lemon juice,
one tablespoon of vegetable oil. There's some salt in there.
I'm getting a sneeze, ladies and gentlemen. I'm sorry.
In a bowl, beat the eggs. Just any typical nonstick bowl.
In a nonstick skillet over medium flame, melt the butter.
After butter starts to brown and sizzle, add the eggs.
Pour eggs into the skillet and make sure the eggs are covered.
And add some vinegar. Bring the eggs to a boil.
Remove the chicken on a plate and cook the cooked chicken
on the bottom of the skillet until it's done.
About four to five minutes. This allows you to control,
if not remove, chicken completely where it lands on the skillet.
Bring the eggs to a boil is where I had a problem.
It wasn't even the chicken part. The chicken cooked the cooked chicken
is funny, but like bring the eggs to a boil is funnier.
God damn, that's fucking so stupid.
Boil your eggs. But you're cracking them in water?
I don't know, what does it even want me to do?
Damn it, man. Why do they all have to be like this?
This is not going to make a lasagna.
Ugh, I can't believe it.
I found my mother's secret lasagna recipe in the attic,
exclaimed the young hostess.
And I really have never felt better in my life.
She made it. I thought the best way to see it was to make it myself.
I bought a brand and then it was a challenge to learn to make it.
I took the challenge along with the ingredients.
First, I prepared five eggs and three pieces of white bread.
The eggs turned out well. In fact, the batter was actually just too light.
But the white bread was a great help.
I did make the same mistake as my daughter.
I added too many cheese.
The result? Too much.
With all sorts of strange and unpleasant taste to say the least,
but it made for a great lunch.
I made it without the eggs.
It made for one of my favorite lunches,
which we call the frozen foe because of its very good flavor.
The ingredients are as follows.
One pound whole wheat flour, three fourths cup, half cup of sugar,
one tablespoon of baking powder, sour cream.
That's the whole recipe for lasagna.
I wonder why it didn't taste very good.
You wonder why that wouldn't be very flavorful.
Because you essentially made shitty cookies.
How much sour cream does it even tell you?
It doesn't even tell you the amount of sour cream.
It just says to put some in.
All right, this is the last recipe.
Wait, there was no cheese in that recipe.
All right, the first part of this is fucking good.
Second part is just nonsense.
I found a treasure map to a recipe.
It was this one.
I found it in the book called The Art of Making Homemade Pastries.
If you don't like the ingredients, just use the recipe.
This I felt was very misleading.
So I took the recipe, turned it upside down,
and I still found it in the book,
as I just thought the instructions included a hint
to not use a whole box of dough instead of the package that was packaged.
To make it this time, I just used three cups of all-purpose flour,
two packets of baking powder, and two eggs.
I went with almond flour, but the texture of it was kind of like regular all-purpose flour.
I would say it was close.
It seems I have never quite been able to find this dough that comes out nice and stiff.
A few times I baked it on both the top and bottom first,
but then I realized it was the wrong color for such a thin crust.
I could not be more proud to be a huge fan of my new favorite bread
to add to my repertoire of treats.
Now, if only it would come where?
The best part about this one is this.
Oh, just use the recipe. This is really misleading.
So I turned it upside down and it was still in the book.
Like, that was gonna make it disappear?
Almond.
What?
Uh, okay.
Almond flour is disgusting.
That's a pretty big pee pants moment right there.
Okay, no more recipes.
Almond flour is disgusting.
I'm ashamed to have even had the pleasure of using it.
I mean, I know it's made from almonds,
but what does it taste like other than that?
It's very low in protein and the almonds take a while to dry out.
So this is a big waste of money.
It's also gluten-free, or rather, if you want to get fancy, gluten-free bread dough.
But you'd be more than a little disappointed if you made it.
This recipe for chocolate cheesecake flakes came from a local grocery store in my hometown,
and I've used it a couple times now.
They have a fairly large selection of recipes from some of my favorite baking books,
but one of the recipes I really enjoyed was this recipe for chocolate cheesecake flakes.
The ingredients were easily accessible and the quality of the cheese was very high.
I wanted to try a recipe that wasn't gluten-free,
but had high protein in the form of almond flour.
They come out perfect with a little tweaking of a few things.
This actually is real.
But I really enjoyed the...
I really enjoyed the recipe.
Let's see what... Holy shit, this food is gross.
Holy shit, this food is gross.
If it looks this bad, there is no way in hell that you're gonna eat it.
So it was a very satisfying experience.
My wife and I sat here and ate a couple of those hot dogs we saw on the street.
I love hot dogs.
They're simple and delicious, but are usually filled with stuff that makes your head hurt after a while.
I was really impressed with the variety of the various things in this.
I tried a few different options and, oh, were surprisingly good.
This is one of those places that you go when you need a little late-night snack
and don't want to take a table.
You'll be sitting near where the bar is.
I got here after the party was over and it was already a party of around 20.
This has become an established spot.
It's clean and the food is good.
Great for when you don't want to party but need a quick bite.
I will definitely be back to try their other items.
Came here to celebrate my husband's anniversary lunch.
They're eating off the ground.
They're eating, like, off the street.
There's nothing here.
It's too fucking goddamn.
Okay, okay, this one's fucked up.
Here we go.
No, this is too intense.
I will leave a bad review on Yelp.
Why did your restaurant get a bad review?
The other guy at the checkout got a bad review.
My review is way better.
How did a customer get a bad review?
I've seen the cafes of hate and have seen that it's a really good thing,
a place people can go and hang out and laugh at things that bother them.
But even the few reviews out there that are negative
can easily be summed up in the words of a person.
That wasn't funny.
Not too long ago, we've received the following comment to our article on Comedy Central.
I was laughing my ass off, but then I felt sick and went to get my medicine.
The pharmacist said she'd just be right over,
so I gave her a call and she was right,
and I walked out of there with the flu.
I was just so grateful they were still open.
That wasn't the end of it, though.
As people took it as a sign that you were not funny.
Not funny.
Our article on Comedy Central.
Nope, not doing that one.
Talk to Transformers, the website, if you were curious.
This is not...
It's just a bunch of...
It's a bunch of words.
This is not...
It's just words on a...
German985 just made it into the top 500 on Twitch.
The next step was to get his custom character created.
This time around, he started by writing text on the screen.
This step took many hours.
Then German985 received an email from one of the top Twitch streamers in the world.
He was asked by Twitch for his opinion and feedback.
The chat window above was filled with his responses.
It's great I see so many people having fun streaming,
German985 said, and his stream was live with no issue.
In the Twitch chat, German985 was asked by a streamer about his character.
This time a lot more questions were asked and some feedback was received.
There were questions about the appearance and the way the movement looked and felt,
to the height he could reach on the stage,
the timing of the sword swings, and so on.
German985 told about the last thing he thought to check
if there was a potential fix to the character.
And the first few minutes of the stream he had a small hiccup.
Don't even need anything else.
This is... I don't...
No, I don't...
What?
What the fuck?
This is fucking so dumb.
Alright, I'm ready.
We need some other music for this.
This one is fucking crazy.
Here we go.
I am slightly below average height, which I know isn't ideal.
I'm five feet tall and I can wear shorts and a tight athletic shirt
that shows the tops of my underpants and also shows my thighs.
Since there is no other way to show the legs without exposing my bikini lines,
I don't have to keep any of the rest of my skin out of public view.
However, I do wear a bra, which leaves my breasts exposed.
So I'm not able to wear a bra while I swim in a pool, swim or do gymnastics.
The only other option I have to show my nipples is under a t-shirt.
However, as you can see in the photo on the left, that t-shirt is mostly skin.
So there is a part of me that would like to show myself while I'm wearing it.
The next choice, swim or do gymnastics, is not an option for most of the ladies at my age or age range.
I've always loved the workout part of summer and I do love dancing and dancing in a bikini.
I understand.
The only other option I have to show my nipples is under a t-shirt.
However, as you can see in the photo, the t-shirt is skin.
So you don't have a t-shirt on.
That means you don't have a t-shirt on.
I wear a bra, which leaves me exposed.
Hold on, I need to scroll through this one.
Is this gibberish? So it's another gibberish one.
I am way stronger than everyone here combined.
Because you never ask questions, because you don't know how to answer.
You're an asshole.
That's your only weakness though.
You can't change anything.
Oh, but you can.
You just need to have more faith. You can help this person.
I'm just sorry that I'm a dick.
Why would someone like you want to help the person like me?
They just need help. They're doing fine without me helping.
I don't know. I never knew who this... I was helping. I never understood.
I don't know why someone wanted to help though.
How can I help them then?
There's nowhere else to go.
You're not helping them. You don't know this guy.
I don't know. I don't know what happened.
This guy has taken so much from me and I can never repay him.
The end. Gibberish again.
Wrong title?
Ancestors the Humankind Odyssey.
What the hell is the name of this game?
Ancestor the Humankind Odyssey.
Here we go.
This is my Ancestors the Humankind Odyssey review.
And this week, I'm going to be reviewing some of the great role-playing campaigns currently being created.
The campaign I'm reviewing this week is the One Night Stand, which you can read my review of here.
When the world and everyone within it is dying, it is up to the human species at the center of the universe to stand up to the forces of darkness.
And darkness to stand up to the forces of good and fight for a vision of what is right.
So there's no other choice than to go and get something to eat and stay warm.
Which brings me to this fantastic adventure in which players take the role of the characters in the fictional town of Shady Hollow.
And through the power of the human spirit, most attempt to get a job done.
And that, I say again, isn't all that different from a regular game of Call of Cthulhu.
So yes, you're playing a modern-day pulp novel.
It's the same basic concept of an ordinary person facing off against hordes of evil to achieve their own individual salvation.
Good review.
PogChamp. L-U-L-W-what-the-fuck PogChamp.
I don't know. I think it's like, I just play the game. I don't feel too much. It's just fun to be part of something that is fun.
You want to win? WWE.com.
And then, Pog. I want to win too.
But right now, it doesn't feel very good in the end.
It feels a little bit good to win every time, but then a little bit of pain later, but then it's fun.
Well, you've only been in this business for a year, so you probably aren't quite used to the grind.
PogChamp. L-U-L-W-what-the-fuck PogChamp.
I try. When I first started on NXT, the first week was probably the worst day of my life.
So that's one thing I try to learn from.
And also the whole, what are they doing out? What are they doing out when I cum this thing?
When people are on their last...
Is this a username though?
What? What?
Social media emotes. Some of the best in the industry.
Is this all like info for real?
It's an industry with a ton of people and some great people.
With over 500,000 accounts on Instagram.
It's way less. It's way more than that.
With over 500,000 accounts on Instagram, hashtags, videos, and photo albums under its belt.
The company has a head start on Snapchat, which hosts around 100 million accounts.
With a revenue of 4.8 billion US and growth in the US for the past two quarters of 2016.
At 17 and 18%, the success of Snap could prove to be a game changer.
Snapchat started as a photo sharing app for sharing brief photos of one's current location.
However, the company soon came under fire from critics who dubbed it revenge porn.
Snap launched its messaging service in 2012 and has since been rolled into its various media apps.
Including Snapchat, Instagram, and Facebook Messenger.
Its stock market value has almost quadrupled since its acquisition by Facebook in 2013 for $2 billion.
However, the company recently unveiled what appears to be a departure into another media category, video.
This is fucked up. This is so stupid.
Okay, here we go. Who has the best Snapchat?
And it's a picture. It's a picture by the NFL, apparently.
NFL picked up to international football league December 29, 2015.
The NFL was on a full Twitter snapping alert Thursday night.
Tweeting out the name and phone number of every professional football player in the league.
This has gone too far.
Hashtag NFL is not okay.
To Snapchat, to NFL, and get your name and number.
What the NFL is doing is giving a shout out to Snapchat.
The league's tweet has been blasted by many players of all teams, including some outspoken veterans
that could easily see the hashtag trending on social media.
So it made sense for the league to respond in full force.
Disrespectful is the word that springs to mind when you look at this tweet.
The NFL has done more disrespect by tweeting about the Snapchat app over a video than it's done by doing something else.
Tweeting out the name and phone number of every single player in the league.
Every single fucking player.
For what reason?
It's like, there's no reason to do that.
Hey, everybody, big football fans.
Hey, it's the NFL, the official NFL Twitter.
Here's the fucking personal information of everybody.
That's so bad.
This fucking thousands and this thousands of people in the league.
Oh my God.
And how do you tweet that out in one picture?
That is a sixty seven thousand by forty one thousand resolution picture.
You really have to zoom the fuck in.
And they compress it.
Two pixels for every player.
God, that's ridiculous.
Oh, the official NFL Twitter.
OK, let's try.
And I love how that's supposed to be a shout out.
They're giving a shout out to Snapchat somehow.
That's their shout out to Snapchat.
Hey, Snapchat, great to be a partner. Partner with the NFL.
I like these ones. These are fun.
You know, my favorite part about that is names and phone numbers.
Names.
I don't know, Tom Brady. Oh, I know Tom Brady.
OK, this is, this one is going to be fun to read, but it's dog shit.
Grandpa, tell me a story.
The boy goes to his grandpa's house for dinner and his grandpa tells him a story.
I'm sure he'll enjoy reading this and I'm sure I'll enjoy hearing it.
The boy is a little excited about the meal.
Grandpa is going to make him cheese, but the grandpa is just bored with the story.
A little boy is bored by the news.
Grandpa tells the boy something interesting and the little boy is happy.
His grandpa then goes to another room and tells the boy a new story and the boy is still happy.
A little boy is still happy from his favorite story.
The grandpa doesn't know what is to come.
The boy is surprised that his grandpa has no idea what's about to come.
A boy is bored with his grandpa's dinner.
The boy takes off running.
I don't know why, but I think that boy needs space.
The boy hears footsteps on the steps he left behind, I assume.
This is just like research data.
This one is also just like, just nonsense.
I just want, it's just, it's generating this over and over again.
It really is not though, it's not.
I completely disagree with what I just brought up.
Uh, Kraft macaroni and cheese is the best.
Kraft macaroni and cheese is the best macaroni and cheese I've ever had.
You really need to try it. I promise you'll go back for seconds.
I think this is my favorite macaroni and cheese I've ever eaten.
It's creamy without the cheesy texture.
And it makes for a great lunch with a veggie side.
I usually use the ground beef mixture to make a filling meatloaf.
I also love to make macaroni and cheese over a bed of lettuce
and use some leftover shredded carrots.
There's no reason you can't use some leftover vegetables and potatoes
with some of the vegetables from this recipe when you're making your meatloaf.
It's very easy to make something awesome over the top of meatloaf
if you make some additional layers as well.
My latest videos, the meatloaf is really rich and full of flavor.
I can't wait to eat it with an apple or cheese on top.
You can leave out the macaroni and cheese, it's really easy to make in a crock pot.
It.
Just leave out the mac and cheese, fuck it.
A larger model. What is that?
At least a larger model.
What does this one do?
Oh, it's already implemented, okay.
Is there a way? It's already in here?
They're not good.
This is not me, by the way. This is not the store.
I guess it could be.
This could be.
Alright!
Six Flags sucks.
But the food is good.
It's like a family dining table for my friends and family.
Our menu is small but the service is friendly and attentive.
We'll all do four courses tonight, please call us.
I went there in January and they seem to have been open most of the time.
Had a great ambience, good wine, great price.
And I felt like coming here was good for me because I'm pretty overweight and a dietitian.
So I'm not that big of a picky eater.
It's pretty small but we had a table and the waitresses were friendly and attentive.
So come on down to Six Flags!
Not a star for what they did here.
But we were there in January before Christmas and waited about an hour to be seated and was immediately greeted by a waitress.
I had a bottle of water so I got a glass of wine to drink and eat while I waited.
Service was friendly but somehow slow as there seemed to be a lot of staff.
I was also disappointed with the food.
This is the cheapest place to get a plate of food.
Okay.
What? Hold on.
This is not... Is this fake?
They're all fake.
What am I talking about?
This is the only funny line in here.
Oh god.
What?
Oh god damn it.
These are all so... This is gibbering.
No, no, no. You're not supposed to... We're not supposed to...
We're not doing the... We're not doing the Venga boys.
Okay, we are now.
Get on that bus!
Six flags eating contest with different styles such as the ones that look really neat with red stripes, yellow stripes, and black for the last one.
The second was for the 3D printed flag that looks like this and also the 1.7 gigabyte file where I show how it can be made in Photoshop.
The 3D printing process is similar to the printing process for the flag.
In case you're wondering, yes, the flag is made from cardboard for the same reason a flag from an archive folder is.
Step one, create a folder that contains two layers, one for the flag and another for the flag file inside.
Step two, I'm doing that because for the flag I'd rather keep it small and as simple as possible so that it's not hard to follow.
Step four, open the main.png file inside.
Step five, in your new folder you'll need to go to the two layers that are inside the flag file folder as shown in the picture.
Step six, go to step three because you didn't do it.
This is fucking nonsense.
Alright, let's try this one.
Unlucky.
Number 13.
What a terrible day.
But at least I'm not in a coma or some kind of superimposed vision.
You have no idea how much it means to me that my son is finally coming home.
He's a hard worker and was the one who taught me math.
He's a good kid, but he never seemed to get what life or the Internet was really about.
He played all the time.
He took the same interest in a game that everybody else did.
That was the only thing that made us a family.
Then his mom decided to get sick of the Internet.
She couldn't do any work, couldn't do any online shopping because the Internet had made her life unbearable.
So she gave up her job at the local grocery store, took the truck driver job, and she became a waitress to get some extra income.
And then she quit her job as a waitress and she went back to school because she always had something to do in school.
She finally made it to the point where she had enough credits to open an online account at work and did just that.
Yes, she did. And there's more.
And with these credits, she bought the necessary equipment to start her own business.
At that time, however, she still found employment as a cook.
When this job expired, it was easy pickets for other students hoping to get a job for themselves.
One of the best places to start is with an online site like this for entry-level opportunities.
For example, with online career fairs.
Aspiring chefs are a bit different from the ones I had grown up around.
For example, they are not only more educated but also more likely to earn the credentials needed to open a food service business.
To become the next generation of culinary experts, it is vital for them to get their hands dirty with real work.
In order to do this, they need to take their apprenticeship programs very seriously.
I met a lot of great people, including some of my colleagues at the Food Service Industry Association, during that internship period.
The people who took me under their wing were some of the most down-to-earth and down-to-earth people I've ever met in my life.
And that's when the accident happened.
Well, I guess the question is, who is it?
Anyway, this one was a bit odd to read.
I've heard rumors that it goes like this.
People that have a lot of money like to gamble.
The only way to do that is to have an umbrella.
I've heard that it's also a sign, a warning.
A sign to say something.
A sign with something to say.
But I don't remember anything like that at all.
Well, the question is, what does a couple of umbrellas stand for?
It depends on the year.
I would have thought of it, but it was obvious.
But if it was a couple of umbrellas, then I think the message was a little too obvious for me to think.
The question is, is it a sign from someone who wanted a warning of something?
And if so, is that a sign?
I feel a little more doubtful of the message being a warning than a warning from the person.
Is that a warning? What is it?
That warning.
Please, no, let me tell you this. It's my fault.
As she stood in front of him as through the shadow of the trees, the air around her was filled with the perfume of spring flowers and the grass was full of golden fragrant grass of the mountains.
You think there's trouble down at the other end of the woods that isn't even here a hundred years ago?
The girl asked.
And where, can you tell me?
We don't know.
Do you remember the forest?
She shook her head.
All I remember is the grass and everything else about it was so empty.
So empty.
We can't even be sure that it's still here.
Yeah.
It turned to walk away without looking back.
We have to remember.
There are people down here.
They're looking for us.
They're coming.
And then, as though she had imagined it, they appeared to be a different set of individuals, both in appearance and behavior, said police department chief Steve Priest.
It appears there are non-members of the public and we are looking at them as potential witnesses.
When asked if he thought that they may have fled the scene and gone into hiding, Mr. Priest said, I would think, I'd like to think it depends on when those guys got into the car.
If they're actually on board.
Oh, well, just get the ride.
Then the next day he comes back with a ride for $55.
Which...
Hey, Lyft can be crazy in these markets.
The driverless cars are now being piloted by hundreds of thousands of students and employees around the world who take UberPool in the US, UberX in Australia, GrabTaxi in Europe, Airbnb in Africa, and dozens of others.
The company has been rolling out its program using taxis in Europe.
The company has been rolling out its program using taxis in Europe for several months and is also rolling out a pilot program with private transport operators in cities like London.
It announced in late April that UberPool, a program where customers pay a flat rate up to $1 each way, to share with anyone could end this summer in Chicago.
A number of other governments, including the United Kingdom, the United States, and India, are now considering whether regulations that would ban companies from driving commercially on city roads will actually prevent self-driving cars.
Uber said in a statement on April 12th that it had not yet tested a self-driving car in London and would have to work with the city to make a decision.
The company is testing a cell...
Uber.
This is another fucking ridiculous one.
This one is just...
My Uber driver was insane IRL.
I was scared we'd get arrested and fined for speeding.
He was so friendly and friendly.
I felt so blessed to be the first picket passenger in my Uber ride home at 10am.
I never dreamed my Uber driver would be the most caring friend a person could ask for.
You are in need of a friend in an Uber or Lyft.
This is the guy.
I've had an Uber car for over three years.
I've had plenty of issues, but the one that made me take this last trip is so far the worst was with the driver.
He got upset and wanted me to leave his office.
He was very improved with me in person and had to get my money back.
I'm never returning and my phone is silent since I left Uber.
I had an excellent 3 out of 5 stars because of the quality of service of the driver and his demeanor of not being an asshole.
He was attentive to us and did not make me feel anxious.
That's all I could ask from Uber.
Overall, it was really good.
He left his office.
Fucking office.
Oh, another one.
My Uber driver was name is not on the record in the book.
What I really want is name on book.
So I called the police.
This was around 7pm.
They say I'm stealing name on book.
This was at a restaurant in my neighborhood.
I'm not a thief. I'm just a girl from the community.
I'm just going to try to stay out of more trouble.
They sent me to a police station and I wait out there like I'm a child at a birthday party or something.
They take my name. This music is very loud.
I'm also dropping frames.
They sent me to a police station and I wait out there like I'm a child at a birthday or something.
I fill out some forms and they send me my summons.
If you look at the map, you'll probably see a lot of white dots.
But the cops have my name and the time and the phone number.
One cop said I was an adult when I called.
I'm like, Whoa, dude, but it's not illegal.
If you were 16, you were not supposed to be calling the police.
The whole last one for Uber and Lyft.
I don't know.
This could be I don't know if this could be like factual.
OK, here we go.
We need different music for this one.
Uber and Lyft are a scam.
They have no business being on the roads in any city in America or the world.
And even in New York, they don't operate legally.
Uber and Lyft are just the tip of a giant iceberg iceberg of illegal, unsafe and unlicensed ride sharing services.
Here's why. Number one, illegal ride share rides to taxi zones.
As Lyft and Uber were introduced to the public with a media blitz in 2014,
their ride sharing platforms were just the start of a much larger illegal network.
From Seattle to Boston based Uber's ride hailing platform had been banned
and at least five other cities with a combined population of more than seven hundred thousand.
As a result, the average driver's annual earnings would be more than thirty thousand dollars.
Many cities are still enforcing Uber and Lyft regulations,
but they're often not the most fair way to run the business.
By allowing these illegal Uber and Lyft ride sharing services to operate legally in a city,
cities are forcing Uber and something else.
Okay, one more. What the fuck is wrong with my brain?
I'm not reading this. What the fuck?
All right, here we go.
My Lyft driver was crazy about Uber, said the man sitting across from us as he waited in the dark, sweaty traffic.
He was a real Uber driver.
Uber is a ride sharing app that uses a car to shuttle passengers around the city.
But as Uber became increasingly popular with riders,
it raised some eyebrows when it became partnering with ride sharing services instead.
And now for some people it feels like Uber is doing to ride share services what it does to taxis just without your fingertips.
The question then is how can ride share apps be made safer and more transparent in order to keep passengers safe
and Uber drivers less tempted to cheat their passengers?
We spoke to drivers like the one across from ours.
There are currently over two thousand Uber drivers across the country.
Many of whom have been with the company for up to six years.
We spoke with them about the company's culture and the risks they face and then asked them to share their experiences.
Lyft driver Dan for one believes that Uber and Lyft are a double what?
We need to know. This is just this is not even funny.
Lyft driver Dan for one believes that Uber and Lyft are a double edged sword.
Rather than giving their drivers a better sense of ownership,
a lot of drivers are still learning the ropes.
Gathering and self-driving vehicles are a risk to what we do.
And it's very important that we're not putting our drivers in harm's way when we're putting other in our vehicle.
Also, this company is supporting technology, self-driving vehicles that abuse public allow drivers to check the weather and take photos.
And at the same time, driverless vehicles literally take more and more of the taxis business.
And the biggest threat to our tax industry is that indoor use is declined.
But the future of driving remains far away because so far the markets don't have that one or two players.
We're linked to Google. This was like accurate.
All right, this is the last one.
Is this a bounty?
A bounty for talk to Transformers?
OK, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Thank God. I fucking go.
How the fuck do you spell this stupid thing?
I don't know.
I'm not reading another recipe.
No more recipes.
All right, this is the last one and then I'm going to get out of here.
We're going late.
This one sucks.
And then the monster peered around the corner, his hundred teeth grinning at us, blood dripping from his mouth.
The monster was a beast, a monster that couldn't be killed.
There was an old man, one who knew the town, and the old man came and told us,
These people will die if I don't do something about the monsters.
They're killing your kids and killing our old lady.
It's so sad.
He told us he was the local mayor.
He didn't like the goblins because he said the goblins would always be looking for someone to kill.
The people in this town were so scared that they would run out from inside to get away from them if they ever came near them.
But the old man said,
Let's do what the old man doesn't do and get rid of the monsters.
And so we did.
You might think that a town in the middle of nowhere doesn't fit in with modern society.
But in fact, it is a small, sleepy, sleepy village with many local businesses like bookstores and inns and small farms.
The first time I saw the monster, the story ended.
I tried to stop the monster, but his jaw bit down and killed me.
He let me go for a little.
I'll never forget that feeling of getting up after that.
Hearing that, the man paused.
Was he an arboreal creature?
No one's ever seen it before, but I think he probably lived in grass.
Grass?
This is the same land I've never seen.
They sat on the sand as they talked about their history.
They started their stories about how they got to where they are and where they will go next.
We left the palace a long time ago for the desert.
The man smiled.
Desert?
No.
After I got my hands on magic, I wanted to go anywhere in the world but a place as cool as Mount Olympus had just become too much.
I couldn't imagine not being able to see magic.
It was like the end of an era, the man said to himself.
What an era.
This is the end.
The end of an era?
All right, last one.
This is it.
I'm going to end the stream.
What a perfect one to go on.
Magic Mayor.
He has an incredible ability to not only tell you great stories about the game, but help you to develop games of your own and to become a part of the gaming world.
He loves it.
I'm having trouble with this one.
Let's get some of the music.
This is the last one.
A duck, a shoe, and a frog walk into a bar.
The bartender turns to the customers and says,
Hey, what's your favorite sandwich?
Ah, the stream's dead.
Hold on.
Let's do it again.
Let's try this one one more time.
A duck, a shoe, and a frog walk into a bar.
And the bartender turns to the customers and says,
Hey, what's your favorite sandwich?
The people sitting at the bar turn to the customers and say,
Your pizza!
But these days he's on a tear.
And he says he thinks he really can be the most important man in the world again.
The only problem is his customers aren't going to buy it.
The most important man in the world is a guy who doesn't listen, he complains.
You have to listen first.
And why should they?
The people in front of Mr. Trump, why should they take advice he can't deliver?
They'd be taking advice from the guy who's been on the front lines in the battle between those who are powerful and those who are more powerless from the guy who said,
Don't be stupid.
Be polite.
Be gracious.
And be a man.
They'd be taking advice from the guy who can't even be bothered to answer his own questions, I think.
Last one, I promise, from Kylo.
It was nice to see you guys again, though.
Before you start doing anything here, make sure to back up your safes before posting it.
Oh, a few notes before you start.
Get a fresh character.
If you have at least one character that wasn't in a full game save, make sure to add her.
Make sure to use the correct save file.
All other versions will show up with the incorrect version from you.
Last edited by xVacation.
Ahem, ahem, ahem.
Okay.
Coming soon to xVacation.
New and improved animation quality.
All new animations for the following skills.
Bashing attack.
Blunt attack.
Kick.
Lightning.
Lightning only.
Kick.
Stun.
Stun only.
Kick.
Bash.
Blunt.
Kick.
Bash only.
Flat.
Kick.
Bash only.
Stun.
Kick.
Stun only.
And kick.
Bash.
Animations for Sword Art Online 2.
The vast sea of clouds, the southern seas, and the east blue sea.
When animating characters in the southern seas, they will not have that area as a region
so they will animate in the ocean.
Please keep in mind this update is on patch v version 0.2.8.
The current live build is 0.3.4.3.
So it's higher.
Actual patch notes.
Interesting.
This is it.
I'm such an epic coder, I can smash all lines of code.
Python, Rust, C++, you name it.
I don't know why, but I don't have the time for code reviews.
You'd be amazed what I'd do with code.
I'm probably the only one in the world that can write code well.
And my code is always awesome.
I know the code is easy to explain, but I can explain it in 20 words or less and make
it understandable.
I like to write simple, elegant code so I can explain in more than 20 words.
But I think I'm going to get a C++ guy to help me out with my code review.
But what is there to say about that?
I think I'll go back to C++ in a month or so, at least.
I don't know.
But what is there to say about that?
I think I'll go back to C++ in a month or so, at least.
But I'm also a guy that needs to make money, right?
I'll fucking talk.
These are all fucking...
What?
Hold on.
What the fuck?
Let's try to process this one.
Fuck off, Jeremy, the bartender yelled and he started rifling through his pockets.
What kind of fucking bitch doesn't give money back?
Oh, I don't know.
Steve's face paled.
The fear was gone from him.
The look of disgust and rage was gone from his face.
He didn't even care about what happened right now.
He just wanted to get a taste of his own medicine.
Well, fuck me, this feels like a $100 bill.
Sir, would you mind if I handed over all of your cash?
Sirs.
Fuck you, Steve, roared his anchor rising to new heights.
You can't fucking steal shit you paid for out of the restaurant.
I gave you plenty of warning.
Now I'm going to break your fucking legs.
The bartender laughed.
Ha ha ha ha, he said, making his escape.
You have good manners as long as you're drunk and you'll think twice before you steal.
What happened here?
The bartender said fuck off, Jeremy, and stole money out of my pocket.
Sir, would you mind if I handed over all your cash?
Who said that?
I have no idea.
But that's it.
That's going to be it for me tonight.
We've been going for a long time.
So the streams this week are going to be kind of all over the place.
Because I have a couple of things I need to get done over the next day or two.
So what's going to happen is on Saturday, Star and I are going to do Terraria.
Friday, let's see.
So Friday, Saturday, Sunday is probably what we're going to do this weekend here.
That would make the most sense.
So nothing over the next two days.
Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
I want to probably start Mario RPG.
Remember we talked about that last week?
I'm assuming that'll start probably this coming weekend.
Probably Sunday or something.
Actually going to do it.
I think so.
But besides that, Star and I are going to try to finish the base game of Terraria this weekend.
Ancestor Part II.
I don't know if I can play Ancestor again.
It was kind of a little too all over the place for me.
I really want to love that game, but I can't.
There's a lot of random things in the way for me.
It was funny.
It was fun.
It was a fun, funny game, but a little too frustrating, I think, in some aspects.
But I'll see you guys on Friday.
Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
We'll do some fun stuff.
Connect will probably come back.
Yeah, Connect will probably be on Friday.
We will do a horror Connect night on Friday.
Saturday, Terraria.
And then Sunday, Mario RPG start.
I think that sounds like a pretty good plan.
But thanks for joining me.
Thanks for hanging out.
I'll see you guys on Friday.
Join me for more Connect.
And we'll get into the bits.
Let's go back to about eight hours ago.
Earlier.
We'll try to go through these fairly quickly because it is getting late.
It is 2 a.m. Eastern.
Later than that, even.
So let's start with Gnarly gave $2.50.
Thank you.
How come Twilight Summoner from Hearthstone has not been in a rumble yet?
He was your sub sound for a good while.
Do him justice.
Oh, yeah.
Wait.
What?
I can do better than that.
Wait.
What?
One of those worked.
Uh, there are a lot of characters that should have shown up in rumbles that never did.
But thank you, though, Gnarly.
Thank you, Master Chicken, for the $5.
The store manager that had a problem with my prescription medications got fired for trying to fire me for them.
So I can now continue slaving way to earn bits for you.
Also, I have a huge image for the Where's Waldo, and it's too big for Discord.
So you got one of those, like, huge ones.
Well, is it possible to maybe compress it a little?
But I'm really sorry to hear about that stuff at work.
Imgur?
Oh, yeah.
You can probably use Imgur.
What are we linking here?
What's this?
Auto?
That game was, like, so fun, too.
Like, it was so interesting.
Like I told you, there's a box of gold underneath all that sand somewhere.
There is.
I wonder if they patch the fuck out of it over the next, like, year.
Maybe it'll be, like, really fun later.
Who knows?
That's so funny.
But thank you for that.
And thank you, Master Chicken, for the $5.
Hopefully you get all your stuff at work sorted out.
Hey, Bitslay, thanks for the $5.
Hey, Jerma, I ran that nasty burger from last stream into Selfie to Anime AI.
What the fuck does that mean?
What?
Why did you do this?
This is actually pretty cool.
Selfie to Anime.
Also, please wish me luck as I am stuck at an Air Force base waiting on orders.
It's the worst Air Force base I've ever been to.
And I'm losing my damn mind.
Can you ask the President for help on my behalf?
Well, I do wish you luck.
I believe that doesn't take too much longer.
But thank you, Bitslay.
Hopefully you get some orders soon.
Thanks for the lovely Anime hamburger McDonald's double cheeseburger picture.
Hey, Miniclips, thanks for $10.
Our ancestors didn't have tutorials or HUDs.
Just remember that.
Thanks for the $10.
And yes, you're right.
Poo and Pee Party, thanks for the $5.
They say Stan?
And then Luna?
I don't know what that is, but thank you Poo Poo and Pee Pee Party, whatever your name was.
Poo and Pee Party.
Patrick Johnson, thanks for the $10.
Hey, Germans, I want to give a big thank you for the countless hours of entertainment you provided me.
I work a pretty dire nightmare office job here in Wales, but your streams always manage to make it bearable.
Thank you, Patrick.
Thank you for the $10.
I love streaming.
I love hanging out.
I love just making all kinds of fucking stuff.
What?
I got lost there in my brain.
I was thinking of the fucking Stan thing and I couldn't figure out what that meant.
And then like I was in the middle of talking and I ran into a wall.
But no, I love being here.
I love streaming.
Even though I didn't think the game was very fun and I wasn't doing very well in that fucking monkey game,
I still had a lot of fun playing it just because by its very nature, hanging out and, you know, talking shit.
And, you know, I don't really mean half of it, but it's still fun.
Making all kinds of stuff, you know.
Teleporting tigers are dumb.
Somebody that has time in that game that is more than like 10, 20, 30 hours.
Do you get like tigers spawned on top of you?
Does that happen?
I felt like that happened.
Or was I doing something wrong?
You weren't supposed to bring your whole clan out with you.
You were bringing out your entire clan.
That's ridiculous.
In one of the clips, the tiger literally appears from thin air.
It spawned right where you are.
Alright, I just wanted to make sure.
I still had a fucking fun time though.
Even though I like, I didn't even rage quit.
People were saying, you rage quit.
No, I didn't.
I rage died.
All of them.
Everybody.
All of us.
I think it was still worth playing.
But thank you to Patrick Johnson for the 10 bucks.
Glad to be here.
Buffalo chicken is probably my favorite party food, I would say.
And now I'm making myself hungry and I'm going to have to figure out what am I going to eat.
I think there's food in the fridge.
I'm going to eat it.
But yeah, buffalo chicken.
I'm a huge sub sandwich fan.
I love Italian subs.
I love buffalo chicken subs.
I love like steak and cheese subs.
I love like Rubens.
I'm a big sandwich kind of guy.
Pastrami, like a nice pastrami.
From a nice deli.
I would love to have my own deli.
I just, I'm not a talented fucking chef.
I would just be there.
I would just want to own a deli just so I could eat the food that like hire like a talented person to make it all.
But yeah, those are some of my favorite foods.
Thank you.
I don't even like Taco Bell for the $2.50.
Thank you for the $5.
I don't even like Taco Bell.
Hey Jerma, I'm not sure the emotes worked properly in my last donation.
Did you delete Jerma Hairy Buttcheeks?
I'd be awfully sad because Jerma Hairy Buttcheeks is my favorite emote.
Spamming Jerma Hairy Buttcheeks is the only thing I love more than spamming...
It's the backpack thing that I'm not going to read out loud.
And Jerma is mad and bald because I'm so funny.
I don't even like Taco Bell again for $2.50.
Hey Jerma, one last bit donation while I'm on break at work.
Can you drop a raid on Ital Chad tonight?
Seeing a bunch of hairy primates tonight reminded me that the notorious ETL doesn't get enough love in this community.
Jerma Hairy Buttcheeks.
That's not an emote, first of all.
I did not delete that emote.
So sorry to tell you that that's incorrect.
And second of all, Italics is not live right now.
So I can't do that.
But I'll tell you something about Italics.
I think the two of us are going to play something together real soon.
There's a game coming out.
It's like a two-person horror, like choose your own horror kind of Until Dawn game.
We're going to be playing it together.
I forget what it's called.
It's called like the Mad Land of Doctor something.
I don't know. Whatever it is. I have no idea.
I knew it if I would see it.
But it's like from the Until Dawn depth.
So yes, that'll probably be next week.
Whenever it launches.
Thank you Razzle for the 250.
Hey Jerma, the first video of yours I watched was Grandpa Runs a Fast Food Joint and I think it's a hidden gem.
Like I'm literally shitting and farting.
Okay, thanks.
Also as a side note, I showed a friend one of your second Jerma Stream highlight videos and they stopped talking to me.
Sorry to hear that.
Thank you Jamie for the $5, Jamie2803.
Hey Jerma, I finally unlocked the 10,000 bit badge and I just want to say that I think you're the best streamer on Twitch by far.
Keep doing what you're doing mate. Much love.
I'm happy to hear that you think that.
There are a lot of people on this website.
There are a lot of choices.
And if you've chosen me, I hope you've made the right choice.
Right?
In your mind.
I'm just glad you think that.
Because there are a lot of other people that stream that do very cool fun things on this website.
And you've decided to come here.
So thank you.
Really appreciate it.
Also thank you to Cold Warhol for the $10.
Howdy Jerma, hope you're having a good day.
This is the first stream of yours I've ever been to, able to catch, and it's been a blast.
Hope to be back for more.
Well hell yeah, welcome.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Thanks for sticking around.
I hope you enjoy it. I hope you have fun.
I'll see you on Friday maybe.
If you come around.
But welcome to the community.
First stream I've been able to catch.
Thank you.
Man, boy, thanks for the 250.
This game is just overly complicated doodle god.
In a way, yeah, I can see that.
The great Canadian FK club.
Thanks for the $15 and the community subs.
Time for finger extended out and pointing to the sky.
Thank you for the $15 great Canadian FK club.
Fuck, it's fuck club.
Fuck, fuck.
No, it's not.
I got corrected like three times.
It's like frick club.
Thank you InvaderZ for the 250.
$2.50.
Your content makes me happy.
Here's pictures of my rats.
Leviathan and Judas.
Those are some cool ass names too.
Leviathan.
Hello.
They're very cute.
Thank you for sharing.
Thanks for the 250.
They are adorable.
Thank you 420Squid for the $10 thousand bits.
Hey, German just made this sick mashup.
It's you singing the ABCs as Broccoli's son in the Mind Show stream.
Over dance with me.
Hang on to this.
See, I told you.
Some of you maybe didn't believe me.
But people make shit all the time.
And we can start compiling these and have one of these community nights way sooner than a lot of people think.
That channel for the Discord, by the way, will be open this weekend.
Tomorrow, no.
But 420Squid, hang on to that video.
420Squid is going to be a place for you to officially submit it so we can have as many people see it as we possibly can, including me, during our monthly community nights.
Do you care if I use your voice as a sample in some music?
Don't do that.
No, I don't care.
That's fine.
As long as it's not like any TOS breaking stuff.
But thank you 420Squid.
Hold on to that.
Mark Meltzer, thanks for the three bucks.
Hey, German, popping my donation here since I got my part-time job recently.
Wanted to share this movie clip because I felt it related well to some parts of the stream.
Gotta get that fucking community Discord up.
So many, like, good links that I want to watch.
This is exactly what I was talking about.
Would you accept an interpretive dance?
Oh, this is like a full Nacho Libre movie clip.
Hang on to this.
I want to try to, I want to make, I guess, I gotta say, I gotta try to say this, like, very clear so we can, like, clip it.
Ready?
Here we go.
If anybody asks, clip this.
For the future, any community-oriented videos, artwork, music, or fun, interesting content that you create
or that you pull out from the internet that is related to the channel,
put it into the Discord for the community nights, the monthly community nights, so we can show them all and show people.
And we'll have a lot of fun doing it.
For the future, I will not be watching videos or showing artwork or original community content at the end of streams.
There you go.
We are going to save them for our big community nights.
I want to make sure I talk about it more and more and more and more.
Clips can only be 60 seconds long.
Let's summarize.
Well, they'll get the idea.
They know we have to really talk about it.
How long can it be?
There will be official stuff there, but any video, I think, that would be longer than five minutes, ten minutes,
stuff like that, I think, would have to be kind of a special thing.
I don't really want to have a ton of big, long, ten-minute videos over there because people, I think, would get kind of...
It's almost like you get video exhaustion after a while.
So I think that the cap for just general video stuff will probably be about five minutes.
Any more than that, I think, is a little too long.
But sometimes somebody makes something so good that obviously we have to waive that.
But thank you, Mark Meltzer, for the three bucks.
And if you want to get a sneak peek, because that stream is going to happen soon, after this weekend, the first one.
I feel like there's going to be a lot of submissions.
I'm going to rip the Godfather and post it in the Discord.
Then you're going to get snapped.
You're going to get banned.
Don't do that.
That's going to... You actually will get...
The mods aren't going to mess around, by the way.
You will be banned from that Discord, from that channel.
You will not be able to post in that channel ever again.
Hey, thank you to Bike Richards for the 19 dollars.
Thank you, Bike Richards.
Jeremy, you need to have the apes discover wave dashing if you want to defeat the tiger.
Yeah, the new Planet of the Apes movie stinks.
Jacob had gave 30 bucks earlier.
Thanks for the 30 fucking dollars.
Jeremy, can you put on a monkey suit when playing this game?
I would overheat and pass out.
I don't think I could.
Thank you, though.
Thank you so much for the 33,000 bits, 30 bucks.
Thank you.
Jeremy, will you play this game again?
No.
I will play Ancestors again if there's a tiger patch.
Minus 25% spawn rate.
Maybe after a few updates.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not going to write it off completely.
I wanted to love it so much.
But, it's okay.
But thank you, Jacob, for the 30 bucks.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you, Emmanuel Depressed for the 9 bucks.
Jeremy, have you ever thought about doing streams with Kim?
Because you're a cute couple and I think it would be fun.
Only if she was okay with it and shit.
Yeah, Kim pops in from time to time.
But Kim doesn't really like to be on camera.
You know, she's not like a performer or like an entertainer.
So, she kind of doesn't really...
And that's not for everybody.
Sometimes she'll come in and just be like,
here's like Otto or here's this or...
But she has shown interest before in doing like a special one-off kind of stream.
Like a cooking thing or we hang out and do...
We'll play like a card game or something.
So, I mean, there has been talk of that of what we would want to do if we did it.
She's been on streams before during a lot of my bullshit.
Like the seed box thing.
You know, that was...
She was there.
She was on camera for that one.
That was almost a whole year ago.
Yeah, time flies.
It's ridiculous.
But that's kind of the stance on that.
Maybe eventually.
But there's no...
There's no like pressure to have her be on camera or do anything.
You see her pop in from time to time, but not like full streams.
We'll see.
What a dumb fucking way to have you...
I'm not even gonna get into it.
I don't know.
You keep saying you need sticks throughout the entire game, but I've been here the whole time.
Yeah.
S-T-I-C-K-S, not S-T-Y-X.
Spelled differently.
It's like there and there.
I need to go there.
Not like there as in T-H-E-I-R.
There isn't there.
That's bought over there.
Sounds the same.
English is weird.
I don't know why I said date.
This date is not what you said.
It's not in this message.
You said, can you go on another one of them hiatuses?
I don't have much free time, and I've got a bunch of games I've been meaning to catch up on,
but you keep doing all these great streams.
And before you say it's a choice whether to watch it or not, it's a lifestyle.
JermaJex.
Well, I mean, I kind of just have been streaming when I want to.
Streaming a lot, time-wise, to something I'm really into.
But recently, you know, I've been pulling him back a little bit.
I'm not going to be streaming.
I didn't stream for the last two yesterday, and I'm not streaming tomorrow or the next day.
I mean, sure, you're going to get Friday, Saturday, and Sunday loaded with content, by the way.
Two Kinect horror games.
The end of the Terraria saga.
And Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars.
I mean, it's loaded with content, but it'll take a couple days to get there.
Cox permitting, of course, right?
I know. Don't say that.
It's been so good lately. Don't say that.
But yeah.
Thank you for the $5 air elicited.
The VODs will all be there for at least two months on Twitch with the chat.
And then there is that archive channel where they're just kind of there forever.
They have some time, but thank you.
Thank you, smelly boy, for the phylactery lich did it again.
But let me just first say to smelly boy.
Thank you for the 250.
When is Mario RPG stream Sunday?
I just said it.
I'm glad I got this message right here.
Thank you, smelly boy and phylactery lich.
Holy shit.
I mean, like that's this is next level.
This is like four or five hundred subs that you have on the channel now.
Are you responsible for like at least three, four, five hundred people?
A couple of people have done this before.
And it's wild.
There's been at least a handful of people in this community that were responsible for at least two to five plus hundred subs on the channel.
But holy shit, phylactery.
Thank you for your mountain of subs that you just dropped here.
Again, only.
Only two hundred and thirty seven.
Only two hundred.
That's not that.
That's not like a huge ridiculous fucking more than two almost two hundred and fifty fucking subscriptions on the channel attributed to one person.
Thank you, phylactery.
Seriously.
And congratulations to people that got those subs.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Getting down to the end.
And I'm going to put on the credits and what a good opportunity to put them on now, considering that that sub drop just happened.
We still have some some bits to go through.
But as always, thanks everybody for joining me.
Hope you had fun.
I'll see you guys all on Friday.
Much love to everybody.
Thank you for the subs.
Thank you for the support.
Thank you for everything.
All of you here listed.
You continue to be the oil that moves this engine forward.
And there's going to be a big like oil explosion on that carnival stream.
Well, I mean, there's going to be like a there's going to be a all of the support from everybody will be on that stream.
I worded that weirdly.
No, not like oil spill.
Not like no, no, no, no, no.
I'm talking about like you guys.
Look, I'm fucking stupid.
Just call me a pee pants and we'll get over it.
No, that that stream should be so much fun.
I really can't wait for you guys to see it.
I have another kind of update meeting.
I've actually heard.
I mean, why did I tell you?
This is I mean, what am I going to I'm not going to talk about this stream anymore.
Oh, there are more than there are more than a few robots.
And one of them has just been completed from what I've been told.
So one of them is like kind of almost ready to go completely.
And apparently they apparently said it's a lot of fun and it's pretty crazy.
So that's a little update for you.
And over the next couple of days, I'm going to figure out some more stuff, get some more details.
What the hell is even going to happen?
I would just hang out and show up on the 21st.
That's all you need to know.
Who is they?
That is the robotics company that is engineering and making the robots and the production company team
that is responsible for a lot of the on-site stuff as well.
And this is this sub.
This is still going.
There's a lot of people.
Thank you guys.
Also, thank you to S10W update for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, I know you told me that I don't need to donate if it's too expensive, but no matter what,
I will support even with one dollar in my pocket.
Hope you have a great night and I hope to donate lots more.
And they say war and hate war and hate.
P.S. Why did you leak every football player's phone number and home address?
I didn't want to donate lots more war and hate.
How about safety and fucking happiness?
How about like mac and cheese?
How about pistachios?
Not in the ice cream, but flavored ice cream.
Don't like the pistachio in the ice cream.
I like the pistachio flavoring in the ice cream.
Don't give me pistachios in there.
I just want the taste of the pistachio ice cream.
God.
But thank you.
S10W update.
I really hope that you would keep your last off though, because it's yours.
But I do appreciate it.
Thank you.
We also had...
Where, where, where, where, where?
We're almost at the end here.
Schworzard.
Thanks Schworzard Ed.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Please read out the story that I got.
Read out the story that you got?
Oh, from Tonk to Transformer?
Well, it's loading.
Let me see.
Errorless.
Thanks for the 250.
Can't wait for the streams this weekend.
Connect Horror, Sturma, and Mario RPG.
Those will be fun.
It will very much be interesting, I think.
Thank you to Dr. Steen for the five dollars.
Leave your next deli sandwich in the car.
I still have flashbacks of doing that.
I am so mad about that.
That was from a really good deli that was around me.
That place was awesome.
It was like a little sandwich shop and they did a sandwich.
I can't even say it.
I'm not even going to think about it anymore.
But thank you Dr. Steen for the five dollars.
Thank you BDLujay for the five dollars.
I actually pronounced Blujay.
Oh, sorry.
Thank you Blujay.
They say, Hey Jerma, my brothers introduced me to you a long time ago, but I only just
started watching some second Jerma highlights and they brought me a lot of laughs and really
cheered me up after long days at work.
This has been the first stream that I've gotten to sit and really enjoy.
It was so good to cry laughing at the 8 a.m. Eastern bit.
Thanks for being a cool and funny, genuine guy.
Incredibly nice message.
I'm glad that you're here.
Glad you're hanging out.
Thanks to your brothers for introducing you.
I'm just me.
I don't know who else to be.
I'm happy that you find it interesting.
Thank you and welcome.
Right?
Welcome.
Also, we had those subs from Phylactery and that's the end.
I will.
I was skimmed through this talk to transformer that was posted here from Schwarz Ed.
I just had a horrible burrito at Taco Bell and I hate it.
I'm not a vegetarian, but I hate my burrito.
I've seen my dad eat the same burrito, which was incidentally very decent, but this burrito
was awful.
This was an incredibly disappointing burrito.
The burrito was very fatty, very dry, very greasy, but that would be my main complaint
if it was just a burrito.
The taste was all kind of bland, to be honest, and the portions were actually pretty small.
The guacamole was good, but to be fair, I didn't order the guac because I was in a rush
and the guac is not a burrito.
And there are some things you can't have in a burrito.
You can't have cilantro, onion, and cheese.
And cilantro is a bit of too much.
The beef was good, but so was the avocado.
However, the tortilla is so soft that I could eat the tortilla without breaking it.
At the same time, the...
Thank you for that.
I'll see you guys on Friday.
Thanks for watching the APE game.
And of course, talk to Transformers is always fun.
And Tingy just dropped 10 community subs right now, right before the stream turned off.
And S10W update gave 250.
And Dr. Steen gave $5.
Right now.
We all just came in right now.
Dr. Steen says, what's the cutoff point?
For hours, a sandwich can be left in the car where you'll still eat it.
Uh, an hour.
No, depends on where.
45 minutes, maybe. 30 minutes.
Depends on where I am.
How hot is the car.
If the car is...
If we're here, talking about Vegas.
105 degrees out pretty much every day.
102, 105.
Uh, 10 minutes.
15 minutes.
Before that sandwich is destroyed.
If the car is negative 10 Celsius.
A few days.
Five, 10 days.
Put it in the microwave.
What the fuck? What do you mean?
Negative 10 Celsius?
That's like, that's freezing.
You can keep shit in the freezer for months.
I think it'll be okay frozen in the car.
But thank you, Dr. Steen.
And then S10W update.
Sorry about that, Jerma.
That was my evil clone.
S...
Slow update.
Peace and love.
Right.
I think you've...
It's not S10W update.
But I keep saying that.
Right.
Uh, thank you though.
Appreciate it.
Minus 10 is freezer temperature.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
Alright.
Good night, guys.
I'll see you Friday for more Connect, Horror Movie Connect, Horror Show Connect.
Take care, guys.
See you soon.