Oh, hello, cats. Hey, what's going on, guys? It's Gerber here for the 4,000 subscriber video.
This is my dog, Simon. He's a dachshund. He's like 17 years old. He's really, oh yes, hello, hello.
He can go down. But, uh, thank you guys so much. I got a couple of things in this video you guys
gonna like. I've got a setup video and I have a crazy kind of cooking show. But hopefully you
guys enjoy it. I really do appreciate the 4,000. Let's keep rolling, everybody. All right, so this
is my desk. I'll give you like a nice wide shot of the desk. So there's the desk, there's the monitor,
there's my chair. The desk is kind of messy, so I apologize. I didn't really have time to clean it
up before I made this video. But anyways, the computer is under the desk. It's lit, it's all
lit up blue and stuff, nice and cool. So that is the computer. The specs on this thing, it is a
custom-built Digital Storm PC. Highly recommend Digital Storm. If you guys don't know what Digital
Storm is, go find out. They're awesome. So it is an Intel i7-950 and it's overclocked to 3.6
gigahertz. It has 6 gigs of RAM at 1600 megahertz. It is a, oh, it has a Nvidia GTX 470, the super
clocked EVGA edition. Shibby will like that. And it also has a one terabyte, I believe, one terabyte
32 MB cache hard drive. I think it's a Western Digital, I think. Here's the monitor. It is a
27 inch monitor made by HP, the HP 2710M. It's a very, very nice monitor, nice and glossy, nice
finish. I really enjoy it. So that's kind of my computer setup. Oh, I also, here's my external
hard drive right there. I have it plugged in with eSATA. I don't have it plugged in with a USB
because eSATA is faster and more efficient. And yeah, that's pretty much my computer setup.
Hope you guys enjoy that. And now let's make some breakfast. All right. So we're here in the kitchen.
I'm going to cook you guys an American classic. This is the two eggs, two pieces of bacon,
two pieces of toast. Cause a lot of guys ask me, they say, Jerma, how do you stay so healthy?
How do you stay so physically fit? Like how, what can I do to get healthy? Besides exercise and
besides obviously keeping a good diet, you want a good breakfast. Now let's start out by talking
about the bacon. Bacon, you want premium cut. You don't want any of the gross, bad stuff. You
want the good stuff. Two eggs, two pieces of toast. And we're going to start. There's only one egg in
here. All right. Let's just go to the store real quick. Yeah. I'll go. Just, uh, it's, uh, the
supermarket's open, right? Yep. Did someone ask for an egg? Oh, it's the egg. Oh, all right. Come on
in, bro. Let's, let's do this. This is, uh, this is the egg. For those of you that don't know,
this is the egg. He's a really good friend of mine. He's been here for a long time.
Um, he had a crazy accident at some point in his life. I don't know when it was, but he, uh,
he turned into this and, uh, I mean, I don't, I don't know why I'm introducing you. You could
potentially do this yourself, but, uh, the egg. Um, I'm trying to do a healthy, like American
iPad. I kinda, I kinda only wanted to be honest. I wanted just like a few eggs. Like I only wanted
like two eggs. You can never have too many eggs. Um, you gotta tell me you're the egg expert. So
you gotta tell me if this is true. Is it true that the egg yolk is like the unhealthy part?
Don't you really want to cook like the egg whites and... In the military radium, we only cook
hybrid goat and chicken egg. Okay. So what does that have to do with anything? This is not how
you cook eggs. I don't know where you, where you figured this was a good idea. Whoever told you
this was a good idea was completely wrong. Everybody, everyone thinks this is funny. What
are you, what are you doing? So I, I mean, I, I at least want to add a little bit of bacon because
if bacon is... Not only egg. All right. The egg has, uh, has officially left us. Uh, I don't know
where he went. He just took off. He like stormed out of the kitchen. I don't understand, but I'm
going to try and fix this breakfast because this is an atrocity. Thank you, egg. You, uh, thanks
for bringing me extra eggs. I appreciate it, but you, um, obviously have a few problems in your life
you need to deal with. And that's something that you can figure out on your own. Okay. So it has
been a painfully long time since the egg has left and to be completely honest, I'm getting kind of
concerned. So, um, did you hear that? That is the shower. That is the shower. Egg. Egg. Shh. I knew,
I knew this was going to happen, dude. Watch out. Watch out. Get out of the way. Watch out.
You all right, egg? It's time for you to go home. Okay. You gotta, you gotta go home.
See you later, egg. When you're out of the shower, get out of here. Okay. Leave the house.
So thank you everybody for 4,000 subscribers. You guys are awesome. I hope you guys enjoyed this
little skit we put together for you guys. And, uh, yeah. Thank you for 4,000. See you guys next time.
Take care, everybody.