Hey, what's going on, everybody? How you guys doing?
Jerma here with a update little video.
I know this is like the second update video in the last three or four months.
And, you know, some things need to be said. There's a lot to talk about.
About the channel. About me.
And in the background of this video, it's not gonna be Spider-Man.
I promise, it's not gonna be Spider-Man 2 this time.
It's gonna be Spider-Man 3.
Shatter Dimensions.
Let's get started. These neighborhoods aren't gonna friendly themselves.
First of all, I want to say thank you to everybody for all the support,
all the kind words, and everybody that watched JermaRumble live action.
It's been live for a few weeks. It's had a chance to soak in and settle.
And I feel like now is a good enough time for me to, after that video being uploaded,
can talk about not just that video, but the direction of this channel
and the philosophy going forward that I want to use for the rest of the time I really use YouTube.
Because I've been doing this for a long time.
I've been doing YouTube for about five years now.
I think my fifth year anniversary, I believe, was in July.
I'm an old man. I've aged. I've gotten older.
I look like shit, by the way. I look like I'm gonna show you a pretty recent picture.
That's a picture of my face.
What the fuck happened?
But I've learned stuff. I've learned about myself.
I've learned about what I like to do, what I don't like to do.
I've gotten to a point where I think I've figured it all out, at least for myself, internally.
And it's as follows.
This channel from now on is gonna be videos that I really wanted to make,
that I wanted to spend time on, that I actually really wanted to care about.
And that might not be a video every couple days.
That might not be a video every couple weeks.
Whenever I get the urge to, you know what?
I want to make that, and I'm gonna make it, and I'm gonna put a bunch of time into it.
I'm gonna put a bunch of effort into it.
More than a couple weeks, more than a couple months.
Higher production value videos is what I want the main focus of this channel to be.
Now, that doesn't mean that every video from now on is gonna be a wrestling video.
Okay, he's gonna make like 40-minute live-action wrestling movies for the rest of the time he uses YouTube.
No, I mean, there will be more wrestling videos.
I guarantee you that, absolutely.
There's already ideas flying around of the next Jerma wrestling video.
But that's not gonna come out like next week.
That's not gonna be for a little while.
You're gonna have to give me a little while on that one, you know what I'm saying?
I don't want to throw any hopes up for people that it's gonna be coming out soon,
but we're working on it already, and other stuff already.
There's a lot of things that already are coming down the pipeline over the next couple months.
And some people might be saying to themselves right now and out loud,
maybe, maybe you're pointing at the monitor and talking at me.
Where, what about gaming? What about the gaming videos?
Are you just gonna be a live-action sketch comedy channel?
No, it doesn't, the subject matter doesn't matter anymore at this point for me.
Like, I think that's really the point I'm trying to get at with this whole,
with three minutes into this now, is I want to snip the line on the balloons that are tied to my wrist.
And just watch them fly.
You know, some balloons are gonna get stuck in a tree.
Some of those balloons are gonna keep flying.
Maybe some of those balloons are gonna reach outer space and get in contact with aliens.
Who knows? I just want to see the balloons fly.
I want to cover a lot of different bases. I want to do a lot of different stuff.
I already have a lot of things that I want to spend time on.
Like I said, it's one of those situations where game, non-game, it doesn't matter to me right now.
It completely is, that's out of the question for my brain.
It's what do I care about right now, and what do I want to spend time on.
But, here's the second part of this video.
And this is, you know, people that might be upset about the fact that I'm not making as many videos as I used to.
I have a second channel now.
And it's already up, it's already live, there's already like six videos on it.
You can go right now, the whole screen is a link.
This, right now, the annotation on the screen will take you to the channel.
There's a link in the description.
Go subscribe to that channel if you want to see a bunch of videos all the time.
Because what the second channel is going to be is a stream highlight channel from my Twitch stream.
And anything else that I want to put up there.
It could be random videos anytime I deem it necessary.
Just stuff that I don't want to put on this channel.
Because like I said, this channel I want to be reserved only for stuff like German Rumble live action.
And, you know, the high production, I just, we just talked about it for five minutes.
But second channel stream highlights, and we're going to have a schedule now.
We're going to have a schedule. Before I go into the second channel anymore,
my Twitch.tv stream is going to have a legit three day a week schedule.
Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Fridays, we're going to be live at seven o'clock Eastern time.
Seven p.m. Eastern time. That's my stream schedule.
I ain't doing this anymore.
I talked about this in the past how I don't like to have schedules because I never can adhere to them.
But sometimes it gets like to a point where it's like, what time is it?
Or it's like seven forty five. I wasn't like two in the morning.
Yeah, I'll stream for like six hours or whatever.
No, no, no. Two weeks go by.
What is this? A fucking thing of orange juice.
I'll chug that and then stream for like 20 minutes.
I got I got to have a schedule and that's what's going to happen.
Every Tuesday, Thursday and Friday, Twitch.tv slash German nine eight five.
I'll be live. I'll be playing anything.
It doesn't matter what it is. I'm going to just stream it and have fun.
Like I did like a month or two ago when I was streaming all the time and it's going to get edited.
The streams that I think are funny that I think are good are going to get put together
and get uploaded to that second channel.
They're going to be condensed. It's going to be high quality.
They're not going to be just thrown up for our live streams.
It's actually going to be videos like ones that you probably were used to seeing a couple of years ago
are going up on the channel.
I have a lot of them. I have a lot of videos to upload to that channel that is going to take me a while.
But you can expect at least a few videos a week uploaded to this channel.
Second channel links in the description in the screen.
Go there if you want to see a bunch of stream highlights and a bunch of other random videos
who knows what the hell I'm going to upload there.
I don't even know. You might see me eating breakfast.
It could happen. It could go up on that channel.
That's the second channel. You know what I'm saying?
That's pretty much it.
So let's go over it. Here we go again.
We're going to go over this one more time.
And I'm going to go over very A, B, C.
Okay. A.
Jerma985.
The channel you're on right now.
Infrequent, higher quality videos.
Videos that I cared about that I wanted to spend time on.
Infrequent.
Jerma.
I don't have a name for the channel yet.
It's just second Jerma channel.
Stream highlights.
Other videos.
Very frequent upload schedule.
All the time.
Content.
Twitch.tv.
C.
Tuesday.
Thursday and Friday.
7pm Eastern time.
Every single time.
No exceptions.
Unless I get like sick.
Then I won't stream.
But Tuesday, Thursday and Friday.
Twitch.tv slash Jerma985.
And that's all I got to say.
That's it.
I hope I could make it clear enough that these things are happening.
That this is kind of the direction the channel is taking now.
And yeah.
Go subscribe to Jerma2.
And I'll see you guys soon.
Have a good night guys.
See you later.
Have a good rest of your summer.
It's not even summer.
It's like, it's like September 26th.
Oh my god.
Yeah, the last time I made like a hey what's up guys video was in like fucking June.
Or like May.
It's been, have a good rest of your summer.