Fuck the title. The title still says just chillin'. God damn it. Hold on.
I need to change this right now. I wasn't supposed to be like this.
Just chillin'. Oh no. Uh... lay... lay in low.
Ugh. I don't know. I have to keep it. I got nothing to put here.
Titlet colonoscopy reflections. I was gonna title it.
I'm not supposed to be here. It's only been like 30 seconds.
I was gonna... uh... hold on. I'll be right... hold on. See ya.
Okay, I'm back. I was... lay in low. Post colonoscopy stream session.
Chill session. This didn't just happen.
I didn't just get out of the procedure. That's kind of misleading.
That's a little misleading.
Hey, I just got out of my colonoscopy.
Five minutes ago. I'm gonna turn my stream on.
How am I doing? I'm doing all right. I'm doing good.
Butt hole. Yeah, I walked out of it. I'm still in my... what do they call them?
Johnny's? What do they call them? The open back ass dress? What's it called?
Diapers? No, I'm talking... a gown?
No, they're called like... johns or something.
Kilt? No, no, no, no. The tablecloth!
The blue picnic tablecloth that has the big open ass.
Why does it look like that, by the way? It does. It looks like a curtain.
Hospital gown. Yeah, but that's like the...
that's like the technical way to say it.
It's called like a... like a gurney or something.
Oh, I know what a gurney is. I'm not stupid.
Anywho, we can talk about it if you want.
I'll give you some insight if anybody wants to hear about it.
I mean, it depends on how much people want to hear about this.
Tell me everything. All right, I'll tell you.
All right, is there already a resident sleeper in the chat? Is that a bad sign?
Hey, don't tell your story about my colonoscopy.
Sleep.
Show us your ass.
Okay. No, no, it went well.
I still have to hear back for a couple things.
I had like two or three biopsies done, and it takes like three of...
it takes like more than two or three weeks for you to get results back on a biopsy.
I'm fine. The doctor said it doesn't have any major concerns.
The reason why I did it, people are going,
why are you doing a colonoscopy before like 50?
I have irritable bowel disease, and if you have irritable bowel disease
for more than like a decade, I started developing some new symptoms
that I wasn't really used to, and fast forward,
I just wanted to make sure everything was okay.
And it is, apparently. Everything seems to be fine.
We'll wait and hear back from the biopsies,
but he said he didn't have any major concerns,
and that's the end of that, I guess.
I have been put on some new medication,
which is very, very hard to get used to.
I'm healthy. I'm, yeah, I'm doing all right.
But I'm on a new medication that's...
it's kind of odd and hard for me to get used to.
So, pardon my absence for the last four days or so, like three and a half, four days.
But I didn't really get... I couldn't eat anything
even a day or two after the procedure.
It was two days ago now, right? Let me see, yeah.
So no, yeah, it was like two and a half days ago.
I... I felt just like shit. I couldn't eat.
I was eating bread and scrambled eggs for like the last two days and peanut butter.
You forget how good food tastes when you don't get to eat it for four days.
I can eat now? Yeah, I can eat normally now.
A normal diet? Wait, bread, scrambled eggs, and peanut butter
for every meal is a normal diet?
I don't think so.
That's normal? Every day?
Don't get me wrong, I love peanut butter.
Remove bread and eggs and it's good.
Well, the reason why they're easy to digest foods.
White bread and scrambled eggs and peanut butter, they're easy to digest.
What do I eat normally?
Succulent fucking fish.
Broiled caviar.
I couldn't eat those things.
It was horrible.
Roasted legumes in a creamy tomato broth.
I couldn't have that.
It was hell on earth.
Anywho, so let me give you a breakdown.
I know I'm just kind of hanging out here, but I still am.
Not 100%.
I'm like 84%.
Because I'm still getting cramps.
And I actually talked to the doctor today
and you're not really supposed to have abdominal pain and cramps
like two or three days after.
So they're like, let us know in a couple days
if you're still having that.
And I'm like, okay.
But I'll be fine, don't worry about me.
Let the camera in.
Here's a breakdown of what's going to happen.
But let me be very clear about something.
This is very important.
Take care of yourself.
Take care of your health.
If you're able to and have some issue
that you want to just be reassured of,
go get seen, please.
You got to take care of yourself.
Just be careful.
Take care of yourself.
You got this one body and you want to keep it.
Hopefully, hopefully you do.
Big bits just came through.
Holy shit, they did.
Kali Brady gave 100 bucks.
$100, 10,000 bits.
Thank you so much, Kali Brady.
Really appreciate that.
Welcome back, Jerma.
Hope the recovery is brief and goes well.
Keep on being the best streamer.
Jerma Hart, thank you.
That's fucking incredibly nice thing to say.
I'm going fine.
Recovery is good.
I'm pretty much back to normal.
Which you'll see, I'll make all kinds of...
You thought like I was going to have a colonoscopy
and I was going to have any jokes the next day.
I don't have any.
So I've been like literally sleeping
and playing Hearthstone for four days.
I don't have any material.
And is that another 100 bucks that just came through?
No, it's the same one.
Stream Labs is late.
Hearthstone stream.
No, I'm not good.
I make mistakes.
I make tons of fucking mistakes.
I've been playing the new Dalaran expansion
and I make...
I fuck up so much.
But the best part about playing
those single player campaigns
is...
I'm going to give you an opinion here.
This is just my opinion.
I'm sorry if you don't like it.
If you think I'm wrong or stupid,
you're completely able to say that.
Hearthstone has kind of turned into like this clown show
where they've added so many crazy things to this game.
Oh, Echo has played the same card seven times.
Last time I played it, it wasn't like that.
And I'm just like, what the fuck is going on here?
There's like clown...
Yeah, there's clown cards in the game now.
Oh, cast a random spell at a random person
target selected randomly.
So when I play that game against other people,
I have no idea what I'm doing.
And it's just like embarrassing and frustrating.
When I play against a computer,
I get to use all the new cool, fun,
ridiculous, randomized clown cards
and beat the computer.
And it's fun.
I don't buy card packs.
No, I just play the solo adventures and they come up.
That's how I play most games, to be honest.
Yeah.
Solitaire mindset.
Yeah, it is very...
Okay, I can talk like shit about like
all these new ridiculous cards that I don't understand
that throw the game upside down for me.
But I have absolutely put into that Dalaran expansion.
Absolutely.
I mean, this is not even...
I'm not even kidding.
This is some big some kind of currency thing.
I've put probably 50 hours into it in the last seven days.
Had to...
Anyways, today I've been like away for like four days.
So I'm just trying to...
We're trying to get like a state of the channel address here.
Heroic mode.
I can't do heroic mode.
I'm too bad because I get fucking mad
and I like fucking grab my iPad
and I'm just like the fuck
and I like scream into the iPad like it's hearing me.
I can't do it.
I have to like...
Okay, you know when you have like your grandfather play a game
or like your mother or something
or like a friend of yours that doesn't play games
and before they get to touch it,
you turn the difficulty down to like zero
because you just want them to have fun.
I feel like that's what has to happen to me.
I have to like be given an experience that I look at
and I'm like, well, this is hard and crazy.
But it's on like zero and I get to go,
oh, I just see what I just did there.
I like in my mind, I calculated like lethal.
I'm on like the easiest difficulty.
I just feel good, you know.
My whole family are god gamers.
He's a child.
Hey, look at that.
You probably...
What's the name of the stream?
A very childlike.
Yeah, you have to give me something.
You have to give me like food
and tell me it's other food and make me believe you
and like tell me it's like Captain Crunch
but it's actually broccoli and I have to believe you.
What?
I don't want that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Jeremy, that's Captain Crunch broccoli.
What?
Is it?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not regular broccoli.
That's Captain Crunch broccoli.
Oh, that means I like it.
Well, you know, it's just...
It's a power of suggestion.
You know that if you hand somebody...
I've been away for four days
so you've got to let me get this out.
You know if you hand somebody various liquids
that are just water with orange, red
or blue food coloring in it
and you tell them that the orange one is
orange tropical punch flavored
a certain percentage of people will taste it.
I was in that study.
He's on a tangent.
If I can tell you, I gotta get this.
You gotta let me get it out.
I haven't been here for four days.
But, okay, I was gonna break down what we're gonna do.
Anyways, colonoscopy good.
Everything's fine.
I'm good to go.
Sorry I was away for a few days here
but you know, I'm trying to take care of myself.
Today, tomorrow and Thursday, three days in a row.
Sam and Max and maybe Heroes of Might and Magic clean up.
Just chill while I get back to normal.
Tomorrow, cooking...
I'm talking like the stream's over.
It's not.
Tomorrow, cooking simulator.
Been waiting for that game for a long fucking time.
They delayed that game like seven times
and every time it was like a week away
I was ready to stream it.
They pushed it like another six months.
So cooking simulator tomorrow.
Thursday, if cooking simulator is a lot of fun
maybe I'll do it again.
Bingo.
Fast forward.
E3, E3.
I'm gonna do professional E3 breakdown streams
for all the major conferences like we did last year.
So that's what, three days?
It's what, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday?
And then, excuse me, hold on a second here.
What's that?
You got something else planned.
I've been, what do you think I've been doing?
I've been playing Hearthstone and planning streams.
I've been lying in bed calculating lethal
and then what am I gonna do next week?
I'll show it to you right now.
I got this.
Wait, how do I look?
It doesn't matter.
Who cares?
I just had a colonoscopy, god damn it.
Let me look like shit.
I got this.
You know, you don't need to see me.
We're gonna play this.
This is a card game called Unlock
where you have to escape from the scary carnival.
You have an app that you load up on your phone
or on your iPad or whatever.
Whatever, doesn't matter.
And you have to escape from like the circus.
I have three of them.
There are like many little
hour to two hour long board games.
I have three of them.
I've got escape from the dinosaurs,
escape from the clowns, and then the wild west.
We're doing that after E3.
I'm glad we could have this conversation.
I'm glad, hey, I'm glad to be back.
Let's start.
Sam and Max, we're gonna clean up some stuff.
Sam and Max, last episode of season two.
That only took me 14 minutes.
That's it.
Check your watch.
Welcome guys.
Here we go.
I just make sure you are ready.
Some people may have been in the bathroom.
Oh, wow.
This is called.
Ooh, it's not what that's called.
Spaceship will self-destruct in three, two, one.
Spaceship destroyed,
but I've still got the greatest enthusiasm
and confidence in the mission.
Looks like we escaped that horrible explosion.
The nick of time.
You okay, Max?
I don't feel disintegrated.
You know more than usual,
but it felt like landing on a boiled ham.
Oops.
Sorry, Mr. Featherly.
I forgot you were in there.
The indignity.
Dude, these are the only characters
that get to stick around.
Why on earth have you brought me here?
Do you recognize this place?
Does no one study the classics anymore?
Farewell.
We're obviously in the eternal twilight
at the banks of the River Styx.
The land of the dead.
All the coolest people are dead.
I should have brought my autograph book.
Well, you've delivered Bosco to his final rest,
so let's be off, shall we?
Come on.
We can't just leave Bosco here.
Yeah, we should at least staple a note to him or something.
No, we're gonna have to find Bosco's soul
and get it back into his body.
Find Bosco's soul.
You the peace and quiet was too good to last.
Final episode, season two, episode five.
It's titled Beaselbub.
I don't know, something like that.
Anyways, what are these moles doing here?
Do I have any items from the last adventure?
Federal related egg.
Don't ask me how.
So I have an egg.
We have the cake sample.
By the way, if you missed last time that I played this,
there were aliens and we got like sucked into a spaceship
and then we got sucked into this wormhole
and now we're all dead.
I think.
I don't know.
I haven't read the manga.
The AI isn't useful on creatures with natural intelligence.
Okay, so we gotta get Bosco's soul.
Poor Bosco.
The shock of seeing time-traveling mariachis
was too much for his heart to take.
Stress-induced heart attacks are the second most common cause of death
for conspiracy freaks obsessed with alien abduction.
What's the first?
Unexplained organ removal.
Well, this moment.
I need to like bring this up.
This like cut off a little bit for me.
I can't stream under these conditions.
I'll see you next week, guys.
Maybe like a couple months.
Once I like get over.
This is what happens to babies that get thrown out with the bath water.
Bye.
Okay, so let's talk about them.
All those times on the mariachi spaceship
when you saw only one set of footprints.
That was when I carried you.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
All right.
Can I run for rent?
Bookstore game cartridges.
What the hell is this?
Is this ET?
I heard rumors about a company
burying millions of mime sweeper cartridges.
But I always thought that was in the desert.
I bet the sand worms carried them here.
I think it was actually in the desert in Nevada.
I actually think that's true.
Looks like the bottom dropped out of the Esperanto literature business.
Harry karaoke machine and gumball machine.
Oh, it's the gumball machine from upstairs.
Ball machine.
We've been missing.
Oh, I wouldn't say we've been missing it.
Let's talk to Harry.
Oh, cute Max.
It's a little goth mole man.
So can he dig stream.
So now we're under representing the mole man demographic.
I thought we were just insensitive to women and minorities.
No, you need a token.
You've ruined my big entrance.
Wait, Harry mole man?
In a past life, yes.
Now I am become deaf.
Okay, let us on the train.
What are you doing here?
Where's Bosco's soul?
Have you seen Bosco's soul lying around anywhere?
Bosco.
Is that his first or last name?
We never asked.
Just do two palms up.
Center of left shoulder.
Center of right shoulder.
Two palms up.
Center of left shoulder.
Center of right shoulder.
Push as hard as you fucking can lunging forward into the acid.
Guaranteed to fall over.
What do you mean what?
What?
What's wrong?
There's something wrong with that.
But he's still sedated.
Oh, hold on.
I got like a funny story.
I got a funny...
Oh, he was sedated story.
Well, not really.
I was like really polite and really nice.
But so Talix picked me up
because you have to have somebody drive you there.
You can't drive because obviously for very obvious reasons.
So when he came to get me into the, you know, the recovery room,
he overheard.
I mean, I remember this, but I kind of don't.
But he overheard me talking to the nurses.
And I was saying some strange things.
Not really that strange.
But apparently I got up and was putting on my shoes and falling down
and like falling forward and almost like hitting my head on the wall.
Putting my shoes on and the nurse was like,
Hey, hey, sit down, sit down.
And apparently I looked at her and I went,
Hey, don't worry.
This ain't my first rodeo.
I don't know.
Like as in, as in what?
Like as in I do drugs all the time.
I was like, no, don't worry.
It's ain't my first rodeo.
I got this.
And then I like announced to everybody.
I was, I said like, like five times.
I was supposed to say, you guys are pros.
You guys are pros.
All of you.
Thank you.
You're all pros.
Tell the doctor that he's a pro.
And they're like, yeah, yeah, we will.
Thank you.
And all I remember is like, yeah,
there's like Talix holding my arm and like walking with me,
like step by step.
And I'm just like, tell everybody in the office that they're pros.
And then we were driving on like the road.
I felt like we would.
I didn't, I didn't actually feel like this,
but I said like, oh cool.
We're like going through space because the lines on the road going down.
I knew we were on a road.
I wasn't like stupid.
It was the lines on the road.
You know, like Star Wars and they go to hyperspace
and like the, the lines come forward.
I wasn't, I didn't actually believe that.
I was just drugged up saying words.
Anyways, that's the funny.
Look what happened to me when I was on drug story.
Your final stop depends on what's in your permanent record.
But if you two are trying to get to hell,
that really shouldn't be a problem.
Can you imagine if I had gone forward to put my shoes on it?
I'm like, I went like this, you know, when you,
you're going to laugh at me, but I don't care.
So, you know, when you put your shoes on
and you lean forward to like pull the last of the latch up over your heel.
When I was doing that, I pulled too much and started to go forward.
Imagine if I just kept going forward
and like smashed my head through the drywall.
It's not a choker.
It's the ripped shirt.
I like this shirt.
It's a very sentimental value shirt.
What's that hair?
It's just, look, I'm, I'm in recovery.
Okay.
Don't get me too, don't get me too hot right now.
I'm not supposed to get stressed.
Okay.
I really like probably shouldn't be laughing.
No more like funny things.
Don't say anything funny because like I,
I really think I'm supposed to like take it easy down here.
So I'm not going to, I'm not making any more,
I'm not going to laugh at anything and no one,
no one in the chat is going to make any funny things.
Okay. Let me be serious.
Okay. So we have to die.
So we have to die.
Are you allowed to get angry?
No, no, no, no emotions.
I have to be like emotionless.
Why do you think I've been playing Hearthstone?
Cause that's emotionless.
I just sit there with like my fucking eyes wide open,
just staring and I hear the guy go like,
Uther versus Carl Drago.
I don't even need to think.
It doesn't matter.
There's so many people in that game now.
Did somebody just give community subs?
Dermal lied about the clown car.
Thanks for the five community subs.
So they're just right above hell.
It's just in the sewer.
Okay. Well, wait, what?
Mama Bosco's ghost?
Mrs. Mama Bosco?
That's Ms. Mama Bosco.
You think just cause I'm dead,
you don't have to respect my independence?
How'd you get to be a ghost?
Disable pop-up notifications.
It doesn't matter.
My steam is broken, guys.
Do you understand?
I don't remember hearing or causing an explosion.
It was a great big geyser of vinegar and baking soda.
Let me give you a quick little story.
I've dis- I disabled my steam notifications
like seven years ago.
I've done everything.
I've turned off everything.
It doesn't matter.
I have so many broken notifications
for like the 5,000 invites that I've gotten
over the last like almost decade.
I can't turn them off,
but I think I can do this though.
Damn it.
What the fuck?
I'm not even logged into steam.
I'm not even fucking logged in.
I am not even logged into steam.
I'm not like on my friends.
I'm in- I'm disconnected right now.
Like disconnected as in I'm not-
I'm still on my steam library like in my store,
but I'm not-
Why am I getting notifications?
I'm not supposed to-
I'm supposed to stay low stress.
It's the Tuesday maintenance.
No, that's the wrong button.
Why is that showing up?
Hold on.
What?
I gotta get-
I gotta-
Hold on.
If I just exit out of steam,
I'm gonna be able to stay in Sam and Max, right?
Like if I just physically exit steam,
that's not gonna kick me out, right?
Stop shouting.
I'm sorry.
Will it kick me out?
What the fuck?
Why am I getting notifications
that I'm not even logged into steam?
Oh, stress levels are getting fucking high.
Hold on.
Don't-
Oh, I ain't going in-
Hold on.
Let me save this.
All my fucking notifications are off.
Steam, why can't you just let me never have them?
Oh.
Okay, I'm gonna-
Let me just exit steam.
God damn it.
It is exiting Sam and Max.
Fucking technology, man.
I saved it, though.
All right, so somebody explain to me again
why while I'm not even logged into friends
or signed into steams,
like friends and chat,
that I'm still getting fucking notifications.
What is that?
Why is that happening?
I can't do game capture.
You cannot game capture this game.
I'm in offline mode.
I'm disconnect-
I'm not online.
Why would I be getting notifications?
Whatever.
I'm-
We'll try it again.
Thank you, staff.
Thank you, Skeletor.
Daff Skeletor for the five community subs.
Should have gotten the GOG version.
You wanna know what else is really-
You wanna-
Like, you wanna be like,
let me just shit talk steam for a second.
You know what else is really dumb?
Did you guys know
that you cannot delete a steam group?
You can't delete a steam group.
It has to get to zero members.
If your steam group does not have zero members,
it cannot be deleted.
Why?
And why am I getting-
I'm gonna scream here,
but just pretend I'm screaming.
Notifications when I'm not even fucking logged into steam
and when I'm not even fucking connected to the friends account.
I'm offline mode
and I've had notifications turned off for 10 fucking years.
Why are you still showing me notifications?
I don't want any notifications.
I'm going really low here.
Okay, let's do this back.
Okay, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Back to what we were doing.
Wait a second.
Where is your apartment exactly?
On the second floor above the store, fool.
Where else would I live?
Put something over on the bottom, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna put like steam sucks down there.
No, it's gotta be like a square.
I'm just gonna make a black square.
No, who cares?
All right, I'm just-
Here we go.
How do we get to your apartment?
Hell if I know.
Some fool blew up the stairs.
Somebody blew up the stairs.
How do we get to your apartment?
Hell if I know.
Some fool blew up the stairs.
Okay, how do we get up there?
How do we get to your apartment?
Hell if I know.
Some fool blew up the stairs.
Okay, some fool blew up the stairs.
Wasn't somebody there to guide you to the afterlife?
There was some little man
who kept going on about a token and some train,
but the second explosion scared him off.
That was Jerma last year
when he was talking about cryptocurrency.
And I can't get up there to get that token.
Get on the crypto train.
Okay, say it again.
Did you get a token for the afterlife?
I told you, it's still up in my apartment.
Okay, so we have to get up to Mamaboska's apartment.
Sorry for your loss.
Any final arrangements you want us to take care of?
Oh, I ain't going anywhere yet.
Even if I could get to the afterlife,
I can't rest until I find the man who trashed my store.
That was awesome.
That was over 40 years ago.
Wow, she really holds a grudge.
I'm glad I broke up with her.
I spent the last 40 years
thinking of new ways to make his life a living hell.
But then she says things like that,
which makes me love her even more.
All right, we got to get that token.
Rest in peace, Ms. Bosco.
I also have to fix this
because this is going to drive me crazy
for the rest of the stream.
I know some people are already being driven crazy.
Here we go.
The black bar is gone.
I'm, I can, I'm, look, I'm hearing your feedback
and I'm putting your feedback into place.
Anytime somebody says a piece of feedback,
I always hear it.
All right, can we go in here?
Hiya, Flint.
What's shaking?
What the fuck?
Can't talk, fellas.
I'm still waiting for Bosco to get back.
Oh, we already found Bosco.
Yeah, his corpse is already decaying down in the sewer.
Hey, that's cute, little pals.
But I got a 40-year-old case to wrap up here.
Okay.
All right, we got to go look in crack.
Ooh, it's getting hot down there.
So that's where the Esperanto bookstore went.
He doesn't know.
What do I not know?
Don't freak me out.
My stress levels.
It's a rock.
MameTron9000.
All right, can we finally do something with this?
Jimmy2cheese.
Spent the whole season looking at it.
I haven't seen much of you lately.
Yeah?
Well, I got an image to maintain.
Can't be seen with you, lowlifes.
You know, that's a lot of attitude for somebody
we first met crawling up our toilet.
I'm building a child-friendly resort destination here.
Is the MameTron coming back to life?
Nah, he's brain dead.
We're turning him into a fantastic laser light show.
You know, for the kids.
Something about this is really sad.
This is really sad.
Oh, casino?
I thought that said to Lucky Vegan.
I was like, why is that the name of your casino?
Stop letting your emotions get to you, Jeremy.
They make you weak.
Weave them out.
What like a Sith thing to say?
What like a nice evil corporation way to see things.
All right, we got to get up to that apartment.
Let's go into symbols.
That's a Jedi thing.
No, Jedi is a balance of the force, right?
Sith is absolute.
That's a Jedi thing.
It's about emotions and being in touch with your emotions
and Jedi about locking and blocking your emotions out.
What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah.
Huh.
Well, that's why I like you need a balance in the force.
How you doing, gruesome?
What have you been doing since you confessed your love for Sybil
and she turned you down?
Mostly just replaying that moment in my mind.
Over and over again.
Hey, monster, which color do you think Abe would look best in?
Stop.
Maroon.
I have so much Star Wars merchandise, but here's the thing.
Listen, guys, most of the Star Wars merchandise that I have
was like random Christmas gifts, okay?
It was like Christmas presents.
Oh, look, the new Star Wars is coming out.
Here's five t-shirts.
Okay, I guess.
And they're comfortable.
I have like 30 Star Wars t-shirts.
Not because I think Star Wars is the best thing I've ever seen
is because, you know, like Trekkies to infinity and beyond, right?
I'm a Trekkie.
I don't like Star Wars, but because I get them as gifts.
Hi, Sybil.
I don't have much time to chat, Sam.
I've got so much to plan.
All right, let's be in the wedding.
Is there room in the wedding party for Max and me?
As president of the U.S. and high priest of the ocean chimps,
I'm qualified both legally and spiritually to conduct the ceremony.
How to put this tactfully?
They'll be serving ice cream in hell before I let them-
They do serve ice cream in hell.
Oh, come on.
Vanilla's my favorite.
Like, you had a perfect opportunity for a hysterical joke.
I'm able to consult, by the way.
What's the wedding gonna be like?
Is it a shotgun wedding?
Max, what a thing to ask.
Oh, wait, he doesn't know what that means, does he?
Just let him enjoy his fantasy version for a while.
Did we accidentally leave our monster in here?
We just left him here and she left him here?
We're gonna have to get a leash.
Back in the trunk, gruesome!
Don't you dare take him away.
Stop this!
I've been spilling all the details of my whirlwind romance with Abe.
I'm getting really emotional.
You're fucking with my Sith mentality.
Why am I made to suffer so?
Okay, well, that's bad.
Did we accidentally leave our monster in here?
Don't you dare take him away.
Okay, so...
Good luck, Sybil.
Wedding stuff.
Snooty overpriced wedding invitations.
I still haven't gotten my invitation.
Strange, since the wedding's only hours away.
Lost in the mail, I'm sure.
I know what that's like.
Cake at a wedding?
Okay.
Uh, cake in the mail.
Enjoying all this quality time with Sybil?
Let me see this one more time.
It's so fucking horrible.
All right, let's go out the exit.
It's not... what?
Hey, it's open.
Just kidding.
Oh, I didn't do that.
Why?
Over like 12...
8 episodes, 9 episodes.
You're gonna do that to me?
Okay.
Anything else I can do?
What about the fox?
Sure, they talk about personality.
But Miss America always goes to the fox.
All right, we have egg, gun.
Let's just...
I want to go check out Stinky's.
Can I drive anywhere?
Well, hold on.
One thing at a time.
Hmm, they're closed.
Closed.
Hi, how are these guys doing?
Hello, and welcome to Pimplica.
Okay, um, got any car upgrades?
What car upgrades are you offering this time?
Turn your vehicle into a super fast, nitro-burning, funny car.
Funny car.
Offer in Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
I like funny things.
Oh yeah, I can take that mother out on the street away,
push her to the red line until she screams,
pop the clutch, kick you the afterburners,
and smoke them pigs as I sail over the county line.
Whee!
You can't see over the wheel, Max.
Fascist.
Hey, Jerma lied about the clown car.
What a perfect opportunity for you to come in here.
Thanks to the five community subs.
Five more.
He gave more earlier, too.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
What's wrong with the bluster?
Is it my imagination or is Bluster Blaster acting weirder than normal?
He suffered severe injuries while testing an experimental wireless
antenna.
You guys, you guys, I'm in so much pain right now.
We have been using laughing gas to keep him sedated.
I know what that's like, too, except not laughing gas.
Somebody says, how do I get a sub?
Now, how do I get one?
Well, you either wait till one of somebody in the community
graciously sends a community subs or it's $5.99.
That's not right.
It's $4.99.
Adding a dollar for no reason.
Last time I looked at that.
$5.99 for a sub.
It's actually $4.99.
I'm like scamming.
I have my own button down there.
That would be so fucked up.
It's $5.99.
We want that nitrous upgrade for our car.
I want to go fast enough to blow the stink off of Sam.
We're sorry, but your vehicle has gone on to a better place.
We are sorry for your loss.
Can't you fix it?
We're afraid the car is completely dead.
Repairing it is beyond our current skill level.
It still had so much to live for.
Can't you guys upgrade the DeSoto?
The nitrous speed upgrade is only for vehicles in working condition.
We're sorry, but your vehicle is completely dead.
Where are you guys getting enough nitrous to do car upgrades?
Blaster Blaster was given laughing gas to ease his suffering after his recent injury.
Wait, you've been selling the leftovers from his prescription?
And these guys are the only ones not going to hell.
The rest of his prescription.
So long, cops.
Stay virtuous.
Somebody just subscribed to Twitch Prime.
Thanks for the Twitch Prime.
Okay, so we need to I can't believe the DeSoto died.
I think I can do better than that.
I can do better like like streamer voice.
Hey, thanks for that Twitch Prime.
No, hey, thanks.
Hey, that's Twitch Prime, man.
Really appreciate it.
That was better.
I had to turn the volume down.
Didn't want to hurt anybody.
All right, let's go.
How the fuck do I get?
I need to like go to her apartment.
We can't get up there.
And where is her apartment?
The thing's blocking the way.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ow, my stomach.
Hey, hey, buddy.
Throw us that remote control, would you?
You're gonna need this.
Wow.
Thanks, buddy.
Be you later.
What a perfect time loop.
So we have the remote control, the Boxing Betty remote.
Where's Boxing Betty?
Wasn't Boxing Betty...
Where was Boxing Betty?
In my closet?
I can't get up to the closet, though.
Well, oh, right, right, over here, over here.
Nobody gonna come in here.
I don't need to come in here.
I'm just gonna control from outside here.
Come on.
The remote won't do much good while he's dead.
He's dead.
Damn it.
What else could I control?
Is there any electronic device?
Maybe can I go in here?
Will he let me in here now?
How's the search going, Flint?
Still no sign of Bosco, fellas.
I'll let you know as soon as he shows up.
Maybe down in the sewer.
I don't think Flint's taking us seriously, Max.
If I were as cool as him, I wouldn't take us seriously either.
Is there something I can...
Let me check down here.
Can I talk to this person?
Hey, pal.
Can you?
Whoa, hey.
Yours really knows how to fill out a soul.
Well, I never.
No, that means you're fucking stacked.
When I was working out, and I started to wear tight,
extra-small shirts,
almost like if I moved the wrong way,
I would just pop out of them.
People would say,
man, you're really filling out shirts now.
And I'd be like, yeah.
But why does this shirt only come down to your belly button?
Oh, it's just, you know, it's a new style.
Okay, so...
No siree.
What about the karaoke machine?
Nothing doing.
Gumball machine?
Not happening.
Video games?
Can I control the video games?
Bosco.
No siree.
No.
The train?
Fuck, what do I do with this?
It's, I'm so close.
You've got to get Bosco's soul back.
I know, I know.
I'm trying.
What's the map say?
Why can't every belief system have a transit system this efficient?
The ego on this guy.
Guys, the only ego that I like has another G
and toasts up in a minute,
and you put butter and a little bit of cinnamon on it,
and it's great for breakfast.
I know that that was probably the worst thing you've heard
in like probably the last six months.
It was terrible, but I don't care.
If you saw that joke on like fucking ABC this morning,
like your parents would have laughed,
and that's all it matters is a laugh.
It doesn't matter where it comes from.
What about on you?
Can I control one of these guys?
No way.
I can't like do anything with this.
Not even your parents would have laughed.
I guarantee they would have.
If I call my grandmother right now,
and I make that same joke, she'll go...
No siree, delicious, yeah.
Guys, do you know how...
Never mind.
This is a thing.
No, I can't talk about this.
I'm not going to talk about this
because this is like a thing that I've wanted to do
for a very long time, and I haven't done it yet.
No, I can't because in case I do it,
it's going to...
It has to be done right,
and then no one can know about it.
What about Sybil's office?
The car?
Not happening.
Nothing in here I can do.
Well, no, have they left at this point?
Wait a minute.
To when you throw the egg.
Yeah, okay.
I know.
Because blocking the door.
What are you doing?
Somebody's blocking our office door from the inside.
No, I just gave them the egg.
Don't they leave?
I don't want to bother ourselves.
AI?
TAR?
Can I give this to them?
That doesn't need a new AI.
Whoa, wait.
I know what needs a new brain.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
It's all neat and computery.
It's got to help out with your laser light show.
Thanks, Sam and Max.
This will be playful.
He's reading chat.
You can never prove that.
That ain't right.
What did you guys do?
Reconfiguring neural network donors.
So you're back from outer space.
Evacuate!
Did you think I'd struggle?
Did I lay down and die?
I'll reach you out.
You will not die.
I will survive.
I need Timmy.
Did you just kill that rat?
So cold.
So f***ing cold.
Medic!
For emergency medical service, press or say one now.
Just save my boy, Hanger and Timmy!
Live, damn it, live!
How many other people were inside?
Well, if that doesn't help us get into hell, nothing will.
That just got turned upside down.
There's like 30 dead rats in here.
He stood up and they were all playing cards and stuff and it just tipped upside down.
Somebody's head got crushed with a desk right here.
Think about that.
There's like four or five people at that blackjack table.
When he stood up, it flipped over and crushed him.
What the f***?
Hey, robot.
Greetings, morons.
Dude, that's crazy.
You guys are going to put me in like the f***ing hospital.
Okay, what's with the attitude?
What's with the attitude?
The artificial intelligence unit you installed is refreshingly blunt, jackass.
My time subroutines have been disabled.
I don't care what I say anymore.
This is my life.
What?
That was like perfect.
Does he still not know?
Let me hold on a minute.
Is it this?
Now that you're mostly rat-free, what's next for you, Mr. Maimtron?
I am planning to relocate.
Not that it is any of your business.
Are you going to make a move to a town that's right for you?
Affirmative.
A town to keep me moving, to keep me proven with some energy.
All right, we need your help.
Do us a favor.
I can't go for that.
No can do.
With my new AI, I can only be controlled remotely.
I can do that.
We'll talk to you later.
You can call me.
Call me any time.
Ooh, let me, let me.
There'll be snow flurries in hell before I let you have control of a two-story tall
battle robot, Max.
Here I go again on my own.
Down the only open road I ever known.
Right.
Like a drifter, I was born no one.
I know how to do it.
All right, so I'm going to start breaking stuff.
Earth is on fire.
Smash.
What are we smashing?
Foscos?
No, you're never going to get it.
Mama said knock you out.
I'm going to knock you out.
And we'll have fun, fun, fun, now that daddy took the T-Bird away.
Stop getting me riled up.
I saw like two people tell me to, I'm not doing that anymore.
It's a nice day for a white wedding.
Watch out, boys.
She'll chew you up.
She's a man, either.
Thanks for the $50 just came in from TalksRay.
50 bucks.
There's no message, just 5,000 bits.
That's a lot of fucking money.
Thank you.
Talk about mudflaps.
My gal's gone.
It's a lot of money.
Thank you for that.
What am I supposed to break here?
In the manhole?
That leads to a land down under where women grow and men plunder.
Vegemite Sandwich.
I know these songs.
We didn't start the fire.
It was always burning since the world's been turning.
I'm going to sing you a song.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
And I feel fine.
I read the news today, oh boy.
I don't know that one.
What's that one?
I read the news today, oh boy.
No.
Earth is on fire.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I had to stop that one halfway.
It's not a rock.
It's a rock monster.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What am I supposed to be seeing?
Hello?
Is there anybody in there?
They're just too shy shy.
What was I supposed to do?
Get me back in here.
Did I click on everything I possibly could click?
No.
Maybe they could've cracked.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Never heard of the Beatles.
Night train.
Tomo Arigato, Mr. Roboto.
All right, got the token.
Look.
I don't think she'd appreciate a ride on the Soul Train as much as we would.
So now we can go down here.
Game's fucking easy.
Sam and Max.
Could you guys hurry it up?
I've heard about a robot full of seriously injured rats
and I've got a quota to fill.
Hold your pale horses.
We're working on it.
Easy when you reach out.
Yeah, but look.
Here's the thing.
Yeah, we've been doing this for like an hour,
but we've just been having fun just talking and fucking around.
It doesn't matter.
Like the game is fun.
It's cool.
We get to see references and fun stuff,
but like we're just taking our time.
Like right now, 35 seconds have gone by
and I didn't click this guy yet.
You know, like it's all right.
That just happened.
That's what happened.
One adult and one Max, please.
How did you guys get a token?
We've done things, Harry.
Things we're not proud of.
Wicked things.
Shut up, Max.
Zombie Abraham Lincoln didn't want his.
Oh, good.
Put your token in the machine to call the train.
Crazy.
Hey, that's how it goes.
Everybody get on board.
Oh, I thought they were going to do the Ozzy Osbourne train.
That was the intro.
Oh, God.
Hold on.
I wasn't cut out for this today.
I should have taken another day.
Get out of here.
Leave me alone.
I'm not even logged in.
This is hell.
Thank you for holding.
No, hell.
What number were you trying to reach?
No, they are 666.
Yeah, no problem.
See you soon.
Can I help you?
We want to talk to the guy in charge.
He's taken Bosco's soul too early.
I see.
His schedule is full at the moment, but I'll see what I can do.
And you are?
Sam and Max.
The ones who killed me.
Oh, yes.
The ones who sent me here.
Oh, I'll get right on that.
Jrgen, be a peach and clear out my calendar for...
Who authorized this?
A giant horned skull?
Really?
I'm sorry.
I thought this was 2008.
Teeth are disgusting.
Oh, very well.
Cancel all my appointments, would you?
I'll be in my office.
Oh, did I forget to introduce you.
How careless of me.
You can have a seat and wait if you like.
He doesn't like the skull.
Somebody really needs an antacid.
Stomach acid.
I wonder if that thing folds out into a bed of spikes.
What are you talking about?
I really shouldn't be watching my weight.
Don't worry.
They're all nearsighted.
I've lost it.
I said the word stomach acid once and then my internet like fucked up for a second.
Did I drop frames?
This is hell.
Hold please.
Yes.
That's like annoying if I am.
Shouldn't be.
Can we get a tour?
Can we get a tour of the place?
You'll have to guide yourselves.
I have to answer the phones.
For eternity.
Don't we need a visitor's badge or something?
No.
As frequent contributors, you can go where you like.
Just look, though.
Don't touch anything.
Okay.
We want to visit Bosco.
Where's he hanging out?
No.
If he is a friend of yours, he has a personalized hell in the back.
At least he has a sick gamer headset.
Uh, that's like an original Xbox headset.
This isn't at all what I expected from hell.
It's, uh, soulless.
Yeah, which is kind of missing the whole point of hell.
But the corporate presence has done wonders for our productivity.
My soul taking operation, which you destroyed.
The soul crushing on delivery system, which you destroyed.
Hell is now running at peak efficiency.
Or at least it was.
Well, we want to talk to Satan.
We want to talk to Satan.
Yes.
Well, I fear you just missed him.
Much like you just missed saving me.
Back right to the hell.
You even had your chance.
Well, yeah.
But you know, you are kind of evil.
And you killed us.
No matter.
I will mention you are waiting next time the boss visits.
He drops by every 66 years or so.
Where's all the cool hell stuff?
Yeah.
Like the carnivorous.
Cool hell stuff.
Acid baths and karaoke bars.
Please.
This is so divinely comical.
This is the 21st century dog.
Cool hell stuff.
All right.
Second.
Hold all our calls.
Yes.
This is so funny to the point that I cannot remember to laugh.
Can we actually get to it?
All right.
Hold on.
Give me, give me a second here.
Let me save it.
I haven't done a manual save in a while.
No, this is, this is autosave, does it?
Right.
No, it's fine.
Fucking stress.
I thought we were much further in.
Okay.
Whatever.
We're fine.
One adult.
I, I specifically remember the doctor said don't, no screaming.
Skipping.
We already saw this.
I know.
Okay.
Give me.
Why is it so close?
It's like.
Tom Jeremy, I want to make sure.
All right.
I'm fucking.
I'm turned off all steam.
I'm disabling steam forever.
You've already seen this.
Let it play out in the background.
I've disabled the whole steam overlay.
Like it's not, it's impossible for anything to pop up, right?
Impossible.
If I, if the whole steam relays off, it's impossible.
Sure.
Okay.
We're good.
Yeah, but the doctor told me.
We've already seen it.
I'm just going to get there.
Thank God I had the autosave.
Otherwise, I mean, it's just the intro.
Don't worry about this.
You can, this is how.
Yeah.
This.
Okay.
We got it.
Yeah.
We've already seen it.
But, but, but, but, but, but, but, okay.
Good.
Good morning.
Wait, was Bosco found out?
Okay.
Now we're going to say.
Nothing happened.
Now, Jeremy, I want to make sure you're very, very clear about this.
The doctor did not sound anything like this.
But for some reason, every single doctor needs to be like this crazy,
intelligent, sage, wizard type person in every piece of media.
Geez.
Must be from.
I'm not supposed to frame George Washington.
Yeah.
Guy, you find me a fictional doctor and a fictional George Washington.
And I guarantee you that they both have the same voice.
Fictional doctor, fictional George Washington.
And no, like George Clooney in ER doesn't count.
I'm talking like, like a cartoon doctor.
The corporate presence.
Hugh Bliss.
This is, people doesn't work here.
Hey, shambling corporate presence.
Dr. Mario.
That's not, that's no, sorry.
What you working on?
Dr. Mario is a costume that Mario wears.
If I put a doctor's like costume on, would I then be a doctor?
No, it's a costume that Mario wears.
Mario's a plumber.
He's not a doctor.
Mario's not a doctor.
He is a plumber and he wore a doctor costume one time in like 1989
and had like a Tetris game.
He's not a doctor.
Oh, that's funny.
Coffee cup from you.
You don't have to be damned to work here, but it helps.
It looks cold.
I can't even.
Hey, SCP.
SCP.
Oh, I see.
Is that intentional?
Had to bring with 10 years ago, 12 years ago.
That has to be.
Hey, buddy.
Look, it's Hugh Bliss.
What the fuck?
Hi, I'm Hugh Bliss.
I don't say hi.
Nice trick with your head.
Do exorcisms work on people already in hell?
Messed up.
All right, well, we missed you.
You busy?
We're going for lunch.
Want to come?
Did you get that meeting request I sent?
What are your dreams?
Have mercy on us.
Sorry about killing you last year.
It happens.
What do you do here?
I work for the largest division at hell, the FCC.
Doing what?
I bleep.
Right here in your cubicle?
In front of Satan and everyone?
You bleep?
I listen for naughty words, and I bleep them.
No swearing, no cursing, and no oaths of any kind.
That takes the fun out of everything.
Exactly.
Now, can we say?
Can we say?
No.
What about?
Tugger?
Yanker?
Tool handler?
Okay, good to know.
You're a lousy bleeper.
What about that time Jimmy Hoffa said,
ride the fucking surfboard?
Oh yeah, you should have bleeped the shit out of that.
Fucking is not on the list.
Sorry.
Tool handler is safe.
Later, Hugh Bliss.
Okay, well, let's see, we got Brady Culture.
Brady Culture?
Got some good callbacks here.
I didn't even know he was sick.
How do I not get an obituary?
I'm a major television star,
an international buzz generator.
A cosmic pain in my backside.
How did you get here?
What are you doing in hell?
Living large.
I'd been a temp in purgatory for the last year and a half,
but finally, I'm a full-time employee.
Right, we don't actually care.
We're famous TV stars.
Sticks and stones.
I don't care what anyone says.
It's the announcer from You Don't Know Jack.
And I'm happy.
How would you know?
That's a very specific thing to know.
Wow, I think it is.
How'd your fro grow back so fast?
Elf tears.
Does your on-the-job training include evil laughsmanship?
I guess that's a no.
No, I can't do like an employee match on that laugh, guys.
I'm sorry.
I know I usually do that, but I can't.
Laugh.
I could do way better than that.
You know I can.
Somebody click clip when I did it before.
I can't do that right now.
I'm going to slow down.
Forgive me.
My mouth is too parched for a spit tape, but you like hell?
I mean, sure, the wailing of millions of tortured souls gets a little old.
And my headphones are 10 sizes too small, but none of that matters.
Because I finally found someone who believes in me.
Satan.
He is the only true equal opportunity employer.
Do it now and rip your ass.
No, I'm not going to.
I can't.
Later, Brady.
I screamed loud.
And like I can't do that.
I can't be screaming.
Like I'm telling you, type into Google, can you scream after a colonoscopy?
And some of the major results are no.
Soft talking?
Okay, who forgot to fill the pot?
Reminder, your mama don't work here.
Hey, we needed her token.
The only place here that's room temperature.
Things have gotten so bad they had to cut minimum wage in half.
You're going to tear your stitches.
I don't think I have stitches.
What the hell?
What the fuck is this?
Sexual harassment and you.
Oh, I've touched all those places several times.
What?
Wait, wait.
What did Sam just say?
Of what?
Holy shit, Sam.
Ah, they went for the swivel throne.
Good choice.
Nothing inspires investors like a few dead smugglers frozen in carbonite.
Ask anyone.
I like that chair.
I want a chair like this.
Okay.
What's this poster?
I guess the kitten was off on another photo shoot.
What about this pam?
A key card.
Can I take that or do I have to distract them or something?
Can we have your key card?
Well, considering you already took it, I guess so.
I don't need it anymore.
Now that I'm full time in hell, suckers.
Yeah, Brady.
You win.
All right.
Well, we can just have it.
Greed, lust, greed.
Oh, big door.
Sam and Max relief.
Why do we have like our own personal stuff here?
Have we been here before?
Dry erase blood.
Sam and Max relief.
Ah, what kind of hellish bas relief is this?
I don't know.
And yet a mysterious voice compels me to enter.
Let's go in.
I'm impressed by the decor, but what kind of place is this?
Are we Satan?
They've got little play sets of all our pals.
Hey, Bosco.
Hang on.
I know what this is.
This is where they keep all the souls of people who died during our cases.
They opened it already, but I had a speech prepared and everything.
You guys have killed a lot of people.
Oh, my goodness.
Uh, okay.
Max the Destroyer.
Sam the Devourer.
Very flattering like this.
Max the Destroyer.
They got my bad side.
I want a do-over.
Looks like everybody's permanent record's on file, but they're all locked.
Plaque.
Dedicated to Sam and Max for a lifetime of generous donations of souls,
both evil and simply led astray.
Somebody said Hornstein and Smog.
Bosco, we see you in there.
Dear God, they're watching me.
Help me!
This is fucked up.
You're like stuck in a nightmare.
It's everyone we know who's died in the last year.
I must have lost count.
Oh, no, it's Santa.
Oh, yeah, Santa's dead.
I'll never get any work done with that infernal cry.
Street diorama?
That looks like our car.
What did it do to deserve help?
Oh, the car is dead.
Wait, can we get like, can we get in here and take the heart of the car?
It's one of Santa's elves.
Oh, dear, I'll never make my ship date with all these distractions.
Is that grandpa stinky?
More looky-loos.
Have we really killed this many people in this last season or two?
Well, let's read the key card.
Let's see what it says.
The key card unlocked the dioramas.
Where to?
The street?
This is as fast as it goes, little buddy.
We are in hell!
Exit diorama, horn, boomer, driver.
Go for jump?
Maybe I need an item to do something here.
Heat.
No, I don't think I can do anything here.
Let's try the other ones.
We expand it again.
I thought I'd finally figured out how to keep the weight off.
Can we use it again?
Let's go to the Bosco one, right?
Street theater diorama.
There we go.
Oh, no, I didn't have to do it.
We're coming to watch me.
Bosco, you're nude.
It's okay, baby.
We're all still watching you.
For eternity.
Demon Mariachi.
Demon Sibyl.
Why do we have to watch Bosco naked?
Nitrous oxide?
Dentist chair?
What the fuck?
Howdy, Demon Sibyl.
What you doing?
I'm analyzing Bosco and it's causing him excruciating.
Never-ending agony.
Wow.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to break it.
Well, Bosco, I've almost gotten to the root of your problems,
but I'll have to keep studying you.
For ever and ever.
No, we can pull him out of here.
Stop looking at me, woman!
We're just gonna suck like a vacuum down here.
Like a demon vacuum.
We'll just suck him up.
Hi, Demon Mama Bosco.
This is my hell.
That's Ms. Demon Mama Bosco to you.
What are you doing?
Not really.
Bosco suffer eternally.
Isn't it great?
You know, it's all right.
I've still got my eyes on you, sugar.
Sweet Tabasco, make it stop.
Okay.
What about Demon Mariachi?
Demon Mariachi?
What's your story?
I got a job watching Bosco for all eternity.
I don't have that much time.
Can we just call it a day now?
Is this game for kids?
No, I just can't find a way.
It's like a car accident or a funeral.
But not as beautiful.
No.
Senor, I am watching you all the time.
T-H-E-M!
No, it's not, obviously.
This is not a game for kids.
Is this a game for kids?
Forget about like the naked guy that's over here.
Nah, I don't know.
You know, it's tough.
There's some funny humor and...
All right.
Well, let's go look at...
Let's go talk to Bosco.
What do I have in my inventory?
Coffee cup.
I need coffee.
There's some funny humor.
It's nitrous oxide.
Looks like Bosco has some dental work in his future.
It'll be twice as hilarious without anesthesia.
It's a cartoon because it's...
So it's for kids.
It looks pretty comfy.
If you find getting your teeth yanked out of your skull comfy.
Yes, I understand that...
Yes, that is like going to GameStop and buying like outlast for your 10-year-old.
Because it's a video game, so my kids will like it.
All right.
What if it looks pretty comfy?
If you find getting your teeth yanked out of your skull comfy.
My son said he wanted to have this game called Outlast.
Do you know about the mature themes in that game?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shut up.
Just give me it.
Okay, so I have nitrous oxide.
Okay, so somebody upstairs wants this, right?
Can I do anything about Bosco?
Hey, hey there, Bosco.
Don't look at me.
Trust me.
We don't want to see you any more than you want to be seen.
What is actually going on here?
Why are you standing naked on a stage in front of your mother,
your therapist, and a Mexican?
Wait, wait, I know this one.
I'm in some kind of one-man play, but it never ends.
And I don't know any of the lines.
Bosco's personal hell.
A play in an infinite number of acts.
I thought waiting for Godot sucked.
What do you have to do in this play?
I just got done playing a game of truth or dare with all my ex-girlfriends.
And after this, I gotta get a root canal while taking an Algebra quiz.
No, that would suck.
That's not cool.
I didn't even study.
I could do this.
I could be naked down there.
That doesn't bother me at all.
If I was just on stage naked,
and like there was fucking 5,000 people in the audience,
I'd just be like, whatever.
I don't care.
No, don't care.
Like, sorry, guys.
I didn't, this is not supposed to be happening,
but I'm just here and this is what's happening.
I don't care.
You put me in like a dentist chair for eternity.
I've, I'll take the naked guy over the dentist.
So how are things?
Oh, you know, not too bad, except I'm in hell.
Eternal damnation sure made somebody cranky.
What if everyone was screaming at this balls, balls, balls,
everyone's screaming that.
I mean, at that point, it becomes like a show
and maybe people will pay for it.
And I'll start doing like the floss
to the beat of them saying balls.
And then people start laughing
and everyone just starts like having a great time.
So what, what am I going to do?
Who cares?
Oh, I'm trying to buy things.
Standing butt naked on an empty stage
miles below the surface of the earth.
Does it look like I have anything?
I would get boring after 10 minutes.
Do you have any chainsaw gasoline?
I really am in hell.
Are you sure that would get boring after 10 minutes?
I don't know about that.
I feel like I could stand that in the audience
for like two hours.
I mean, it would that's balls, balls, balls, balls.
I could probably sit there
and then think that was interesting
for like at least a couple hours.
And the person's doing the floss faster and faster
and they don't get to stop.
You wouldn't pay a hundred dollars for a good seat.
I would pay like a hundred and fifty dollars
for like fucking front row seats
and get like two like Bud Lights
and just sit there and just have fun.
If this is hell.
They probably serve Bud Light in hell.
I'm assuming they do.
I forgot what I was going to say.
Cheer up, Bosco.
None of this is real.
It's all an illusion.
What are you talking about?
Of course it's real.
I've been pinching myself.
Bud Light Lime.
My face is real.
My chest is real.
My stomach is real.
Okay, we get your point.
Bud Light Lime is fucking disgusting.
I remember when I drank Bud Light Lime
for the first time.
All right.
Do you know what Bud Light Lime tastes like?
Are you ready?
I'm going to ruin this for you if you like it.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to ruin it.
Do you know what grape,
grapefruit juice tastes like?
Squeeze a grapefruit.
Squeeze a grapefruit into a glass.
Water it down with water
and leave it in the sun.
Take it back in and add yeast to it and stir it up.
They tried to market that as some cool beach drink.
You would just, oh.
You know that, hold on.
You know, I hope this is important.
I haven't been here for like four days.
You got to let me do this.
You know they have like a special Budweiser now
in like a case.
It's like a Budweiser in a case.
Why do you have that?
They're trying to sell it
as if it's like some special secret beer or something.
It's like a Bud, Budweiser Reserve.
No, but wait, the clientele of like Budweiser Red,
mostly are people that get like in fights at tailgate parties.
They're not going to buy that.
I'd be like, this is, that's just the way it is.
Why don't you just leave?
I can't.
I've got to perform.
They're watching me.
Who?
Them.
I scared myself.
He peaked the mic.
All right, so long.
See you around naked Bosco.
I don't think I'll ever stop seeing you.
Save me.
I can only stand girly drinks.
What, what, what, what does that even classify?
Okay, so we got nitrous oxide, key card, nitrous into the coffee, but like lime.
Now we already know that I'm like an alcohol snob.
You guys already know that.
You guys have made fun of me extensively for it.
Let's go check the other ones.
Jeremy, you can't put gas in a mug.
If you seal it with fucking rattle's wrap, you can.
The special Budweiser you're talking about is
a jolly old elf working hard on his delivery,
the sound of children playing, and a jolly Christmas jingle.
How could this possibly be hell?
Maybe Santa's Jewish?
Why?
The 50th anniversary Budweiser is to celebrate the moon landing?
Is it really?
Is they putting moon rocks in it?
It's true.
Oh, hey, we're back.
Moonshine.
I've had moonshine before.
Well, it is a bit warm.
How did you mention it?
But I can't worry about that.
I've got too much work to do recalling this blasted toy.
But these beastly children are ruining my concentration.
What the hell?
Up, up, up, up.
I feel like that face that was that caterpillar was making
is just how I feel like all the time.
Like I'm in hell.
Right there.
That one.
I feel like that's me.
I love that mood.
You know what I mean?
What dangerous toy are you recalling this time?
It's the Rex Skirmish Danger Hero action figure.
Completely irresponsible, and it just keeps coming back even worse.
It's taking me four months just to get them to remove the candy
flavored lickable lead based chest tattoo.
OK.
Well, what's the audio?
You hate the matter with the babies, Chris.
Santa loves children.
Why do people always assume that I took the one job where
there's only one day a year.
There's even a chance I'll be near children with very strict
rules that they're not allowed to see me.
Holy shit.
When you put it that way.
I got fucking woke mood as fuck.
A hero man like me has been married for centuries with no kids.
Did you think of that?
I'm trying really hard not to think about that right now or ever again.
That is pretty true, though.
What's going on?
What kind of miserable work are you doing here, Santa?
I'm recalling dangerous toys.
Ah, all the dangerous toys of my years.
Like laughing gas.
The savage tongue ripper.
Little patio fisticuffs.
The belligerent drunken leprechaun.
Oh, I remember that one.
He really wet himself.
Having to recall toys must be horrible for you.
Hellish even.
Oh my, no.
I love recalling toys.
The problem is these babies make it impossible to concentrate.
Okay.
Have a holly jolly eternal damnation.
What did I do to deserve this?
Looks like he's in Jimmy Neutron.
All right, demon babies.
Leave the nice Santa alone and let him do his work.
Santa has not yet learned true suffering.
Anyone want some coffee?
Nope.
Computer.
Christmas tree.
This long after Christmas and Santa still got his tree up?
Hey, it's never a problem and never mind.
I was going to say like it's not a problem if you leave it up all year
and then it's Christmas again or something whatever.
I've fooled with enough toy playing switches for one lifetime.
Wee!
Must be one of those Rex skirmish dolls.
Do your worst, Dr. Despicable.
You'll never kill Rex skirmish.
Trampoline?
Is this trampoline still useless?
Yep, still useless.
And anything else?
It's fun to go back and look at old stuff.
I don't know how to work it.
Computers in hell all run Linux.
Oh wow.
Programmer joke.
Ah, this record player brings back memories.
Oh, you never forget your first semi-successful exorcism.
We go in Santa's room.
It's magically sealed.
Okay, well we have laughing gas.
Anything else to do here?
Torture me Elmer, must feel right at home here.
Want some Santa?
I don't want to waste it.
Let's get out of this one.
Still have a couple more to look at.
We did this one.
This one didn't do this one.
Let's go toy factory.
Looks like some kind of vaguely familiar hellish toy factory, Max.
Oh boy, I want to see the assembly line where the injection mold the doll's heads.
I hear it's strangely hypnotic.
Oh, there's no assembly line.
I make all my toys one at a time.
It's the only way to guarantee each child loves it as much as I do.
Okay, so this is a Santa competitor.
I'm going to waste it.
Oh, this is the casino machine.
His arm's off.
Tis but a flesh wound.
Computer.
I hope the elf can work this stuff.
Because I sure can.
Okay, what else we got in here?
We have this computer.
Wait, wait, fire's thing, we sure have in hell.
No, I can't take it.
Look, Max, it's our favorite demonically possessed elf.
Well, maybe not favorite, but he's in the top five at least.
Oh, hey guys.
How did you end up here?
We haven't seen you since the exorcism.
How'd you end up here?
I'm not sure.
When I woke up, I went outside to find Santa.
But the last thing I saw was a horrible monster.
I must have fainted.
When I woke up, I was in this fancy factory.
I guess Santa gave me another promotion.
Looks like Charlie Brown.
You're looking cheper.
Are you enjoying sending overpriced toys
out to overprivileged children?
Oh no, it's awful.
No matter what I do, my toys keep getting sent back.
Okay, look, just because you're an elf
doesn't mean you're good at making toys.
Stop living the stereotype.
Oh, I'm pretty good at making toys.
But what good is that when there are no children
to enjoy them?
It's like being in, well, the place where bad people go
and it's really hot.
Tampa?
Oh, he doesn't know.
He really doesn't know.
It's the hottest new toy for Christmas.
The Rex Skirmish Danger Hero action figure.
He's a testosterone packed champion of the glorious art
of savage brutality.
Sounds like someone's overcompensating.
The head office keeps sending him back,
but I know I can make him perfect.
Okay, so can we help?
Max and I wrote the book on gleefully violent entertainment.
I'm especially proud of the appendix
detailing the ripping out thereof.
Why don't you let us help with your toy?
Maybe I have been overthinking it.
Your childish simplicity could be just what I need.
I live in Tampa.
Childlike.
Me too.
First, what kind of cool outfit should he have?
Cool outfit.
Okay, I think we need some info here.
It's titanium.
Commando.
Wait, no, maybe make it naked.
That makes sense, right?
He should be all buff and shirtless
with a big flaming skull tattoo on his chest.
Done.
Now, what should his action path attachment be?
Magic spatula.
A list of enemies.
A list of enemies?
Or a handbag.
A handbag.
Tampa.
Yeah, everyone's from Tampa.
We're all from Tampa.
A sequined yet tasteful handbag
to show he's in touch with his feminine side.
I can do that.
Now, what's his tragic flaw?
What drives him to seek out danger?
All right, this is Bosco.
Acid for blood.
Brain disease.
Chronic halitosis.
Didn't Sybil say that she was trying to figure that out?
Acid for blood.
Death.
It's, yeah.
Because we're going to replace this with the Bosco, I'm assuming.
He's buried under a mountain of high interest credit card debt
and outstanding student loans.
Okay.
Thanks for the suggestions, guys.
Well, he keeps on giving us, you know,
he has plenty of money.
Never mind.
Bosco has a lot of money.
Recalled.
I made him a trillionaire.
Yeah, there it goes.
All right, so let's do this guy.
Hello, Mr. L.
We'll help with your toy.
All right.
First, what kind of cool outfit should he have?
Naked.
He should be all buff and sh-
Okay.
A handbag.
A sequined, yet tasteful, handbag
to show he's in touch with his feminine son.
I can do that.
Okay.
And acid for blood.
Highly caustic acid for blood
and various related digestive disorders.
Okay, thanks.
I'll send out the new version right away.
Hold on.
That goes into, because Santa has the same shit.
Didn't Santa talk about this?
No, I mean-
Are these like, are these interconnected?
They have to be, right?
Hi there, Santa.
Yeah, okay.
So this is, so what's your problem?
Why don't you soak down again?
I can't work with these plastic babies
and I can't get rid of them.
It's hell!
Okay.
What toy are you making?
Which toy is that you're working on again?
Some deathtrap called the
Wrecksturmish Danger Hero doll.
I'm gonna be recalling the hell out of this one.
Yeah.
Okay, so make it so he can't recall it.
So there's nothing he can recall.
Everybody knows Santa loves kids.
Yeah, so much that I moved-
Yeah, we already heard this.
He cool, Santa.
Must be one of those Wrecksturmish dolls.
To your worst, Dr. Despicable.
You'll never kill Wrecksturmish!
How do you know that you're not in hell right now?
I don't know, could be.
We can shoot-
Okay.
Blood!
Guess this is the end of old Wrecksturmish!
Wait, what?
Geez, Sam!
If you don't like the gift, just say so next time!
I just murdered him!
Acid blood!
Did you come to enjoy my wonderful toy?
I thought I'd never be rid of those blasted types!
Why am I just dumping-
Alright.
I'm not pressing that button.
He is.
Oh, listen to that silence!
It's heaven!
Okay.
So, we've made-
Thank you, Sam and Max.
You have been very good boys.
Is that Santa's souls?
But as long as Satan owns our souls, we have to stay put!
Okay, so we got two.
Hell efficiency.
Oh, we're losing efficiency!
Okay.
Ooh!
Let's go down to the cooking show.
Now, my next dish is based on a favorite recipe of Grandpa Stinky's.
Which I'm taking to the ninth circle of hell.
To the base of milk and pickle juice, just add a little chocolate covered horseradish.
That was an emerald.
That was an-
Some of you guys don't know about emerald.
Emerald is who made cooking shows.
Cool.
Alright, so we got coffee, nitrous oxide, book display.
Growing up stinky.
The early years.
Trashy celebrity biographies and hell are a natural combination.
Everybody knows emerald?
I don't think so.
That was like 15 years ago.
Emerald has not been really on TV in more than almost a decade and a half.
Alright, we got Stinky's-
Stinky's baby book.
Okay.
What about bucket of lard?
I don't think I can eat lard on my diet.
Emerald Lagasse.
Oh, microphone.
Yes, I have a question for Miss Stinky.
Your seven layer bars turn my stool bright orange.
Is that normal?
You will pay for your insolence.
What about the cure?
The cooler's not for food.
It's for the inevitable organ transplants following the show.
Put something in the food?
Sticky tar cake.
Oh, here it is.
Tar cake sample.
That's one of the few things that's not better with tar.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, well, let's talk to Stinky.
Well, well, well.
So you're finally paying the price for offing your own grandpa, huh, Stinky?
Do not interfere with my plan, Saturday Max.
Uh, do you need a lozenge or something?
Ah, that's not our Stinky, Max.
It's just a demon cleverly disguised as her.
Go away.
Making food for Michael's birthday.
What's cooking?
I've been wondering when you two would show up.
He remembered us.
See, we were killed.
Girl Stinky really did murder you.
Maybe next time a couple of travelers from the future come to you with a warning,
you'll pay attention.
Murdered my impacted colon.
It was not but a mountain climbing accident that felled old Stinky.
I'm getting a lot of references to, like, the last three days in this episode.
It's weird.
Did you say you were killed in a mountain climbing accident?
Aye, I was in the Himalayas halfway up the north face of the devil's nipple
when Mr. Port Cables just fell off.
If only someone had developed a better adhesive.
Interesting how those things work, yeah.
How's hell treating you?
Your hell is just being on a TV show.
You doing good?
I thought for sure a mean old coot like you would end up buried up to your neck in poo or something.
Yeah, this doesn't seem so bad.
Not bad.
Just look at that crowd hanging on her every word.
And they've got the nerve to reduce me to her, to her sous chef.
I can't appreciate a real genius of the culinary dark art.
Culinary dark arts.
Does that just mean you burn everything?
Right?
Like, what would be, like, the bad thing to do?
So what is the deal between you and girl Stinky anyway?
Evil cooking.
Yeah, you just leave it in the oven too long.
I made her what she is today, but now they call me her apprentice.
Making mac and cheese?
Hold on, you making mac and cheese?
Give us the recipe.
This stream is not gonna go forward until you say how you're making it.
I hope you don't say, like, box orange mac and cheese.
I want to hear the real recipe.
Don't say box orange mac and cheese.
Kraft mac and cheese with barbecue sauce.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What if it is in the box?
Don't do that.
It's Kraft shells and cheese.
No, you look at one cheese plus three noodles.
What?
So Stinky's got her own show.
What's the big deal?
Every second this show stays on the air is like swallowing another handful of
acid dipped razor blades, twisting and churning in my gut.
Well, as long as you aren't bitter.
I actually love the boxed orange mac and cheese.
We'll let you get back to the show.
Yeah, we can't wait to try it.
It's like, I love it.
I told you guys this a long time ago.
Everything I say is not like 90.
I don't even need to say the fucking thing you already know.
Okay, so I got a book out of the fridge.
It's just for show.
But what a show it is.
I can't leave.
Can I?
It's magically sealed.
All right.
Well, let's try this.
Hey, hey, what was that?
What was that guy doing in here?
Hey, someone opened the two teeth drawer.
Two teeth.
Wow.
Jimmy's personal file is huge.
He must have been committing a dozen unpardonable sins a week.
We got Jimmy's file.
Okay, let's go to the car.
Try this.
Shells and cheese is better.
This is as fast as it goes a little buddy.
So can I use?
I have to go back to like the real world.
Shells and cheese is better.
Well, I can't.
I'm sorry.
I cannot give you an opinion on that.
It depends on the day.
Sometimes you feel like shells.
Sometimes you feel like elbow macaroni.
Sometimes you feel like rigatoni.
I'm not going to be like a pasta narcissist here.
We've taken a tremendous hit in efficiency.
Are we going to have to demote you back to hourly?
No, no, no, no, sir.
I'll do better.
Hey, Lucifer, we want to talk to you.
What?
I'm quite busy.
Settle in an appointment with my secretary.
Man, six years a jerk.
Who does he think he is?
We're going to have to do some more damage to get his attention.
Okay, so let me go back to the car.
No, get back in here.
Cheese, it's I mean, people crumble crackers,
cheese, it's and stuff on their mac and cheese.
That's, I mean, I don't see an issue with that.
Baked macaroni, bread crumbs.
Let me go up here.
He said cheese, it's in milk.
Yeah, but I selectively read the first half of that.
Well, is this going to work?
I can't.
The de Soto's dead.
I don't want to waste it.
What are you guys doing here?
How'd you get back up here so fast?
Guys, I'm omnipresent.
Now, keep it down.
These mortals can't see or hear me.
Please death.
You can't take Timmy.
He ain't never hurt nobody.
Okay, how did, how could he be so cruel?
You wouldn't be so cruel as to take poor tiny Timmy away, would you?
Just look at that kid.
He's got the life expectancy of a tomato and a knife commercial.
Heartless fiend.
Can I watch?
I don't see what everybody's so upset about.
He's going to a better place than this one.
That doesn't really narrow it down much.
Heaven, dimwit.
Heaven?
Timmy seems like he's a heaven kid.
Why not give him a break?
It's out of my control.
He could go at any moment, but don't worry.
The kid with his permanent record is definitely going to heaven.
Permanent record.
Well, weren't you just down there looking at records?
How's the death business going?
Finally slowed down.
Now that those rats have shuffled off.
But it'd be easier if I didn't have to cover every death myself.
Can I go take another?
Assistant or partner would help everything.
Yeah, that's what you think at first.
Well, you got a lot of work to do.
You've got to take care of everybody that dies all by yourself.
No, it's not as bad as it sounds.
All my travel and expenses are covered.
How did you even get up here?
I'm looming.
Part of the job description.
Take it easy, Harry.
So I've got Jimmy's file.
Nothing doing.
Can I give Jimmy's file?
It's Timmy Two Teeth's permanent record.
Looks like he's led a pretty sin-free life.
So we're going to swap these.
I always knew that kid was all talk and no action.
Why are we doing this?
Doesn't that seem like very bad?
Hands off that permanent record.
We're going to get rid of him.
By the looks of this kid, I'm going to be needing that any minute.
There's still a chance he'll pull through, right?
Uh, sure.
Okay, so how do we get rid of him?
How do we make him leave?
Somebody else's die?
I need 20 milligrams of monosodium glutamate, staff.
How come there's only one rat here?
We're not very good at medicine, apparently.
It's really good to see.
All right, uh, and they can't upgrade the soda.
Nitrous speed upgrade is only for vehicles in working condition.
We're sorry, but your vehicle is completely free.
I have to bring the vehicle back to life.
Okay, I already got nitrous.
So long, cops.
Stay virtuous.
He has a mustache body.
How are you holding up, Timmy?
What does that even mean?
Who's that?
An angel?
A mustache body?
He ain't got much time left.
He's starting to hallucinate and the Tourette's is getting worse.
What's that, St. Peter?
Why, yes, I'd love to play with you.
Okay, well, obviously we have to get that file.
We got to swap it or something.
Let's go in here.
Hey, Sybil.
How are things?
Do I have anything I can do with you in here?
It's been a while since we've last spoken.
Can we give you anything for the wedding?
We kept one of the zombie's arms that fell off.
It's old and kind of blue now.
You want to borrow it?
That's a lovely offer, but no thanks.
Why can't we be in the wedding party from Max and me?
As president of the U.S.
and high priest of the ocean,
chance spiritually to conduct the ceremony.
Oops.
How to put this tactfully?
Yeah, we already did that one.
All right, so.
Good luck, Sybil.
Key card, Stinky's book, coffee, hell coffee.
I'm not sharing it.
Gonna have my cup of joe.
What do I need this coffee for?
Jimmy's file, gun.
Don't judge me for this, Max.
It's for his own good.
Bless you.
All right, monster, monster.
I've never handled a monster before.
Hey.
I'll have to figure out how this works exactly.
I missed your opportunity.
I'm back and I'm knocking.
Holy running, Oswald.
Get that reference.
Thank you.
It's Timmy Two Teeth's permanent record.
Looks like he's led a pretty sin-free life.
I always knew that kid was all talk and no action.
Swap.
For your own good, kid.
It'll make the eulogy more interesting.
What did you do?
Give that back.
Settle down.
The doctor said if you exert yourself,
a simple straight.
That's terrible.
Let me just look at his file and we can go straight off.
That's so bad.
Hello.
Really, this kid's file?
Harry, please.
You can't expect us to do your job for you.
I swore it was smaller.
Kid must have really been busy on his death bed.
You should have seen it.
It was like every single letter ever written to Hot Bunny
combined into one debaucherous rampage.
Oh, well.
You can tell me about it on the way to hell then.
Later.
My God.
He's in a bad place now.
Just kidding.
He's in hell.
Oh, my God.
That's terrible.
Holy shit.
Do you want a book or something?
I don't think anyone wants to hear about Stinky's early years.
How are you holding up, Jimmy?
I'll just say you,
Timmy would have wanted it that way.
Well, okay.
So long, cops.
Go back to hell.
I need to bring the car back to life.
You've watched every stream?
For the past month?
What's up?
That's all really I have to say.
Can I do anything with it if this thing works for everyone?
Oh, it dodged.
Is that a colonoscopy reference?
How would that be a colonoscopy reference?
All right.
Let's go back to the...
Let me see the efficiency.
This is the first stream I've watched in a month.
Welcome back.
We're happy to have you.
Nice to meet you.
Usamemac streams are my favorite.
Well, I'm glad you like them.
It's a fun game.
All right.
So we've got hell.
No more two teeth.
We've got efficiency down.
This is the last stream I've watched.
Well, it is.
This is currently the last stream you have watched.
Unless you have like three streams open at the same time.
And even if you have like four or five streams open,
I'm the person that you're listening to right now.
I'm the last streamer you've heard.
So, I mean, they just talked, but I'm talking now.
So I'm still the last thing you've heard.
What a waste.
No, no.
Can I just put it in there?
This ought to boost the DeSoto spirit.
Taint just shrunk to the perfect size when I put it in.
Now that's efficiency.
So now it's alive, right?
Well, should we check it out?
Cruising the endless...
Let me just check it out.
This is a...
Go.
Wow.
Jump.
Go for jump.
That didn't work.
Are you supposed to do this?
Are we going into Bosco's painting?
Are we about to save Bosco?
Holy shit.
My mom walked in when I was watching Naked Bosco.
All right, we got Bosco's soul.
Hill efficiency is almost down to red.
We need to do the cooking show.
We've got to do something with the cooking show.
I've got the baby book.
I've got the coffee.
We're almost there.
And we'll find out real soon after I take a piss.
Don't go anywhere.
Well, go pee.
But take me with you, though.
You know, if you're on, like, a phone or an iPad or, like,
you have to get to take the whole thing into the bathroom.
Just like, no, no, no, take...
Never mind.
I'll be back in two minutes.
Okay, we are back.
Did you miss me?
So cooking show diorama.
We need to get the souls out of here.
I'm not entirely sure how.
I still haven't done anything with the coffee.
I'll save this for a...
I've done Santa's workshop.
We did the theater.
We did the toy factory.
Wait, did we?
Is he still alive?
No, he...
Yeah, no, he...
Grandpa Stinky looks even more miserable than usual.
I didn't think it was possible.
Wait, where is Stinky?
Oh, she's in here.
Okay.
You're gonna put coffee in here?
Nope.
Um, I feel like I missed something in this room somehow.
The rats.
How are you folks enjoying the show?
I thought the casino was nice, but this?
What a treat.
I ain't no expert on food or nothing,
but that Stinky's a master chef.
I think we're gonna have to come down here for vacation every year.
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
Tyrone!
Now, Miss Stinky, I've warned you about the responsibilities
that come with hosting a live program.
It won't happen again, I promise.
Okay.
Just keep the language clean and that'd be fabulous.
I'd hate to have to cancel such a wonderful show.
Hey, Timmy.
Hiya, Chimmy.
Is your soul finally at peace?
Oh, he's swearing.
I'm f***ing static to be on stage with such a f***ing...
Ah-ha!
What was that?
What is he doing?
Calm down, kid.
Did you taste her f***ed, f***ed, f***ed nutmeg with a f***?
Whoa.
Simply divine.
I don't know if this might be it.
It's not a kid's game.
Oh my! Oh no!
And the smells.
It's like teen p***.
Ooh!
With a f***ed f***.
I simply cannot allow this.
This show is cancelled!
Well, that was exciting.
What?
Cancelled.
You're finally free, Grandpa Stinky.
Seen her denying it.
My show got cancelled.
Made to suffer like I suffered.
I can't remember when I've been so happy.
Hmm, was that a happy ending or not?
I just can't tell anymore.
I watched all 16 hours of Heroes of Might and Magic.
But I'm not!
Until you reprobates get the rights to my soul,
I still can't leave.
Well, I've got news for you.
We're in the red here.
Looks like we've broken hell.
Don't worry.
We can always raise some more.
Heroes of Might and Magic is...
I'll let that high and mighty Satan jerk
won't be too busy to talk to us now.
Right after this game is over.
After finishing season two of Sam and Max,
episode five of the last, this is the final episode,
I'm going to try to finish that campaign that I was already on.
This is a two-parter clean-up stream.
Not a two-parter, it's the same part.
But okay, now hell is in a turmoil.
Let's go check it out.
I was under the impression you were here to increase productivity.
And yet our efficiency is at an all-time low.
How do you explain that discrepancy?
Vladimir, what the hell are you guys talking about?
We haven't been properly introduced.
We're Sam and Max.
You know from the statues.
Pleased to meet you.
I hope you've guessed my name.
Yeah, and you better release our pal souls from hell
because my excitable little friend is getting angry.
And I'm angry too.
There's no need for that kind of talk.
I'll gladly release your friends.
Just sign this release.
And that's that.
Well, gee, Satan.
Thanks.
Now just do me a favor and think of the most horrible thing you can imagine.
Okay.
No, wait.
Let's think of a horrible thing.
Good.
Now, off you go.
Hey, what just happened?
He traded his soul for that of all your friends.
They never read the fine print.
Now, Sam will spend eternity in his own personal hell.
That's my favorite character.
Why would you take him away?
This doesn't seem so bad.
Right, little buddy?
Hell's a poppin'.
No, you took away the best character
and you replaced it with the worst character.
Look, I'm sad too.
Wait, hold on.
It's busted.
There shall be no letting off of steam in hell.
No, at least a hell of my stuff.
At least I can bring my stuff to hell with me.
A saw?
A bone saw?
Hey, a bone saw.
Gosh, I hope I can find someone's bones to cut.
Oh, Banang.
There shall be no quenching of thirst in hell.
No, he didn't do it.
Dark board?
One of these days we're gonna finish that game.
But I don't like darts, Sam.
They're dangerous.
Max, where are you?
What are you doing here?
All right, peepers.
Let's talk.
What are you talking about?
I'm your partner and best friend.
But stop being so silly
and let's work on our next case.
What happened to Max and why are you here?
A likable partner?
That's ridiculous.
Always been your best friend
and I always will be forever.
You're one of those crafty demons, aren't you?
Of course not.
We've been pals since we were little.
We used to take baths together.
What?
We did not.
I took the whole tub.
What case are we working on?
Don't you remember?
The commissioner wants us to investigate the proposed bill on income tax reform.
It's fascinating.
All right, well, let's go, little buddy.
Let's be off on our new case.
We can't leave without doing extensive research, silly.
Oh, all right.
You direct me up, little buddy.
But I didn't say anything funny.
Where's the rest of the noose collection, peepers?
Who would keep nooses in an office?
That's just silly.
Must get Max.
Hole in the wall.
Who's in here?
Stop! Do not look outside!
Hey, Sam.
How's it going in there?
Am I like a dollhouse?
I remember now.
You're my partner.
Well, duh.
Um, help me.
You could come in here, little buddy.
It's the most horrible thing ever.
Sounds fun, Sam, but I'm too big to fit in the hole.
Hey, Sam.
Listen to this.
It's funny.
That's what she said.
Get me out of here.
Yeah, that was pretty bad.
That was awful.
What's going on out there?
After everybody saw what Satan did to you,
it got pretty awkward.
I don't like hell when it gets all tense like this.
Well, you should be in here.
Isn't the same without you, Max.
I'm bored out here, too.
Can you believe that Satan guy tricking me like that?
Let's stack onion rings on his horns
and throw them in the pit where they keep the gluttonous.
It's that kind of thinking outside the box
that makes me wish you were my partner.
Yeah, peepers suck.
Peepers keeps telling me he's my partner.
What?
Nobody tries to steal my sidekick.
I always thought you were the sidekick.
Oh, sure thing, Sam.
My name's first in the title.
Can't you find a way in here?
Think tiny thoughts.
I always do.
I'm still too big to squeeze through that hole, though.
Okay.
Don't go anywhere, Max.
So I get to get bigger or he has to get smaller?
Relax, Sam.
You're getting all weird on me.
Okay, so that's...
I'm obviously little.
Never thought I'd see his ugly mug again.
Can we leave the office together?
We can't leave now, Sam.
It hasn't been eternity yet.
Turn the lights off and bone saw him?
Unfortunately, this is a 12-gauge bone saw
and he's clearly 9-gauge.
I'm small bones, a big...
Where's a heart saw when you need one?
Well, why is this floating here?
It's taunting me with its precariousness.
Can I shoot it?
Can I bone saw it?
I mean, is this...
You can't die in hell.
Missed?
Satan must have messed up my aim to torment me.
But you're a lousy shot in real life, too.
I said Satan must have messed up my aim.
Can I move the chair?
Can I stand on the chair and saw the rope?
I can't reach it.
Satan just put it there to torment me.
Arsenic?
Arsenic.
I know just the person for this.
It's past the expiration date, Sam.
Totally unusable.
Spoiled poison.
That's the worst.
Oh, what do I have here?
So what?
Just go get in here.
Is it gonna work?
Hey, Max, look alive.
I'm about to scream yes, but I'm not gonna...
What do I do with this?
Don't eat it.
Just get in here.
Max, meet Demon Peepers.
Oh, hi.
Demon Peepers here says he's my partner and best friend.
Hey there.
What are you...
Oh, God!
Is that Peepers?
Hi, Leonard.
That was some of your best work ever, Max.
He's dead.
I'm really proud of what I did around the carotid artery.
Yes, excellent grouping.
Shall we motor?
Let's.
All right, Satan.
Boss fight.
That hell was practically inescapable.
Sorry, Satan.
Your demon imposter was no match for the true power of friendship and cooperation.
Plus I ripped out his kidneys.
Well, this does put me into a bit of a pickle.
Management will have my head over this.
Management?
Who could possibly be more horrible and universally reviled than Satan?
Oh...
Who is Super Satan?
Oh, it's the...
It's the Poopers!
So, you finally figured it out.
Sure took you long enough.
I take it you already know, my bosses.
Know us?
The soda...
These fools have been essential to our plans.
But how did you get...
But you can't beat Satan.
When did you...
What have you got against us?
And what did we do?
Please, one question at a time.
Okay, so the soda team are the rulers of all hell.
How did you guys go from minor annoyances to become rulers of hell?
You still don't get it?
Hate is the real power.
We thought nothing could be worse than former child stars.
But that was before we beat Brady Culture to death
and realized we were destined for much greater evil.
It just felt so right!
So we began to commit greater atrocities on the world.
Reality television.
Politics.
The Intelligent Design Movement.
His eyes are fucked.
Each step made us more hated and more powerful.
Okay, what did we ever do to you?
You only ruined our birthday.
It was one year ago today.
You thwarted my journey to evil pop stardom.
And you gave me some bitter diarrhea.
And these glasses aren't cheap.
And worst of all, the Mariachis never came to sing for us.
Wow, who knew the princes of hell would be such whiny little babies?
Well, what's with Santa?
You meant to get Santa possessed by a demon.
No, that was a clerical error.
We thought some corporate efficiency would help Satan get his act together.
But it seems he'll always be antiquated and useless.
You know I'm standing right here.
We did mean to kill that elf, though.
So what's the endgame here?
It would be better running hell than Satan is.
The old ways are dying.
It's time to bring evil into the 21st century.
Our subcontracting and outsourcing of soul capture and processing
has increased our efficiency tenfold.
But we still have to convince the shareholders to believe in hell
as a relevant player in the afterlife.
Current marketplace realities and underlying economic considerations
mean we have to downsize.
Satan, we kept you on staff for sentimental reasons.
But your performance continues to disappoint.
But if you'll give me another chance.
Clean out your desk and don't come back!
That was fun!
What about the other ones?
What about the other employees?
We've heard quite enough, thank you.
Very well.
Now that you've helped us depose Satan,
there's nothing stopping us from continuing our agenda
for domination of the infernal realms!
Right in the middle of that sentence.
Thanks, Salmon Max.
That would have gone flat soul against his nose.
First action item, seducing a human woman
and conceiving the new hellspawn.
Footprint, like crush his face.
I'm all a second, tempting humanity to repeat the original sin.
I've got it covered.
And finally, winning a new modern soul over to hell.
Because of the technical skill required,
I'll be handling that one, obviously.
Thanks for all your help, Salmon Max.
All right.
I think unwittingly bringing about the apocalypse
is a first for us, little buddy.
Sorry, I completely zoned out there.
Did they say anything important?
Never mind.
Okay, so what we need to do,
let's go talk to people.
Got three things.
Lord, keep up the good work.
Nobody has any new dialogue?
Hey, buddy.
What about that time Jimmy Hoffa said,
ride the bucking surfboard?
Bucking is not on the list.
No, no new dialogue.
Later, Hugh Bliss.
That's the list.
Can I see the list?
It's a list of swear words.
Why do they all start with S?
Listen to that.
They all start with S.
Okay.
So let's go to the new board.
Action items.
Conceive Hellspawn.
Original sin.
Challenge for soul.
Two.
Original sin.
Three.
Challenge for soul.
All right.
How do we get it?
How are we going to do original sin?
What about you?
Do you have anything new?
You got a new boss.
So then I says to Gonza.
I says, Gonza?
Yes.
Help us stop the popper.
You want to help us get Satan back in charge.
Why would I do that?
With that fossil out of the way,
I'm next in line for the promotion
at the next shareholders meeting.
Wish me luck.
Why didn't you tell us the poppers were your bosses?
I thought it was obvious.
You're a liar.
You actually think someone could be as mean
and despicable as that by accident?
You are so slow.
This is bullshit.
You said you were going to start season three
right after this.
Liar.
Did you see where Satan went?
There all the husbands go, I imagine.
Such disrespect for the prince of darkness.
Prince of darkness is more like it.
Well, now we have to wait in line to see the poppers.
During a lot about the clown car,
thanks to the five community subs.
Five community subs from the clown car.
Thank you for that.
I want to see the poppers.
Call the poppers back here.
They are there on a very important meeting right now.
If you want to talk to them,
you'll have to find them for yourself.
I'm going to go back to the real world.
See you later, Jorgen.
Yeah, sure.
So anyway, then I says.
Let's head back up.
Wait, magazines.
Anything else?
Stuttgart nightlife.
Figures the reading material in hell would be two months old.
Did I play season three off stream?
I just couldn't.
I couldn't take it.
I had to know what happened.
No.
Why would I play season three before finishing season two?
You don't skip a season.
Just a spike.
Come on in.
We're throwing one hell of a bachelor party for Lincoln in here.
Why would I go and spike you guys?
I haven't been paying you to party.
I spent 40 years tracking down the man who trashed my store.
Hiring the best private investigators.
It's time you tell me where he is.
Tell me where he is.
Well, there he is.
Bosco?
You mean you never thought to mention
that your suspect was my son?
I thought it was obvious.
You're the one who's been after me all this time.
It was all just a simple misunderstanding.
Yeah, that is pretty dappy.
A lifetime of persecution.
All just a simple misunderstanding.
Hope you're not mad, baby.
We all go a little mad sometimes, mother.
Run along to the bunker and I'll be in later with your dinner.
I'm a ghost, baby.
I don't eat dinner.
Just do it!
Bye, Sam and Max.
Well, now that case is wrapped up.
Wow, that was quick.
You coming, Bosco?
Party?
That was just like a disconnected from server.
No fade out.
No, like, drifting away.
Maybe even crazier.
Okay, well, let's go.
We got a lot of things going on out here.
Let's start right to left.
Well, well, well, specs.
Just what do you think you're doing here?
I'm going to do what Satan never had the skills to attempt.
I'm going to win the soul of a computer.
Ha, you talk big now.
But wait until you've heard me play.
Beat that.
You can do it.
Play like you've never played before.
Come on, Chippy.
No, I didn't.
Well, then I'll just be taking-
Oh, but there's a technicality.
Right.
Sub clause 48, section five in the contract clearly states that
entities running at less than eight megahertz are entitled to infinite do-overs.
I don't remember reading that.
Oh, specs.
A perfectionist like you and you didn't even bother to read the details of the contract?
Well, all right.
It doesn't matter.
I'll still win.
Okay, so first of all, five community subs came in from anonymous, whoever you are.
Thank you for the five subs.
Whoever you are, whoever the sacred person is.
All right, Chippy.
Don't you know any better songs to play?
It's kind of important.
We've got to get Chippy some music.
He's just too set in his ways.
We've got to get Chippy a-
We've got to get Chippy a video game cartridge from down below.
Stick it in there.
Right?
I mean, that's what I think.
Dump coffee on him.
No, that would just break him.
Hey, cops, what's shaking?
Specs has challenged us to a musical contest.
Yeah, that's what we're going to do.
Solid gold violin.
Second prize, eternal damnation.
Who'd be stupid enough to take on that kind of challenge?
We cannot talk him out of it.
Okay, so, hey, we want you to upgrade our car.
We want to upgrade our car.
We're sorry, but your car already has the nitrous upgrade installed.
He's just afraid to go near me.
Okay.
So long, cops.
Stay virtuous.
So, I've got to get the cartridge to put in there from down in the cartridge pile.
Right to left.
Let's go, Mac.
Can I go into-
Can I go into Sninky's?
I can.
We use only the freshest ingredients in our pauper's own forbidden fruit of knowledge cider.
One sip, and for the first time, you know the difference between good and evil.
I don't know.
I've heard some bad things.
Ah, our competitors are just afraid that if you start selling this, you'll become too successful.
I don't need to tell you the advantages of an exclusive beverage distribution deal.
Seeing as how you're such a savvy businesswoman.
I'm making fucking mac and cheese and nobody can stop me.
What, weren't you making mac and cheese like an hour and a half ago?
How long have you been making it?
That seems like pretty long.
I think it's like takes 12 minutes.
Slow cooking it.
Don't overdo it.
Don't eat too much.
Wait, I said the thing.
Did I do-
Oh, whatever.
All right, fruit cider.
Hey, Stinky, how you doing?
What's up, Stinky?
Oh, good.
It's Virgil and Ulysses.
Actually, it's-
Maybe you two can give me some advice.
Mr. Whizzer's offer sounds very tempting.
Now, it all comes down to your per bottle cut.
Don't accept anything less than 10% for the first year
with quarterly renegotiations.
Yeah, I'll get a meme.
It's just mac and cheese.
Shut up, Max.
I'm still not sure.
Well, hold on.
Stinky's baby book.
I'm pretty sure she's already read it.
What about-
Do you want to read Stinky's baby book?
I don't think anyone wants to hear about Stinky's early years.
What about Grandpa?
Hey, Grandpa Stinky.
We found Stinky's baby book.
Good, good.
Quick, read page 33.
Well, I'm going to take this thing and put a cover on it.
Don't think I'm going to put it in here.
Out loud, you cretin.
Oh, let's see.
Bake, mumble, read.
Fish sticks, tar, coffee, ice cream.
What kind of baby book is this, anyway?
It's a cookbook.
The name of the recipe.
Read the name.
The Cake of the Damned.
What?
That'll teach her.
Well, maybe you, good sir,
would like to hear more about the delicious,
forbidden fruit of knowledge, cider.
Oh, no.
What have I done?
That has turned Stinky into a cake.
The last person I would have figured was secretly a cake.
She's been a cake this whole time?
Nothing doing.
What was the point of that?
Get lost, wizard.
Stinky ain't buying.
Stop interfering with my plans to bring hell on earth.
Well, what's going on here, Stinky?
Tell me what's going on.
My friends, stay a while and listen.
What turned you friendly so quickly?
I've made a terrible mistake.
You've got to help me get her back.
You old coot.
You tricked us into making girl Stinky disappear.
She didn't disappear.
She's still there.
When you read her true name, you revealed her true form.
Her true form?
Is she a demon or something?
In a sense, I suppose.
She's the most diabolical recipe ever created.
The cake of the damned.
Did we hear you right?
Girl Stinky is a cake?
Aye, to start.
I'd been experimenting with evil food for decades.
What the fuck is this?
You fiend!
It was for the good of mankind.
Humanity is weak and pathetic.
Always complaining about food poisoning
and severe gastrointestinal disorder.
But only the strongest could survive my dishes.
I'd create a master race.
And the most vile.
Combining an entree, sides, and dessert all into one bowl.
No, never.
The cake of the damned.
Okay.
Well, now what are we supposed to do?
Do your evil spell and get girl Stinky back to normal.
You've got to do what I did that fateful night.
The cake of the damned was only the first step.
I knew that to take the dish from just evil to purely diabolical,
it would need more.
An appetizer.
So I added spare ribs.
Plasphemy!
The next thing I knew, she appeared.
The rib is the key.
Service of an order of short ribs.
I'll take an order of ribs.
If I could find any, I would have already done it myself.
With this barbecue convention going on,
good luck finding anybody in the city with spare ribs.
All right, well, obviously we have to take a rib from somebody.
Whatever you do, Grandpa Stinky,
don't let Whizzer tempt you into making that deal.
Don't listen to them.
They're just jealous of your experience and wise life choices.
All right, well, he does have a point there.
You really think a guy dressed like that
knows about wise life choices?
You're right, of course.
Look at me.
I need a rib.
As weak and old fool as I've ever been.
The girl always was better at keeping her head about her,
much as I hate to admit it.
Okay, so we need a rib to get that back to normal.
We need to just shave it off at this point.
You know what I'm saying?
Stay strong, Stinky.
Don't leave me alone with him.
What was it?
Okay, I need to get in.
What do I need to get?
And a spare rib, a rib.
Let's talk to you.
Get lost, Whizzer.
Stinky ain't buying.
Stop interfering with my plans to bring hell unheard.
All right, so we know we need...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just check everything.
The decor is ingenious.
No matter how many times I come in,
I just have to look at these things again.
No, this is bullshit.
All right, so I need a rib.
I need a game cartridge.
Two things that I need.
So let's keep going.
Right to left.
Satan.
Can we borrow some of your stuff, Satan?
Well, I suppose so.
I was hoping to sell it on eBay.
What if I received no bids?
Is the cross-country driving or something?
Father of Lies 666 might have something to do with that.
Let's see here.
What do you got?
One super long barbed paperclip chain.
And one grocery list written on company letterhead.
Am I taking all those?
I know you're the source of all evil,
but wasting office supplies for personal use?
That's just wrong.
Oh, God, I took it all.
Okay, so paperclip chain, grocery list,
and pork rinds.
Let's talk to Satan.
Hiya, Satan.
How's it hanging, old scratch?
The financial situation is quite dire, I'm afraid.
I did wash your windshield for you.
Oh, I must have left my change in my other suit.
Max?
I'm naked.
Yes.
Well.
What?
All right.
Hey, don't harp your nose.
Still angry at us for getting you fired and everything.
Angry?
You destroyed my entire life
and unleashed an unspeakable evil on the earth.
All out of carelessness and a desire for personal gain.
I invented that.
I couldn't be more proud.
I mean, it's true.
Now just to hunt for a new job going.
A few nibbles, but nothing promising.
I'm expecting a call from Rupert Murdoch next week.
All right, what about some advice?
Any suggestions on how to stop the poppers?
Oh, so we're stopping them now, are we?
I just assumed, since you spent so much time helping them.
Jeez, Satan.
We said we were sorry.
Or at least thought it real hard.
Oh, very well.
I began to lose power when people stopped taking me seriously.
Too many comical football mascots
and cartoon depictions on the devil family.
That's funny.
You can ruin their plans.
Make them appear ineffectual.
I'll be able to stage a corporate takeover.
Okay.
We never expected that getting you fired would leave you with nothing.
Yeah, after all these years, you should at least have a retirement fund.
No, my golden parachute has just this cardboard box of all my possessions.
Will condemn for food.
I feel somewhat foolish.
God bless.
Considering the billions of insurance salesmen
and investment bankers I've met over the centuries.
Okay, well, do you need anything?
Did you get you a blanket or something?
Might I trouble you to crash on your couch?
It's just me in the box.
Oh, we want to help you to help yourself.
The poppers are stealing all of your material.
Satan can't crash on my glory days at that.
If they're successful with this, I would do it.
They'll be unstoppable.
I feel like he'd owe you it just doesn't have the same rain.
You know, Satan own you a solid is that's kind of a big deal.
You're going for a new job.
I still have to update my resume.
It's been millennia.
Make sure you include detail oriented.
Okay.
The poppers are stealing all of your material.
Yes, and from my glory days at that.
If they're successful with making that's making a deal with say they'll be unstoppable.
Wizard made me do it just doesn't have the same rain.
No, the deal is hey buddy, you're crashing on my couch.
I'm going to hold that over your head forever.
That's not a deal.
That's you said can I sleep on your couch and I just said yes,
we didn't make a deal.
It wasn't yes, but no, no, no, it's just sure sleep on my couch.
Hope you enjoy yourself.
Do you need some water or something?
For the rest of your entire existence.
I'm going to hold this over your head and when I need something
you don't answer you look like a bad guy.
Stay strong, Satan.
You'll make it through this.
You're a survivor.
All right, we stop doing this.
That doesn't look hungry for pork rinds.
Stop it.
What are you doing this for?
The DeSoto seems different somehow.
I think I'll just walk for now.
He's Satan.
He already is a bad guy.
Nobody's the bad guy of their own story.
Everyone says he's the bad guy.
You know what I mean?
He thinks he's like the good guy somehow.
Somebody's blocking our office door from the inside.
How you feeling Timmy?
Oh, feel like ****.
That's a handsome Jack line.
Are you completely cured now?
The doctors say I'm all better.
But I've still got my ****ed up condition.
Hyped for Borderlands 3?
Not really.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Maintrom's looking after me until daddy gets back from his party.
We're playing song lyric trivia.
What the **** was that?
What the **** was it?
Get that out of here.
What the **** are you doing?
Glad to be back from hell.
Oh yeah.
I'm just disappointed the ****ed soda poppers never showed up at the hospital.
It was my dying wish to see them because I'm their biggest fan ever.
No Timmy, that's wrong.
Max is right.
The poppers are evil, wicked creatures.
And besides, I'm their biggest fan ever.
Ask me anything about them.
All right.
Let me pay.
Back to normal here.
What is Peeper's real name?
What's Peeper's real name?
Everybody knows his name is ****.
What was that?
I said his name is ****.
You lose again.
So we have to stop Hugh Bliss from censoring.
I'm on top of the game today, guys.
Stop Hugh Bliss from censoring so we get the name.
Are you old enough to write, Timmy?
Oh **** yeah.
I've been in the hospital so much that daddy's been homeschooling me.
So far, I've learned to write ampersands, asterisks, number signs, and exclamation points.
Max is the king of poppers trivia.
Do your **** worst.
Okay, so what's the name of the wizard's doctor?
In episode 205, the joy of specs.
What was the name of wizard's urologist?
Is that a trick question?
Because in that episode, wizard saw a gastroenterologist.
Dr. Thundercolon.
Sorry, Mr. Max, but I'm just too **** good.
Max is the king of poppers trivia.
Do your **** worst.
All right, so how old is specs?
How old is specs?
He's officially nine years old because he was born on a live day.
You lose again.
Nine years old, all right.
Hold on.
Max is the king of poppers trivia.
Do your **** worst.
Yeah, it really is, just the past week.
Okay, how many times has wizard been arrested?
Four times.
Gotcha, it's four times total.
But one was and another was declared unconstitutional by the supreme court.
Sorry, Mr. Max, but I'm just too **** good.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Maintromp's looking after me until he gets back to his party playing song lyric trivia.
Mr. Maintromp's almost as good as me.
The boy cheats.
Okay, so we got some info here that we're going to ****.
I'm piecing together this gigantic puzzle.
Let's talk to Maintromp.
No, idiots, I am engaged in a song trivia contest with this precocious rat child.
Guess it's better to say goodbye to you.
Goodbye to you.
Okay, I didn't go right to left.
I was supposed to go right to left.
Oh, baby, I'm going to be loving you all night long.
Did he swallow that microphone?
I think he swallowed the microphone.
Peepers is making the move on Sybil.
She's totally into it.
Just wanted to make sure my dementia hasn't kicked in early.
You can forget all about old Stoneface.
What the hell?
Peepers is the only man you need now.
Oh, Peepers.
He ate the karaoke machine or he swallowed the microphone of the
karaoke machine.
Lady, you're making me all tingly.
Hey, Peepers.
You may have Sybil fooled, but we can see what you truly are.
Evil will reign.
You must not disturb the vessel.
Fruit cider, bow and saw, paperclip chain, Satan's grocery list.
All right, one at a time.
Hold on, let's talk to Sybil.
Sybil, pay attention.
Sybil, Sybil, Sybil.
Snap out of it, Sybil.
It's, it's Peepers.
I know it is, but I've just never seen him this way before.
Oh, you're going to be seeing a lot more.
Over here.
Look over here.
Don't be a fool.
Show some dignity, Sybil.
But he's just dreamy.
It's like for the first time, I'm seeing him for who he really is.
I hate that.
I have hate, I hate that.
What the fuck?
What about your wedding?
Don't forget about Abe.
Abe who?
Oh, Lincoln.
Right.
I haven't forgotten.
I've just, I'm still single tonight.
All right?
Whoa.
What happened to the monster?
Oh, is he gone?
I wasn't paying attention.
Said something about Abe's bachelor party.
Abe's bachelor party?
Does it bother you that Abe's having a bachelor party?
No, we should all be free to have a little fun before we're married.
Oh, stop doing that.
I, I don't want to see that.
That face is just, again, it's blah.
Try to stay chaste, Sybil.
Mind your own business.
Okay.
Well, we obviously have to break up the bachelor party.
Cake at a wedding?
Oh, okay.
Hey, it's open.
It's open.
You're open.
Just had to, I like, I had that hurt me saying that.
So that's where the Esperanto bookstore is.
Okay, so we need to, we need...
Bosco's.
There's a lot going on here.
You're just in time for the stripper.
Wait, is Bosco the stripper?
Shake that moneymaker.
Take it off.
Take it all off.
I knew women were hard to find in our neighborhood,
but I didn't think it was this bad.
You people should be ashamed.
It's a living.
All right, what's in the cup?
Mr. Featherly.
Oh, a salmon, Max.
Is this a kid's game?
Better not have a cow in there.
Oh, I'll show you who's hiding a cow.
This chicken's drinking vodka.
Another celebrity meltdown.
Shut up.
You don't know my world.
What are you doing here?
You're not one of Lincoln's friends.
I'm taking bets on which one of these amateur drinkers
is going to pass out twice.
You ought to be ashamed, Jimmy.
That's just wrong.
50 bucks on the chicken.
What?
That's a pretty good investment.
You should see a pretty high rate of return.
Bosco, we freed you from your personal hell.
You don't have to be naked anymore.
Oh, that wasn't part of my health.
I just like to be naked.
And I'm not the only one who should be naked.
Woo!
That's right, baby.
Nah, I'd better keep it.
It should take all night to solve this case.
Sober him up.
Honest Abe, after all you and Sybil have been through,
you got a stripper?
Look, fellas, I'm marrying Sybil tomorrow.
Today, I got needs just like any other giant stonehead.
It's a color full of punch.
Punch.
What are we going to put?
Are we going to put fruit cider in the punch?
This ought to add some kick to their punch.
That's a snap right there.
Well, boys, another round?
Oh, dear.
Oh, man.
Oh, he passed out first.
I'm naked!
Oh, I thought we were all just saying that.
What have I done?
I'm so ashamed.
He's going to do the camera again.
I should have known hiring a budget stripper was a bad idea.
Cool your heels, flattop.
The show's over, but I was just getting started.
I knew it.
There is no use for me.
I broke it up.
Congoline, who's with me?
I am.
Okay, so now, get out of here.
Sybil's the only one for me.
Not monster strippers, no.
All right, coffee.
Let's go, coffee.
Is this the last we'll see of Bosco's paranoia?
I hope you've given up the degrading exotic dancing career.
Yes, I suppose now I just have to let this body go to waste.
That's kind of bad.
All right.
Have you finally come to your senses, Flint?
Somebody put a Mickey Finn in the happy juice, Sam,
and I'm going to find out who right after my head stops pounding.
Sober up.
Coffee in the cooler.
Coffee and punch don't mix.
Do you mind if we perform some quick elective surgery?
Can I get him?
Whatever.
He has ribs?
So with no soul, who cares about my feelings?
Great, thanks.
Wait, the monster has a rib.
A fool and his bones are soon target.
I got a rib.
Everybody has ribs.
He's made out of steel and like stitched together
clay and duct tape and fucking stone and stuff.
And we've got the rib.
They're all realizing they're naked.
Yeah.
Don't look at me.
I've never seen Frankenstein?
I've seen Frankenstein, but this is not Frankenstein.
Hold on.
Let me scroll over his name for a second here.
Frankenstein's monster.
That's not what it says.
Plus this steel here, metal, and we put stuff.
I put like chocolate and rocks and stuff in them.
I know what's inside of there.
Confirmed.
Denied.
What, does he have bones?
All right, so we got the rib.
Monster's rib.
Let's go do that first, I guess.
It's done.
It's gold, not chocolate.
Well, it was chocolate until we transmogrified it into gold.
Yep.
Happened.
Sam turned you back into a cake, but then we-
Whatever.
Look, Mr. Wizard.
Thanks for taking all this time to talk to us, but we're not interested.
But if you just-
The lady said we ain't interested.
Then maybe you-
I believe the two of us have made ourselves clear.
Ah, fine then.
That's too good for you just to-
One sin foiled.
And stay gone.
Looks like you two have learned an important lesson about cooperation.
Fine.
You going to order something?
You can't just offer something, woman.
You got to push the spacels.
I think I can do fine without your input, Grandpa.
Oh, you can, can't you?
Very good.
Well, let's just talk.
So stinky.
Why have you been lying to us all this time?
What?
I've never lied about anything.
Specs gave me the answers to that trivia contest.
Do you mean to tell me Herbert Hoover really was president?
Nah, we meant all that bunk about your history.
You never told us you were a golem made from cake and fish sticks.
I like that.
She doesn't know that.
And let's keep that to our secret.
That's like part one of the German 985 logo.
We just need some, like, magenta.
He hates one third of you.
Yeah, you're a logo.
I'm not a, I'm what?
Stay strong, stinky.
All right, we did that completed.
Now we've got to do the rest of this.
Get some red, some magenta, some teal, some cyan.
Recreate my whole logo from scratch.
All right, I need the game.
But first, I have, I know what I'm certain I have to do with this.
Let's go do this now.
So I know what I know to do.
I know what it is.
Redesign my logo.
No, that's my, that's my brand.
Yikes, don't touch that.
It's harder than a third rail at rush hour.
It's my brand.
Okay, we need to make him able to swear.
So we need to know his name.
Yeah, you can get t-shirts there.
Hear the band.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
If this doesn't work, then I don't know why this wouldn't.
Max, distract Mr. Bliss for me.
Yep.
I seem to be completely naked.
Oh dear.
Hope I don't have to bend over provocatively to-
That's enough, Max.
Twenty dollars.
Twenty dollars, yeah.
I got like probably one,
I got probably the cheapest shirt on Twitch.
Wait, hold on.
I'm reading the list.
It's Satan's grocery list.
Cantaloupe, melons, chicken breast, oregano, vanilla, and what?
And soda.
I got the-
Yeah, I got like one of the cheapest shirts on Twitch.
That shit's not like 32 bucks.
All right, anything else I can do here?
And, and, those shirts are made of high quality.
High quality material.
I could have picked like the Hanes t-shirt.
No, I picked the premium t-shirt.
Twenty dollars, premium t-shirt.
I want to make sure that you can get something good.
I don't want to charge too much for it.
Didn't select like the Hanes shirt.
Come on, I'm looking out for you.
Somebody, especially overseas.
You know, 20, 30, 40 dollars for like a shirt or something.
What are you talking about?
That's like 60 bucks.
You know what I'm saying?
I just want to make-
I'm looking out for you.
They are currently available.
Did I just build the wall and take the wall down in Minecraft?
What was I doing there?
I did what I was supposed to do, right?
What was I doing in there?
Okay, right, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Self-promotion.
Yeah, well, I mean, they're good shirts.
I'm going to tell you right now, they are.
Those of you that have purchased one of those shirts,
come on, speak up.
We need some testimonials here.
High quality material, beautiful artwork.
I'm an incredibly talented artist.
So now we can hear, uh, the name.
Max is the king of Popper's trivia.
What's Peeper's real name?
Easy, it's Dick Peacock.
Dick Peacock.
All right, so we got his real name.
So wait, can we get him to swear?
Where are you feeling, Timmy?
Better than I ever have in my whole darn life.
Shoot!
Nuts!
Fudge balls!
No, come on.
I've still got the Tourette's,
but that weird ringing in my ears has finally gone away.
Sorry we ruined your dad's fancy casino.
He wasn't actually swimming.
Ah, that place was a real doo-doo-ho anyway.
Doo-doo-ho.
I like having the robot alive because he flippin' loves trivia,
just like I do, and he's got a new reverent interface attitude.
Timmy's just, like, cute.
Just like Daddy.
You're my best friend.
He wasn't even being bad or mean.
Ah, there's nothing more heartwarming than the love of a rat for his abusive robot pal.
Okay, well, hold on, let me see.
Max is the king of Popper's trivia.
Bring it on!
Okay, so did we get any squares here?
In episode 205.
Is that a trick question?
Because in that episode, wizard-
No, okay.
Doctor Thunder-
Sorry!
All right, we got what we need.
See you later, Timmy.
Okay, so we have the real name.
We also need the game cartridge.
Let me see if I can get it.
Wait, how do I get the game cartridge if the train is there?
I can't do anything with the car.
The decoder seems different somehow.
I think I'll just walk for now.
I'm gonna look at my items.
The book, Bonesaw Paperclip Pork Rinds.
No, sorry.
I'm supposed to do the paperclip.
Is there anything changing here in the-
You just let people know how you want it, baby.
Say my name.
Hey, Dick Peacock.
What?
You- What have you done to his eyes?
You still want to make out?
Oh, hell no.
Well, we've saved Sibyl from a lifetime of regret.
And given ourselves a blackmail opportunity
to secure our financial future.
Richard Peacock is a pretty cool name.
All right, so we got that taken care of.
Is the wedding back on track?
Yes, but now I'm behind schedule.
Um, let's not mention any of that peepers incident around Abe, okay?
We'll try not to.
You know, a donation to my re-election fund
would make it easier for me to keep my mouth shut.
Okay, so we have two things taken care of.
Now I only have one more to do, which is the game.
No, that's- but it's Dick Peacock.
You're forgetting the first three letters of the last name.
I would have- I would open up my own, like,
private eye investigation firm.
Okay, now I need a game cartridge.
Let me see.
Can I get a game cartridge here?
This has to move.
But if I get inside of it, can I get a game cartridge?
I didn't think the game was that bad.
Games based on a license are never a good business decision.
There's one just sitting right here.
I mean, look, that's- the text is facing the screen.
All right, hold on a second.
That's right up here where the steam is.
Is this gonna be too hot?
So that's where the Esperanto bookstore went.
Yeah.
I win, I win, I win, I win, I win.
Console, here's a new song for you.
And then they- all of them fail.
And Satan gets to come back.
Here we go.
Let's see who has a better song.
That is nice.
Melted.
Start it into a giant bar and make like a hundred grand.
Here comes the finale.
You've lost, poppers.
It's time we put an end to this charade and return to hell to its rightful owner.
What Satan said?
Poppers assume demon form.
Behold, papers the omniscient sea of-
Guy fairy.
Ah, that's killing.
Oh, that was spicy.
You got cayenne in there, man.
Out of the park.
Behold, specs the dominator of-
Oh, come on.
Those are your demon forms?
They're different colors.
Why am I always the only one who puts any effort into these things?
This is fucking a little twisted.
I'm not enjoying this, poppers, anymore.
Can I kill them?
Not if I get them first.
Banish the irritants!
Sam and Max, we cast you into the pit.
Wive up the book.
The bell.
The candle.
Oh, no.
So be it.
Now we gotta get out of the hole.
Well, Max, unless we learn how to fly, we're destined to spend the remainder of our days
on a tiny outcropping surrounded by impossibly hot lava, ash, and soot.
I don't mind, Sam, as long as I'm with my best friend.
Oh, that's sweet.
So how do we go from here?
Sorry, buddy.
I already ate them all.
Goiters of Rube Goldberg.
Look, Max, it's Santa's sleigh.
That's funny.
What an unexpected stroke of luck.
Or is it, Max?
Remember that time long ago when we jacked Santa's sleigh and had to save Christmas
and drove it recklessly into a hellish vision of the future,
very much like the one we're standing in now?
I stopped paying attention halfway through that sentence.
I wonder if our ghosts are here guiding us right now.
Pay past me!
Check this out!
Classy as always, little pal.
Now let's get out of here.
Fork rinds.
This is expert handling.
You enter here.
We escaped?
That's highly possible.
This baby out in flight donuts around the seventh circle.
It's out of power, little buddy.
Guess I shouldn't have left the afterburners on.
Commissioner?
No, Sam's here.
I don't know.
He just let me answer it.
Is it cold in here to you, Max?
I should have worn my muck locks.
What the hell?
What's that, Commissioner?
I won the Nobel Peace Prize?
Congrats, pal.
I can't think of anyone who deserves it more.
Is it Sam in there?
Okay, thanks, Commissioner.
Okay. Roger that.
Love you, too.
Do we have a new case, little buddy?
Nah, same one.
But Sybil wants me to officiate at her wedding.
Well, that'll be fun.
We'd better hurry up and restore the balance of power in hell, then.
A little help here, guys.
Eggs!
I have eggs!
Time to pay, poppers.
One second, thought. Perhaps I'll wait here.
Is this just a snowball fight?
All right.
Ice ball right in the face.
Fuck it.
Let's get Satan.
Sing fast, wizard.
Rock in the snow.
All right.
We got it.
Hold on.
What else?
What's over here?
We got a candle.
People really shouldn't leave ritual candles lying around.
Candle.
We got coffee.
What else do I got?
Candle.
What about the ice cream truck?
No, stop doing that.
It's locked.
You can't shoot the rulers of hell.
Say the line.
No, I'm not saying the line.
Okay, so what about, um...
What about SCP?
How you doing?
Hey, SCP.
Whatcha readin'?
Norbard!
What came over him?
He's actually being productive.
We live in a world of times, Max.
Santa's sleigh doesn't work.
It's out of fuel.
Why couldn't Stinky have lied more?
Okay, so I got the candle.
What about the coffee?
Ice cream bell?
Can we shoot the bell?
Maybe they'll go over to the ice cream?
Oh, the bell of the...
Okay, hold on.
The bell of the book.
And...
I don't like that we can see him digesting, Sam.
It's all part of nature's hideous circle of life, Max.
Candle.
So then what can I...
Put the candle on there.
Here you go!
Bye!
Time out for number three.
No!
Yes!
What?
Ice cream.
Plain vanilla.
Okay, so I got ice cream.
Snowball.
He's gotta blow out the candle.
Looks like a plain shit.
Vanilla.
Vanilla ice cream.
Do you eat it?
Do you want this?
Poppers.
I gotta get him to like, get out of here.
You fucked it all up.
All right, there it is.
What about SAP's desk?
No.
Anything over here?
Water cooler.
Microwave.
Good thing Mr. Specialist's fish tank is open,
so he can enjoy the winter wonderland with the rest of us.
Microwave.
It has three settings.
Bake, popcorn, and cremate.
Can I put anything in here?
Can I put ice cream in the microwave?
Can I put...
Why would I do this?
Why would I want to do this to you?
Coke?
What did I just do?
All right, hold on.
I'm making the cake.
And coffee!
Blow out the candle!
No, put the candle in the cake!
Put the candle in the cake.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Candle in the cake and it's done.
They baited me with the snowball.
Got it.
And then he gets happy.
Birthday.
I'm gonna drop them all.
Kill them.
I don't think we'll be seeing them again.
Don't ever say that again, Max.
Not even as a joke.
Well, boys, you've restored the infernal realms to their former glory.
Thanks to your quick thinking and irrepressible spirit,
hell is safe.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm extremely proud of myself right now.
We better run, Max.
Sybil and Abe's wedding will be starting any minute.
Oh, you gotta appreciate the wedding.
Let's go.
Sam's paying me by the hour.
Does Satan go to the wedding?
Don't lie to the reception, Satan.
Really?
I don't want you to get tired of me so soon
since you're going to be seeing so much of me later.
I didn't like the sound of that.
Don't sweat it, Sam.
We're bound to get reincarnated as each other a few times anyway.
You crack me up, little blasphemer.
We're going to see the wedding?
Love is in the air, everybody.
So hold on tight while we get on board.
Wedding train.
Season two, Sam and Max.
There it is.
Why are you with the bride or groom, sir?
What if I don't like either one?
Daring credit scene.
I'm gonna be quiet for this.
Oh, hey.
You're wearing white.
Interesting choice.
Dearly beloved, we're gathered here today
to celebrate this twisted mockery of holy matrimony.
It's so beautiful.
I hope they have lots of children.
He came.
He's out.
I wouldn't say that.
Do you have the ring?
Oh, shoot.
I promised myself I wouldn't cry.
Hunter box says they don't last three months.
Ready, girl?
Anytime.
Fail.
And what is it that you do?
Listen up, because I'm only going to say this twice.
I'm a bug.
A bug.
Interesting.
May I interest you in a new blackmail opportunity?
Oh, the zombies.
That's so sweet.
Thanks for coming.
Thank you so much.
Enjoy the dinner.
Are we having the wedding?
We're not in the White House.
It is kind of-
You put your left foot in.
You put your left foot out.
Play love, Shaq, baby.
It tricks the egg.
Bye, kids.
Have fun.
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
You think we can trust them with our car, Sam?
It's possessed by demons, Max.
Can we trust the car with them?
The end.
Hey, and that's the end of season two.
But it's a question mark.
That means, hold on.
Could be another one.
The poppers are going to be come back.
You haven't seen the last of us, Sam and Max.
We can never be defeated.
We'll be back.
Oh, shit.
They aren't going to be back.
They won't be back, actually.
They just got torched alive.
That's fucking funny.
Well, I don't think we will see them again.
Well, there you go.
That's season two.
We've gone through season one and season two.
So it is time to put Sam and Max away.
I know Jerma lied about it.
We're going to do season three right after,
but there was extenuating circumstances
because I have a campaign in Heroes of Might and Magic
that is still not complete.
That I did say I was going to finish too.
And so I figured today, first day back from colonoscopy,
let's just get some of these things that are not finished finished.
And season three will come back.
We'll do season three.
I have some plans for streams of the next week or so,
week and a half.
But as of like a week or two from now,
we'll go we'll go back to season three.
So don't worry, we will.
I promise that we will do all of these.
But like I said before,
I don't want Sam and Max exhaustion
because that could happen.
You know, but it's fun and interesting
and kind of comfy as these streams are.
I'd rather spread it out a little.
You know what I'm saying?
So we are going to move on to the campaign
that I left a few nights ago.
I'm probably going to lose it,
but that's what we're going to do for the remainder of the stream.
If you do not want to see that,
if that's not something that interests you tomorrow,
we are going to do cooking simulator.
So I'm looking forward to that.
Should be a lot of fun.
I've been waiting for it for a long time.
Probably going to lose in this campaign,
but I do want to see the end of it.
At least try.
But I'll be right back.
I'll take this opportunity to be right back.
Grab a snack, go to the bathroom if you need to.
Heroes of Might and Magic 3 will be what you see when I return.
See you soon.