Hello. He forgot to talk. No, no, all right, all right, all right. Listen, listen, listen.
He's very early. I'm like seven minutes early. Somebody said, were you, were you all right at
the end of yesterday's stream? Yeah? Yeah, what, what do you mean? At the end of the stream? What
happened? What happened at the end of last night's stream? I don't know, what is the person talking
about? He forgets. Jesus, this is bad. Wait, wait, didn't I scream because, wait, didn't we raid
somebody? Did we raid somebody and I like screamed because I ran out of time? Is that what you're
talking about? What happened? We didn't raid anybody last night, did we? Yes, we did. We raided
Ludwig. Anyways, oh, by the way, I was there for Ludwig's raid song. It was fucking pretty good.
You guys just make everybody do the raid song. He's sitting there like,
like do the raid song, do the raid song. Keep seeing. He's like, what is the raid song? He said,
we don't have a raid song. You're just confusing the absolute fuck out of him.
And on the spot, he just turned on a little music file and he did a song better than anything I
could have ever done. Do the raid song. You're just going to confuse everybody we ever raid.
We're raiding you right now. No, you're not. Yeah, I think everybody we've raided has had
to do a raid song. You guys can't just force people to do a raid song. Anyways, tonight we're
going to play Hitman 3. I'm very scared to open up the save file because I'm going to be very
honest with you. This third level, I'm just going to kill them and run to the exit. I don't like
this place. I'm going to just find the people. I'm going to kill them and run and like save state
and run out of the level. I think we also had a thing today, which I want to go over.
It was about maybe playing Hitman while a little bit high, right? And while I think that's a fun
idea, I want to make sure I let you guys know this. There's going to be no debt wiping today.
This is not going to do any debt. This is not for any reason in particular.
I don't want to incentivize like doing drugs on stream for a benefit. So if I'm going to do
anything, it's going to be because I just feel like it. I do it sometimes, but no, I don't really
like the idea of incentivizing me doing drugs. I don't think that's cool. I think that's not a
good way to, I think that's not a good start to like doing something like this. So cause like,
oh, hey, hey, hey, dude, 500 million. If you get high right now, wait, right now. Okay. Yeah.
No, that's not going to happen. So there's no incentive here. If I'm going to do it today,
I'm going to do it for fun. And that's it. So there's no, don't, there's no debt wipes or
anything like that. Pull, pull out the what you've bong rips. No, no, no. And I'm not going to do
that. I look, Hitman is a very complicated game. And I know a ton of you guys are going to laugh
and be like, no, it isn't. You just have to go strangle people with piano wire. I know, I know
it's not, it's, but it is this, okay. If there's more than like a hundred people in a room and I
have an apple in my hand and all the people in that room can get hit in the face by an apple,
it's incredibly complicated. There's too many, the flow chart is all over the place. So we're
going to try to do this level that I, I don't, dude, I don't remember. It was, I just walked
around in the circle for 20 minutes and said, I hate this. I hate this place. I hate cement. Delete
this level. And I couldn't figure out how to get back to the dance floor. So I'm just going to
really try to beat this level because I want to see the rest of the game. You're no longer family
friendly. It's, you got to click the 18 plus mature audience warning. How many times do I have to say
that? How many times do I have to say that? This is a mature audience stream. We talk about mature
things here, like your favorite Yoshi character. Mine's definitely
Oshi. All right, let's go. You hit the beat. All right. I have to be ready for this. I was,
I got to, I'm trying to look the best pitchers in the major leagues. If they let up a home run,
or they let up 10 runs and they have to pitch two days later, the last one didn't even happen. You
got to delete it from your memory. Didn't even happen. So that last stream didn't happen.
All right. Here we go. So like, I'm ready. I'm ready to pitch. I'm ready to pitch right now.
I'm ready to pitch. I got to kill that guy over there. Gun, uh, with the gun, gun, gun.
This is really loud. Hold on. Spoilers. This is level three. Yeah. We're playing hitman three,
level three. Are you high already? No. All right. Hitman three, level three. I'm currently the DJ.
Poison. Those look pretty good. What's going on here? What's wrong with my computer? All right.
No, don't go into this. Don't go. Don't go into the cement yet. All right. Who'd I kill?
Kill somebody who died. Did I, somebody died? Somebody just walk off a cliff. Okay. All right.
Where are you? Where? Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to kill that guy over there.
David. Somebody died. Perfect. Holy shit. That's fucking unbelievable. All right. Thank God.
I only have to kill. I don't even know how many more people will. Let's go. What do I have for
weapons? I don't have any weapons. Do I? Oh, yes, I do. All right. I'm going to syringe somebody in
the neck. That's very important. I want to go. He's so good. Let's go get this guy over here.
I want to syringe this part. Put the syringe away. Wait, I thought I'm going to, I'm not allowed
in here. Is he going to be mad that I try to come in? Tech only. Brown this guy and froth. All right.
Hold on. There he is. I played cool. Intel. What? You want to bench press me? What the fuck? That
was Intel. Actually just kill. What do you think I'm trying to do? Okay. I'm going to follow this guy
around. That's the guy I have to kill. I'm going to syringe him in the neck and I'm going to step
on his head. This person is going to fight me. Look at this person walking up to me like they're
going to punch me in the face. Get away from me. Where are you going? Okay. So I can't do it on the
dance floor. Does he like go to the bathroom over here? All right. He goes in here. Who else is in
there? There's some tech people in there. Wait, that's two of these guys to get. Oh shit. Hold on.
They come in this little staff room. Can I go in that? Maybe I can go. Okay. I'm going to go kill
people in the staff room first. What do you think? That's probably a good idea. Does he walk this way
or that way? God damn it. I hate this place. I'm really thinking about just going for stabbing
him in the neck and then running and stabbing the other guy in the neck and then killing the other
guy and then stabbing. I just want to kill both these guys right now. Shut up. Does he only walk?
All right. I need to get in this. Can I sneak around him? All right. He goes in here. His path
goes in here. What's in here? I need a key card. The DJ is just following a guy around.
There has to be a creative way I can kill this guy, right? I'm going to syringe him in the neck
and run. What else am I going to do? I don't know. Look, I know there's probably an elaborate way.
Just do it and run. I just want to see if this guy's path is just a circle on the dance floor
because if it is, then we have to drop a chandelier on his head. That's the one thing I wasn't doing
last time. I wasn't following their individual paths around. Where's he going? Okay. There he
goes. Where's this at? Where's this at? Where's this at? Opportunity coming up. Probably right
here. I should have done it right there. Oh my God. Can I throw a beer bottle?
Fuck. Are you talking about? God damn it, dude. Really? Shut up. Don't point. Don't point. Hide
and seek. Don't point at me. How could you? You don't know that I'm the DJ. I'm the DJ.
You want to? You're going to? That's just random guy here is the guy that you're going to
give information to. You came here to see me tonight. Don't you want to make me happy?
He's dead. Here's the broom. Who's shooting? I'm just going to go fucking kill this guy. I'm
just going to go syringe him. I don't care. I don't like this level. I don't. I don't like
this level. I'm just going to go syringe him. Who is this? Is that one of them? How could?
Oh my fucking God. I hate this level. Where is it? Right here? Just use a gun. I don't have
a gun. The syringe doesn't kill them. I'm just going to fucking sprint. I'm allowed to be here.
I'm the DJ. What do you mean? What am I doing back here? This is my set. You're on my set.
What do you mean they see through you? They see 3PO. What? They see through you.
Hey, what are you doing back here? You're not supposed to be back here. Oh, by the way,
I loved the last song you played. You'll be paying me in the parking lot, right?
Oh, I did it again. Oh my God. I hate this level. I have to beat this level.
I hate this place. Where's my opportunities? I don't have any intel. I need my intel.
There's no good things to do. I just have to follow these people around and then kill them.
There's like 3,000 people here. Entitled streamer needs his intel. Where's my intel?
You know what? I'm going to go after that guy up there. Fuck this.
Where are the opportunities? No, there's no opportunities because this is not like an
assassin mission. This is just going to avoid the red guy but kill the red guy.
There's no assassination here. I'm going up there. All right. I'm going to go up. I'm
going to wait for his path to go up that way. Why are you already mad? I hate this level.
This guy's got a bodyguard with him too. All right. You know what? Do I have any grenades?
I'm throwing a grenade in that room. He's going to come through here. Hold on. This
is my opportunity right here. I'm going to save it right here. Watch this shit.
I'm going to get one right here. Come on. Walk through here. He's zonked and naked.
Does he take a right or take a left? I think he takes a right. Here he comes.
Where's my intel? I need that. Look, I know. I'm one of those... Wait, this guy's number six,
but I'm not allowed to be... Wait a minute. Do they like me now? No. Put that back on.
Look, I know. I'm one of those people that I'm playing hitman. You got to play it the real way.
You know, you can't have any intel, no blue markers on the map, but I'm sorry. I need those.
I need you to show me where the thing to drop the chandelier is. I need it.
Let me go up. They just walk up and round a circle. All right. This guy's dead.
I'm going to cut this guy off in the concrete up here, and I'm going to kill him.
Could I disguise as somebody else that he trusts or something and lure him away or take him
somewhere or do something? I feel like I don't have anything to do. There was the electrocute
the guy with the tree. What are the things going to do to these guys? They just walk around up
here. All right. I might be able to kill him over there. I can come back here. Yeah. That's the
play. The play here is I'm going to brick. Okay. This is the play. I got it. These two guys walk
down here. I'm going to wait. They're going to cycle over here. I'm going to hide right here.
I'm going to brick the first guy and I'm going to punch him. What will kill them? Definitely.
Crowbar? A knife. All right. I'm going to stab him. I'm going to stab him in the head.
Did they walk back this way? If they do, I'll hide over here. I just don't want these techs to see
this. He's definitely ADHD. Too much to wait that long. Oh, I don't like this. I like the 47. This
is Diana here. Here we have a Bingleberry Tingleberry, an oil rig, a machinery extraordinaire.
He's welled up in his panta. I don't want to just wait around and follow the fucking red outline guy.
No, I hate this. I don't like this level. Just go kill them. I tried that. Every single person in
this dance floor has a gun. They just start firing at me. I really might be too ADHD to wait this
long. I have to wait this long. Kill one and take their gun. That's the plan. The plan is when this
guy dies, I'm going to stab him in the throat. No, first of all, I have two of these. I'm going
to throw the knife into his face and then kill his partner. I'm going to take his gun. I'm going to
lean over the edge. I'm going to shoot that guy in the fucking head and then I'm going to go to the
exit. This is going to take so long. In fact, I could probably just do this right now. Can I reach
from here? Wait, can I reach from here? Nobody will know what it is. Nobody will know if I can
get it from here. No, it does not. Okay. All right. Here they come. Where are they? Where do you go?
There he is. Okay. I'm ready. I'm going to be ready for the save it so I don't fuck this up.
There are five guards. No, there's not. There's four. Wouldn't I have found the other one by now?
If there's a fifth guard, if I have to walk around and just stand next to people until
one of them puts a thing on their ear, I'm not going to be happy at all.
There are five. Great. Got to get up here already. This is awful gameplay. I don't, I look, this is
probably the worst hitman gameplay you're ever going to see. You could put a headset on your dog
and put the mouse on their paw and then put a treat in the air and the movement from the tail
wagging, the moving, and their paws going back and forth would probably kill both these guys.
All right. Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait a minute. Is he alone? They're both
coming up here. Can I get a double? Here we go. Here we go. This is important. I got two of these.
I'm going to throw one in his head. Let Otto play. Hey, tiger. Thanks for the vibe. Give me
it or these apps. You're just standing there. Yeah, I'm being an assassin. Assassins wait for
their prey. Come on. Just walk down here. This is a nice concrete stream. Don't even get me
started on that concrete. Where is he? Why is he walking that way? They're going to come this way.
You're a camper. I have to get out of this level. I did. I need to beat this level because if I skip
this level, like a lot of people have said, then I didn't beat hitman three. Here they come. Don't
walk all the way down. Take a right. There we go. Okay. Here we go. You play the other games. You
should know how to play this one. This is the first time they've done a mission like this
where there's no target. You just have to like wait around and like fucking kill the guy.
I'm ready. This is it. Are you ready? First time. Here we go. First try. One, two. Who? What? Who is
it? Get off. Get off cover. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Where is he? No. Did anybody hear the shot?
No. Nobody else come up here. What? He was two people. He just dead ringered. Kill that spy.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm skipping the level. I'm skipping the level. Why did he hear it? He
shouldn't have heard it. That was so stupid. You got face stabbed. Okay. Well, obviously they see
this, so I need to move. I have to wait even a little longer. This is surprising if this guy's
standing here, right? Don't shoot. Who found it? Oh my God. I hate this place. You fucking suck.
Stop saying that. It's making me unconscious. It's making me self-conscious. Stop saying that.
I need to move. Hold on. Here's the play. Here's the play. Here's the play. Ready?
Will he see me or is he stupid? He's too dumb, right? Too dumb. No. I want to stab him with the
fucking syringe. What are you doing? Oh my God. No, no, no, no, no. He's arresting me.
I'm being arrested. Oh shit. I'm being arrested. All right. I'm good. Eliminate agents too.
That guy's fucking alive. What do you mean? He's alive. He's alive. He's not alive. Oh my God.
He's alive. No, no, no, no, no. I didn't take his knife. Oh my fucking God. Are you kidding me?
Get the fuck out of here. Leave. What the fuck? Oh shit. I have to hide in the locker.
Is there a locker over here? Oh my God. I'm in so much trouble. I'm in so much trouble.
Oh my God. He has to die. That guy has to die right now. No one will hear it, right?
No, no, no. That guy has to die. That guy has to die. No, this guy has to die. He's fucking naked.
No, the other guy. The other guy. The other guy. The other guy. The other guy. The other guy.
There he is. Thank you. Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. I need new clothes. Montgomery Burns?
Wait, we're clearing the place out. Get back in here. Get in here. Come in here. Thank you.
Oh my God. Why did you open that fucking door? Why did you open that door? Why did you open
this door? You're supposed to be clearing out the facility, not opening doors to like staff rooms.
I need a new clothes. Just evacuate. I'm compromised. I need new clothes. Everybody
knows me. Ow. Every single person here knows who I am now. This is like Batman dropping down with
the Batman costume on. Oh, I'm fucking in tons of trouble here. I think I'm in... I just messed
everything up. I have nowhere to go. I just blew it so bad. I can't go anywhere. Can I stand up and
grab that? Stand up. Why can I not stand up? Just go and kill. I... All right. I can't even stand up.
Whatever. I don't care. Save it here. I think I'm all right. Holy shit. Nobody saw. All right. Good,
good, good, good, good. I got two tech people down there. There's one dude over there. Oh,
nice. Okay. Who's here? Okay. Perfect. There's no one else in this room. I need to lure these two
over. I don't even... I don't have no idea. Wait. That's... There he is. Oh, no. What? I didn't even
put him on. I have to find the last person. I have to find the last person. Intel. The drug dealer
is apparently supplying some of the staff and security... Where was this? I can't follow that.
Where's my blue marker for that? Wait. Is that right below me? Is that the drug dealer right
there? Where's the drug dealer? It's my Intel. Drug dealer. He's got a red hat on. There he is.
Oh, God. That's the drug dealer. Okay. I need a new costume. Follow that guy. Follow the guy in
the red hat. Save it here. Follow that guy in the red hat. There he is. Where's he going? Destroy
that guy. I need a new outfit. This one's already compromised. I have to lure... Oh, you up there.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Get him. Get this motherfucker right now before he goes upstairs. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Get him,
get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him.
I want to follow... I want to do a mission. Follow the drug dealer. There he is. Okay. There's somebody
in here does not know... Can see right through me. He's not in the room though. Okay. What's going on
here with these drugs? Apparently busy. I was getting killed by a derma in Team Fortress 2
last night. Was it you? What happened? Am I searching what? What do you mean searching?
I don't understand. Searching for what? Okay. How many fucking times? He's still alive?
Where's this last person? Look at the link, please. Literally just you're in a bad trip. I'm fine.
Look at it. Look at it. Mission stories. Just click this. Oh, my God, derma. What? Hold on.
What do you mean? Just click this. Just click this. Mission stories. The game's like crashing.
Mission stories. Not available for this mission. It's a really good game. It's a really good...
Where's this last person? It's probably you. Is it you? I don't care if I get a zero in
this mission. I don't care. Where'd he go? Where'd you go? What? Did they find this body?
Who found this body? It said searching. Does he turn around and come down here? Let's find out.
Why did it say searching? I shot someone. No, no, no. When I went to the drug dealer,
it said, oh, searching now. I didn't do anything. He got scared. I think somebody comes up these
stairs and sees him. Okay. Found him. Found him. I just karate chopped his neck. Okay. I think I'm
in a clear now. Talk to the drug dealer. Drug dealer. Hi. What's up? Ask about buying drugs.
Follow me. I can't go that way. I can't. Can we go a different way? Can we go a different way? I
can't go... I know somebody here. I don't want them to see me here. I don't want them to see
we went to the same club on the same night. I literally texted this person that I wasn't
around tonight, that I had family in town. Okay. So fucking come on. Can we go a different way?
Thanks. How do I syringe him? What's wrong with him? Why is he not falling down? This guy,
I think this guy does a lot of drugs. So like, it's not going to make him fall down. I think
he'll be okay in like five minutes. I can't kill. I feel kind of like, I can't hurt this guy.
How did I break it? I just stabbed him and I was trying to take his clothes.
He's stupid. I wanted to subdue him so I could take his clothes and hide his body because I'm
the drug dealer now and I can go to one of the staff members with the drugs. He was sitting there
going... The game was glitched. I couldn't even get out of it. So I had to shoot the guy. I gave
that plenty of time for that to work itself out and it didn't. So I had to shoot him. I had to.
Don't sell me the drugs right here. What are you stupid? Can I save it here? Okay. Thank God.
Oh, Richard Nixon impression. Sure.
There. That'll be a thousand dollars. In joke currency, fake money. Not real money.
Why does he drop it on the ground? You notice that? So give it to me. Oh, right. He wants money.
That's what I wanted to have happen last time. Get silent. Somebody will hear me if I stab him.
Okay. I'm now the drug dealer. So now I have to walk up to one of these guys and sell drugs to him.
Okay. Which one of these guys does the drugs? Let's see if it's you.
I have something for you. You might like... You think that... Why wouldn't he? He should put on
like a... Put a voice on, right? 47 never puts a voice on. Every time you disguise, he's just like,
yes, I'm here. The chef ready to serve you. You think if he was an assassin like that,
why wouldn't you put a voice on? Put a voice on. Okay. And would you like some drugs?
Why do I have to just speak my normal voice? This guy doesn't want any drugs, I don't think.
At some point, I've never been recorded. And if I'm the most incredible assassin in the world,
nobody picked me up. I'm like a microphone in an office complex being like,
the job is done. I just blew it. I got too close. I was talking.
The game crashed. It's a hard crash. I have to... Oh, god damn it. Okay.
Oops. I think that was just... You just walked directly in front.
I was so quick that you wouldn't even be able to avoid it if you wanted to.
Did that person lean in? Was that person over my shoulder with a stretched out neck being like,
hey, what's happening over here? Like Beetlejuice style? Like a long neck?
Hey, yeah. Whoa. Bang. Like, I don't understand. Watch the clip. The hitscan was behind you. What?
No, hold on. I actually do want to see how this happened. At some point...
Let's see. See how this played out. Okay. Let's see. So, I'm walking around.
Like, at some point, I've never been recorded. And if I'm the most
incredible assassin in the world, nobody picked me up. I'm like a microphone in an
office complex being like, the job is done. I just blew it. Who is this person?
I got too close. I don't see... It was a lady, right? Is this lady right here?
What happened? What? I just blew it. I got too close. I was talking.
There she is. She walks forward. The gun is out. The gun is in front of me.
And I shoot her directly in the head. It's like I held the gun up and pointed my wrist
backwards and just blew her head off. What? I got too close. I was talking.
This is one of those scenarios where this is the assassin behind me.
And this is just a big show with this guy in front of me.
She's coming up to kill me. Wrist back kill. The bullet is from the camera.
Third person game. Let's go. Let me turn it up too. It's a little low.
The hitscan is from the camera. Well, I guess we figured that out.
Where's the save point? 17 right here. Where is it? Yeah.
Hmm. This game is zonked. When are you going to get high?
Look, relax. When am I going to... Hey, I'm only here for the guy to get high.
Yeah. I mean, I heard that this dude was going to just get high today.
That's the only reason why I showed up. Wait. Why does the guy have a...
The drug dealer has a key card? I may or may not be currently partaking.
You don't know. And I'm doing it on my own for my own amusement.
What is even back here? Okay. So this dude right here does not care about drugs
because he literally... I followed him around for a minute or two.
Okay. I can't unlock this door. Yes, I can. Oh, no, I can't.
Let me guess. The person that wants the drugs is somebody I've already killed.
Let me guess. We get to do the fun thing where we now walk around in circles until somebody goes,
yeah, I'm looking for him. I don't see him. Out of the 5,000 people here.
Why are you dressed up as Paddington Bear? I don't know, man.
Okay. So I don't think it's anybody else on the dance floor.
We're looking for a girl. The fifth agent is a girl.
Does the guy want drugs? Get out of here. Looking for a girl.
Who are you? Approach. What? I really think it's one of the people back here.
I did not explore this way yet. I got to find this last person.
Why not? Hey, hey, vouch for me. Vouch for me. Look, I'm with the tech.
Can you vouch for me? Can you say something, please? Say something.
Or I'm going to blow this up right now and say that I'm selling you drugs. Say something.
Hey, Bob Richardson is buying drugs from me. Say it. Let us in. Let us in. Are you really trying
to get me? I will expose you right now. I don't care. People know I'm the drug dealer. Everybody
knows me in here. I'm the drug dealer with the red hat. All right. Looking for a girl.
They keep communicating that there's a girl assassin somewhere. Up top, maybe.
Is this guy still following me? He is. What if I never give this guy drugs? I just take him on
an elaborate just follow mission where he just follows me around. I can't talk to him. Oh,
you're getting upset. Omega Lol Skyrim partner. Oh wait, here's the merch store. Is there an assassin
in here? Nobody here. I'm looking for the last person. Staff only. There's no one even back here.
This is the front. Did I even check out front? You know what I mean? I feel like I didn't spend
very much time back here. Is somebody in here? Is somebody out here in the line? I don't know
where this final person is. They're just waiting in the line. I don't know. What?
What? What is he talking about? He's doing like a football juke to spin around him.
Okay all right all right I'm gonna leave. Okay you whip around.
Where's the other one? Where's the last one? Where's the last guy?
Where's the last one? Where's the last one? Davenport. I killed Davenport.
Where's the last one? No no no no no no no no I don't hurt anybody.
No no no I don't want to hurt anybody. I don't want to hurt anybody.
I don't want to hurt anybody
With the last guy ways alive
The guy live with the guy that I shot in the head is live. No, he's not
I can't save it until I'm not a country anymore. Oh fuck. I gotta go down. I save it
Shit I didn't I gotta get his body
Give me the body. Who the fuck are you? Who's looking at me? Who are you? What are you doing?
That's unconscious. What is it? Does he know the controls? Yeah, but you hold holding G is awkward
It's like a weird button to have it be like E. There's a real nasty troublemaker out there
You don't you say that for like somebody dropped like firecrackers like outside
Not like someone's killing people with an axe. Thank God. I found security. There's a real like rascal troublemaker out there
He's dropping the firecrackers
You gotta be fucking dead
No
God damn it. It's give me out of this mission. I don't want to do this one anymore
I hate this place fucking game is lagging. Oh my god, of course this cameras it hits me
Really that camera is gonna do this audible frustration intensifies. It doesn't even feel like a hitman mission. Where's the exit?
No, the exits like up here. Okay, where does he go? They have to go up another floor
Let me see. Let me look at the map. Club security. Let's go level zero
Let's see. He just that guy just walks around down here. He just walks around in a circle
I probably had to have done something to him down there
The exits up here you leave through this way. I just gotta run but how am I gonna kill this guy?
How do I kill this guy down here without causing a huge scene?
Poison or something. He's not that I that's not the drug guy. I don't know. He goes into that side room
I think I'm gonna shoot him in the head and then run. I need to took out of the next mission
I just to get out of here and run by with a bicycle. That's plan
Yeah, I know this is dogshit gameplay. This is like horrible gameplay Andy
I know but I want to see that I want to get it. I don't like this level. I'm just gonna go for
Kill him already. I'm just gonna wait till he gets into view so I can do it and I better not shoot this lady in
The head I better not get up don't no one stand behind me. He's actually coming upstairs. It's perfect
Alright, here we go. Line it up. Get a good line of sight here
Right there right there. Here we go. Three two one action. Don't get out. Get it my way
They don't know it's me, right? They don't know it's me. They've no idea
What I just went the wrong way. I got shot himself. Wait, what happened? This wasn't the right way
Isn't this that you've done you hold on? Let me see with this. Where does this go? This goes up here and then
Bang a left right out this way. How do I get out of here? What's the actual like exit?
It was the other way. So like down here. Wait, so come here. I go here
That's not good. You have to go up the exit. Don't you?
Up the stairs to the right this way and then you're trapped here. No, not off this. It's the same staircase
And then to the right but then wait the straight through here. Let me see
It was just the actual I've never been out here yet. What the hell is this place? What the fuck? What is this?
Why is it like nobody out here? What's the point of this whole area? Just follow the exit sign. Hold on. This is the exit
That's the exit, right? I'm going for it. There's more areas with more agents. I hope you enjoy it
I hope this is your favorite level. I hope you love this place. I will never open this level ever again
I'm not gonna open this level for any reason you could tell me that love it
It was like five BTC hidden on this level and I wouldn't care. I'd be like, I don't care
I don't know. I don't want even going there. I'm not going there. I'm following that follow the goddamn exit signs
There was two green exit signs
Okay, fine. Where am I?
It's the bright lights and the fucking concrete and the thousand people get me out of here
Get me out of the streamer room. I don't want to be in this live streamers room. Okay, get me out of this place, too
Excuse me. Excuse me. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. It was very nice. That was very fun to see you. Goodbye exit
I'm out. Where's the exit?
What I let me locate the exit and I didn't leave who the fuck are these people I'm going to the fucking sewer
Get out get out go in the sewer. What are you doing? Go in the sewer
Go in the sewer. Where's the my fucking god? Why can I not go in here put the gun away get me?
Hiding behind this guy. Oh
Yes, when will it end why can't I leave
Why can't I go down sewer? What the fuck is this buggy shithawk?
Shithawk, what's a shithawk?
shithawk
That's some kind of large bird
God why can't I fucking leave?
Why are they doing this to me? They're doing it to me on purpose. They're doing to me. This is on purpose. Move
Please get away from me exit combat. Are you kidding me? Just reload it. Reload it. Reload it. Reload it. Reload it.
Is that what was happening? I couldn't go in. Use the map. The map in Hitman is one of the most confusing things in the whole game
No, no, what do you mean blind? I can't even go up there. It was an arrow
I know but I was trying to sneak away. It's just taking me the same way
Why can't I just go in the in the in the manhole cover?
Jesus you're a stormtrooper
Because you were in combat. I've no I wasn't I wasn't in combat when I opened the manhole
I I did like the whole G to exit and it didn't do anything
Go right into the store and then right again it bugged out but the silencer run I guys I didn't unlock the silencer because the game
Doesn't stay connected to the internet for more than fucking two hours. You remember that shit. I don't have any unlockables
I've completed like two missions being kicked off line, so I have no progress
Just stop killing them die. It's the starting gun. Is it? Oh, we're getting real anger
No, we're not I just like I couldn't unlock any cool things
All right, just fucking come on. Just get out of here. I'm gonna listen to the one guy
Let's see if they're right. I said go to the store take a right. Please don't let me down. Don't let me down one guy come on
I can't I can't just run. I'll die guys. I'll die. I will just die and I can't say
I'll get shot like three times in the back and die
Yeah, I will I'll die. I will die
These guys are made out of like ceramic. Why I don't
Alright, I'm gonna settle down. I'm gonna relax
Okay, if I could rank every hitman level across every single one of the video games. This is below ET
All right, my favorite comment I've read was in all capitals this sucks and you suck at least we both equally suck
It's not just we both equally suck. I'm like, thank god damn it man. Just fuck this place never coming back here again
There's gonna be like a five achievements to get here. I'm never gonna see this opened up one way ever
We started back here like taking a phone call. Remember there's a guy. I gotta try to call somebody
The Joker how did I get this many achievements for this? This is so embarrassing
This is so embarrassing
That's the most amount of achievements for a level think I've gotten in any level even doing it right and doing it the way that you're
Supposed to but what it isn't that's embarrassing, isn't it? Oh man. Finally, what a shithawk of a level
Shit cock maybe that's what I was saying. I don't know. Oh cool
He's and I'm right here and he's doing jumping Jackson he's looks huge he's really really good
47 he didn't suffer did he he made it
Nobody cares about the hitman story skip. I
Mean, I don't but I'm still gonna watch it
I didn't care about like the Sonic the Hedgehog the movies storyline, but I watched it and thought it was cool
You stormed the heavens took down the untouchables and yet here we are
Status quo it just goes to show you can't fight power miss Byrd would power never dies
It only changes hands
the best
Pretty nice picture of a
It's the thing that gets you to the thing as the next constant you can be the
Transform the system from the inside
Be transformed the thing that gets you to the thing
Power is the thing that gets you powerful. It gives the thing to different people to you to me. It's power
It's a bit of an object that we can grasp and hold and bring it and bring it hard and bring the gas
Power power power is power power is a curious thing. Are you fond of riddles?
Why am I about to hear one three men stand in the barracks a priest a rich man and a clergyman
Each is bidding the sellsword to kill the other man
Who kills who well that depends on the sellsword does it he is if not gold or no favor with the crown
It depends on the sellsword. I don't know. Well, I'll tell you a very small man can cast a large shadow
No other way. It's a very small. Did I say it right?
I said it wrong
Closer. I'm telling you the file John
Constant doesn't so much burn his bridges as blow them up Arthur Edwards, whoever he was don't exist anymore
His personal data somehow deletes itself from any system that records him way beyond advanced
The partner spared no expense to make sure that controller would be untraceable
How untraceable I?
Did what you asked but gray's gone and I'm no Diana. That's the first since I actually comprehended in about you gotta be kidding six minutes
I see they're hacking somewhere. I used every encryption known to men. Who are these guys best?
It's only a matter of time before they get luck. We need to take them down
You and which army I don't need one the agency stores its files mission reports client data
If we leak it to the public you want to whistleblow the ICA
It's the path of least resistance. Holy shit. They made a hitman movie
Did anyone see it? I don't think anybody saw it
And i'm out. So what are we breaking into data facility and chunking three of them run by a man, of course
The ICA side in Chongqing houses the agency's data storage and analyst division
Needless to say security is daunting
The state of the art server vault is biometrically wired to the facilities to overseers
imaging reuss
behavioral analysis pioneer
and hush
A data security guru with a taste for fringe transhuman experimentation
Tell me about hush. It's a matrix a former cyber terrorist for the ministry of state security in kadan yang
Who fled his country after one of the po regime's periodic purges?
He made a career doing cyber security for dark web deplorables human traffickers organ harvesters
Scum like him with no code or conscience no code
ICA sure can pick them
No offense
Can you disable security? Whoa?
A dual authentication wait are they plugged in any handling of data must be directly authorized by hush and royce
The proverbial human factor device to make the system impenetrable
Luckily, I found a loophole
If both overseers should unexpectedly die within a short space of time
Oh, no, the system reverts to a temporary failsafe protocol, which I can buy so they both have to die within like a minute
Take them off the board and you'll have free access to the data core
And i'll handle the rest
And you're sure it'll work
Look, I know hush. Oh just like the romeo and juliette encounter. We won't live long enough in carousel
Yes like that
Wink wink both of us leave you to prepare. I'm so glad i'm getting just massive minus two
All right, let's go
That's on master
Excuse me. Oh, no, I thought it was selected. Okay
Oh
All right. Here we go
neon city
I'm ready mission stories
Certainty principle impulse control all seeing I i'm looking forward to this one. Let's go. I'm not doing master. No chonking china
This city is big brother's wet dream with more than 2.5 million cameras covering 15 million people that seems
That seems like they would get stuck everywhere
It's pretty ironic four of those would just be in your pantry randomly during the day. That'd be horrible
You'll find hush conducting his fringe experiments in an abandoned apartment building while imaging royce the archivist
Runs a day-to-day business of the ica data facility. Okay
I just hope you know what you're doing 47
All right sniper
All right, eliminate hush eliminate emojin royce hack the data core
What we got here, this is pretty level they're very very far away. They're very far away. Okay
Holy shit. This is so high up
And look anybody that wants to tell me
That says durama don't push her
She's only here to be pushed
You understand?
It's the beginning of the level
It's just one person right at a balcony
They put this person here to try to just see who will push her off. It doesn't it's why there's no reason for this person
To be here. Okay. Look at look. She's the only one
All right, let's get I want to get some intel. It's a very pretty map. It is
ooh
Can I ride that? I think i'm gonna go this way go back and shove her now
No, you can do it in your playthrough. I guess i'm just gonna just check out up here
Oh, wait
I can drop these
But why would I want to do that? This guy care that i'm going into this like a house
Laundromat what's going on in here?
Uh, wait, what is going on in here?
It's like just buckets. So they do you go to a laundromat and like wash your
Clothes and like just like a bucket
Wait, i'm confused. Well, where are the wait a minute. Oh, they're just not here. Okay
Any intel
Oh, well, sorry
Buy one buy one and let it come up
Oh nothing came out
You just kick it. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, we just boot that
You didn't get one here
Here I can help you
Look, I know these things can be kind of finicky
There yeah, I pressed on uh lemon lime soda and a root beer came out. That means yours was in the queue before mine
um
Okay
What's in here?
Sorry, I like looked at you for a second
Just throw it to her
Oh, yeah, good call
Okay
Out of the laundromat. We're now
You up there opportunity 47 a guard patrols are clearly searching for something on the roof of the laundry
What could they be looking for?
Why don't we find out?
Okay, is there a ladder I can climb up on is there a way to go up from here?
What about this way interact with the keypad?
I gotta get the code from this guy
Watch the code to the door
Say it on one of the uh, one of these things. No, that'd be funny if it did
Ooh, what is that?
Okay, this like poison over there. Hold on. I just want to get heaven. I want it to come out
Wait, can I give me the iron?
Is there a way to go up from here? I gotta get on the roof
And wait
Can I jump out when it's right there?
It's written on one of the laundry machines
Is it?
Well, do I need to do that?
I climbed the pipe. Let's go down here. See if I can wrap around. I don't want to push him yet
No, I need to explore the area. What's going on in the noodle place?
Noodle run. Okay
That wasn't data. How was that not data? I just don't want I don't want that to be very loud. Hold on
Okay, that wasn't intel of any kind
But up there
Okay, I see a pipe. I'm gonna let me get on top of the laundromat. Let me find a way up there down here
And then go up that way. He's drinking a heel
Okay, get on top of the laundromat. What's this?
No, I already went up this way. Is there how do I get on there? I do I think I have to jump out of that
This just takes me around the back
It's a loop. Yeah
Can I hang from here? How do I need maybe I can't can I get on this pipe? I don't think I can get on the pipe
Can I jump from here? I don't know
What's the map look like? No, I don't know because this is the laundromat here. There's a staircase
Wait, I think I might do I need the password?
I think I need the password
Do I need to reload the whole map? Is that you guys not fucking around? I was gonna explore
You know, okay down i'm gonna down to this. How what's the time? How I have to kill him in a certain time frame
Is that legit?
Stealing her past
What does that mean though? What's that mean?
Is it just me or have they upped the crazy lately? Where's the fucking intel? I want to do this one
It says I can make a lot of money to be in some experiment
Oh put me in the experiment, please
What the hell is happening?
What are you guys doing? Why is everyone freaking out?
This is my chance
Are we throwing it on sub only?
Throw it on sub on throw it on sub only immediately. I just missed this
All right disguise yourself as a homeless person, right? They were talking about like the okay
This is I kind of I don't this like I don't like this
Why do I have to take a homeless person's disguise?
Why can't I just say i'm homeless? I don't understand that
Why do I have to like take this guy out?
Oh shit, the fucking channel points shit
Turn it in emote only instead
Or turn turn slow mode. I don't know what to do. I don't what do I don't know what to do
There's tons of shit going on
All right. Let me let me turn off channel points. Hold on. I wish everybody could just fucking behave themselves
I don't want to have to do this, but I will i'm gonna have to turn off the chat channel points
Sub only emote only mode. Holy fuck. That's like a extreme. Let me turn this off
All right. I just typed into fucking google channel points. God damn it
I'm ready for this right now
Great
Hold on why i'm on the front page of twitch right now. I want to be on my own damn channel
Hold on. I gotta fix this go to channel
It's 160 channel points to chat with purple letters. I'm just gonna turn it off. Okay. There we go. We're safe
You can no longer send a message in sub only for 160 points
Hooray, it's done. Okay, let's go. I'm gonna keep i'm keeping an emote only till everybody fucking calms down. Here we go
Okay
So i'm obviously i'm gonna take this guy's costume. I don't want to kill this person
I was about to do it right there. This is the worst spot to do this. What's in front of him?
This is like the place to do it. I no no, no, no, I wanted to choke him like that was any better
No, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, just hold on
Shit, what do I do? Oh, this probably hurts. Oh, no
No
Okay, hold on. I need to
Oh, I want to get him out of the rain. I need to like just bounce it off though
I want I don't I want them to turn around
What
Why did you see this? I want them to turn around did I use my all my coins on sodas?
Okay, still have a couple here we go. Ready?
Fuck I don't know what to do with them
I don't know
I don't want to dump them over the railing because that's horrible and I don't want to do that to this guy
Oh, no, but someone's gonna see him. I have to take him this way
Okay, I have to
Just don't turn around
I don't want to do this
I don't wanna
I don't want to do that
I thought it was the ocean
Oh
Damn it. Damn it
Okay, don't just don't kill anybody i'm just gonna oh my god, I have to push her off and then dump him I have to
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do about this? I'm sorry
I don't want it to play out this way, but I need to i've got to do this. No nay nay nay look i'm
It's got to be like a box or something there is there is one right there, but there's a person there
There's a person there are people over there throw a coin. Okay. I i'm sorry guys
I'm sorry. I I got i'm dumping them
I'm just gonna dump them. I'm dumping both of them
I was trying to like not have to kill but I know I whatever i'm just gonna push and then dump whatever
I tried I really did I didn't want to even have to disguise as this person
Nay, nay, no, no, no
No
I'm seeing a lot of germa fludos. I know i'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Oh, man, hurry up before this lady. What's this lady doing here already?
Fuck fuck fuck. I thought that was a shotgun. I was like that's not blending in
Why am I blending in I didn't do anything
She has no idea what happened. All right, i'm taking it off emote only mode
Sub only staying on but we're taking emote only mode off
Fucking behave
All of you behave
I am
So I have to go into the homeless shelter
You only had to kill the homeless guy. Well, I didn't want to kill the homeless guy
Entrance to the homeless shelter kill kill kill kill
You're wondering why i'm like level fucking six
And this began the game been out for like fucking two weeks when this game come on. It's gonna do it again
It's been out for four days. Oh, well, whatever
one one
Zero one one eighteen zero one one eighteen zero one one eighteen
Nice. Thank you
That's intel. All right. Where's the fine entrance to the homeless shelter?
There's an unusual number of chefs entering the restaurant kitchen in the middle of the night might be something worth investigating
hmm
They're gonna see if I climb on this though, won't they?
Where's the laundromat up here?
How do I find the homeless shelter? Excuse me, the numbers germa the numbers I could go just do that
Unusual amount of chefs going in and out welcome to yuzong district. What is this place?
Why does it have a passcode for what?
zero one one eight
Zero one one eight one of the restaurant chefs seems to have lost a note with an access code
What kind of a restaurant requires a code for the employees to get to work?
So this is the is this restaurant? All right, so I have the code. Let's check it out. Let's see what's down there big doors
Someone is here for a tour of the facility
Might be a way to get in
The p41
the p41
Back of the restaurant
Mr angus pritchard the visiting ica board member forgot a form in his apartment across the street from the restaurant
He needs to bring this to the facility guide before she can take him on the tour
He's going to go there. He's going to use the bathroom. Give him a swirly until he dies
47 good luck. Did he leave already?
I'll see to it. Oh, no, he's like distracted. I'm just gonna go over there now
Here we go. Let's go get the p41
Hard candies. I wish I had something juicy for you straight laced as they come
Everyone just gossips about everybody, huh?
41 throw scissors to the guy's head
You know how many times wait? Oh shit. This is the fucking door. Oh, this is his door
I like needed that info to get in here
Does he walk back over here? I need to I have to wait for him, right?
I have to like smoke weed in his gta apartment before he comes over. Ooh, we got an answer machines and
The 41 what's the answer machine say?
I've just learned that will be delayed beyond the lifetime of the entry code you received for the facility
For your convenience. We've set up the new
To match the one for the apartment why would somebody be guessing that
Some ladies like
You forgot it
This guy's talking from around the wall
Yeah, that was not a message that person's in the room with me game volume
That was perfect best part of the game right here. Oh, he got that right here
I love this
Can I just I suppose I got to talk for the rest of the game?
All right. Wait, is this guy gonna come back to his apartment?
Where's this dude?
Will he come up here?
Because I have to swirly him till he's dead
I don't think he comes back. I was hoping I could just do it cleanly in here. All right. Well, let's go
This guy's as the board member. Yeah, isn't that the guy that was just sitting at the restaurant?
restaurant restaurant
He's opened up a bunch of zorn tabs on his computer save it here. How do I just how am I supposed to do that?
Um, does he end up going to the bathroom?
Can I talk to him?
Yep. Yeah
You can you go somewhere? I feel like something is supposed to happen with this interaction or something
Why are they letting me just go in the kitchen?
I just like walked behind and went to the kitchen
Um, I guess i'm gonna i'm gonna poison this guy
People talking
Ceiling shit, no
I wanted to
No, get me out
I need uh, can I get him to move?
In the bathroom, he's gonna go to the bathroom
Why is there rat poison in here? He's absolutely he's gonna go to the bathroom
He is now
I mean honestly
I guess maybe this wouldn't be a distraction because I would just think whoever was in here was just doing it right into the water piss
No, here we go. Hold on. You don't hear this. There we go. Okay. Here we go. I tried to close the fucking door
Sorry, i'm just i'm just kind of weird
Fucking why is it g?
It should be e always
Okay, i'm ready
Rebind it then no in principle. I will not
Doctor doctor
What reference what movie is that what movie reference is that tell me?
And I will mute for one full minute
No, no, no, no, no, nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. No one's getting it
Muppets in space. You got it. I'll see you in like i'll be back
Start a gas leak. Sorry
Okay, i'm preparing this and i'll put the poison in it poison the plate of food
This guy's gonna see me do this
You have to hit him with a comedy utensil. No, I don't I just have to poison it. Is he gonna see me do this?
You might be mad about this
Find out now. Hey, I got it. Take this food out, please
Oh my god behind
behind
fucking god
Get that food to mr. Uh, pritchard, please
Ready
Take it take it out to him. It's ready
Thank you
Please don't eat that is he gonna eat this
two
Chefs come out one puts the plate of food in front of you
The one that just has an apricot in his hand and puts it down on your plate
That was instant
swirly time
And here's does that you're fucking idiot dump him. We're good. It's time to go do the tour
Nice 1080. I know go ahead and keep making fun of me. It infuriates me too
Are you hungry? Uh, yes, I was very hungry till I ate the food from your restaurant
Not hungry anymore. That's rude. I just think I just puked. Well, I poisoned it but still
Hello need to inspect the facility now good. Hope you enjoyed the food. Nope. Did you bring the p41?
We left for you in the apartment. Yes
Everything I need good. Okay, good. Let's continue the tour continue you may say
We haven't even started the tour yet
But we have without you even noticing it. Mr. Pritchard. It really is the best security there is
You see the red
All is a break, please. Why?
Oh, that's what this is the secret takes you along
Oh, I know the password
It's zero one one eight
See I know the password
Yeah, I knew it was zero one one eight
I'm pretty good at guessing
No, this is why it's cement everywhere. I can't wait. Well, there's the big reveal
Welcome, please report to security desk for visitor sign in we'll do
Is really looking out for us and we're in the inside is a self-contained modular bill that can be disassembled
I'm in in less than 12 hours. I'm in we are compromised no trace. We will ever hear I agree
Leaving no trace behind is the only sensible
The outside shell is a building marked for demolition. We put a hold on it with city planning a deliberate misplacement of the order
But have people in place to rectify that
At first shift city construction will move in
Our policy around ica personnel is that they are a resource but also a risk on top of contractual repercussions
If breaches occur, we perform detailed vetting on every
Blood
To vetting is a frisk. We have of course never had you can use your camera to hack that panel
But we do consider that important i'll need to stop the setup of your visitor security clearance
I'm just like taking pictures of everything
Please give me your people you want mr. Richard so we can get things rolling
Hello, sir, p41. How do I give it to you?
Procedure
Okay, you'll have to be frisked like everyone. Oh, I should probably put the gun down mr. Richard
All right. Let me take a let me look around first
There's no way you're getting through that door 47
It only opens for people with an authentic security clearance. The signal is encrypted without a dongle. We can't hack it
Uh, did you see did you see on your camera? Did you see I hope you did?
Of course, I got it
Oh god damn this guy's on a fucking cell phone, of course, he's not gonna pay attention
Wait, that means I can just walk by him
Why her because I was trying to run out the door and she was in the way
Tier one access dongle. I don't even need to be in here anymore. I got an access dongle
Holy shit. I got an access dongle
A dongle provides olivia with the encryption key needed to hack access tier one rfid panels
Now I gotta hide my gun
So I can I you what is it? I guess that blocks out the view
Security protocol overruled
Security protocol overruled I can just open up off the door. Wait, can I open up the door behind them?
God, that would be funny
No, don't first me yet. I'm not ready. I have a gun on me
I'm just fucking with their house
Server room
What's in here? Whoa, what is this?
uh
Is a vent into this room
Okay, hold on. Cool. This is cool. I like hacking stuff
This is way cooler than the the 15 watchdogs allegiance missions that I played
Where was the same two missions back and forth?
What's this package? I'll take it. I don't even know what it is. I'll take it though. All right, I gotta put a gun away
All right, we're gonna conceal, uh the gun
Do I have anything else illegal?
No, what the fuck man?
I have okay. I have a lot of illegal items
What is it? How do you drop stuff? F G L
Z
All right. I have no more illegal items. Right?
I kind of want to get frisked while I hold a meaty bone in my hand. Yeah. Sorry. I just got back from disneyland
Have you had one of these have you had one of these yet? I'm gonna need to go through your pockets my friend
Let me just pat you down here
Proceed by the way, those things are gross
Oh the gigantic turkey leg those things are disgusting. I hate them. Who wants to eat that? They're terrible
They get cold and shit you you bite like two bites off of it and it's cold in five to ten minutes
You're walking around like outside. It's really like stringy meat. It's just like a meme
I don't know. They're not even they're not good. Don't order those go get the mickey mouse ears chocolate bar. Can I close this window?
Good you're here. I am here
It will take a little while since you're covered by the zero protocol
all your data will
Be encrypted and inaccessible without your authorization access only facility ai will use it for id analysis
Fully anonymized, of course, but we can do a few more steps on the tour while it's validating
Id analysis what the hell does that mean?
Give me a minute. I'll try to find out
Nothing in here take something something to take chloroform and
Tiered an access dongle
Caught
I'm just so annoying. This is probably you know
This is probably what it was like to like be a hotel concierge and deal with the rock bands that came in
Back in like the 80s
We perform a type of obnoxious shit. They probably had to deal with to guarantee that no
Drug use physical health issues external pressure or moral hesitancy the scan only takes a few seconds
Let's step inside
Until the iSafe facility has top-level security because of the highly stressful nature of the job employees are put through mandatory checkups on a regular basis
Additionally, they are being monitored for elevated stress levels and other risk factors while in the workplace
Will they scan my barcode? We can't proceed beyond this room until your security clearance is finalized
So why don't you have a little look around while we wait? Mr. Richard? It should be here
Shortly
Shit
We need to intercept that 47 or the facility ai will blow your cover
Blow me up to one of those computers and do it fast computer. You've got 60 seconds before all hell breaks loose
I have 60 seconds to get into a computer. What do we 60 hack this one?
Wait, don't look at me
security protocol
Good i'm in i'm in and and you're safe
That was a close one
You didn't see shit
What's on your desk?
You are way too close to me and you're really freaking me out
Your clearance just came through let's continue
How many of these dongles do I have?
All right, let's see what it did
Come on this way. Uh, your floor is two floors up on the elevator
Maybe just go take a look inside what we just did over there with the printer. What did you do?
I signed my ass and I scanned my ass on it
Ha ha ha great very serious about security
What we protect is after all core to all ica operation we and we alone store all legal work
I just made her mouth closed do like the closed jaw teeth it like
It made like a loud and she bit her teeth together that sucks when that happens
Target profiles and of course offer real-time contract support
If your chin gets closed too hard like you get bumped and it's like you bite like that takes constant vigilance to keep safe
We have a team of engineers solely dedicated to that task and on top of that we have a dual human authentication process set up
all
Access and alterations to the source are authentic
Oh
I'm sorry. It's like if you get too close to the ropes in the wrestling ring, i'm gonna push you over
I saw that coming. She was getting really close
Wait, that was the target that walked out
Oh my god, it is
Imogen royce i've been looking forward to meeting you likewise
Wait, hold on. Did that just say attack?
I'm gonna get you
Wait a second. Hold on
Hold on just a second
If I can I pull her off?
I hope I can
Nice to meet you. Yes, it is. It's very it's wonderful
What I could have pushed him out the grade
Try to put the gun down
All right. All right. All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Can you imagine seeing that?
The person you're giving the tour to oh, yes, it's very nice to meet you. Nice to meet you, too. Yeah
Over the edge, although that guy's fucking weird. I don't know why excuse me. Um, mr. Mr. Pritchett
Do you know can you come back over just grabs pulls her over what's I don't even know his name
I want to remember this moment the rest of my fucking life
Looking forward to meeting you likewise
Let's go
So show me what's going on in this facility
God damn it. Don't get close. Don't get that close to the edge. I'm telling you
I'm like a fucking trapdoor spider if you get too close, you're gonna go i'm gonna grab you
This is the blood and emp shielded call room the nervous system of the ica where we store the past and facilitate the present
In general only a handful of people can access this room hush and myself plus bodyguards and a chosen few of the engineers
I'm the most likely person to meet in here because I perform a regular physical check-in on the core console as you plug in
We have a strict routine of daily core maintenance part of that procedure is a flash process evaporating all biological matter in the room
Yeah, do it with that maybe we could
It's her job to initiate the maintenance. Don't worry. We're safe. I read the safety mechanism is engaged
Even if reed presses the button the procedure will not happen until we leave the call room the doors to the call room
Are all equipped with
What screw this tour?
I know why you're really here. It's a chase. I see
Knowledge is power
More importantly knowledge stand the way turn around. Don't look at me spin around you kill him. Don't kill him
Power is power
Has not been reported it has no doubt brought you here
You do have authority to shut down unwanted efforts, but I just did that like an hour ago
But there was not an opportunity to do it
You have sway with the board and as I see it your opinion is now power is the thing that gets you the thing
So here we go imagine this
Having a time schedule on a target with minute details on location doesn't matter who has the power someone will always have power
power is
Attainable and one of us will have it will have that transform a contract
powerful
No mess no fuss
Low cost just how I like it
I've been working on a prediction algorithm based on a combination of big data analysis and micro targeted surveillance of defining target markers
I have to pee so bad
are astounding
All this state of the art is nothing but heavy old-fashioned machinery compared to what I offer analysts preparing detailed files
Dedicating days weeks to prepare our contracts gone handlers and analysts supporting our operatives during missions
Gone teams for cleanup and media manipulation in the rare case something else does happen
All of it gone. I asked you to imagine that scenario
But what good is imagination when you can see it with your own eyes?
I've set up a little demonstration for you. This is where they kill me
Three employees unaware that I can accurately predict their behavior
Accurately predict my behavior in an already clearly defined reaction on the top left
We have sharon reed who you saw downstairs. She's a dutiful and trusted employee
If she is to be fired my algorithm predicts with a certainty of 97.8 percent that she will finish up her most important tasks
Before she leaves the building interesting specifically she will press the maintenance button within 11 seconds
Will she the guard in the lower left is as tough as nails when on duty
But in private he's a real mummy's boy
If fired he will immediately call his mother and at her advice seek out who he considers his best friend for support
Why is she giving me mission intel objectives?
Explains why he's always next to me at lunch at the top right you see alicia reynolds right and very passionate about her job
However, also very possessive about her contribution
Okay, my prediction is that she will try to disable the work she has done for the ica
If she's not allowed to enjoy her results
No one is specifically that means she will try to enter the call room and disable the safety mechanism
I'll leave you to consider your choice of who you want me to use for the demonstration
Just let the guard outside the door know when you're ready and i'll be right back. I will have a closer look
Maybe your project could play a part in the future of the ica
Just let the guard outside the door know when you're ready and i'll be right back only two of us in here
If you decide to leave the room a guard will escort you around safety protocol
So there's only two of you. She really takes the term god complex to a whole new level
Sitting in there pulling the strings like that. Oh, I think you should take her setup and give it a spin 47 sure
I see
Potential if you time it right
Use terminal who are you gonna fire?
erin reid
disabled
jeremy bolt
or alicia reynolds
disabled safety mechanism
performs core maintenance by disabled safety
Uh, okay, that was weird. All right. I'm gonna fire alicia reynolds. We're gonna disable
The security system alicia reynolds
I regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status
Thank you for your service
Don't mind me, sir. I'll be escorting you around. I'm ready to see voice now. I'll let her know don't mind me, sir
I'll be escorting you around. Can I do that backwards?
The vip is ready to see you
Sharon reid
I regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective firing everybody
Thank you for your service
Okay, um
Yeah, so I I disabled the safety mechanisms and then I go do something
Do I have to do these in a row? I gotta pee. Let me go pee
I'll be right back first beer every other night if you time it right beer be
Let me know I have to go to the bathroom
I'll be right back. All right. I may have startled you. I don't want to five cat boys cat boy. All right, let's go
Streaming. All right. So there's a there's an order to this right? Okay, so
Core maintenance
Engineer so why hold on right and very passionate if fired
There's a 98 that she will try to disable the safety mechanism in the core room
Okay, if fired he will leave his post at the core room door to call his mother
Okay, if fired she will finish her most critical task before leaving the facility
She will press the core maintenance button within 11 seconds
Okay, so we need to so core maintenance so we have to go
one
Fire alicia fire jeremy fire alicia and then fire
Sharon read or fire jeremy fire alicia then sharon so fire jeremy
Fire alicia and then sharon
All right, because we have only have 11 seconds. Let's try it first. Let's try jeremy sharon alicia
jeremy bolt
Correct to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status. No alicia first because I only have 11 seconds
Code 41 is confirmed effective for your employment status
alicia reynolds
I regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment. She has 11 seconds to get over there for your service
No, it was it was sharon first
right
Sharon read
I regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status
Thank you. Oh, okay. So I hold on the way over there. I did them all okay. Wait, wait, wait
Yeah, okay. I get it. I understand. I get it. I get it. Okay, so you do it to jeremy you wait till he unlocks the door
Actually, did I do too fast?
It still might happen
Okay
They're going
She got in they switched
Here he comes
Got it. What happened they get it. It's way too early wait for the safety mechanism to be disabled then fire sharon, right?
Right, right. Okay, that's true. All right, so we go disable disable jeremy give it like five to ten seconds
Disable alicia and then wait like a minute and then fire sharon read here we go. Jeremy bolt
I regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status
Thank you for your service
Be right code 41 is confirmed effective for your employment status
Okay, hold on one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine
Ten go
And then we're gonna wait a minute and we're gonna get rid of farron
Is this sub only?
Well, I thought I told you guys you needed to behave what people freaking out people be non with people misbehaving
Okay, so
Alicia disables the safety mechanism sharon gets fired
Okay, man about
Okay, we have to wait. She's gonna go into the thing
Okay
Here we go
and
She's about to disable it. It's been disabled
Go
Sharon read regret to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status
Thank you for your service
Now go perform maintenance
Too late. You're talking about too late
Why did she just walk in wait this place on fire hold on so wait I have to kill her with that
But wait, she she was
Okay, let's do it again, I missed her by five seconds that was two or three seconds too late
Potential if you time it, right?
Here we go
Jeremy you're fired
Give it a five seconds or so
Rep to inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status. Thank you for your service
And we here we one mississippi two mississippi three mississippi four mississippi five mississippi six mississippi
Seven mississippi eight mississippi nine mississippi ten
And then right when she touches that panel i'm pressing the button
To inform you that code 41 is now effective for your employment status
Thank you for your service
Earlier, wait, wait, can I see her on the camera?
I okay, but I wish I don't see her on the camera anywhere
Okay, here she goes
She's in there now. She's in there right now. She's in there right now
She's there right now
Okay, now go now go go now go now go now go now
Here comes thank you for your service
Yes
No, it's gonna be close. That was a was it perfect. No, it was no it's not it's gonna be close
Turn it off
Yes
Got it. That's imager moist down. Take care of hush and we can get to the core. Ooh, that's a silent kill
silent kill
Cool, really cool
All right, the next we gotta go up
It was gas
It kind of was
Oh camera there
Okay, he is he's even higher up here. Okay. I don't have a security clearance for this
It's probably bad. Yeah, this is a hostile area. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm supposed to be here though
I'm no longer allowed to be here
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Close it. Close that door. It's a see-through goddamn door
That's not
I'm good. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm good. I'm perfect
Vent
I'm good
Act event, okay
This is tier two, right?
Oh shit. Okay, I can go out there
Move it this way access granted
Shit, I don't know. Where should I go?
What should I do?
the dongle
Knew vincent's girlfriend was breaking up with him before he did
Save the game. I got you. She's spying on us all of us. Well, we're in it now there is to know
She knows still doesn't feel right
Okay, I think i'm gonna go out one of the vents
I'm going out this vent over here this one
Why not? I mean, this is a little strange that i'm doing this, right?
But I I want to go up. This is super sus what you're doing
I'll let you have it for a minute, but i'm just
That came on like I got hit by a
Truck
I couldn't stop that
That was sincerely one of the most intense feelings. I I couldn't stop I couldn't move
That just came out of nowhere. I have no idea why that happened. Nice ron
Access granted nice, right
Wait, didn't I say I was never gonna say that ever again in the rest of my life
All right, so should I be maybe security office? This is tier two security. Okay
Like an armory
Oh my god
Disable that camera
This is a suitcase over here. Don't ignore chat
You said you would add debt if you did that again. I did
What's in the briefcase? What's in the briefcase?
Tier three
Can I open the briefcase?
I just get to be a briefcase
Man, I want to get in there
tier three sub
Put a gun in there
Oh, I could put a gun in here. You're right, but I need to get over there
How do I get this camera to leave me alone? I mean, does it really matter? Does it matter?
Not really
We're doing grenade
Oh my eyes
I messed with a shotgun twice
Did you see that like kill him kill this motherfucker
2.5 billion. What?
No, that's bullshit. That was probably just that particular stream
That was definitely for that stream. I had it. I fucking got too greedy
I got too greedy had to try. I need the do I need the briefcase? All right. I got the shotgun in the briefcase
I'm good. Neck is tense
Too many conversations happening at the same time
All right, I need to go I got a tier three dongle now I can go up to tier three if that guy had brick massage
Yeah, what is this shit brick massage?
I thought that was a door
That looks that's a door. That's not a closet
All right to go up the stairs all the way up to tier three
Does that mean tier three like three deep or three up? That's three deep
Is it use the map? That's three deep or is it?
With the emergency exit open if I hack it I get in one guide. Is that real? Oh
Plus three. Okay. I thought that that guy was a bad guy because he was red
I thought I was doing this I need to go number three
Up we're on almost to three. Where the hell did I how did I get over here? Oh shit. Okay, cool
I'm like I like i'm outside the facility now. I'm is he in he's not in the facility is he?
Is he in actually actually inside the facility?
He has to be right. This is like an exit
Am I losing my mind or what?
Holy shit. Oh my god. Oh my goodness. That's a lot of cameras
There's no one up here. I can shoot these
My god, that's gamer moment of the fucking century right there
Now I need to kill you
No, they make an explosion
Why did that explode? Oh, it's a stupid drone
Get out of here get
Get out of here
Investigating just where me get over here. Oh my fucking god
I they don't see me. They just see his body dragging away imagine that are you are you sure it's a
A breach or is this just like a really hungry raccoon that grabbed that guy
You don't know I got it. I got it. I know bin right here. I thought the guy was gonna come over here
Someone's apparently of course he is
Come in. All right. There ain't anybody else out here. I'm good. Let's go trapped in here. What?
I guess i'm i'm just stuck in here. Okay, whatever
Give me this gun
Save it got locked out
All right, he's over he's lounging around in here
I wonder
Can I like get let's see what if I go this way, what does this take me?
Is there anything over here I can do if I go back that way?
I need to go that way. Oh, hold on
Oh
Look at this save it. I'm sorry sneak into his room and just kill him with a brick
Oh these guys i'm dressed as one of these guys
They don't care
Yeah, i'm dressed as one of these guys I can climb up that
Okay, so I already killed the first person we get a lot of jupiters here this is like jupiter city
Who's this?
I gotta get a disguise and go around disguise it up go around 1920 right? Look at all these jupiters. Holy shit
Rise up fellow saturns. You are one of probably 30 people that have done that emote in the last year
Screenshot it. All right. Well, obviously you gotta go this way for a minute
Gas
Oh, yeah gas
Did I drop the gas?
Holy shit. He's in here. I know the password. It's zero one one eight
Oh, no
What if I just tap on the window? I could just shoot him through the window right now. All right, we're climbing
Can I not climb this?
Poison the ventilation system. He missed it twice. I did what do you mean? Is he coming out here?
I guess I do have gas I could do this and that goes into the room that he's in right now
Gas no gas
No gas the white board germ of the white board the white board
2552 how come the gas is not working. Come on. I did it fast test subject
Okay, I gotta be a test subject. Is this get him get him get him get him get him get him get him get him
Anything to hide him in here closet go pick him up and put him in the fucking thing
Save it. I have to turn on the ventilation insert fuse cell
I got hold on
I got intel a male detaining how to activate the sensory calibration for a hushers therapy session
Get rid of your gun get rid of gun get rid of gun. It's not illegal. It fused pro bar
I'm definitely gonna need that
It's a gun. What is it? I'm a security. I'm a security guard. Do I have to pretend to be a test subject?
Okay, let's let's let's do the test subject one
Because it doesn't I don't want to do it
No package for you
Bye. Okay. Now I why would they give me the opportunity to do that now? I have to get rid of the gun
Here we go. He's coming up. Oh, they're coming to get me. Did I save it?
Are they gonna come get me? I'm ready for my treatment. That's him. That's it. He's in this chair bastard
He looks a lot older
Tomato in his face identify memory marker 90. I mean, I can't keep getting away with it, right?
Why it wants me to throw in his head
You can't go around people's heads like that
I understand
Does that jog the memory does that jog your memory?
I mean, I guess I could could I just go and zap him. Okay, I just I could just overload his brain with
Just junk, right?
I want to overload his brain
I can all right. All right. All right
I'm ready to experiment. Oh good. I'll let sister. They know to join us for the experiment
We'll get started now. We're gonna lock in and have like a battle inside of our heads
I see what we have an eye and e is there an o
He's ready for you. He looks strong. Hey by good specimen to conclude this phase. We'll get started when sister lays here
It's gonna be a mind battle. Yeah
we're both gonna be like
Came to his senses. I see sister lay
Yes
Please I need space
What sister lay yes, we're about to perform the final test of this project here we go
Hijack the data
Ready when jimmy let's start at 100 signal spectrum. What am I supposed to do here? I mean, there's no need
The subject is clean cooperative. I was thinking 25 percent and then adjust if necessary
60 percent is minimum. We'll get no motor control below. Am I actually gonna like blow his head up with my brain?
Long experiment page 109 initiated operation 60 percent
I feel like I was supposed to mess with something
page 109 initiated load suggestion motor control
44.1
The signal's too low resist
The signal is too weak. We'll get nothing
100 percent
Is the meter on the right it's safe don't resist
100 percent I can't say continuing experiment h 109 volt meter. Should I watch should I watch the volt meter?
100 let's go
Is
Voltage is getting too high
We're going to a hundred and fifty percent attack him with the soda
Became to be without pain calling it quits hush. You need rest. Okay. Okay a short break
What the fuck how did I did it wrong
link impulse drink point zero two two to defining a moment so
Do I have to overload? I have to overload his chair
Because I I definitely have to overload the chair. Hold on the same that calibration unit in the other room
I'm supposed to wait. What I was doing it, right?
Wait, what?
You can't do it on the first one
Oh
Okay
Run simulation an experiment. I need to do it. Uh, I thought if that was it like, oh well, we'll try it again
I thought we were resetting his encounter
Oh, okay. I thought I I needed to do something else
ADHD dumb fuck
Jesus
He's ready for you hush he looks strong good specimen to conclude this phase so
The test subject came to his senses. I see. Hi good. Just delay. Yes
We're about to perform the final test of this project
All right, sit down let's get it saved right before he sits down so I can just not have to do this again
Because something screws the fuck up. Okay sick. Yeah sick sick sick sick sick. Yeah sick
Take a seat ready when you generally let's start at 100 signal strength 100 percent. I mean
200 percent
60 percent is minimum. We'll get no motor control below and wasting my time but
60 log concluding experiment page 109 initiated we talked yesterday about
Going into a vr headset and controlling somebody else like an avatar in the real world
This is that this is what he wants to do
Wow, you're paying attention ban that person for six days six days in dog years
It can cause you real physics it's safe you're strong you can overcome it
100 percent do it log continuing experiment h 109 run calibration. Yeah, that'd be about that'd be about four hours
It's like an hour. Yeah
You're fucking nuts
It's too much it's too much it's too much
He is a strong one and you banned me for a little bit. It's a sex thing
Do not ban that person
Came to be without pain. I'm calling it. Nothing can stop the blob
Okay, okay a short break
I'll return with a clear head
God damn that assistant if they up the signal it will kill him. Oh
You need to be the assistant
I'll stick around
We need to get rid of I thought I just took a gun out
Oh, we need to be the assistant
No, increase the power
Increase power increase the power level increase power
Jack up power to way higher than than we can allow
Tons of power put the power up
Jack up the power
Just wait
What do you mean? Just wait
Kill the assistant. It's definitely I definitely mess with the server room or something
That has to be what I have to do. All right, I mean look at that power. We need more power power
God he is dumb
What?
Mm-hmm. Wait, is this the assistant?
Where's the assistant?
This is the assistant right here. You're pretending he's pretending again. Uh-oh
Let me read this sister lay has been pushing for hush to go further than advisable in his testing
But his personal assistant has convinced him. It's too dangerous if testing is to proceed
That assistant might need to be taken care of the assistant needs to die
so
We need the assistant now. Give me a hand here
I think it's bugged out. Is it? No, it's not
All right. So
All right. So why are you writing that?
You already failed it
The other lady not the one doing that. Yeah, I know but
If we had missed the opportunity to you should have gotten up by now. This is a legit bug
Oh
Is it 13?
1840 he's supposed to get up. It's not bugged. I think I broke it
Shoot him and run
I'm not gonna do that. Like we did the last one just shoot him and run. Okay, so is it actually bugged?
It's not bugged. Why are you guys are people just gaslighting me? Am I getting gaslighted?
He's literally supposed to get up. I mean, there's only three people. You know what? Let's just try this you got up
You're gonna be part of something truly amazing
He's a genius
It actually did bug oh
Actually had to get up if you could just go along with it, okay
Don't try to resist the impulses he sends
I don't want him to exert himself
Can you do that?
That's the most brutal thing i've ever seen
Oh my god my stomach
Okay
It's time to do the test again get to the skies. No, I have to be the patient
Wait, why are you doing that?
I hit an enrage timer. What happened save save it save save save save save. It's good. Just wait
I have to wait up here. You're gonna make me sit up here
I you I have to sit up here and not do anything stupid
Oh my god, are you kidding me?
These people are gonna wake up by the time he gets back. Just make some noise in the meantime. Okay, that's yeah
Sure. What do I have? I have a meaty bone
Sorry, excuse me. You're not allowed here, you know
You know what the best part about that was
That yeah, it didn't make any noise. I hit him with like the meat part. What's wrong? Is the gun I need help here
I couldn't fucking wait. I couldn't I couldn't wait. I couldn't wait. I couldn't wait. I couldn't wait. I couldn't wait
I couldn't wait. I couldn't fucking wait. I couldn't wait
I'm gonna take my hands off. I'm gonna take my hands off the mouse and shit. Well, I did wait
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, let me give it. I gotta take some credit here
I didn't know that walking by this guy would make him immediately be like hey get back here
So I had to hit him in the face of the meat and I and I had to improvise so I dragged him into
The thing and I've left the gun
I'm not moving not going anywhere
You were fine when you took a step back
Idiot call me an idiot. How dare you? That was my day. My day is going pretty well
First thing I see in chat doesn't matter what it is. It doesn't even if it's an unedible. I'm gonna eat it for dinner
What is it?
ass
No, the first thing was burger
Excellent. Hey, you know a burger could be ass
It could be
Right. It's ground beef that could be like ass. So
I'm good. Here we go
And it's between two buns. Yeah
That's that's fine
Don't load save
All right, let's go
Push yourself harder
Yes, 100 percent I feel strong I can take him
um
So does 47 just have some type of power where he can resist this dude?
I didn't do anything special. Like i'm just 47. He's going into my head and stuff
I hope his head explodes
What does that say on the safe and then gamer he's gonna go full gamer mode or something I don't understand what's that mean
So I should just let him do it oh resist nope safe
The way we have to build it up. Okay
47 has a huile brain
Experiment h 109 calibration 120
I have to wait like right to the very end and then pull it
That was a plus two chat joke it was
Let's go his head's gonna explode you're gonna get to see the head explosion part
Brain blast both targets down good
Give me a second
And i'm in you can now access the core 47
I'm fine, by the way
Okay, I need the data core are there so many I don't know which one is which
All the guard what
Where's the guard just got some personal shit going on where's the guard all the guard
You're currently enough shit it's too late
So I followed it was too late. That's all right one earbud andy. Oh, is that the problem?
Okay, did the guards say follow me follow me freeman so focused that he just forgets
I mean, this is a nice big kitchen. He wants to be alone. We can just sit in the corner. We won't bother
What hey you what the
Hold on. I'm very
Just wait, what do you mean? Wait, I was wrong again. I turn around
Is somebody in the room?
Follow that guy
Go back to preschool. Why don't you go back to preschool? I could be way better painted than you could be in preschool
They used to hang my shit up in the classroom
I did that they did not do that to you
I would be they put it on the table with some tape and it'd be on a table as a placemat
I didn't do that to you
Okay, I need that data core
You save it. All right, so we gotta keep going down. It's all the way down
It's a placemat
All right. We gotta get you out of here quick sirs. This is where I this is where I killed this guy
I mean like it's a perfect place
All right, let's get that
Don't do it. Should I beat this guy? You do so don't pretend to be bad. It's it's not funny
It pulls in so many viewers. I've posted the views man. Come on. You really do. I need to tell you that
Of course, i'm gonna keep pretending at video games and like falling down and stuff. Are you crazy?
This is a statue
A horror game soon. Uh, maybe this is a very big level, isn't it? This place I I forgot that we were outside at one point
we were outside
it was not a
There was a facility
We brought a bunch of people alive in a room
In this weird ai room. This is a huge level. This level is a monster level
I keep going
There's nothing special that I need to do here
Like look at this. I forgot this even existed
Any of you gods through here
Okay
Did that guy just say security's tight? We're not allowed to let you guards in here
Excuse me
I am a guard
What the fuck are you talking about?
We're guards. We can't let you guards in here either
All right. Well, I gotta get in there. It's the same lady from earlier
Actually, are you okay? You coughing something up? What's wrong? You okay? Just a frog. There's a frog in his throat
Well, I mean i'm just gonna climb this
Both of you go check it out
Can't let you through
Sorry for the inconvenience
We have someone in serious trouble could be an assault
I was trying to get behind him. He didn't go far enough
What was I doing? I I was trying when I threw the fire extinguisher one
I got to keep going so I could choke him over there and put it this is not mafia
You're playing it like mafia. That's a really weird thing to be compared to be playing like
Hey, this is not mafia
I mean like a third person. What do you mean?
Dta would be better. Wouldn't it like comparing to mafia?
Free the non-subs that depends that they're gonna behave. I needed to go like there
The guy on the right saw that how the guy on the right see that i'll take any chances you go check it out
Oh, come on lady
What's up save it it's time to get the data
Um
Hello, good morning
Can't believe they let me in. I can't believe they let me in. I can't believe I got in. I can't believe I got it
I can't believe I got it
Holy shit. Cool
Fantastic. I want to see if it worked. It's the same lady. Yeah, the same lady with the umbrella. All right, so that's that's the exit
Don't let me forget that it's on the ground. What is that? What is this fucking iron? I threw this over here
If didn't I i'm trespassing down here. No, does that really matter? All right, i'm gonna become one of these security guards
Are you behind me? Okay, i'm gonna lure somebody over here with the iron like right here. Come on over
Um, something's wrong with that guy. I got him out of the wall. Anybody hear that nothing at my I didn't do anything
You can't be here pacify the bastard
Nothing at my position. No, of course not. I just want to see if you're stuck in the wall the pacifier starring vin diesel
What is going on down here? Hello, let's go this way
I'm i'm trespassing but doesn't matter these two guys there. Hold on the data center
This is the wait. This is the wait. This is the
Whoa
It's a way to get out. Okay, please follow the gray line to security check. Thank you
You already forgot the whole map. Yeah, this place is fucking enormous
This is like the biggest map in hitman. I gotta get one of these guys to come in here
I need to screw up
How do I get somebody to come over here? I know there's a gun in the trash can
Oh shit, there's a gun in the trash can there is a gun in the trash can which one?
Who's this guy?
Pass the blunt bro. No, it's mine
This level is deep
all right, so
Uh, let me go
I need to get at one of these disguises
body found
Where is this body?
I need to get one of these disguises which one of these is silent. I don't have anything silent anymore
I had to stop to choke somebody's face
Damn it. They saw it
What is all this shit?
What is all this?
Wait, this is the gun this thing with the trash the gun trash
What's this on a gun? Wait
Go to the trash
47 this is exactly why you planted the gun trash
Now I remember. All right. Now i'm gonna go get the gun and i'm gonna snipe somebody
Thank god you guys reminded me that I would have completely forgot
Here we go
Give it to me. Yes
Get all these knives and shit, too
I gave myself an entire arsenal
Okay, here we go. The plan here
Is we're gonna go
This way I just need a disguise
It's got to be one person hanging out somewhere
one
Wait a minute. Can I get in there? Wait, this is just the core
What? Um, what about the lady up there? Good. You're alone. I'm sealing the room and dimming the windows 47
No need to worry about intruders. Oh
What about that person? Oh, what's on the ground here?
Opening up the data core
Holy shit
It's all here
Clients operatives every hit the ica ever sanctioned enough to shut them down for good
But first you need to locate all files referencing diana and yourself. It's not in this mission, too, is it?
Oh, okay. It's a cutscene
We're gonna start overwatch back up again
Send the word out to all the operatives
taking lives
disorder
Well, we are here basic training starts at 600 hours
I should
Leave you to prepare
Perhaps I see possibility where others see limitation do I have to escape?
I choose him
The two of you go way back
I didn't realize that you
I don't know. I get why at what point does the lady that was looking over this go
I can't see somebody blacked out every window killing the past delete the files
Okay, good. I've set up a link to an information non-profit site
When you press that button is up there and the whole world will know
There's no undo 47
This will shut the ica down for good
you
Really? Okay with this
It's who you've been for so long
This is I'd make a choice
upload or
upload only
I'll just return things to normal no need to alert than we were here prematurely
I better save this shit
We're blown 47 give me a save point for a little while use the fence to get out go now
Use the fence this is bad that means they'll shoot on sight
I'm gonna create some havoc 47
You're gonna create some havoc
Make the core melt down maybe we'll divert their attention a bit
There's a photo I can take over there
venting
Get in
Oh, I need some help here can drop the gas
On it got it 47. Well steam just burst it out. Can you turn down the pressure?
Got it working on it. Ah, those fans are gonna be going too fast. Aren't they?
on it
briefcase stashed
What who is that?
locate the exit
Hurry up. I asked to go faster. I don't I don't know what i'm supposed to be doing
Initiated to go like up or there's a shooting
I can't go this way
vent song vent song a riot
You'll never catch me i'm disappearing jump into the depths of all i'm
Coming up to write the rest. I don't care. Why don't I get out of here?
I know but how do I leave?
just leave
Is there another staircase over here? I can't there's so many guards over there. I can't go that way
How the fuck you have to kill?
Just kill just kill them. I don't think I have to
just kill
Kill kill kill kill
Oh my god, one guy went there
Holy shit, only one of them went over there. Oh my god dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb. Come here
Are you fucking kidding me?
Well, they're dead now
What happened down there?
Then didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't
And i'll go this way let's go up higher oh it's peter
I know i'm doing like a peter griffin. I'm sorry
Got it got it
Personnel
All right, we're out and that was pretty clean too
I only killed I killed four people in a row. That's it though. Let's see what kind of achievements I get for this shit
Got it. Boom. Boom
Boom i'm gonna get a lot of these
Okay, this is a lot of achievements, right? This is pretty good. This should be a pretty good score
40 000 how much is it worth for you when you kill somebody that's um like innocent
You would have if you didn't kill so many people detailed score
Finally leveled up like 10 times
detailed score
flexible murderer
zero
why
Zero you killed too many people minus 65
God whatever hacker mk3
Oh, I got okay. I got some cool stuff now
cutscene
The disclosure of
You win diet coke button
What happens now?
The balls in your court miss burnwood. I do have other candidates, you know
Most of whom have never tied me to a chair
You've seen the news
That was 47 acting on his own
He is untethered. He is unstoppable and he cannot be bargained with
He will find you. Mr. Edwards
And i'm the only chance you've got
I'm listening
47 has one weakness
Me me got it
I got it
I saw it coming from my every flight all the video games, you know
You just know
Okay, um mission accomplished. Let's keep going
next up
A farewell how many missions are there two three left in the game? I found something
Buenos Aires international airport this morning now watch this
heralds trail ends at the airport, but
Turns out that a top providence operative owns a vineyard in the area three faces were on that
Of infamous new york law firm morgan yates and colin and that fucking terrifying look behind the luggage
Today you can barely see it fucked up. She's infiltrated them. She's sending a message
She needs my help could have fooled me. You don't know her anyway
You're going after her
You'll need to deal with the herald her name is tamara vidal former cia asset and political firebrand
She's a master of surveillance and the constant's most trusted aid. She'll have eyes everywhere
You won't get far as long as she's in the game
Why are you telling me this?
I thought you were out. Yeah
Old habits, I guess
anyway, I
I need to go
See you around 47
No, see you tomorrow
Rendezvous with diana burnwood in mendoza and ascertain her allegiance
Landed out smuggled items. I don't have anything
Fiber wire or a snow globe
No, how about?
all I have
coins or
remote taser
key hacker
I don't I have not used
the
I've not used the fiber wire once the entire game
I don't think I ever have
P break collective p break. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I don't i'm not sure i'm gonna beat this one tonight
I'll check it out. We'll see but i'm probably gonna get to get to the point where
We'll finish it up tomorrow. Just want to let you know
There's two missions has been about like four or five hours about
But all right, let's let let the non subs out
And we're gonna take a p break. Yeah, we're gonna take a p break, but just whatever be good
Be good
Don't fuck around be good hang out and go pee go pee
We're back. Uh, let's do this for a little bit. Let's check
You know, we're gonna check the level out and then i'll probably stop
I like the idea of actually starting a new level in one of the last levels tomorrow
Let's go. Let's go walk around though. Let's take a look mr. Green. There he is
Oh, look at that fireman, but he is real fireman is real. What do you mean fireman is real?
Huh, he's real iron man is a shitty character. Um, what does that have to do with fireman?
So that's diana we're gonna find out what the real allegiance is because you're not an idiot
No, no talking. Oh replay. Whatever do not ele you know what my favorite hitman level is the ones where
There's a target and they're literally right next to you when you start the mission
It's like I get you could just shoot them right there and run and leave
But you shouldn't
What are you doing?
Has everybody been quiet was it the dot dot dots? Oh god. Damn it. I've
Why are you guys doing? Why are you guys doing that?
She tried to jump to avoid the taster. Why are you guys doing the dot dot dot? I don't know what's going on here
What's happening here? Who's that?
Approach diana burnwood. No, there's no x guys. There's not even an x. So don't even you got my message
So what's the plan? He said no talking. Not the only one who's been busy 47
I'm this close to becoming the next constant
I'll be able to dismantle providence from the inside
Only one man stands in my way
Don yates
That we're here to go partners legal counsel for years
He's the top candidate but remove him from the playing field
If edward suspects
I will convince him you acted alone
retaliation for gray
Trust me. I know what i'm doing poop wine
She has eyes everywhere I fixed on you unless we take her out
She never leaves my side for long
Whatever your plan is
I'll help you if I can you're sure about this as sure as i'll ever be
What was that?
I just went to like ds graphics. I got you an invitation just like old times come find me when it's done
Good luck 47
Holy shit, there's a little big party
I'm not muted
Eliminate tamara vidal eliminate dawn archibald do not eliminate
Diana birdwood do not eliminate diana birdwood
Like I said, we'll talk again when it's done. My mic is not muted. I can look over and see
You did liar. Why is he not talking?
Okay, let's have fun. Let's have fun
Right clap right now. Yeah. Okay, isn't this in the first hitman? There's a good reporter outside
New york-based law firm morgan yates and carl has been among the most
Oh
I mean no one's ready
No one is ready to be grabbed by like the neck from behind when they're looking through a small eyepiece
It wasn't long at all. Okay here. I got you an invitation. We need a fucking invitation. She's in my head
You're in my you're in my head when it's done
Good luck 47. Okay. Here we go
Save it here. Jim. What should I play when this stream is done?
Well, you'll know very soon
You will know very soon because we're gonna pick this up tomorrow before we start around the same time probably around like four o'clock pacific
New york-based law firm yates and cone has been among the most successful and the most controversial companies in the united states
Founded in the greed is good downtown era of the mid 1980s by kenneth morgan don yates and theodore cone
The firm quickly amassed an impressive. Oh jeez. Can you believe these people don't let them get to you pam
Let's just take it from the top
You don't care about this
And van orton tobacco a reputation for ruthlessness and dirty tactics. No doubt originating with the notorious
Affluenza defense of you don't care if he does that. Hey everybody. It's me on live tv
And I just want to say that every
I just want to say if you take a picture of me, you're gonna send me revenue
And i'll give you permission
If you could show me the invite, please x to show invite go sir. Thank you. Thank you. You're welcome
Um read chat read chat what?
All right. Yeah. All right. All right. I think we're done. We'll pick it up tomorrow afternoon
No, I tried to knock him over the railing. That's how you know, I i've gone off the rails
I thought the guy had a leaf blower
I saw the leaves down here and i'm just like, oh wait, it must be a leaf blower. No, that's a shotgun
Can I pick up the camera hey i'm trying to take it I can't there's no indicator I can't take it
Please behave attention to yourself. You probably have to kill him. Give me the fucking camera
From place explosive in camera. Why'd he throw a grenade?
Yeah, no, we're done
I'm just messing around. I'm just dicking around
link link link
Heal the nation. We need bionicle
Joe biden is sad. He will not he will not repay the debt unless you stop everything and play the
Mata nui online game. It's a free flash game. You can find it at bio media project
I don't know what that is. Go will clear half a billion dollars. Is that a flash game?
Well, I can't play it because it doesn't exist anymore
biden
I'm trying to get i'm gonna try to make that bionicle viewing stream happen. That was a wrong link
It usually is best performance pretending to be
Oh, this is funny
Is the award right we talked about this
Previously, we talked about the best pretending on twitch a bit
Yeah, I remember that and then I get up and I bump into stuff accidentally and like I can't see the audience
I'm like putting my hands up. I remember that. All right, let's uh, let's call it here. Let's call it at 4 20
Perfect, right? Uh-huh. Didn't mean to do that. But like funny right everybody laugh at it, please
We'll pick it up tomorrow afternoon. I will finish hitman tomorrow
I will complete hitman 3 tomorrow at least like the story because this mission looks like it could be pretty ridiculous
So i'd like to see it. So we'll see tomorrow somewhere around four o'clock pacific time p.m
Mark it on your calendar if we'll see we'll see if not, then maybe we'll see you again soon
When are those announcements very soon?
I have one in particular that I cannot wait to tell you two actually in particular two of them. Thanks for watching though
What time?
Tomorrow 4 p.m pacific 4 p.m pacific. That's tomorrow
About 359, you know, I might go I might just do it at 359 just because that one person said to
But thanks for the subs everybody
I haven't really been keeping up with subs
Um, I still just can't believe that this many people will subscribe to this channel. So thank you all of you
It's shocking that this many people pay me money. Um, all I can say is thanks no shit
It's because they wanted to be able to chat
That's not well
I only turn sub only on for a short period of time very seldomly. I don't use it that often
We have to make you a billionaire somehow
Tyrant
Apologize for sub mode. Well, i'm not gonna apologize for sub only mode because it was used
to just
Just chill everybody out. I use sub only mode like once a year. I'm very sorry. I'm sorry
I'm very sorry. I turned on sub only mode. Please don't hate me. I turned on sub only mode for like a couple hours
I'm very sorry. Please accept my apology accept my apology
You accept my apology. I'm so sorry
You don't don't apologize. No, no, we do not accept your apology
Well, then I rev I revert my apology. In fact, i'm gonna turn it on tomorrow
For at least 25 minutes
No, i'll see you guys tomorrow. Good night guys
We'll finish it man
Bye. Good night. Take care