What's happening? What's up? Somebody said, what's cocaine like? Will you relax? First thing that
you're going to say in this chat. First thing you're going to ask me in 2023. That's your first
comment of the whole year. Oh my god. No, what's up? How's everybody doing? Welcome to the first
stream of first. There's a lot of first time chatters. What's going on here? It's, it's like
only first time chatters. What? Have I just not paid attention to any of this? Does this happen
all the time? There's a lot of these. It's because it's EU friendly. Oh, it's an EU friendly stream.
It is noon pacific. You're right. Well, happy new year. I mean, it's not that early. A lot of my
streams start only a couple hours from now. I wouldn't say this is super EU friendly.
But whatever, I'm doing the thing where I'm very clearly leaning back and my chin is going down
because I have to burp, but I'm still talking. You're still fucking hearing my sentence,
by the way. I'm not going to stop and burp and I'm not done talking yet. I'm good now.
How long is this stream going to be? I don't know. I'll tell you what we're doing though.
It's a little game called Wrestling Empire. I do admit I have getting the itch to come back
to this game. The last time we played it was six months ago, five months ago. I saw a lot of what
Moon Moon was doing and it just made the itch just unscratchable. So I had to play it. So
Wrestling Empire is the first stream of the new year. It's itchy. And I will tell you,
how many goblins approximately do you think you could take in a single time?
Um, a lot. I actually think a lot. How big are they? I'm thinking 10. Do I have a weapon?
10. Is it just fist? Is it just fist versus fist? I don't know. I forget who even said that,
but is it, do I get a weapon or is it just like I can punch? It's my grandma's birthday,
play Elden Ring. No, I'm not playing Elden Ring until later. Stop stalling. It's the first,
it's been four minutes. Just relax for a second. Four minutes is not a stall. That is one to two
minutes for the intro. And I've been talking for less than two minutes. This is a stall would be
15 minutes. Stall is 15 minutes, not four. I've only been speaking for two minutes. This is a
normal length for an introduction to a broadcast. Very normal. But I think I would beat up, I could
beat up 10 goblins without a doubt. Honestly, it might even be 20. If there's no weapons involved,
I think I'm all right. So, uh, something, so Holly and I last night were making characters in this
game. I was like, you know what, maybe I will play it. Yeah. It sounds like fun. I made a bunch of
people. Holly and I, we kind of just took turns making characters. I think it was like 12, 13,
14 characters we put in the same league. I don't even know who to play with. I have no idea.
I just, in fact, I, I don't think I'm going to make a character right now.
We'll have to see. Goblin has a battleaxe. That's easy. Stop stalling. I'm, this is not a stick.
Get out of here with this. Goblins have claws and I've got, I don't know, choke them. What? Well,
oh no. Claws. What do we think I have? It doesn't make any sense. I have, hey, I, what,
you don't think I have claws too? You don't think, all right, we're moving on from this.
Welcome back. Uh, happy new year again, everybody. Hope your 2023 goes well.
No, I would just, I, I'm, I could do it. I don't have to prove this. I'm already proving something
later this year. All right. Wrestling empire. You guys ready? Everyone's just ready. We don't
have to sit around. It's ready to go. So the question here, all right, let's go over some of
the characters. So here's who I've made. Again, Holly and I sat down. This is Sebastian Seles.
I just picked wrestling revolution because that was the, I think the most characters are here.
So we've got Sebastian Seles runs the operation. I made scorned. I don't know if that was like
funny, I guess. Here's the Android, which I thought, I think the Android looks kind of cool.
Here's Waltie. Waltie. I didn't make Scally. I think I just added the Y because I just saw
that before making the characters. Here's Phil. Phil. Here's Wicked Wilma. Uh, Lionel of the
Mountain. Q-Jean. Handsome. What else is here? Oh, scratch. The gnat. I think it's already on the
gnat, by the way. Uh, Amphibia Adam. Who else? Oh, Gil. And I think that's it. Who should I,
who do I play with? I don't even, I don't know who to play with. I don't know what to do right
now. This would be what the third or fourth run through of this game. Make another character. You
want me to make another character? I think I want to play with, no, should I play with the gnat and
just, who cares? Make another, all right. All right, fine. Who do I make? I feel like I put all
of my, my, my, my happiness is in some of these, right? But first of all, hold on. You can't even
see me. All right. You want to make a new character? All right. Who should I make? Make sure I'm in the
editor. Hi, by the way. Good to see you. All right. How about, uh, this will be only four weeks left
here though. All right. Okay. All right. All right. 16 weeks. Make you. No, I made, I already made me
before and I don't want to make me. All right. How about Scally? No, we'll keep in Scally. All right.
Woodrow. I need to change this. Uh, I don't want you to have a partner. So who do I make? You guys
didn't like any of those 12 characters. Now he's stalling. That person gets it. Make Miku. You want
to make Miku? No, these are all original characters. These are all original characters. I, I, I, no,
no, we're not, we're not, no, not yet. We'll do that later. No, you know what? I'm getting started
on the Nat. I don't even care. I'm just playing as the Nat. I'm playing as the Nat. We're starting
with the Nat. I, I made all these characters. I made all these. I'm going to relax because I don't
want to get angry. It's the new year. Polly and I made all these characters last night. Let's go.
I'm going Nat. What do you mean too late? All right. It's already on the Nat. I promised that
wasn't picked previously. I did, I was, I didn't mean to pick that. I didn't want to pick the Nat,
but the Nat was there already. People are going to think I like did it on purpose.
All right. So let's go. For those of you that have no idea what this game is, you're balding.
Yeah, I'm almost 40. Good. I can't wait. Um, what was I saying? All right. So you, of course,
you know how this game works. You've seen it like five times now. Let's go. You never should have
taken the step of the Nat. You don't have what it takes to survive in the real world. I didn't make
this person. If you want to be escorted to the ring safely, just admit you made a mistake and back
out. This is literally the first time I've ever been here. I see you decided to take responsibility
for what happens behind the scenes, the Nat. What's wrong with this guy? If you take this road,
it's your responsibility to get through the curtain in time. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. It turns green. You
have to get through the curtain. Yep. This guy, why is this guy so fucked up? This character, yeah,
it's like four, five or four, six. Okay. Yeah. We know how this works. The first match is singles
match. Wait, does this character suck? This character might actually be awful. All right.
Will you stop explaining? Dude, go sit down. I missed. Should I just hurt him? All right.
Fuck this guy about it. Wait, it's not time for my match. When's my match? Look at how hurt this guy
is. This guy's like helping me. Shit, I forgot you could do that. What do they want? What do you want?
Power slam? What is that? A magazine? Give me that. Can I take it? Give me that back or I'll show you
what it's for. What? I'm already fucking everything up. What is this? Is this a menu at a restaurant
or is this a magazine? Oh shit. Okay. Here we go. Light reading. That's not my time yet. Don't let
anybody scare you out of taking this route. They're at risk, but it can also be more fulfilling. Oh my
God, that's Lionel of the Mountain friend. Got it back. Oh wait, this is this lady's magazine.
All right, here you can have it back. Right in the nose. What is this? Oh, that's right. They added
new items. Like you can dig. That's right. They added, I remember reading the patch notes.
I got to get back inside. Find a treasure. There's a treasure? There's also a presence too,
which you can open, I think. Yeah. Oh my God, there's just $300 on the ground. Stop. This shovel is
mine now, Nat. Just assume everything you own is mine. Why is this guy such a dick? God damn it.
Right before fucking match two. Help. Somebody help me. Why am I getting Rube Goldberg wrestled?
Oh my God. This is bad. All right, let's go. This microphone. Oh my God. This is just look
at how big this microphone is. This microphone is huge. It's not supposed to be like this. Look at
even in his hand. Someone's going to take this from me and you'll see how big it. Oh wait,
there's a scorn. I'm realizing right now that scorned it is just pain. It's just different
color scheme. Look at how big the microphone is. Even if it was in somebody's hand, that's bigger.
Act right. I know you're cowering backstage clinging to that inter title of yours.
That may be the safest place for you right now, but that treasure can't stay buried forever.
If I had the shovel. What's happening? Are we all right? Did I win? All right. This motherfucker
has an urn in his hands. Uh, I'm running. What the fuck was that? I don't even have a microphone
anymore. All right, let's keep score. Oh wait, give me that apple. Give me actually give me that
apple. I want it. My health is so low. Wait, is my health low or did it not save the all the shit
that happened right when I got beat up backstage? It did. Come on. So this is just a regular match.
First match of the evening. Let's go. I'm already going to lose. I think I made this guy's stats
awful. I hope I didn't. Sorry. We're good. The Nat sucks. Well, no, the Nat sucks because I got
beat up backstage. All right. The character sucks. The character actually a pretty effective way to
deal with that. Here we go. All right, let's get it back together here. Get up. Okay. There is a
shovel out there. Oh my God. What the fuck are you doing? God damn it. Tries to leave the arena.
I've covered in blood already. Oh my God. All right. Already a disaster. Get up, get up, get up,
get up, get up. All right. Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out. Is this illegal?
Why did the ref get hurt? I'm so screwed. Illegal. Call him out for that. Get him in
trouble for that. He should be. Are you going to restart? No, I am going to be a coward though.
You better believe it. Shit. I'm too, I am too short. I'm hitting the ledge when I throw the
things into the ring. Are you kidding me? All right. I got to do a stand up with this guy.
All right. I'll be all right. Look, I'm not, you don't win every single match. It's okay.
What a moron. Advantage. Take the advantage of it. What is with this reversal? Bullshit. Stop.
He's almost, he's going to get counted out. He's at six right now. I just got to be,
I got to be an annoying little nat. Just keep him out here and win. He's doing a move to me.
Oh shit. No, no. Get up. How is he still standing? Here we go. Give me that. Yes. Same deal. Just
keep him out here. Oh, come on. How did he not fall down from that? The only way I can win is
if I get him outside. Change the camera settings. What is it on right now? What should I do too?
I feel like I did change this for some reason when I was making people. What should it be?
Camera's fine. Is it good? Hard camera. Players only, right? Do first person. Yeah, raise the
first person. We'll do it later. I think it's fine. Yeah. What are you? I'm an idiot. Although I have
not lost yet. So we're okay so far. All right. Let me do some actual technical wrestling here.
Good start. Oh my. He just was palming my face. Can I just go for like a little pin right now?
That would be so awesome. Technical wrestling. I mean, it'd be great if he didn't reverse every
single move I did. You suck. Dun, dun. You suck. No, I was just being a little asshole backstage
and it's what got me into trouble. It's all right. We're going outside. There's only three
minutes left. How big of a hole can you dig? Can I make a hazard? Stop swinging so much.
I'm going to win. I'm going to win right now. Oh, it's over. I win. Just don't fuck this up.
I'm going to win. That's game over right there. First match won. Looks like a VIP. That guy paid
10 grand for that seat. Who was that guy? I can't make a giant hole, right? What happens if I just
keep doing this? Can I fall in it? VIP says, okay, let go of my arm, please. I shouldn't walk in by
that. Somebody in the crowd comes out and puts me in an arm bar. All right. Scored is really good.
Look at these stats. I try to keep everybody between like 70 and 80, like 72 to 75 ish.
All right. Well, the math's progress is being hindered by the limitations of wrestling revolution.
What? Why? But what? The limitations. He has worse stats than everybody in the whole league.
This is the worst promotion. Oh, so I made everybody in the worst league.
I wrapped that cash for somebody else. Nat, who said you could open it? Who's talking about it?
Remember the money that weighed the present in the very beginning? I opened up a present on the
ground and there was money in it. But dude, why are you putting money into a present and
just leaving it on the ground? There's so many people around. Okay. All right. So this is the
really popular one, but everybody in here has like 90, 90, you know, 85, 85, 85 vending machines and
water bottles. Freeman sumo contest. What is this? What is it? How? Why would it be in a sumo contest?
Who are the, who are the two of my opponents? Can I see that? Okay. 20 o'clock at two hours.
The Nat is in a sumo. Yeah, that's weird. Am I going to get in trouble for this? Oh, wait,
was that for me? What do you think? He was happy about that. Something you want to say to me.
Um, yeah, I have a proposal for you. What do you have my attention? What do you want to talk about?
Let's work together. How do you see us working together? Um, can you be my manager?
Oh, that's right. Okay. All right. Right. Right. If they're in a different, right. Okay.
If they're in a different company, then you can't do any of this. All right. Well,
I'm just looking for food on the ground. I've got an hour. Yeah. You have to be in the same
promotion. And what I remember. Oh, there's Lionel the mountain. He's my friend. So you've got a
microphone in your gift. I received a sign in mine once. All right. Cool. Very cool. Nice. You got a
sign. All right. I got to get in there. Any more food on the ground? I'm not going in there with
half health. Grab the gun. You can't use the gun though. I'll take it. No, it costs money if you
take it. Right. All right. I think I'm all right. I've got like 70%. No, it costs money. Hot dog.
If you walk out with a prop, it costs like a hundred and fifty dollars every time. Who's in
this match? Oh, it's a sumo match. Right. Okay. I get ready. Is it us? Who's in this match?
Reman sumo contest. Why is there a table on top of their table? That's very confusing.
Is this for the championship already? This is not for the championship already. Is it?
What's the. What do you do here? I just hit my fucking head on the stairs at the back of my
skull. Like the worst part. Like the soft part of your head. I just hit it. Okay. It's red eye.
Should I put tables in here? I'm sure you think winning a fight involves being on top
for three precious seconds. Did I set this up? Somebody just got hurt. When you win a real fight,
the loser doesn't get up ever again. Ow. It hit me right in the face. You dick. Somebody already
went over the table. What's wrong with this guy? Dude, I'm just going to drink all the fucking
drinks out here and have full health. Are you serious? The match doesn't start until I go in.
There's so many drinks out here. I'm going to get to full health. What is this? Is it something on
fire? What's burning? What happened to you? What are the rules? That's my finishing move.
Why am I losing health? Is it a pin? If you fall out of the ring, you lose. Oh shit. That's not
good. All these tables are meaningless then. All right. I got to. So don't get thrown over the top
ropes. So there's no submissions. There's no nothing. You could help. You could do anything
right now. All right. So I'm just going to do this. I got a great idea. Are you fucking kidding me?
Why did I do anything else? Check this out. Now I'm safe. I don't give a shit what happens. I'm
fine. Just don't get thrown over the top rope. They're both so concerned with wearing the belt.
Yeah. What are you going to do about it? Nothing. Throw him over. Get him over the top. He's out.
It's over. I win. Oops. Don't do it. Stop. Oh my God. Get up. I'm trying. How did I miss? I fruit.
How did I miss that poorly? That was so bad. Get outside. Get outside. What are you? What's
Okay. The guy won. I was going for a spectacle. I was going for a spectacle. Wait, they are friends?
But weren't we just fighting? I did pretty well in that. Somebody interfered, but whatever. I won.
I actually, that was for the championship. That's the second match I've ever had.
All right. Going pretty well so far. I'm the new champion. That's actually amazing. I can't believe
it. I heard you smashed a table. We'll never be welcome back in this venue. They were everywhere.
Why is that my problem? I'm winning your second match. You remain undefeated at wrestling
revolution. Yep. I'm going to stay that way. Do this thing right here. You dream of this belt
every day. Do I have a match today? It's only a matter of time before the intertitle is mine.
You might as well drop it now. Give me that back. You may have beaten me in the ring. What is this
guy talking about? What the fuck are you doing? Leave me alone. We had a match like two weeks ago
and it was a regular match. You just, I, well, actually, yeah, actually I kind of didn't I beat
him with a stick for a while. Am I okay? Oh, it's the end of the show. I'm going, I'm getting out of
here. I got to go to the hotel. I got to wear my belt. How do I wear it? There we go. Do not
hit me with a sledgehammer, please. All right. Bedtime. Is this food? What is this? Oh,
the brass knuckles. They just look huge on me. All right. Go to bed. I think a few from the floor.
Go to the bar. After eight hours of comfortable sleep, the Nats energy levels are now at 75%.
Scorned has developed a friendship with Hugh Jazz of Federation Online. Okay. Okay. All right.
So this is versus, this is a non-title singles match versus Eugene. Then I got nothing tomorrow.
All right. 21. I need to, I get a heal. I need to, uh, eat food or something. Why would I be
fighting? Why are we in two completely different weight classes? What's up guys? All right. Just
need to eat. Just get close to full health. Oh no, there's a spear. I don't want that.
Imagine eating four double cheeseburgers before a big athletic event. All right. That's good.
That's good. I don't need anymore. Costs like 10 bucks every time. Eat the table. Skate five. Oh,
that, wait, you can, can't you? How do I do it? How do you skate? Enjoy it while it lasts,
but nobody actually believes you're the inter champion. I mean, I, I get it. It's been too,
it's been two weeks. How do I use it? Not right before a match. Get off. Oh my, I think he
accidentally just did that. Not right before a match. What the, how do I, I know you can ride
this. Why can't I ride it? What? This skateboard is mine. Stop. I'm more skillful than you.
God damn it. I'm actually fucking annoyed right now because I don't want to be fighting these
people. Give me the skateboard. I have to, I have a match. Why are they all such dicks?
Somebody said, am I an idiot? I didn't do anything. This guy just jumped me. I can't see where I'm
going. I have to get in the ring right now. Please. I got to get there in time. I have to
get there. I have to get there in time. Hopefully the skateboard Uber can get me there quickly.
This is not the title, right? Is there any food? Look at how tired I am. This, this microphone's
costing me money every time. I'm fighting the biggest guy in the entire league. This is not
fair. Those like to keep count. This is the first title I've won in my career. It's also the last
title you'll ever hold. If you want to make history, I'll make you history. This is not,
this is actually not fair. Maybe I should start counting title defenses so that you get to be
another notch on my belt. Just run. Just run. He, okay. Thanks a lot, ref. I appreciate it.
Somebody is doing this on purpose. You making me fight the huge guy?
Good luck because I won the belt. Move over the commissioner on his desk. I'm just wearing the
belt. It's like a toy. What do I do about this? I can't even reach his head. Get him out of the
ring. Just hit him in the head with a chair over and over again. Holy shit. I can't, I can't. Yeah,
I have to. I gotta take him outside. I have to rely on weapons to beat this. Test of strength.
There's no way I was ever going to win this. Get up. That hurt my back so bad. Get the ref
out of my face. Stop, stop, stop. This is unfair. It's just actually unfair. What was I supposed to
do about this? I'm out of stamina. I can't even run. God damn it. What am I doing? It's like awkward
shit. Okay. You got more attitude. What am I supposed to do about that? You can do proceed to
match. Yeah, but I just, I have to go and just attack people. It just happened. I made, oh no,
yeah, see the prop. It's $350 every time to take that stupid microphone out. All right,
get me out of here. Give me the hotel. Sorry to see you lose to Eugene. That knocked your profile
down to 70%. Yeah, well, you could have helped, couldn't you? See, you lost another match. The
nat. That brings your win rate down to 67%. One of you two has the math wrong and I don't know
who to make fun of. So fuck both of you. How's that sound? Still got this, don't I? Still got this.
Mm hmm. Chumps. Wait, give me the, yeah. It's haunting everybody. What a little shit. Hey,
whoever can grab this out of my hands gets to keep it. Nobody. I just saw a stool in the bar.
If that's what you're looking for. No, I wasn't looking for a stool. Hey, by the way, it looks
like you look like you're struggling. You need a ride to the hospital. Do I? Should I? Do I go?
Yeah. Don't worry. I'll get you to the hospital as fast as I can. What's the matter with me?
With my hand? Okay, this is the doctor, right? And I, doctor, can you give me a heel or something?
Just sleep in the bed? Why are people doing that? Okay, I'm going to bed.
My attitude is down for no reason. Do you get more health if you sleep in the hospital?
Sweet warriors. Yeah, it looks like he was going to attack me, but 43%. All right. We tag team
champions released. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh shit. An ad has been booked to face scratch in an
inter championship match on the fourth week of May. All right. I gotta get ready. Nothing
scheduled. All right. This is where I can make up. Uh, let me, so I'm in the hospital. Let me get
some, let me make, uh, let me get some health. I could probably sleep again. Couldn't I? Let me
eat first. I'm going to open these presents. Money. I'll take like 400 bucks for no reason.
All right. Sleep. Okay. I'm all right then. The MPCs are so scary. I'm kind of bleeding money
though. All right. Lost weight. Okay. Todd's snorting has been released. Steel cage. Oh wait,
this is tag team versus Eugene's team. All right. Let me get a little bit of revenge here.
Let's just go right to it. This time I actually have me an Android. I actually have the skateboard
this time. This is a pretty good team. Android's actually really good. I take the skateboard into
the gate. This is really fucking dangerous. Um, that was pretty cool. Do a kick flip. How do you
do a kick flip? Leon lock and Eugene. Wait, this is the guy at the table that I beat up in the very
beginning that I thought he was a VIP, right? He's not even in the cage. This is not illegal
what I'm doing by the way. How is this not, how is this allowed? Why should I be allowed to do this?
Are they booing? How do I kick flip? I can kick flip. How do you kick flip? No, keep him in,
keep him in. He'll get in trouble. How do you kick flip? I think I, I, did I break it? Wait,
no, he picked it up. Give me that. Give me that. That's mine. Oh my goodness. Thank you.
You just have to escape the ring, right? And this house works. Come and get me. He's too big. He
can't climb. Somebody come get me. Come on. I'm up here waiting for you. I'm up here. Can you
actually do a kick flip? No, you can't. Shit. I'm not in trouble. I could just beat him with it.
Do not let him do that. Oh, she's got money. She has money. I want it. She's bringing money.
Do I want that money? You stay in the ring. Where'd it go? Yes, I got it. You fucking idiot.
I'm it. I think I'm still all right. Get up. What are you doing? What is wrong with you?
Did I just lose the belt? I didn't lose the belt. Wait, it's not over. It's not over. I can't.
Is he climbing out of here? Why is the ref climbing out? It's because the tag team. All right.
But I need to, they don't even, they like, don't know what to do. I can't climb it. Yeah. I can't
climb. I'm stuck out here. Come on. There we go. I just shook it. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
I can still affect the game. Where am I? Switch characters. I feel like it's more fun this way.
First person. I feel like I'm going to puke. Hey, who's winning? Whose arm is that? I want the bat.
I don't have any weapon in my hand. Dude, get this shit out of the, there we go. I feel like I'm in
VR. Get him. Get him. What's wrong? He's trying to attack me. He's so big. He's like wedged in.
Three. We did it. Oh, that's my belt. Get up here. Shit. I think I just puked.
That's a green slime come out of me. We did it. I can keep the title.
Suffered considerably. Good. Yep. The androids is not supposed to be here. Okay. Your character is
so annoying. Here I'm a missing 450 splash compilation video. I forgot just how
unbelievable this game really is. It's just so unbelievable. I want to wish you luck in your
match tonight, Nat. Okay. After all, dangerous things happen back here and it would be a shame
if you ended up crawling to the ring, but neither of us want that, right? So hand over $760 and I'll
let you live. You're not even worth my time. I'll get you when you least expect it. I'm not going
to give you a thousand dollars almost, but what non-title. This is the first blood match
versus act, right? I gotta be careful. If you notice, I believe I've been bleeding every single
match from the very beginning. I'm like, okay, I got pretty good health. What's up? You want that?
Is it good? I didn't. I was trying to put the, I was trying to put the belt back on. This caused
mayhem. All right. Well, I'm not, I'm not messing around. Press room. Oh, this food in here.
I thought I'd lose agility. It's unhealthy. I thought it was in the water. Get down before
someone gets hurt. Okay. I'll get down. Yeah. You can't put that in the compilation. Oh, it's not
my time yet. I'm going out there with a, I'm going out there with a desk. Wait, it's my time. What
about your belt? Oh, who cares about the belt? The belt's mine. It doesn't matter who's carrying
it. I guess I own that belt. I gotta get rid of the microphones. They just, I'm bleeding money.
Is this the championship match or no? Those first blood. All right. My goal is to get something
heavy and throw it right in their face in the very beginning. You know what I'm saying? Like
throw it, throw the iPad directly into the mouth and instantly first blood or it's the chair.
What would, that would probably cause blood first, right? Yeah. Like horizontal in the teeth.
They'll line it up. It's going to be immediate. Go ahead. Start talking and act right. I'm sure
you're very excited to be standing in the ring with a champion like me, but we both know that
you do not belong here. So there's no point in making this match for the title. Figure yourself
as my sparring partner and perhaps you'll benefit from the experience I'm offering you.
Don't patronize me the nat. We both know why you're scared to put your title on the line.
Shit. Blood, blood. Wait, I am bleeding too. What, what is that? How do we, I thought it was first
blood. What, what exploded? What happened? What's going on? iPad blew up in my face.
I'm all right. It's all right. I'm fine. Fine. Fine. How is that not blood? I'm so confused.
How do I, it's, there's a lot of blood on the ground. That's me. Oh, so, okay.
So he's bleeding an explosive went off in my face and there was blood pouring on the ground. Nice.
I want, what happened? Why the lights off? Let me give the audience a show for a second.
Why is it? Who cut the lights? There we go. All right. I didn't know this was the worst promotion.
Again, $149 for the mic. I got 10 grand. There was a landmine desk, I guess. I saw you get smashed
with that desk. Hope you're feeling better now. I mean, I feel all right. I was shaking my hand.
Are we hugging? Oh, okay. It's a friend. Where's the owner? I want to talk to, I want to talk to
the owner. I hope that's not the owner. Are you the owner? Who owns this place? Should I not be in
here? These, it looks like they're working some, they're, they're working something out in here.
Oh, that's Lionel the mountain. I'm just going to go to sleep. Get a good night rest.
Hi. Why are you tracking me? What's going on? What? What? Hi. Hotel time. I want, I want to go
for the world championship. I think I could get it. She fell off the bench. Don't I have a title
match coming up? What? Evan Gillette could not be woken from his sleep this morning. The 57 year
old veteran is thought to have died of natural causes. Okay. That's too bad. Stage a special
tribute memory of Evan Gillette. Prior to the public show, private funeral will take place at
5 PM. Okay. 5 PM at the cemetery. Sounds like right now. I gotta go. Get up. Where's the cemetery?
Okay. It's gym cemetery or airport cemetery. Where is it? Hospital cemetery. Where's the,
where is it? It's hospital is all the way to the behind the gym. So this way it is. Is that it?
That was this underground. Shit. It's the other side. Go take the, I don't leave the belt. I've
got this. I got a funeral to go to. Go, go, go, go, go. Hurry. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go. Oops. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
get out of the way, get out of the way, get out of the way. I'm sorry. I can see in the
mirror where I am. I gotta go to a funeral. Where is it? Okay. Here we go. Thanks for attending the
funeral. Evan Gillette would be happy to see this turnout. Before anybody says anything in public at
tonight's show, we thought it might be more appropriate to gather here. He would have also
wanted your lives to go on. He would want the show to go on. Okay. Evan Gillette can never take
another step in this world, so we must appreciate the time we have. Just for one day, let's put
aside the fighting and respect each other as fellow warriors. Okay. I'm into that. Where's,
um, where's the, where's the, which casket is his? Okay. I'm just shaking everybody's hands.
Put it down. That guy has the tombstone. That guy has the tombstone. That's, I would put,
put that down, please. I'm not going to start anything. Can I play a song? Keep it up. All
right. He's a hot dog. Wait, there was a little altercation over here. I have to keep my friends
close to my enemies. Now I only see you suffering and I'm glad I don't have to keep the
pretense anymore. Don't worry. I'll take care of blonde blunder for you. That's not this guy's
name. This guy's name is Scratch, not the blonde blunder. Who is he referring to?
Can we find the blonde blunder? I don't see a person here named blonde blunder.
I mean, it's got, I mean, the guy with the blonde hair? No. Who else has blonde hair? Not you.
Is it you? I don't know who this guy's protecting me from. No, it's my broom. You can't have it.
No, it's not for sale. I found it. It's mine. The guy's got adrenaline from being on the phone.
Okay. I think that's good. We did the funerals over. Okay. It's time for the match. I have a
match today against one of, against one of these people here. I have a match. You give me that.
This is so big. Heard you crapped yourself. When? Let's go. I'll deal with you on the first week of
June. Get out of my sight and prepare. All right. Bring it on. I made it. What? This show is dedicated
to the memory of Evan Gillette who recently passed away. Yeah. Evan Gillette's work in this
ring meant a lot to fans, but the person was backstage. What's happening? What's happening?
What's happening? We're not in a ring. We're not in a ring. Who am I versus? There's no one here.
There's nobody here. There's nobody even here. What's happening? Ow. Why? Okay. I guess we'll just
wait till we get there. Hey, don't forget. That's my belt back there. It doesn't matter who has it.
It's like a library card. I fucking own the book. You're just cashing it out. Wait.
Fuck you. Yeah, that was easy. The three stooges routine. I'm going to beat the shit out of this guy.
Once I get out of this, I'll be okay. Oh, great. At least I'm holding the belt. That's all I care
about. No, no, no, no. Okay. Now I got you motherfucker. Sit in your seat. Sit back in
your seat. Sit back in your seat. Sit down. Sit down. Oh, that's real, real cute. Okay.
Just sitting down. Okay. All right. Hit me in the back of the head. He caught me.
No. Give me that. Give me that. This guy just keeps scooping me up. Ow. I'm not going to let
him win. No way. I can't. This guy is so hard to knock down. Oh shit. Thanks. Why are you
pitting this guy for no reason? Grab him. Grab him. Grab him. Grab him. Grab him. Grab him. Grab him.
Yeah. How is this a Memorial match? I think we were scheduled to have the Memorial match,
but then he just hates me and like fighting me on the plane. Fine. I'll grab this. You're in the
way. Get out of the way. Oh my God. What is this? Is this a piece of glass? You ruined everything.
That would have been so cool. Don't. I'm so weak. Yeah. This is the worst Memorial match I've ever,
ever seen. It's just two people trying to hurt each other. They're trying to do permanent damage
to each other. Oh my God. Get off of me. Let's get out of the seat. All right. I got the upper hand
now. Oh my God. You have to be kidding me. When did we get off the plane? We're still in the air.
Where is he going? So much blood. The Nat has damaged the reputation of Wrestling Revolution
by failing to win that inter-promotional contest. That was very bizarre. That was a very strange
day. That was his client. Okay. I mean, I got to get out of Wrestling Revolution then.
It's a huge banana. All right. No more messing around. Actually get to full health. Back to the
hotel room. You got to make Miku. Well, we're currently invested in the Nat. We will make Miku,
but I need to see how this arc ends. I'm still carrying around the tombstone. Yeah. That's not
messed up at all. Come down with an illness. Wait, what? Speaking tour has been hired in
controversy after sharing some inflammatory views with the students. Okay. Oh, this is important.
This is versus, um, this is versus scratch. Okay. This is the title match. I can't screw this up.
Just give me a water. Give me, uh, something to drink. Careful. Listen, the Nat, a lot has
changed since we first signed you to 1400 per week. Uh-huh. We all have to make sacrifices to
stay afloat. So how would you feel about taking a pay cut? I'm the champion right now. You know,
you're going to pay cut the champion? No, that's not happening. We'll find some other way to
balance the books. I'm the champion. I am the intercontinental champion. Are you seriously going
to talk to me like that? All right. We'll help. All right. Get me out of here. Don't do anything
dumb. Don't provoke anybody on the street. Don't bite anybody. Don't just leave the belt. Don't
provoke anybody. Okay. Anything in the gym I could use. I could train. What do I have stats right
now? No, no, I'll turn on an off day. Conference is starting in the press room. There's more to
this business than what takes place in the ring. The Nat. Why don't you join us for a drink to
unwind? It would probably wouldn't cost more than a hundred dollars. I have a match in 40 minutes.
All right. Fine. Yeah. We can't hurt. What? What happened to my health? I'm on my way to the studio.
Do you need a ride? Um, yeah. All right. I, yes. I'll go with you. Please take me to the studio.
No problem. Just follow me and I'll get you to the studio as soon as possible. All right. When I,
I want an interview. I want to interview for the game. Let me sit in this chair. You look exhausted.
Why don't you take a nap where there's still time? Can you guys stop telling me what to do today?
This is a, this is a sham. Oh, come, come get, come get drunk an hour before the match.
Hey dude, you should take a nap 20 minutes before the match. They all, they want me to lose.
This is a league wide conspiracy. Welcome to this inter-championship clash between scratch and the
Nat scratch. Could you start us off on how you intend to cope with the Nat? I got drunk before
a title match. The Nat is in no state to compete and I won't be taking it easy on him. You think
I'm going to be easy on you? How do you respond? I earn more than scratch and I'll prove why I'm
worth every penny. Is that the potential be the best match on the card? So buy your ticket to see
it live. Oh, it's time. Okay. Wait, I have to, this is a title match. I can't mess this up.
Food, tombstone. All right. This is huge. If I go, I can go out there with this lucky bastard.
I am okay. That's like one of the most popular people in the world. I almost just ruined
everything. As you may have heard in the news, my contract with wrestling revolution expires
next week. If chef Buffalo and I can't come to an agreement, this might very well be my last
appearance. And that in case that happens, I want to take this opportunity to express how much I've
enjoyed. All right. Don't fuck it up. He's got something to prove. I don't one, two, three.
Okay. Just do moves, do moves, get set up. Good. I'm getting fucked up. No, I'm not. I just did
like three moves in a row, but that was unfair. I just got like scooped up. He's ripping off your
head. I'm fine. I'm all right. Come on. Don't be like this. If you win this, can you play Fortnite?
I've never played Fortnite ever again. I just, that's never happening ever again. Put that down.
That's illegal. I put it down on the ground and he hit my head into it while it was falling. I fell
on top of it with his hand on my head. This is getting ugly. We might have to go with the
strat. And the strat is just beg him to come outside and beat him with a weapon until he's
dead. That's the strat. God damn it. He was so much more prepared than I was. Get him off.
Oh my God. He's going to beat me. I'm going to lose the title. No, I'm not. I grabbed him and
he reversed it immediately. What are you doing? Who's doing what? Go outside the ring.
Okay. Here we go guys. It's time to, it's time for me to win a match in wrestling revolution.
Run outside. That's what happens every time. He's smart. He's much smarter than anybody else I've
fought. He's not taking the bait here. He's too smart. Good. Oh no. How would you let your head
be that vulnerable? Catch your breath. He's not coming in yet. Five minutes. God. I'm just trying
to get some punches in. He's got so much more reach than I do. Look at his arms. His arms and
legs are so much taller. It's not fair. He missed. That's good. You're so bad at this. This character
is four feet tall. I can't do anything. I have to get out of the ring. How's that not a rope break?
I'm right here. All right. We're good. We're good. We're okay. Three minutes, four minutes.
Get him. More pressure on the neck. More pressure on his neck. Was I in that? How did I get caught
by that? You reverse every move I do. I'm going to get a weapon. He reversed it again. Reversed
again. Get the pin. Get the pin. Pin, pin, pin, pin, pin. You reversed the pin, didn't you?
Oh, this is bad. Zero health. Referee's not in here though, so that's good.
Come on. Who am I doing? How did that miss? There's no way it missed. He hit his head on it.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, you got six twice. It's over. I'm gonna lose the title. No
Still counts. I have to pit him. I have to pit him. I have to fit him
What if it's a tie? I don't lose the title, right? Uh-oh don't
Oh, it's anybody's game
You want this motherfucker?
You want this you want this you're gonna have to take it out of my cold
Dead hands one. Oh, that's what happens. No win. Sorry. You don't win
I get to keep the title. You can't lift that. Why?
Why does it have set? Why does it have 10 minutes on the clock?
Yeah, fuck you. You didn't win the title. Stop. Why are you doing this?
That guy told me that I was not gonna be alive after this didn't he? Or is that somebody else?
Wait, why did your profile rise? By the way, how much money does uh scratch make? Because I make
1400 and that was all of my argument was I made way more money. How much more money do I make than scratch?
Why would we know it wouldn't it would have just said it wouldn't that was pay-per-view
All right, still the champion. I can't believe I won the championship in the second match
Why would I why was I even given a title match? Oh you wrapped that gift for me
Really appreciate that
Thanks, how much is it costing a lot of money to keep this thing with me at all times? These are my friends, right?
That's why we're sharing the hotel room. Um, I need I want this is why I need
Uh, how do I wake up the android? Um, it's good to see you
But can I sleep in the bed, please?
I don't want to hurt you
But why I need to sleep in the bed. I need to sleep
Get down
Did he say what did he say? There's a cardboard box at the airport. Who cares?
Who cares if that's what you're looking for. Don't wake me up
It's a cardboard box if you know if that's what you're looking for
Mike geranus
Okay, only 57 a lot of releases a lot of free agents
Okay
Four-man furniture smash tables. Not no title measure. All right, so I need oh someone left me a present who left it
What's inside of it? Thanks for the sign
Appreciate it. Thank you
Down with that sort of thing. Can you play the piano?
Appreciate it. Thanks bill
I'm looking for the right person to pass my legacy on to I think you have what it takes
How would you like to be the next big bob orson as your mentor? I could teach you everything I know
Is this a joke?
Is this your idea of of playing a little prank on the gnat the smallest guy in the league think that's funny
Sure, i'll do it
Glad you're as enthusiastic about this as I am. There's nobody else i'd rather pass the torch to
Uh-huh. Cool. So now what?
Okay, big bob orson
I'm not big
My name's not bob
So this is going to be very interesting
I'm wearing different clothes
Wait, I just took his look that's it. That's all it is. It's just oh, hey, by the way here here are some clothing options
So i'm not even the gnat anymore get away from me. Do you like this trophy?
Seems like you need it more than I do. Um
Okay. Yeah, i'll take it. You're welcome. That's what friends are for
Why did you be backed up very very cautiously? I'm gonna look down. It's gonna be like looney tunes
It's gonna be dynamite in here. Well, thanks changing your finishing move to the power bomb means you're finished
Um, I didn't want to do that. That was fucking fantastic
Fantastic. I'm so happy that I did that i'm very happy
No, I want to you can't you use it
How do I use it?
How do you use this? Oh my god
Let's go the gnat with big bob orson
I'm just dressed in the same clothes
It's just mini me. I will call him
Mini me
I'm pleased to confirm that I will now be wrestling under the watchful eye of big bob orson
My rookie days are over. It's time to get serious and I couldn't ask for a better person to guide me
Everybody knows that hired help is a sign that somebody can't cope on their own
All the help in the world can't prevent you from losing to me right now
What is this match?
What?
Wait, what happened?
Did we lose what team am I on?
I don't even know what
I don't even know what team i'm on that guy's eliminated too
Who's whose team what who's in the ring?
What is going on?
It's a furniture rumble
Oh
Learned that from fucking bob orson
So it's just everybody in the ring at the same time
Don't break the table because I think that's how you got that first guy got eliminated that way. I think
What is that?
What is this?
Those are thumb tacks. These are thumb tacks
Holy shit. Are you kidding me?
Those are thumb tacks
Thank god. It didn't hit me
I'm gonna tax
On the taxi. These people are so stupid
Like you are so dumb
It didn't break. It didn't break. I'm good. I'm good. It didn't break. That's a win. I just won
Thanks. Wait, thanks
Scally for coming in and helping me
I have no idea what's going on
I just know that I want
Oh, that's bob. I'm sorry bob
That was a mess
Okay, that was for the title that has cemented his reign by defending the inter-championship
Okay, their profiles suffered
Yep. Well, I mean he jumped out of the ring and landed on his back through a table
Of course, he's gonna lose popularity. That was dumb
That was really dumb
Okay
Oh, I have to pay
Management now. So let me get this right. He came in to help. Is that what it was?
And I already have bob orson though go to the barber. Where's the barber?
Uh next to the bar
Okay, who's the barber?
Are you the barber? Oh
um
You won't let me
I think I
Dedicated my whole character arc to bob orson. So I can't do anything. Hey andrew
I just want to let you know you should probably face the desk the other way
This is a terrible reception desk should be over here. What are you doing out this late?
Never mind. Actually, it is pretty late. Isn't it phone with the phone? Oh, whatever. Just go to bed
There's a lot of people that are in this hotel room now. There's like four of us. I keep adding people to the house
This is another championship versus gil
Okay
All right. I'm i'm not messing around
I gotta defend the title
I actually think this character is pretty strong
Wait bob orson comes up with me every time
I'm so small
Oh, this is so weird. This is weird, isn't it?
Hey gil, can you believe that we've been booked to face each other in this match?
Things could get awkward, but I hope you appreciate that. I can't go easy on you just because we're friends. Oh, that's right. We're friends
Don't worry. I wouldn't have it any other way. I can't afford to lose this match either
Get him this character is so bad
Everything is reversed
Gil's too strong. This is no this guy is just he's too small. That's an advantage right there. I think all right here we go
Wrestle time
If I lose this title match, i'm going to retire this guy and make miku
Stop reversing everything
What you're rooting against me?
lose lose lose
Put me in the middle of the ring
It's comparable still this guy walk. How do you block everything?
It's over i'm gonna lose title. That's a rope break. That's a rope break. Am I all right?
Like if I just scream
Shit, that's it
You just did his finishing move
bob help
Bob do something bob
Yeah, a little too late bob, thanks
Yeah, that was a shit ref job
get out of the
Can you help me please?
It's miku time
All right status drop, but you're the champion. So who cares?
Congratulations to gil for becoming the new inter champion of wrestling revolution
Big bob orson is disappointed that his client lost that match
Oh, you didn't help at all
Do miku with every stat maxed? No, that's
Gotta give it a little bit of challenge
Uh-oh, we're running short of staff tonight. Would you sit in on commentary for the next match? Oh, would you have to do this first?
Yeah
Okay 630 bucks. Okay. So this is the oh, this is rain man
Why am I talking into a microphone over here?
And that will be joining us on commentary to share his insights in this match
You know what it takes to win. So how long do you see this match going for?
Uh, it's gonna take less than five minutes. He heard it here first and that thinks this match will be over and soon
Let's find out
Who's this other guy in a suit? I disappeared into the crowd. Oh, there I am
This is such a little shit. I'm just supposed to be hanging out
I'm just ruining everything
This guy seriously just dodged it three times. I can't take it out of his hand
I swear this guy is just everything gets reversed even when they don't even see me doing anything. I'm behind that guy
He didn't even know I was there
And I went to go hit him in the head with the bell and he dove out of the way
By the way, I won. I was right
The real winner tonight is you than that you predicted this match would be quick
Almost as quick as your ankles are gonna snap
Oh my god
This guy's so fucked up. You seem a little sore
Okay, you damaged the reputation of the
Okay, who will meet?
Okay
Is that the same character?
No, chef buffalo with perfect shawn
Okay
This is wait. Hold on a minute. We have a confrontation with big bob orson
What's this about?
What's this about miku you promised I know but this is important. This is important lore here
I'm about to have a confrontation with my mentor the person who I took all their clothes
And pretended to be them for the last three weeks
What does he want now? I've been carrying you for long. It's about time. I dropped you
Sure propping you up made me stronger, but I also held me back from everything I could be
Once I'm unchanged from you. I'll be free to go as far as I want in any direction I choose
So am I supposed to just take the
You never even felt my full weight big bob orson. You'll find it was better to be with me than against me
Can I put my old clothes back on?
It doesn't say anything about no weapons
Sorry bob
Yeah, hope you got it
They can only be one bob orson. I'm sorry
It's got the same idea too. One of us one of us has to go
They can only be one bob orson
It's gonna be me
my god
Um
Okay. All right, everybody relax
Everybody relax
Okay
All right
I get to be bob orson now, right?
Zero oh no
Uh-oh listen nat did you ever stop to think that the heat between us doesn't have to be so destructive
You just watched what I just did to bob orson on the the backstage camera
I'm joined forces
Don't I already I have three friends already. Sorry. I don't have more than room room for more than three friends
Uh, i'll make mika right now
A lot of news today I get another title shot. Ah, all right
Okay
Should I do it in wrestling revolution or a different one? Like should I go into?
like
This one or like strong style or something?
Do a different one
How's this one? But wait a minute i'm
In the middle of the career
With the nat I can't stop
Retire the net
Just should I just
Yes, you can just make the net miko
Can you can I just do that?
Can I?
Yeah, but I don't want to be in this
league
I want to be I don't want to be in this league
All right, let's retire the net
We're gonna retire the net
So you want to end your career? What do you mean? No, no, no, no, no
But I have otherwise I have to stay in this league
All right, I saw a great idea i'm gonna go for it. Somebody said
Nat sune miku. Where is the nat like this, right? Um, how tall was miku? That's not
Like that, right
Is that right? It's blue right miko's hair is blue. What does miko wear for clothes? Is it also blue, right? It's teal
Not even how the hell you make teal like that, right?
Like that. Oh shit. All right. Thanks for the reference mods
Okay, that's good. That's a little too
All right getting there. I mean, this is the best I can do guys. I can't I can't make that hair
Do better what this is the best I could do
Okay, this is like gray. Does it matter?
This is like okay. This is like black gray and teal
Hold on. Let me see if I can get a pattern
This is I will make this like gray
Actually, wait, hold on wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Look at this. Look at this
All right. We need to it needs to be gray up on the top
Like gray, you know what I mean? It's kind of like a light gray. Is that too gray?
I think that's all right
Don't forget she has a necktie. Oh, okay. She has a necktie. Oops. Wait, um, he's very pale
Trying to get it without it being like a
Like a bright
Yeah, that's not
That's not accurate at all
Is that better?
Maybe like 10 percent
It's hard and it's hard
I think it's too bright still
I think that's close enough. I don't know. I don't know. The shoes need to be black. Okay. Okay
I kind of like I like this one. I like this one. Which one five
seven or
Five do you think five is five? Yeah. All right. We're staying with five. Let me fix the shoes. Hold on
It's with the what color these black headphones are. Oh, that's right. All right. So
How big is miku? How tall is miku supposed to be?
She's like five feet tall
He needs okay. I had necktie. I was in necktie. All right, i'll do five i'll do five two
How tall is miku miku is five foot two
This is a wish.com miku figurine
All right, i'll just keep this here
Okay. Now we need
The music has to be accurate
It's gonna be very fast. I think this is the right one
Fast disco, okay. All right. Now, what about these?
popularity, I mean
It's I I don't I i'm pretty sure this is at least 80
No, no, no, no
I disagree
I'd say it's like I'd say it's like
82 percent or like let's say 85 percent
I mean, you know why I know this because when I opened up the hatsuit of miku across game
Um, there were like a dozen people that just said cringe
And they were mad at me
so I mean it's
It's like 90
Do a hundred strength. No, no a hundred strength
for the attitude up
And this is too strong 75 and everything except for popularity
Trying to be 99
No, I want it to be a challenge. We'll do 78 percent and then
72 there we go. That's better. That's better
Stop nerfing her
Hey, we're fine. I gotta fix the rest of this
This is blue too, right? I think this one's more accurate
This one it's like this one
Yeah
Is it like that
That's kind of like that
Let's go, let's go, let's go
It's like
Is that accurate?
I think so
Whatever. So now how is this?
Nat sunamiku
It's just hat sunamiku
Covered in tattoos
This is a bunch of tattoos. Oh, you need the headphones, right?
Okay
All right, I think that's good enough but this still is bob orson's stuff
Shit, hold on
It still wants us to be bob orson
Uh, whatever this time
Um, okay
Okay
All right. That's good
Heal man. Okay. Wait, I can change the promotion. Should I should I change promotion?
I'm gonna change promotion. Let's go. How about let's go right in the big leagues all american wrestling
All right. I think we're good to go. I think so
I I won in the biggest one because that's where all the look look at the stats
If nat sunamiku stats are gonna be this good then i'm gonna be in in the big leagues. All right, you can copy and paste
Wait, so does that mean?
Why am I still fighting gil?
Okay, 21
This guy I don't work for him anymore. All right, let's go. There's no match right now. Oh, that's right
There is a match right now a new phone. I gotta get out of here
Yeah, oh really give me that shovel back. You're about to hit me with it. Go find your own shovel digging over here
Go find your own shovel
What holy shit that train went by fast
If you want my world title that bad you should beat me in the ring for it
You're gonna give me an opp give me an opportunity then
You both know that will never happen nat sunamiku. So drop it before I drop you
Yeah
Know what you have to say?
I've imagined literally five minutes
Oh, no
Me
Where did he go?
I'm okay
It's actually pretty bad
Get away from me. I'm trying to go to the curtain. I mean I blew everything. I've got all day for
I got all day for
I missed my concert
This is actually very bad
How did I get hit by the train?
It ran over my shin
It's all right. I'll come back to it tomorrow. I'll be fine. Thanks. It's such a cartoon sound effect
Now am I hurt
Bird boy
Okay
Eugene is glad that I left wrestling revolution
Glad that I left
Sad that I left
Disappointed that I have joined here
Glad that I left
Sad that I'm now in this one
I'm good
Okay
singles match versus gruesome Sharon
I'm just going for it
who might
Gruesome Sharon
Damn it. I missed
Not by very much
Two middle fingers things been spiraling out of control here at all american wrestling. Well
Not tonight
I'm restoring order
All right, let's do it
Nice reversal. Oh my god. Miku is so much better than that
Like a hundred times better
Even injured I got hit by a train last night and i'm doing better let go
You okay? Can you stop?
God
I keep losing focus
Again, we're still every move is getting reversed
another reversal
I can't do a move
Oh, I don't submit
I'm just handing
Her my head
You it's because you have pre-baked the nat rng. That's actually true
I look like shit right now. I'm going to the top row still standing unbelievable
All right
Let's go put them up
Here we go. Shit was right my head
I feel like i'm gonna sneeze
Here i'll give you a thousand dollars if you can tell me what uh, what rng is what's an acronym for random number generator
Thanks for the money
Zero health. I gotta get the ground game up better. Yeah, it's all about the ground game
I'll just get every move reversed every single one
Uh, i'm okay filling it
That's it. There's no getting out of this
Oh, I actually kicked out
Starting to feel the crowd a little bit here
She's feeling the pressure
too far
Shit, what's the fucking reversal?
That's a big deal
We're good. I'm good. Get off reverse it
Oh
No
My neck
It's all right. It's all right. We weren't prepared for it. It's all right
It was just a regular match. That was a good fight
Take her to the subway
I can't fuck around the subway because i'm the one that
What's up? What a dick what an actual dick
We're both so fucked up
Bob is literally hiding right here
He's waiting for me to go across the threshold here. Yeah, fuck you bob
Ah
Oh my goodness lot of popularity what an asshole
Bob just killed miku. I think i'm still fine
Hey natsune miku. I popped for that counter you did into a closed guard
I think you could teach me how you pulled it. What is this person talking about?
Who is this?
I guess I could teach you my one of my moves
Sure, I don't even know who this is. Thanks for sharing your knowledge
I hope I can return the favor sometime
Okay
Your buddy phil grave suggested that you might like to join us at federation online
You're not exactly a priority for us right now, but we consider bringing you in with this deal
Thousand dollars
That's fucking crazy
200,000 dollars
I don't have
I don't have a salary. They're just gonna give me 200 grand
What do you mean? No salary zero dollars a week. You gave me two hundred thousand dollars
How is that? Oh, um
That's fucking amazing
Zero dollars, but I get 200,000 right now
210k
It's for a year in what world is over?
200,000 dollars not an unbelievable income
I was gonna make sure I don't take it from here and lose it on the way back to the hotel room
This is such a weird no creative control
Wait a minute. So
They might just make me stop being me cook
Tomorrow which is kind of funny and I think I want to see what they want me to do
Oh, this is two hundred thousand dollars. Are you kidding me? I'm taking it
I'm glad you could read our turns. Welcome to federation online. That's the most money i've ever seen in this game ever
I've never seen that money
What do you think of the new hairstyle our stylist suggested for you? I haven't got up from the chair yet
Uh, yeah, I think it looks great
Okay
Thanks
No creative control, but when you put the creative control into a moron's hands, who cares?
Are you fell for the no creative control clause?
You're as stupid as you look
I have guys honestly look at the top right corner
Look in the top right corner. I i have played this game
How many how many times have I screened this game 10 15 times maybe with the course for a couple of years
We've never seen a number like that before over two hundred twenty five thousand
Never happened. It's been like 30
Max
Sell up now quit with that money. This is so much money. All right, so let's do it tag team at 20
What do I have a hammer?
How am I losing health for?
Wait, do you this was this person to talk shit, right?
I can't fuck around. I have a match
I don't think you can do that for real, right? That's illegal
I gotta go to my match
I
I don't know why I did that. I just
I don't know. I don't know. I just didn't know what was possible. I'm not I didn't miss the show
I don't know what to say
That was fucked up
Wait, that's not a tombstone for the guy that I just killed
I'm like waited a long time for this moment and I can't wait to set about achieving my goals
Felix thinks he's the future of federation online. Perhaps i'll have to challenge for the intercontinental title
Maybe i'll form my own team and give stunner stew and roadhog something to worry about
As long as it's only a matter of time before I cross paths with comic connie for that woman's title
But of course my ultimate aim to win the universal title
You fucking piece of shit
Somebody's getting their ass kicked and now and you're gonna call you gotta call in wait, is it for me or you so far?
We're good. It's fine. How did that miss?
You threw the mic at me and you ruined everything of course
All that would have been insane
She went through
I'm gonna tag in now bill
Who's bill?
Bill come here bill put the money down and tag in
I don't know what you're doing. All right, this guy's just doing his own thing. That's fine
tag in
That was I just blasted
Bill tag in
tag in
You're being crazy. You're being ridiculous. Stop
Just stop and tag in you're being ridiculous. Go behind the police
I don't want to fight somebody with full health. Give me that fucking money. By the way, it's mine
Again tag in
Thank you. Jesus
All right. Good luck
You really just don't know what you're doing
Do something. Why are they doing this?
Yeah, yeah, i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm going
Give me that
Oh
He got sick of my shit so bad. All right. Nirvana is not doing well
Oops, i'm sorry
i'm dazed
Okay, I don't know whose team these two are on but whatever. All right, come over here
All right, tag me in i'm ready
Tag me in
Nice. There we go. All right
Good good good good
nice job
Get that tap
This game is just so
So goofy
It's just a goofy game
it's
Did I was this my game of the year two years ago? I don't remember
It was up there. Wasn't it?
Back in 2021, right? How did you do that? How did you do that?
He killed somebody I didn't kill anybody actually it didn't say anything
There was no oh, hey, by the way, this guy's dead
I'm I just i'm i'm somebody on helping me and I just can't get them off
God
This is no way he isn't dead
I'm bringing the ladder in this is illegal
If I extended the body a little it would be fine
You tagged me in and he went over to fight the other guys over there
Pin would do it right here
Let's give me it
Tap tap tap tap tap
tap
You just gotta come out here and
This is my time
My time to shine right now. I'm not even legal
Come on
This is the time to shine is right now
You ain't getting up from that
No counter owed
That could be the end
Perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect. Where am I?
Stop, we both can't be up at the same time you moron
You you've blown it so bad that I don't even know what to do now I don't know what to do you blow it so bad
Shit
All right, he's back. He's back. He's legal
I don't know why she's not getting in the ring. All right, just need a pin and we're good
Although I don't know where I am right now
It's a great question
I have no idea where I am
I can't get in the ring
All right, go for a pin or a submission move or anything
This is it
All right, go with pin
Pin
Sorry, I got it. I think you're getting away
You're not getting out of here
Bell hasn't even rung yet
There's no way that you get up from that
Go for the pin or tag me in so I can pin
Go for a pin
You're just letting her get strength
His ai brain wants to go on the top rope so bad
Look at come tag me in please
Tag me in. Thank you. All right, let's end this
We lose this build
Throw you in the train track
Uh-oh, oh it's over. No way. It's over. How is it? I don't know how you still look up
Bill I swear
big move
How are you still?
Doing this
tap
It's only one a minute
just tap
Come here
Oh my god, give me a break
Oh, there's the tap. There it is. Finally finally have a tap
It's just a back and forth to who can break the other person's spine first
They're using furniture to block me now. Yeah, like that's gonna help. He only gave me like two seconds left
Okay
Skill, how how does the skill rise? Look at all this money, by the way, that guy's not dead
Did you see anything about that guy? That guy's not dead. That guy's alive. I need a referee tonight
Yeah, sure. There was nothing left from the body
I don't know about that
Ultra bowl versus these two. I'm gonna call it very very clean
Lady
Make it a little harder. What do you think?
Make it a little harder
Wait, I have to call wait
So if I bring a weapon in here
It's not illegal because i'm doing it, right?
so therefore I could
Drop this in the ring
And then one of them is going to pick it up and i'll throw them out of the game
It's one of these people am I supposed to be
Am I rooting for either one of these?
I just want everyone equally hurt
This guy
Interfered for one second
It was one second too long
Dude, I am kicking the shit out of this guy. This guy stands absolutely no chance
What happened?
Lady here. All right. Hopefully you learned your lesson
You come right back into the ring you stupid asshole
Oh somebody's out of the ring
Get out of here
Look at this guy regenting health
What is there a gun in the ring?
He brought a gun in here
The first person of this
He was like waving at me. Why was he waving at me?
Why?
He's like, oh, hey
I missed him twice
Where is he?
He keeps going into the ring. This is not even what is he doing?
He keeps interfering over and over again
Get out of here. Stop interfering stay out
He's gonna understand what's happening
What's happening? I don't know. I feel like this is like most pov
Don't you feel like
I feel like i'm like a rodent running around
Is this motherfucker right here?
Is this a fan?
Dude a fan got in
Why is he holding the bell?
Is anybody gonna win the match?
All right. Okay
All right
Back to it
Okay
Now cut it out. I don't want to see you back up here again
If I see you back up here again, you and I are gonna exchange words
I won't stop
He won't stop
This guy is a machine
He still hasn't gotten up yet
Damn it. Oh are you tapping? We got a winner
What are you doing
I'm still attacking him somehow. How am I still attacking him?
That was actually fucking insane that guy hit his head on the metal stairs
At least like at least 20 times. Oh my god. That's so fucking funny. He just kept like
He just kept falling back and smashing the ground of his head
Okay time to go to bed. All right bedtime. Geez
I didn't realize that they actually live they got run off a full speed twice by the subway train. What was that person's name?
Is this guy here?
How long has he been lying there?
It's been it's been four weeks
Was found unconscious in the subway
He was supposed to ref the match that I just repped no way
No way, that's so funny
Oh that shaky cam pov of that guy just fucking getting just the shit beat out of him
Need to finish the job
Oh, oh get up. Get up. Get up. I'm late. Oh, that was so stupid. This is the wrong way
Yep, I may be the universe champion, but we're all responsible for it. Yep. So this is the guy to beat ripper race
Forget who did that?
My mind first first
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on
Why do we perform in front of the same gormless crowd every week?
I would only give the fans a great show, but this is one place. I can't wait to leave
Let me handle the entertainment natsunamiku. These fans will go home happy after they see me kick your ass
Is this tornado tag?
Dad's tornado tag
And what's with the where's waldo guy in the back?
Found him. Oh, this is illegal. Whoops. How do I already have this half health gone out?
I have a gun in my hand. I'm reversing every grapple I do
Okay, I think this guy's on my side
Reverse another grapple again
How do you level up skill appreciate it? We're gonna get a submission right here
He's got a special move
All right, pin him pin him pin him. I'll keep this guy busy
Go for a pin. You can't just cartwheel into somebody
That was pretty sick. Can I get the cover?
Come on
Stop catching everything I do
Hmm
Another reversal
I gotta get my skill up
My skill is probably low because that's how I think I could get reversed on this character
another reversal
The skill issue that's what i'm saying
I put miku in this league. They all have like 80 plus skill
And I was trying to be
Don't look don't do that
Stop stop him from doing this
All right, he lost his bed. That's fine
Oh good good good good good good
Again another I grabbed him. That's like honestly, this is crazy
That's crazy. I think like eight out of ten moves i've done to this guy. He's reversing
I'm going to get a weapon
He reversed it again. All right, i'm done with this guy. I'm done with this guy. That's that's nine out of ten reversals
You know what?
Get out of here. Fuck you
Finally, I did a move to him
All right, protect me so I can do his submission on
This is fuck
Oh, no, no, no, no, no get up get up get up. Yeah, that's good. No, that's bad
They keep reversing each other what is with this reversal shit
Get out of the way
Shit
I can barely walk
Thank god for this random guy in the suit otherwise we would have lost a long time ago
Who is it?
He's just breaking this guy's leg
uh
I don't really give a shit about that guy. So let me just rest
I don't care about that guy
He's like yoga who cares?
legs
Yeah, this guy's not even in the match and he's just still fucking around
Is anybody else?
Anybody else confused to why this is taking so long?
Why has nobody tapped?
stop
That was a quadruple reversal
Dumbass
We're going the distance again on one of these fucking things I swear to god
I swear to god
Just do somebody tap. I don't even care. It's me at this point. I seriously don't care
It's only 35 seconds
He missed
dude
This is outrageous
If we went the distance again, I don't I don't understand
I am not leaving until somebody taps out
Get over here
Reverse andy motherfucker
He's not done
tap
Got it
Good
Now let's leave
It's always right after the bell too every time
You're like kind of funny, but you're annoying
Okay, there's agility
I have more skill than this guy and it still was a problem
I gotta do some training. I'm training skills
I can't believe I have two hundred and twenty five thousand dollars. All right. Good night's sleep
No messing around
Sorry, we didn't win that match. We'll do better next time
I mean you did great
It was a 3v2. We still couldn't do it somehow. Don't ask me why
You should have been fine
Okay, slow down oh shit i'm gonna die
Zero hp need to go to the hotel
Wait, can I can just eat snacks, right?
Let me eat a bunch of snacks
Okay, how do you actually use this?
There we go
This is my food get out of here
This is my food. I bought it
All right. We're good. All right
Do I have anything going on? I feel like I've had a match every single day every single week every single day
This bit and I haven't been one week where I haven't had a match
I made more money than that
Progen forces feud with natsume miku appears to have lost momentum and is no longer over with the fans
They don't like it anymore. They think it's stupid
I'm at zero health. I can't fight right now
I cannot do a match right now
How am I supposed to do this? It's the random beer you found and drank in the subway
Can I like do anything else?
I'm scarred for life because of you now. I won't rest until you share my pain
This is the guy that got hit by the train
What did he just do to me?
You're not getting away with that. You're not getting away with that
You're not getting away with that. Get over here
Stop talking to me. I'm busy. I'm doing something
Oh you do walk through that door. How much time do I have? I have an hour to eat as much food as I can
Eat eat eat eat. I have to eat as much food as I can in an hour. Thank you. I appreciate it
These are beers. I don't want a beer
Move you gotta go. No, I don't. I'm not
Oh, what's that? You want my fucking finishing move dick? Give me water. Give me water
All right. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm good. I'm good
I'm good. I'm good
Okay, at least I have maybe some help. It's kind of not fair. I'm sick today
What kind of name is Harry Harris? Were you born with that or did you choose it?
Do you think I got where I am today with a name like that? Give yourself a chance
That looked really bad
I don't suppose it matters what your name is anyways. It's going to be history
You're right. My name is going down in history as the guy that ended the career of Natsune Miku
Nice job ref
Keep it clean. I gotta play very very cautiously
Dump him over the edge
This guy out of here
test of strength
Okay, it's gonna go a lot worse
Never mind pretty bad now
rope break, right
I'm sick too. I'm probably taking more damage because I'm sick
Couldn't lift him
Stop grappling dude when I punch they just catch my hands and kill me
I just punched me grab my arm and midair and been and broke my neck. I'm in a bad place here
Tag out. I don't think it's a tag. I think he just came to the ring with me
You know, it also doesn't help that both the characters I played with today are five feet tall
All right, relax relax relax
God that dodge
Yeah, this guy has to be six five he's six six
Move the control stick in the direction of the move opposite direction to reverse
I think i'm doing that
Like you fight this right like i'm holding in the other direction
Because if you hold it when you're doing a submission if you hold it the other way you'll like pull it back
back out I think I just lost
No, the biggest issue is
When I throw a punch
It goes like here to their face and when they throw a punch it goes over my head and around my ears
Because there's just so much bigger than me
I don't think it's not I don't think it's a tag, right?
There's no way I can beat this
Just get away from me for five seconds
I can't punch him
Oh my god
That's pretty cool
All right, give me the momentum back
Don't not in the middle of the ring, please
Harry harris
This character is so weak, too
I had I woke up this morning. I was sick. I still have to do the match
I have like t-rex level reach in front of me
Did you see that? Did you see that punch?
We both were in the exact same far away from each other he punched me I missed him
Damn it
How am I still alive? I have no idea how I haven't he's put it away yet
He's been me like three times
You've got to be fucking hitting me. That's impossible
I'm just i'm just gonna i'm gonna go into the settings and just make her eight inches taller
I'm just gonna i'm gonna make her like six feet tall
What have you done? I'm angry now. He's got instantly reversed again
I don't even have time to press me, but
I
Fuck off. He's got he's got like an entire subway sandwich length of reach on me
Do you understand he's got two meatball subs attached to the end of his hands. It's not fair
What the fuck is he doing? He reversed it
Tell you run that tape back and you tell me what happened there. I just hear my head being crushed
You need something black and white
He's gonna revert watch i'm gonna grab him. I'm surprised he didn't reverse that too. You know what?
No, i'm not done. I'm not done with you. All right, just get out
Get up somebody help me up
Oh, okay
I love him. My eye suffered for that
Harry harris is now a face and he has the support of the fans
I'm gonna beat the shit out of this guy backstage
Let's go
Do a training arc
I really do need to train skill or something. All right back to it
I need to
No more fucking around. I need full health the next fight
I need 100% health
I swear if I wake up with diarrhea or something i'll be so pissed
No, no, no, stop it. I want to the doctor. Let's just get him
Iled on right now. All right, i'm gonna i'm going to the hospital. Uh, oh
Is he all right
Want to do an interview?
No, I said no messing around this is bad. How have they not found his dead body yet?
It's gonna have to wait until he's supposed to ref
Before they actually know go to the hospital. All right. Yeah. Yeah. All right. I don't know. I know where's it
It's like in a weird spot
it's next to the
Okay, it's like next to the gym
Down here, right? Okay. Heal me go confess at the church
Okay
Don crocket. No
Federico fisher was found dead in the street this morning. We started
Appealing for any information about the 36 year old's death
He literally killed him
The industry will come together this week to stage a special tribute in memory of federico fisher prior to the public show a private funeral
Will take place at 7 p.m
I'm gonna find a spot for you on the card just to take this opportunity to improve yourself and become more valuable to the company
Okay
um
We can't always blame rip race for the ratings. We all have to make the show worth watching. Oh, no. No
Wait, this is from the hospital to the cemetery. Okay
Does this go actually faster?
I'm here to challenge you to a match on the fourth week of august. Yeah, get out of my face
When's the funeral? I just realized what i'm doing right now
This is the equivalent of like I am showing up here like all my arms. We get fucked up, too
Yeah, it's like when you're in trouble with mom and dad
That's like but like but no i'm hurt, too
That's my seat get up. What do you mean? This is your seat. There's a wheelchair. No get out of here
No, I didn't want to give it no, that's mine did I say yes it's like wait a minute
Natsune, didn't you kill this guy?
Yeah, but I mean
Like yeah, we got in a big fight and like he broke my look at me
When is this funeral?
Put the head put the tombstone down
You're not come on. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I've ruined the funeral. Oh my god
I have to get out of here. Oh my god. Oh my god
What happened to me? What happened to me?
Is everything okay?
It's not still broken, right?
Oh
Yikes
To be fair. I'm gonna let's be very realistic and be very fair
He tripped over my wheelchair and smashed his head into it. Okay. He was all over my face
And tripped and hit and smashed it
So that was not even my fault
When is the funeral eating and drinking is good for an energy boost, but you'll make yourself sick
When's the funeral?
It's 7 a.m. Tomorrow. I missed it
It's tomorrow. You kind of ruined it dude. It's tomorrow. Oh, okay
I'll be back tomorrow. Did I just spend twenty two hundred dollars on the wheelchair? Is that what that is telling me or props?
Listen, that's it amiku. We're going to market a wait and we'd like you to promote it
If you could just mention the product during your next show, it could be worth twenty one hundred dollars
Oh, yeah
sure
I'll give you a wait to take to the ring. It'll be worth every penny to see you with it
Okay
This is against uh, harry harris
But did I did I miss I missed the funeral?
I ruined the funeral
Um, okay
Should I roam?
No, no roaming. No, look what I got. What do you think about this?
standard 20 kilogram 45 pound weight
Take a look
You all should be buying this. All right. These two were a huge problem last night
I just realized the music is very loud, but whatever
Is the game loud or are we good? How loud is the is the game been really loud? Are we good?
How's the audio are we all right? Is the audio been too too hard?
This weight changed my life
I don't know where i'd be without it and you don't have to be a federation online star like me to own a weight like this
For just a few dollars. You can pick one up of your own. I suggested you so before stocks run out
You're obviously sold out
But so has this arena and they paid to see me kick your ass
Come on
I tried
I don't care if it's illegal
Why can I swing what why can't I swing the
What's going on?
I got disqualified. Yeah, that's fine. I can still win. He just hit himself in the mouth
Term of violence isn't the answer. I mean, what do you what do you want to say?
I got disqualified for doing my product placement. I don't know what happened there
I climbed it and fell off. I need someone to get knocked outside so I can use my product
Oh, that's my friend. Well, this is wrong people wrong people. I'm sorry. That's my bad. Where's my weight?
We're on the ground I don't even know where's the weights right here somewhere there it is. All right now it's now it's a bad
Now it's a bad time for you to first person. Is he all right? What are you looking at?
Is that my guy? Yep tap what happens arm? Oh, no. No, I was like, what the hell did I do? That's one
two
Yes
Harry harris injured his back in that match. It'll be out for oh look at the glass strategic disqualification
That's kind of what happened picture. That's in amiku is upset that she was barely involved in that match
We're still number one give miku more screen time. Listen miku after what happened
I realized that none of this is worth dying for
Why don't we put all this behind us before somebody seriously gets hurt the world would be a better place without you in it
It's all right. I want to start at the title. Listen miku
I've been keeping an eye on your progress and I think some changes need to be made
You know that you've only won 43% of your matches so far this year actually really good
Get your win rate up to 48%
or i'll give you a spot to someone else just completely ignoring the
like sometimes over one to two hundred pound difference the two foot long subway sandwiches for arms and
What are you talking about? 43% is fucking unbelievable being in like five to ten weight classes lower than what I should be
All right, there's a ten man team
Where 10 v 10? What does that mean?
10 man team
This is gonna be a nightmare
Just break something. All right. Thank you free time. See you later. Remember you're on a mission to increase your win rate
I'll get it right now. I'll get it right now. All right, where do I want to go in a little bit time?
I have I could go to the toilet. I could go to the gym. Let me go to the gym
This is 10 man. Should I train do I need strength or should I just do maybe agility? This is agility, right?
That's 75 give me one more 76. There we go. All right. All right enough now i'm gonna eat some food. Okay now
Um, let's get out of here get some food. It's just water hear him at the funeral
That guy's been dead for three weeks. The funeral was like three weeks ago. I did not just do that
Did I what did I do to that guy? That guy is really hurt and I didn't do anything
I didn't do anything. You've got to be kidding me right when I was preparing for this shit
Do I have his head? Thank you. Now. Let me just eat something for a second
Okay, that's fine. That's cool. Thanks for the hug, but I've got to go. Is that good enough? That's good enough
All right, go go go go go get up
All right
I don't want to be in first person for this in no way. How are we gonna do somebody to get pinned for this?
This is impossible. This is not
possible to
Who is who? I don't know. I think it's just every single person versus themselves or
It's a how many people are in here it's 10. It's 20 people
It's a 10 man
There are more than 10 people here though
I'm just gonna hang out up here
We can actually do first person for this
What is going on?
My reach sucks
Have you guys ever heard of the movie hardcore henry?
This is a hardcore henry. This is the movie. This is the only thing you see in the whole movie
This is vr. It just is
I don't know where I am. I all right. I'm just gonna watch
Fuck this
We're watching from here
Mike that's me getting counted out
This is blood
Whose blood is this?
Oh
This is just a dream fight
Somebody said dude, can you please stop playing the game with a steering wheel? That was fucking fantastic
What a great comment
Everybody in this ring is gonna get hurt
There's no winner. There will be no victor
It's only going to be pain for everyone. No everyone's gonna get hurt
I can't wait to see the i'm telling you right now. I ain't leaving it till at least seven people are fucking in the hospital
Not leaving it till that happens
I went you broke the ladder you idiots
I can't put the ladder back together again
We're gonna all right place your bets. How many injuries do we see?
Before the match actually ends how many at the end of the match cards are we gonna see?
I'm gonna say three
Do I even care if I get disqualified by the way?
Do I actually care?
I mean do I care about this?
My win rate. That's right. You're right
All right. I'm just gonna litter things all over the ring so everyone can hit their head like hit their head on it and stuff
It's only five minutes remaining
A random pin could actually just win it like this
Don't
Oh my god, you actually won
Huge jazz won't always be the predictor. What happened?
Was what why does it say his team won?
Was huge ass even here? Oh he was
Somebody interfered
Ain't oh, but ain't ain't no one getting by
You gotta pay me 50 bucks to get by
You fucking idiot
You can climb that
I didn't know you could climb this
Oh, whatever. It wasn't enough time for anybody to get injured
Nirvana required stitches after recurring some facial damage in that match and will be nursing the wounded till next week
Okay
That was
I remember that actually
That was the
first person chair
It was one injury
Okay
Donor stews profile suffered
I didn't i'm fine
Disappointed
No, just one
All right, we're still in second. This game is insane
I still I feel like I
Feel like half the stuff I saw today
Is is already in the long-term memory which is crazy because it happened four hours ago. All right, let me heal
Would you be willing to sell that water bottle for six dollars the one that I just threw on the ground?
Yeah, it smashed into a million pieces. This water bottle will be worth every penny. I hope it is
Yeah, congratulations. There it is. It's on the ground
I don't know. I'm just trying to cause mayhem. All right, stop causing mayhem. Get out. I want that tombstone
That's the injury doing okay
Okay, harry harris has recovered from his injury. So I was not on the winning team was I okay singles versus joanna fight
All right 18
Get off of me phil
What did I puke?
I puked the bed and rolled out of bed like that was actually uncalled for and now i'm already hurt for this match
I didn't do anything. You know what? Fuck you phil. You just ruined everything you blew it big time
Yeah, now they're gonna be fucking he came in and saw yeah
I was like in bed and he just attacked me in bed and I shit and pissed the bed and now i'm hurt
Before I have to I have to get my win rate up
Please get away from me. I just
He's blocking. No, i'm done with you phil. Forget it
Now it seems to be an altercation backstage between uh phil graves and natsumiku
apparently this morning natsumiku pissed shit and puked the bed
And uh phil did not like that very much
Uh causing a little bit of a stir
Weird because they're tag team partners
Uh, oh
Is he can't be dead
Uh, oh, who's this?
You didn't see shit
I missed my match
I'm going to bed
You cannot fault me for that. I was
Attacked because for no, I don't know for no reason
There was no reason phil graves was found unconscious in the hotel and we're resting up in the hospital for the next four weeks
Okay, come on
I have to win this match. I have to win this match
All right, it's over
So we need food. I need to eat something. I got a little bit of time. I need food
I'm not gonna start anything with anybody. I have to win this match. I just no beer just water and apples
That's all I want. He's not talking to me. Thank you. Yes, it looks a little low find some to eat or drink
All right. Listen, I've had that's enough. There's no time for a nap, by the way
Why did that happen
Was it because I was I was spamming it or if you pissed yourself
Why don't you do it in the you know what? Well, you know what phil? You know what phil fuck off
You're going into the fire
You're more popular than me miku. I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to tell you. Oh, wow. You peed your pants
You can't take it back. You can't take it back phil. There's no taking it back now
So put away wait, wait, can somebody explain to me what happened
What why did the vending machine do that?
Are they gonna are they gonna hold on a minute? Are they gonna hold a memorial?
For miku, that's the longest career ever. Are they gonna hold the memorial? Where was that federation, right?
Oh, no, okay
Well, there's effing gilette. Oh, yeah heck. I like god of natural causes
Nice job gil gil with the championship here. He used it too much while it was damaged. When was it? How was it damaged?
I'm playing as walti
All right, so i've had enough I know how to play. Why do you laugh like that? I mean like this
An orange for free you can keep forgetting that you if you eat while you're full i'm so whatever i'm so
Stupid he's a sesame street character. So wait a minute
Why is he stuck here? It's not happening. You're welcome. How did I do that before?
Didn't happen another stream. I'm pretty sure it's it's an intended mechanic
But wouldn't isn't it already broken? I'm just i'm gonna see how it works
Okay, so that it just exploded
It must just be random like while you're using it if you use it too much
Let's drop a bunch of like eat on the ground
All right. Somebody said we want power. I'll give you power. Stop playing old shitty wrestlers. We want power
Okay
I'll give it to you. I'll give it to you. I love them already. Did you shit your pants? I think this guy shit his pants
Look out everybody. It's walti the master of the death valley driver
You seriously think that a medic move like that will work against a warrior like me?
Should be worried because when I hit the death valley driver this match is over
You're in deep shit. The match will be over when I hit you with my tombstone. Your entire career will be over
Let's see about that
No
Eat that this is a pretty good match so far
Test of strength good reversal. What's that? That's sting. It's a good first match. It should be a victory here
Oh fuck off. What's this? I don't know what walti special move is
We'll find out
Maybe not. Okay, whatever. All right. What's the special move? Let's hit it build the momentum if you talk about the way you build momentum
Ready death valley driver
They literally said it in the beginning. This is so rude
All right, this sucks. Where's miku miku? Um, i'm okay
You didn't even get hit by that. Wait, what she just blocked it for you. Wait, were you proposing that you help me?
Oh, whatever. You totally dripped down. I think looks pretty good. Stop doing old shitty wrestlers
Yeah, they're always like a squirrely guy
I don't think i've ever done anything normal. It's always a squirrely weirdo or a huge
Like seven eight foot tall
700 pounds there's never been a normal person
Okay. Uh-oh
Singles match. I can't I can't I just can't see where i'm going. I can't see where i'm going
You prescribe me some steroids
Okay, thanks for the steroids look at all this food that's still here go work out
Are you saying that because i'm old? Oh nice. That's all guys. We stayed again. Uh, I need a dumbbell. Here we go
76 i'm on steroids. I need to eat all that food on the ground like an hour. I'll be all right
Sell that burger for five dollars. Thanks for the money
All right. We're good. It's time to fight. Why'd you give him a half-eaten burger? I gave him nothing
Can we get an update on your weird pee?
Oh, you mean when I pissed on a water test strip and it said there was a shit load of iron in it
I didn't really follow up with it. How did that miss? You gotta be kidding me
That was perfect
I think you're a great wrestler greg mcmahon, but you're not even a wrestler at all
You're a glorified stunt man who can only win matches by swinging weapons and smashing through furniture
When I step into this ring it becomes a war zone. I guess that's too much for you to handle
Matches too much for you to handle because you're not civilized enough to play by my rules
It was a weird exchange, but whatever
He's kind of kicking my ass
Damn it
That move it just did 10 to 15 damage
stupid
How are you doing all this? Oh shit, it's gonna be over really quickly
I'm way out of my league here. Get off. It's got i'm way out of my league. I'm so out of my league
I can't even get up my head
He
Demolished me that was not even a contest. I got so badly beat. That was unbelievable
Bring him to the subway. I don't think we're gonna be able to see him on the subway. Forget about the subway
I need some I need some appointment
I think I have a few cuts
No new pin tweet liar
right look
76 strength 89 skill 86 agility. What is he doing here? Why is he in wrestling revolution?
This guy is way way too good to be in this league. That was ridiculous
Oh, yeah, somebody's people asking what the hell are you talking about?
So I peed on a water test strip and it said I had a bunch of lead in my piss
And I just never followed up with it
But I i'm glad greg mcmahon to teach you a lesson. You don't belong at wrestling revolution of walti
All right
I love people asking what the hell I mean
All right. So
I got water test strips to test the water to see what's in it. Like, okay
Just to see how it's doing and I was like, you know, I just for no reason
I just thought it was like kind of funny. I just I just for no reason
I wasn't like, oh i'm gonna do this. I just I I pissed on one just to see like what my piss looked like
Like what my ph and everything was because it's designed for water. It's not designed for anything else
I was like, that's kind of funny
And the only reason why i'm saying that is because they put
A hundred of these strips into one container and guess what you only need to use it once
So it's like, oh look water test strips, you know buy here's some water test strips
Why am I ever gonna need more than three of these? That's enough water test strips for 40 50 years
I was like, you know, whatever i'm just gonna pee on one. You explained that really badly
I mean, they're not designed for pee
Gil feels great today and is in perfect health. Why would you pee on one? I don't know
I put in my mind. I was like, why not? No, I didn't pee on all of them
You guys are making it sound like I took one out tested my water
And then just laid them all on the ground and pissed all over them
No
I peed on one. I didn't pee on all of them. That would be so wasteful and stupid
All right. So now let's go
It would have been way funnier if you did. I wasn't even trying to be funny
There was nobody that I was making this joke for I just felt like doing it because I just I just feel like doing this
And it's just completely just something completely benign. It's not it's just like you're just doing it because you feel like it
That's impulsive
It's really not okay
It's a it is impulsive but it's not oh my god that what impulsive behavior that's wrong what you did
It's I peed on a fucking test strip. I peed on a water test strip. Who cares? This is
It's not doing anything negative. There's nothing wrong. Why is that lead in your pee? There isn't I
It's not designed for pee. So it's gonna come up wrong
What are you somebody always does this shit? I swear to god. I'm sorry
Stop fighting me leon. We're not you and I have friends get away
Get away from me. Where's my guitar? There it is. That's what we're gonna do
We're gonna rock out when we get around to carton. That's what's gonna happen
This guy's glow in the dark
Why is this guy glow in the dark
Walty i'm sure you think you'll win this match and I certainly know that I can
Why don't you put your money where your mouth is and bet it on it?
2190 says I kick your ass
Okay
That was a lot of damage. Just do that over and over again. This is free money. You can't okay
There's a you can't hold it. You can't hold it forever. I thought you could what's wrong is this guy?
I actually really want that money. Come on. Walty sucks
Get her to kill walty
Really? Because walty's the only one that's been able to do wrestling moves in the last like probably three and a half hours
How is this not a rope break? What do you mean?
Walty is based what i'm saying good reversal. That's just I got my special death valley driver
I just pretended to be excited. I'm sorry
That was like me pretending to be excited great
That's made almost 2,200 bucks resident sleeper walty gaming. That was two clean wins in a row
This song sucks
It's so annoying
It's just
Uh-huh. Okay
Walty's not bad. Why does everybody hate walty so much?
But the one just makes you another target walty don't fucking threaten me. There's a lot of people here
That was I was playing with fire there. Why do I feel like if I just sit right here you can see through the glasses
What's a good one to do here? Probably? Yeah
you fucking idiot
They're really they're really dumb. They're just I just gonna stand on the other side. That's it
I almost just died. I just gonna stand on the other side do third person is watch he's just
Third person he's taunting me. I'm just like come and get me. I'm just annoying
Scary
Jesus. All right. I gotta be careful
I thought it was stop. I thought the train was coming to a stop. I'm actually okay
All right
Okay, the train I thought the train was stopping and I could get across
I think i'm dead
What the fuck he's 326 pounds
I'm, all right. I'm okay
I just was unconscious
No, I need to see this through this guy that's I got this guy's one of the reasons why I feel like shit right now
You can I need to take a pay cut. I don't want to take a pay cut
No, fuck all of you
What's that for a pay cut?
No shit, I want this
I need to get back up. I need to get back up. Stop telling me to eat food and leave me alone
Uh-huh
Damn favorite adam. Oh my god. Look how fast I am. What do you guys say? I'm so fast
This is so fast. You'll never catch me. Do you go faster in the chair?
You actually don't go faster. I feel like I could move faster though, couldn't I?
I promise i'm not trying to hit anybody bring miku back. Miku's not coming back. I'm sorry
All right, we're good i'm obsessed with the subway right now
Ah
All right. I gotta stop doing this. I gotta stop doing this. I gotta stop doing this. I gotta stop doing this
I gotta stop doing this. I have to stop doing this. I have to get the fuck out of here. I have to stop
I have to i'm i'm i'm gonna leave this is incredibly uncalled for
That's just it's just uncalled for there's no reason to do what i'm doing
All right. I didn't even do that to that guy, but I guess i'll grind on him. This is so weird
I can't think I might be done
He's so fast. He's so strong. This is gonna be unbearable
Relay, I know you're watching backstage, which is the safest place for you to be this guy
I was just running over backstage the guy that had no health i'll get my hands on you one day
And this is just a preview of what's gonna happen. Do you want strength?
You wanted strength
You got it
This guy is an x-men
He's only except if you have 99 in every stat i'm pissed right now
Oh
Why is he bringing the chair over here?
Okay, get a tap out you think you can test of strength, this is a really dumb idea
What do you think you're doing?
Yeah, excuse me
Get a pen bob knows not to get involved. That's so funny. I can't believe he hasn't tapped. It's actually pretty crazy
All right, that's it. Yeah, you don't understand
He's an x-man
I don't even care. I can't even get hurt
Nothing can hurt me. I'm a superhuman
I'm a heel. Oh, no put it in reverse. All right, maybe like 10 more minutes and then i'm gonna call it for today
He's running from me and talking well come back and talk to me then don't just run back to the subway
All right. I want i'm curious just how superhuman this character is we're gonna do a test you ran right into me
It was just dumb what he did. I don't think you want to mess with me right now. This is a big mistake. I'm just saying
I mean, this is a huge mistake. Why would you even say anything?
Why would you try to attack me?
He ran behind me and ran into my shit and then said hey watch where you're going
And then now he wants to fight me
Where are you going smashing an announcer's desk?
He's fine
He really is an avenger
He's an avenger. He's actually an avenger. He says like the hulk. He can't get killed
He's super strong
He's an affair. I just did bat chest
Come on. I can take one more of those
Yeah, right in the belly right here. Let's see it
What am I drinking blood?
He's all right
He's fine
How many is it gonna take to put me in the hospital? It's never happening. It's never gonna happen
Hulk number one
Okay, you want to check it out? You want to check this out down here? Okay, come here for a second
I want to show you something
He can't lift me
Am I okay what's wrong with me
Let that be the end of it. I hope you learned your lesson
Why am I asleep? He's asleep. Oh no
Does the train come on this side?
He's he's sleeping again. I'm done. I'm done
I'm done playing wrestling empire. It's been fun. I don't think I can die. I don't think I can die
What's wrong with me, um, it's uh, I'm not controlling the guy
Oh, that's all that's all just a little bit uncomfortable sleep. I don't think this guy can die
Tanked four trains
Can I just not die I lost control
You're literally the hulk. I'm invincible. I can't die. I'm invincible. I actually actually invincible
It's so many times, dude
I can't get up, but I can't die
Don't tell me that's it
I had one match only
The whole time
Oh, man, I'm super powered. I'm a superhero. Wow. This is crazy
man
Might as well just run up with a train 15 times
That's how you go. What the hell are you doing?
He won a hundred percent of the matches
That took a lot though that took a lot
Oh, what a mess. That's so funny
100 win rate
Yeah, 99 in every stat means you can get hit by the train
in consecutive days
About 10 times in a row. That's unbelievable. All right, I think i'm gonna call it for today
That was funny. This game is always funny
This game is always just ridiculous wrestling empire glad to go back to it train got us all I think right
All right. I will see you guys. What's today? Let's do
Uh, let's do friday saturday this weekend. I think there's a bunch of stuff we can play
So I want to give you guys a little insight as to what's going to be happening in 2023
I want to do more streams. We're just chilling out playing a game like I told you this last um
Late last year
But I want to bring back more just hangout streams where we just play games. I'm gonna do more of those this year
It's oh fuck it's 2023. Yeah, it is
No, not not omega gaming weekends, but just like if I just feel like playing something i'm just gonna play it then that's it
But yeah, that's wrestling empire. That's the stream good to be back
I will see you guys in a couple days on friday
Thanks for watching as always
Yeah streams will be we'll we'll stay in this early period too something that like the noon to two
You know what? I figured out
Notice how I was perfectly on time today. I got a new 2023 strategy. You ready for this?
so
The sus is always for this 2023. I'm gonna try it
Sus is always going to be set
At least an hour or two later than I actually really want to be live
So what's going to end up happening is sus will be set for like two or three o'clock pacific sometimes, right?
And here's the strat
Just whenever i'm ready, let's go
And i'll just make sure that i'm always ready before the set time and i'll make sure it's always an hour or two
later than I want to be
Lying to us
Because then it doesn't matter. I will always be on time because if it if it takes until two
Which it shouldn't but if it does i'm here you're delaying without the shame. That's right delaying without the shame
Especially when our clocks are so late
Me and holly were sitting around just laughing at what let's think let's talk about this really quickly
At what point of your clocks being slow or fast is your entire life fucked up?
Imagine operating it forward after 20 minutes
Everything is messed up. Nothing is correct. Yeah, even 15 minutes
So the fact that this dude is just sitting here operating on a 46 minute wrong clock
How how is it possible and then they maybe they had something read up that was super super meaningful
And oh guys 2023 here's to this here's to this here's and you missed it and you fucked up and you just pissed
Like fuck this holiday. I don't even care scrap the draft that I had i'm talking about me
I don't know. I thought it was funny. Why'd you write that? I don't know dude. Why did I pee on a why did I pee on a
Water test. I don't know. I thought it was funny. Yeah, I talked about the tweet from new new years and I was 46 minutes late
Anyways, i'll see you guys on friday
Uh, I don't know what we're gonna do. We'll do whatever we'll do whatever we want
There's a lot of games that have come out over the last month or two that I haven't played
Uh, so we'll get more of these more game streams
And i'll see you later. See you friday. Thanks for watching
Take care of yourself drop that and go like this
Hey
Uh, here come the credits there are 55 pages of credits i've been away. Oh my god. Thanks for the subs though guys
That is a lot appreciate it. Oh, I need my um music
You can't hear it now you can
What about your pin tweet? I'll figure it out
Hey, i'm serious. By the way, there's actually an option to disable the white flashes in the great ace attorney chronicles. Are you serious?
I'll have to look into that because that's what is just put me off completely
You're gonna do more breath of the wild?
probably
Yeah, probably
days waiting for driver one
1693 I didn't I play driver one? I played it already like five years ago. Was it a different driver?
Okay. Okay. Fine. Fine
Where do I how do I get driver one? I will play driver one as soon as possible so that person can now delete their twitter
Yeah, what should I play it on is it on pc? Let me check is driver one on pc
We should do infomercial nights. No, i've got something way better
And this is precisely what we are doing on friday. Are you ready?
Those of you that left a few thousand people left. They're not even gonna get the secret what the stream is on friday
We are going to watch
We're gonna hang out
with some
Coco and chill
And we're gonna watch a shitload of 80s and 90s
commercials
And we're gonna break them down
I'm gonna talk about them and go over them
80s and 90s era commercial watch party
Be pretty comfy. Yeah
Play megaman legends 2
And guess what guess what we're doing on saturday
the day after that
driver one
If you don't think that 2023 is going to be a year where I tell you exactly what we're doing and I do it
It sounds like a pretty good weekend
Although I can't promise i'll probably play for 30 minutes and despise the entire experience and leave immediately, but I will play it on saturday
Or maybe i'll beat the whole thing
We'll see
I will reveal my present
on friday as well
You'll see
Yeah
Should be a pretty good start to 2023
Reveal we've seen it. Well, i'm gonna reveal it on stream
It's gonna be fun telling you what about grotto beasts?
Okay, it sounds like you're giving them a present
oh
No, no, it was a present. It was a thing that
some community members helped
to like get
ready
And it's awesome
And you'll see why on friday
All right, so grotto beasts
You can expect
To see some very very major major news
on the grotto beasts release date
incredibly soon
I would say
There's going to be a major major release date reveal
and potentially
even beginning sales
Over these next two or three weeks
Okay
All right, we're trying to get it
ready
And ready to be purchased
There's a lot of moving parts with this project. So
It's not just quite as simple as oh just release it
There are 200 cards
There's a starter kit. There are booster packs. It's a whole thing
It's gonna be wild
Release the armin video. I haven't seen that in a while
All right guys, i'll see you on friday. Take care of yourselves. Happy new year if I
Didn't hear me say before
See you friday
Have a good night. Take care