Hey, what's up, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and
tonight, I got a very special Team Fortress 2 upload tonight, because this is the start
of a new series I want to do. But let's back up for just a second here. I want to give
you guys the origin, I guess, of this series. So a long time ago, I did a video, well not
really a long time ago, more like maybe a month or so ago. I uploaded a Crusaders cross
bow medic bonus clip on top. I think it was a Huntsman sniper gameplay. But if you remember
that, I called it a stipulation match, where I was only allowed to use one item or two
items and it was a very strange way of doing things. And I believe in that one, it was
I could only use the crossbow to heal people or damage people. I could not use the medigun.
It was definitely a whole lot of fun. So I decided to turn it into a series. And this
is episode one of stipulation, where just like in that crossbow video, I'm only allowed
a certain set of rules or guidelines or item sets, and I have to stick to those rules.
So I'm going to start the series off with the heavy. And I really do first right off
the bat apologize for this, because it's been at least a month or two, at least that, since
my last heavy gameplay. And the reason why that is, is I just honestly don't really
play heavy that much anymore. I play them every now and then just kind of joking around
messing around. But I haven't really sat down to play heavy in a long time. But I did
it this time. So let's start talking about the stipulation you probably know what it
is by now by watching the screen. Only allowed to use the fists of steel and the family business
shotgun. I am not allowed to use that minigun. Minigun off limits. That is the stipulation.
And you'd actually be quite surprised that this setup does work very, very well. As you're
seeing in this gameplay, I'm killing quite a few people. And I've only died one time.
So if you guys are liking what you're seeing here, and you want to try this out on your
own sometime, this is the strategy I was using. You want to walk around with the fists of
steel up pretty much at all times. The only times you want to drop the fists of steel
is if you get close enough to shoot someone with your shotgun. And you can also duke people
out and fake people out. You'll see coming up here, me and this pyro get into it. And
so often I'll bring up the fists of steel. Because if you don't know, the fists of steel
absorb 40% of the damage you take. When you have them up, that is. So this setup really,
it's not that bad. If you can time when people are going to shoot at you, and then after
they're out of ammo or they're running out of ammo, like a soldier for instance, let's
say he shoots two or three rockets at you while you have these things active. And you
absorb a lot of that damage. You only have one rocket to worry about now. So you can
just put these things down, whip up the shotgun, put the guy full of lead and he might miss
you, or he might hit you and it might not kill you. So definitely, definitely give this
a try. It is a whole lot of fun. It takes you out of that typical heavy gameplay where
you pull down the minigun and just brrrrr. It takes you out of that. It's also going
to give you a reason to put on that shotgun. Because let's face it guys, let's be totally
honest, not very many people use the shotgun as the heavy. Nobody, especially the family
business, my goodness. This thing pretty much collects dust in everybody's cabinets. So
definitely give it a try. Take the sandwich off for once and just go out and have fun.
You probably just saw the top frag in that last gameplay right there. I really didn't
top frag. I was playing as a different class earlier in that round and the round was going
on forever and I just decided, okay, let's just do this now. I'm going to do the heavy
with the shotgun and the fist of steel. I think I was actually playing as a sniper earlier.
So just disregard that. So let's talk about the gameplay for a second here. I'm currently
stuck inside of this building right now because there's a heavy outside and I think MLC Stealth
just got the backstab on and we were in Skype and he's like, oh, I got that heavy and I
went, oh, thank God, because as the stipulation goes, I would have just got my ass totally
handed to me right there. So thank you MLC Stealth for saving my life. I get behind these
two guys right here, kill the soldier with my fists of steel and then I put the Pyro
six feet under as well, kill him with the shotgun, jump around here to the corner. I
go down in that building again, just trying to get some more health and some more ammo,
even though I don't really need the ammo. So at this point I'm thinking maybe I should
get on that cart. I don't know why I thought this was a good idea. Maybe I just forgot
that I couldn't use my minigun because I see this Pyro and then watch, I get air blasted
almost off the cliff. Oh my God, it almost happens twice. I don't know how I ended up
surviving that. I should have gone right off of that goddamn cliff, but the gods of Hightower
were on my side at that point. So coming up to the end of the gameplay here, I'm checking
this spy over and over again. I don't know why I could have just bumped into him. Like
are you a spy? No, are you a spy? No, he's not. I get a lucky crit on this Pyro, pull
up the fist of steel and shab-bam right in his face and then I get the karma because
I get crit right in my face. So that is going to be the end of this gameplay, guys. Thank
you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. Just wanted to showcase another
small clip, I guess, of using this setup. And if you have any suggestions, if you guys
want to see a certain stipulation, then definitely, definitely drop me a comment and we'll go
from there. So thanks guys again. I'll see you all soon and take care everybody.