Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Super Meat Boy!
This is going to be Rage in a Basket that I open up and birds fly out of the basket and peck my eyes out.
I am going to be doing the Dark World.
And of course, I'm going to start with Chapter 1. We're going to go back to the beginning, back to the roots of the game.
I don't know, let's get this started, I don't know how long this is going to last.
I probably, to be realistic with you guys, I'm probably going to rage quit the Dark World.
Like, two to three chapters into this.
Because some of these levels are just ridiculous.
But I am going to do the Dark World, going to try and do it.
So what do you say to all of you? Welcome to the Dark World.
That hurt my voice, but you know what? It's okay.
Here we go! Dark World Chapter 1, as Meat Boy.
Oh, this already sucks.
So if you don't know what the Dark World is...
Actually, I should go from this way.
The Dark World...
That was easy.
The Dark World is just much, much harder versions of the levels you've already played.
So let's get...oh my god, this is so bad.
Good!
This one, if I remember...oh, there's a Band-Aid here.
Should I even dare try to get the Band-Aid?
Oh, I don't know if that's happening.
No, not happening. I'll try for it later.
I may in fact do a series where I get a lot of the Band-Aids.
Kind of like a Band-Aid-tage, I guess you could say.
That might be coming in the future, but for now, I just want to try and get through some of the Dark World.
Some of it!
So let's go, go, go, go, go!
That's the name of the game you go!
Oh, that's not the way you're supposed to go.
The Dark World. Everything is dark and dim and dying.
That wasn't actually that bad.
I am the Knight, says Batman.
Batman Begins, Batman Beyond.
I still have not seen The Dark Knight Rises.
I don't know why. Why have I not seen that movie?
Can somebody answer me that question?
Jerma, yeah. Why have you not seen The Dark Knight Rises?
I don't know, I haven't seen it yet.
I guess that's a good enough answer.
Ooh, A+.
So what happens if you, I know to open up the Dark World levels, you have to get A-pluses on the Light World levels.
But what happens when you get A-pluses on the Dark World levels? Does that do anything spectacular?
I think it just adds to the overall completion of the game.
And this, yeah, oh, I didn't even see that saw blade!
Ugh!
Keep that in mind when you get up here again.
That's not what you want to be doing!
Uh-oh!
Starting to get a little bit mad here.
You, alright, just slow down.
Slow down, you freak.
Ooh, oh!
I got this. I got this.
Slow down! Jump!
Oh my god!
I swear!
And I swear!
By the moon and the stars and the sky!
What song is that?
Whoever can guess that song gets a cookie!
Even though I don't have any cookies to give, I can just pretend to give you one.
Oh no, I'm really ruining this for myself right here.
I gotta...
Oh no!
Oh, it's over!
Just get out of my way.
Get...
Stop falling over back and forth.
Getting up there is no problem.
It's when you're actually here.
This is...
You want to get up top like this and...
Oh god!
That's a cat.
Hissing.
You know you're starting to lose your mind with this game when you actually start to hiss or make animal noises.
So if I...
Oh, look what I just did!
Yay!
Look at that!
I can jump over there now!
Urgh!
Let's go...
Watch it!
That was close.
That was very close.
Indeed.
I gotta not do that.
Get the top layer and then...
Shhh...
Just like that.
No!
Just jump over it.
Who cares about the stupid thing in the middle?
Fuck face.
I am going to elbow drop this game.
I'm going to go to wherever this game is stored on my Steam Cloud.
And I'm going to Randy Savage elbow drop it.
Off the top friggin' turnbuckle.
This is so hard.
I just gotta...
You know what?
Just jump over.
Jump.
Jump over.
No!
I had it!
I just had it!
Alright.
Seriously.
Seriously, no.
Let's go.
Come on.
This is getting a little ridiculous.
Jump.
I can't believe that...
I sound like Stewie Griffin.
You know, I say...
I can't believe that Super Meat Boy is this difficult of a game.
You know, I don't like it at all.
I would much rather kill Mother.
Oh my god.
Just beat the level.
When am I going to rage quit the Dark World?
Probably right now.
I can't do this.
All it takes...
See, the hardest...
You know what?
Screw this!
Should have done this so friggin' long ago.
This is so simple with Commander Video.
What the hell am I doing?
Oh, look.
Commander Video.
Oh, you like beat it with Commander Video because it's easy with Commander Video?
God.
What a stick in my eye and turn it around five different ways.
Commander Video.
Come on.
You're the best character in the game.
Let's go.
Oh, look at that.
Beautiful.
That wasn't beautiful.
That was not beautiful.
Started out okay.
And then got real ugly really quick.
Wow.
No.
I held it down.
Wow.
How the hell did I survive that?
I'm coming, Princess.
I don't even know.
What was the name of this level?
Fire something?
Fire something or other?
Oh, I just fall down and ditch and die.
Can I jump up the top there?
I think I can.
Can I make that?
No, definitely not.
Maybe if I had the patience to try this.
No, no, no.
We're not going to do that.
We're going to do this the way it's supposed to be done.
Just like this.
Just like that.
And stumble a bunch.
And now you're screwed.
Yay.
Doc.
World.
Take the whole damn wall down.
I can't be going that high.
Okay.
Jump up here.
Jump around.
There it is.
Finally.
And I got an A plus to boot.
Oh, I should have.
I should be showing some of these lives.
Oh, man.
That was tough.
What?
Was there a Band-Aid up there in the top left?
Band-Aid right there.
This is going to be tough.
Come on.
Come down.
Why?
Up, up, and away.
Again.
Wow.
Just don't be stupid here and you got it.
You, you're stupid.
You did it anyways.
Kick machine.
I'll give you a kick.
I'll kick you right in the balls.
Floating is so good.
It's so useful.
Man.
Oh, man.
This is going to hold.
I got to look at this.
I got to look at the pattern here.
So you got to go up in the very beginning.
So I got to go up right here.
No, right here and wait, jump, wait, jump.
And that's it.
And I have to go through.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, dude.
Really?
I'm going to jump over it at perfect times.
Get it.
Night game.
Sure.
I'll play some night golf.
You guys have ever played night golf with the illuminated balls?
It's actually pretty fun.
Go, go, go, go.
All right.
Now I got to go now.
Damn it.
I went at the wrong time.
Oh, for the love of just.
Wait, go.
I'm done.
This is over.
I got this.
Get up there.
Hello, my sweet queen.
Getting close.
I only have a few more levels of the first dark world.
I might change back to meat boy for this one.
Maybe not.
The floating really helps like that.
But it didn't matter anyways, because I'm stupid.
Damn.
Oh, I don't know what to do with myself.
There we are.
Oh, God.
OK.
After this one goes around, go now.
Hey.
What do you know?
Level 18.
The level that hurts your eyes.
Just know.
Wow.
That gets close.
I got to go before it comes up.
No.
That thing is really close.
You got to get it done.
Meat boy.
You have to go really, really fast here.
Right when this moves over, you got to go right now.
Quick.
There it is.
The Queener.
Here is the end.
This is it.
Give me that bandaid.
Can I get it?
Oh, I can get that.
That's a bandaid I can get.
No problem.
Give me that bandaid.
Oh, no.
I want that bandaid.
I can get this.
Come on.
Stop being such a fool, man.
There it is.
OK, cool.
Don't.
And bandaid get.
Hooray.
And this is it.
Hopefully this doesn't take me 5,000 years.
Whoa.
Yeah.
OK.
Got to be even more cautious here.
No.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
I'm running on pure just anger and hatred right now.
Wow.
That was close.
Come on.
Yes.
I did it.
This is going to be the Dark World completed for Chapter 1.
Excellent.
Phew.
Oh, my God.
That was pretty nuts.
So yeah, that's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And we're going to take on Chapter 2, Dark World, in the next episode.
And you might see before that, I don't know how I'm going to do these next few videos,
but you might see a bandaid run where it's a montage or a few clips of me getting all
the band-aids in a particular world or something or other.
So, thanks, guys, for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And, of course, take care, everybody.