Hi. So I'm realizing the tweet that I just put out, uh, sounds kind of weird.
Relaxing for a bit with some stuffed animals. Like, am I just lying on my bed,
camera pointed at me, with like all of my stuffed animal friends?
Anyways, hi guys. Welcome back.
Kinda. Welcome back. Kinda. I am not moved. I mean, I'm in the process.
Uh, I actually haven't really had a moment to sit down until right now.
It was like the first time I've sat down, unless I was in bed sleeping in about six days, five days.
You can, hey, you can hear the rumor. That's how you know.
But I just sat in this room. It was all bullshit. I'm just, you know, I'm not going anywhere.
He lied about canceling streaming. Wait, what? I 100% guaranteed there'd be a stream today.
It was one. I mean, you cannot go back on a 100% guarantee.
Hey, you get yourself in some trouble. What do you mean you banned that guy?
Oh, right. I was supposed to ban somebody. That's right. I'm sorry. I've been all over the place.
Uh, these last five days, someone's going to get banned. They said, ban me if you do, right?
You remember their name? Yeah. They were like, there's no way you're streaming on Saturday.
I fucking guarantee it. Otherwise ban me, dickhead or something, right? So ban that person, I guess.
Uh, turtle toenail just gave 5,000 bits. We haven't even started.
I wouldn't give me any money before I tell you what the plan is. You know what I'm saying?
Like, let me just be really honest with you. Uh, okay. Let me give you the plan first before
anybody's like, he's back. All right, let's there. There we go. He's back.
Let's talk about, let's go over the plan first. Uh, anyways, thanks for the huge money though.
Seriously. That's 5,000 bits. Appreciate it. I'm turtle toenail. They say, hey, you, you, do you,
hey, do you got a Mitch Hedberg? Oh, do I have a Mitch Hedberg impression? Oh, I was like, what?
Uh, it's kind of, Mitch Hedberg is kind of hard to do. He's fucking legendary comedian.
Um, Mitch Hedberg is kind of like this. He talks about, why the Pringles? No, I can't do it.
I got it. Maybe a little bit. Uh, the answer is no. Uh, he's a legendary fucking comedian.
Some of the funniest shit ever. I can't. I'll do an impression of Mitch Hedberg. I tried.
Look, if somebody's all right, I'm seeing a lot of minus twos. If somebody's going to give me
$50 to attempt an impression, what am I going to say? No. All right. Thanks for the $50. Uh,
you know, I don't think I feel like saying one sentence for $50. Come on, man. Come on, Gwen.
I can, I can, I see some, come on, wins here, please. You know what I mean? Why is nobody
doing it? Oh fuck. I forgot pre-stream chat is not every single person that watches this channel.
Sorry. I, I seriously like forget that. Anyways, uh, so here's the deal. Here's the deal. Uh,
there's been a lot of, it's been slow going. Let's just put it that way.
And it's going to take a lot longer than initially anticipated to actually move.
So because of all the coronavirus stuff and social distancing and all that shit, we're trying to do
this right. And we're trying to do it in a way that we're all comfortable and everything. So
we're not really ready yet, but we are, but we aren't. So, uh, streams for the next few days,
I'm going to be streaming, but they're only going to be three to four hours each for the next few
days. This is temporary until all this is kind of get where we need to be. You know what I mean?
So that's the way it is. So hold off on your, on your, on your $50 donations.
Fuck somebody already did it right. So we're going to do, we're going to relax. I haven't really had
a time to relax. I've been, I have, like I said, I haven't stopped moving. So we're going to play
Viva Piñata, uh, trouble in paradise is the one that everyone wanted me to play. Here comes the
hype train. Why don't you just try moving harder? It won't be that easy. But, uh, anyways, let's get
going. We're going to play Viva Piñata, trouble in paradise. Jerma sucks gave 10 community subs.
This guy sucks. Well, not you, me. Cause that's what you're referring to. So short streams over
the next few days. Um, we'll get back to normal here soon. I promise, but not immediately. Not
immediately. Here it is. So this is the good one, right? This is the one that everybody wanted me
to play. This is, this is the good one. You don't have an active gamer profile. Yeah, I do. What
are you talking about? No, I don't care about Xbox live. When you change a gamer profile,
you be returned to the title screen. Enjoy your time with Viva Piñata. Trouble in paradise.
Like your message. I'm not going to fucking do that. I don't care. Cause I haven't like paid
for Xbox live in probably like nine months or something. I already did this. Oh no. I'm saying
I don't, I don't have it. I don't own Xbox live right now. I, I consolidated all my subscription
services. What does it give me a warning for? The auto save. Yeah. There's a big donut in the
middle. Another 5,000 bits just came in. Uh, you missed my pre-stream bits, but they're irrelevant
now due to the poll being closed. Thanks for the 5,000 fucking bits dude. Seriously. If you were,
I was here like three hours ago, just checking in. I'm not even going to say this because the
votes are over and I'm not going to cause a fight in chat. Long story short, Nancy Drew was on that
list and it had 6% of the whole vote and a lot of people were angry. How many times do I have to
pick? Do I really care about this? Yes. I'm aware that that is a name of somebody that I've
potentially made up in the chat. Okay. I don't just, what the fuck do I care? Chat will never
forget. This is my, no, I'm changing it, but what if I, just be careful. What if like who's David?
I don't fucking know. I probably made that name when I was drunk or this is a used Xbox 360 console.
That could be like some other person's account or something. I don't know. I don't remember.
I don't remember. I don't know. Stolen. No, it's not. I made it or something. I don't know. I can't.
I have no idea. I cannot tell you the real reason why it's just there. All right. How do I, hold on.
What should I name this? This is a stolen Xbox. I didn't fucking steal this Xbox.
It didn't steal it. I purchased it. God damn it. I purchased it. I purchased it.
Prove it. People, you want me to show you the receipt from when I bought this Xbox 360.
Guys, that receipt went into the trash. What do you want me to say? Do you think I held on to the
Xbox 360 refurbished receipt? This thing was like $44. No, I think this thing was like $38.
That's irresponsible. For tax purposes. I don't know. You want to write off the 360?
All right. Fine. I'll go get the receipt and I'll write off the 360 for you. Okay.
Look, I've got a CPA that takes care of this for me. Jeremy, did you itemize that fucking 360?
No, I don't care. Want me to throw it in the trash? I'll just open the trash. I've not dropped
the fucking thing into the trash. No, I wouldn't do that. I would fucking donate it. Stop. Anyways,
what's the name of the garden? What's the name of the garden? Anybody got a name for the garden?
David's garden. David's garden. Well, I don't, I don't. I've missed you guys. It's been like five
days. I've missed you guys. David, wait, where's the, where's the little symbol that shows possession?
Okay, there we go. Put it on the hard drive. Oh, finally we can get past the fucking main menu.
Great gardeners can make their piñatas candy-o-city meter full and piñatas at full
candy-o-city are much more valuable. So this, you say this one's much better than the last one.
Why? Why is this one better than the last one? Extra, extra sweet? It's the same fucking game.
Oh. I just love fireworks. Oh, get away. This is my moment.
Okay. It's been like five days since I said that.
No such thing as a simple hacking technique. It's all incredibly detailed code and shit.
I hate when people fucking say that, by the way. As a fucking coder myself,
that's so fucking irritating.
Is this a bit? Hold on. You can't tell if me saying that I'm a coder is real or not.
There's absolutely no way I know that's accurate.
Um, no, I don't know anything about code. In fact, I tried a long time ago and it was a
disaster. Seriously fucking impossible. It's like one of the most detailed,
most difficult skills in the world. Okay. Let's open up the menu. This is the garden. Oh,
it's just like the last one. We're gonna, here comes the same stream we did with different animals.
This is gonna be, we're gonna get introduced to all the weird bugs and
foxes. It's a rerun.
Hey, at least the garden is done. I don't have to like do any bullshit.
Oh, you can take pictures in this one. Oh, wait, we already get a frog too? Holy shit.
Wow. Okay. What do you want me to do? Make a flower?
Okay, so if we read this, this is a bispati.
and lacquerate spots, and those eyelashes just don't naturally curl like that, you know.
Okay, must be a maximum candy-osity.
Okay, you can get your pinatas ready for their trip in a
cano, can, canonata by feeding them. This is a lot, this is not the same game.
Nobody said, feel good ink laugh.
Find the many ways that you can increase a pinata's candy-osity meter and then send it off to a party.
All right, how do we fill the candy, what, you have to like dress it up in clogs?
All right, we, we need a flower. That's what he wants, right?
Somebody make that? Yeah, I'm sure somebody will. Don't worry, give them like five minutes.
It's like the bug with your cursor. Information button. All right, we need a flower, right?
Have three poppies in the garden and that will bring a bispati in.
Move the cursor into the garden and open up the menu and put a flower.
All right, so where should I put these? I know people are gonna scream at me.
I'm gonna get screamed at for doing this wrong.
You have some lovely poppies. Somebody already made it.
If you put the cursor on a bispati and press Y, you can find out what it means to stay in your garden.
How the fuck have you already done this? You need at least like five minutes to upload
the video to YouTube. It's impossible. Are we doing animal crossing tonight? No, we are not
because during the process of the move and packing and getting bought, Kim has been playing animal
crossing each night because it's one thing that we can like do. So that is currently in the
occupation of Kim. They cannot play animal crossing. It's been commandeered. Oh, we have
lovely flowers. If you put the cursor on the bispati and press Y, you can find out what it needs.
So we need three of them, right? Oh, he's here. Okay, cool. So it wants three of these. Oops.
What did I just do? Wait, can I plant this? Wait, there are already three in here, aren't there?
There's one, two, only two. Do I have to buy this shit or can I plant this? Kim stream. Kim stream.
She's not here. This dude is a simp. What? Hold on. Let me get this straight. So because
my girlfriend is currently occupying the Nintendo Switch during the potential downtime of a move,
that makes me a simp. Is that what we're understanding here? I don't know what that
word really means. Simp meme is already dead. Give it a rest. All right. Yeah. Give it a rest.
That's a dead meme according to that one guy. That's a one guy moment. All right. So how do
let's wait. What? Oh, fuck. There's another one. I remember these guys. Well done. You attracted
a world. Good soil. Oh shit. Here they come again. This is part two snakes and worms and bugs.
Okay. Some grass. All right. What do you need? You need
three poppies in the garden. All right. And I got to buy a poppy.
Shovel. So would you just dig a hole? Does it matter where? Hey, hey, hey, get away from there.
Get away from that. Don't eat that. I'll just. Can I put it on? How close can they be?
Just dig it. Just do it wherever. Let's do it right here. Okay. I'm going to put a poppy, right?
Oh, that's a poppy right there. Don't ignore the story. There is no story. It's invite a bunch of
fucking stuffed animals over your house for a few hours. That's the game. Menu. Now I can get the
watering can. You're missing the lore. You make up your own lore when it comes to stuffed animals.
As I used to sit in my bedroom with a dozen stuffed animals and make up TV shows with them.
That was my lore with them. I can do whatever I can say, whatever I want with these guys.
All right. That's good. So now it's going to grow and that will that guy will stay. So I have good
grass, right? What do you, what does this say? What do you need? How do you, how do I get you to be a
resident? Let's see. Okay. You have two square, uh, penometers of grass has eaten a mouse mallow.
All right. I need a mouse mallow. He wasn't a kid. That was last week. I mean, that's kind of accurate
if you think about it. All right. Get that poppy to grow. What are you? Are you, are you a resident
here? Romance has eaten one green flutterscotch. Okay. Wait for the bug to reside. But how long
does the flower take? These things remind me of a toad. This is a fucking toad. I don't want these
things. Let them out. Well, I don't know. I'm not letting the frog out. This is my only friend.
I only have one friend and it's this toad. Max candy-osity hint. Okay.
Okay. This is a new thing. This is different. Candy-osity award for being a resident. What do
you get? Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. Let's figure, let's figure out how to raise our
candy-osity meter. New resident, new resident. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, look, it's kind of cool looking.
Okay. So and rename this potty. What should we rename this? Toad. I mean, I did just say it. So
why don't we just do it? It's 7 40 a.m. I don't know. Do you think I ever set the date and time
on this Xbox? Never. Wherever David lived is where this is probably set to. All right. This is the
house, right? Cognata at full candy-osity. Okay. So now it's like you pack item. Wait, I'm packing
this? What am I doing? I just disintegrated them. Wait, where are you going? Am I harvesting this guy?
Congratulations. You've completed the first challenge by successful. All right. So we,
we gonzo the graded into where? That wasn't too hard, was it? Now let's try something a bit more
tricky. Oh, you. So is that the point of trouble in paradise? As you make them really happy and
then you fire them out of a cannon to a party. You sent them to the glue factory. Oh my god.
You fucking psycho. All right. Anyways, candy. So we have to make them really happy and then send
them to the, to the party, to the party in quotes. God damn it. Oh, why did you have to say that?
Langston. Okay. Bring them back alive. I've got a request from someone having a beach party.
They want a sandy pinata. So I suggest you go to the desert area and trap a sweetle.
Follow the cursor and we'll soon have this one done. Ooh. Jeremy's garden. When you're here,
you're family. Okay. So we've got to get a, a sweetle. Oh, sorry. I just read that. That was,
that was not even my joke. Uh, that was a bit joke. I just read it. I just stole it. I'm going
to make sure I give credit. That was potion dwellers said that that was a stolen joke and
I want to make sure I give credit for it. Oh, and now everyone changes to plus two. That's really
funny. That's very, very interesting, by the way. When the sun goes down, look for a suitable
garden moth drop more. Oh, it's a pretz tail. I had a couple of these before they're hard to
manage though. They eat everybody. It's on his ear. The tag has appeared. They like to investigate
a garden in the dark. Okay. Here comes another one. All right. Select the desert. You can go to
multiple parks. All right. Where are we going? Is it the desert? The desert dessert, the dessert
desert. What? I don't know why it is red. Do you want to follow the shitpost to the desert?
Sure. I would not follow a shitpost map. You'd end up, you'd have been like fucking another country.
Oh, there it is. A sweetle, right? First sighting of a sweetle. How do I get them?
Yurt bag. Okay. Let's see. We have to bait, put bait down. Oh, again, selling traps is my
sideline. And to help you along, you can have a freebie. Wait, he talks? Wait a minute. This is
one of the squid billies. Bucky feel. I can tell. It was the frog. Okay. Place the item. I have more
than one. This is kind of cool. I like this. I get to manage more than one right in the corner.
Make sure it's perfect or I'll delete my fucking whole account on Twitch. I use that too often.
You know what I mean? That carries no weight anymore. I say that like every four or five days.
That doesn't carry any weight anymore. Bait trap. Have we been alert? Okay. How do we use it?
We need new material. I'm not sure I do. Think about it. All right. We've got to put bait on here.
Yams? How many yams do I have? Oh, you just buy one. Okay. That's good. Right. Wait for the
trap to catch the... All right. How do we... Is he just going to walk the whole perimeter?
I probably should have put this a lot closer. Not all the way across the whole thing.
Go get it. Why don't you go eat one of those yams? Come on. Make a trail of yams. Let's know. That's
a waste of money. This one's going for it. Here we go. Geki. I want one of these. I want one of these
so bad. You can only find the Geki in the desert. You can only find the Geki in the desert.
I'm just going to say that's an ugly piece of shit lizard. What is wrong with you? Look at him. He's
perfect. I want you. How do I get you? Okay. A Geki finds it hard to resist a delicate snow drop
flower. I want one. All right. We need a snow drop flower. How do I get one? I want it. I
want it now. I want that Geki. I will get you a golden goose when we get home there, darling.
I want that one, daddy. Mr. Wonka. How much for the golden Geki? It's not for sale. Come on. Will
somebody eat this? Somebody please. Not today, son. Do the whole movie. I can't do the whole movie.
Somebody eat this yam. Look at this party. Is this the party they were talking about? Look at how
much fun they're having. Oh, I need you. I need to have you forever. Somebody eat this.
Look at this party. They don't even need music. Hey. All right. Can I direct you over here?
You. Scared? No. Why do I feel like this is exactly, this is exactly the shit that happens
if you go to a doggy daycare. This is exactly how they all act. This is why I walked back and
forth like 10 times. I'm going to go around the edge of a whole building 50 times. Who's
that over there? I don't know. Who are you? Let me see. No. I'll go this way instead.
This is doggy daycare. And then there's usually one just chewing on a bone over in the corner
all day. Somebody eat this. All right. Do I have to make another one? Oh God. Okay. Move. Wait.
What are you doing? What are they doing? The party's over. Party's over. Apparently. What?
Everybody scram. No. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
God damn it. How did I fuck this up? What happened? This is free, right?
You scared them. All right. Where the fuck is one of these things?
I don't know. So did I soft lock myself in the tutorial for a game for five year olds?
I think I did. I'm fucked. I think I really am. Please come back. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want one daddy. All right. All right. All right. All right. Put one down. Look. Go eat it.
Go get over here. Why are they not even coming inside the circle?
Only one is brave enough to come back after the party pooper. Here we go. Here we go. Come on.
I'm sorry. I take back everything I said about doggy daycare. If that was, if that was like a,
if that was like a begging strip on the ground, a hundred dogs are running after that.
Like, come on. I was incorrect. Get it. Yes. You've eaten. Now you're with friends.
Oh, what I meant to say was, um, got you.
Return to the main garden and visit the post office to unpack your trap.
I have to send this animal through the mail and that wicked fucked up. You're evil. I'm not even
evil. Oh, there's Fanny Franker. You know, passing stuff on, getting some goodies off other Xbox live
gardeners doesn't exist anymore. Sorry. All right. Ooh. The trap has triggered.
And now we have to put, just put it anywhere. It doesn't matter.
The post office. There's no Xbox live guys. Howdy sweet pea. Welcome to the post office.
I heard there was a new face in town. We can help you with crate sales, crate delivery,
messages, invites. You just holler when you've made up your mind. Anybody else like this is
a nightmare person. Like, don't you see in a nightmare, the flap going up and down
really fast to like very distinct laughing sounds like,
while it's fucking running after you. It's fucking terrifying. Deliver this crate to me.
Sleep around. So does it matter where I put this? Right in the corner. All right. If I then,
you know what I'm saying? Unpack. Move out of the crate. Ooh, there you go.
Why is that? Why is it saying my name up there? You have a new sweet old visitor. Congratulations
on catching this little pinata. Now put the. Okay. How do I make you stay? What is this ominous
fucking mothership flying over us right now? What is going on? What's the fucking, oh, okay.
It really is a mothership. You have one square penometer of sand or you need sand.
So I see you've got a sand critter. Might be just the right time to give you this
sand packet. It works just like the grass packets and you can find it in the same place on the menu.
So there should be no problem for you to use. Okay. Cool. Sand packet. So he just needs one
little meter of sand. Short grass sand. Okay. Let's do a right in the corner.
This is going to be your little house. What's the snail doing over here? Get out of here.
Why does this guy always do shit in the corners? Cause you build out. Oh, okay. That was relax.
Relax. Um, okay. I need to change that. Um, no, no, I'm not going to do,
I am not going to do medical textbook penis for, no, I'm sorry. I'm not, it has to change.
That's better. Okay. Are you happy here? Fucking unfollowed. Okay. Sorry. All right. Select.
Go over here. Look, he's my friend. Apologize. I'm sorry. I said it. I know that wasn't a real
fault. That was it. I'm sorry. I'm saying this because you're making me. I know. But look,
name him. What does he want me to direct? Direct over here? Oh, eat this.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that. Yes, I did. All right. Has eaten one turnip.
I have a sweet little house in the garden. Okay. This is bad. Romance. What does he want me to do?
Select and do what? What do you want me to do? Direct it to where? What do you want me to do?
He's blind. Am I blind? Oh, read the instructions.
Read. I'm trying to. Oh, so that he's done with the party. Okay. Cool. It's not enough to.
It's not. Now stop. Oh, didn't I already do this though? I thought I already did this. Oh,
he has to eat three. Okay. You need to eat three of them. No, no. Eat, eat, eat. Fucking
mothership returns. All right. Now I can replace this, right? Eat. I need to build a house for you.
He's eaten one turnip. You need to eat turnips. No, I'm shipping this guy off.
It's ready to party. All right. It's time to party. Turnips have feelings.
It's like the future of Amazon package delivery.
All right. Time for a challenge. One more.
A bouncing baby piñata. There's going to be a baby shower. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Romance two piñatas. I will do that. I remember how to do it. Do you still have to do the mini
game from like the last one? Okay. You've leveled up. You filled the petals around the clock,
which means you've taken a step closer to becoming a truly great gardener. He remembers.
All kinds of things happen when you become a better gardener. Costalot store has opened. You
can buy some paving, some fences, a couple of items to decorate your garden with, and some seeds.
Oh, that guy. The guy that you hit with the shovel, right? New piñata spotted. Where?
All right. So these two need to, um, come here, come here, come here. Stop. What are you going?
Where are you going? I need, they need a house to have romance. Stop flying around.
He's like got a cursor underneath him. Like he's going to drop. Like what are you doing?
Is that your firing cursor? Well, there's a crab. It's not a giant crab. It's a regular sized crab.
Everybody relax. Beach party animals. I love what they want. They're beach party animals.
So there is sand over here. Sand and sunshine. Okay. All right. Come here. You, you too.
Actually, no, I need to see what it takes. I need to eat a daisy and we need a bespotty
house in the garden to make a bespotty house. Oh, there he is. I see. Cool. All right. There's,
there's no reason ever any human ever on any fucking circumstance. He's obsessed with gathering
seeds. Go like this. Talking to him. This is, that's like the Nosferatu fucking Dracula like
hands. Like what, there's no reason to anyone do that. If you do this, that you, that the, I,
I get away from me. Like that's universal. Like nobody fucking does that. You're in the same house.
Yeah. I told you. I'm not in a different place. It didn't move. It was all a ruse from day one.
All right. Let's talk to Acidos. That's pre-recorded. I can prove to you this is not
pre-recorded. Okay. Oh! Like would I be able to time that perfectly? Oh! No, no way. Today is,
it's, it's March 28th at 4 15 PM. March 28th, 4 15 PM. March 28th, 4 15 PM. That would have been
really fucking hard for me to do that. Pull out a newspaper. Pull out a newspaper. You're assuming
that anybody has newspapers anymore. Oh, there he is. Acidos. I'm Acidos. Take a seat and don't
hit me with your spade. Oh man. I remember this guy. Oh, we have a worm resident. I wish I put
the sprayer. It's like there's already dirt here. It's perfect. No, I want the shovel.
You have improved again. Lottie has some new items in her store including only eight more
levels. That's kind of a long way to go. All right. Let's plant this like right here.
Let's get out of my way before you make me angry. What kind of plan is this? Attack him. I'm not
going to attack him. Oh, a sparrow mint. So how many, how many Pokemons are in this game?
How many like actually exist in the game? Oh, they can hear the worms. All right. I'm going to
start to, I'm going to start to do some builds here. Kill him. I'm not going to, you can't kill
anybody. Oh, there's another one. Let's plant this right next to each other. This is a daisy.
Somebody has to eat a daisy, don't they? You can't kill anybody, guys. Why does everything have to be
but like, kill him, kill him, kill. You're killing the animals. I'm not killing the animals. Oh,
what did that, what's that for? I'm not killing any animals. No, that's a lie. I don't believe
the people in here saying that. That's a lie. They're lying to you. Be on the lookout for people
with false information right now on this channel. They're lying to you. Oh, I didn't know it was
going to be overwatered that far. That's that far. I thought it was a little more. Can you suck that
up? You can just like suck it up or something. All right. Wait, there's another one of these.
Give me this thing. I don't like this pavement here. Why would you pave a huge square around
one flower? Are you stupid? Terrible design, awful craftsmanship,
and a lot of new animals. Oh, I thought that was his tail for a second.
Congratulations. You have attracted a sense of flowers. Okay, a taply. No, I don't want, I,
these things, these things remind me of Otto, but I don't want to. Remember we had too many
taplys before and everybody freaked out and told me, put tap, put taply in fire.
Put taply in fire becomes fire taply. It was a lot of, I didn't want to do that anymore.
All right. I got to, I want to get rid of this shit. How do I like delete an area?
Shovel. Like I was getting rid of this. This is so dumb. Sell it? What do you mean sell it?
How do I sell it? No, I want to take a picture. Go on. Yes. Okay. What was I doing?
Yeah. How do I sell this? Can I do that? I don't think I can sell this stuff guys,
unless I can't select it or anything. I just delete. Can I just go to the store?
Go to the store. There is no store. There's the post office. I have to unlock the shop. Okay.
No, just don't, don't slap that, the mouth up and down really quick and make a laughing noise.
Oh, this doesn't, this tutorial doesn't matter. Okay. Somebody said, please do a chocolate
factory stream. What would I even, how would I even do? Would you like, you want to do like a
travel channel? This is the chocolate factory. Show me how it all works. Yes. So you guys
unanimously want a chocolate factory tour. There's no jokes here. It's just, hey,
this was the chocolate factory. This is what you want. There's not going to be like any,
there's no clowns going to run by her and it's, it's going to be like, that's what it is.
Okay. Not a joke. Okay. I'll see what I can do. I'll see what I can do. I'll see what I can do.
He, he, what he, he acts like he doesn't want a factory tour. I mean I do. That's kind of cool.
I do want that. Okay. I'm going to try it. All right. All right. Let's see what I can do.
He's going to tour a chocolate factory. Yeah. I don't think this is going to work.
It's going to be, it's going to be working loud. You don't really hear anything. It's going to be
like, so what do you think? Like just, you want to feel it. It's going to be like a vacuum cleaner
in the background constantly. I'm going to have to get like a shitty lapel mic that's going to be
like, I think that, yeah, that looks like the chocolate coming off the rack there.
It's going to be the worst dream. All right. Fine. Cut his lapel mic. Fine. Okay. I still
need to make a hole here with the jelly bean factory. Am I going to start doing like
candy factory tours? How do I explain this to one of these factories by the way?
Make a phone call, make a few phone calls, talk to them. Just so I'm just wanting to get in touch
with you with your like your PR, your marketing or your, you know, your tour department for being,
you know, on like on camera and do it for like a broadcast. What am I supposed to say? Oh, cool.
What industry do you work in? Well, I'm like, I'm an e-clown. Oh, so why do you want to do this?
Is this like a new food channel? No, no, no. I just, one person in my community said that it
would be a fun idea to do a chocolate factory tour. So that's why I'm here. One person told
me to do this. Oh, so there's literally, you know, this, that you don't have any reason to be here
besides this one person told you to do this. Yeah. That's it. And that's, that's pretty much all
that's going to happen. I'm not like a food blogger. Should I make a food blog in the meantime,
just to like have a website and just like having for like the next couple of weeks,
write about like fucking foods I eat and then just send them there and say, hey, I'm an e-clown,
but I also do have a good a food blog. I just started and really try to, this is like,
this is like when, like I make it till you make it. Don't eat that. You don't know where it's been.
Okay. First of all, okay. Fine. I'll do like fucking, I'm going to do my own like fucking
restaurant guide streams. Like chocolate factories and restaurants. This one's called
take a bite with Jerma. Take a more than, ah, more than you can chew. Starring Jerma985.
Got it. Got it. Printed. Done. Welcome back to more than you can chew with Jerma985. I'm here at
this joint. Well, that's, that's literally just ripping off completely. Um, guy fairy. I can't do
that. I can't do, I can't do that. I can't talk like that. All right. I need to play this game.
First of all, why? Why? Why? You, you put an idea in my head and now it's like the only thing I care
about. All right. I'll make, I'm going to make this happen. No jokes. I had so many other things
like planned. This is stepping over all of them. All right. You guys need a house. You even need
a daisy. What the fuck? Don't eat a daisy. You eat a daisy, please. They're over here. Eat it.
Eat daisy. Go do it tonight. I, I'm sorry. I can't, I can't take a tour of a chocolate factory right
now. You guys, it's not, it's not possible. All right. You need to eat two of these. One more.
Has eaten one daisy. What? You just ate it. That's not a daisy. Wait a minute. Did you just not eat
a daisy? It was a daisy. He just crushed it. What are you doing? Remember you should get bangs before
showing us the chart. Why would I get bangs? Why do you want me to have bangs? Are you going to eat
this or what? There you go. All right. You got to eat one more of those. There we go. All right. Now
we can do it. Now we need a bespotty house in the garden. How do we do that? Uh, nay. Thank you. Nay
means nay for the 11 community subs. Thanks to the fucking 11 sub drop. Well, I don't want,
why do you want me to keep doing this? There's something deeply wrong with your audience.
Okay. I'm sorry. All right, guys. Stop being so weird. You're scaring people off. Stop being so
weird. No, no. Yes. Uh, I am the ruler of the kingdom and the rule of the kingdom says to relax.
I have a new visitor? Never. No. Fuck the king. Uh oh. What have I done? We are influenced by you,
weirdo. No, don't. Don't do that. Captain Crunchy, thanks for the five community subs.
Jerma sucks. Thanks for the five community subs. Thanks both of you. Cool. Hey, cool. Thanks.
Finally, we can build a house. We need a, uh, build a house for the beskotties. A beskottie house.
There it is. How much does it cost? Zero. Good.
Now what if? No. God damn it. Don't fucking do this. No, it's, I can't right now.
I can't do that right now. It's not possible. I can't do it. It's not possible. I can't.
I actually can't. I was gonna say instead of going to a real chocolate factory, just do a huge
fucking bit where they make a fake chocolate factory and go through a tour with like six
different people and they're all characters and like I'm in a costume and shit. It's just,
it's just Willy Wonka, but it's not. Oh, there's a lot of, that's a lot of money and I can't,
right? This is like all the, that's not possible right now. Maybe, maybe in the future.
All right, I gotta put this down. You're a, I'm not a millionaire. I don't know if you'll get
this idea. I don't have, I don't have millions of dollars. This is, this is like, this is like
expensive. Making a fake chocolate factory is, that's extreme. You own two houses. Oh,
I don't own two houses. What are you talking about? He owns three. That was very, I'm kidding.
No, but for real, that's, I'll have to figure out how I want to do that. That'd be really fun.
He owns a Boston vacation house. I don't own that. Stop.
Tore, tore a sewage plant and pretend it's a chocolate factory. Holy shit.
And the whole time, the whole time I'm asking questions about like, so what do you wrap it
and everything? And they're just, they keep correcting me. This is not a chocolate factory.
What's wrong with you? So I see up there, is that, is that where the, is that where the vanilla
paste is added? This is, this is shit up there. What's wrong with you? The whole time, I'm just
so fucked up and so oblivious. I think that's where I am. This is very, oh, they have like a
nice little driveway. Just ask for money from your 985 relatives. I can't, okay. This is
fucked up and wicked fucking disgusting, but I can't even say it. Okay. So, oh, come on.
Do you know where it could go? I'm not going to, I can't, I can't even talk about this. We're
going to move on. I can't talk about that. It's too fucked up. It's too fucked up. It's too fucked up.
I can't, I can't, there's too many people here. There's 5,000 fucking people. I can't be on,
I can't record myself saying this in front of 5,000 people. My mother would be so ashamed of me.
All right, let's open it. Ta-da. Make bugleberry say it. It's not even you. Oh, that's not,
that's not how this works. I, I can't, I can't like plead insanity to my mother. Oh, it's okay.
No, it's okay. My mother's going to be very upset with me. I can't, I can't do that to my mother.
Here, I'll say it. Just type it to me. I'll say it. No, no, no. Okay. I was just, I was going to say,
let's, let's just, okay, let's make these two bugs. Let's just, let's just let these two bugs
have sex with each other and maybe we'll, oh, don't hit them. Come here. You guys ready? Oh,
no, no, no, wrong. It's these two. And here we go. We're going to have some bespotty children.
I always go, okay. Welcome to the romancing mini game. Like this, no. You need to take
control of your pinata and try to reach your partner without hitting any loavers.
The loavers are creatures created by Professor Pester and they hate the pinata being happy.
It's so fucking messed up. I can't say it. But it's kind of funny. If you hit a loafer,
you will lose a chance and waste some of your time. If you lose all of your time.
All right. So like the sewer water is coming down, right? Just like through like a pipe.
It's like, and I'm like, oh wow, cool, man. It's like a fountain. Like can I try it? I just like
dip my head underneath it and like, and it's like, you know, when like a huge amount of water
in a very concentrated beam, like it hits a part of your body and it just like it fucking goes
everywhere. Imagine that like directly in the forehead. There you go. That's what I was thinking.
I didn't say anything. I just that's what that's what I was thinking and it's like ridiculous.
Okay. I said, I said the sewer. I said the water. I said the sewer water coming down
and say anything else. Okay. This is game over. How did I get a game over? Your mom is my mom.
No, mom. I know you, mom. I know you're watching. Just remember I almost ate a shoe on camera.
Okay. Like just, I don't know. We talked about that and it was like, don't do that, honey, please.
I was like, mom, I'm not gonna eat a shoe on camera. I'm not going to unless, unless in a
few days, maybe they get like a hundred million, like 10 million channel points will come in and
maybe I'll do it. Oh, the romancing mini game. Right. Okay. Let's go. The old saying goes,
you can't hurry love. And that's especially true on Pinata Island these days. You'll notice that
the object of your affections will be none too pleased if you make your approach before proving
your feelings. To do this, you need to collect the required number of love hearts.
You'll do anything for money. Oh, stop. I won't do anything for money.
But I do like that word. I do like that word money. Any heart tokens you leave behind. No,
I won't. Okay. To do this, you need to collect the number of hearts and you get a bit of meter.
Okay. Let's go. Okay. All right. You've walked in the way. This is tricky. This actually is
tricky. This actually, this actually, this actually is actually, this actually is actually
tricky. Oh, fuck it. This time of it. Holy fuck. I was lost. Actually, it's actually, it was actually.
Yep. Now you've completed the game. Your happy pinatas will go into their house
and do a romance dance. And this is, they do the dance, right? Do we get to,
I really don't want to say this part out loud, but do we, the last time in the last game,
do we get to, do we get to, um, in the last game, you can, they did a dance on camera.
Do we get to watch? I don't, okay. First thing I thought that was a dead snake. I was like,
holy shit. You want, no, they do like a dance and can't you see? Yeah. It does it automatically.
Great. The storkos. Your pinatas have made an egg. Your pinatas have done the romance dance.
A new baby pinata is brought to the garden safely packed in a patterned egg.
Oh, so now we're gonna wait for that to hash. Level four already. What is level four? You really
seem to have taken a shine to this garden. New store items. Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. Uh, you,
I don't, uh, don't eat that. You know what? You can't eat that. Don't eat that. Your new
egg has been delivered safely. Don't eat that. Just, excuse me. You, you are encroaching on
my property. That's the only wormhole that I have. Just murdered him. Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
All right. Now go back in and do it again. Go eat a daisy and do it again. Cause I need more
bespotties. Oh, he moved in. He ate one of my friends and decided to move in. Well, that's
great. Why is my frog in prison? Is he not? What do you mean prison? I mean, yeah, he kind of is.
How do I free the frog? I didn't even know. Uh-oh. Apple, right? Sour shelly bean.
Seed feast. All right. Uh, this is, I feed, this is the same way in the last game. I feed it a, uh,
an apple seed and they become my friend, right? Do the Gary. Do Gary. No, I'm not gonna do Gary.
Do Gary. Do Gary. Oh man. I can't. No, I'm not gonna do Gary. All right. All right.
Ah, all right. You know, people are begging me. Have to. Every time a new pinata is hatched in
your garden, your label is fixed to it. You can change your label by using the label designer.
Where does it ship these up? You want to get rid of? Pack. Are we going to fire them out of the can?
Wait, this is a baby. Hold on a second. Have I, did I just take their baby and I'm going to fire
the baby out of a cannon to a party? Congratulations on romancing your bespottis. You breezed through
that. Well, it looks like. That's crazy. That poor baby. Hey everyone. You should all know
my store is open again. I expect to see you in here very soon. Just bring lots of cash.
Nobody likes the taste of chocolate coins more than Lottie, I can tell you.
I love chocolate coins. I used to pretend they waste to play poker with them.
And then we would use them instead of money or chips. It was so much fun.
Okay, remove the fence. He's a child gambler. You guys didn't, when you were like a teenager,
you didn't play like chocolate coin cards. You guys didn't play like Oreo poker.
Nobody in here played Oreo poker. You, what the fuck? That's like, you didn't play like
war for like Oreos. The fuck is, what the fuck is going on? No, we play Fortnite.
We play, we play Fortnite for Oreos. All right, let's do, I need to get some seeds. I need to
build, okay. I need a sweet little house. I need, what do I need? Okay. Get out of here. Leave him
alone. Leave him alone. He didn't do anything. You're like, you're just being annoying to the
frog. Okay. Let's go to the store. Don't play with your food. Well, then tell them to stop making
chicken nuggets in the shape of dinosaurs. Not my fault.
Or whether you're here to buy or sell, which will it be today? Highlight and select one
and let's get those coins flowing shopping. All right. Paving. But now I, I can select this
and I can sell all the shit that's over here. Right. You're buying, huh? Is there, how do I
just sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell. Okay. This is the dino nuggets are good.
I know you don't think I know. No, no, no. Don't sell the toad.
Wait, how is it a toad? What is it? That's a toad. Oh no, your name is toad. Right. Okay.
They're okay. I guess you can make my garden as I see fit. Yes. If not for spending, I'd spend,
surely can do. This game is so chill. Yeah, it is. Do I like fish sticks? Um, yes, I do. I do happen
to, I do enjoy, I do like fish sticks. Everything from the freezer aisle. They're very good.
Sell it. Yup. Yup. Say fish sticks five times fast. Fish sticks, fish sticks, fish sticks,
fish sticks, fish sticks, fish sticks, fish sticks. Oh, he's the cheese, the chosen one. I know. I
know. No one even asked him. I know. What do you got? What are you selling? What are you buying?
Stranger. What should I get? Fruits? Oh, paving. No, let's do, uh, no, I don't want anything. I
just want a regular round. Is there anything? Wait, let me check. Should I free the, uh, no.
100 I just a hundred dollars just came in right now to 10,000 10,000. That's from Gaza. Whoa
That's a hundred fucking dollars. There's no message. Just a hundred bucks in bits. Thank you. Seriously. That's a lot of fucking money and
It's just a bunch of money that you just gave me in bits right now
That's that's pretty much all there is to it. I can't fucking believe that you did that and there's no message. It's just
I'm fucking forever grateful. Thank you. Thanks a lot
Chocolate funds play Resident Evil 4
It's a huge money
Yeah, I actually here's the thing. I want to play Resident Evil 4 for the Wii
Because that's the best version and uh, but I know a lot of people gonna say PC play piece
No, the Resident Evil 4 for the Wii version is the best version. I'm not playing it PC
Resident Evil 4 for the Wii by streaming tomorrow. Yes, but we're gonna we're gonna continue to do these reduced
Stream hours for a little while until
Just to be up to be frank with you to be upfront with you
a
Lot of services and a lot of stuff has slowed down a lot since all the corona virus stuff
But that's why it's taking a little bit more time. It's kind of get it all done
so that's why
Didn't really get everything done that we wanted to
But that's just you know, that's the way it is right now, you know have to do we can right?
So over the next week or so
We'll be doing these reduced streams for us to kind of get everything we need to get done get done
He's never gonna play Hulk. Well, that's funny you say that because Hulk is actually
Scheduled for two or three months from now. So you're right
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I just wanted people to go wall park. Here we go
Oh
No, probably do it next week. All right, I need I need to let me focus let's focus on I have you need a house
I need more flowers. Let's water this stuff. What do I just seriously ship them off?
He's never going to do a sir is wrath DLC. Ah
I know I want to but I got I know we're gonna do DLC day
Okay, I'm gonna set up a thing where we do the DLC for every fucking game
I said I was gonna do DLC for at the same day whoo cocoon hatched where
Has emerged from a cocoon
From a light about no, I'm not no, no, no, it's just not not jump King you serious
I'm not playing not no. No, where do you get the idea? I'm gonna do jump King
I'm not doing the jump King DLC you out of your mind. All right, let's eat. Let's do some more
Let's get some of his bodies. Come here. Eat a daisy. Can you eat this daisy? You need this one?
No, I'm not. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, I'm not doing jumping DLC. No way
It's not gonna happen. Like I'm telling you just for being completely honest here. I'm not going to do that
Um, I got to like this the second the DLC ice level place up a little higher
I'm not prepared for that. Oh, what about Odama? No, I'm not. No, well, why do people hold on?
I've got a very important question. Why does everybody think I'm gonna play Odama again?
Do you not remember when that stream ended and I said and I quote without any paraphrasing
I will never play this game ever again. I cannot wait to never see this game on my screen ever again
And what it's all of a sudden now, it's like I can't wait to leave place on Java again
I can't touch that once you're gonna play a Java again
No, no, no never I need a seed. I actually liked Odama
I'd like that game too, but it was I was dumped. There you go. All right, what's in the seed bag?
this clam
I want it. What's this?
What's this? I want it. What's this one? I want it. Oh
It's a turnip who doesn't something need to eat a turnip
buttercup cool and
Day, see ya. Okey-dokey literature club confirmed. I'll never play that game either
Hey
What are you looking for need one fruit? All right here here here here here. I'll get you fruit
DLS DD D DLC day. No of a purple place. Oh my god
Morning interest you in something seedy. Oh, no, I don't mean like any fruit, right? How about just like all a holly berry
You're buying, huh?
Delete the snow hang out right here
All right, come get it. I'll be my friend
I
Smell's okay, but is that for me? I don't know. Who's is that? Can I eat that?
Hey this I'm not hungry. I don't eat it early in the chocolate factory the video game confirm
Is there a game
You need to eat something right? What do you what is it? What does he need again? I need a mouse mellow
How do I get a mouse mellow?
It's not good. Sorry to break. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, you guys ready to
Need a worm house. Sure. Let's do something. Let's do some world producing
It's not that bad
But what system did it come out for?
Oh a sweet little home, yeah
Is that game cube can I put it here? Can I put it on?
Fuck. Oh not good. Not good. Not perfect
There's no game keep. All right
Like logan brothers. That's another one. I see all the time. Oh, look at you. Wait photo opportunity
Thanks a lot
Play play tell who you I actually have Icaruga
Good news you
This little pinata must have smelled a turnip in your garden. Oh
They like turnips. Okay
Nice. It was terrible
Remember this one
He's making a funny face
Your way suit is being Oompa Loopa than Willy Wonka
All right, I'm done laughing. All right, so open it link urban build it taking so fucking long
Come on, come on cool awarded for having a mouse bellow. All right now I have to
It's actually been an hour and 35 minutes just in case you were wondering leaf lady
Levels until your garden size increases
This is a pillar stream. No, it's not. This is a chill animal stream
No, this is this is a
idea of brainstorming stream because we just
You know together as a community came up with the chocolate factory tourist ring. I mean, that's pretty good. That's pretty good
Okay, so we're good now
Let's put we need some romancing in here
Okay, this sweet old is it too sweet old we'll pull for animal I can't play animal crossing Kim has the switch
So I think we we haven't had very much to do in the meantime of getting everything ready and packing and moving
So Kim has the switch and she's playing animal crossing right now on the switch right now
All right
Ten minutes at least ten minutes now two minutes. Yep, I went down on you
No, I went down I went down in time on you. I went down in time on you you bastard
More gaffes
He's the master of the gaff
I
Want more desert stuff
Can I make this circle any bigger and it feels hard to do? No, you don't spell gaff with an O
It's not G. Oh mega. Well F F and that would be golf
Okay, this is too much
Go off
Okay, there we go now it's correct
So now maybe I'll get some more odd desert desert creatures
All right, sweet old one lives here. Well, this is there only one sweet old. How do I get sweet old?
Oh, look at you. I love to do home. You're my just go off. I think I've been doing that for the whole stream
I love it. These they just follow each other around
Okay, they're just happy family
Except for the one that we can in the somewhere. All right, let's plant. Oh
Feel kind of bad. You haven't been on leave this this whole thing. All right, you can leave
You can you leave I need a green flutterscotch get a Gekki get a Gekki
All right, I'm gonna try what's happening my money. All right, I'm gonna go try to get a Gekki
I'm basing my entire home around a Gekki. I got a good bring another one of you too. All right here. We're gonna do this
I'm gonna put some bait here. So I can have two of these so we can do with some breeding of the
Okay crap home edition why is this a Windows version what
That's got a lucky feet. I put it right here
Made it up like ultimate spider-man. No, I already played the best spider-man
Let him in to know we go. How do I get a Gekki to come out again?
All right trap play to Hill
How do you pronounce that?
How do you pronounce that to who it's to who?
No, that's not correct. It's not to who
You who?
If people still drink you who you know what?
I have not seen you who on the shelf in probably five to ten years because that was a chocolate dry. I used to drink it
All the time
Let me tell you
Listen to me you who out of the can in the fridge, right?
Get it in the fridge in the in those cans was awesome. It was so good
I used to love drinking you who out of the can freezing cold. Um, it's a chocolate drink. It's not chocolate milk
It's just chocolate flavored water. It tastes like metal though. You just said that I didn't
It doesn't taste like a metal
Alright, everybody everybody relax. We found one. Okay, a Gekki finds it hard resist a delicate snow drop flower
It does not taste like fucking metal. It tastes like chocolate
It just tastes like it just tastes like kind of gross, but I like it. Remember the
There we go
Yes, I'm get it I need two of you drink one on stream and be disappointed I've used to drink the ten of these a day
I like to drink ten of these a day. That's a lie. Maybe like four
Volturo, I don't that's like a fucking cereal mascot. I don't want that thing
I need to put it on a trap. Okay
That's like the off-brand cocoa puffs bird
I like your style. That's the shit that's in the bag on the bottom row, which by the way, just buy that
It's like the same shit. It's like four dollars less expensive. That's got a look cut his mic
All right, put it down here and then put this here. All right, get it. That's quite a stride. Holy shit
This motherfucker means business. This motherfucker means business. I like a mouth. What do you need eat something?
Volturo likes to eat something to make it sweat hot hot food hot pepper
Here we go. I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get a Gekki. Yeah
amphibians and reptiles only and a couple of
Chad birds
There it is again
I'm gonna link it. No, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't fuck that who cares. Let's go back and open up the boxes
return to
Central garden
You're not gonna get me
All right. Here we are time to open our boxes
Come on out
Unpack, where is it? Oh, it's at the post office
stupid
Did you're not actually dumb? Um, well
All right, this is tinted room for why do I have three of these I don't know how you drop great and
unpack
He got out. He got up
He escaped. All right
Okay, I'm gonna put this down here, okay unpack who's in there
You okay, but yeah, I just somebody says I'm wicked fucking messed up and I had to read it
All right. So we have now you
Now you
Alright, you're now a resident and now you're gonna have some babies
All right. Uh, there's another one was the Gecko
We say words like this leaning in to make them like more funny for no reason
But they're not and that's just like a comedy thing to do
All right, let's go post office if you have a crate related problem
It's a comedy thing
What's wrong with this guy?
Not really that much. I'll be honest
I'm fucking normal
I'm just like you
What do you want to be resident one? Flutterscotch you have to eat a flood. All right. Well
I need to have a flutterscotch population then I have a flutterscotch here. I need another one four daisies in the garden
Shit. Okay. Hold on pause
Pause it
I need daisies
Did you already eat one? I'm gonna do a line of daisies down here. The frogs are so cute
I know they are they are incredibly cute
All right question
question for you
Because streams have to be reduced in time over the next like week tomorrow
We're gonna keep going with this tomorrow. We're gonna keep going with this. Just just kind of get just just just keep going
No, not i'm not into the stream yet
I can't I guys I can't go to a chocolate factory tour
We've got to wait till like some of the social distancing stuff is
Yeah, not yeah, but they're probably not even doing tours wherever wherever I would go. I can't just do that tomorrow
All in no, no, no, no, no, no. Why am I picking them up? Just make your own chocolate
No, you know, oh it's not ready
It's not ready
But there's gonna be a stream here within the next couple weeks
of
uh cooking
Cooking not what you think though. I have purchased i'm gonna be using i'm gonna be doing
cooking the way that I know how to cook
And that is with an easy bake oven
and uh very
various other
cooking devices
Get the fuck out of the way. I'm gonna make uh some of the things in the packet
Bugleberry cooking
If you know there's a bugleberry cooking stream, you know, there'll be at least a few. Oh, oh at least like one or two
That's guaranteed
So I need a here we go I need a uh, a lot of scotch population
So then the geckos can live here
If it's bugle it's not gonna be bugleberry, okay, let's get those daisies up so we can get some more flutter scotches
Look, they're friends
Why is he weak?
Why go to bed? Why are you awake? Why is he nocturnal?
He's so I love him. He's hey, he's just stepping on things
He's like smelling this guy. He's like, what do you smell like?
Are you gonna go to bed?
He's so funny. Oh, he's my favorite
He's just rucking everything
You stink if you're about to where the
How do I keep you around?
He's to eat a turnip. Uh, isn't there a turnip over here?
Where is it? It's right here. Is it not ready? Hey look
Eat
That's for you
Eat that turnip
Oh, don't eat that turnip you eat that turnip mouse eat that turnip eat this
Yeah, there we go. You piece of shit
Oh, I thought he just didn't okay. He did it. Here we go eating a turnip now. He's a resident good
You live here now a resident
What are you what's your color scheme?
Pink and white. Okay. Okay now
We need these daisies to grow
How do I make his candy bar status go all the way up? He needs to eat flutters. We need more flutterscotch
All right, you two ready
All right need that they both need to eat a turnip. Do they? Yes, they do. I need more turnips
Let's make another. Okay, we're gonna put turnip this daisies. We're gonna do turnips this way
I'm getting so fucking pumped up
Not actually though you lost 100 people since the bugleberry impression whatever
Okay, get that away seed bag he doesn't give shit
All right
water
Can I
Can I upgrade the can or no? Is there even a reason to upgrade the watering can yet?
Probably not how quickly could I lose every single viewer? It wouldn't take very much time
I would just play white noise as loud as I can possibly go and turn it up all the way to like plus 5000 db
You would just everybody would leave you have to
Like the people wouldn't stay for that as much as people like pretend like they would
All right, here we go
You want to experiment no, i'm i'm i'm playing uh, i'm playing viva piñata. I want to like just kill
I don't want to blast white noise for 25 straight minutes. Why i'm not doing that right now
Or I know I mean, I know a way that it would
I could I would probably lose two or three thousand concurrent people that are here right now
if I like switch to like
like singing stream
and like I was actually trying like
Really really hard and it wasn't my I was really off key and shit and I was looking right in the camera
If I was looking directly in the camera and singing
I think at least three or four probably three thousand people would leave instantly
so
And then i'm not like jokey like that. I got a feeling not not like that
I'm talking like i'm looking in the camera and singing like add everybody here
I think it would take wouldn't take very long because i'm I can't i'm not like that great at singing
And if I was like taking a dead serious, I feel like people would be like I gotta fucking get out of here, man
Dude like
Really deep songs to not like rock and roll or like a beat or pop
Like really like deep emotional song. I feel like people would be like, uh, i'm not really into this
You think you would say you would not
All right. We got turnips. We got daisies. I need to wear those. Uh,
Yes
Does have Reese's egg
a tartridge
A lot of daisies. Okay, where are those?
Where are the flutter
Moths. All right eat these are you guys ready to romance eat a turnip eat a turnip immediately
You eat a turnip immediately. I stayed for the whole city skyline stream. That was a fun stream
It was a pretty cool town. I had and then I don't think you want to stay in guys. It would be like
You don't you don't understand
I would go all in on it and it'd be like
Like it would be like that for like 30 minutes
With like instrumental behind me
You'd hate that they can move in any direction and we'll try to chase you down and zap you with their pesky pest power
If you get too close
They're all so indestructible to boot. So take care
Okay, watch out for the super loaders
Okay, watch out
Yeah, we actually have to like and actually
Oh actually have to be careful. All right, i'm done with the actually like i'm making a youtube video
gag
Come get me. Uh, I don't like this. What do I need five?
That's just kind of hard
All right. All right. All right. Did I not get them as many?
actually
Your viewers are already going down. What do I need to keep like track of every single viewer?
What there was five thousand two hundred and twenty five another is five thousand two hundred
Oh, what am I supposed to? Oh me? Oh my
This guy what do you want to do? I'm just playing a game man. Let's see what this dance is
Sing them back to us. Um
Did it work? I thought he was good at streaming
Now you just want me to do this
Because you want to have a clip forever of an insanely important. Excuse me. Please stop talking
We're about to watch two people have sex
Please shh fight in the theater
Oh, are you here? Are you here forever another little already?
Well in that case you should take a look at the new fence amongst other things that lotty is selling
She also has some milk for sale. I deal milk. Oh haven't happened to tf2 fucking meet the medic video
That exact thing happens after the amount of time you have invested you can call yourself an experienced gardener
I'm experienced now. All right, so
the
Bum, okay. I just said that because it was like right the camera was okay. So the
Requirements are eat three daisy seeds three daisy seeds
I was trying to think about this thing was called
Three daisy seeds you got it. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got it
You got it. You got it. Let me reach in my sweet bag and see what I have
Relax relax relax. All right daisy seed
Take it
There's one
No, what?
I don't know
Sorry, where you at? Come here thing first German
All right, if oh
Did I I got you? I got you. Nice. Nice. Nice
All right
has eaten one snow drop and question mark
I need a uh
What's this spider? Yeah, if I turn the camera on just stared at the camera and just started singing
Like happy birthday over and over and over again
As hard as I could as trying as hard as I can and being dead serious about it
That's how we would lose people only visit the gardens of more experienced gardeners like you
I don't but I i'd have to have that recorded forever. I don't want that
I don't want that
We're talking guys we're talking about
I'm gonna give you a quick sample
Of what would happen? No, i'm without the camera. Fuck that
No, fuck this
No, I don't want to do that. I'm not doing it. It's like embarrassing and weird. I'm not doing it
I need a flutterscotch domain. You can that's fine. I'm a coward. That's fine
I am a coward. Sure
Oh the egg. I thought you never got embarrassed. Well, it's not about getting embarrassed. It's about
What happens when somebody raids this channel guys?
Every time and I mean every time no matter what what's what's a what's the clip that you see in this in the chat?
That's that's spammed
a hundred times
Right. Okay. Good. So
Do you want me to add more ammo?
When some you know what I mean? Like just have that somebody's oh here the day somebody day welcome to this channel guys
Thanks for here's like the me singing happy birthday directly into the camera to you. That's
That's how you
What the fuck am I playing? This is viva piñata
I mean, what the fuck am I playing?
We're talking like
Happy
No, I can't
I can't do it
It hurts. I it takes every inch of my body to say that
like
Happy oh, I can't I can't do it. I'm not doing it. I refuse
I can't even do the first two lines
He's important for making stuff that you qrs is different because two are I was I was fucking drinking wine all night
That's different
And that was like a weird song and it was like a it was like a routine going on in there
It wasn't just me singing happy birthday to you directly looking at the camera
And trying as hard as I can to sound like good and sound like fucking good. It's not the same thing. That's not it's not even close
Um qrs is worse now we can start for real
I never needed help when I used to run this garden this shovel gives you the ability to dig deep holes. Oh, I can do water now
Wow, that's a fucking a shovel upgrade. That's amazing now sing
Oh, there's no way
You won't get that for me. I'm sorry
Shovel I thought he just was holding the frog's head. I was like, wait, what did you what you have a new pret tail
Exciting
Oh, there he is
Wait, we have a new pretzo. It must be his birthday. Happy birthday. Yeah
No, oh
Oh
Nope. No
Uh, ah, ah, ah
It hurts my whole body hurts
No, wait a minute what this is the only cartridge we have
Are you kidding me? You used to kill them with her girl? I
How do we get him back?
Actually, you hire a singer to sing it. You're like kid's birthday party and he's like happy birthday. Oh, oh no
Oh, oh, it's my whole body hurts. Oh, I can't do it
I'm too embarrassed
Um, yeah, I have 60 dollars an hour
It's gonna take me four hours to get the courage to do this
You have to commit to the bit. No
Okay. Oh, he's a resident now
Let me try to get through half the first line
Oh
Fuck no
Your entire career has been leading up to this
To then ride the roller coaster down into the ground
Like this is that
You're talking about the peak of my career. Now we go down. That's what you're describing
Oh, here we are at the peak of the career. Now, let's start to ride it down
No, this is not you think this is just yeah. Yeah, I'm about to go to a fucking chocolate factory. You think this is the thing?
Happy birthday
I can't do it. Happy birthday
I'm turning this frame off. I'm gonna leave I have to leave in like 10 minutes. I'm not doing it. It's over
I'm just not gonna do it. Somebody's standing behind me with a taser
I feel like i'm on like a challenge tv show
Welcome to fuck you with steve. Oh, whatever it was, right? Yeah, we're gonna zap you every time you fucking stand randomly
Happy birthday
Hermes tonight's biggest loser
You're repressed. Why?
Bart I triangulated circular friends
Can I bring to your attention the arrival of my mobilistic dwelling and the tinkerific tool that lies within myself?
Please elect to pay me a visit whenever you like and we can talk some more about the signs of turning one item into another
Duping gotta get banned
So we have two i don't know how you guys became residents of what plant dried out. What are you talking about?
Stupid idiot
Oh, there's a one of those snakes do one of the simpsons, which one is there a certain simpson that you'd like me to do?
Do them all at once
Okay, all of them at once so we got marge
And then uh, lisa
And then bart yeah, and then
And then okay
This kind of that was probably all of them, right?
Worst
Worse than singing happy birthday get out of here not even close
Guys come on. Oh, I would wait. I need two of these
How many I need a I need a moth the sanctuary. Whatever. Wait crab. How do I get you come over here?
No, it wasn't worse. I need water water water water water water water right here. There's a shovel
That was not worse
Big pond look at this. There's no rhyme or reason to this whole place
big pond
Want to try your hand at hard landscaping, eh?
Here's a tip hold down the x button and you can adjust the size of the affected area
By moving the left stick left and right if you dig a larger area you will get a deep. Thank you. Thank you
No, no pond
pond
Pond let me stop. I mean stop
I want a bunch of I want to have like frustration. Look the frog wanted a pond
Being so mean to me
chat hates him
Can I seriously pick it up and put it over here?
All right, we got another uh
What are they called?
I don't even know but I got three of them you guys ready to do again
Eat a turnip go eat a turnip. Let's do another more eat this turnip
And then you'll eat this turnip. Let's have let's have some more sweet, uh sweetles
Newt gatt nice. I'm gonna play this game long term
Um, I mean i'll play at least into tomorrow depending on how much fun i'm having the next day. Maybe
Well, I don't know. We'll see. Here comes a newt gatt
The little pond that you made has made the garden newt gatt interesting to this pinata
And then we're gonna have more uh, sweet little babies
Yeah
All right. All right. All right. I got uh, i'm ready. Where's my um, where's the gecko? I need that gecko
The gecko needs to eat two butterflies, right? First of all, don't do that yet. First of all
your residence, right
Snow drop. All right, we need snowdrops
snow snow snow snow snow snow snow
Do I have any snowdrops?
I think I have to buy it from the store
Transylvania wait, what the hell is all this?
I'll buy you snowdrops if you sing for us. What are chocolate coins if not for spending?
I spent a lot. All right, if I were you better value
What is it? What is it under?
Is it under just seeds?
yam
bluebell
Do I get it? Do I have to buy it from the
What the heck is it?
vegetable
No, not unlocked idiot
I would say
Shut up to you, but I wouldn't
I'm sure you can do better than
This is a shitty version of animal crossing. I'll be counting
Like i'm playing this because I don't have access to animal crossing
And by the way, this came out before animal crossing. Is it a lie?
No, I don't think so
When did when did viva put me out of one come out when the animal crossing original come out?
Animal crossing was on n64. No, it wasn't it was on gamecube. No, it wasn't
2001 animal crossing came out in like 95. No
What the fuck are you doing? Hey
What just stole money from me?
Get this guy out. He's like dancing. All right and stop stop stop. I need to hit him with the shovel
Original animal crossing was gamecube. Yeah
n64
All right, everybody eat up
Didn't he go straight to hell fight he respawned. It was n64 first. What now this thistle right here
I should get rid of this
This is junk
Yeah, this is junk man
It's called animal forest. This is junk right here
Was japan exclusive
What's this?
Thistle flower head. What is this junk?
negative 30
Can I just like throw it over the fence?
Today is literally my birthday. Well, happy birthday
Hopefully you have a good one. You have a great birthday party. All of us are invited, right?
I back I need to go back to the desert because I want to get go not good enough
Don't invite yourself asshole
Whoa
This is not the desert is it
Here is an angry pinata blow up don't make it mad
Okay, look this is snow fox
Any bait will do. Oh, no, it's a pretzels
He's so cute
Hey you
It's all of our birthdays. Happy sing. Happy birthday. Uh, yeah
Is there any snow?
only
critters
How do they get them to come out?
How do I get a snow biome?
No
Gotta be daytime. Oh, okay
Well, let's just go back then. I don't I don't want to pretzel they eat everything
I had pretzels before and they destroy everything
Wake me when he sings happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
To happy
It's like somebody driving by their car and yelling out the window to you happy
Birthday
Thank you
Damn it. How do I make you extra happy?
He sleeps all this all this lickato does is sleep. I've never seen him awake. He just sleeps right here
All right, it's time to wake up. Wait, I need a
Resident sleeper your stream
Wait, wake the fuck up
Come on, wake up and click that x in the top right corner. I don't need that negativity in my stream positive vibes only
God, you don't need to water grown plants, please. That's I said don't be negative to me
Don't criticize the perfect streamer
Hey you give me a seed
Sometimes pinatas prefer eating seeds to the plant they grow
What is it what kind of seed is this
Don't critique mystery seed. Okay
When you can play wow again, right?
I'm not gonna play wow again
I'm not gonna play wow
actually mad at chat wait, wait
Are you really gonna miss are you really gonna mistake my comedy scream?
or
Actually being mad at somebody
Any more seeds my seeds say that I shouldn't talk to you
Wait, this is supposed to be funny
Now that was funny
He hates us doesn't he
Oh
Avoid it for growing a carrot who eats carrots
If I were a little seedy the soil would give me all
Who was that a box?
What is this?
Mr. It's a mystery seed
How's that a seed?
Don't eat that nobody touched that I want to plant the crab. I don't know what the crab wants. It's a mystery look
You uh, oh
12 square kilometers of sand 12 square. Wait, that's like the whole place
I need that's too much
That's so much
More water more water more water. That's so much water though
Remember, there's a snail
You fucker get out of here. All right, everybody move lightning strike. Excuse me. Stop sleeping
All right, was that lightning I would somebody just drive a car into my house, what the fuck was that
raisin
They like buttercups, okay
cluckles
Cluckles and a quackberry
Yep, they're gonna have a quackberry
I want them. Yes
The pond you have made has attracted
All right, how do I make I want all quackberries I don't care about anybody else quackberries frogs geckos
Yeah, we're gonna sell everybody else. Was that quackberry?
All right. What do you need?
Over here. What the fuck is this?
Oh
What is what happened? Why is this evil?
Uh, that was terrifying. No, it just planted
Get rid of this thing
Where is it?
Where's the seed gone? All right, it's gone you I want you. What do you what do you need to stay here?
Okay, eat one piece of bread
Bread this garden is fucking madness. Good evening. So i'm not the only person who can't afford to sleep around here
Produce do we have bread? Yes
That's expensive
That's a whole loaf. Wait, i'm gonna feed a duck an entire loaf of bread
Uh, holy shit, that's not good
Welcome
What does he look like?
And tell all your friends they can come too
Oh, wow. It's like plucky from tiny tunes
Well, that's the name
Plucky. Why do I know that? I love that show
like that, right
Ck, or is it I think so
Uh bunny comb get a lot of new animals
Did you see that bunny comb appear? Is it a carrot? That's all right
New items good
All right. I want more ducks
All right. It's time to start to get rid of people
keeping the frog
and um
We're gonna we gotta start making this is this looks like shit. I'm not gonna lie to you
I mean i'm gonna be really this looks like dog shit. So it's time to start cleaning up a little bit
We're gonna make what we want
I want plucky's
I want ducks. I want
Congratulations, you've unlocked the trick stick
Use it to train pinatas to entertain you with amazing feats
Press y to find out the details
My tip is to feed a sparrow mint with a daisy seed
While it's performing tap it with the trick stick to teach it the trick now you won't need
Uh, I don't care. I don't I don't teach any of my animals tricks
Uh, is that gonna just for her be the bottom of the ocean?
Slow down slow down
Now I want
All right. I need more ducks. There's one more requirement there. At least do you need to eat a crustacean?
I need the crabs to come down. Okay, let's we gotta sell
I need more
Shit, I need more water and more sand
I want ducks. I'm sorry guys. I want ducks
I'm not gonna do foxes
I have to sell the perch you're on well, you can keep that for now. All right, how much sand do I need?
for uh
So many people all right, just get this shit out of the way for now
Somebody's just random people eat the carrot. I need a duck house 12 and 12
Morning gov. I'd offer you a bacon buddy, but i've just eaten the last one. We got 550 for a
quackberry house
I'll get
All right, where can I put this?
Does it have to be in the water?
Eventually will be in the water. So that's okay
Maybe it does have to be in the water
Okay, I gotta get rid of this shit. Okay, hold on
Get the fuck out of the way put the box down wrong
Put the box down what box put the box down
What do you mean put the box down?
Like this box the box
Put the box down put the box down
Sell the worms
I'm going all right. I'm going on a selling spree
Now keep these whose house is this sweetle self, but this is the sweet of the who's what house is this?
Okay
All right, you get the fuck out he's just ruining everything that's fine
Am I not hurting him get out of here
Uh
Get rid of this carrot. No, actually you can here. Where's that bunny rabbit? We're here right here
Try that let's go. Don't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Um
I gotta get crabs in here. Where's it going crabs crabs crabs you need crabs. All right, sell this
You can't kill anything this game you can't kill anything
You're gonna defeat them. Can I interest you in something? Sure we can
Okay, now I got room
Move this down here
Did I get rid of the all the animals that live in this house?
House
I did didn't I yeah get rid of this
Okay, you guys can stay
I want a mouse house. Maybe
Still no gecko
Oh shit another frog
I need tafflies to get another frog
Another bounce over here
You need to eat a turnip come eat this turnip i'll make a mouse house because the geckos need to eat the mice right
One of the snakes do
Here look what I got
Eat the turnip
Go for it, and then we'll make a mouse house
geckos eat butterflies
but I can't um
I can't do these snowdrops yet. So I have to make mice and then the snakes will come eat them
I can have a snake house for now. Hey, look dude friend. All right, let's make a mouse house
Or no, i'll make a duck house first
Because I need that I need duck house. I need a gecko house
Let me finish my breakfast and we can before I can
Right on the beach. Yeah, this this is the this is what I want right here
Perfect look at that. That's gonna be beautiful. There's gonna be like 15 of you ducks
I'm gonna breed as many of you as I can
Now we need a mouse house. Oh, he's currently building. I can't do anything doors on the wrong side
um
Can I move it?
I can't can I move the house?
I will expand out. It'll be fine. Yeah, i'll do like some water over here, too. Yeah, that's fine
It'll be fine. I want this frog too
I need tafflies
Let me attract tafflies
Find out how do I get a taffly to come over here? Okay appear requirements have two daisies in the garden
There's like five daisies in the garden
Where's the taffly?
Where's the pinata cheat sheet? I just looked at it. Ooh, come on. Come on. Eat that bread
Eat this bread look this bread over here another one get over here quick
Bread come eat it come get that bread and then you two can be best friends
Do it you'll have a house to live in come on and do it you can do it. I know you can
No
It's bread. You'll love it. Don't leave eat it
Come on, go get it, please
Oh my god, that's the tackiest fucking thing i've ever seen in my life. That's the duck's house is a pirate ship
It's not a series of rocks and moss
Oh
the bread
All right, let's do a mouse house
Oh, no, let me go see if I can get a gecko
I'm going to get a gecko see if I can just go take like a gecko from the desert, right?
Remember when you pause the game. I have to go to the bathroom. Okay. Sure. I'll give you 10 seconds
Okay, how do I get you?
Something spicy. All right. I need a snowed uh drip whatever it's called
You're pressuring him to pee all over the place even at night that's gonna look
Go drop come get it. I could I could get one of these guys too. These guys are kind of cool
I'll take one. Yeah, i'll take one
Why not? I mean they're cool. They're cool
Even at night, they're a pinata. I'd recommend that
Will he eat with him when he'll eat all the friends willy?
What does he eat?
Don't take it. Don't take it. He eats friends
Well, there's that one he eats everything. Okay, we got a gecko. Let's head back
spongebob laugh
God damn it. Okay, put him out here over the box the box the box the box the box
Hey there don't work got yourself you can go right here unpack
Is that a gecko? Wait, that's a snake
Oh shit, why did he eat the snow drop?
No, I don't want him to eat it. No, no, no, no, no a kitty floss
I think this is one of the last things I saw
Prowling at night and stalking at night
I know something else that does that
You still won't come over here for the bread
Why are you such a dope?
Well, there goes the mouse at least I have a snake friend
How long am I gonna play this for?
uh at least
until tomorrow
So i'll be i'll play this tomorrow too
Because I I can't I have to this tons of shit. I still have to do
But I didn't just want to not stream
So we're gonna go when we can right?
No, no, no, not like until tomorrow. I mean like
After tomorrow's stream of this we'll see how where we are. It's too late already confirmed it. No lying again
Try to have a snake house
the snakes and
Need a weedling but I know how to make any weed disappear. Oh, do please think about it
I'll just be in here drinking milk, but not eating the cookies. I'm sweet enough already. What a sick fuck
I'll just be in here drinking milk
Imagine giving that information to somebody for no reason
Yeah, so i'll uh, i'll pick up around like i don't know seven o'clock eight o'clock. Yeah, we're gonna go to the arcade and shit
Yeah, that sounds good. I'll just be in here drinking milk. All right
um
All right, see you at eight see at seven. Well, I don't need this info. It's a useless fucking info, but not eating the cookies
My in's just the right place to come find a way this guy made it's got milk guy turning up
You should come pay me a visit come for a worker stay for the milk. Wait, i'll just be in here drinking milk
Uh, I don't get it. Is this guy this guy give the milk. Is this the milk is this the milk man or something?
I don't understand
Does he like lean over and like drain his head congratulations I did it when you get a chance
I'm gonna stop talking. I I can't stop talking. I'm a i'm a twitch.tv slash broadcaster
I'm a hunter can get any so I won't want as a resident or stop talking. I'm a no he's perfect
He's cool. All right. I need a snake house. I also need a
Marshmallow house. I also need
Hmm
Snake house. Let's have some snakes. They're cool. I like snakes
I told you guys a long time ago. I wanted to get a ball python, but I didn't want to feed them
Can't do it serpent house take your time
All right, i'm gonna put this back here if I can
Yeah, like right there
It's right in the water. That's okay snakes like
No, they don't become the snakes
Remember you're being rude and interrupting the stream. All right, I got you
Um, why are these not growing you guys told me to be
It's because of this motherfucker, isn't it
This guy's fucking up everything
I need an apple seed, right? How do I make this guy become friendly and not keep fucking my shit up?
Up bash that smash it dead. Don't smash. Don't smash. I thought he said it was done. What are the snakes living? Cool
That's not a bad design
now
Seeds come here when mine can't hear the game. You can hear the game just fine
If you talk us
You got a trampled who somebody got trampled who got trampled
Why can't I start giving them funny hats?
All right, let me all right daisies finally now i'm gonna have a taply. Uh, let's take some plants here
Spoken like a tf2 player. What did I say?
What did he what did I what he's what did what did I say?
I don't even want to get it
hats, uh
That was so much fun
It really was just collecting hats
The angry he's mad. Why is he so mad?
What's his problem?
He hates this thing. You don't like it fine. I'll get rid of it. You happy now. Oh, it's a pumpkin. That's kind of cool
How much water does this fucking thing need
uh
What the fuck?
Oh shit. Okay, cool
Can I get a pumpkin seed out of this?
I've not been using right now. I haven't been using fertilizer because I want to oh
Look come here
Finally my dream of having ducks and frogs and geckos is finally coming true. Yes plucky and
gaffey
and then donald
daisy
We're gonna have them all
Huey louie
gaffey
Get the crab. Um, I will
All right, they need to eat a crab
So we need crab food and crabs need a bunch of water and more sand. Let's put sand over here
This is such a chill ass game, you know what I mean
This is fun. Just to just do who cares, you know what I mean?
It's just fucking it's like animal crossing but I can't play animal crosser right now because this is not here
Kim has it and can explain animal crossing. She's probably a ton of fun, but i'm playing
I've got my own version of animal crossing right now. You know what i'm saying?
I don't want to be too sandy because the ducks probably don't like that
I would assume the ducks don't like sand do they?
That's fine, I'll just replant it somewhere else
Makes like sands, right?
Okay, that's all right
I'll just pull this just sell it. Whatever. I see you. Wait, what is this?
Tower of sour base. Can we see one? Can we see a sour tower guys? Don't you dare touch this pumpkin?
There it is. Nice
Let's get sour tower. I like it. I'm into it
I want someone to eat this pumpkin
Oh another snake
You need to eat a mouse, right?
Come on down. There's another one here. There's a mouse right here
You do have complete this access to eating a mouse
Eat it. It's a snake. It's not a snake. It's a surya bent
Okay, sorry. Oh look another mouse
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, no, don't eat this yet. You get over here run away
I need a mouse house to generate mice
Because that um, what do you need to turn up?
I gotta turn up right here
Eat that turnip and become resident because I want to breed them
Don't eat them
mouse house
House of mouse
Just get it out there
Because then i'll have two
These they can romance they can have they can breed and then we can have a bunch of snakes
Come on in here. Come on. This is a turnip right here
I know you want it. Don't eat it
Come on. I know you want to please come on
No
Eat
Just have the hunter bring you the mice. Yeah
Yeah, that's what I probably end up doing
Where's the seed dude I've heard
What is this? Uh
I don't even do a hole a yam. Oh shit
hangy
There is nuts
You hit him he gives you seeds
Yeah, but he also gives you bad shit too. I remember this from last time
Once I get the animals I want remember this is this is this is the setup
Once I get the animals I want we're gonna make a bunch of garden shit. We're gonna make a bunch of fertilizing
It'd be great. Just need to I want the animals that I want in here first snakes ducks
and geckos
Maybe some frog
maybe
All right. Did you finish it?
What does a mouse house look like?
Oh, that's that's just adorable
Now that is just adorable
Yam coming up
Hey
You're just still here code. I'm sorry, but you gotta go
I'm sorry. I mean it was just it was just not that what am I supposed to do about that? There's nothing there
This whole again get out of here
Bluebell should I water?
Play doom
It's doing what it's doing good. It's doing good. Should I play doom like eventually here?
Is that like a game I should play on stream? Is it a good game?
Do it on hard mode
Maybe I don't know. I'm probably not
Okay now this is good to go. There's a yam here
I need what is that? Uh, all right, let's go buy a mouse
He's scared of doom
It's a joke if you bad problem if no one else can help and if you can find me
Uh, you did find me
Okay, i'm gretchen the resident hunter. I can find it's not good
But it's gotta be a type that's already resided in your garden. Uh, what's their express and standard?
How long stick to get here?
Holy shit, I can that's a thousand dollars. Never mind standard delivery. I'm a natural born tracker
Does that mean when do I get it?
So
That's stupid it's great
Single player shooting game omega lull
Here we go
There he is
Come here
I i'm reading chat. I'm reading chat. I didn't guys i'm not saying that when he said that in chat
I don't have 12 square panometers of water. What the fuck dude, that's not even possible
How do I get that I have to expand oh you fucking asshole
Why can't somebody just like attack this guy
Is that is that a seed get these seeds get these seeds get these seeds get the seeds
Get tell them get rid of them. They're bad seeds. Get rid of them. No
All right, there he is again. Okay, so I can't even get you over here
How did I press the middle button? I I don't know just did
I don't know
All right. I need a mouse. Where's my mouse delivery?
This chat's full of bots is actually 385 people there. There's only 388 viewers here now
Um type one of your reel see how many people do it. Okay, that's that's definitely more than 388 people
Where's my mouse delivery? I'm getting impatient
You know
Oh chat bird eat. Oh, oh wait. Wait, wait, wait eats corn. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Here you could eat you could have some corn. I'll just put some corn down here. Sure. Why not?
Apologize for what?
Morning interest you in something seedy. Oh, no, I don't mean like that
You're buying con
Oh, I love con
My grandma used to say it
What do we have for dinner tonight con? Oh, I love con. That's so good. There's three coins here. Come here
The duck is hurt where the duck isn't didn't get hurt it's like stepping on flowers and being a weirdo
I can't choose
More
Hunter caught yes. Oh, what's this thing? That's a new
plant if i've ever seen one
This is a
He's a cool looking. All right, let's put him over here
Don't touch that. Oh, you're gonna get sold
What is this?
I don't so this what is it lily somebody said lily pad. I plant it here
Where should I plant it the watercress? Oh, I put it in the right spot
It's a snow drop. All right
You have new cluckles visitors
All right hunter caught pinata. All right. So where is it in the shop?
Oh
Yo germ man, i'm so high want to hear some hunting stories. All right, cool. Or are you here place it in the garden?
What do you want? What do you want me to do about it?
you
Immunity no, this is not community crack night. Not even close. I can't wait to see you again
You give me the best challenges i've had in years
Community crack night is way more ridiculous than this. This is very very just tame. All right, they need yams. Let's have some romance here
I got a yam right here
try it it's
Oh delicious
I was gonna say multibane, but I mean that's like three years ago at this point. I just gotta move on
Uh, i'm just gonna buy a few yams just buy them. I got money
Bring back multibane. No
I've always got a smile for you as long as you always have chairman moves on from multibane, but not spi
When was the last time you actually heard me say spi not in the context of I don't want to say spi
I'm gonna say spi just to make one person happy
Uh, when was the last time that was a context when we do that and we need yam
Let's start going
Eat yam and then we're gonna see the mouse dance. I can't wait. I am so excited
Eat yam
You eat yam
Wait, did you already eat yam? You have not if you already eat yam
You've not I give you a hundred thousand dollars for the spi voice
Okay
What why would I not do that? You know i'm saying like if you it would be that would be the i'm gonna be honest
I gotta be I gotta tell you just up front that is the not a great use of your money
Not at all. That is not a use of your money a hundred thousand dollars for me to say the word spi
Is uh, just such a bad investment
That's not a good investment. There's so many other things you can do with that money eat this
They're afraid of snakes. Oh because this snake's sleeping here. Hey get go go in here
Get away. They were trying to i'm trying to breed mice
Hey, you two go watercress is drying
How could watercress dry if its head is dunked in water right now, like it just leaned down dude eat this come on
All right. I know you're scared of snakes
Go in the snake house
Let's get water through their roots
It was the one wouldn't the roots be stuck down in there?
Oh, I got a new resident. Here comes a kitty cat, whatever they're called
shnattacat
Be like
Oh shit, they also eat mice
All right. We gotta get we got a good breed in here. What is why does this thing take so much fucking water?
Okay. Now it's time for it's time for
Let's go. Where's the other one? So I can have cats now
Just need like a dozen
uh mice
blind
He's inside the house, isn't he? Let's take a look
They both are just like yeah when we leave we're gonna get eaten
so
What do you want to do on our last night?
Come on out. Let me direct you to the bedroom. Hey, come on out for a second. What is it?
All right. Now go to bed and go in the bedroom
Oh, okay. Leave us the fuck alone, dude
Here we go. Who's going like
Oh, it's you level 11
We once whatever I think you've earned the right to call yourself a skilled
Okay, guys
Good board for growing watercress
Here we go
Wow, a fucking title upgrade. That's fucking amazing. I think it's time to play doom eternal now. Thanks love
You know, we got all the time in the world
like
There are think about this
There are 365 days in a year
like
Four of those days will be played playing doom
So it's like that's
It's okay
Or he's that bad at doom. How long is it? Wait, is it how short is it?
One of these doing too many tricks man. Oh, I got the upper grip for the garden space
Let's make things a bit more interesting
finally
Oh shit nice
That's much bigger
Wait, why are these moving?
floating around
Dude, this is a fucking absolute pogchamp moment. If I see anything else in the chat besides pogchamps
It won't you'll be hearing from my fucking lawyer or something. I don't know
What?
No, that was quick. That was quick
It was like
can't even man
the mice
Who's flying above my who is this? Oh, it's the egg deliveries. Just all right now
Get out of here. Hey, look at this
Let's have oh time for eat another yam
yam
EDM
The yams will produce the children. I want at least 10 to 20 mice
Because we're gonna have snakes that eat them. We're gonna have cats that eat them, too
You're afraid of the snake snake. Just I really should have put you guys on the other side, huh?
Don't go eat him yet. I know he wants to but I don't just don't just eat it
He's not gonna get you. I promise
No, he's not gonna I promise he's not gonna get you just go hang out over here, please
You're scaring them. He won't i'm trying to get he's just still sleeping
What do I do for you? He eats worms now, you know, I mean
Thanks for visiting. You're really interesting. You're really cool
You're not part of the plan
I know where's the other one? All right. Look at the little baby
He's visiting the baby
I just want to say hi. I'm your new neighbor
That was kind of sad this is an onion
You're a goddamn psycho
Okay, i'm cleaning him
True true true
Did you eat the other yam yet? Have you eaten the yam?
Are you guys ready? You are
Here again
Here we go
End of the stream voice
Not yet, but kind of close. I have to get out of here. I've got a lot of shit to do
Trying to put streams in where I can
We'll come back to this tomorrow
Species the challenge will become tougher
No, you don't more heart tokens to collect more hazards. No, i'm not in the process of moving
No, i'm not
I'm just trying to turn this free month because i'm trying to fucking eat a burrito like in the microwave
And i'm gonna sit there and eat it for an extra four hours
I want to take a bath. That's why i'm doing this
Yeah, you caught me. You got you caught me. You caught me. You got the fucking munchies wicked bad, man
Hey jerma, i'm high as fuck right now. There's another all right. You have to eat somebody
So go for it. You can eat whatever you want right now
I'm gonna do more yams
Can I just do it from here? Let's just plant i'm just gonna plant them, right?
No, no, please being hunted
What are you talking about? I have a newt gat visitor. All right, don't get yourself killed
He eats three watercress
Yeah scared of ducks well, i'm sorry i'm not you can't stay here then i'm gonna buy like a bunch more yams in the shop
Does this game suck
No
No, it's actually quite relaxing. Hi there get in get spending then get no only joking take your time
An excellent choice trust. Uh-oh. Well, it's all right. There's still three left
Yeah
That means he's not you're a resident right and now I can breed you two
Wait, and where's the other one? You're over here somewhere
fair
Eat are you a resident yet?
Yeah
Okay, now mate
Actually, not yet
I want at least like
five or six mice
What does it take to mate you two need oh shit he's eaten one roe bean
So
Why am I making all these mice
I'm making mice for no reason then for the cats, I guess
Well, then I don't want to have that many
All right. You guys ready to romance
You're afraid of frogs, too
You got you afraid of everything
You're afraid of frogs. You're afraid of snakes
I'm about to fucking launch these guys into a cannon. What do you think?
You're still not ready yet
All right, I can do more water and more sand because I just got this upgrade
Let's do some water over here
And you're scared of mice
The synergy here is not really that great. I've done kind of completely wrong, but it's okay
nice
It's all water i think you might have a problem
And you're out of being hunted stop that did you just lick him leave him alone
You're oh you're right here here. Are you stuck in here? You're stuck, aren't you?
Oh you dumbass
Go on get out
Mouse island. Well, we just need enough to have
So there's another snake very
Good thing they are mating because here comes another one
Every time I make a new mouse they just get eaten and killed by a snake that then becomes a resident
Whatever. All right, let's go
Bad no, I can't
I can get this one
Don't even fucking risk it. I'm just too terrible
All right new resident. So that means I have three there's a lot of snakes. Where do I get these raw beans?
Uh-oh, it's our sherbet. Can I get a um
apple seed yet for the
Okay
You still not a resident?
No, you're you're a resident, right?
All right, where'd you drop the seeds?
I don't know planet
What is it
Uh, whatever
Garlic what's wrong with you? Oh send him into the
Cannon send him into the cannon, right?
Send him into the cannon rare. Where is he? Where is this? Where is he? There he is into the cannon
Kenyatta sent to party get a lot of experience with doing that, huh?
Almost a 60 of a whole level this is left two mice, right? Yeah. No, wait, it's only two left
The selector is kind of finicky. It's like almost like it doesn't want to attach the things that you're near
I'm just like goes by them
It's finicky
Go to the tinkerer with a pumpkin
Uh, I think the pumpkin that pumpkin gone. Oh, there it is. Go to the tinkerer with a pumpkin
Should I just throw it over there? How do I take how what do I do? Are you good to go?
Well, get up and eat that yam
Hmm, this is ladybug
Oh, no, it's just a toad
The hell what what is going on? What's wrong with you?
Wait, what what's wrong with this thing? Oh
Okay
They do that, right? I don't want the birds
Fuck I gotta go. I gotta go. I gotta go but I don't wanna but I gotta
I'll be back tomorrow
This is so inefficient. It's unbelievable. It's like the most inefficient thing ever
I'm not even gonna get a coin bonus good
Fine, just leave
Don't worry. I'll be back tomorrow
And the next day don't worry. I do want to I do want to do a few things though
I need
All right. I got three snakes two ducks one frog. Let's take inventory
What's the thing on the top right?
Pepe hands just go get out of here. I'm not yet. Hold on just go pepe hands
Just go get out of here already eat fucking leave
Oh, hey
Mate
Okay, that's it. I'm not doing any more mating with the mice
Now I just want to make sure that there's enough water
You're not going anywhere. Okay, what's the efficient way to do this?
It's to go
left side
I don't know like this
Who said I wasn't gonna get it? Who said I want to know who said it? This is a fucking yam. Let's see
Sell this yam too. I don't fucking want it
All right
Now let's get a couple seeds
Let's do some more water
Up there in the corner like I wanted and then let's do some water on the left for the ducks
What is this this thing fucked up looking?
Is it it's a chili, ooh
Just leave leave i'm i'm fine
I got like 10 minutes
I got 10 minutes
Hey, this guy's using that water. That's not that's not you can't use that water. You gotta live here
That's right. Get in here and live here. All right, we can send that mouse into a cannon move
Okay, that's all right. And then i'm gonna do the front of the duck house
over here
I can still hear him. It's like he never left
It's like he's still here pond city
Hot mic hot mic hot mic. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
All right. That looks good for now. We'll pick up tomorrow
Around the same time we'll pick it up tomorrow. Thank you for joining me everybody
On this weekend of short streams. We'll see you tomorrow
Just make sure it looks all right. It looks awful
But you know, wait, I can connect it down here
Oh, that looks a little better. That's much better
Why is fill pond and dig pond the same button? It's gonna be a different button angry to fucking kids game
Holy shit. Jeremy. It's like this game was made
It's not a penis it's a penis sad face
Feels bad, man. It's a penis
This is not a penis
Okay, it's not why are you doing sad face about that? I I don't you guys like that you guys think that like
Penis humor is hysterical to you guys. I thought
it is
Batman
It is I think it's very funny. What is points? Oh, that's cool
All right. That looks all right. I can this is over here is a kind of a disaster, but we'll pick we'll get it
We'll fix it
Come on. It's just random water. No, we're gonna do we're gonna change this. We're gonna patch this up
All right. I gotta go. I actually really do I have to leave
Doing what I can fill in
What I say three or four hours there. There you go
All right. I'll see you tomorrow
Let's wrap this up. Let's hang out for a little bit and do the bits
Please scram get out of here. No, not you. Let's keep this music on. All right
Uh, wait, how do I save the game? That's very important. It just auto saves, right?
There we go. Are you sure you want to save and quit? Yes
Do I have a profile? Yes, I do
When would the uh gift or highest tip bit leader work? Never probably never
I hope your data gets corrupted. Holy shit
God, what the hell?
What the hell man?
Why?
Because then he can play doom
Hmm. I mean that's
Well, no what we would actually be playing no more heroes or a beautiful joe wouldn't go right to doom
All right, let's do the bits and the subs and everything only about four hours. So
Should go through this pretty quickly
We had ten dollars from lm man. Thanks for the ten buck germa
If you were if you were a pinata interview pinata, what kind of pinata would you be?
Um, I would just be one of the seeds
You just plant me in the ground and just make sure I have enough water
And just sit there and i'll be fine
Uh, thanks for a thousand bits though
Pixelated cabbage. Thanks for the four 150 bits. Love them streams germ man. Good luck with the move. Thanks a lot
Appreciate that. Thank you
It is going uh lm man again. Thanks for the 500 bits kiss mary kill
uh
Drew crew moo crew or the wink dinks
Uh, all right
I don't I flee the country
um
You can't uh, all right. I vote the murius
It's just it's like so cute. I would give I would here. I like kiss otto's head. So I would kiss the move kiss murius
Uh, I would marry the drew crew
Because the drew crew is just so so incredibly passionate. They are so dedicated
They're incredibly loyal. So that makes sense
and I would go the wink dinks would be uh eliminated because it um
I I wouldn't they would just be I would not hang out with them anymore. It's okay
That's based
No, I don't even I I
All right. I I did I answered I answered your fucked up question ocean dweller
Thanks for 250 jeremy's garden when you're here your family that stole that from me
And I immediately gave you credit for it five seconds later. So it's not stealing. It was an attribution
Uh fire rossi. Thanks for the 600 bits
Thank you for admitting how much fun stuffed animals are because my dad always calls me a furry
or a
Flasho pildiac for liking them. First of all, thank you for the charm of the fun
Um, no, you're not a furry if you like no, excuse me. I gotta correct this
You're not a furry if you like
Uh vivi pinata because this is you taking care of animals. This is not you
Pretending to be the animals on screen. I'm taking care of these animals
I'm not pretending to be the animal on the screen. You know what i'm saying?
I mean wrong
Like if I was in the chair and I made that frog and that frog was supposed to be me
Then okay, that's like okay. I'm I'm that's me. That's my fursona, right?
For my understanding i'm taking I am a farmer. I'm taking care of aunt. I'm a farmer like a shelter or whatever
There you go. Sorry. I had to correct that. Hey, jamie. Thanks for the 500 bits
Hey german today is my 24th birthday and your return is one of the best presents
I could have ever asked for hope you and the others are staying safe in these scary times you as well
Stay safe. Happy birthday. Happy 24th birthday jamie. Thanks for the 500 bits. Happy birthday
Thank you
He's doing it on a kazoo
Hey trance goat. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey germa. Have you ever played graffiti kingdom?
I remember being really weird when I played it as a kid
You might like how wacky it is. Good luck with the rest of your move. Thanks a lot
Graffiti kingdom i've never played
Kingdom is
Oh, it's old this old game, huh?
playstation 2
What do you do?
It's pretty good
Do you read these or did I just waste 1200 bubble shirts?
Um, I well that answers your question
You draw your own character. Okay. Well, that's all I need to know put it on the list
Thanks to the 500 bits
Uh, where's my keys? Thanks for the thousand bits. Please do a chocolate factory stream germa. Thanks for being uh,
one of the one guys to um
Make that stream happen and I it will happen. I just can't say that'll happen now because obviously of
All the coronavirus stuff. I'm not sure that would be possible
We'll see though
Thank you apple shift for the 250. Hey, oh, when will the next community content night be?
Yes, welcome back
Sort of welcome back sort of not here at 100 yet
uh
april
april 5th
April 5th will be the next community content night sunday april 5th
What year?
There you go. Hey peaceful hailey. Thanks for the 250. Hey germa. Hope all is well. Hope the move goes well
I know the world is in shit right now
And it makes it hard to do anything. Hope all this passes soon. Also i'm happy you're playing at viva people happy
Me too. It's a really fun chill game
Yeah, we're taking we're taking it slow and we need to kind of
Get to where we need to be
And do it slow
at a good pace
but slow enough where we can actually get stuff done and
To work around some of the companies that
Um have some coronavirus uh restrictions. So we're taking it slow, but thanks for the 250
Uh, stay safe
kill kilk run or kill
kilk run
Thanks for the threat. I don't know. I couldn't read that. Thanks for 300 bits germa
What about rain world? You completely forgot about it. Please play more. It's a good and slugcat is cute. Please play more
It's a good game pepe hands
What do I do now?
We cross the threshold
Those of you that don't know some of you new viewers don't know what the threshold is and that's a huge quote
The threshold is I play a game
And I say yeah, I might go back to this
Uh, maybe like uh, maybe next week or something. Uh, and two weeks go by
After the 14th day
You've passed the threshold on if i'm gonna go back and play it. So
We've passed it
holo night pepe hands
DOS games, no
Fucking pepe hands
Sir's wrath dlc. Oh pepe hands
He promised to play half-life alex
Well
Put your pepe hands down for a second on that one. I want to play that I want to play vr
There's like so many good vr games that just can't physically do it right now. That's not a pepe hand scenario
That's a you wait and see scenario. We didn't pass the threshold on that one. I'm still there
Sit down and play alex
I think the the device on my head
Because it's kind of heavy and annoying. I feel like that's gonna put pressure down on me. I
Very soon here i'm gonna have some actual real answers for what i'm doing with my life
in regards to my medical stuff
so
We'll cross that bridge soon reason for the short stream. Yes, the next few streams will be like this
because
Right after I turn this off
I'm going back to the moving process
I just wanted to make sure that I didn't not stream
potentially like a full week or two straight
Because I do want to stream I want to hang out and play games and just chill and dick around I love doing it
So anytime I can put some time in and do what I want to so
He just wants to eat a burrito. Shh
Say that
He's gonna move from his stream computer to his bed
He's just gonna sit in the chair till four pacific. Oh my god
Anyways dark soul, thanks for the 250 tonight
I learned that trying to fake vr with resident evil 2 first person and vore px makes you instantly sick
Never try that shit
Also, when are you going to collaborate with someone from hollow live? You've already said ayaya
So you may as well. I have no idea what that is
If you said I will give you a million dollars if you tell me what hollow live is
Um, I would not get the million dollars. I would cry and go home and be like how the fuck
I don't know what that is
No, and I said the word. Yeah, whatever
He said it get him obstinare wall lover
Thanks to the 278 bits. Do you prefer 2k 14 wwe or 2k 15 to 2k 20 creative?
He's doing emote contest
Uh, everything after 2k 14 is absolute absolute dog shit
They just pulled the rug out from underneath the creative process that that game had after 2k 14
2k 15 all the way to now it's just been utter dog shit just dog shit
They cared more about having a realistic fucking sports simulation than having fun characters fight each other in a ring
That's what happened. That is just what happened when the companies changed over the the new company that took it over was like
Let's make this a sports game
And it was the biggest mistake that they ever made and from my understanding now the last one they made
Was an absolute total fucking joke of a video game. It was riddled with just awful bugs
No new features. It was a piece of dog shit from what i've heard
Um, so it did it did it turned into it turned into like the like a madden or like an mlb 2k fucking 20
But they just release a roster update and uh tweak the fucking fighting mechanic. He's so passionate about this
Yeah, I am because that's one of my favorite things on earth was making characters
In wrestling games and making them fight each other. I've been doing this shit since I was like fucking 13
Oh, I mean I could we could sit here with I could sit up
Grab a fucking cup of coffee right now and sit here for two hours
And talk to you about how much of a how much of a fucking injustice this is
I would sit here for like an hour straight. Anyways, uh, it was a big mistake
And I don't know who was responsible for that
There's a lot of people a lot of moving parts in that
where
Making it a more realistic sports kind of game rather than
Look, you're making a bunch of crazy monsters and you're doing fighting and CPUs are fighting each other in the ring
I don't know, but they've been stripping pieces of it for the last five years
I would do 2k 14. I would play it and I would continue to make characters and do rumbles on it
But it's so old at this point
It takes forever to do fucking anything in that engine
If you have more than five ten fifteen layers five layers on a character and you're painting on their face with something
You'll you'll press the button to do a circle and wait four straight seconds for the game to load the circle
It's just it's just old at this point on old hardware is not
It's just I can't I could never go back into that again. Wait for that new aew game. We'll see we'll see what happens
I know that um, was it yukes?
Didn't yukes broke off completely and was like fuck this we want to make our own video game from my from my understanding
That's in big quotes yukes was like this is boring the fuck out of us
Uh, we need to creatively
Re-imagine the series a little bit for ourselves and we want to make another game. That's a wrestling game
That's what i've heard
That's very encouraging because let's hope that they actually make something fun
I wish them the absolute best of luck and all the support and I hope they're passionate and I hope they make something good
That's all I can do but moving on uh, thank you
Nv11 casting for the 250 remember yesterday was my 21st birthday and it was pretty stressful
I can think of no better birthday gift than my favorite streamer. This is in all capitals singing
Happy birthday as poorly as possible jokes. Oh, it's a joke. It was a joke
They say jokes aside, uh, you don't have to sing if you don't want to look at that
But i'd appreciate any beverage suggestions you might have thanks for the laughs. I got one for you
Uh sprite a little bit of cranberry juice squeeze the lime happy
the rest
Happy birthday. Hey trans scout. Thanks for the 500 bits. I'm playing
I'm planning on getting two rats next semester and i'm in the process coming up with names. Do you have any suggestions?
Um, yeah black and blue, you know
Like is that because they fucking pray at night and they fucking stalk at night those are shit names like they're bruisers
Yeah to the two bruisers you have to try try harder. I like those names try what do you mean?
Try harder spaghetti and meatballs. That's way worse than what I said
If you name don't name any of your animals fart fart. That's such a bad. What a terrible name
Don't know. I can't believe people are laughing at that like give me a frank guys
Really my well my my cat's name is art
Okay
You wouldn't think that was real
But if it was that's actually kind of funny that it is real because it's such a that's such a rotten
awful terrible name
That if you just saw like fart the cat lying down on the windowsill or something just sitting there with his eyes closed
Like holy shit, that is the cat's name
That's such a bad name don't name your cat art thanks for the 500 bits
Uh scruffle. Thanks for the 400 bits cough cough. I don't know. I don't understand. This is why you coughing
Did I say are you like trying to tell me something like hey, uh, excuse me
What did I do? What did I say?
Tar alacran, thanks for the 250 bits. I doubted that you would stream this weekend. I was gravely in error
However, i'm a man of my word and gave you permission to ban me if you streamed and chat must have their ban
I throw myself at the mercy of you and chat and ask that you commute my sentence
From a lifetime lifetime ban to only a ban for a week. I swear. I will be a reform chatter who never doubts the streamer
Yes, man. No mercy thumbs down thumbs
What do you mean? I actually did it?
What do you mean?
We have to have justice. It's like oh sire. I'm so sorry
Yes, I threw a javelin through your window and skimmed your forehead
And was trying to kill you. I was trying to murder you sire
But please just know
That fuck you and I die hate you but I am willing for you to drop me into the pit of the lions
But just know that I only expect to be in there for a day
And if I can make it a day then I want you to release me
So you don't make the terms
It seems your terms
Are unacceptable that was a convoluted example
It'll be back in i'll i'll unban them tomorrow. It's fine. I'll put my hand down to the fucking lion pit
And i'll be like, i'm just kidding. It was a joke. Let me see your
And then my hand gets fucking ripped off
Ah, it turns out hubris is the real killer
Anyways, what what what what happened? I just banned somebody for like, yeah. Oh, okay. I'll unban them tomorrow. I'll probably forget
I probably guys i've like told you that I was playing a certain game like tomorrow and I don't play it
So if i'm gonna forget about what i'm even streaming tomorrow, you think i'm gonna remember unbanning this guy?
I'm gonna forget i'm gonna forget forever
Okay, one of the mods unban tara alecran as of tomorrow at 7 32 pm specific standard time
I have a ban log. Okay
And I did ban the right person. There was no misspelling there. I didn't like add it
I had like an extra c or something. Hey goo berry juice
Thanks to the 250 I doubted that you would stream this weekend. I was gravely in error
However, i'm a man of my word and gave you permission to ban me if you streamed chat must have their ban
I throw wait, why is another person saying this just banned that guy too
You just you killed that you banned the wrong guy
All right, that was goo berry juice
Okay, by the way, just i'll give you another convoluted fucked up messed up like go around in five circles example
If there's a guy in front of you
And he's robbed a bank
Okay, and he's got a bag of money
And he's like I gotta get out of here
I just robbed the fucking bank and like money is flying out of his the bag and he's running down the street and he's like
Cops everywhere. You're just watching this happen
Don't um, don't run after that guy
And chant that you're also robbing the bank at the same time like me too. I'm robbing the bank too
Yeah, we both together. We're both robbing the bank together
I don't think you should do that. You're gonna get you're gonna get arrested
Uh, because that's just what happened and i've got him i've got justice has to be served
You don't want to you don't want to participate in that
I'm just saying hey grave embrace. Thanks for 250
I streamed doom for 14 and a half hours. I would say it's pretty good, but look out for the glitches
Some bosses have invincibility mechanics that depend on range, but doesn't properly gauge the range other than that
It's a whoa. That sounds terrible. Can't wait to not play that terrible fucking game
Wow, maybe there's a bug. It's a small like glitch or something. Get that off my list
I want nothing to do with it. I am I am appalled
And and offended that it would be released in a state like that
I want nothing to do with that shot. Why would I stream it? Yeah, thank you
Why would I stream that game god if i'm yelling thinking i've been playing on my own time
So i'm i'm not gonna stream it. No. Hey goiki. Thanks for the 500 bits
Attention streamer. I hope the move and everything went well happy to have you back even as for short streams turn my heart attention streamer over
Thanks. Why is he so mad?
I'm not i'm not even fucking mad. Oh shit. I gotta quickly quickly quick quick quick quick
Oh, hey there they are let's roll the credits here come the subs. Thanks for the subs you guys all of you appreciate it
I've been gone for a while
And you'll see me in little bits and pieces here over the next few days
While I continue to get this all done
I really appreciate it. Thank you for your patience
because
I know that a lot of people right now are
Kind of just in their houses looking for something to do and i'm kind of the same way
So I would love to be here just I have to get this done
I'll see you tomorrow. We'll keep going with uh
viva piñata travel in paradise
Thanks for the support all of you
There's a piñata in the corner
It might be
Thanks for the subs. We have some bits to do left. There's still a little bit left. We have rtx 4 20 69 ti
Eventually, they'll have to have that number although just skip it because they're too embarrassed to have it
Uh, thanks for the 250. Hey germs
I went shopping recently and I realized that germa raptor is incorrect and inaccurate. I don't understand
Germa raptor is incorrect and inaccurate
Because you went shopping
I don't get it. He's a fake
Oh, and they say there's another here's another 250. Oops. I did my bits early. Here's what I meant to say germa raptor is inaccurate
Oh, I see
Okay, so that's the yeah. Well, what?
That's right, they look the same
Of raptor faces of whatever
It's not it's a diet. Uh, really gonna you're gonna throw me under the bus here. Look
That's a raptor. It's not a raptor. That's et
look at
Jurassic world tyrannosaurus rex. Jurassic world velociraptor mass
Can I just tell you something?
Let's go
five stars
There are 519 ratings and this thing people love this shit
Look at those reviews
Why are there so many people getting the velociraptor one? The t-rex one has 10 reviews and the velociraptor one is 500
But what's with people don't want the t-rex one. Why?
Because it's a sans raptor
Okay, you and like 16 other people know what that is the people buying these toys don't care that this is a sans raptor
Why does everything have to be said? It's like and I see it too. Why is everything I
Hey reaper 500 thanks, but the 250 hey germ boy minister convinced chat to stop to shop
To stop asking you to show something if you use your germ powers to stop this
Endemic, I wish I could I would I would love to have this all go away
Uh, I i'm not gonna say the thing you want to be saying because that makes that means people will
Say it over and over again and never stop saying it
The more you talk about things like this the more the people go i'm gonna say let me say that
So, uh, no not blt. We're we've got we're over that already and I just said it. I just fucked it all up
Um, I had to tell okay gnarly. Thanks for the 250. Good luck on the move david. Thanks a lot. That is my name
It's david
Thank you for the 250 ruined blood line. Thanks to the 250 germa
Why are you hiding the fact is you're a furry?
And a sleeper agent for the dru crew
Uh, because I i've invested in the dru crew
I bought the fucking dru crew super pack
Which has like 35 games in it. I have a very vested interest
Play more of it then I know I buy
That's that's
That's like last resort streams. You have to you have to understand that's like
Oh, no, there is nothing left for me to do. That sounds bad
Those are great games to have when it's like
Oh the thing that we're doing turns out sucked or really wasn't fun at all
I have nothing else to do and I don't have any plan and I have nothing set up
I okay. Will it open up nancy dru?
Apocalypse stream. Yeah
Those are excuses as a last resort
Yeah, uh dru crew is not my first choice
For what I want to do on a day-to-day basis. It was
It was
I mean it was
Was it was
Those you yeah, you said you would marry them
Rain world is second to dru crew
What do you want me to tell you? What do you what do you what do you want from me? Hey, okay?
Uh, no, thank you. Oh kage
Oh kagesha
Doh
Oh, it's hard for me to read this name because it's all in lowercase and I don't have there it is okay
Okay, okay shadow king
Thanks for the 300 bits. I'm fucking stupid. Hi gerber. Really love your streams
They've been a good way to find happiness in the current hell. We are all in
Would you ever play a disgaea game? Probably not probably no. Yeah, where the wink thinkers at sad face
I don't think there are any there's not very many anymore
I don't think there's very many wink thinkers. I think they never was very many wink thinkers to begin with
You had some bandwagon wink thinkers that kind of jumped off after links went away and
I can't even read that. You're fucking crazy
Hey morning maple. Thanks for the 250. Hey gerber before I forget
There's a game you can get on the pc and switch and think you enjoy called
pico nico
It's a short physics based puzzle exploration game. I think it'd be worth streaming because it could be beaten in just one stream or two
If you play your cards, right?
The humor can be a bit lol. So random and there's a cringy meme or two in there
But the gameplay is consistently fun is the trailer. Good luck with the boob lol. So random. Okay, i'll give this trailer 10 seconds
It looks all right. It looks all right sour, please
floygan 2
Show us
I don't want to show you guys
I don't want you to see I don't want to wait you you want to see what like a stream could be
I want you to be surprised
He's too lazy to put the browser source on and resize the window to youtube
He's a toxic streamer. I'm not a fucking toxic streamer. What the fuck are you talking about?
And finally we have uh 250
From jason. Thank you jason
Here's the person you're supposed to ban for life. I already did
This is uh, this is tar tar alec for they've been banned. They did they says but they said they said
Here's this and I quote
The odds that germa manages to move to a new house set up internet properly find the motivation to stream is less than zero percent
If germa streams a real stream next saturday, I give him permission to personally ban me for life
That's the right guy. Yeah, it is. It's the right guy
You didn't move though
I mean, I mean look i'm in the process of moving
That's why I had I took the last like four or five days off
It's a process
What do you mean it doesn't count you didn't move and didn't stream a full stream
um
Four hours. All right, four four and a half hours. That's a stream
If this was like two hours, okay, I'd understand if this is like
2016 two-hour stream germa sure
Four four and a half five that's four and a half. That's a stream. All right, that's a stream
He still didn't move I bet assumed you'd be in a new place and you're not
They're only banned for one day. It's okay. It'll
What constitutes yeah, what what constitutes a full stream
What when it when it what is it? What is a full stream?
It has to be
six hours
eight hours
At least six hours six to eight hours at least 24
Six minimum six minimum
minimum
Six to eight. Yeah, six to eight is all right. That's a full stream. Yeah. All right. We're doing small condensed ones
I typically do six to eight. All right
Okay
All right. Yeah, you got you. All right. I didn't sorry
I didn't know everybody every single person in chat here is tar alacran's fucking lawyer
The ban will be removed just doing my civic duty
Oh, you see my client said full stream and germa 985 a typical full stream from germa
985 is presumably anywhere between six and eight hours sometimes even longer than that your honor
And you tell me this man comes in on a saturday after not streaming for four or five straight days
And only turns the stream on for about four to five hours
And says specifically in the beginning of said stream that this is not a real stream that these are going to be shorter
Streams that are not going to be typical your honor. You should throw the book at him
not at my client at germa and
And it's not aim for his chest aim for his shoulder. All right, let me see if I get
Uh, all right missed completely
I mean, I mean I hit the wall like 40 feet away. I look I i've i've thrown a fucking ball in a long time
Mr. Albertson. Yeah, sorry. I was there was a noise 40 feet over here. I know
Yeah, well i'm trying to do something funny for somebody
Mr. Albertson, you are hereby named guilty for
banning
Let me see tar alacran for life
Uh, that ban will be removed will be reversed under the order of the court. Have a good day. I've made my decision
What what the fuck are you fucking what the fuck you're kidding me. Oh, oh the fuck man. No, no
What the we all leave the courtroom. What was the other guy's name? They've both been on bed
This is corruption
Move no move
I'll see you tomorrow
Good night. Goodbye. I gotta go. See you soon. Goodbye. Good night