All right, so what's the plan? PC gaming show trailers? What were the trailers that were worth
watching? Play Five Nights at Freddy's VR. I could probably, okay, instead of a top five list of
things to do, I'll give you a top five list of things I'm not going to do, and that's number
one. Okay, um, let me see what are some of the trailers that I missed from earlier. Let's see,
PC gaming show. PC gaming show trailers. Let's just put, maybe there's a compilation. Anybody,
is there a compilation? I didn't see any of it. I heard that like Terraria broke or something,
right? Play Uno. I'm not going to play Uno. Oh, is it like a site that has it all? Oh,
geez. Okay. Uh, oh God, there's a ton of random shit on this website, huh?
Play Uno. I don't even, I don't know how to play Uno. I've never played Uno before,
maybe twice in my whole life. Play Just Dance. Man Eater. All right, hold on. Wait, wait, I'm
messing this up myself. I gotta get this on screen and we'll go through it together.
So I just click on one of these and then we just, we go. Oh shit, this is pretty nifty.
This is a cool website. The tweet, no, I saw the tweet. I talked about it already.
I have talked about the tweet already. It's like from like this worst joke from yesterday,
but it's all right. Let me do this and get this on screen and then we start interacting with it.
Did it work? Hey, look at that. So now I should be able to do this, right?
So this is from, can I not? Oh shit. Oh, Ray-Ban. I fucked it up. Watch myself
watching the conference. No, this is, I don't, let's move on from this. What am I going to open
right now? I don't, it didn't have any plan. Okay. Actually, I can do this. This'll work. This'll
work. This'll work. I got it. I got it. I got it. Everyone, everyone can relax. I got it. There
it is. You see it? You can see that, right? Oh, there we go. I don't know why that wasn't
working before. Everything's under control. Hey, this ain't my first rodeo. Okay. This
needs to be moved a little. I don't know why. What the hell are you doing? Fuck it.
Whatever. Whatever. All right. So let's go back here. So I, this is the midnight ghost
hunt. This is just from earlier today, right? Shave your head on stream. I don't think I will.
All right. Let's try midnight. You guys want, you guys want to decide what trailer I watch?
I'm going to just watch them. There's no like pick which one I'm going to watch. Midnight
ghost hunt. Here we go. Wait, you get to like haunt objects.
This is prop hunt. It's actually prop hunt.
Somebody decided to finally make a game about this six years later.
Oh my God. That's unbelievable actually that it took this long. People still play this?
Yeah. Sign up for the alpha. More videos. Well, we don't need more videos. Wait, there's more.
Something like this could be really, people could get really, really into. Okay. That's that
one. That was midnight ghost hunt. Seems pretty fun. If you like prop hunt, you probably like
that one. Unexplored to the Wayfarer's legacy. Is this a VR game? Let us click. Are you guys
going to riot in here? Is that what's going to happen? You're just freaking out about this.
I took away these privileges for a very specific reason because people were being very,
very inappropriate with me. All right. Don't make me take it away again.
By the way, I'm going to skip things that I don't really care that much about
because I get my, you know, I get to look for, I'm going to give you, for instance,
I don't really, I don't care about mutants year zero. So I'm not going to click it.
So just be aware of that. I'm not going to watch it because I don't really, that doesn't,
I'm not into it. I can, it's like a, I got a TV channel changer in the hand of my remote.
All right. Fine. Go ahead. Go away from me. I'm going to have watched that one anyways.
I'm like, what's the, okay. Let me be honest with you here. What's the point of the smart
clicks? If one, two, three, four, five, six, it's like spread out. I'm going to
watch them all except for mutant year zero. Wait, there's another page. Oh Jesus.
Uh, well, we already did this. I saw this. I'm just going to watch them all. I'm just,
okay. I'm going to watch the ones that I don't know anything about. You ready?
All right. So I watched Terraria because you guys picked Terraria and then I'll show you.
Ready? Interested in this one. All right. I already know what that one is. Uh, I don't
play into the gungeon, but probably fun. Not going to be watching that one. So we got one
carrying. I'll watch this one. Messenger picnic panic. I don't know what it is.
Looks interesting. Maybe I'll watch it. My friend, Pedro, I guess I'll watch that one.
Borderlands two DLC. I have no interest of watching this. So no, uh, the final fantasy
seven remake. Sure. Destroy all humans. Already saw it. I already logged before E3.
Let's start with, uh, Terraria though, because everyone wants to see Terraria.
Where, where is it? What the fuck is that? What is that? All right. Um, what is that?
I got to go back to page one to click on Terraria. Terraria,
let's see what it is. Is this expansion? Terraria was really cool. My only problem with Terraria was
I was kind of overwhelmed because they added so much shit to it.
Would this be a good time to start playing it? Or is it just adding a ton more stuff?
Like, see what I mean? Look, look at all this stuff. Looks pretty cool.
Master mode. Look at this. Looks just so fun and so interesting. This is someone's bosses
and this is very overwhelming game though. You can fly kites. That's awesome. Coming 2019. Okay.
That looks good. All right. What the hell is meat fortress meat fortress with the gracious
permission of valve. Oh, it's a, okay. Hot dogs, horses, hand grenades update.
We can use all the TF2 items. I'll play this when it comes out. Definitely.
Three meaty modes of mayhem. I might as well try it. You actually have to load this sniper.
I would try it. That's so cool. That is really fucking cool. That's soon too. That's like,
what, what, when is that? Is that like in a week or two? Dog two, dog two, dog two, dog two.
What's dog two? Why is everyone saying dog two? Dog two? Where is it? Dog two. Where was dog one?
I don't remember playing dog one. Dog two. No, I know. We already saw this. Dog two. Oh,
it's a raid. Oh God. Joel coming in with a raid. Happy, happy E3 everybody. Dog two. That's
what we say here. This website is 2019.e3recap.com. Pretty cool. You can see every trailer. It's all
there right for you. I hope you had a good stream, Joel. Thanks for the raid. The shitloader you
just dropped in. I did not see any of the PC gaming conference, so we're going to take that
time to look at it now. And we're, where, where, where, where, where were we? Dog one?
Were we dog one? All right. So, uh, where are we? I don't, I don't, I already know, but fall guys.
Let's take, let's do fall guys. Is this de blob? Why does this look like this? 87 fall guys in
the main. This looks, this is like de blob. Oh, they got a turkey. That's an instant
vibe for me. Is it like Lemmings? What, you got like a hundred people and you got to get through?
Or is it like a massive multiplayer? Everybody jumped from, well, it's a death run. Okay.
How many people can play at the same time? All right. Uh, this looks fucking cool. I'm
excited about this. A hundred people. All right. I'm going to play the hell out of this.
I am absolutely going to play this. That looks awesome. That's like a BR,
but a BR that I would actually enjoy playing. Chivalry two. All right. So that was fall guys.
I don't need to see that. Uh, I don't play under the gungeon, so we're going to veto that
one. I don't really, I don't really know what any of this even means because I don't play it.
Uh, what is this carrying? I was going to say hell and then fuck at the same time. So it was
like, what the fuck? Shit. Do you just grow as a parasite? That looks, why do these games
all look better than any of the games I saw already? Why is the PC gaming stuff cooler than
guy with backpack on five times? Wait, gungeon is, it's not, and it is like a,
this is not DLC for the dungeon. It's a light gun game. Oh man. I'm going to destroy this.
Do I have to buy the cabinet?
You have to buy this. I have to buy the cabinet coming exclusively to arcades.
How is it? Oh, what? I got, I got a tax write off coming up here soon.
That's really awesome. It's too bad that it's only in arcades. I would love to play that.
So that was here. Should I click this? We're right here. Release date trailer. Let's see.
This is embark on a perfect ninja vacation. You can pre-order one for five grand.
That's a $5,000 joke that I'm not sure I actually want to do.
All that. Bosses. Yeah, I mean, it's cool. It's cool. But is it, I don't know if I would buy it
because it's not like kind of the kind of game that I would play, but it looks good.
Not sure what's going on down there. You in trouble? Not sure. Bone works? Yeah,
we'll get to it. We'll get to it. Hold on. I'm just browsing through. Don't need to see
this. I already saw this trailer before, so I don't really need to see it again.
Final Fantasy VII Remake. I already, I don't like it. Do I really need to? Is Cat Sith in
this trailer? Otherwise, I don't even want to click it. Like, is Cat Sith in the trailer?
No. Then, then fuck it. I already saw this one. The Legend of Heroes II. No, not interested.
Persona 5 Royale. Oh, I have, hold on. Hold on a second. I need to, I gotta see this shit.
Persona 5 Royale. Like, this is a Battle Royale Persona 5 game. They have like four
different Persona 5s. There's like Persona 5 Dancing, Persona 5 The Game, Persona 5 Starlight.
This is a long trailer. Do I need to know the story to care about this? All I know is that
the Joker is in Super Smash Bros. the new one. Stop watching anime on stream. I'm gonna get
DMCA clenched. I don't care. Like, maybe I would if I played the original game or something. No,
I don't, I just, I don't really care. It's probably, I, Persona 5 Royale, like,
I don't even know what it is. Lord of the Rings Adventure Card Game. I refuse to click it.
Dance Central VR. Dance Central is the hottest club in virtual reality.
It's the hottest club. This is how it starts. This is how they keep you in your room forever.
I want to play this. In addition to practice mode, customizing your avatar,
competitive and cooperative online multiplayer, we have some exciting new features coming to Dance
Central. Playing Dance Central can be a workout. It's definitely a great game for fitness,
so we created the fitness app. And the fitness app allows you to track your calories burn
in real time as well as your stats over time. A huge part of the experience in Dance Central
is dancing with the characters. Currently, your friends can challenge you to beat their scores,
but now the characters are going to challenge you. You think you look really cool in the
game, but in real life, in real life you're doing this. And finally, we're releasing
six songs as DLC. So if you've mastered all 32 on the soundtrack,
no problem. We have more content coming your way. Dance Central is available now for the
Oculus Quest, Quest S, and Rift. So pick it up. Did I get the wrong one? Did I get the
wrong one? Dance Central can be a workout. Can be a workout. I got the vibe and they're
coming out with like the valve is coming out with one. The Oculus is coming out with a new
one. HTC is coming out with like a new one. Did I get the vibe? Did I get the wrong fucking
one? All right. So that was just Dance Central, the soul keeper. I'm into the VR stuff really.
I can't hear either. I just try to turn it up. I've been betrayed.
AMD starts at three Pacific. Really? I better go fucking pee.
All for the sake of evil. I'm supposed to be watching these trailers. What am I doing?
I just peed. Yeah, but I'm pounding coffee like I'm getting paid to do it. Like I'm
getting paid per cup of coffee I'm drinking. Somebody's like, I'll give you 50 bucks for
every fucking large coffee you drink. All right. Thanks, man. Can I use your bathroom?
This looks kind of good. This looks pretty, I like this. You can ride a dragon in VR.
That's puke inducing. I can't wait. I mean, a little bit of some graphical frame issues here.
This looks really slow and chuggy, but as a game, it could be really fun. All right. I mean,
this is a guarantee on the channel game. Guaranteed. Like I'm 100% guaranteed that I
play this state to stay informed. The soul keeper VR. All right. Write that one down
because that's 100% guaranteed to be on the channel. All right. AMD starts in 10 minutes.
Was that, did I get lied to? Or is that, are they doing anything? What are they doing?
Hold on. Let's see. They're just going to show graphics cards. I guess. Should I buy AMD
like stock before this happens? Should I buy some AMD or should I like sell my AMD before
the conference? I don't know. All right. Bone works. People saying bone work. I've heard about
this in the knuckle controllers, right? Yeah. This is going to be completely outrageous. I
can't wait. This is, I can't, I, this is going to be so much fun. Stress levels zero.
I've seen like the developer video on that. That's going to be, that's going to be the
best VR game that's ever come out probably in regards to just usability. All right. So
should, should I get ready for the, can I stream the AMD conference?
Should I do it? Wait, no. Can I? I feel like there's like 7,500 people here. If I can't do
this, they're going to find out. You know, you can't like rob a bank like, and before,
excuse me, I'm telling you, I'm going to tell you, I'm going to call my mother. I'm
going to call the police station first. I'm about to rob the bank down the street just
in case you're wondering. All right. Okay. Okay. Good. That's going to be boring. We'll
make it fun. I'll watch like these trailers as well. I'll watch these, I'll watch the
trailers as we watch the conference. No one cares about AMD. What? All right. Let's
watch the zoo trailer and then I have to go piss out coffee because like that's it.
It just coffee is, I could probably drink the, nevermind and get caffeine. You know
what I was going to say. Uh, where's the planet zoo? I'm eating. I didn't say anything.
I just said, I just made a gesture to my face. We finally have the zoo that I wanted.
The PC gaming conference has every game that I asked for and I didn't even watch it.
No, there's no animal conflict in this, but there's, there's animals. This is going to
be fun. Build a habit for your wildlife planet zoo. Let your animals, alligators.
This is going to be awesome. Really well done. Those animals were very, very well made.
Yeah, that looks good. All right. What was the other one? Give me, okay. Give me the
big ones. Give me the big ones. State DLC. I don't care. Trials rising. Don't really care.
We already saw them anyways. I'm Shenmue three. That's a big songs of conquest.
People were just screaming this as loud as they could. So let's see what this is.
Why do they look like heroes in my magic gold gem thing?
Okay. Is this like a heroes of my magic three re-demake?
Yeah, this is, this is a heroes of my magic re-demake. All right. This is made by the same
people. No, songs of conquest. Closed alpha. It's a spiritual successor or like it's
based on, that's really cool. Played heroes of my magic and all of a sudden here comes a new one
that is based on the original ones. That's cool. All right. What else we got?
Telling lies. I need to see this. I gotta see the telling lies trailer. Explore a stolen
database of what? A private life shattered by a terrible lie. Once upon a time. It's late. I
gotta get her in the bath. I don't love you and I don't miss you. You already know too much.
Is there words to find the truth? It's late. I gotta get her in the bath.
Love you. I love you. What? What? I've only ever been in love once.
That was by the first story? I guess I still carry a torch for
which makes me a curable romantic or underdeveloped emotional. Disciplined emotional?
Did he just wait? Hold on a minute. I'm a loyal. Underdeveloped emotional.
Oh, underdeveloped emotional. That's over here. I'm a loyal friend. I'm up. I'm here.
You're down here. I mean I'm a little bit more put together than you. Telling lies. Yeah,
that was too many people. Yeah, you're right. All right. What was he? A couple of other ones.
There was a few more that were very, very big ones. I'm gonna piss my pants. Oh, why did I drink
so much coffee like an idiot? Devarver bootleg? I already know what it is. That's me trying to
tell you that I haven't watched this trailer but I saw it on the Steam store and I like
know what it is. Hey, no, no, I already know what it is. Notice that I never said I watched
the trailer because that would be a lie and I would end up in a fucking database somewhere
going looking in the camera telling all my fucking dark deepest darkest secrets.
Sadly, forward thinking consumers like yourself should find their way to devolver bootleg.com,
which wholly unironically forwards to a Steam page for devolver bootleg. From there,
potential users will have the opportunity to pay a small fee to download the devolver bootleg
launcher. Once the download is complete, users like you can select from a wide variety
of off-brand versions of our most popular title. Off-brand. Yeah, you can play like
off-brand versions of Hotline Miami and stuff. Enter the gun dungeon. That's cool. I'm gonna
pee my pants. I actually have to get out of here for a second. Dude, I fill myself up with so
much liquid. It's fucking unreal. I'll be right back. When even is the Square Enix
conference? AMD in one second? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's just check in on AMD. AMD. Next Horizon Gaming. Where's AMD's actual stream? Do they
even have one? It's over? No, they what did the guy just get out on stage and like scream
as loud as he can into the mic? All right, hold on. AMD has like an age warning. This
broadcaster has indicated this channel is intended for mature audiences. All right, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Why is it like an M rating? Is this even
working? What the fuck is happening? I have to like click the button in here. See, I told you.
Let's go ahead and get started. Are you ready? We just got here, right? Just right in the nick
of time. Okay, so look, as we just saw in the video, it's all about the porn here. What's
next? Our goal at AMD is to push the envelope on technology. And the entire team is always
asking, what's next? So whether it's what's next in PCs, or what's next in console,
or what's next in the cloud, we're going to show you some really exciting stuff
that just answers that question of what's next. So you've heard me say how much AMD
loves gamers. Why do we care about this? Have you heard me say that? We're gamers.
So we love you. And our goal is to give you exactly what you want. And you know,
fact is, you're the smartest and most demanding tech guys in the world. You're the smart one,
the smartest. Yes, I'm very smart. You expect the best of everything, the highest possible
frame rate, the most incredibly responsive and immersive experiences. And most importantly,
what do you think these days, you want to be able to play and share and have they
announced anything yet across every platform and to deliver that incredible gaming experience,
you actually need two things, breakthrough hardware, hold on, don't announce it yet.
Hold on, I need to put like $40 on AMD. Come on. How much is an AMD? How much is one AMD?
You need these two to really be optimized together to create that next level of gaming
performance. And frankly, you know, sometimes the hardware gets a little ahead. And sometimes
the software gets a little bit ahead. But it hasn't always been in sync. Okay, here we go.
It's $33 for one AMD. What do you think it's going to be worth at the end of this conference?
However, starting now, hopefully not like 12. That would be like a recession.
We have the opportunity together with our partners to bring the best technology has to offer
to gaming across hardware, software and platforms. And that is our vision for gaming.
You like that? So look, it's an incredibly exciting time for gamers everywhere.
Just take a look across all of the most exciting. I just said I wanted to buy one.
I was unsure. It's truly everywhere. Just look at every category of the market,
whether you're talking about PCs, or you're talking about notebooks, or desktops, or Macs,
or game consoles, or cloud, or now I can't, the market's closed partnership between AMD and
You can't buy anything. It's the only reason why I'm on this stream. It closed at four o'clock
Eastern. Closed two hours ago. Oh god, I didn't get any buys in.
Technology, frankly, have to make very big bets. And sometimes you have to make those bets
three to five years out. And this year in 2019, what you're seeing is the results
of some of those big bets that we actually made three to five years ago.
Oh, there goes the yacht. We bet on seven nanometer process technology
for faster and more efficient silicon. We bet on these new engines and these engines are
incredible. Our new Zen 2 CPU core and our new RDNA graphics architecture. And frankly,
we put these things together. Am I the only person streaming this? Am I? Wait, am I the
only person doing this? That's not true. I'm not the only person streaming this.
Fans. So last month, Sony and AMD's gonna come watch.
PlayStation would be built around AMD's new gaming architectures. And we've been working
collaboratively with Sony. Get excited for this. To build a custom chip based on the Zen 2
and the next gen Radeon architectures. And we are incredibly excited to partner with Sony
to enable their vision of the next generation console. Now you also heard recently
that Google announced at this year's Game Developers Conference, Stadia,
its new cloud streaming service. And this is also powered by AMD Radeon GPUs.
Radeon. Keyword. Just say keywords while you watch the conference. Then you're informed.
Exciting. Now let me ask, since we are at a three, how many of you caught the Xbox
event yesterday? Wait, is this actually not allowed? Is there any staff in here?
What you heard from Phil Spencer and the Microsoft team is they announced the next
amazing chapter. There are no staff here to help me. Is this not allowed? It's not allowed.
It's not allowed. It's not allowed. How do I turn it off? Stop fucking with me. Is this
actually not allowed? Why would this not be allowed? Wait. It's a lot, right? It's a lot.
To enable their vision for the future of gaming. So that's a lot of platforms to be excited about.
We're really excited about them, but as excited as we are about those platforms,
and guess what? AMD loves the PC platform. My audience is excited for AMD as well.
So look, for all of you who love PCs and love building your own gaming rigs and love
the best of the best of technology, today is for you. What do you think I got in my computer?
What do you think's in my computer, guys? We're introducing today what I would call the
ultimate gaming platform. Let's take a look. What's in my computer? And we're the only
company in the world that can really bring the best in both CPUs and GPUs. And it's
frankly an incredibly exciting time for us as well as the industry because we're introducing
the brand new third-gen Ryzen desktop processors. I have Intel and Nvidia. And the brand new
Radeon RX 5700 series graphics cards. And what are the specs on it? So I can make sure that
I make $47 on my two buys. All right, let's go ahead and get started with Ryzen, please.
Here we go. Oh my god, are my AMD calls going to be worth any money?
Please be 30% faster than the previous generation. High energy music. The game. Ryzen 3000 series.
What are the specs? That was some, that was like a whoo. Are you guys excited about third-gen
Ryzen? Okay, I have to say the anticipation around third-gen Ryzen is really impressive.
I mean, we were pretty excited at the first-gen Ryzen launch, right?
Weren't those great products? And we actually loved the second-generation Ryzen just as much.
I thought you guys played games on computers. But when I read the comments from you guys and
the anticipation on Reddit or Twitter or across the forums about third-generation Ryzen,
it's truly spectacular to see the excitement in the community. So our goal
is very, very simple. Our goal is to give you the best. The best CPU for every gamer.
And it all starts with the CPU core, the engine. So we are so proud of Zen 2.
Ready? I need, you gotta clip this. Zen 2, our architect, just did an amazing job.
We're watching AMD. It is just incredible engineering.
We might be one of the top AMD screens right now.
I'll just give you a couple. Don't fuck this up for me.
15% instruction for clock uplift. Okay, so.
Double the cache size for lower memory latency.
Double the cache size is pretty good. And double the floating point,
which is really gate for creative work. 15 times two cache size, that's pretty awesome.
And if you think that we're really proud of the Zen 2 engine,
when we bring this over to the product side, it's fantastic.
Just take a look at this stack. Double to double.
Third-gen, it's only 320 bucks? So we are extremely excited about our
third-generation Ryzen 7 and Ryzen 9 stack. And if you think about it.
What? Ryzen 7 processors,
8 cores, 16 threads. We have the new flagship Ryzen 9.
Aren't Intel's like a thousand dollars?
The first 12-core processor for mainstream gamers.
And what you really see here is leadership.
That's pretty awesome. Holy shit.
At every single price point. That was our goal.
That's awesome.
So let me just show you.
Don't fuck this up for me.
A little bit of numbers, okay? Let's just start at the top of the stack.
And see how 3900X stacks up against the competition.
What we're comparing now is the 3900X against the competition's core i9-99.
What do I have?
Which by the way, is a $1200 processor.
What do I got in here?
48, 49?
This is a 12-core to 12-core comparison.
And what you see is that...
No, I don't have a 4900. I have like a 68?
We also win in multi-threaded performance.
And all of this...
They're winning.
Is at 105 watts.
4900 is from 2012.
There you go. I got an i7-6850K.
I got like a 64.
More performance, less power.
And by the way, it's less than half the price.
Whoa.
Now, I know some of you have also been wondering
just how does the 3900X perform in games, right?
This is the most important part.
Wake up. Wake up, everybody. Wake up.
We compare the 3900X again.
My hands are covered in oil, apparently.
And this is across some of the top AAA gaming titles.
This is in 1080p so that we can really stress the CPU.
And you just see is incredible performance.
That's like taking a vitamin C supplement.
Very high.
You just piss it away.
Maximum gaming performance where the CPU's job
is to get out of the way of the GPU.
And is that great or what?
It's for half the price.
Now, look.
Numbers are nice, but gameplay is much better, isn't it?
We're going to get gameplay from what game?
So let's actually see a real-world use case for the 3900X.
Not just for gaming.
We're going to show you gaming,
but we're going to show you what you can really do
when you take the 3900X for a spin.
And for that, let me invite Robert to the stage.
For that, we're going to put on Minecraft.
You saw the PC gaming show Terraria.
Robert, my shoes.
Thank you. Thank you.
We've got 48,000 frames per second.
Choose 1080?
What's after this?
How long until Square Enix?
We've got like three hours until Square Enix.
What the fuck am I going to do?
I'm about to eat like fucking bread on screen.
Should we go back to floor soup?
To YouTube at 10,000 kilobits using the slow OBS.
All right. Well, which is just a quality preset
that's so far above what most processors can do.
We got a long way to go.
So I'm going to play something.
This is what a viewer would see
if we stream this game on both of these processors.
Yes, we did start the stream for the other guy.
I can't do heroes.
That'll take longer than three hours.
Right. That dollar on chapter five.
No, that was the magic of a 12 core processor for gaming.
You can do things that you couldn't do before.
The other guy with eight cores.
Sorry. All right.
So let's say I tried to sneeze it off.
I fucked it up.
Whatever. I just I just sneezed.
That's all that happened.
All right. Let me let's just hang out for a second.
I need a 12 core processor for gaming.
Do you believe it now?
I see if I can match it.
Look, we are just taking gaming and streaming to the next level.
This is what we want to do.
And now let's take a look at the Ryzen 7 3800X in action.
You know, my point earlier was that at every price point
we're giving gamers something special.
And this time we're comparing the 3800X
against the 9700K across the same titles in 1080p.
And what do you see?
Again, you see just fantastic framerate.
Well over.
He was mining buzzwords.
Yeah, that's what I was doing.
There's a Mordhau update?
No, is there?
No, but I suck at that game.
Why is it still playing?
This shit's still going.
I've already closed it and it's still somewhere.
The Ryzen 5 family is just a perfect fit.
Right now somebody from AMD was watching the stream going,
I'm just leaving.
They're like, what the fuck?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm going to go play like kitchen simulator.
Watch the rest of the trailers.
Hold on.