Good morning or good, uh, good afternoon. Is it morning for anybody right now? What time is it
right now for anybody? It's 1 30 pacific. So what time is it? Let me look at it. Let me look at the
big country map. Let's see. Map of the world. I'm curious about this. All right, so what time is it
in Russia right now? Or Japan, right? What time is it in Japan or China? It's 10 30 am in Hawaii.
There you go. Good morning. Those of you that live in Hawaii, welcome to the stream. Today,
we are going to do something a little different. I did declare last night this was going to be a
fuckface stream, and it is. We're going to start with the super higher AI learning predictive
text machine called Talk to Transformer. Highly requested last night. Pretty good way to open up
the fuckface stream. Um, and then we're probably gonna move on to Jackbox. Haven't done that in
a while, so probably do that for like, I don't know, two or three hours. Do this for like
an hour, I don't know, 30 minutes. How long can you, how can you realistically do this
for more than an hour? I guess you could just sit here and write sentences, right?
But, uh, reason why I'm starting so early and the reason why we're stopping so early
is because I have to go pick somebody up at the airport and then hang out with somebody.
That's why the last couple of streams have been in the earlier afternoon Pacific. No, it's not
star, okay? I'm just gonna make that really clear. You know, I wish it was sometimes.
I think I'm gonna see him real soon though. Sometimes, you know, I just wish my fucking
friend would come and visit me, but I haven't visited him either, so you know, I haven't
gone like to see him. No, everybody has to come see me, but yeah, I think actually I'll
see him in the summer. Yeah, trapped in my house. Germany is the center of the universe.
That's a pretty good way to start what we are about to start. I think that's a good one to
start on. So, uh, this little machine here, what this does is when you type in a sentence
or a paragraph or a phrase, this will make up an entire predictive story, predictive text. It
just, it just essentially is a story generator or phrase generator, like when you're typing on
your phone. I don't know where it even pulls information from. It just works. Yeah, this is
blindingly bright. Can you adjust the colors? Uh, hold on. Let me see. Is it, is it bright?
How bright is it? Maybe I can. Let me see if I can adjust the brightness.
Oh, check this shit out. Yeah, I can. No, I can't. Oh, yeah. Look at, look what I can do.
Look at what I'm capable of. I might be a little too much. Hold on.
Hue shift. We can make it green. Whoa, hold on. I can make it like purple. Now that's blue is
fine. That's fine. Turn it up a little bit more. Is that good? Is that easier on your eyes?
Can you see it better? The contrast up a little bit more. That should be fine. All right,
so we're, we're going to press complete text. We're going to just test it out and see
what it does. Germany is the center of the universe and I kind of want to make it so I
have to scroll down. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh, this is, this is really fucking long. Let me make it so you can't see this shit until
I'm ready to show it. I need to do this. Hold on. You know what I mean? I don't want
you guys, I don't want it to be a spoiler. I want to just, I want to be able to read it.
There we go. Okay. All right. So this is the first thing we generated. I'm going to,
I'm going to dramatically read every single one of these. So you know what that means.
You're going to get fucking voices today. So why don't we start. Germany is the center
of the universe. The only other planet in our solar system is Neptune because there
is no ice in its orbit. While the atmosphere of Mars is much thinner, the atmosphere of Jupiter
has a larger density than the atmosphere of Mars, which makes it much less dense
than the atmosphere of earth. This can account for the fact that Jupiter has so many moons
and are so crowded with comets that moons orbit Jupiter more than planets do.
This is similar to our own moon. In addition, while planets like Jupiter and Saturn have
surface areas about the size as our own planet, planets like earth have many times the area of
our moon compared to other worlds. And so the density of our atmosphere is closer to the earth.
So while planets can have water oceans, the majority of the water on earth lies within the
atmosphere because Venus has no atmosphere. It is completely vapor-filled and is the only
planet in our solar system that can be seen with the naked eye. Venus has an atmosphere
that can withstand a tremendous amount of ultraviolet radiation since water vapor and the
light it emits is the. This is just a gigantic logic problem. I feel like I'm
going to have to solve for X here at some point. Okay. The only other planet in our
solar system is Neptune. How does that make? Wait, what are they talking about?
They just went off on like a huge tangent of how Mars and earth and
stop this music for now. Build background contextual music.
Hello. Say less science. Well, I didn't know that was going to happen.
There, you happy? I eat boogers. Ha ha. I probably shouldn't tell you this though.
Just go and have a look anyway. It was fun while it lasted. Lying back against the wall,
Coy gave the bender a look that told her the boy didn't care that she was lying right next
to him. Asami though did. It was a simple but effective tactic. What?
All right. So it didn't know what to do with that. It didn't know what to do with that.
It just, we got the first sentence and then it went on some fucking fan fiction.
All right. Keep reading. I'm not, I'm not going to read that. I'm going to break a rule here.
I'm not going to break any rules, okay? Here, here you go.
This music doesn't fit. The wonderful world of classical English music. Okay, here we go.
I'm not going to break any rules here, but I was also not interested,
says Mr. Bostrom, who was appointed professor of management at Harvard Business School
in 1999. So I went to a meeting with a group of distinguished men at the end of this trip,
which was chaired by Mark Zuckerberg. Zuckerberg's proposal on a research budget
of a hundred billion dollars was clearly the most promising way forward for the young
scientist whose main motivation for taking the job was to learn how to build big,
computerized software. It was an obvious choice. The prospect of sitting near the most successful
people in the world and taking their advice meant I had long interesting life and I loved
it, he says. But that doesn't mean I am completely comfortable writing about it.
One day I got an email from Facebook asking if I would like to do something to write
a book on them. There were some early issues to confront too, with Mr. Bostrom describing
how he was told by another engineer that the company wanted a prospective candidate.
He accepted it. Boring! Boring! Snooze!
Okay. German streams suck. He has less than 5,000 viewers. The show could have been less
racist. And less racist. This is where I will go on a rant. Why? Why? Why? Okay.
German is a good person. Don't believe the internet. Okay. Here we go. Turn it on. This
is like fucking scary music. We need something happy. Oh, this music sucks. Who cares? The
rainforest. Who cares? German is a good person. Don't believe the internet. That girl
in the bathroom at work is probably just mad that you broke her laptop. Not me.
This post has two things in common with the old. If you're an asshole, you probably can't do
anything right. Mentality. Both are not really true at all. Most of- What the fuck?
Most of- Why? Why? Why? I'm going to write an assembly's play on- Why? No!
How do you take- You can't take this one. You can't fucking ruin me with this one.
You cannot possibly take that anywhere.
Germa is made out of metal dust. But you don't need to play Blood Moon. It's a solid
guard. But the most important part of this deck is lightning storm. Not only can you
discard the rest of your creatures to your hand as well as the removal from it, you can
also play it whenever it comes up so that you keep the lightning bolts even in the first
place. Well, I did not take the opportunity to compare this with something like Blue
Sun's Zenith. It's really interesting that the two cards have something in common with
the colorless artifact mana. And while I didn't mention the combo card in that card's
description, this does come with the potential for huge value. The first time you get
lightning bolt, you're going to get one-shotted by a red creature and a blue creature from
your side, depending on how much damage your opponent has from your lightning bolts
and what you're using to do that. In fact, if you want even more lightning bolt, you
can use Blood Moon's ability to discard your lightning bolts once the opponent's life
total drops to zero. Why are they always- okay, why are they like exceptionally boring
or horrible? We're gonna find out. Okay, here we go.
Sometimes I ponder life's mysteries. Are hippos actually aggressive? I keep hearing
they're the most vicious, but is it really true? Is the King Kong actually afraid of
women? Is the dinosaur really so strong? Does a chicken actually poop? Are the birds
really friendly to each other? Can I actually talk to a chick? Does our planet actually
exist? I'm curious. If I want to learn about these things, I think I'd have to
ask them. I've read about them. They're all my friends. They all tell me they know.
They're my friends, and their favorite thing is their pet dog. I'm guessing I
don't need any more convincing. Editor's Note. This interview has been excerpt from
the novel Where to See America's Great Game by Mark C. Smith, published by the
Penguin Press. Rant things of a crazy person.
All right, somebody give me the German craft coffee pasta. I mean, I have to do it,
right? I'm gonna go on a rant here about German streams lately. All right.
Mm hmm. Okay. Okay. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of
Germacraft, the series where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single
player let's play. And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely
because I'm an idiot in this game. You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of triumphs. At least I'm hoping. So grab yourself
a nice hot cup of coffee, hot cup of cocoa. I got myself some apple cider
here freshly blued. Let me take a sip. Ah, that's some good cider. All right.
So the whole thing is pretty simple. In this game, there are three classes and
there are four different ways to play the class. The three classes have a
number of skills or attributes which can boost your character with their
attributes. Your class might get bonuses to your movement, casting
spells, attack power, or your armor. It also has some sort of defense,
which is essentially just armor. If your class has defensive spells,
armor, movement, attack spells, or defenses, it gets extra points or
something like that that you might want to...
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one
of Germacraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player let's play. And by let's play, I use
that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails, lots of triumphs. At least I'm hoping.
But I'll leave it to the players to decide what is and what isn't. I'll
just do my best to make them as successful as possible. The first
episode of Germacraft is entitled Broke. If you've seen the last few
episodes then you know this isn't a one-man show or anything.
And the player is very involved to make sure that people play well with each
other. I'm going to be focusing on new players
and how they should be taught the ropes and how to get themselves into
some bad situations. And since we're only one player, let's
focus on one topic today. You've been warned! I won't use wasted
time or similar terms. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to
episode one of Germacraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
I've been playing mostly since beta 2.5 and this year I'm having a huge
improvement because this summer I've been having some issues
I know quite a bit about. I've been trying different things for the sake of
my gaming to fix them. Like I've lost my PC and
internet for eight weeks. I've learned so much about how to
deal with my system and improve my gaming.
It's been really useful learning a plethora of things about my own
system while I'm dealing with a lot of
issues and glitches. I'll try to update some of this as I go along.
The topic of this week, how to reset games, how to use console patch, etc.
I'm getting better as a programmer when it comes to my own hardware and
software. I've been able to get through to my
computer since it works so well with me now.
Now to see how I did it. What I've been playing. Minecraft 1.7.
I've been playing since 2.5. Minecraft 1.7.
This is just like nonsense. I can't even read that one.
What is this? So is the stream.
Does anybody have the whole thing? All right, here we go.
All right. My father was fairly wealthy.
And here's why.
All right, here we go. My father was fairly wealthy.
He would sometimes come home and shower us with gifts.
Various toys, trinkets, and the like. My father also brought us something
else to the house. Animals. Lots of animals. You see, he
was a zoologist by trade. The money was great. We had an entire
zoo in our backyard. But over the years one would say
sharing a bed with a giraffe is not so great after a while.
We grew distant, him and I. The last time I spoke with him was July of 2006.
And here's why. We weren't even friends after our divorce.
We were never friends. We were separated by so many years of love.
We still talk about it every day. And as I said before, we still see each
other occasionally. Like once a year. We talk when we are
out on the town. We don't talk every day because I have classes.
No! I have to be at work or in the shop. In a couple years we'll be able
to speak again. Possibly. God damn it.
Okay, it's time. It's time, guys. I'm gonna try.
This is too stupid for me to... Hey bro, uh, you need some help with those weights?
I could give you a spotty grade on that subject.
But don't worry, uh, I won't get mad if you get, uh, something in. You know,
I've seen you fight. You know, just watch that leg kick.
You won't be able to keep your pants on forever.
What? And just before you did that, you had him drop off the top bar of his
own chair? It's fucking porn again. What the
fuck? This is like bad. Okay, you look like shaggy today.
Maybe I should change my shirt. Should I go put another shirt on?
All right, here we go. No, I don't think this is public
information. No, I'm keeping it on. twitch.tv revenue
earnings call, to which she replied that she does not have any data to
back up the claims. On Monday, the company announced that
it made 2.9 billion in revenue last year,
beating wall street projections of 1 billion to 2 billion.
Due largely to its strong audience. On Tuesday, Twitch's third quarter earnings
showed that the number of paying members rose slightly to 10 million
from 10 million. In total revenue, Twitch added 14.8 million,
down from 15.9 million in the same quarter of last year.
Reed Moran wore for Twitch battle the real-time chat platform fights to
survive. In an interview posted to a Twitch
page on Wednesday, she denied that this was down
to a rise in revenue. However, she added that this doesn't mean that all
of Twitch's growth was down to higher viewership.
It does mean that more people have an opportunity to create and share better
looking streams, such as in the photo series below. If so,
Twitch will need to work to generate that stream
without being seen as a video game's video. This is real?
I don't know. Okay, Otto's Big Adventure?
Okay, we'll do Otto's Big Adventure. Did anybody have the
transcript? Do the rats? Yeah, I'll do the rats.
Okay, rats? We're rats. We're the rats. We pray at night.
We stalk at night. We're the rats.
What? Rats? We're rats. We're the rats. There we are. Rats.
We're rats. We're the rats. We pray at night. We stalk at night.
We're the rats. So if you want kids around when they're kids and they're
living in a cave, that's fine, but don't let them walk
around in leather jackets and beards and run around where...
read it! No, it could be taken... somebody could take this out of context
and like clip me and put it on like fucking sickos.org
or whatever. I don't know. Okay, let's get a
appropriate song here. Didn't work? It doesn't... it won't do it.
Maybe it's the... yeah, it might be the... it might have to delete that.
Okay, here we go. Let me get this on here.
I am the strongest. I will show you. My power level's been rising for
centuries now.
It was a scene I had watched hundreds of times. What is more than
what? That one man could get it but only one woman?
That's what happens with men too. You must...
You will know it. Don't worry. Just do what I say and letting...
I'm so conscious that this is gonna be like fucking...
Okay, yeah, you're right. I fucked it all up.
I'm sorry. I just keep... like when it starts like that
like I feel like I'm gonna get down here and it's gonna be fucking heinous.
Don't be such a coward. I didn't know...
Guys, here's the problem. I should have seen this coming from a mile away.
There's more porn and more like porno and
fucking weirdo fan fiction on the internet than ants on earth.
So, um, it's pulling from all kinds of places.
Okay, here we go. I am the strongest. I will show you. My power level has
risen. It's been rising for centuries now.
Raw pace data. The only true hero in this world.
I probably just like woke up the whole house at 2 p.m.
We fucking sleep, man. We'd like to sleep. Here we go.
I am the strongest. I will show you. My power level has been rising for
centuries now.
The rest. If you're really strong, then it is obvious you could become a
mighty hero. And don't hold back. The one who will save your life is you.
I should have done more research for that, you know. I would have seen even
researched your strength for the master. If you are still in the same state you
were earlier, then I will save you from danger.
Oh, I won't be afraid if I get rid of him.
I suddenly heard the sound of an explosion from within the tunnel.
It looks like Noir is about to make a move against us. I heard you were
already looking for them. But I see here they go, Noir. Oh, there's a
certain Noir mage right there along with Kurururu. Kurururu? Who are these
people? How are they and why did they come?
My sweet child, focus your energy. Forget about what is happening
around you. Go inside into your mind. Connect all the dots and put forward
the power that you know is inside of that brain of yours.
Just like that. Boom! He's going off script. Oh, so cool. Okay, here we go.
Anime really isn't any good. There are like three good animes and two are
the worst. A good anime is hard to find, especially on Netflix,
because it sucks to see it all the time. Well, I'm here to make a good
anime. A good anime is like the movie of the week. It's probably the
only show I can watch, even while waiting for the next episode. That's
how I feel about this anime and how I feel about nearly everything else on
Netflix. It's too big for me and I don't want to watch other shows or watch TV
with an empty mind. So just imagine if my least favorite, my last favorite
anime wasn't, I don't know if I want to watch this on TV anymore.
I'd be like, how can you even fucking expect me to be entertained
when it's all over the place? So here I am watching this new episode
in my sleep. If it sounds really weird, you've got to understand
there's nothing weird. I've actually been here before. I'm pretty sure
this has taken place to a random room somewhere in Tokyo. What?
Let's see the other side of the coin there. Come on, we've got to check
them both. No, this is just more of just nonsense. This one is really
going, it's still going. God damn it. Okay. Anime is so good,
every anime is worth watching, but the real art form that makes me laugh
is the show progresses as the show is when they finally do.
Anime is so good, every anime is worth watching, but the real art form
that makes me laugh as the show progresses is when they finally do take
a look at the plot line with characters that can't say the same thing about it
as they say what makes it funny. Funny?
I can easily watch some of the most beloved shows with this level of
understanding and come to the conclusion that it is because a
character can't say the same thing, as long as there is a twist.
It makes no sense and it's all part of a plot. For those movies that
have gone this route that they can't take the character to
explain the story to make it laughable, well, they just plain missed the boat.
Even so, this was really interesting and interesting in some ways
and it reminded me of other anime that I had never seen that didn't go
the approach of writing characters that can't say what makes the plot so
funny. Helpful is where it gets interesting.
In fact, this aspect is so unique to anime that when I say that I love
this series, I can easily watch some of the
most beloved shows with this. This background music. Look out behind
you, the monster is in the room. Hold on. We need to up the ante a
little bit here. Get up the ante a little. No, no
thunderstorm. I feel like this one's gonna be pretty good.
Where's the audio? Here we go. Look up behind you, the monster is
in the room. You can do something about it. I know the drill. When the
monster attacks you, call 911. When was the last time that you
used those phrases in public? This is very different than police
officers. The police in New York have been very aggressive lately in trying
to get me to talk about this, and it won't do. If you got a problem,
talk to the authorities. Not my lawyer and not my attorney general,
not my U.S. senators. Talk to me and listen. You're not going to get
people in jail or in handcuffs or on trial or even in jail,
but I'm going to get the person who did the real assault behind bars.
He's a very dangerous guy who's no business out here. I will not allow
you to threaten me with your gun and your words if you're going to do
that. I'm so worried that if I don't talk or say my piece, this was
probably out of control, and I will talk to my attorney general.
How do I? Oh, the huge spider? The giant spider? You can't, like,
spin. Look out behind you. The giant spider.
I've done too many of them. What? Bridges.
Let me play. I gotta turn this off. It's just like a dumb piano.
I hear it. Oh, no, no. Look out behind you. The giant spider has jumped up behind you.
Yeah, it's okay. I still hear it. Oh, you should probably just jump away from
it. He's on the move. Oh, there's more. Yeah, he's still in
the back, so, you know, watch your step.
No, that's not why I'm still here. You know, Bertrand and all,
they're trying to get behind me. Don't worry, we can protect you.
Yeah, okay, that's the plan. Bertrand will do that. Yeah, you'll have to be
patient with him, but he's the boss of this forest.
I bet everyone is watching us if we keep on this way.
You know why it's okay to give people the finger? They're always telling me to
jump through hoops. They don't understand,
and I don't care to explain. You've got to get the message across.
Not, not, not. Like, aliens have taken over the Earth.
Aliens have taken over Earth. What do you do here?
Aliens have taken over Earth's solar system.
Humans and other races who aren't Earth are being hunted by the powerful
beings they call the machines. However, you don't have to fear these
new threats because you don't know about the machines yet.
With no one to save you, no one to protect you, and no information about
the machines, you must discover your true purpose
and fight in the battle for humanity with the others from around the world.
Play as a single player character or as an AI-controlled avatar
in multiplayer battles and multiplayer battles with the AI to find out
who you are fighting for. You will experience the story of the
machine wars in four episodes at the beginning of the campaign by
following a journey throughout the world of space.
What is new? Now with Game Dogs. We have added Game Dogs to our system
and added access to content in the game section of the website.
You can still play on your PC or Mac using a compatible gaming device or
a mobile OS running Chrome or Firefox. The new Game Dogs app is available on
both iOS and Android. That was just an ad on TV. That was
just like a two-minute YouTube ad. They pull you in with something fake
in the beginning and then it's just a video game or just a TV show.
Actual E3 presentation. Okay, here to announce our new game at E3.
Hold on. Wait, wait a minute. This is important. Nobody move.
I have to find this. Oh, hold on. This is so important. I have to hold on to this.
Give it to me. Come on. I know it's here. I know it's here.
Is this, wait, is this real? No, it's not even real.
Fuck. It's not even real. I was, okay, never mind.
I thought it was real. You'll see what I mean in a minute.
I'm here to announce our new game at E3. It's called Tales from the Tomb Raider.
You'll probably hear plenty of that from people all over in Australia.
In the United States, it'll be called Tale from the Tomb Raider.
I have to start over. Okay, this is going to be hard to do.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
I'm here to announce our new game at E3. It's called Tales from the Tomb Raider.
You'll probably hear plenty of that from people all over in Australia.
In the United States, it'll be called Tale from the Tomb Raider.
It's not going to be called Tale from the Tomb Raider yet.
It's going to be called Tales from the Tomb Raider.
I love the sound of that name. It's going to be called Tale from the Tomb Raider.
For some sort of convention in 2014.
The Tomb Raider title.
I'm here to announce our new game at E3. It's called Tales from the Tomb Raider.
I have to start over.
You'll probably hear plenty of that from people all over in Australia.
In the United States, it'll be called Tale from the Tomb Raider.
No, it's not going to be called Tale from the Tomb Raider yet.
The Tomb Raider title is being developed by a group of team members
and they're actually talking about a new game. One of these days we're going to
announce that game at E3 this year or soon after or maybe even early next year
but at this point we're actually trying to convince people to actually
buy and play the game instead of coming just to enjoy the game and see
their own photos in its world. But as far as we know this isn't a
sequel or a reboot right now so I know. I really like the sound of that
name. Tale of the Tomb Raider. Tales of the Tomb Raider.
And now ladies and gentlemen please welcome the head
of Xbox studio Phil Spencer. Okay all right hey hey everybody how are
you here? Yeah okay that's right cool really
cool very cool yeah uh I'm here to announce our new
game at E3. The next game from our studio is about to be released on PC.
This is because the game is on PC and Xbox One
and due to some technical issues we can't show it in our booth.
We believe that PC and PlayStation 4 users
will have many more features and more fun than consoles
so please check out the game on our forums.
If you want to keep up to date on our progress in your favorite gaming
platform we're looking into other projects like
the next game in the upcoming Super Monkey Ball series.
Thank you for reading. Thank you for reading.
Oh that's what throws it off. Thank you for reading
and please come get to know us. We hope to see you at E3
this year. Thank you for reading. Phil Spencer would be backstage
and he'd walk off people like four of his assistants would be like Phil
are you all right? Do you need some water? What are you
talking about? What? Super Monkey Ball. What the fuck was
going on up here? The next game from our studio is about to be released on
PC. This is because the game is on PC and Xbox One.
We believe that PC and PS4 users. Phil Spencer like took like three or
four like Xanaxes and like got on stage and just started talking.
Oh my god. We'll do another one. All right well I'll
do Todd Howard now. This is gonna be hard to get through.
This is gonna be really really really hard to get through.
Ladies and gentlemen please welcome the head of Bethesda Softworks
Todd Howard. I don't know but what does Todd sound like?
Okay right thank you thank you so much. Look yeah fuck yeah fuck yeah
right you know fuck yeah fuck yeah thank you thank you all right
quiet. I'm here to announce our new game at E3.
Yeah that's right. This new entry in the award-winning genre
comes out on the second week of June. We're also introducing a new
multiplayer mode known as Team Deathmatch. We haven't
announced any details as to how this would work until now
but it's a lot like Dominion except a little faster
with three different modes. One has a very simple element of capture and
hold but it's very unforgiving. The other two have a little more
strategy in it with you controlling all three bases at
once. If you win a match then you win
because your team gets kills and captures all three bases together.
At the end of the day if one of your bases is captured then it's out of
game and you can win a bunch of coins
which means you can take control of the rest of the game and play the
exact same map. This portion right here I thought I was going to crack on this
one. You're coming to E3 to announce Team
Deathmatch? A game mode? Another one. I like these.
One more. Okay. These are all so stupid. All right
hold on. Ladies and gentlemen please welcome to
the stage the president of Nintendo of America, Dave
Bowser. Hey hey hey how are you? How's everybody
doing? That's right. Yeah yeah yeah. Welcome everybody
to E3. Oh yeah that's right. Let me take a look. Hey hey easy.
For the first time ever we are at E3 and let me just
burn some time. Well the technical people.
Yeah that's me. All right I'm here to announce our new game at E3
after working on a lot of different things recently. We're finally getting
ready to reveal this project. The game is called
Witches of the Deep and it's for PC. What is Witches of the Deep?
Witches of the Deep is the most immersive game we've made so far
although it's not just for the PC. I would like to make this announcement
more personally in order to let the players know.
If you played the game or played with a friend you know what I'm talking
about. I'm talking about the feeling of
freedom that comes from trying something new. I hope you will have the
same feeling. Witches of the Deep is being developed
at the same time as a website and we will be sharing
this title to everyone through our Facebook and Tumblr.
The game is created entirely from the ground up by a team of game producers.
Our story has been told so far. We are currently writing and recording
some music and writing the final scripts of the
music. Our goal on the release! Why would you announce an E3? I can't turn
off the crowd.
All right, where is this one? It's right here.
Okay, so we are delaying our new game.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to the stage Gabe Newell
from Half-Life Softworks. Thank you, thank you everybody.
Whoa, okay, so everybody used to settle down here.
Okay, yes I did, no I am. Okay, very much, thank you.
Yeah, okay, here we are. We're here. Wow, interesting, wow.
Hold on. We are sorry we are delaying our new game
to 2013. Yeah, I know. Not many of you here today,
unfortunately. We're delaying our new game to 2013.
A few days ago, a few days later, when we reached out to Warner Brothers,
we were assured the delay would be brought under control.
At least for now, but no further information was forthcoming.
At some point in 2011, we also came across an official
FAQ from Warner Brothers that stated,
we would like to thank you for your great love and support of the Kingdom
Hearts franchise and in a recent business decision, we
decided that Kingdom Hearts Unchained X would not be
going forward when the previous game was released
and would end up on its own terms and for its own time.
Advertisement. This is where the story started.
A few weeks ago, Warner Brothers released a press release
that announced a series of new games for Kingdom Hearts 2.
One of the most popular things about Kingdom Hearts fans
is the fact that this series takes on so many different forms,
including the addition of a new game feature featuring a new game in Kingdom
Hearts 2, reads the press release. This is
precisely what we'd like to introduce in Kingdom Hearts Unchained
and that is all. Thank you. Oh, come on. Oh, come on.
Fuck you! Yeah, I've wanted to say it for a very long time.
Fuck you all! How could he say something like that? No, god damn it!
No, that's like the meme! Like, my brain just typed the thing that's the meme.
My brain literally just typed the, like, the meme.
The shitty meme. For some reason, like, neighbor.
I don't know, like, E-I-G. I don't know why my brain was like, yeah, that's
correct. That was unintentional. I'm not, I
wouldn't be that much of a dick to Gabe. He's a fucking great guy.
No, he's not. What? He's not? Low IQ. I blame my low IQ brain on that.
That's not what I wanted to do. I'm just stupid.
After nine years of development, hopefully it has been worth the wait.
My favorite part about the mod was the fact that I could just install the file
manually into your user's username, documents,
my games, my first action directory. You did not need to put it in any
other location. Thanks for reading. Edit.
I've decided not to add any of the existing mods.
I'll start with the main one and then move on to the others.
Also, just for funsies, I've added in a couple extra scripts
so you can simply execute the mod just to give you more ammo.
I will also have to rewrite the description because it's really not
that important. Thanks again, everyone. For more
information, please refer to the original description here,
github.com, aurora gaming, the big boy A1V, the big boy 1AV, oddball issues.
Why do I have scary music? I'm not, I don't want that mod.
Click the link. I don't want, I don't know what this is. It probably didn't even
exist anymore. I'm really like mad that I had to type
that out like that. All right, um okay. How about, what's a
song? And that's not a song, but you know,
do all of basket case. What? Okay, really.
Frogs will become an alternate reality for many, while fans will be
disappointed to know that the series isn't returning until 2019.
The episode opens with a brief footage of the future, including the
time travelers themselves. The new episode will appear on
November 16th, 2018, the same day Marvel Comics' Captain America Civil War opens
in theaters. Okay, that's an ad. When does Tale of
the Tomb Raider release, I wonder? It's Tales of the Tomb Raider, not for
other countries. When does Tale of the Tomb Raider
release? Sorrowful dead drummer Billy Breathes and bassist Mike Campbell
are excited about Tales of the Tomb Raider coming to Xbox One and
Windows 10 in early 2016, according to guitarist Mike Campbell
in Rolling Stone. A Microsoft representative reached out
to EAM for an answer, but didn't take the report seriously.
Why would Microsoft reach out for it? Why wouldn't
the magazine reach out for an answer? Why would they
decline a comment from Microsoft? That doesn't make any sense.
It says Tales, but let's change it and see.
Okay, here we go. When does Tales of the Tomb Raider release?
Some reports say the release takes place April 25th, 2016,
but that's only one day. At 4 p.m. Eastern time on that same day,
we will get a notification from Valve that the vault is open for you to play
it, according to the news release. There it is.
Takes? Take? Take? Wait, what do you mean take? What are you talking about? What happened?
What happened? What happened? What happened? Oh,
whatever. Well, let's see when Tales of the Tomb Raider.
Tales of the Tomb Raider? Tales of the Tomb Raider
is an iPad game that is desperately trying to get you to download it.
Okay, fine. What will...
This is like, it's like English is my second language, apparently.
What will Takes of the Tomb Raider be rated?
All right. A bit different for this week's game. You see
a few different ways that a new game is expected to be. One has to do with
marketing, and that is by putting ads on the front page.
Many have mentioned that a new game has to have content that will sell for free
to make up for not getting any ads. Well, that kind
of has to get a little boring. With this week's game and some of its other
options, that is exactly what happens. This
week's Take of the Tomb Raider will be the last game of the season
that hasn't been released yet. They expect us to see the game
come out a little bit later in January than usual,
so hopefully by then it will have sold out. It also won't be the end of
the season, which means it will have some free copies on sale for another few weeks.
Take of the Tomb Raider is available for free order on Steam.
Are they calling this the game of the week? On a somewhat related note, this
week's game of the week are some games...
Ah, that was all over the place. What will Tales of the Tomb Raider...
What will Tales of the Tomb Raider be rated? I'll ask about the game of
the week after this. Boy, what? What does this mean?
Okay, this is weird. What will Tales of the Tomb Raider be rated?
It will be rated T for Teen, but you'll still be able to use other
content that's approved for older age groups.
I'll also be allowing players 18 and up to have a non-commercial
online game. Do I have to own Tomb...
Just putting the blanket statement out that you're gonna allow and like
completely and totally support like porn mods? Do I have to own the Tomb Raider game to play
the online multiplayer? Some of the online games that already
support multiplayer will still continue to function for players on PS3 and Xbox 360.
However, I think there will be more content added to the servers so that they're ready
for Xbox One. Do I have to own Tales of the Tomb Raider to play the online multiplayer?
I'd like to say yes, but we don't have any official details on the matter just yet.
I don't buy games. Will your Xbox Live games fail to download?
What a stupid statement.
As a reminder, PS3 gamers who own a PS3 can play games through the cloud
and even download... and even download from Xbox Live in their online mode for their...
on their PS3. This is the best one.
I don't buy games. Will your Xbox Live games fail to download?
That's unbelievable. I feel like that's like a fucking question that somebody has had to answer.
Someone somewhere in some comment section or some review or something.
All right. What's the game of the week? I don't buy games. Will your games fail to download?
Okay. What is the game of the week?
No, no. Game of the week.
Week one, team opponent point scores. Score by points, points by.
With the total seven points from New England Jets at the New Orleans Saints.
Minus 4.513 minus 2677 to the Jacksonville Jaguars at the Oakland Raiders.
Seven point five points from the Tennessee Titans at Houston, Texas.
We had the Kansas City Chiefs. Point four five thirteen thirteen five seventy seven.
There's no New England Jets.
They're all playing at the same time.
Chicago Bears at the Dallas Cowboys at the Miami Dolphins. They scored seven points on the field
against the Denver Broncos who also at the same time were playing at the Minnesota Vikings
who scored negative eight points during the same time period versus the Jacksonville Jaguars
who were also at the Carolina Panthers versus the Los Angeles Chargers.
The Washington Redskins were versus the New England Patriots and they scored
two touchdowns, 20 minus seven. And then they were also playing the Washington Red...
No, the Indianapolis Colts versus the Tampa Bay Buccaneers who scored latitude 15,
longitude 17 at the New Orleans Saints versus the Atlanta Falcons and versus the Tennessee
Titans. Every single team played at the same time. Tennessee played themselves.
Wait, the Tennessee Titans. There's no New England Jets.
So the New England Jets won the game. Did...
Okay. The only way that's as possible is that this is like 500 people on the field at the same
time. So the New England Patriots and the Jets made one team during this mess and decided to be
on the same team and like switch shirts and stuff. Every single team played. All right.
What's the game of the week? Give us a video game. What's the video game of the week?
Write dialogue. It's thinking. What the fuck is this? This is... No, this is just... No,
we need video game. What is the video game? What is the video game of the week?
I don't want to do any more coordinate spreads. I don't... Is this even...
Hey guys, what's the video game of the week? It's a little different each week.
You can watch out for our video game of the week every Tuesday on the Twitch channel
or by following us on Twitter, Reddit, Facebook, Tumblr, and YouTube. You can also
follow me on the blog at jasonwilkinson.com. You can also ask questions on the official forums at
fandomofthebigplanet.com. Please help bring this show to life here on the Big Bang Theory.
This episode also brought to you by, join Sheldon and Jeremy in this special one hour
special of the Big Bang Theory. Links and merch, Big Bang Theory Facebook page,
Big Bang Theory Twitter account, Big Bang Theory Instagram. If you enjoy the podcast
and want more, check out my other projects listed on my About Me page. For more information on any
of the shows and our projects mentioned and for all the latest episodes and trailer info,
head over to my iTunes and Stitcher page. Thanks for listening. Links.
Is this made up? Just predictive, made up words? Big Bang Theory.
What is the PS4 game of the week? What are the best games of the year?
And then the next one is going to be who won the Oscar? Who is? No, I'm not. Okay, well,
we'll try it. What are the best games of the year for 2014? I don't think you can make a
claim for best video game ever. There are so many that are quite excellent, whether that's
Uncharted, Bioshock, or Mario Kart 8 Deluxe. Games like Splinter Cell Blacklist, Grand Theft
Auto V, Forza, Motorsport 6 all seem to have their fair share of fans. I think it's
really an amazing year. What do you think about 2014's big tech releases? I don't necessarily know,
but when I go to see the big tech stuff, it just feels better than what I normally get. I mean,
I'm not saying GTA V is a great release. I'm more saying that it's definitely the best GTA
game to date, and it's got some very cool features. I definitely enjoy the new things
like split screen for the best in business racing games, but obviously, what are you
really playing? What you're really playing is Grand Theft Auto. That's when you're playing
against other gamers online through Grand Theft Auto Online or against other racers by others.
So it's really... I definitely enjoy the new things like split screen for the best in the
business racing games, but obviously what you're really playing is Grand Theft Auto. This isn't
fake. Best in the business. Taking a while for this one. Is this... I don't know if this is real.
I don't think this is real. I have no idea if this is real, but I'm gonna go for it. Is it?
I don't know. Okay. Who won the Oscar? Oscar winner Joaquin Phoenix is not nominated for an
Academy Award, despite him getting an ovation by a capacity crowd at Thursday's Tony Awards.
The 42-year-old actor received a standing ovation and applause throughout the ceremony,
with other celebrities including Lady Gaga, Miley Cyrus, and Jennifer Hudson also receiving
special guests this evening. Phoenix has been nominated in numerous categories over
the past 10 years, most recently for the best performance in an ensemble cast including Bill
Murray, Tom Hanks, Jason Robards, and Julianne Moore. However, as much as that might be a bit
of a surprise, Phoenix has always held a particular soft spot in the hearts of young
actors, and in particular in a group of aspiring Hollywood stars. This is partly because
Phoenix plays Dr. Phil on a CBS program called The Talk, and in 2006 the singer made
headlines for being spotted in a pair of suit jacket and ties after attending a performance of
the movie Walking with Dinosaurs. I got the biggest standing ovation this evening's
Tony Awards, and I haven't walked. Joaquin Phoenix, does he play Dr. Phil? No, does he?
I got the biggest standing ovation, and I haven't even walked. He does? No, what do
you mean? Dr. Phil is... he does. What? What if one word just says no? Yeah, that'd be funny.
Stop the questions. I like the questions. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Does German 985 deserve...
What the fuck is this? Does German 985 deserve... Dan Olson, I hate people who play
video games. The Tesseract, I'm actually starting to find my preferred method of dealing
with video games to be going to an indie game jam. LOL, good times from Ian Chong. Yep,
he's cool. It's you guys talking. The best part of the... Folgers, right? Is there a D there? Is
it like Folgers? Is it folders? Folgers? No, it's Folgers with a G.
The best part of waking up is Folgers in your cup. They have a great assortment of
fresh and dried fruits and veggies and delicious sandwiches. So good. The rest of the day we drove
to the river park and enjoyed some paddle boarding and kayaking. We ended up on the
south side of the park, which is where we stayed while we were out. We found the place
nice and cool and we walked all the way through the park to the north side where we stopped
for breakfast. To make up for the delay, the driver decided to take our bags out back,
which was a surprise. She was like, oh no, you know, that's not a car park you're on.
Let's try our next stop. But the whole time we were walking, it was super cute, even in a bad mood.
It's actually really nice to stay in this area, as it's closer to home and it's closer to my
apartment and my parents. I think because this area is much less busy than any other area when
I'm around. By the end of the morning I started to... It's a normie blog. Hey, no,
my going kayaking. Don't go, stay here. I got it, I can do it. Don't move.
Ahem, welcome to the Nintendo Direct E3 2014. The first big announcement of E3 2014 was a new
updated version of its website dedicated to Nintendo, along with the official trailer
for Animal Crossing, New Leaf, and Super Smash Brothers for the Wii U and Xbox One
and PlayStation 4. A new Nintendo Direct is held now, which is the culmination of two
weeks long events from October 26th to the 31st. The two days are spent on presentations,
demos, and interviews with Nintendo on a number of topics. With this Direct still in the early
stages, we've gathered a list of the best of the best announcements as reported by media,
as well as some of the best news that was revealed in the videos. You can expect to know
what Nintendo has in store for us before all the rest of you have been given what you've
paid for over the last year. For our coverage from E3, please use the links below as our
guide. Nintendo Directs for Nintendo Switch, New Nintendo 3DS, New Nintendo 3DS XL,
subscribe, rate, and comment below. Mario Maker 2 is in its third version of its popular Mario
game series since the 2014. Released on the Wii U, Nintendo 3DS, and Nintendo 3DS XL,
the game was announced on Monday and went on sale earlier this month as part of a weekend
bundle deal. It's not surprising the games have struggled to make its mark on consumers
after its 2014 release, with many fans questioning how Mario Maker will hold up to later,
more mature versions of the series. Now, Microsoft is trying to remedy that problem
by releasing the new version of Minecraft. See more on Nintendo Switch launch bundle.
The new version of Minecraft, dubbed Minecraft 6.3, has been released for the Xbox One this
weekend and is part of a Microsoft exclusive weekend promotion. Minecraft 6.3 is the first
version of the game released for Windows 8 or Windows Store 8.1 and also supports the
new Nintendo 3DS XL gamepad. However, the new version also requires players to upgrade to the
new Nintendo Switch console. And Nintendo says that is why players can no longer jump into
Minecraft with Minecraft 1.1 installed and running. Minecraft 6.3 by the way. The new Nintendo
3DS XL gamepad. Quick, quick, quick, come on. No, people are leaving. What's storefront?
Oh boy. Yoshi is returning in Nintendogs. We'll get to see him in this week's update.
So look for us to keep you updated on how he reacts to our new characters.
Yoshi in Nintendogs. You don't have to go see the direct. Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, okay, okay. Star Fox. Big Star Fox announcement here. Star Fox Switch has been
delayed due by the Nicholas team's ongoing support for Pokemon Go. They're pushing on
with development of the upcoming title and the team is also hard at work securing more
games to the platform, including an announcement. For years, game developers have relied on the
popularity of Pokemon Go and other applications to secure funding from Nintendo for development.
Nicholas will also be working on more projects that are not the core title but specialized
like a Pokemon game. In fact, if a game is licensed and released and has a dedicated
platform, you can count on Nicholas to be working on these. And it'll be interesting
to see what projects Nicholas works on next and what its next titles include. It's worth
noting that Pokemon Go's success can also be attributed to its mobile and gaming versions,
allowing users to get in, out, and interact with Pokemon in different ways.
The game even takes the same approaches to Pokemon related items with its item collecting
mechanics, including using Pokestops as an in-app store and in-app purchases user interface
where users can... it's just Pokemon. Can I stream the direct? Am I allowed to do that?
Like, can I do that? Can I like stream it? Because I just need a sentence.
You'll be sent to prison. Let's see here. What's going on? What is going on? You're right.
I don't, I don't see anybody, I don't see anybody doing this streaming the direct.
I don't, I'm not sure if I can. I don't know. Oh, okay, wait, somebody is, yeah, okay, hold on.
Where the hell is it? All right, I just need to like, hear what they say. Like,
I just need one sentence. Where is it? Okay, Nintendo Direct. Super Mario Maker 2 Direct.
Okay, here it is. We just need whatever the, whatever the first thing we hear is. Okay?
Ready? Tap this icon here and day becomes night. Done. You don't even need to watch that direct.
You don't have to leave. Tap this icon here and day becomes night. You are now part of a magical
world, the realm of our dreams. So I guess there are a few things wrong with what that
last line says, and I guess I could be thinking of some sort of magic that I can talk
and feel in place and be within. Or maybe that doesn't happen at all.
And when we are able to truly come and be here with you and speak with you,
it will be a more wonderful experience. Well, thanks for listening. And as usual,
I hope you have a lot of fun during this week's lesson. If you have any questions
for me or the host, I'm always available on Tumblr for questions regarding this blog as well.
I'm also free with a couple of free weeks of writing in exchange for reviews,
links and posts. Check out some of the links that I've written in the past for a taste.
If you want to be notified when I publish more posts that might be of interest to you,
you can sign up below. I'd like to hear your thoughts on this blog.
Why is everybody Tumblr? If you hit the angry sun,
Mario will lose a life. Okay, let's see what happens.
If you hit the angry sun, Mario will lose a life. A lot of Mario is fun and I think he
has always been. I like it. But the characters in Mario games tend to have a very special
way of making me cry. My favorite game to play while crying is Sonic Lost World.
I don't play video games but there has always been something I like to do when I'm crying.
I usually do this before watching something sad. I just play the games and it takes
me back to the real thing. I'm a bit of a sadist when it comes to my games.
I usually like to listen and think about my mistakes and why I made them.
When you're playing Mario, when you're sad, there will likely be something to think about
but when playing something sad, when you're sad, you can take in that experience in a
different way. I always love Mario's music. So my first suggestion would be to listen to
the game while crying. It can really bring you to the edge of your seat and
I wasn't prepared for that one. I wasn't prepared for it.
What else we got? One more and then I'm going to stop doing video games. This is
too much fun. This one sucks. I don't need the music but if you hit the moon you wipe out a
screen full of enemies. Just keep your focus on that screen. Also know that the game has not
been released on Xbox One or PC. You can check out the demo here. You can also download
the game on PC here. At night, expect a surprise or two depending on the theme and how things are
presented. It should be about an hour long but there might be a couple of extras like some new
faces. There's also some nice lighting and a nice view so it is more of a short story with
more action than a true movie but it's good fun and there are plenty of other people to
play with if you want to. The story starts in 1774 in an English town called Freetown
and runs through the years from the Civil War to when the country decided to leave the Union.
The American colonies were devastated by war. The colonists in Liberia had to learn
to survive with a strong central government in order to make a living and find shelter.
This is where Mr. Smithfield comes up with the idea of helping out.
After all, if the government were to give up on Liberia, where it is going to go,
you have to start from scratch to survive. Mr. Smithfield's mission is to help rebuild
this new United States and help those that come to him.
If you get a dog and a lizard, you'll get the dog, which means you need both these pieces to be
in order to form a proper functioning lizard. So it was a long while before I could see the
world beyond those two small legs. Until the last bit of my life changed, my legs began to
grow. I developed legs as an adult which gave me a chance to travel and meet so many others
My children's legs also gave me this chance to experience life with other people. They gave
me the chance to live life with other people and explore different cultures. Now my children
are the only ones who need those legs to live. I am so blessed that I've had such an amazing
journey and the people in my life have become so much nicer. Life with my kids and my new
legs were just amazing to me. They're beautiful faces. They've even gone to places I'm a long
way away from in different directions. It's so cool because my kids and I have to go. We have to go.
Okay, I don't know. This one's not even sad, it's just fucking weird.
No, no Mario music. In the ground theme, goombas will float. If you combine a rat and a donkey
in the ground theme goombas will float over them until they die. They look like two tiny
goombas playing chicken. Mike Wachowski, Donkey Kong Country CFO. For those of you that prefer
video games over music, Donkey Kong Country 3 is also a solid game and it's worth mentioning
that some of the characters don't even appear. You don't hear them when you kill the giant
goombas or the goombas come out of the ground after beating the game and you don't
hear them while the player does anything with the super mushroom after defeating the crazy
Goron. A few of the characters also appear in a small area on the game's loading screen
on Kong Skull Island. The game starts with Kong having to defeat his way through what appears
to be many flying enemies. The only enemy he's encountered in his exploration of the island
he can easily beat without using any other weapons or items. When he finds King Slump's
nest to start his journey he's... somebody said to try this one. Use the last sentence
of this to make a new one. Okay, use the last sentence. Here we go. Let me tell you a sad
story. There was once a young boy who was not well liked. The older his friends became the
more bitter his hatred escalated. Every day they were beaten up so badly he lost half of
his face. His eyes were swollen shut and he was covered in bandages. To see how he really
felt was beyond words and every time it seemed they could just keep going the punishment
would get worse. One day a woman stopped in to buy some bread. He didn't listen to her.
He didn't seem to care. Then one day he walked right into her bedroom. She screamed
and ran out screaming. The next morning she said to her parents, I don't know what I did
to him. You're useless. He just stood there and didn't even move. All the while the old
man tried to comfort him. Then one day there was some sort of accident. A boy was playing
with his friends and the big wooden hammer fell on one of his friends and knocked him
down as well. At the hospital the nurse looked on but still as she said not that bad and then
something. Isn't this a goomba story? The big wooden hammer. That's Mario with the goombas.
Princess Peach like they're just walking around like screaming. Let's try another one.
It's not that bad. All right okay let me tell you a sad story. Uh okay I don't we
might have to abort this one halfway through. Let me tell you a sad story. Two friends.
My best friend and myself. We were young and cute and cute little girls. We loved games. We loved
music. We loved movies and books. We made fun of each other. And our mom liked games. We liked
music. We loved Disney movies. We loved sports. And we all enjoyed playing games. We went to a
game every weekend. It was always about the games. We would sit alone and play each other's
computer games. And our mom would always ask what was that cool thing that we played. We would say
that it was fun. And then when she wanted to play something that would involve kids she took
off. And that's when it gets weird. So then that's what happened. Because while my friends
and I had a blast playing our first electronic games. I didn't have a great time. Something
is wrong here. But you won't find... It was always about the games.
Whatever. What the fuck? I've no... This one's all over the place. I don't even...
Just... Let me tell you a sad story. For weeks I had been thinking the worst about my
daughter and I was so ashamed about that. I would not take her out of bed every night
because I really loved her. I don't mean to be a cruel mother or take all the credit for
anything that happened. But my wife is so nice to me that I was just looking at you and
I couldn't put my face up so she wouldn't notice that I was crying. That's when I knew something...
I knew I had to do something. My wife came home from work and gave me a list of the friends
we would be spending the night with. I don't know if I was the smartest person ever to
think about any of this. But after talking with several people, two men and a woman,
I remember one of them telling me, she's going to be so lonely tonight. I put together
about $500 out of my own pocket and started planning. I asked about my wife's and told my
daughter to stay home. While I sent the money home with friends, she wanted to have dinner with
that night with her. I have no idea. The world is a beautiful place. What is this?
The world is a beautiful place. Beautiful all the time. I'm just happy you can see the
trees in the sunset. I wish I knew your name. I don't know how to get it, but I wish I knew
Molly to Charlie's girlfriend. Due to her life stolen from her, Molly may be very naive,
naive and naivety. That was shown quite clearly when she told Charlie's girlfriend, Nicole,
that she wanted a ride for her birthday. When Nicole found out that Molly was missing and
wanted to speak with Charlie's girlfriend, Charlie's girlfriend, Molly, immediately blamed
herself and immediately took Nicole to the school. Charlie's girlfriend could just see that
the girl was scared and started to get angry. This is how Molly began to distrust strangers,
such as Nicole, Charlie or the police, and often began telling Charlie to go away and not
come back. When Molly was trying to get rid of Charlie's girlfriend, she did a similar trick
to Charlie as she also tried to get rid of Nicole. When the situation became complicated,
she realized Charlie... What the fuck? The world is a beautiful place. I fixed it. I
fixed it. Pretty relaxed. It's just meaningless. I don't think I can ride the Superman
roller coaster. It looks too tall and scary on the front. One man wrote,
I just want to ride it to visit. A Facebook friend who identified himself as David said
it wouldn't make a difference for him. He only rode the roller coaster at night.
I like to ride. I just prefer to ride at night. His post read, I would rather ride
on our local amusement park. I have a seven to 15 year old son, so I want him to never
be bored or not be distracted by the fact that my son rides one day. Do you know how
old your son is? He's between seven and 15. I have no idea. I missed a few birthdays.
That's a gigantic gap. It's somewhere between seven and 15. You know. He's a kid.
Okay, here we go. Ready?
Six Flags is the best amusement park. It's a great place to get your fix while you spend
the day and you can count on them to offer you the ultimate family experience.
We had been visiting their theme park for the last five years. We've enjoyed our time there
so much, we decided to move on to another location for our visit and the first thing
we found was the parking. We were confused, so we went back to the park with our four-wheelers
and went through three additional cars before walking right past another large park.
That was it. We drove past the same cars and then stopped a second time with no one there
or our SUV, but this time we didn't even bother leaving the lot for it to be in sight.
It was just another car park. It was just another car. It was just another car park with one other
vehicle or even a single vehicle on the lot. The four-vehicle limit. They made me look like
a fool and I had to take it out when I did finally manage to move one of the two spaces
I decided to stay. They have a long story that includes a lot of comments from customers.
We were on the road. Oh god damn it. I wish I could fucking compose myself on some of these,
but when you drive it around in circles, they have a shitload of parking lots
when you paid to get in and then you drive it around for parking and there's a four-vehicle
limit and you're taking three cars and four four-wheelers? How many four-wheelers? How
many cars do you have? You're just driving around looking for a parking spot.
Uh, Fmeric, thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you. That's 10 big subs. Really appreciate that.
Oh god damn it. All right, let's try it. I like these, but thank you for the 10 subs.
Six Flags is the best amusement park. They're located in Orlando, Florida,
which is in the middle of Florida. The Orlando attractions are outstanding and are worth
checking out. I had the opportunity to visit the following parks during a promotional tour.
Inn of Dreams is one of the top attractions that's currently under construction.
They did not say if the opening will take place soon or not, but I was told that
the attractions would be ready at the end of summer 2017. I will give Inn of Dreams a 9
out of 10 for their experience. You can check out some photos below. It didn't even go.
What are your favorite amusement park attractions? Let me know in the comment section.
Do you enjoy visiting the parks in and out of Orlando? Do you have any experiences to share
with us? Share with us. Like this video if you can. I'll do Disney World. One more Six Flags.
I'm gonna try. I'm gonna try really hard.
This is fucking hilarious. Oh, this is huge. Bitch just came in. I'm gonna try as hard as
I can. This is like the best one of the night. This is the best one of the whole day.
Okay. Thank you so much to Lexi. Lexi Z for the hundred fucking bucks. 10,000 bits. They say,
I can't remember the last time I laughed this much. I'm crying of laughter and gasping for
air. Thank you so much for making my day. Sincerely, an EU pleb. That's a fucking ton
of money, Lexi. Thank you. I'm glad you're having a good time. This is fucking, this is
a blast. Gasping for air, but yeah. Hundred bucks. And I'm gonna compose myself as hard
as I fucking can because this one has to be done completely without cracking.
Stupid. I have to get it out of my system. I gotta like fucking shake my body.
Six Flags is the best amusement park. It's a park of, it's a park for fun and I think it's
pretty amazing. When we visited, our park had a really nice view from the park. You can see
the entire park at your own pace for $5. This is a fun, cheap ride. For $8 you'll get a ride or two
that takes you through the whole park, including a little fun boat ride down the park's pirate
ship. So you get your ride, some food, and then you go back down in the boat and ride
through the fun ride. The ride includes the ride itself with the boat, fun ride, a few
drinks, and some souvenirs. It's a great place to hang out with your friends and a great
place to visit during the day. All in all, this place is well worth the $7. They have tons of
rides. I've been looking forward to some of my friends coming there, including the Great Wall
of China, the Three Kings, King Kong, the World's Biggest Monkey Fries, all the giant bats.
The Great Wall of China is in Six Flags. It's $5 by the way, $8. What a fucking value for
$7 to go see the Great Wall of China. The Three Kings, the World's Biggest Monkey Rides.
This is fucking, I want to like eat this one. It's just this sentence here.
This is like, the ride includes the ride itself with the boat, fun ride. It's just like,
oh my god, more fucking huge amount of money. Thank you for the hundred fucking bucks,
mother of, 10,000 bits. Well, I know where I'm heading this summer, to Six Chinas.
Imagine if somebody was talking about like this place, Six Flags, and yeah, yeah, this is
cool. They have a fun boat ride. You can have a few drinks. It's cool. You can hang out
with your friends. You can also visit the Great Wall of China and the Three Kings. This
is like a historical landmark. This is not an amusement park. What do you, what,
why is Six Flags right here? And it's only seven bucks and you get all the giant bats.
Yeah, the World's Biggest Monkey Ride. What does that even fucking mean?
Like look, is this included? Is King Kong included in the World's Biggest Monkey Rides?
This is the World's Biggest Monkey Ride. Oh, I feel like I have to do one more.
This is, give me a fucking break.
Okay, you ready? Okay, this, last Six Flags, last one from Six Flags.
Six Flags is an amazing amusement park. We've always said that. It's one of the
nicest locations around as well. The ride is fun and the staff are all fantastic.
I always liked the rides because of their unique nature. Our friend got the two-day
pass which included the 5,000 and 8,000. While my friend loved it, the other two fell in love
with it. The 5,000 has a great layout, a great sound, a great view of the park
with parking behind you. There's a lot of people walking around. We had the 1.25-mile
loop track of it. The 8,000 is about five blocks long that goes around every park
and there's benches on the end for people to sit and talk. We really enjoyed both and the
only issue that came up was that they had to change the speed of the loop as that was
confusing for children. They would go faster after the loop as they're getting the feel of
it and then slower when they're taking it back. It was frustrating that they had to change
the pace after just three minutes. While they are great, from my understanding,
this was $5,000 to walk around in the circle. And the $8,000 one is smaller.
Wait, it's a marathon. An 8K? We had the 1.25-mile. Wait, wait, hold on. Wait, it's a five
kilometer run? They said miles. You just go to Six Flags to do a 5K? I thought it was
talking about it was five grand or eight grand packages. One more. I have to. I'm sorry.
No, we got a bad one. This one just sucks. Six Flags is the best amusement park. It's a
unique nature in history. Make it more than just a place to go to sleep. This one sucks.
Okay, this is the last one. Okay, final one from Six Flags.
Six Flags is the best amusement park. I love the roller coasters. Roller coasters,
amusement parks, roller coasters. It's always crazy and has such great music.
I was going to try Haunted Mansion at least once, but then after watching the video,
it looked really good on TV. I did get one roller skater, but I was too afraid to ride
because of how weird it looked. I was going to try roller coasters the next day after watching
the video, but then I realized that I still have a lot of stuff to do while I wait,
which is not fun. I guess I'll stick with the attractions for now, but I'll definitely
come back next year. I love watching this video. There were so many things to consider
and it was really interesting. I'll try to read the directions on the website and make
sure I get my roller coaster properly constructed. You could really make many
choices if you follow it very precisely. It just wasn't there for me and it was too weird.
I love this one. I'm a big fan of roller coasters. Roller.
He's going to build his own like Mount Doom in his backyard. You're going to build your
own like Superman ride of steel. I did not read that. I did not see that part. That
threw me off. Wait, wait, wait. Oh my god. My fucking, my throat hurts.
How long? Holy shit. It's been two hours and 20 minutes. Oh god. All right, so we need to...
No, no, no. It can't be that again. Well, like, I don't know. What's the...
If I play Disney music, I'm going to jail. How about this one?
Ahem. Disney World sucks to see us. More news... Disney World sucks to see us.
Battleship has been shut down until further notice. More news and updates though. The
Hollywood Reporter has issued the following statement after the Disney parks and resorts
announcement. This morning Marvel announced that Guardians of the Galaxy 4 will be returning
to theaters on March 5th, 2017. As it is a brand new franchise, the announcement of a movie
is always the biggest event of a company's lifespan. At this late stage of the game,
nothing is announced even with an official announcement the following week. However,
after reading the statement Disney released after we were able to go backstage with the cast
at the opening night premiere party in Burbank and see the trailer from last weekend's movie,
I think we can all agree with them it'll happen. Marvel and Marvel Studios have
invested a hell of a lot of talent into this universe and I applaud them for pulling it
together to do so. To all their fans out there, Marvel has been wonderful to visit
and we will see you again in a few weeks for yet another exciting release in another chapter of
Marvel Studios Phase One Avengers. They're going backwards. Phase One Avengers. Uh,
this one seems all over the place. I, okay, let's try it. Uh, okay. I fell asleep during
the presentation and my son did not wake up until four hours later while some people
complained to me that they were sleep deprived while they were watching it.
It was not until after 4 a.m. or 6 a.m. that I woke up. My son stayed up later than me
and I've always known that I slept for five or six hours before an appointment.
I remember not being sleepy in the morning or even when I went to work.
It was the night before my first birthday. My parents are both doctors. My mother-in-law is
in obstetrics and gynecology and while the two jobs are completely different positions,
it is clear that our family's backgrounds have little to do with each other or our work
schedules. The main difference between attending an obstetrician or gynecologist and an
anesthesiologist is that a doctor is trained from an early age to handle medical emergencies,
to be able to offer better care and to give faster feedback. Both a medical doctor and
an anesthesiologist are trained in anesthesiology, which is the application of current medical
techniques to... Wait, am I under anesthesia? Wait, am I... Is it... Was I just on...
I was under anesthesia. All right, I'll do a... Okay, I'll do a wrestling intro after this
one. We've been playing for too long. I need to capture again. Yeah. All right, let's...
I'm just gonna put this up and on. Random music in the background.
I have trouble sleeping, I said. What's the matter? And then when I lay down, it won't go on,
to which I told her not to worry, for she will be able to get me up again in six minutes.
She looked at me with disgust. She then looked at me with disgust. Then she pulled me up by
the shoulders again till I gave up all hope and asked all my questions that she might
be able to help me. The time was three in the evening. When I saw myself on the floor,
I was in pain. It had blood running down my face. After some time, I woke up and I saw the man
sitting there who could not reach me. Hello, Mr. Jackson. How's the end? And I answered him
without a word, as if it was very simple, since I knew it could only be solved by a miracle.
No, he said. It's nothing. My wife's dead. He looked for surprise at me as well as I did at
him. He was trembling like a leaf that's just broken. Okay. In this corner, weighing in at 260
pounds from Burbank, California, the cruiser crusher, as he says in the video,
when you think about the size of that thing, it's a miracle that I can make it out.
It looks like it's in trouble. So I'm not too worried about it. I'm really excited for
to get started on my next ride, the last ride of your life, the end of your road.
It's yours. Check out this video for more photos. Here we go. It cleans out pores and heals blemishes.
Use it to hydrate the skin with the benefits of coconut oil. It leaves an impossibly beautiful,
almost organic look. The oil transforms your skin and creates a truly luxurious effect. The
coconut oil provides hydration, hydrating, and nourishing ingredients like coconut flax seed oil
and aloe vera gel, and the oil helps to replenish damaged seboscis glands. No,
go forward. Optimus Prime, because I type, this is the last page I was at. I typed in,
talk to transformer. Optimus Prime, Bumblebee, Mega, I gotta take that one.
Optimus Prime, Bumblebee, Megatron, Transform, and talk to Transform.
Fuck, what was it? Bumblebee. Why am I playing YouTuber music? Because I was going
to do like a YouTuber ad for like makeup. All right, here we go. This is a theme song
to Transformers. Oh, it's the old Transformers. I want like the new one. All right, this is fine.
Optimus Prime, Megatron, and Bumblebee. The Autobots are later encountered again in a fight
against them, which ends with the latter being defeated. Prime's body is then dropped into the
sea by Starscream. A few years later, Galvatron was fighting his fellow primates.
After suffering from a debilitating brain disorder, he had to take a rest
and was then replaced by a new body. Later, Megatron took the new body on his ship
for his own purposes of testing its abilities. To no avail. Later, Galvatron used its powerful
powers to destroy the Autobots on Cybertron. Galvatron would later come up with a plan to
use these powers on Cybertron himself. He used some of the new body's power to create
a gigantic giant Energon beast. The beast was so massive it actually affected the size of Cybertron.
The beast used these powers on the Autobots, allowing them to eventually destroy that monstrous
being. In another scenario, Starscream used Megatron to create Energon beasts to be used
to power a massive weapon which would destroy the moon, despite- I hate to leave a review this
bad- but it's all because I wasn't in a good mood last week. So how do we feel about the
current state of both our homes? Our pets? Our marriage? How do we feel about the fact that
I will be giving a free presentation at a local pet convention this year, but I have to cancel.
I would like to have the opportunity to talk to the people at the conference about pet
therapy. I would like to be invited. I'd like to talk to other pet therapy professionals,
but I've already missed that last time. We've already missed the holidays with our families,
and there's nothing to do. You can't even attend the Pet Expo. I'm not even allowed into any of
the pet shows because I've missed all the parties. It's really difficult for me to be able to
attend these events and not feel like my life is in jeopardy. What? There are a lot of
myths out there about animal behavior. I just want to stress out on this one. Myth. Dog owners
are too strict. Dog... What is at this convention? Are you... Is it a bunch of wild bears?
All right, let's use this. Myth. Dog owners are too strict. Dogs are... What the fuck? Okay.
This one doesn't even need music. Myth. Dog owners are too strict. Dogs are smart about
obedience routines, but many dog owners simply are not. As a result, many dogs are not only
misbehaving, but also causing problems for owners and other visitors alike. If you live in an
apartment complex, you are one of the most frequent visitors to your apartment building.
If, as a result, you discover that one-bedroom apartments you once occupied in an older
building no longer function smoothly, or other furniture has deteriorated severely,
or that your dog has been barking and barking and so forth, it's highly likely your dogs
will cause the trouble for other visitors as well. A 2012 study conducted by Dr. Richard
L. Poulin and his colleagues published in the September 2012 issue of Veterinary Practice
suggests that no matter how good a dog may be in obedience training programs,
it is difficult to train and test them adequately, because they are trained and
tested only on a limited number of dogs. Poulin and his team examine the relationships
between six types of dog behaviors identified in previous studies by the American Kennel Club,
and boring. This is just the rest of the paper. We just got the rest of the article.
Just gonna read a whole science article. This stream is making me resident sleeper of
laugh out loud. At go fund me lol, at go fund me lol, at go fund me lol, ay, ay, ay, ay,
ay, I hope so, and so can make this thread awesome. Hey yo, I hope so, and so can make
this thread awesome lol, ay, I hope so, and so make this thread awesome lol, epic donation.
Ay, cap is in the chat. I'm an optimist because I know it can wait, and I like that. I'm a pessimist
because I always wait until I know you'll see something I'm not expecting. Doom OST for this
one. That's it. Type Undertale. I'm not sure I want to do that. Dante's trip to Six Flags.
I've been to hell. What do I, in the last 10 years, number of American pills.
Okay, we're not, we're gonna do a different one. Back to Six Flags.
No, I'm just having trouble with this one. Here's my Yelp review. Play the song. I have to wait
till I get something. Uh, no, this is, you're gonna get Six Flags advertisements for the next
six months. And then I'm just gonna write total nonsense after this. Do a roses are red,
violets are blue. It doesn't have anything. This is the one that's gonna make the machine
not know what to do. Wow, that's surprising. Mine isn't working also. Uh oh. Did we,
did we kill the website? Uh oh, the website's broken. All right, everybody X out of the window.
Yeah, I think it's over. This is the, I don't remember when I said that. Is it my internet
that's fucking up? No. Well, I think, quick, everybody leave. Uh, I think we're gonna have
to move on to Jackbox. The website is currently down and we're, ah, what time is it? Ah,
I don't know if we can do Jackbox. We can probably play like, I don't want to just open
up and play one game. I guess we could. I didn't think we were gonna be doing this for three
hours. Um, I got about like, I have like another hour and a half or so, like one to two hours.
We could probably do a couple of Jackbox games. Yeah, we'll do that. Let me try
this one more time. This was the funniest shit ever though. I mean, this is, what a
funny website. Hour, well like an hour to play and then like 30 minutes to do the end
of the stream, kind of hang out and do bits and subs and stuff. Let me refresh the page.
Did it work? Yahtzee? No, no, no, no, no Yahtzee. We'll do a couple of Jackbox. Mario
Yahtzee is the new Geo guesser. The page is working, the AI is done. That's okay,
we'll just move on. I'm gonna do Jackbox Party Pack 3. That was really fun though.
You promised Yahtzee. I played Yahtzee last night. I just did it. Is your Discord invite
only? No. It is open to anyone. It is a public Discord. You can hang out. There's
plenty of channels there. There's a sub only of Rome, but you don't have, what do you mean
no you didn't? I beat Mario in a World Series last night. Jackbox, we're gonna do Jackbox
3 and we'll do it for about an hour. Let me change the title. Thanks for hanging out.
You just kind of drop by to see what this was. We'll do Jackbox for an hour and by the way,
I'll be back this weekend. So Saturday and Sunday we're gonna go, we're gonna do MS-DOS
Night probably on Saturday. I don't think that would make the most sense, Saturday night.
We'll do part two of MS-DOS Night and then Sunday we're gonna do Sam and Max episode one and two
and depending on how I'm feeling, we might just try to power through all three episodes
because it's not six, there's five. They might be willing to power through them. We'll see.