Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerema here with a Team Fortress 2 Gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Medic. It's been a million years. I know, I'm sorry. My last Medic video was like, at least two months ago.
I mean, I've done live commentaries and, of course, livestream stuff with the Medic, but I haven't done a sit-down, discussion-thought-out Medic commentary since I was like 11 years old.
We are gonna change that right now. Gonna talk about the Kritzkrieg. Gonna bring up why it is my favorite out of all the Medic guns.
Well, there's only three, but it is my favorite out of the three. There's a couple of different reasons for that, and I will get into them.
But I also want to talk about computer upgrades in this video as well, because I just bought a bunch of them, and I spent all last night putting it all together.
And it can be kind of a headache, and it can be really irritating sometimes, but the end result is awesome. I have pretty much a brand new computer.
It's like taking the engine out of a Chevy and putting it into something else, you know what I mean? It's still the same case, but it's got different stuff in it.
And, of course, I want to tell you what stuff I put into it. But first, we're gonna talk about the Kritzkrieg right now.
What kind of transition was that? What am I, introducing a king?
And here he is, your grace, the almighty Kritzkrieg. All hail the Kritzkrieg, your grace. I'm watching too many episodes of Game of Thrones.
Anyways, the Kritzkrieg is my favorite pub medigun. Now, specifically because of the word I just used, pub.
This is the easiest medigun to jump into a game and just play with, because you never really have to coordinate Ubers.
This is the only medigun where if you pop an Uber on somebody, Kritzkrieg on someone, it doesn't matter if you timed it right or if there's a sentry around the corner or something like that.
When you use the Kritzkrieg, you are gonna get some benefit no matter who you do it to or when you do it.
As long as you're weary of people's reload times, that's the number one thing you need to remember.
Because if you pop a Kritzkrieg randomly on a soldier, a demo man, or really anybody that has to reload their weapon, you're kind of putting yourself in a bad situation.
Because they might not even have anything to shoot. And even if they do, even if they have one or two rockets or one or two grenades or something,
you put them in a freakout mode, because they go, why? How many times does that happen to you?
It happens to me all the time when I get Kritzkrieg'd and I have one rocket or two rockets inside of my rocket launcher.
And I go, okay, hold on, do I shoot? No, reload. And you can make the person really, really uncomfortable.
So remember that when you have your Kritzkrieg ready to go.
Besides that, and of course knowing where enemies are and if there's gonna be more than one or two people around a corner,
that's the only coordination you need with the Kritzkrieg, at least in a public game standpoint.
Now with the Uber Charge or even with the Quick Fix, you need to know where sentries are.
You need to know who to Uber. You need to know when to do it.
But with the Kritzkrieg, a lot of that pressure is taken off your shoulders and you just become a healer.
You don't have to worry about really anything else. And if you Kritzkrieg somebody, oh, I Kritzkrieg that soldier.
What did he do? Kill two people? Sick. Nice job, dude.
It's not like with the Uber where you do it to somebody, turn a corner, sentries there.
Sentry doesn't go down and everyone is just like...
That doesn't really happen. But it does need to be noted that this kind of carefree Kritzkrieg...
I just made a tongue twister right there. Kind of carefree Kritzkrieg.
This style only really works when there's another medic on the team that's using regular Uber or you're on defense.
Because obviously if you're on offense and there's a bunch of sentries around, you're not going to be able to really push anywhere.
So keep that in mind. So with that, let's transition to talking about computer parts.
I want to bring up this because I'm so excited. I just got three new additions to this little home of a computer here.
I got a GTX 670 and I used to have a GTX 470. So that's the video card upgrade. I'm loving that. It's awesome.
It's so much cooler than the 470. I will say that. Oh my God.
My 470, I used to have to put the fans up to 75% to keep games like Team Fortress or even Diablo 3 to stop from running at like 90 degrees Celsius.
That's how insane that is. So that's a huge upgrade for me.
The second big thing is I got six more gigs of RAM. So instead of six gigs now I have 12 gigs.
Which is obviously going to help so much with video editing.
And I got another hard drive. So I have a brand new 7200 RPM hard drive in here now, internal.
I was using an external hard drive for a lot of my recording stuff through eSATA.
So I'm glad to throw that thing in the garbage. Get rid of it. I hated that thing.
The one thing I could not upgrade, which it's kind of, if you're going to do that, you might as well buy a new computer.
I wanted to upgrade the processor. I have a 950, i7 950 in here. It's overclocked and it's getting kind of old, which scares me a little bit.
But I couldn't really do anything about it. I think the sockets in this thing and this motherboard only allow the old generation i7s.
So I wouldn't even be able to get one of the new ones. I'm not that concerned about it though.
I got these upgrades. I'm good to go for a while. I'll cross the processor bridge when I have to, but for now I'm fine.
So that wraps up this video, guys. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll catch you guys all soon. So take care, everybody.