It's going to be like the hug heavy. Once he gets a hold of you, there ain't no I'm like a
fucking boa constrictor. You ever seen the Discovery Channel when the snake bites? He blew himself up
on me. Shit. Once I find that like hotspot, I need the melee power-up. That is so important.
That is more important than anything else. That guy still has crits. Okay, here's a hotspot.
We're at a hotspot. What's that guy got for a power-up? He's got the melee power-up. I gotta
kill this guy. What? I don't want the vampire power-up. No, I want the... How do I throw a
power-up down? Can I throw a power-up on the ground? Shit. Whatever. I got it. I got it going.
Let's keep the heavy boa constrictor going. I don't think I'm going to run out of things here.
That would have been so cool if I hit him. I'm attached to him. I got him.
All right, cool. This guy. See ya. Give me somebody else. That spy. I'm starting to like not
know what's happening right now. My brain's not like piecing together where I'm going.
All right. I was still attached to him. Come here. I missed. He's too fast. Holy shit. I still
killed him. Anybody else? Sentry gun. That's not somebody else. I'm actually not totally against
having this power-up, but he has it too. That's bad. We're good, but please don't die from the burn.
Give me that health. Do I swing faster too? No, I just move faster. This is going to be hard
because this guy has that power-up. All right, we're cool. Moving on down. Nope, that's bad.
Run him here. Get some health. I want to attach to that guy. Got him. That's not a snake. I just
did like a cat hiss. That's not a snake. Actually a snake. Yeah, the fucking sentry again. The same
fucking one.
Bye. That's what I wanted. That's exactly what I wanted. I'll get this heavy. You bastard. You
bastard. I even have the speed power-up too and I didn't even get him. I got the spy though.
It's okay. I'm okay with that. Oh shit. Who can I dig into now? Don't backstab me. He's looking for
a backstab. He could have got it too. I was attached to him. I was attached to him. Here we go.
Get this guy. Ready? Watch this. Watch this. Intercept him. Damn it. That was an Olympic-style
punch too and I missed it. I missed the opportunity. That guy's not going to die. This is where we
seriously start to separate the garden snakes from the king cobras. I mean, if you want to be a garden
snake, that's fine. You want to like grab somebody and like bite them in their toe.
That's all right. Whatever. For the second you start bringing in the king cobra, or the python,
that's me. That's who I am. This guy didn't even know. Got you. You can run, but you can't get away
from the fucking python. That's where we get away from the mini-sentry. Get me out of there. Let's
fall back to the grass. Get this guy. Gotta, come on, bite him. Bitten. Keep it going. Another one.
Let's get, let's get another one. This guy right here. I had him. I had him. I lost him. I lost
him because I like turned around. I just did like the hokey pokey. Turn myself around. That's what
it's all about. You just, come on, man. I need that health. This is dangerous. That was really
dangerous. I should not have done that. Somebody coming right now. Somebody coming right now.
No, I'm going to die there. I'm going to die here. Get out of there. Oh shit. Oh God.
Oh God. Get away from me. Get away. Up through the laundry chute. That guy's not even paying
attention. I'll take it. I'll take the guy not even paying attention kill. Do we have a medic?
I gotta latch that guy. Yeah, there's the medic. There's the medic. Medic, please help me. I'm in
the middle of a great snake run. If that guy, seriously. Sorry, that was a pretty good run.
I'll take that one. We're actually going to win? How long have I been doing this for? I feel like
I've been doing this for a long time. Okay, we did it. Nice work. 118. Yeah, this has been going on
for a long time. Had a little bit of an issue there, but I still, what the hell's going on?
Give me the health. You're so fast, but it don't matter, does it? You're never going to outsmart
the snake. I'm going to burn here. I need to keep going. Hopefully I don't burn.
Woo. Who's next? Oh, you next? Yeah. Keep it going. Keep it going. Gotta find someone to latch. Latch
on to somebody. Latch on to somebody. Pick up the health. I got the super power up. Oh, man.
Oh, God. Got ya. What, you want some too? Who's next? Who's in the long list of potential snake
bite victims?