Hey, what is going on, everybody? Welcome to Dark Souls. Prepare to die.
Did you hear the dog? Alright, let's make this guy. Class. Warrior. Knight. Well, they all have different stats. I probably should be looking at that. You know, whatever.
Hunter. Sorcerer. Pyromancer. Cleric.
What? Hold on. All these guys have armor and clothing and stuff. Why does this guy only have underwear on? What the hell is this guy? Alright, we'll go with this guy.
I'm gonna get my ass kicked.
Alright, well good thing I look like a dipshit. I'm happy about this. Oh my word. Is there anything else I can do?
This guy looks like a fucking idiot.
Hey, what's up, man? How's that wall looking? Looking good enough for this?
Dark Souls is so hard. Left stick and hold that. Alright, like that.
Target lock release. Ooh, alright. Alright. Okay. Hey, buddy. So that's a weak attack. This is like a strong attack. Good to go. What am I using for a weapon? What is this?
Am I using like a popsicle stick for a sword? What the fuck? Honey, I'm home. What's for dinner? Are we gonna have lobsters tonight?
Read the message. Whoa! Oh my god, that's a big boy. Alright, just go ahead and stand here and like watch him while he smashes you.
What is this? Magtherodon from Warcraft? I gotta get the hell out of here. Wait, do I have to fight him? I don't know. Just go. Run this way. No, not this way. What am I doing? Oh my god, I'm an idiot.
Oh, an exit. An exit. Yeah, what you got on me? Not the prick. Ouch. I didn't even pay attention to any of that. I was too busy laughing at my like stupid jump. Yes, I'll do it. Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, screw your family. Can I just shut this guy up? Can I kick this guy? Oh, oh my god. Oh, oh, oh my god. No, you could do that. I didn't know you could do that. Oh no. Was I not supposed to do that? Sorry.
Wield right weapon. Two handed. Oh, I can use this as a two-hander. Oh, great. Yeah, let me use it. Dude, you know what? Seriously, get the hell out of here. We're fighting in a stupid hallway. I can't even swing my sword. Seriously, you are so annoying. I should have just gotten rid of you when I had the chance.
This is the lamest fight ever. No, don't kill me. I'm just gonna go this way. Screw you. Resting in bonfire. Where's the bonfire? Where's the? Oh, it revives enemies too. Oh, shit. Oh, god. No, what? I can't. Why can I attack? What the fuck is going on? Oh, to keep me out of the menu. There we go.
Not gonna be an idiot. Oh, that does so much more damage. That's so much better. Oh, this game just became so much easier. Holy shit. Come on. No. Dude. No. I'm getting chased. I'm getting chased. I don't even know what this does, but I'm drinking it. What does that even do? I can't even do it. You can't get me while I'm jumping. I know. I want my shield back. I like the shield better. Oh my god.
I wasn't even locking on to enemies. I was just flailing around like an idiot. Give me my lost power, and this time we're gonna do lock-ons, because it's gonna be way much easier that way. That was a double hit. You like the double cheeseburger hit? Yeah, you do. That's a klat right there. Come on. Shoot it. Shoot it. Did I block it? I did. Good. Critical hit from behind. Oh, it didn't even work. Let's get behind this guy. Come on. There it is. Oh, how's your back?
Now this guy. This guy is dead. All right, buddy? I'm prepared. I played for a little bit. I know how the game works. Let's go. Yeah. Get locked on. Come on. You want me to do a little dance? Oh, dance, baby. That hurts still. It's all right. We're good. Yeah, what you got? You ain't got nothing. Hey, look, I learned how to play the game. It only took me like 25 minutes. Hi. This guy. Look at this guy. Look at how eager this- Holy shit. Oh my god.
No, dude. Come on. I was trying to make a joke about what he looked like and he just- Let's go. You big ugly bitch. Let's go. Let's go. Oh, Lord. Get smashed. Whoa. Whoa. Can I break these? Maybe if he breaks these things, I get like items of health or something. Oh, he's stuck. Get away from me.
Can I punch him in like his bum? I hit him in like his thigh of his leg thigh. That didn't make any sense, but I'm gonna beat him. Holy- Oh, I thought he was gonna belly flop me. He is gonna belly flop me. No. How do I drink these flasks? How do I drink a damn flask? Escape. Dodge through his stomach. All right. I need to figure out how to drink this stuff. Recover lost power. Take it. Is this like a potion? Like a healing potion? Where's my shield?
I didn't even have my shield. No, put it back on. Um, hold on. Time out. There is no time out. There is no time out. You can't pause it. Get him. Keep hitting him. I'm hitting him right in his butthole. Wow. The butthole technique is gonna work. I can't believe my butthole technique is going to work. This is working. I can't believe it. Oh, God. Give him the kill. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Victory is achieved. Yeah. Oh, yeah. That was pretty ridiculous. But yeah. Oh, yeah. Muscle man weirdo to the rescue. This game is hard.