Yes, yes, I know that you were expecting Christmas dinner tonight, and instead you walked in the door, hung your coat up, you looked around the room, looked around the kitchen, and there was nothing in the oven.
There was no trays out with foil on them. There was no atmosphere that there was any food, and you were told now when you came in, yes, we're going to be having microwaved pizzas tonight.
Hello! Hi, how are you? Welcome. Welcome to the stream. Some of you may be confused by the title and the game that's on that title.
And a lot of you might be wondering, man, what does that microphone sure does sound better, doesn't it? That sounds a lot different. That sounds much cleaner, doesn't it?
I'd like to see ones in chat if you can tell me if it sounds very clean and very new and refreshing to you.
Alright, so let me tell you what I did. Finally, finally, finally, I know, I know, finally, I didn't do anything. I lied. You see what I'm saying? Do you understand now? I didn't do anything.
It's the exact same mic, the exact same setup, nothing fucking changed. Not one thing changed. It's the exact same microphone.
You know, like, 2020 hindsight, but here's the thing. I need to, I might just do it and I don't even care, like just the few thousand of you that are here right now, just don't, just quiet about it.
If I had like an audio tech guy come on stream and do a bunch of shit, and he'll put up a bunch of shit on the stream, I'll capture it on OBS, moving knobs left and right, having a big pair of headphones on, raising the, you know, on the equalizer.
Yep, that's better. Keep talking. Keep talking. And I don't change fucking any settings. Like the next day, people are just going to think that it's better when he didn't do anything. It was an actor.
I should have just done that. But yes, no, we have a lot to talk about. Oh boy, do we have a lot to talk about. Okay, so here, let's start, let's start with the bad news.
The bad news is today was going to be Green Screen Movie Night Part 2, but it's not. There's nothing wrong with the playlist. Everything's done. It's ready to go.
It's been ready for the last few days, from my understanding. The problem was I got up today and a problem I've been having recently, you guys know that the last week or two has been kind of a pain in the ass.
COVID kind of came through the house and I didn't get it, but maybe I did. I don't know.
And ever since, I've been getting these digestive problems and these fucking headaches. And I woke up today and I had one of these annoying headaches.
And if I were to laugh really, really hard like we did last week or whatever week before, I would have to turn the stream off in like 40 minutes.
So I've got kind of an issue in my brain today and I knew for a fact that it would be a bad idea.
So if I were to watch two or three of those videos and they were really funny, I might have to just leave and turn it off.
But here's the good news. It's not like, oh, it's over. You're never going to see it.
No, it's just whenever in the next probably few days or in the next, maybe next weekend or something.
Because let me tell you something. Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. We have this stream every single day next week, pretty much.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. So it's a packed week.
And the reason why I'm doing that is not just because there's a lot of fun stuff to do with, you know, friends and streamers and stuff.
It's the baseball show is the 19th of this month. So I want to get a lot of streams.
So because I'm obviously not you're not going to see me for a little while after after next weekend.
You are going to not see me till baseball. You don't want to laugh, but you're going to play this sim casino game.
Well, here's the difference, right?
There's there's there's laughing at like somebody, you know, puking on the floor in the casino game, whatever.
And then there is I don't I can't stop laughing or I can't stop having a major reaction to like three to five straight minutes of video.
And I like I do remember last time I was dying last time.
So I think it's going to be a little different. It killed me, too. Yeah.
And I'll be honest, too. I'd rather be in a better state on like an important special fun night like that.
I don't want to just be kind of like, oh, yeah, I feel like shit.
Let's do that thing that, you know, I've been looking forward to for, you know, months.
No, no, fuck that. You know what I mean?
And I know I know it's disappointing. I think it'd be more fun that way.
I don't want to just I'd rather be able to enjoy it. Right.
But so we're going to his his plan. We're going to do this today. We play sim casino.
I'm not going to laugh, but I probably am.
I will explain the tweet, by the way.
A lot of people are confused by my last tweet, you know, one one tweet a year.
Andy, I will explain that because there's a lot of people saying, what are you even talking about?
Who's he even talking to? Why is he saying this?
OK, let's explain that real quick.
If you have an iPhone and you open up an app called Pages, you can do it right now literally while you're sitting and listening to this.
Open up Pages and go to, you know, new like I'm going to make a new document.
Click on templates, choose template and then new note.
And it's just a fucking spell. It's like it's just Latin.
So what I had to have done is I have a ton of notes.
Right. Because anytime I think of like a stream idea or something, I need to write down some I want to remember talking about.
I open up like notes and let's go. All right.
It's going to be a stream where I sit on my head and drink a glass of milk. Right.
Whatever. That's not you know what I mean.
So I must have opened it and didn't do anything and then just went, oh, I'll get to this later.
And then a year plus later, I'm cleaning out these and I didn't remember that's what that did.
I had no idea that's what that did.
You know, like I didn't remember that it fills in placeholder Latin.
So I'm sitting there freaking out thinking, why did why is this here?
Why is this here?
Just think about that. If you have if you don't remember that, if you have no idea why that's there, that somebody wrote Latin in your phone.
Who? I didn't fucking do it.
You think I don't know Latin? I was going line by line and I was translating it.
And it was just gibberish.
I was like, what what was I trying to even tell myself?
Like, what am I doing? Did I do this like as a joke?
Like I was showing somebody like, hey, look, look at my notes for a stream I'm thinking of.
It's in Latin. But no.
Yeah, it was Lorem Ipsum and it's just the default placeholder for a note take and you just delete it and do your own.
But it was scary. I was actually kind of scared for at least 15 to 20 minutes.
Yeah, it's just placeholder. I know.
But I was putting it into a Latin to English translator and I was getting English words.
I was getting English sentences.
One of them was like, oh, removal of the makeup or something.
And I'm like, removal of the makeup because this is what does that mean?
What am I? What do you mean removal of makeup?
What does that mean?
And I had to forget about it. I had to.
When are you going to do the welding stream?
Never. What are you talking about?
All right. You guys ready? You guys good to go?
Latin stream incoming.
And there's something about Latin, right?
That's all I'm thinking of this. Hold on.
All I'm thinking of is every movie I've ever seen where, you know, the priest is sitting there like,
And I'm just like, oh, my God, I don't know why.
Latin is a scary like demon language in all these fucking movies.
So I'm sitting there going like, what is this?
The only time they use Latin ever in the last like 20 to 30 to 50 plus years is to make it a scary moment in a horror movie.
It's nowhere else. Oh, he's speaking Latin.
Oh, shit. The movie just got way scarier, right?
So I'm sitting there thinking like, what the hell?
Why is this on here?
You might be the Antichrist.
No, I don't think so.
I think I think I would have figured that out a long time ago.
I don't think Satan makes the Antichrist baby and then waits till he's 37 to like, oh, OK, time to go.
It's the Antichrist. There he is.
37 year old fucking comedy dork streamer, German 985.
You guys are fucking nuts if you think that. I'm just going to be honest with you. You're crazy.
I don't believe that's accurate. All right. Let's go.
What do you say? Sim Casino. This has got music, too.
All right. What do you say? I mean, I don't really feel that great.
Maybe no face game for a little while, but I do need to like learn to play.
Now, this is Sim because this is not Casino Inc.
This is Sim Casino. It's a different game.
What I have confirmed and I know people saying, oh, my God, remember Casino Inc.
Where you could like there was like a bunch of crazy shit in that game.
I can confirm that I think that people do beat each other up in this game.
That's all. I didn't look too much into it, but I know that that's a possibility.
So, OK, everybody calm down.
But I kind of want to like make a hotel.
This game is fairly new as well.
This was I think it was an early access or something.
It's got a saxophone. All right. Let me learn to play face cam.
I'll turn the face cam on in just a minute. Wow.
Damn, that that you can always tell when the person that's playing the saxophone
knows what they're doing when they do one of those.
They do one of those. It's like that.
You know what I'm talking about?
Did I break it? Sixty. I think I broke that break it.
I think I broke it. It doesn't seem like it's functioning.
I give it five more seconds.
It's crazy because when I do that sound, it sucks and everybody hates it.
But when the saxophone does that sound, everybody loves it, right?
If I do that sound, everyone's going to leave.
All right. I got to reload the game, I think.
I want to make a casino.
Game is like it's messed up.
I messed it up somehow.
Try again.
Dude, quit. Stop being the Antichrist.
Would that be like public knowledge?
Could I could I could I even still stream?
Would it be you know what I mean?
Like, dude, like, of course, like Antichrist Andy like fucked up the game again.
Would that would that be like public knowledge?
Andy Christ, please.
OK, can I maybe tutorials?
Maybe because I tried to continue the tutorial.
It screwed up. Oh, OK.
Here we go. No, what?
Oh, no. OK, here we go. All right, let's go.
This is a sim casino.
All right. Welcome to sim casino.
Selected tutorial. All right.
How to control the camera.
This music.
OK, let's see.
They just take bags of money outside.
OK, let's get a good view of the casino.
Remember that you can change the keyboard shortcuts in the settings screen.
Hover over an objective or additional info.
OK, yeah, that's move, tilt, zoom.
Yeah, easy, easy.
Continue.
All right. Zoom the camera.
Move the camera up and down a level.
OK, right bracket, page up, left bracket, page down, left bracket, page up, left bracket, page down, left bracket, page up, left bracket, page down, left bracket, page up, left bracket.
I just got fucking flashbacks to being invent.
You motherfuckers that used to do that.
OK, move the camera up and down.
Right bracket, page up, page up.
Page up.
Right bracket.
I can't take it.
Oh, all right.
That's easy.
So this is how you go up and down.
Is that the only way to do it?
Cool.
All right.
Or click on the arrows on the far left of the screen.
Oh, actually, I think I like that better.
All right.
Tutorial seems like it's pretty quick.
We should expand our structure's foundations, which creates a base for us to build in.
Hover over the objective for additional help.
It's like the wall tool.
OK, look at the left toolbar.
Hover over the buttons.
Find it in the build menu at the bottom of the screen.
All right.
So we need to make a wall tool.
Oh, yeah.
There go walls.
OK.
Add at least 100 10 by 10 new ground floor cells.
All right.
Doesn't matter where.
Right there.
It looks kind of awful.
What did I do wrong?
My mic just cut it off.
Like, stop cutting it off.
I'm trying to do it.
Drag to make rooms.
Oh, I'm doing it like the Sims.
OK, that's fine.
OK, cool.
So you can make rooms like this.
OK, pretty sweet.
There are two ways to ensure each area is accessible.
Removing an interior wall or adding a door, staff door or private door.
Staff doors are used to secure areas away from the guests, while private doors are used
for dressing rooms and hotel rooms to separate from the other guests.
Make sure all ground level areas are accessible.
OK, so we can just.
How do we remove?
Google bar or building?
Oh, we can go like this.
Uh, like this.
Control Z.
Yeah, this is like a terrible hallway.
Well, I didn't know that was.
How do I delete this?
Cigarette Andy.
Stop calling me that.
Oh, fuck.
This is a tutorial.
Who cares?
OK, so how do I make a door?
Fence.
The zone.
Dismantle walls and fences.
Here we go.
OK.
Push tab.
Remove an interior wall, toolbar or building.
Drag a line across the area to remove it, but it must be all indoors.
Oh, this.
What the fuck?
Didn't say I can just remove a wall here.
Stop.
Cigarette Andy.
I'll just add a door, I guess, then.
Dismantle wall.
D zone.
Fence.
Wall tool.
Operations.
I don't understand.
Should I build a fucking fence?
I'm not crazy, right?
This is really confusing.
I don't get it.
Build menu.
Where's the build menu?
This is the build menu here, right?
He's too high for this.
Once I figure this out, we're golden.
But what the?
B?
Well, I didn't say B.
How am I supposed to know it's B?
OK.
Indoor only.
My god.
If I wasn't just a fucking idiot and didn't build these in the middle of nowhere.
Indoor only?
OK, we're just going to delete this because, honestly, god.
What's the delete tool?
Demolish structures.
Just get rid of this.
This needs to be connected to here.
It can't be a door leading outside.
I have to make a hallway.
OK, so let's make a wall.
Does that work?
This cannot be reached from the bus stop.
What do I care?
There we go.
Does this count as a room?
Is this mad that this is not accessible?
So what's wrong now?
I wouldn't want it needs to be a door.
It's mad that it's not a door.
What do you want from me?
Why does this count as a room?
All right.
I get it.
This shouldn't even count as a room.
All right.
So what's going on here is the same company got hired.
No, no, no.
Two different companies got hired to do the same job and we didn't cancel on one of them
and they just malicious compliance came and just installed their doors and we didn't stop
them.
OK, cool.
Zones create rooms with specialized functionality.
They can be any shape as long as they meet the minimum requirements.
They look like bright striped cells with text.
Go to the game settings to adjust the transparency and press Z to toggle them off and on.
OK, so this is the garbage zone.
Oh, OK.
So this is deliverables, deliveries, garbage, storage, cash vault.
Oh, we got a cash.
Why would the cash vault be right here?
It's just going to be underground, man.
This is going to be underground.
OK, that's cool.
This is gender neutral restroom.
OK, that's all right.
That's cool.
OK.
How many zones can I make and unlimited amount?
Could I have like a thousand cash rooms?
Could I have?
OK.
My plan is to have like 20 cash rooms and I only have one of them have money in them.
You want to come rob my casino?
You better you better get the right one because it's going to be a maze for you.
This music is nice.
Yeah, it is.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Because this is to create.
Where was it?
It was here somewhere.
Oh, D zone.
OK.
All right.
Cool.
Let's add a bingo hall.
Well, you know it.
Create a bingo hall.
Find entertainment in the build menu or search for bingo.
Drag an area inside the building that meets the minimum required size or shift to quickly
fill the whole room.
Let's go.
Bingo.
Wait.
Oh, bingo hall zone.
You got it.
Cool.
Check which objects you need by hovering over the zone.
Ah, all right.
We need this is cool.
All right.
We need a bingo podium.
Man, man, can you imagine?
Never mind.
Shh.
Quiet.
Hey, everybody be quiet.
Hey, quiet.
Hey, can you imagine if, you know, quiet?
OK.
I gotta be careful here.
I'm getting I'm treading on water.
I shouldn't be.
All right.
I need a bingo podium.
I guess I can just type, right?
Bingo.
Two thousand dollars.
How do you rotate?
Oh, there we are.
Cool.
Uh, and then I need bingo seating.
Waiting for a delivery of payout receipt by a workman.
Check you have enough stock assigned.
Wait, what is this?
I can't even understand what this is trying to tell me.
What are they?
What are they doing here?
They didn't even do anything.
Moving crate.
What did they do?
They didn't do anything.
OK.
What else needs to be here?
Bingo card counter.
Cool.
All right.
I get it.
Malicious compliance workers.
All right.
I get it.
That's fun.
You can customize designs and colors of walls with the paint tool.
Hold on.
Control it.
Damn.
This soundtrack actually is goes fucking hard.
OK.
With the paint tool.
Hold down and control.
All right.
So let's do some painting.
Where's the paint tool?
Paint tool.
You guys see a paint tool?
Somebody else tell me where this other is.
OK.
All right.
Oh, all right.
I'm into this.
I'm into this a lot.
That's fine.
Cool.
What about the...
Can I do the carpet?
I have to be able to do the carpets, right?
Look at the floors, too.
Oh, to do matching floor.
Hold control just like the matching floor.
Matching floor.
How do I do that?
Is there already people playing bingo?
How much does this cost?
OK.
I want bricks on the ground.
How do I do that?
Hold shift.
Hold control.
I don't get it.
Oh, come on.
That was...
I half-assed.
That one's so bad.
Oh, come on, Gun.
I don't even care anymore.
OK, there we go.
I love that phrase, but I really didn't give it any effort at all.
OK.
Move a single object or...
Yep, yep, yep.
Move a single object or drag multi-selected and move multiple objects.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Move.
Oh, that's actually pretty.
That's useful.
Copy an object with the eyedropper.
Sick.
Yep.
Clone an area with the clone tool and you can clone the whole thing.
Whoa.
All right.
That's very helpful.
Finally, you can click copy on any designer tool and click paste on another object designer tool.
You can also copy certain settings and use multi-selected many objects.
Stop doing that.
I'm going to give myself another headache and paste the settings multi-selected.
I don't think I need to do that.
My brain is too small for that.
I don't care.
All right.
A successful casino.
Do we know?
I think we pretty much know what we're doing.
I'm going to go through this pretty quickly.
Wait.
Delete.
Slime machines are fundamentally a success.
Some have been built already.
If you haven't destroyed them, of course, you can change the game type, which affects its stats.
Ooh.
Play.
It's a dollar to play it.
OK.
Jackpot chance is five percent.
Jackpot is ten dollars.
What a terrible jackpot.
This needs to be fucking like a fucking million.
House advantage.
I don't know.
Five.
OK.
Slime machines are fundamental.
Click on a slot machine and switch to game settings and tap.
Yeah.
OK.
Cool.
Gamblers have a confidence score.
New gamblers generally enter with a low confidence score, and this is increased when they win or push in games.
The higher the pay play cost, the more confidence they need to try it.
To avoid alienating new players, it's good to have a variety of play costs.
Increase the play cost to one dollar.
Note the confidence value.
OK.
Zero to two point four.
So what if I made this like ten bucks?
OK.
This OST is Jerry Martin.
It's the original composer of Sims 1.
Is that legitimate?
Are you for real?
Because that's pretty fucking cool if you're accurate.
All right.
House advantage has got to be more than that, but whatever.
We're just doing the tutorial.
House advantage is how we make a profit.
Imagine a coin toss where you pay one dollar with a 50 percent chance of winning back two dollars.
On average, you would break even, and the edge is zero percent.
Charge commission on those winnings will replace it with a biased coin that lands on our side more frequently, and we would have an advantage.
Remember that if players lose too often, they will get frustrated.
OK.
Copy these settings to at least four other slots.
How do I do that?
Copy game settings to bingo.
Copy.
But how do I do that?
Oh, got it.
Paste game settings.
What the hell?
Copy game settings.
How do I paste?
Paste game settings, right?
What the hell?
Control C, control V, control C.
Oh, that's not how you do it.
I mean, I'm very clearly doing it.
Ten bucks.
Jackpot.
Thousand.
House advantage.
Ten percent, right?
Like, OK, copy settings and paste it to everything.
That had to have done it.
What?
He's never used the keyboard.
Um, hundred dollars.
Player cost.
One dollar.
Oh, OK.
And whatever.
That had to be the exact thing.
I just whatever.
I get it.
Payout receipt by a workman.
And when a gambler wins, the machine will print out a payout receipt.
The gambler will take this to the ATM to collect their cash as long as they don't forget.
Thought machines have electricity costs and require a higher confidence to play for low play cost amounts at first.
You can research high limit gambling and higher advantages.
All right.
Table games have a higher betting amounts.
I know what a casino is.
All right.
Let's build a cashier.
Cashier cage.
Build a table game.
A gambling tab.
OK.
How about a Texas Hold'em?
I don't know how to play this.
I don't like playing this.
Zone and build a pit boss office.
OK.
Pit boss office.
Failed.
Oh, OK.
Hold on.
We need a door.
OK.
We need a computer desk.
Requires to be protected behind a staff door.
Oh, whatever.
And now we need a computer desk.
Listen to the sounds.
OK.
Cool.
This is crazy.
A player's club desk will allow you to track info about your gamblers if they sign up.
Encourage them to sign up with a complimentary gift.
Once signed up, they can come back as repeat customers and retain their confidence level
for next time.
Nice.
All right.
Managing staff and crime.
Your staff handle the...
All right.
This music's too good for me to talk.
You're...
Jesus.
Are you done?
Have you finished?
OK.
We need to clap, I think.
I feel like everyone needs to clap because we've got to kind of get back to what we were
doing.
Your staff handle the operations of your casino.
They work at desks or drinks, watch for criminals, and drain your bank balance with their wages.
That's an odd way to word that last sentence.
OK.
There are a lot more...
If there are...
I'm just...
I'm thinking the solo's going to come back and it's freaking me out.
There are a lot more tasks than staff.
A warning will show.
You should schedule more if the warning stays on for a long time.
Note that staff are automatically hired when scheduled.
There's no need to hire or fire staff.
You'll always have the right amount for your schedules.
OK.
That's kind of helpful.
All right.
Let's do it.
Let's take a look at the staff management screen.
On the right of it, let's see how many are a busy or idle on patrol.
As our casino gets bigger, we will likely need more...
Canada.
Add a garbage zone if you...
Fuck!
That was so bad.
I was trying to do, like, to the music.
You know what?
I could have done it, but when stuff doesn't rhyme...
It feels weird to sing it.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, if something rhymes, it's like a song.
The last word usually rhymes, but I can't do it right here.
Do it again?
I'll try it again.
But it has to be in, like, a poem format.
OK.
Oh, this is embarrassing.
And that's why I'm at...
You're making me do this because it's embarrassing.
OK.
Press unassigned key.
Or find the button on the bottom menu bar.
Stack of operations menu.
OK.
The staff type is automatically hired.
Click on their placed object or zones to edit.
OK.
Garbage.
Scheduled hours.
All right.
So we have...
From 8 a.m. to 8 p.m., there are two...
There are two janitors?
Add schedule.
All right.
This is pretty...
I get it.
What about the housekeeping schedule screen?
Housekeeping...
Where is that?
Oh, OK.
This is it right there.
All right.
Cool.
Look at when the janitors will arrive during the weekend and the weekends.
By default, weekdays and weekends use the same schedule.
Does it help?
I guess number three.
OK.
Easy.
You do not need to hire these new janitors.
They are hired automatically when you schedule extra workmen, guards, and chefs.
There are chefs in the game, by the way.
Everybody relax.
Setting up your staffed objects like cashier cages, bars, and desks is simpler.
Schedule editor is basically the same, but you toggle the open close hours instead of
the number of staff.
They're also hired automatically.
OK.
I'll figure this out later.
You can set patrols up.
OK.
I'll figure this out later.
All right.
We can do area patrols or the security guard over the front door.
This makes sense, doesn't it?
That makes sense, right?
OK.
That's good.
That looks good.
Oh, it's like drink servers.
Oh, OK.
So we can make them go like this, right?
Because they're going to start here at the bar and they're going to go, yoink, and then
they're going to go like this.
This is going to walk around.
This thing.
At least four points.
Oh, come on.
And then back over.
I don't know.
Over here to this table.
Yeah.
All right.
Looks good.
Free the person in the bathroom?
What do you mean?
Hungry, thirsty, bored.
Wait.
I am this person now?
You can run?
All right.
This is inverted mouse controls, by the way.
That's kind of funny.
OK.
Pit Bosses can be set on patrol to calm the frustrated players of slot machines and table
games.
They also look out for hackers and cheaters near them.
Security guards are a lot different.
They look out for thieves, hackers, and cheaters, and can chase them, too.
You'll want them spread around your casino so they will be standing in ideal locations
to capture criminals.
When you look at the recent crimes and the local crime rate, suburbs tend to have much
less crimes in the big city.
Oh, open the crimes overview screen.
What are all these people doing out here?
All right.
The crimes overview.
Woody Lane neighborhood crime five percent.
How many guards should chase down a single criminal?
Eight?
No.
That would be crazy.
One is fine.
The three main crime types are slot machine hackers, stalk thieves, and table game cheaters.
Thieves can hack your staff doors to access restricted places.
Cheaters take longer to detect and may win multiple times before getting noticed.
There's a good chance they will fail to cheat and end up losing more money than they started
with.
These failed attempts do not show up in the crime report.
Research security cameras, detect criminals.
Okay.
All right.
We are almost done.
We're almost done.
Free the lady.
What are you?
I don't have...
It's a tutorial.
I don't know what it said.
These are your recent thoughts.
I lost at the slot machine.
There were no nearby bin.
Not the fact that you've been trapped in the bathroom for like 12 hours.
Oh, it actually said the bar.
Can I play a machine?
Okay.
Open the...
What was it?
Manually delivery is enabled.
This means we need to set how much stock to order.
On the left is a graph showing current zone capacities.
And in the middle is all the stock types.
At the bottom of the screen, click on the truck.
Bedsheets, beer, betting tickets, table game chips, and soda.
Okay.
Set the target of payout receipts to at least six.
Payout receipts.
Six.
Okay.
Cool.
Let's say you have two crates of payout receipts in storage and a target of six.
In the next delivery, you would expect to see four additional crates.
If you ever have too much of something because of a higher target than the number of crates,
the excess will stay in your inventory.
You can click on crates to sell them.
Okay.
How long has he been streaming for?
I don't know, like 40 minutes.
I'm just chilling today.
Yeah, all right.
So now that there's enough people here...
Let me go over this one more time.
My green screen got moved to a different day because I didn't really feel that well.
And I don't want to make my headache worse by laughing every 15 seconds as hard as I
can, especially considering that there's a lot of shit going on this coming week.
And then baseball.
So don't worry.
We're still doing it.
I'm just moving it to like another, I don't know, maybe four, three or four days, maybe
next weekend.
Maybe...
I'll figure it out.
Don't worry.
We are going to do it.
Don't ask me.
It's...
I've been looking forward to it for a long time.
I'm not going to just skip it.
Okay.
But anyways.
All right.
Transport tab.
Supply truck comes...
All right.
So you can determine how often this shit comes.
I get it.
Most important stock is cash.
ATMs and cashier cages get filled regularly because they need to hand out cash when gamblers
win.
What if I don't have any cash?
Don't worry, guys.
He'll watch more videos and play Yakuza Zero and finish Red Dead 2.
All right.
But you can't take something from like four and a half years ago and say, hey, man, remember
when you didn't finish Red Dead 2 five years ago or whatever it was?
No.
You...
This is how it works.
You get to have a trailing six months of things to be upset about me with.
Right?
It's a trailing six months.
If it's been a year, I mean, come on.
I didn't play Yakuza Zero.
It's been a year.
It's been like two years.
You can't...
It's trailing six months.
Where's Paper Mario?
All right.
So that one, I understand.
I understand that one because I said, you know, within it, remember the trailing six
months that I would play it.
What about Sly Cooper?
I don't want to play.
I don't want to play Sly Cooper.
Here's why I don't want to play Sly Cooper.
I'm going to open the game and I'm going to do the first two levels and go, I don't really
care.
And I'm going to sit there and go, I remember this game was really fun.
This is like a really cool game back in like the fucking seventies when it came out and
it's cool.
But I'm going to get through the first three levels and go, all right.
That was some nostalgia.
That was fun.
And when I played Ratatouille, everyone was so excited for it.
And I played for three hours and I said, why this is OK, that was fun.
Sly Cooper is a great game.
It is.
I remember playing it when I was younger, but I would probably on stream, I'd probably
be like, all right, let's go.
And then I would get like through like an hour and a half in and be like, oh shit, I
got to shit.
I've got to take a shit.
I've got to leave guys.
I got to take a shit.
I would take a big poop.
And I would leave and then I would go to Holly after and go, man, that game, that game was
as bad as I remember.
Was it as bad as I remember?
I thought it was good.
And I'll just rant for like an hour and 25 minutes.
It's a totally completely fabricated scenario.
All right.
Stop.
I have to get to that of the tutorial so I can play.
All right.
Let's open.
Let's open the cash screen.
OK.
So this is how much cash like this is my cash management.
Lower the rate guards empty machines to less than 30 percent.
Now why is that?
The guards should attempt to empty objects holding cash when they have this full.
I get this 2500 bucks in machines and this 2500 bucks in the casino.
Cash in the bank.
Seven hundred eighty five thousand.
You are a background character in Friends.
Are you saying that because I'm one of the people that just says nonsense and moves their
mouth talking with a drink in their hand while like they do the scene in front of us?
What you're describing is I'm the person that I have that exact same conversation with one
of the other extras and it looks like I'm really talking and moving my hands.
But I said almost nothing.
That was I said almost nothing.
Is that what you meant by that statement?
No, you bet your ass.
You bet your ass I would look directly in the camera.
If I was ever in if I was ever in like a background actor in one of these shows, the camera's
going to go by and look directly in the lens and they're going to edit it and they're going
to be like, what the fuck, dude?
This guy looked right into the lens.
He looked right into the camera.
Why?
The one thing they teach you in like acting school is the camera does not exist.
And any time you like look into the lens, it's like it's like playing operation.
It's like, nope, wrong, wrong.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
We got it.
We're done.
I'm ready.
It's time to make our casino.
All right.
New.
Here we go.
Instant research, auto delivery, instant staff.
That's fine.
Watch.
How much money should I start with?
I'm going to say I'm going to say clean, cool, one million, clean, cool, one million.
So cool.
Is Mr. Green's back?
Well, well, stop talking.
Stop talking.
You're gonna get me in trouble.
All right.
How about just me?
Pre-built starter map.
No, I want to make my own.
We know you don't know.
You don't have any idea.
All right.
So this is where we're going to go.
132,000.
What's going on?
Is the fucking meteor hitting?
Oh, OK.
Why is it getting so dark?
Why did we hit the shadow?
What is this?
Oh, it's over here.
Oh, I like this.
279,000.
Isn't this a hotel?
All right.
So I make a hotel.
OK.
I'm going to buy these both.
This is going to be the hotel and this is going to be the casino.
All right.
Let's start here and go.
279,000.
You have no parking.
All right.
Here's what I want to do.
I want to have.
All right.
What is this music?
This is nice.
OK.
Look at this area we got to work with.
All right.
This is this is huge.
Oh, my goodness.
This is way too much.
This is too big.
Oh, my goodness.
This is way too much.
This is too big.
Uh, OK.
Um, let's just make a I'm going to have this is the big lobby, right?
Lobby is going to go off to the hotel.
So let's do here is this just opener that is huge is going to be a big lobby and then
leading over this way is the hotels.
So it's going to go yoink.
You need to start a war with pasta Italiano fucking crazy.
I wish they would remake that game, dude.
For those of you that new viewers that don't know what that is, Casino Inc is one of the
most outrageous video games I think it's ever been made, that it's I can't even explain
it.
Just you need to go.
You need to go watch the VOD.
That's all I can tell.
I'll go download it and play it on your own and just spoiler free and be like, holy shit.
What the hell were they doing?
It's like almost a perfect video game.
All right.
So let's go over this way.
This is going to be the hallway leading to the hotel.
And this would be a these would be a bunch of rooms here.
So this is like, all right, is the hallway then?
And I just wait, I just do a big.
Can I separate the rooms like, wait, hold on.
Oh, I can do that.
All right. Let me do that.
Never mind. I like that's going to be the table games room.
This will be the hallway to the hotel alone.
Delete this. If my how much do I get my money back if I delete stuff?
I don't get my money back if I don't if I do this.
How come I don't get my money back?
Wait, actually, I just let's have like a staff room right here.
We're going to find your casino and playthrough.
Um, it's just be on YouTube on the Archive Channel.
OK, I need to figure this out.
This is way too big.
So this would be like a casino floor.
We add a wall here. Hold on.
Yeah, like this, I like a bathroom here, right?
It's bathroom.
What else is in a casino?
Is casino ink a good purchase?
You know, I don't know how well it runs on Windows 11
or 10 or anything, right?
Because I played it, what, three, two, three years ago.
Was even on Windows 10 two, three years ago.
I don't know. Does it still run?
OK, so that looks good.
I need to get rid of this because this is going to be slots.
This would be table games and this is going to be the hotel.
Jesus. All right.
Hotel. This hotel is right here and it's going to be sick.
Build. OK, here we go.
All right. To me, this is a trap.
Right. This feels like I'm going to walk in here
and it's going to the room's going to like spikes.
They're going to shoot out. Hold on.
Can I put this higher?
I don't know. Why is the ceiling so low?
I don't get it. I don't care. Whatever.
I need outdoor paint. I need an ATM.
All right. All right. Hold on.
You only have one floor.
This is some Hey Arnold shit. That's what I'm saying.
OK, I needed first of all, I need front door door
commercial double door.
You know, it's been one of these.
Oh, wait, this is this with a garbage.
I can't have the front door be where the trash gets taken out.
I feel like I'm making this in Roblox.
OK, that's fine for now.
Wait, I want this to be different.
Don't people make full video games in Roblox
that you can't even tell the difference?
You can't tell that it was made in Roblox
because every pixel has been changed to every single
every ounce of paint.
That's crazy.
That's ridiculous.
Something about that is really cool.
OK, so what's this?
Oh, that's better.
And they even get through that. No, delete that.
How do I get this looks stupid with the grass.
I need like a new floor.
Um, excuse me.
OK, floor terrain. There we go.
Oh, here you're going to get the red carpet experience.
Yeah, that's fine.
What are you talking about?
It's been indoor floor. Why? OK, well, that's annoying.
This is this saxophone.
I don't care. That's fine.
All right, let's do, um, combinations.
This is OK, hotel.
So this is I got to put a sign here, right?
Desk to sell rooms to you. Oh, here we go.
Wait, why is it like a Wizard of Oz door?
Hold on, move this.
I don't understand. Why is it like this?
All right, door and an interior door.
Holy shit. All right.
I need a bathroom to the indoor door.
Hotel room zone. OK, this is the hotels.
I need to move this a little bit.
Now, because this is where somebody at the window takes the they pay.
There's a washing machine.
All right. I need a door, just a door door.
Commercial single door there. All right.
This is not a single hotel room, right?
This room or one of the sub rooms should contain a bed.
This is a that's a no, it's not.
Well, whatever, we make it fucking ten grand a week to rent it out.
No, it's not. I can make a little sub rooms, it said.
All right, so I need a I need a staff.
This hotel requires a laundry zone.
No, it doesn't.
The hotel requires a laundry since when?
OK, well, laundry make the laundry zone.
We'll make that like over here.
Yeah, that's perfect over here.
OK, this is laundry.
Laundry can be reached from the bus stop.
Why do I care that it can?
I don't care.
Oh, it's just that it has to go door to door door door door.
I get you. OK, I understand.
All right. That's the laundry room.
Let me do this later.
Let's get the fucking casino games.
How much money do I have? I got money.
OK, laundry washing machine.
How many should I do like two or three?
OK, and then what else does this need?
Requires to be protected behind a staff door.
You got it. OK.
Add storage shelves to increase the capacity.
Easy. Wait, this side probably.
Yeah, we're here. Look at that.
And we'll put we'll put we'll put a painting.
All right. Cool.
Our laundry room is here.
How much does it cost to use the laundry room?
How much does this cost to use the laundry room?
Make the wallpaper very loud.
I will in a minute.
OK, first of all, we need to figure this out because this is messed up.
Yeah, this is all messed up.
I got to fix this immediately.
It's not what I wanted to do.
But god damn it, whatever.
How do I just I want to get rid of the wall?
How do I get rid of the wall?
I just want to get rid of the wall.
There we go. There we go.
Yeah, I don't I don't want a door.
When you move around a casino floor, you don't open up doors
to go to the next area. You just walk.
There's not a single steam room door.
No, it's just open.
But it has to be this because we have to pay to get in here.
Why is there no face cam?
Yeah, I don't really feel that well today.
I've been like really fucking sloppy recently.
That's another reason why the green screen is not tonight.
But I still wanted to stream.
I didn't want to just not stream because I want to stream.
It's fun. I enjoy it.
But we'll do it again.
We it's ready to go.
The playlist, I think, has our two playlist, I think, hundred and twenty videos.
So there's a lot to watch.
I just didn't want to start laughing and just pop a blow a gasket in my brain
and get a migraine, have to turn the stream off in half an hour.
You know what I mean? I'd rather just save it, especially considering
I need I want to be ready for baseball in like a week and a half.
So I just I got to be careful.
I don't want to mess anything up before doing the baseball stream.
All right. But anyway, let's go.
Oh, you.
What do I want to do?
What are you doing flying a spaceship?
You didn't know what that was.
Find that person out.
OK, let's I don't get overwhelmed by the blueprint.
Okay, let's, um...
I'm gonna do tables first. Table games.
Or should I do decorations first?
Yes. That's what we're doing.
Okay, floor. Carpet. Oh, there we go.
Alright, I want...
Ooh, that's cool looking, but I can't undo it, so I need to make sure I like it.
This is cool.
Dude, casino floors all have
this wild,
actually cool grandma carpet.
It's like if grandma
wore a hat backwards, and
like, rode a skateboard. That's the kind
of carpet that's in every casino.
Yuck. I like that.
Hold on. I'm not picking it yet.
That hurts my head. These are all just
magic eyes. Oh!
Oh! Oh! Yeah,
look at that. I don't want it to be the entire casino.
That's a bowling alley? Yeah, bowling
alleys and casinos are very similar.
That's true. Why
is that? You know, I think it's like the same
mindset of casino
design and bowling alley design. That's
true. And bus seats.
Yeah. Oh, I know. I know.
I hide the puke. Right?
Yeah. It makes
sure that it hides all the puke. If you
puke on this carpet,
no one's ever going to know. That's
a good... That's true. You're right.
Should it be that the whole way? No.
This one's kind of boring.
I like the blue.
The first one?
Wow. That could be in a different
room. Could that be the hotel room floor?
Oh, wood.
What about this wood? That looks all right.
Wait, what?
What?
How much is this?
$28,000. That's it?
That's so stupid. All right. I gotta
make a decision here. This is
indecisive. This is fine.
No, that's ugly. I like this
one. Yeah, this one's good.
Laser tag. Yeah, I mean,
it's starting to kind of look like a Nickelodeon
TV set. That's fine, though.
This has to go all the way to the wall.
This looks fucking ugly. Get it right.
Get it right or don't stream.
You know what I mean? Get it right or turn
off the stream.
Okay, walls.
How about just bricks?
I need an exterior.
Ooh, I kind of like that.
I like this.
It's so bad. Why? I like...
It looks fine. It looks cool.
What's the problem with that?
If my grandma had a mansion, it would look like this.
Yeah, and your grandma would be having the
time of her life there.
Let's continue.
We haven't even put the games in yet.
I need interior paint.
Wallpaper.
Patrons are complaining of headaches every time
they come to the casino.
Themed walls?
I mean, now it's a casino.
Every casino has to be
Caesar themed.
Or Roman.
Why is that?
Why does a bunch of casinos have to be
like, look where it's Roman?
You know three casinos.
No, that Roman kind of
architecture is everywhere down here.
Bro, I live here.
I don't live in a casino.
That was my actually moment.
I actually don't hate this.
Yeah, definitely this.
Definitely this.
That's perfect.
It's so ugly.
Most casinos are kind of ugly.
They just are. They're very tacky, a lot of them.
It's like Roman statues
and bright green and pink
and like orange and magenta
colors.
They're wacky.
I think that's why I like them.
They're wacky places.
There's a fountain with a lion.
You know, a lion statue.
Guys, there's a casino boat here that has
a fucking pirate ship in it.
It's bizarre.
Oh yeah, there's a big pirate ship here.
All right.
It's cool. It's just weird
and tacky. It adds
taste. Oh no, you said ADHD
taste. I thought you were
being nice. Okay.
So this is going to be a bathroom.
This room looks delicious.
I want to come in here and just breathe the
air in here without the toilets.
I'm just saying the empty room.
I mean,
I just mean this.
The way that it looks, I feel like it's clean
and crisp.
Forget about what goes in here after.
I'm doing it.
Are you high? No, I'm not.
Guys, I'm not high.
All right, that's the bathroom.
Dude, this is going to be sick.
I need like a staff room too.
All right, I can start putting stuff down.
So I want
table games here.
Baccarat. Sweet game.
Blackjack.
I don't really, you know, I don't like Blackjack
that much anymore. I love Blackjack
but you know what? The game kind of sucks, if I'm honest.
PyGal. That's the game.
Now that's the game.
This game, let me tell you something about PyGal.
Ludwig put me on to this game.
And you can sit there
all day and not lose any money.
Like, well, let me preface that
by saying something very important.
Yes, you will lose money. But like, it's the slowest
fucking game in the whole casino.
You can just sit there
and just do little
bets and it's so easy to
push on PyGal. Blackjack
is like, oh, you lose, oh, you lose,
you lose, you lose, you lose, you lose.
It takes like, it takes like fucking
a full two or three minutes to do a game with PyGal.
You just sit there.
You can do fucking small little bets. It doesn't even matter.
Don't play at the fucking casino though.
Is that fun?
Gambling is only fun
if you go in with a small amount of money.
A certain small amount of money that you
know you're never going to get back.
And it's a form of entertainment that you
do very rarely.
Every so often,
rarely, is how
I find fun with the game.
Rarely. I lived in Vegas,
right? I know how
fucked up it can be.
Trust me. But,
I would be dishonest if I told you
that I didn't enjoy playing the games.
Uh, maybe every
few months? But,
that's it. Rarely, it's a
what do you mean? I moved
there. Dude, fuck off,
we know you live in Wisconsin.
What if I was just lying about living here the whole time?
No,
but PyGal is slow.
The last couple times I played Blackjack,
it's just like, okay,
I just, the dealer hit 20,
dealer hit 21, dealer hit 19, dealer has
20. Okay, well, what the fuck?
It's been 10 minutes.
He lives in Wisconsin.
Yeah, gambling should only be
a form of entertainment, very occasionally.
That's how I feel about it.
That's truly how I feel about it.
But I do enjoy it.
Go out with friends, sit around a table,
and just hang out. They got casinos
in Wisconsin!
Do they actually, do they? I actually have no idea.
You just seem bad.
You guys, you can't be bad at a casino
game. That's the thing you have to be, you want to
talk about fucking what you need to get out of your
head? You cannot be good
at a casino game.
There is no being good at a casino
game, unless it's poker.
Poker? Yes, you've, yes,
there is some, there's a lot going on there.
Poker, and some of those poker-oriented
games are. Everything else at the casino
is just throw a million
dice in the air and did you win. There's people that go
and they sit down at a slot machine and they go, no, no, no,
I know the secret. There is no secret.
The secret is the gigantic math problem that's playing
behind the reels.
That's it. Even Blackjack. Blackjack
has a low house edge, but it's just
random on, I mean, unless
you're like counting cards, which you can't do,
and a lot of these casinos
make sure you're not doing that. They have
like 8 plus 10 plus
deck games, so
it's not, that's not gonna happen. It's
illegal. You can't, it's not illegal.
What? But anyways, like roulette
too, like there is no like, no, no, no, no, no, I
know the number it's gonna be. No, you don't
know the number. Man, you just don't. You don't.
It's literally a ball that spins around in a
circle and lands on a
random slot. You might get lucky,
yeah, and when you do, nice.
It's fucking fun. That's it.
How come I can't unlock these? I need
to research ultimate house advantage.
Oh, I need a cashier cage.
Okay, I need a cashier cage. Let's put that in
here. But I'm not, I'm not gonna hear
this thing. I'm not gonna sit here and tell you
that what you shouldn't do
with your money, right? But I'm gonna tell you
to be careful with your money. That's it.
Be fucking careful. It's really
easy to get caught up in this shit. Just be fucking
careful. Genuinely is.
How come this is not flush?
Why is this not flush? I want this to be
flush with the wall. What the hell?
It can't be flush? Oh, there needs to be
a way for the cashier to get in.
Oh, they're gonna be stuck.
I'm sitting here going, why can't I make this
flush against the wall? Cause they would never be
able to leave. Okay,
I get it. I'll have to.
Somebody said, what do I feel about pineapple
vodka? That's a great drink.
That's a fantastic
beverage. I would recommend if you
are of the age to drink alcohol and
responsibly can drink.
It's a drink to drink. It's just simple.
There's no bullshit.
Not a bunch of nonsense. That's another thing.
Guys, I only drink like
five times, six times a year too.
As our most celebrated, most
intelligent scholar, Ben Franklin
said, all things in moderation.
Ben Franklin was the smartest person in the world. That's why he's on the hundred.
Ben's not on the one.
Ben's not on the five. Ben's on
the one hundred
dollar bill. Why do you think that is?
Why do you think Ben Franklin's on the one hundred?
He's one hundred!
Is that the guy from Jerma Rumble?
You know, there's a five hundred and a one thousand.
Yeah, okay.
What's the one thousand? There's no
one thousand note? There's no
thousand dollar denomination. Wait,
one thousand dollar bill.
Like its smaller cousin,
one thousand dollar bill was discontinued in
1969. Who was on it?
Grover Cleveland was on
the one thousand dollar bill?
And William McKinley was on
the five hundred dollar bill. They're not
in circulation anymore. Wait,
Grover Cleveland was on the one thousand?
What the hell? It existed,
but doesn't exist anymore. All right, let's
get a couple of roulette tables. Oh, we need
ATMs. ATM Andy.
But yeah, you're gonna,
when you go into the casino, that money you bring in
is, you need to go in with the mindset
of, this is already
gone. It's gone. Treat it
like it's already gone. And that's it.
Don't do anything else. You
are going to lose it. You might win
and it's, well cool, you did it. Hooray!
Treat it like it's gone and that's it and have
a good time with your friends. If you ever go to the, and
this is not, obviously I'm not trying to endorse a casino.
I'm just saying, that's how you should do
it. Don't do it any other fucking way.
I'm telling you, please listen to me.
If you're ever at a casino and you bring
whatever you're going to bring
for the night or for the weekend or for the week,
that's it. And it's gone.
Don't, do not
take that extra step to be like,
all right, I kind of blew through that.
I'm gonna go to the ATM
again. No, don't do it. Don't do it.
Don't. Don't do it.
Don't. Listen to me. Are you listening?
Don't. Do that.
I want you to think of me saying that, if you ever do that.
And just, and then if you're, you know, if you're over 21,
go get yourself a box of pineapple, you know?
And just sip on it. Just fucking walk around
and la la. Okay.
Texas Hold'em, that should be another room
for Texas Hold'em, right? I'll do what I want
with my money. And you are completely,
that's, yeah, that's up to you. Just
be fucking careful. Ben Franklin,
Ben Franklin's gonna like turn into
like a force ghost. He's gonna be in
front of you. He's gonna have a cigar in his mouth.
He's gonna have, he's gonna have,
he's gonna have like a fucking invention in one hand.
And like in his other hand, it's gonna be
a, I don't know,
I almost said chainsaw. He's gonna
just show up. He's gonna just have like a, he's gonna have a
kite in one hand. And
a chainsaw in the other hand.
And just, he force ghosts in front
of you. And I don't know what Ben Franklin
sounded like, but I imagine it was something like this.
What you should do
is absolutely not
find your way back to the ATM.
Turn around.
All things in moderation, my friend.
Leave the casino.
And go with your friends somewhere else.
And then if he just
grrrank valued
hhaaaany in the
d, he's cut he's cut like a bush.
John Oliver. What if you're on a winning streak?
If you're on a winning streak then the Ben Franklin
goes boom! Poops up.
He's like he's with two ladies.
He's got a cigar. Let me tell you
what you should do here. Put it all
on black all things in moderation there's like two there's like three people by there's like
there's like three dudes behind him like cheering him on and then you say ben you're full of shit
weren't you and then he just he looks at you he gives you a wink and he like tick tick he tick
ticks the cigar down poof and he's gone the house always but he invented gambling no he didn't
i don't i want this room to be yeah poker's in a different room it always is blackjack game sucks
i don't like blackjack now being blackjack are not talking at the moment hmm i don't like that
placement i hate this stupid bacon carpet why all right so let me uh this is this is all right for
now we got blackjack roulette uh we're gonna do slots in here these are expensive why are
these so expensive holy shit dude really how do they do it at a casino they like kind of do like
this what the fuck is he doing they do this is i'm telling you this is how they set him up this is
how they do it although this should be this should be over here xgc and then a
this and then uh this one no no that no i don't that's not enough room
this dude's the fucking anti-christ these are way too expensive i need the i need the bar right in
the middle so we're gonna go like this let me do the bar first oh uh-huh there you promised i
didn't do it the right way all right betting big tv oh nice wait this is gonna be like a section
where they can hold on you gotta be able to watch tv somewhere right i should put this over here
yeah no i don't like the bar in the middle bullshit get rid of that uh how do i deselect this sorry
i'll use it in a minute shit i don't want to just i'm gonna lose the money do the bar on the right
do a timeout corner rotate it yeah but this doesn't work over here oh i hate that it's i
don't know i hate this because it can't be flush because the this would be way in and out i hate it
i mean whatever make a couple tvs tv here we go put a small tv in there what should go in the
middle here a fountain like some kind of cool decoration no slots in here lots are all over
here i'm gonna do another one of these corners over here i'm gonna oh the game jack put the
statue of liberty in the middle it's so dumb uh we'll do another corner here did i screw it up
yeah i did here we go should i put this in the corner here or the corner here
here comes the big look at it listen to this um it's kind of too far it's too close to the door
what are you gonna get when the customer is gonna enter um in a minute i just need to make sure i
have everything ready that's okay right there right that's right that's fine and then we're
gonna do one row one row and then i'm gonna put toilets in make the whole and then we're gonna
open this shit up in public so green screen got delayed yes green screen got delayed not by very
long less than a week i just wanted to just chill and just play a game today for reasons that i
described a little bit but i can go over again i woke up with a pretty bad migraine and laughing
really hard at funny hilarious media is stuff i probably don't want to do right now okay i need
to make a second floor well hold on let me do the first floor first okay what do i need business
okay printing stationed computer desk all right conference rooms i need like a staff room don't i
do i need a staff room okay so let's do sync with cabinet sync i thought this was tv
lose the hotel why would i delete the hotel no i'm not i'm not ready for the i can do the hotel in a
second hold on how much of beds this is all i can put wait single i requires researching a grand
hotel all i can do is single beds here we go there it is oh yeah we're gonna make tons of money
it's gonna be insane um and then a couple down here shit no go back go back go back i don't i
screwed it up delete it public bathroom in the hotel no these are these are big enough for a bed
hold on no what the fuck what i can i not make this a bathroom i'm so confused oh okay private
here we go okay just make a singular long bathroom no half the room is the bathroom you know how
uncomfortable a small bathroom is i've stayed in hotels before where the bathroom was as big
as an airplane bathroom and it sucks i need room i need space i need room in the bathroom i hate
the shit where you're sitting on the toilet and the toilet paper is essentially almost touching
your leg and the sink is touching your elbow and the no give me some room give me some room i need
room i've cursed out loud when i open up the door to the bathroom i see that the sink is within
elbows reach of the toilet and it's a bit like wood it's like a box and you can literally just
sit and squeeze in there until i don't know why people like what and some of these hotels are
like fucking hundreds of dollars a night you know what i mean can i i'm gonna go off here
um i'm gonna this is a very important thing to talk about i don't get i don't i don't
let me preface this by saying i don't want to i'm not gonna i hope i don't piss anybody off
with this but i don't think i will hotels that are like kind of old and that's the point where it's
like oh yeah the room is like fucking old and the bathroom is old and the plumbing is old and the
whole thing is fucking old well that'll be that'll be three or four hundred dollars a night i i i want
i want a bathroom that's fucking new i don't want to turn the shower on it's like
and they have to sit there and wait for the water to get like 20 minutes 20 minutes with water get
hot you know what i mean that's an overstatement but you know what i mean it's like just old for
the sake of being old and they cost more than just staying at like a regular ass hotel i just get all
this is all i want i want a clean room small with just a bed a functioning television and a clean
bathroom and the plumbing works and it's not like oh well you know this uh this place has been here
for uh you know 500 years or whatever and the plumbing is 500 years old too give me 500 dollars
a night i just i don't i don't need a fancy hotel just something with a bed it's clean and it's ready
to go this place sucks you it's not done yet so hold off on that dude america hasn't existed for
but you know what i'm talking about where it's like hey by the way we took this whole school gym
and we made it a hotel you know what i mean like i just i just want a fucking holiday in
just give me like a marion i don't care my college dorm was an old old hotel
millionaire streamer no no you don't you're missing the point here i don't want to spend
400 a night on one of these i just want to go to the i just want to go get the continental breakfast
at the holiday in i just want to wake up and get the cereal the orange juice what's by the way
continental orange juice is the best orange juice you could ever drink i don't know why i
love it so much the one that comes out of the machine in the lobby it's the machine and it has
the machine is probably from like 1995 and when you they all make the same noise when you go up
and you press the button you take your glass and you're gonna go and it's the most delicious
orange juice i've ever had dude that's just radioactive it's full of mold and the best part
is you dude listen to me you can go up to that machine as many times as you want that old
barely functioning orange juice machine you can go up there 10 times if you want it's bottomless
oj the it's the continental breakfast he likes the bacteria for flavor yeah and sometimes
he's like they just got bagels they have cereal where you peel the top of the lid off and you
just put some milk in it there's always coffee and let me the coffee at a continental breakfast
is so good i went to uh just a random like two or three star hotel one time i forget what it was
but they were changing that shit out and they were just like i remember going where the fuck
was it i'm trying to remember the what like chain it was but the the person that was working there
was switching the coffee out it was like brand new how's the coffee it's coffee coffee's great
coffee's great man this is fantastic hey how's that orange juice it's clean it's crystal it's
delicious you know it was great i love hotels i really do i swear to god i love just like a
holiday inn or like a like a like a marriott or something just like like a three star or two star
hotel i like a wave in to the uh to the like the the clerk they're set there oh like they're
friendly like how are you like how have a great day you have it no you have a good fucking day
that continental orange juice is the best orange juice i've ever had in my life anyways i haven't
pressed play in two hours and i'm giving myself a headache at least relax okay please play the game
i know come on i gotta go off on my funny comedy podcast rants look all right uh i gotta fix this
do a hotel ranking what's the worst hotel i've ever stayed at i could probably i don't know it
wasn't a chain i'll tell you that i'm certain of that dude give it up i don't know what that
means you mean like the game do you mean like streaming do you mean talking about two star
two and a half star hotels what do you mean what about motel six um nope no it's got to be i'm
telling you no no not a motel six i don't all right i don't like hotels where the door is just
like there you are bill burr had a hysterical uh talking point about this what it was like
and those hotels or those motels where it's just like the door and then there you are just lying
in bed and it's just like if somebody it's just like the outside world is right there and there's
a door right there and you're lying in the bed he talks about this and he talks about like you're
not ready like if somebody's just there just like breaks the door and it's like gonna get you you're
just like lying there it's fucking hilarious it's a hysterical rant a motel yeah no i don't i don't
motels freak me out i want like the door and then like the other door to my room to be snacks in
here you're gonna put the any windows in here no there's no time for that all right beds let me
just get through this so i can i can hurry up and play this game already it's been like three hours
it's been two and the and to be fair the first the first like 40 minutes i wouldn't even playing
turn it turn it why is this different color why is this different color
no it's a hotel room okay hotel room this is gonna make a shit load of money you guys have no idea
um
i'm small i'm a little guy right i don't think i fit on this bed this is so this is like a tube
of toothpaste this is so small i mean i'm smaller this i feel like i wouldn't fit i need a big bed
let me just tell you i need a big bed that's what i need i i like just rolling around it
i take my comfort very seriously okay so now i need to put what else goes in like a hotel room
uh toilet stall oh no that's over here i'll do that later okay what else goes in in their room
oh shit they need sinks do they really need sinks let's be honest oh my god they all need showers
too this is such a huge investment this is an insane investment how they gonna wash their hands
in the shower just turn the shower on and get in the shower oh can you imagine can you imagine
somebody being like oh hey yeah dude we'll get down there oh casino let's go yeah man oh let's go to
the blackjack hold on i gotta wash my hands real quick and they just turn the shower on and they
just get in the shower and they take a shower a full shower i'm telling you i'm just going down
i'm just going i'll be like all right i'll meet you down there hey finally he's finally at the
crap stable all right so now they have a bathroom i need i need they need a goddamn sink don't they
whatever fine spending so much money here look this is what i hate the most this is what i hate
more than anything tiny little toilet in this fucking sink right next to your head and the
toilet paper is right here it's right there and it's touching you and you have to like
you have to reach your arm out of the way in any place any bathroom any hotel room
where i cannot use the hand closest to the toilet paper to get the toilet paper i have to move
that arm out of the way go cross section across my body and pull it with the other hand get that
out of here that's annoying that's what i'm doing it's ugly it's not it doesn't matter how ugly it
is it needs to function i'm telling you you put a 1995 orange juice dispenser in one of these i
don't care i don't care i don't care if there are bugs in this hotel room i thought my game crashed
okay all right what else do i need accommodations let me go like a computer desk 1200 bucks wait
jacuzzis exercise bike they don't they don't need any more than this bedroom entertainment
a wine rack get out of here big okay everyone needs a tv are there any smaller tvs okay there
we go wait why is this more expensive what the what is happening why is this more expensive than
the plasma screen gigantic television uh that's kind of that's a little weird that's weird
oh swanky okay everyone has a tv right everyone's got a tv everybody's got all right oh wait
how much money do i have okay we have is it wait do i need wait i don't get it is this a reception
do i need a reception here before you come in or is that technically a reception is this a reception
i don't get it i don't know uh movie theater ticket taker i think this is good to go how do i
charge an exorbitant amount for these rooms how do i charge money for them neon toilet one neon
wait these are neon wait these are toilets what oh it's a decorative object it's a sign
okay all right all right all right rgb pissing okay no this is not a private bathroom this is
a man-sized bathroom what the fuck just do one singular toilet i'm doing privacy this i'm this
is i'm doing privacy what are you talking about what am i i don't want to do one gigantic bathroom
should i just do one huge bathroom just one huge bathroom make it a maze just one huge communal
bathroom all right fine i'll make one gigantic i was gonna make like privacy it's not gonna be
open by the way no how do i delete this shit should i just put toilets on the casino i'm gonna
put yeah fuck this we don't need a bathroom why waste the space why waste the space people
are gonna be showering at like the most fucked up thing ever oh you imagine there's somebody just
sitting here playing like wheel of fortune slots and there's somebody sitting in this chair and
you have to come over here and take a shit behind them how could you do that there's no way this
works i i doubt this is actually gonna work i'm gonna get like an error message that's like oh
no i can't begin the failed toilet stall yeah see requires enclosed space this room requires
but hold on hold on wait wait wait wait i don't understand wait can i just do two walls
must be a functional private bathroom zone oh place the stall first oh shit what what is that
good enough okay that's fine these are just porta potties what the hell have you done what have
you done i just want to get rid of the wall what have you done i gotta slow down what the fuck is
going on what all right what is happening here dude i just want to take down the wall
okay i promise we're all right we might as well just start the game we have enough right i got
enough stuff i got enough stuff i have enough stuff i'm gonna hit play after we put the toilets
in i'm gonna hit play there's enough to start i would not go to the bathroom in these i would
not go to the bathroom in this would not the best part of all this is no one will play at this
machine or this one it's gonna play at these two dude this should be a slot machine on the other
side this should be a slot built in here okay i'm hitting play come on in everybody oh wait
freeze i gotta do payout shit okay delivery delivery all right what about this game settings
player gambling confidence so this is the minimum bet off off peak hours five bucks is fine oh
saturday and sunday this is good this is going to a ten dollar table now 15 bucks roulette minimum
bet that's fine let's make this 10 15 oh i can copy it across everything right yeah uh here we go
okay atm you know you have no employees the staff is hired automatically right yeah see staff is
automatically hired wait i have to do the this stuff pause i'm almost ready okay bison thrash
it costs a dollar jackpot 10 bucks that's fine uh these are gonna be big though display cost is
five bucks jackpot gonna be 50 house advantage 12 come on oh it's nine percent is the max edge
oh okay all right let's begin all right let's get in the laundry going get that started nice first
customer what's all this trash oh customer nope where the customers operations where the fucking
customers there we go that's the casino express bus where you going hey where you going dude it's
8 30 a.m. oh are they getting ready for the day this is so dog shit i need something here
decoration something cool it's entertainment something cool customer all right where you're
gonna go going for the high slots what are you gonna play oh that's a good choice you're gonna
get the hotel one room hey hey hey you can't go in there you can't go in there without paying
she's confused oh you know honestly okay i thought she was naked or something i looked over i was
like what is going on when i zoomed in i thought i thought she was naked what don't put that shit
everywhere what is this there's only one person oh here we go yep yep good good good all right
i need a storage room all right storage room uh storage zone right where's it staff door okay
good now put that shit over here what's my operating cost there are two people here
oh i need a pit boss zone a pit boss office oh shit okay hold on they can be like right here
boss office staff door there we go all right now let's get some table games running requires
enclosed space i think this is uh i think this is messed up guys i don't think we can do this
here comes the casino bus come on stop driving by i have to close it off damn it yeah all right
i'll have to make a bathroom how come it's so empty because this place sucks it'll get better
once the table games start and we can get the hotel going and we're staying here must be merged
with another private room what i don't understand what's going on wait there are no rooms this must
not be inside of a staff protected area excuse me hotel room one oh okay so um what do i do about
that the lobby is a room but how do i how do i fix that de-zone this has been de-zoned and now
the room requires its own wardrobe get out of here with this bullshit i need to put a wardrobe in
these this is the kind of room that i would wake up in and i i don't know why i just thought of
this me and my family were on vacation one time this is a long time ago this and we were like
little kids i was probably i don't know i want to say maybe 10 and we we like rented out this
cabin or something and we were on like a big vacation to go out and like the go camping and
shit and they had these this big bedroom that was upstairs it was like this kind of big loft
and the ceiling was kind of slanted down and uh our beds were kind of up against the walls
so because the way the ceilings were slanted when you when you were lying in the bed your head
it was kind of the ceiling kind of went diagonal over your head in a way and i'm trying to think
like exactly how the architecture was but my brother woke up in the morning
and he like just got right out of bed in the morning and just smashed his head against like
the ceiling it was the way that like the ceiling was angled i'm trying to forget how it happened
but he just woke up and was like oh yay it just it was so excited to be to get out of bed and
just smash his head against the ceiling i don't know if they were like wooden frames or something
i've done that before clown family
this stuck with me for a decade a decade two decades three decades i we were we were at the
mall one time and we were walking around and there was this you know in the mall how there's those
big standing advertising kiosk things they have like three or four sides it's like a huge led like
a big screen right and it's like there's an ad on this side or something on this side something
on this side i i don't know why there was a goldie hawn movie that we were walking me my brother
and like my family was in the mall and my brother for some reason thought thought that this goldie
hawn movie poster he's like oh look look it's goldie hawn i don't know why this was such a
funny like thing like it was like he was just pointing at stuff and i will never forget this
he was just sitting there pointing and laughing while we were walking at this goldie hawn
poster i don't this is a long time ago and i was standing right next to him walking alongside him
and in my peripheral there was in one of those stand up kind of metal plastic stands with another
ad on it and he walked his face and head directly into the thing it was like that was such a horrible
voice crack but his face went like go go and he smashed his head into it i swear to god it's one
of the funniest like three stooges things i've ever seen in my whole life i don't know it's stuck
with me forever that would just jump that'll jump into my brain sometimes where my brother just
laughing point like like he was not he did not know this was coming and he got rocked and i
think it was like the funniest thing i've ever seen that's a three stooges thing i'm i'm telling
you it's it was funny your brother is the funny one my brother is hilarious yeah my brother is
hysterical cartoon cartoon and dna it just pops in sometimes because it was immediately after he
started laughing it was just like karma like it was just we were walking walking ha ha ha bang
like it was he didn't even have one to two full seconds to laugh it's like it he didn't i don't
know how he didn't see this coming to bring your family on stream i already did that okay is this
good these are good right this problem is solved now right all right we got we got patrons people
are here yeah all right where's our income uh you must have at least one pit boss what's wrong with
the pit boss office it's here pit boss i need a computer desk okay there where's the pit boss
let's go here we go here we go where's the delivery delivery coins and notes by oh i don't
have a security guard oh shit security off requires researching advanced security where do i do that
oh pizza oh you're gonna sit down and uh blackjack why roulette all right what are you gonna do
nice nice nice all right how much does it cost this is where we're on peak hours right now right
just do one dollar on one 100 times you actually can't do that 11 a.m is peak oh what hold on let's
fix this why is nobody using the fucking hope i mean hold on why doesn't why would i swear
why is nobody using the freaking hotel oh it's because it's ugly hold on all right now i need
uh tile oh this is cute i guess i don't know what the freak now i need no it's got to be
something weird something wacky that's kind of wacky do you do what does this person do i need
more machines these are filling up fast nobody why is nobody drinking oh it's because it's 12
o'clock what do you think about the casino i want to gain some confidence before i play anything
risky all right these are popular over here i need more this is an l casino yeah i need pause pause
pause these people are leaving because there's not a slot all right i need more of these let's go a
line like this make sure there's enough room that should be good for a little bit what are you buying
oh nice i thought this was a photo booth what how do i get delivery here scheduling add a you oh
wait wait wait what time is it is monday staff open it up open this shit open it i don't understand
what's what's wrong it's saturday monday through friday what the fuck saturday and sunday use weekday
schedule open it i need security guards well how do i hire them can nobody cash out their chips
where's research that's the problem utilities staff security facilities requires advanced
security where do i research a lot of people coming in i need a payout receipt let's go how
do i hire more people oh wait staff management security guard okay wait wait build a cash vault
to hire this staff build a kitchen build a research office that's what i need this needs
a computer desk and a staff door okay research office complete you don't have a cash vault
employee oh shit um cash vault zone okay well i'll do that right here computer and a staff
door right yep okay must be in a functional computer room i don't get it what are we good
computer room i think they're right here we go are they actually doing it use your other brain
add storage shelves to increase okay no no no this is this is all right i think that just
somebody has a worker has to come over here yeah there we go yep security guard why is this guy
just sitting here there's not enough stuff to do somebody go stay in the hotel please all right
here we go go in here what are you doing i don't understand what's going on i don't get it uh okay
i need to delete this wall what's the what is this guy doing okay i gotta get rid of the walls
no don't go in there wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on
oh shit what i don't get it i can't do i need to move him closer and get rid of this guy
hotel reception window finances scheduling okay so we've get rid of this guy i need paint
no no that's too too clean here we go doc talk to this person i what what are they doing um
excuse me rooms are free everybody just came over here but what are you even thinking right now
it was too hot today all right give me a reception okay consumes 10 cents worth of indoors only
trusted staff a desk to sell rooms and hand back their hotel keys so what's going on this should
work there is no reset reception zone maybe they're just standing right here there's no
reception zone all right he's back is there is no it's not there's not search reception yeah i just
did reception it's just this stuff i need more machines how about take oh we got the cash cash
here's there all right good good good good good let's go let's go let's go there we go what was
that get rid of this what's going on it's not a single working bathroom no one's using any of
these oops sorry well it's a good way for you to leave okay bathroom okay whatever um toilet
no you idiot okay then a bunch of sinks okay there we go stalls on this side too get in there all
right go ahead you can use the bathroom oh man finally people are like holy shit uh no they're
all going to the hotel buy a room at the hotel they're too low on cash they only have three
hundred dollars how much is a night at the hotel i was gonna say really dude really bro there's
like 50 stalls open and you're gonna go to the one next to the person that's sitting in one
i was supposed to say no what the hell is going on here does nobody have enough money all right
this is gonna look nicer this looks like shit hmm what's that roman statue shit where is it
okay we're good table games are doing all right nobody's really playing them
did i make the minimums lower you never have to leave the bathroom they actually are doing this
okay i need another out row slots here oh i think the seat definitely this one nice whoa
oh where are they going they're trying to rush into the bathroom why do they all need to do that
at the same time yeah you tell me this is made 142 total what are you talking about no chance
all right i need something else i need another game i need research am i researching oh nice
you're researching what are you researching boredom okay 100 satisfaction that's pretty sick
everyone's really happy this is awesome social media campaign i'm gonna hand out leaflets local
newspaper and the radio why i need to i need another row machines right here i need minute
oh wait wait wait wait wait i could i'm not gonna put a conference room in here because
dude nobody cares about my hotel devin chat oh my fucking god what happened uh
uh i need to make this fucking bigger this all right these are not big enough
hey don't no no no don't leave don't leave all at once why won't anybody use my hotel room
just going back and forth this is more fun than anything in the whole casino
it's like why won't they go sit down they're all just following each other in a huge line
i need more shit to do no oh my god thousands of people are leaving whoa what are they doing
where are you going oh shit there's no room everything's full oh my god that's what's
going on hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait this is what's going
on oh my god okay all right all right wait wait uh there's too many people here there's too many
people way too many people huh what what happened i'm out of money how do i get more money
no it's gone it's it's gaining what a waste of two hundred thousand dollars this was huh
what a waste of money no one has bought one room zone it it is zoned look hotel room hotel hotel
hotel hotel hotel laundry he's it's ready zone i did make the slots higher get rid of the wall
separating the hotel from the casino hey like that jesus i need an undetected game cheater
bragged online that they stole 27 dollars why would you brag online about stealing 27
dollars from like a multi-million dollar casino what is wrong with you don't do that okay that
means that they pressed the button at the vending machine and got like five extra bags of chips
i'm raking in dough now this is the only food in the entire casino is a potato chip dispenser
people are starving it's just a soda machine and a chip vending machine buy a hotel room buy a
hotel room all right am i researching i need a restaurant research buffet and kitchens oh
there's a movie theater zone the reception you don't understand i there is no zone reception
look where there it doesn't exist look there's no zone these are just it's a sign hotel hotel
room zone but that i this is i don't want this to be a hotel room hotel laundry zone see just
make it a dance floor i'm making money i need i where's my research shit you see what that says
okay look reception this is just a sub menu is that the room price i don't know how
i there i can't yeah that's a sub menu is this person actually researching anything or
what what's going on where's my research tab kitchen requires buffet and kitchens what where
hover over the rooms yeah they're done see hotel room clean status clean single bed
this is ready research is on the bottom oh here we go all right table game rule editing
sportsbook hold on i don't have to wait i don't have to research a hotel right purchase costs
15 000 bucks security celebrity guests faster internet i want food operations finance hub
attractions hub manage entertainment accommodation wait here we go oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah so
what this is what's going on hotel room group settings price per night is this the problem
should be like 40 40 dollars a night 20 dollars a night okay 20 bucks a night wait no come on it's
open right it's open isn't it midnight to midnight open simple 24 hours 20 bucks is steep what are you
talking about 20 bucks for a hotel room for a night all right i got eight grand is it the door
type excuse me hey did you pay to you didn't pay to get in here who's this did she pay
did she pay was it actually just too expensive these people pay no look the bank counts 300
299 one person paid this she paid should i make it like 15 bucks make it 10 bucks all right i'm
gonna make it 10 bucks that lady's gonna be pissed 10 bucks a night get out of here it's the same day
all right we have a new customer look at the time of day yeah it's nine o'clock
people are coming in trying to get some rest okay i need a restaurant i'm at i'm making a profit
here whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what happened what happened what
happened what just happened why did i lose 10 grand what just happened what just happened
they store wait whoa what's happening what pick that up give me that fucking money you
don't store that 10 grand get out of here all right we're getting customers in the hotel now
someone hit the jackpot there the jackpot is 50 bucks on these machines the guys not 10 000
transfer to vault stop transferring money into the vault well i guess wait can i get robbed
it's for the cashiers am i gonna get robbed i'm so paranoid about that look at the bars on the
bottom right popular game gambling is popular entertainment everything else hotel is not popular
popularity five percent i need to make more slots excuse me taxes well i i i can i look and see
what just happened there why did i lose that much money where's my finances staff electricity and
then taxes total cash in the casino 38 grand well go get it go get it yeah when they're like 20
full go get it give me that money this thirty thousand dollars in these machines that we have
not collected um why why why is 30 grand sitting in the machine you mean to tell me i could have
had thirty thousand dollars in capital here well let's go 20 grand there we go all right
24 grand 25 grand thank you that's better all right now let me research um pizza buffet
21 000 okay buffet and kitchens i need 15 grand all right give me that money how how do i just
how do i get this can i just take it how do i take money out of the vault don't sell the bags i want
this money they're bringing bags of money over here this 30 000 it's supposed to be in the vault
well i only have 900 bucks so this trash change stored cash in the menu stored cash involved
20 oh okay um what if i do to make it like one dollar minimum vault level okay minimum vault
10 grand then all right store 10 grand then what the fuck do i care there we go all right now let's
make a pizza place okay buffets and kitchens what excuse me 10 hours required all right research
buffets and kitchens i guess with an urgent environment need wants to leave huh who wants
to leave i don't understand where are you going you crossed the street over you you it's a law
abiding citizen to the very end what was the matter can they can they not get in the why can't they get
into the bathroom i don't understand why they can't just use the bathroom this guy's getting on the
bus what what's happening why does this keep happening i don't i zone the bathrooms yeah
weirdly enough no one's been using them though oh it's because this is technically not a closed
bathroom anymore because the revolving door oops does this count does that count this counts right
i think so no it doesn't what the fuck because i have to make it a fall guys level because they
don't all go into the same door they all run into the same door okay that is good now all right we're
all not on peak hours anymore how's the hotel doing environment what's wrong with the environment
oops hold on oh okay there are no trash bins anywhere okay so let's make that restaurant
how's the hotel doing all right yeah we got their patrons here nice this room all these
rooms are dirty how do we clean them raise the hotel price no it's making me money i need to
hire housekeepers i think oh wait that's right i need to all right where's my staff page staff
management all right garbage i need there's like one person here uh two and then one okay and then
deliveries these are fine cash vault two pit boss how many security guards all right i want to make
that pizza place or the buffet whatever it is i think how long does this take all right four am
five am is it almost ready i guess with urgent thirst well this of this bar has tons of snacks
soda beer wine it's right here wait there's nobody working here has there been no one working here
the whole time is the bathroom not working it should be right it says it in closed space oh
open open all right here comes the crowd there we go all right trash is getting nice and clean
all right cool cool cool cool cool now we're gonna put the buffet right like here no buffet's going
over uh all right the buffet is gonna go this way here put the buffet in the bathroom i can't i have
to zone it i can't do that all right is it ready hurry up oh my god hurry up at least i have money
yeah no one's using the bathroom why they were before people were using it before well fuck it
then i'm just trying all right then fuck this what just happened oh this is a bathroom the whole time
uh that's fine do you fuck with hummus yes a million percent delicious these machines are
really popular i'm not gonna move them have any showers lying around no why would it be no no
shower no shower in here i don't want never mind not a shower i mean sinks what damn oh this is
fucking guitar okay there we go that works i already owned them okay so this is a bathroom
it's good it's ready now that's fine now i need a buffet soon there we go all right people can use
the bathroom now we're good this room is way too popular to dismantle this and move this shit
around no way make it the high roller room kind of already is isn't it oh my god what the
huh stop stop stop stop stop what was that why were they just clipping through steal
who stole wait they just stole that whole group just ran by and just ghosted through everything
and stole everything that was bizarre i don't even know how to react to that uh oh god okay i gotta
get ready um i need yeah we need food everyone's hungry hurry up with that research all right it's
ready pause it let's go from here uh probably off the street from okay i need more foot traffic near
the hotel so you have to walk through the hotel to get to the food the restaurant because i want
people to walk this way and have their dumb ai brain go hotel and buy it okay stupid pile of
shit why why i don't know what what word was i going to say there i don't know punk piss all
right demolish this you're that indoor area huh it's a fucking chimney get rid of it
whatever i'll put the fridge there this is ugly what you make your casino and i'll judge yours
what the hell am i crazy or what why can i get rid of this why can i get rid of those can't select
the wall is the movie night tonight no the movie night was pushed to probably this coming weekend
like next weekend just delete it what are you i'm trying to demolish dismantle walls and fences
demolish structure what the hell demolish structure uh wall objects why can i not do this
stop clicking the x um i don't want to do that though because that's going to delete the whole
thing it's going to be the same thing as it before see what the fuck no oh my god you know what here
dismantle walls and fences see okay look it works why did it not work before yeah you watched me do
that come on man whatever i can have a wart i don't care all right let's do it i need money
all right buffet zone dessert buffet seafood buffet steak all right let's have a seafood and
dessert buffet seafood dessert i can't do pizza i can do steak here we go seafood steak dessert
now we need uh tables dining how do you spell dining beer dispenser oh here we go nice i can't
connect them why not make everybody sit together that's i was trying to make a big community table
all right now i need to make it look nice how much does this cost i don't think i can set the price on
it buffet zone all right now we need flooring that's nice that's more of that let's go uh is
there like a sign i can put up individual letter business enter gym hotel indoor oh individual
letters wait what this is like bridge magnet letters oh wait hold on a second i gotta have my
better my better business bureau ranking i gotta have my uh my health inspector ranking go get some
food how did you get in here this is a customer they've been here for four hours in the pit
office how did you get in uh this is a terrifying room what is g i'm gonna take a walk through the
casino can i play the game nice fucking gamer posture these ceilings they're so low i feel
like this is gonna cave in or something like this is terrifying why are they so low minecraft
ceilings here we go bar looks good this is giving me anxiety i don't like this
this is actually scary i would not be in here i would not go here the doom level are there any
sound effects i'm just realizing something i haven't heard any of this the whole game
that looks weird let's see if this person wins oh you got three pigs you did it he was not happy
about that you're gonna play or what play here we go he's missing cigarettes let's see what happened
oh they're frustrated i lost the slop machine it's too hot he ate at the buffet dude no one is
here uh hold on i mean did they just not know it exists no one's staying at the hotel anymore
by the way why why people were staying all right come on look at this huge group of people to the
buffet to the buffet is it just too far away there's no food yes there is this food this food in there
zero out of a hundred oh how do i put food in it a phase zone right yeah it's there do i need
a separate kitchen uh kitchen prep kitchen fridge does that make sense it doesn't say
any requirements i need a kitchen to prepare the food oh my god really are you shitting me
here's your kitchen um kitchen oh wow there's a ton of requirements here i need kitchen zone
i did that all right i need kitchen prep kitchen hot plate kitchen sink it's supposed to be much
bigger music was keeping me sane well everyone told me to turn it off everyone's like turn it
off turn it off i can't it's it's good music but i don't want to hear it anymore okay kitchen cooker
kitchen hot plate kitchen prep kitchen storage okay are we ready kitchen hot plate kitchens ready
bring me a chef put the music back on okay make the food let's make some more money i need wooden
floors good and then we need um there you go just a kitchen it's a kitchen all right where's the chef
somebody just came in here who is that there we go all right nice now let's make some food and
let's make let's get this buffet rolling why are you moving crates she's coming in individually
bringing crates back and forth i need cash register sign this to a kitchen huh what do
you mean to sign it to a kitchen cash register what do you mean must contain a drinks or beer
dispenser and how do i assign it sign this to a kitchen that that work i just she just i fired
her because i fired that lady no get back in here no don't go home work at the kitchen how do i
assign is there a way to do that go to the kitchen settings oh assign to sign to yeah all right let's
do it fill it up let's make some money yep okay this is where they they're gonna float over here
they're gonna know this food now how much does this cost pretty good there we go get that get
that dessert out there anyway i got 30 000 now we're making money excellent i don't understand
the hotel though oh there we go it's being used nice what i can research other stuff though
giant casino sign linked jackpots sports book high limit elegant decor a gym theater theater
dance floor definitely dance floor you guys got 32 bucks left this is making money all right let's
fast forward 12 hours what an adult movie theater in you can do that in casino language is insane
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa pause pause pause pause it huh urgent sleep so go to the hotel why do
they think i have a hotel here is it occupied oh my god it kind of is it is occupied by everybody
is it another there's still there's three rooms all right but we gotta put the price up
running cost 330 lifetime profit negative 400 environment is really bad well what do you want
yeah we're gonna make this a little more expensive 12 free service offer free snack and drink from a
server if a loss is of at least 10 bucks okay wait no wait what offer a room worth up to 100
dollars they lose more than that value free buffet offer gift vouchers worth 20 dollars
if a loss of at least 20 wait so if you come in here with 20 dollars and you lose 20 dollars
i will give you 20 dollars how how am i isn't that just me giving money to people
like you're just getting zero zero you come in you come in i will give you come in i'll give
you a hundred dollars oh i see okay all right you know if you spend 100 bucks i'll give you
a ticket to the buffet hey you stay in the hotel you get um no i well wait wait no no no no no
free snack and drink if you yeah all right if you lose 100 bucks i'll give you a free snack
that sounds all right people are pissed what a ripoff i come with uh yeah i come with airplane
peanuts oh you lost two thousand dollars that's all right here are some stale pretzels and by the
way there's only six in the bag is there ac in the casino maybe not whoa what's 20 000 what was
that taxes a 26 000 in taxes what is up with that i'm doing all right i didn't take a loan out or
anything it's well how many days how many days has it been it's been three days and i had to
pay that much in tax oh i pay taxes every day no it's definitely been more than three days
oh it's winter time okay when do i get my dance floor dance floor is ready let's go
and i'm gonna take out a huge campaign all right we're gonna go um this way it's 2 a.m
let's do some more building um straight this way from this connection go from here or i could do
from here yeah i'll go from here to here i need some money back make some cash back come on i gotta
make i'm up in the prices this wall is going to be the ones that yeah this here we go ten dollars to
play it jackpot chance five thousand percent jackpot 100 bucks 10 bucks to play it copy that over
everything here in these two yep let's go let's make some fucking money one dollar these are five
dollar machines now with a jack uh jackpot of 40 bucks 50 bucks no 45 really i got we got i need
to start making more money the hotel's not making any freaking money nobody wants to play the table
games the food and the slots that was making the money right now stealing from oh okay we're good
somebody stole from the atm all right here we go should i take it alone who cares i'm taking a
loan out subject to credit approval what hundred thousand interest rate 3.16 daily payment of 3600
that to income i'm good what do you mean like like 562 credit score that doesn't what i want to make
that dance floor right now it's gonna be a huge push all right bring it up dance floor wait didn't
i research it already oh it's almost done okay go come on come on 35 minutes come on i love you but
you're pissing me off i love you what am i we're just chilling what are you talking about we're
just chilling it's gotten into you what do you mean what are you talking about all right i need
a show how big should this be huge i'm gonna move the atm okay this is gonna be a funky room too
okay dance entertainment dance hall dance floor zone okay can i so what was that sound did you
hear that it was like well i what did you hear that i need speakers and hanging lights we're
gonna just blow everybody away no no no shit i have i no i didn't mean to i keep i just i'm
too lazy to delete it so i make us like another row you're gonna come in here all right stop stop
okay speakers and what was the other thing hanging lights it's gonna be may have been here
is this free this room is gonna be torture no okay okay is it done oh does it make it crazy
oh my goodness oh wait i have to make them different colors oh yeah that's fucking nuts
okay does it have blue light maybe not okay this is free um should i just have it open i was gonna
have it open all right go on and get in there and dance but i'd sell oh god damn it here we go
uh this was free by the way oh wait i thought there was gonna be changing colors oh this is
not worth taking out an hundred thousand dollar loan turn the music up other tab oh it's locked
this thing this sucks is this even the music coming out of this you don't go that close no
that's just the regular music yeah this is the regular soundtrack guys this shouldn't be free
play something okay what should i play uh royalty free edm music nobody's here this feels so bad
this cost me 1200 to rent this fucking space out i'm having fun it's so bright in here
yeah nobody wants to be in a room like this dancing around you're gonna have that overexposed
iphone face nobody wants to be in here everyone it's just like it's like a bathroom mirror
nobody wants to be in here except for me of course let's go hey dude yeah this free drinks
in the dance room i would give it away two free drink tickets i thought that lady was pregnant
for a second i was like what two drink tickets let's go somebody come in somebody go into the
dance floor why all right i'll give somebody i'll give somebody 30 dollars if they come in
and dance for five minutes 100 100 100 dollars if you come in and dance for five minutes anyone
put a bar in there uh i've been on one second honestly i i ain't going in here
with this one guy in here alone you know what i mean something weird about this
oh no no no no no please please please please no don't leave like i came in here to get the
100 bucks uh i scared him off no i didn't guys all these speakers are on and turned up all the
way to 10 with no song on it so all it takes is to play the fart reverb and that guy's dead
that guy is gonna instantly die that guy's gonna blow across the room and he'll just be
splatted against this wall you play it is this gonna be loud this might be really loud
be i'm serious this could be loud as hell this is not even that funny
it's not even funny
uh why does the video exist oh my fucking head this video is called one hour of silence
occasionally broken up by reverb fart i what purpose does this video serve okay i'm talking
okay so when you hear that sound i'm talking his arm his his arms and legs are both in the air
forward at a 90 degree angle you know what i mean his arms are right out in front of him legs it's
like he's sitting in a chair and his arms out flying backwards 500 miles per hour and he just
explodes like splatters against the back wall just to leave it on this this is not a hundred
thousand dollar room what a waste of money i don't there needs to be one speaker in the room not
50 oh put it on times two speed
the most replayed part of the video is it is here do half speed
it's on 0.25 speed i actually i have no idea when it's gonna happen again it might take an hour why
do they don't have any eyes for a whole can of pepsi into no relax are people drinking out of
this i'm waiting for it to happen wait who didn't clean this up
did you just scoop it back into her stall he just brushed it underneath the stall do i see
we should whatever oh my goodness the doors are broken i mean they're they wait oh okay all right
what else can i research i have money attractions probably the theater right no all this stuff is
free i need i need i gotta make money jim more food oh my god it's scary
wormhole opening a fucking doctor strange circle oh
that was a fucking doctor strange circle that i it's not even funny but it is why i hate this
yeah that's exactly what i'm talking about this is exactly what i was talking about
vr josh just put something over here this is what i exactly what i see in my brain all right i need
to slow down i actually have to settle down before it's gonna cause me a problem i need to relax
hold on what is this from that is yes it's from the picard star trek spin-off
no that's from breaking bad it's when mike gets hit by a nuclear fart bomb
what what what is this oh my goodness okay so what was oh yeah i was i had the gym uh
what does it sound like when it's times two speed i'm curious
that's not really that this one's fart with extra reverb i all right i'm done with that
um you're five years old i don't know it's only that that does it to me
uh it doesn't even say there's a slow down one just sounds like god okay i want to do a
advertisement campaign uh um where do i do that finance operations where do i do it there we go
all right let's go for it we're gonna get flooded oh please keep it on i have nothing else keep it
on that scared the shit out of me because i opened it oh my god this is so many people please all of
you go to the dance hall or go get food all of you go get food yeah fill it up fill it up there's
so much floor space why they in a single file line i don't have no idea there you go all right
food food food food even more people coming in this is scary they all come in here and then
they all turn around and leave yes what does g do i keep seeing g pop up it doesn't do anything
only 2800 bucks from this so far yeah they're doing the same route they're like ants they single
file do the same thing no one walks over here all the slots are empty what are they why are they
avoiding every game is it too expensive what you have the worst odds in town that's five dollars
hundred dollar jackpot what oh yeah check that out ten thousand fucking dollar jackpot that'll get
sub that'll get some asses in this seat let's go wait what that that word that odd's worth it for
you hmm how are these odds go let's go that's still not enough ten dollars with a ten thousand
that's insane it's one cent to bet it's one cent uh let's go ahead and like do a hard save here
it's one cent bets in a ten thousand dollar jackpot is anybody even going to hit it did
somebody hit it i think somebody hit it urgent thirst i'm surprised it hasn't hit more really
how is it where are all the people oh it's three o'clock in the morning it's three am on a thursday
i'm sorry but if you knew that there was a casino in town that had a one cent bet and there was like
a five percent chance to win ten grand you would bring camping equipment and sit here and you would
pack fucking ten sandwiches you wouldn't leave five percent odds yeah see this person's smart
they came with 295 dollars no what are you leaving that wait a minute that lady sat down
with 295 lost three or four spins and then left pissed one cent all you would have to do is hit
this one time and you would never lose ever you just need to hit this once it's a five percent
chance to win ten grand at one cent bet how is nobody hitting it i'm not crazy right this
costs one cent oh that's still pretty damn good oh the max prize is is a hundred dollars oh never
mind okay here we go what ten like million those odds are still crazy ten dollars a spin five
percent chance to win what a hundred thousand ten thousand you have 20k all right we'll change it
back randomize those games randomized games and odds you're actually delusional why there's been
no fart that's interesting do bingo um uh what a bust this was seriously this was a bust and they're
the biggest in the whole casino and they're the biggest bust what else can i research instant
delivery true longer larger loads better security celebrity guests more marketing i don't even have a
second floor you can invite the real germa to your casino now i'm i'm probably gonna call it
i don't want to push it too hard this was fun though not like casino inc um yeah we were supposed
to do the green screen thing tonight um i got up with a migraine and i can already tell that
it's a good thing we didn't do it because laughing at oh my god is it always going to be funny
probably um i was actually going to say that i was having digestive problems
because i really have been you know that yeah i i just didn't want to be in like a laughing fit
and get make it even worse and i can already tell that from laughing at that uh it's kind of creeping
back up here again so i'm gonna call it this coming week is this is a lot of stuff going on
there is i'm going to stream it on monday tuesday wednesday thursday and then
green screen is is definitely going to happen this coming weekend because then after this weekend
that will be it for a few days because baseball is in um just about just under two weeks yeah not
like casino inc casino inc is a little more uh wild this one's more of a simulation this is still fun
though this is actually still a fun game i enjoyed my time playing it these kind of sim
management games can be fun uh yeah green screen will be this coming weekend this like next weekend
and i can't receive a reason why it wouldn't i'm gonna try to just get better i really hope so i
got two weeks to really get back to normal uh but i'll see you guys on monday monday we're probably
gonna do the mortuary assistant tuesday i don't know wednesday is something really fun thursday
is something really fun thursday's i think um unless any plans change myths uh call of duty
event is going to be this coming thursday the 11th so that should be fun too wednesday uh nice big
fun thing could be happening too yeah i'll get one on on tomorrow night or uh yeah tomorrow night
i'll be here i'll go over everything but there's going to be probably at least three or four streams
in a row if for some reason i don't stream on monday then tuesday wednesday thursday friday
saturday essentially is what it's going to be so there's going to be at least three or four in
a row which i'm not really used to doing but you know it's fun thanks for watching everybody see
you soon see you in a couple days regardless of whenever it is take care of yourselves have
a great night see you soon i wish i didn't have that muted
uh all right i'll see you later good night goodbye take care owen call you mother