Alright, now we're gonna move on. We're gonna play, um, we're gonna play Cook, Serve, Delicious 2
for the remainder of our chillout stream. Let's go ahead and close this and open it up.
That's a thing? Yeah, it is a thing, apparently. They're making a third.
Are they really making a third? How do you make this game three times?
Do you add? What do you add to it? More recipes? No, Xbox Game Bar.
Xbox Game Bar. I don't want to take a fucking screenshot.
You know what I think the weirdest thing in the world is? Why? Why is Xbox trying to tell me
I can take a screenshot with their Xbox game thing? It's like, you just hit print screen
and just paste it. Like, what? Hey, in case you know, you can take a screenshot of this game. I
know. I know. It's a, it's a button on my keyboard that has been a function for 30 fucking years.
What? This song is kind of poppin', I'll tell you though. Now let me change the game.
Is the Cook Serve Delicious 2? Is this better than the first one? No, no, yes, no, no, no, no, no,
yes, no, no, no. We'll find out. Start game. Here we go. Local saves. Cloud saves. I don't have any
saves. Local save. New slave, new slave slot. New save slot. I can't fucking talk. New save slot.
It began like any other morning at Sherry's Soda Tower. You rode the elevator up to your
Platinum Star restaurant, Cook Serve Delicious, and reflected warmly upon your culinary brilliance
and magical powers, life was good. Without warning, police surrounded Sherry's Soda Tower.
It seemed company executives were siphoning funds from the corporation,
while at the same time incurring a staggering amount of debt which drained the accounts of
the tower and all the businesses inside. Everything was put up for federal auction.
Cook Serve Delicious was no more. Angry but determined to rebuild, you purchased a modest
commercial space on the 52nd floor of the Terrigan Tower, the largest skyscraper in the city,
packed with thousands of ravenous tenants. It is here that you will start a brand new Cook
Serve Delicious restaurant, build it back to its former glory, work at other restaurants to rebuild
your finances and expand your culinary knowledge and cement your legacy as the best chef in the
world. Good luck. I already am. That's what happened in Cook Serve Delicious 1. I became the best chef
in the world. So I already know what I'm doing. I already know kind of how to do this. But oh,
no, no, no, I don't need to click this. I already know how to do this stuff. But let's, you know
what, let's just do it. This is a relaxed stream. You're out of practice. That's true. Yeah,
there's the prep stations to your left, where orders appear as customers arrive. Enough talk,
enough talking. Let's cook. Select your order by clicking that order on the left or by pressing
one on your keyboard. All right. One hole in one nachos. Those are the ingredients. Yep. QSJV.
QSJV. Use the recipe on the bottom of the screen to place the correct ingredients ordered by the
customer. All right. So we've got queso cream beans. So that is queso cream beans. I did it in
a half a second and that's it. Press enter. Let's make it more complex stuff. I'm making a hamburger.
Place the ingredient and begin to cook. M is for meat patty. Two patties. Oh, those look good.
Those look good. That looks good. Okay, let's go. The meat is cooking. The white timer indicates
how long this food has left to cook. Once it turns blue, the food is ready to be prepped again.
Okay, so I just wait for it to turn blue. Blue. Select the order once it turns blue. Don't prep
it too early or the order will be raw. Okay, so let's prep it. This food has a greater number
of ingredients that spans two pages. Oh, don't make me do two pages. Ingredients have color boxes
to the left of them to easily show what page they are on. Oh, okay. So you press space. Press space.
Click the green space button or scroll the mouse wheel or press space. Good. So this person just
wants two meat patties and a regular bun. And a regular bun. All right. Done. All right, guys.
I gotta go. I'm gonna make one of these right now. I'm out of here. The bun looks wet. That's
no, that's good. You want the little drizzle of fucking oil on it. All right, so that's it.
Press space. Press enter. That's good. Done. And depending on how well you did, you'll get either
I'm in chat or I'm scared at something. Munkah S. Or you'll get like react harder, whichever one is
better. Yep. Perfect average of bad rating. Always strive for a perfect rating. Yeah. Wait,
there's holding stations in this one. Holding stations are the key to making things much easier
for you when a huge amount of customers walk through the door. In fact, if you don't utilize
them, the game can become quite difficult and sometimes impossible. Try accepting the order
on the left. You'll notice you cannot select this food. It has a red HS icon, meaning that it must
be prepared in a holding station before you can serve it. Let's do that now. Select holding
station one by clicking it or by pressing the button combination. In this case, hold down tab
and press one tab one. Oh Jesus. Select the pretzel and follow the recipe. The recipe will be
completely random each time you make food in the holding station. So pay close attention to make
sure it's done perfectly. Select a food to prep. Each page has a different category of food,
holding station, required foods, holding station, opera, operational, optional foods and side dishes.
Okay, so holding station, pretzel. We just want a German pretzel. Follow the recipe. Just German
pretzels. Get it in the oven. Just like the hamburger, we must wait until the food is finished
cooking before we can select it again. Holding stations are fully automated. Once the food is
finished cooking, it will... What did you fucking just say? I have to restart the whole game.
Pretzel is now in the holding station and ready to serve. Try selecting the pretzel in the prep
station. I got four in there. So that is ready. Oh, that's much better than the first game.
You actually get to put stuff and queue stuff up and have it made already. Now we're talking.
All right, one serving has been deducted from the holding station. You still have three more left to
serve to anyone coming and wanting pretzels. The food is going to decrease in freshness as the day
progresses. Once the clock runs out next to the serving number, food must be thrown away.
Certain things stay fresh or longer. All holding station orders must be cooked perfectly
or they cannot be served. Try serving these next three orders.
Dang. See how fast you can serve customers with holding stations? They're great. You've learned
the very basics of the game. However, there are still items such as side dishes, chores,
drinks, and holding station operational foods that you can learn in the extra tutorials. You
should absolutely check those out when you can. If you're ready to cook, hop into Max Wieners.
I heard they're looking for a good chef or spend your money over the food catalog and start
building your own menu and cook serve delicious too. Good luck from Mr. Risotto. Optional foods,
side dishes. You know, I need to do these. It's one minute. Holding station optional foods are
orders that can either be prepared in a prep station or made ahead of time in a holding station.
Okay, so let's make chicken nugget basket. I like these too.
Place the nuggets, dunk, and cook. Try to dunk. Is that it? Are they cooking?
Yeah, they are. They can be served when finished. Serve the order once it's ready.
Done. All right. Cool. Oh, I just want like a bunch of chicken nuggets and hamburgers and
shit right now. So you can make food beforehand. Select holding station one, then turn the page of
the holding station optional foods, and then select chicken nuggets. Okay. Select the food
to prep. There are no HS required foods on your menu. Okay, here's nuggets. So let's just make
them. So dunk them. How much should I make? Four. Okay. Nuggets are almost done. Now you have six
nuggets. Everybody could smell them. So they ran in. This is great for pre rush hour moments when
you feel you might have an influx of customers try serving all the customers that come in. I'll do
it as fast as I fucking can. Here we go. Ready? Nice. Beware optional foods take up space that
might be better used for side dishes or more holding station required foods. It'll be up to
you to find that perfect balance. I'm gonna fucking lose in the first level. I've already sprinted
to the side dishes. Customers won't wait for their orders for very long. As you can see,
this order that has arrived is quickly going off the screen. If it disappears completely,
it'll be counted as a bad order. You can see how long a customer will wait by the patience meter
measured in seconds. This meter will I'm training. This meter will drain as you make more and more
perfect foods and your buzz increases. Okay, so two seconds. To increase customer patience,
we must make side dishes. Select holding station one, turn the page of the side dishes and prepare.
Okay. Side dishes. So we make make a side salad with lettuce, carrots, tomatoes, croutons,
and cucumbers. Lettuce. That's it. That salad sucks. It was a terrible salad. It's just like
iceberg lettuce and like a bunch of shape. I wouldn't eat this. And then ATRU. Good. I got
five of these. So every unique side dish in your holding station, that's 15 seconds to the patience
meter. Don't act like you eat vegetables. I eat vegetables all the damn time. You can think I eat
vegetables. I don't act like you eat vegetables. For some reason, I don't think a lot of you guys
think I eat Captain Crunch and hamburger meat. No, I eat lots of stuff. I drink pineapple juice
and McChickens. Yeah, I got a steady diet of McChickens, Captain Crunch, whole milk,
and chicken nuggets. No, I am a I'm a fucking adult. I'm 33 years old. I have salads. I have
the good sources of protein. Like I don't even why am I explaining this? You guys already know all
this. One person said I eat like Captain Crunch every day and it freaked me out. Order a salad
right now. No, I don't want a salad right now. So I had a salad fucking like yesterday. All right,
I'm trying let me pay attention to the game. Every unique side dish in your holding station
has 15 seconds. Okay, you can have up to three unique sides on your menu, which can give you a
possible 45 extra seconds of patience. This is huge when you have a large influx of customers.
They will always order a random available side dish with their meal, which also increases your
income. Okay, so you have to have like a variety. Have at least one side dish in your holding station
as it's easy way to prevent walkouts and bad orders. I'm going to do a taste test on spring.
You can blindfold me. You put a bowl of Captain Crunch with crunch berries and then put a salad
on the other side. And I'll tell you, I'll do a taste test with a blindfold on. All right,
drinks and delicious. Drinks like side dish like goes out. Each drink item has a set number of
customers can be served to. I think I'm ready. Buzz cool moves. Keyboard users can fully remap
their keys for holding stations in key options. We should check out the options menu. Okay.
Practice chores. No, no, no. I don't need to practice chores. I don't have to drink out of
the toilet. Fs. Enter. Two is load the dishes. Begin washing the dishes. Wait with the green
light. Release. Unload. Sanitize. Go. Oh, I don't like. Wait, what's going on? Why is there a guy
with a gun? What? Okay. There's a fire. Hold on. Extinguish. There's a fire in the kitchen.
We can't use this. Rat traps. LCS. Toilet clean. Fs. Stop. What was the bug one? Work ticket. Please
clean the pest light trap. Oh, trash. Oh, yeah. I remember the TMS. What? I don't have to mash?
Okay. Let's do the last one. This is bugs. Please set the roach traps. Set the trap. Sanitize.
And here's another robbery. So it's kick, kick, kick, kick, kick. All right. I get the idea.
Let's go. I know how to play. Food catalog, emails, designer, tutorials, tower.
It's an all-new campaign where you can run your cook, serve, delicious restaurant, or work in
other restaurants across the tower. Nailed perfect orders. Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep. Getting yum
points. Gain enough yum points. You'll level up. Every fifth rank earns you half a star. Get a full
five-star restaurant. Be the best chef in the tower. Good luck. Standard shift. Oh, this all
looks good. I want one of these right now. I love this stuff so much. You know, I gotta tell you
that pretzels, a hot pretzel is probably the best snack you could ever eat. A big Bavarian pretzel
is just... I'm gonna have to get one. Okay, if I have a meeting later and I have like a big
Bavarian pretzel, is that not okay? Or should I just drink water? That's bad. What if I wanted
like two big Bavarian pretzels and like mustard and shit and just eat it and talk wicked fucking
loud while I'm chewing? All right, let's go. Standard shift. How do I say go? Oh, all right.
First time. Complete the day with fewer than eight bad orders. Complete day with fewer than five
average orders. Complete day perfectly. We're not gonna get that. Let's go. Prep any food to start
the day. Let's prep... Let's get the pretzels prepped. Let's prep corn dogs. So I need to do
bingo. Close it up. Cook it up. And hold on, hold on, hold on. I need... It's not ready yet.
Come on. I need to prep some other stuff too. Oh shit, you want something else? No, no, no, no,
back, back, back, back, back, back. No, no, no, no. Back up. How do I back up? No, just put the
fucking hot dogs on. No. What? What do you want on this? Ketchup? He's pissed. I hate these key
bindings already. All right, let's go. You want pretzel bun. You want a z and then onion mustard
ketchup. M, K, whiz, what? O, N, K, M. What do you got? Okay, I got it, I got it.
What do you want? What do you want? You want queso jalapenos beans. So that's Q, J, B. Corn dog.
You got it. What do you want? Ketchup. You got it. Toilet. What do you want? Flush it. I gotta prep
something else here. Let's prep a few hot dogs. Let's prep. Is that too many? This is too many,
I think. It's all right. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. There's too many hot
dogs. This is supposed to be a relaxing stream. Five. Hey, you want ketchup and mustard? Get out.
Get the fuck out of my restaurant. What just happened? What just happened? They just deleted.
Why did they delete? Why did they delete? What? What do you want? Open the ice base and fill it.
What? All right, hurry up. What do you want? Pretzel bun, mustard, P, no, Z, Z and then M.
Get out. Ah, you want pretzel bun, Z, and then ketchup and mustard. Do you want
shift? Tab four. Tab three, four. Tab three, four. I don't like this new. I don't like this one.
Premium bun, P, onions. Why the fuck is N onions? Why would you not make O onions?
No, shift. This is incorrect. Q, S. Am I deleting these? I am. Okay, so if you do it twice,
you delete them. C, S. I need something. I'm going out of business. Pretzel. I need. Okay.
Why is B pretzel? I've remapped this whole thing. Who's the insane person that decided that B
was going to be pretzel and not P? Who's the insane person that said N was going to be onions
and not O? Did you use a controller? Well, that's what I did last time. It wasn't a disaster.
Hold on. Just plug in. Really? Is it better? Are you feeling relaxed? Do not use a controller. Oh,
God. I don't know what to think. Hold on. It's better. It's better. It's better. Hold on. Let
me just plug it in. I might have to like restart it. Yeah, I'm quitting. I quit. Why are you not?
Let's go. There we go. Okay. Max wieners. Let's try this. You used to learn the keyboard without
looking at it. I can't. That's literally impossible. I've been using computers for
25 years and I don't know how to use the keys without looking at it. It's not going to happen.
It's impossible. It'll never happen, guys. I'm sorry. This is a thousand times easier, by the
way. Let's do pretzels. I like to hold it. Okay. We want German pretzel. Okay. Cook it up. How do
I do the second tab? Okay. Wiener. Is it L, B or something? All right. I got pretzels ready.
All right. What do you want? Premium bun. You want a premium bun and you want that's it. Nothing
else. Get out of here. Nobody want a corn dog. You don't want any corn dogs. You want everything
on this. There's a premium bun and then we got everything. We've got everything. Cheese, ketchup,
onions. Get out. Nobody wants a pretzel yet. Oh, I have to. Okay. I get it. Anybody else want
anything? How do I? Okay. You go. How do I select another station with the controller?
You want everything. You want, uh, no. You want queso helping his beans. How do I select them
out of a fucking station? Oh God. It's, it's just right on the D pad. Okay. Let's do, uh,
corn dogs. Let's put a fucking bunch of them in there. Close it up. Let's go. All right. What
do you want? No, this is bad. You want pretzels. I got a few of them left, right? All right. Here
we go. You want mustard on it. Mustard is X. What the fuck do you want? You want mustard is X.
What do you want? You want mustard is X. What do you want? You want, oh fuck. Oh my God. They're
burning. Okay. Regular bun and then everything else. Oh my God. This is so confusing.
What did I do wrong? Hold F trigger and what's wrong with this thing? Didn't I just do this?
I think I'm going to rage quit this game by the way. I don't think I want to play this.
This is so much more hectic than the first game by like a thousand times.
This isn't cook to serve delicious too. This is cook, serve delicious harder.
And then no, no, no, no, no. I went down wrong button. No, you got to prep the shit. It's just,
I'm so not used to doing that. I, I don't like the hold and left trigger. Give me the fucking
keyboard. No, that's not going to work. Why? Okay. Then left trigger Y, left trigger Y,
left trigger X holding and then go and a pretzel. Give it to the rats. He's not relaxing.
I've really not. What? What happened? Oh, catch up. What? What happened? I thought I had pretzels
here. What the fuck? It's too much for me. Then I already have, do they have, are these ones German?
I don't know. Are they German? Don't press Y again. Passive aggressive.
That's not passive aggressive. Yeah. I, I can't, my brain sucks. I can't play this one.
It's cool. I wish I could. I can't. I know I can't. I know I can't. You have to admit when you can't
do something. You know what I mean? I'm admitting I can't do it. Do the cash. I don't know. I can't
do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. You can do it. I can't do it. If you wanted to see cook,
serve delicious too, I was like, oh yeah, I can't wait. I just know I'm not going to like it.
I'm certain of it. I liked the first one. I can tell you,
I guarantee I'm not going to like it. Even if I lower the difficulty, I'm just, I'm just telling you.