Hello. Good afternoon. My name, if I may present myself, is Mixy. Nice to finally meet you face to
face. Really? Hold on. Did you make a 3D movie maker reference and you see minus two? Really guys?
That's interesting. I wonder if uh that's odd. I really thought that was gonna hit. Well anyways,
hi welcome. Uh we are at the point of the stream when we do Sam and Max. This will be the final
Sam and Max themed streams. After season three, I have no plans on doing the rest of Sam and Max,
all the other games that they have. There's no plan to do that. But if I started season one,
I want to do season two and season three. And that's what we're gonna do. After this,
you might not see it again because I know that there is at least one or two other games in this
franchise. But there are a couple other things to talk about before we get started.
First thing to talk about is we have some things to watch. We have two videos that from yesterday
that I want to show on the screen. We'll just wait. Let me just give me a minute. Let people
trickle in and I'll be with you very shortly. Two minutes. Okay so this first one we're gonna watch
is from uh it's time for slime. This is called uh German DOS. Let's go ahead and get it on the
screen for you. Uh chunky baloney just came in with 10 community subs. Holy shit. Thank you so much.
These 10 and 20 community subs, the last couple of days, the last like three or four streams have
been like a dozen of these 10 plus community subs. Thank you guys. That's a fucking lot.
That's a lot of money. It's payday. And speaking of money, speaking of money, uh more money
just came in. A hundred bucks to be exact. One hundred dollars in bits just came in from
I in your palace. Can you correct me on how to say your name? I'm so stupid. I in in urea in
in urea palace. Do I have that right? But thank you so much for the hundred fucking dollars. Right?
Wouldn't even get started. Thanks to the both of you. All right let's watch German DOS. More money
than Scrooge McDuck. I'm gonna get it into pennies and put it into a pool. It'll appreciate in value.
All right here we go. I actually think I can just do this. Yeah I have this from yesterday.
Oh my god. Uh thank you for the 10 community subs, Bebraham. Even more subs coming in.
And all I said was like hey and then I went whoa I made my bed laughed. You guys missed
before stream chat. We're having a lot of fun. No porn games. That started before I uh
before I had a chance here. Hold on. Uh this is called this is called German DOS.
It's by it's time for slime. Uh Demi Demi IRO sickat. Demi Rosecat. Holy shit I'm an idiot.
I can't thank you for the fucking oh my god more subs. You guys already paid for the movie.
We're about to watch the movie. You guys are sitting in your theater seats and you're like
you're taking more money out. It's like the movies we already paid for. Big Marsh 10 community subs.
Do not sub me. This is not my good account. No shit I gotta come and I gotta take my like mask off.
Oh my god. These are these are I gotta put my good shoes on. I got my smurf what is it is
this the account that you go on to like talk shit to people and then like whatever I get bad who
cares. Not even my real name. Uh Pon Pon Fresh five community subs. See somebody just said fuck
you to me. Guarantee you that person comes back on another account that's like Jerma's the man is
like what's up dude how are you? How are things? Uh but thank you Pon Pon Fresh for the five subs.
Thank you all of you for the the massive amount of monetary support here before the stream
even started. So thank you guys. See the real thing I'm not even gonna give you this idea.
If I give you this idea that would be that would be not good for me. Back in five community subs.
Nintendo got a community sub. Are you serious? Dude Nintendo's subbing to me? That's fucking oh wow.
I can't believe it. Nintendo is not in the chat. You can give a community sub to anybody. Are they
here? Nintendo liars. Sometimes you have to check. What if they were like scouting me out to do like
a I don't know like a Super Mario sponsorship or something. It could happen. All right here we go.
That was from back in Let's Go. Let's watch this video. This is called Jerma Dos. Are you ready? One
two three. No porn games. The table. What did that say? Of course it has to end on that.
It has to end on that. What did the opposite say? Hold on. I clocked you rooming at 32 over the limit. I hate
to do it but I'm gonna have to write you up a ticket. Okay here we go. That face. Speaking of movies
that is what it looks like in the dark when you are talking and somebody in front of you looks
behind to try to essentially tell you. That's like a shut the fuck up face. That's like a what are
you really doing this face. That's what it looks like in the dark. Hold on yeah it's like this.
Here comes like the climax of the movie. Oh my god here he comes. I can't say any I can't make
a pretend climax because somebody will say it's a spoiler for some movie. Like right now the person
is describing their love for the other character and they're about to like have a big kiss moment.
They're about to kiss on screen and then they just go and they turn back around. Nobody talks like
shit anymore. Have you noticed that? I don't know what it used to be. You'd be sitting in a movie
theater and somebody would be like shit shut up. No I once last year heard somebody scream
at a movie theater before. I've been to a bunch of movies in the last few years and I've not heard
it. I mean I've I've I've done it a few times. I mean but that's me doing that. Am I the guy now?
I don't hear other people do it. It's just me. Right okay. Oh shit I got too old. All right here
comes the next one. The next one is another. It's an animation from Googly Gareth. They passed the
theater yelling torch to you. Maybe they did. No I don't want to yell. I don't yell in movie theaters.
Who do you think I am? I yell after the movie's over. I clap at the credits. All right here we go.
This is called German animated streaming superstar. Actually let's just do this.
Let's get rid of the white background here. There we go. Okay all right ready. This is called
streaming superstar. Three two one let's go. I can't even beat a b-list. Well it doesn't matter.
That's not my style. That's not my style. I'm not gonna. I don't do cell phone commercials.
You see how good my other commercials went with a toothpaste? Wash your teeth if you want. Not go
to fucking jail kids. Nobody can beat me in those. I'm so much more popular than all these people.
You think I care about this guy with a pegasus commercial with a shitty car? Have you seen my
germ commercial? It's 10 times better. Toilet sheriff. It's high noon for gamers. Get germs.
I remember the deodorant commercial. I sold that. You know how many copies of the deodorant were
sold? You know how many copies were sold? 25,000 in one day. They're holding me hostage and making
me film these commercials. So go take your car that like 10 people bought and break. I'm the
important one here. Name something you need a lot of if you have a large family. I swear to god
if this answer is love I'm gonna put a hole through my screen. Don't fucking be love.
You already got the cheeky answer in there. Who's the one person that wrote love? And like you know
you know when they asked and they said love and they winked it's gonna be love.
Yeah oh yeah love you know. Wink. One person. It's gonna be one. One person. Fucking assholes.
Oh yeah you need lots of patience. You need lots of love. We're three people that said this.
We like said it and then grabbed the person like on the shoulder and we're like hey you know what
I mean love and then they like tripped and dropped their fucking coffee and the rest of their day
sucked. They like stepped in a fucking huge puddle after they said that. They were like oh yeah love
wink. Thank you for your time. Yeah I'll see you later. Thank oh yeah I gave you some good answers
some really specific shitty ones. Yeah see you later and they turn and fucking go in the puddle
like they fucking goes all over their fucking pants and shit and their coffee goes everywhere
and the rest of their day was terrible. All right name a real or fictional person with Grant
and his or her name. Hugh Grant. No Grant uh it was the president. What was the president's name?
The president. Uh Grantly. No he's on the fucking $50 bill. What's his name? Quick.
What's his name? Alexander Van Grant? Alexander Grant? Who's the guy? Who's the president?
Ulysses Grant? Yes Ulysses Grant. Shit. How do you spell Ulysses?
Fuck it. We're doing Hugh Grant. Wait what? I gotta look this up right now. How do I look?
I'm just gonna type it into Google right now. You guys are gonna be too far behind. Ulysses.
U-L-Y? Ulysses Grant. Oh shit that's I.
I who? Oh my god. He's gonna do Ulysses. He's gonna do Ulysses. Damn it.
Do you want to see the category? Here goes fictional character. Donald Duck.
Donald Duck. Donald Duck. Donald Duck. Donald Duck. Donald Duck. Donald Duck. Donald Duck.
That's Donald Duck. Donald fucking Duck.
What a shitty ending. Ah that was those are fucking great. That was called a streaming superstar
by Googly Gareth. A very talented animator. I'm not I'm not like that you know. This is this
specific eclipse that I take it of of moments where I you know I have a little bit of trouble
but it's not like that all the time. If you're new to the channel it's not really it's not like
that all the time. It's only like that like sometimes. If a stream is like seven or eight
hours I feel like four hours is that. That's not even 40 percent. That's like that's a half.
It's it's only when he's talking. It's funnily enough 40 to 50 percent of the stream probably
is me talking. The other 50 60 percent is like game stuff and stuff on the screen. So you know
you're probably right. Anyways those are two very very very very funny very interesting videos
back to back. We are going to move on from that. We're going to do we're going to start Sam and
Max season three. You have to have a high enough percentage to be a C plus streamer.
I'll take a C plus. I know it's B minus. I was downgraded. What is it? What's it on social
blade right now? Is it did I get it? I haven't checked this in a long time actually. What is it?
What's my like twitch social blade right now? What do I have for grade? Oh come on man. That's a B
plus. It used to be B minus. Oh I'm happy about that. Oh this is not an intro anymore. Hey look
at that. Sam and Max. So again we're going to play this for that's what we're going to do today.
Tomorrow by the way Star and I are going to play something. We don't know what it is. It's going
to be a mystery game. We both actually don't know what the game is. We haven't talked. All I know is
that we're going to play something together. I'm sure we'll probably figure that out in like an
hour before the stream. So I'll see you tomorrow. No no no no I'm not leaving yet. We'll do that
tomorrow. But for today we're going to do Sam and Max and let's watch two videos and end the
stream after 20 minutes. Speaking of stuff happening on the stream KXZ gave $50. Thank you
KXZ for your 50 bucks and they say hope you're doing well Jerma. Always a good day when that
live notification pops up. Thank you. That's a lot of money. You've given a lot of money over the
years. Wait is there another video? Is it a third? Was there a third video? This looks like a meme
video. Is this a meme video? Is this a meme video? Okay is this is this safe for stream? No yes yes
yes yes yes okay all right all right of course it is. All right we're gonna watch two we're gonna
watch two more videos. All right this is it. This is it. No more videos after this.
There's no more videos. We're gonna play Sam and Max. I don't I don't want to skip that out.
All right there's no more videos after this.
Is this am I in this?
I'm not even in that video. Why did I just watch this?
All right thanks for the video. That was an interesting video. Let's keep going. Let's watch
this one. What would you love to say about this? That's what I want to know. Oh so what you were
watching a live streamer today? Yeah I was. Oh what and and uh what did you type in the chat room?
There's a chat room I heard. Yep there's a chat room. Oh so what did you write? Like hey cool
design nice product. Nice bulge. Oh you said that? You're grounded. It's true. All right it's true.
All right that's it for videos. No more videos. Let me at least press new game on this.
Subscribe. Subscribe to that. I'm not I haven't been logged into YouTube in like fucking four
years. I can't. I don't I don't I have no login. All right let's go. Sam and Max.
The forever delayed Sam and Max stream. Let's get it over here. All right. Welcome to Sam and Max.
Enjoy your stay here. What? New game. I don't know how loud this is going to be.
Prepare yourself. How is it? Is it all right? Is it good? Too loud. Is it too loud?
I I can't see it over here. I need a mod. It's live? In all the universe the only power beyond
the mind's comprehension is the power to comprehend the power of the mind. If any one of us could
unlock this terrible power would we use it to explore the mysteries of the infinite or would
we use it to destroy? Yes. Tremble earthlings. Tremble before the might of General Scutafi.
You know Sam Skunk Ape may be a tool but he brings a refreshingly childlike glee to his work.
All right I'm here Max. It's hard to stay mad at this guy.
Miss Sam and Max stop the dreadnoughts.
I will destroy you and then dominate the entire galaxy.
Wait. Okay yeah I can. I didn't know if I was gonna skip it accidentally or not.
I didn't know. Okay I think we're good. Which one of us is the fuzzy one? Better? It's a familiar
tale. A space gorilla pitted against a canine detective and a sociopathic bunny with psychic
powers. But my friends this story is different. In this story you are in control. Only you can
release our heroes. General Scunk Ape's bizarre space suit. A quest to bring the victor to space
justice. Let's begin the tour. I knew somebody was gonna say it. One person said it. We could
just reach my gun. We could administer an old school freelance police style beat down to that
guy. I can't wait to get my stinking paws on that damn dirty ape. Simmer down Max. Check out
stinky cell phone. We're gonna need that and your creepy new brain powers to get out of this cage.
Gotta get cell phone. Whoa whoa whoa 3D. All right you can switch you can switch control between Sam
and Max by clicking on the freelance police badge in the corner of your screen. Try switching to Max
to use his psychic powers. Okay what why does Max have psychic powers in this one? You are now inside
the dankest recesses of Max's mind where you can attempt to control his horrible psychic abilities
unlocked by the toys of power. Okay when inside Max's brain you can look around by clicking and
dragging the mouse over using the WASD keys. To activate Max's teleportation power click on the
toy telephone. Okay well done my friends now select a phone number that Max has memorized
to teleport himself and his very long-time companion to that location and also Sam.
The toy phone has a button for each of the phone numbers Max has memorized. Click on the button
with stinky's picture to teleport to her cell phone. This is a joke you think right?
We have to do that every time. It's the freelance police. Oh baby I've missed you.
Now what? Listen to the brain. Hey Sam it's our new pal the disembodied alien brain. The same I am
speaking to you telepathically. No one else can hear me Sam and Max. The slug brain? I can. Shut
up your earth weapons will never be enough to defeat General Skunkapne. Don't you still have
that beacons? Okay to see what Sam is carrying in his inventory click on the cardboard box in the
corner. All right so the cardboard box is still here. These are all the items. Find the homing
beacon and left click on it to make Sam pull it out. This is the remote control. This is the homing
beacon. Do I have to do it? Just click it okay. Perfect now you must place the homing beacon on
General Skunkapne's back to trap him in the wheel zone. Easy throw it as hard as you can.
Click on a target make Sam use it on that yeah putting on the yeah just throw it as hard as you
can just don't miss. What's that? Did you really believe it would be that easy? Kind of kind of
yeah we're gonna need some kind of cover to get up close and personal with Skunkapne. Max remember
that you have been blessed with the gift you must unlock your abilities with the remaining toys of
power. Behold! Meat? Uh hang on there we go. Is that a nose? That's a that's a nose okay
you can make Sam use objects in the world by just nice click it. It's a lump of rhinoplasty the
wacky modeling clay that promises hours of fun and delivers about five to ten minutes work.
Okay so I got the nose. Max the rhinoplasty will grant you the incredible power of
shapeshifting. You can use the rhinoplasty to pick up a picture of any inanimate object
then use the power of your mind to transform into that object. This is a dream sequence or something.
Max now has the power of rhinoplasty remember stop doing that remember that you can left click on
one of the psychic toys to activate it. When the rhinoplasty is selected Max first has to choose
a picture of the thing he wants to turn into. You can make Max look around by clicking and dragging
WASD and then left click on a picture to make Max pick it up. A plant? You can turn into that object
you can click on the lump of rhinoplasty to activate it. Try to look leafy and inconspicuous
Max. I always do. Well done freelance police. Now you must get that homing beacon onto General
Skunkape before he reaches the Bronx or all will be lost. I think I can do it you can make Sam walk
by clicking and dragging or you can do they added WASD finally okay it's just a plant. Oh a plant
I love what you've done with the place my queen. He is talking really well for those teeth where
they are. Now what? Now we just used the remote control Mama Bosco gave us and Skunkape gets
sucked right in the penal zone so to speak. All right remote control some of the objects the same
activated on their own highlight the penal zone remote control then left click the activate icon
all right well hold on that's activate right Sam and Max but I'm far too strong to be captured
again soon this gateway will close and there will be nothing to stop me. There should be blood all
over his mouth. I know. You would cut your mouth up every time you were talking. There must be something
I'm talking about like a big like glulate stain of blood all over your whole mouth
I can't open the doors now but I have an idea before he was in prison your friend the mole
man was screaming something about taking over the ship find out what he knows
Can I do WASD? Oh you can. Is there a run? Is there a double tap to run? Space? Shift?
Oh shift is run just like a regular video game. All right Harry Moleman how you doing?
I gotta turn some shit down I can't even hear them talking
even if he could hear you through the glass Sam the sun lamp has made it even more worthless
than usual max you'll have to use another one of the toys of power another one
hold on first of all excuse me what look at I look at where it is I turn it look at I did my
I did my due diligence here you just look at this I tried should I have full cell phone
coverage or like going through a tunnel for hint level what do you think I'm gonna keep a default
disable hints tunnel no but what if I gotta make a call I know I can't what do you mean disable
this is the default you have us I'm doing I'm staying default I'm not changing it one bar is
fair that's the default look if it's too easy then I'll deal I didn't use any hints in the last one
I just pretended to know what I was doing and would read chat and some one person would say
the solution and then I would walk around for like a couple minutes pretending I was solving the
puzzle when in reality I knew the answer like 10 minutes before and was just piecing it all together
to make it look like I knew what was going on that I'm kidding people you guys are taking this too
literal how much lower do I have to make everything how does that is that all right
that sounds a little better now the music's too quiet well there's nothing I can do about it
all right how do I I'm trying to oh it's not it's shift I'm double tapping okay it's an ordinary
deck of playing cards is it max the playing cards have granted you the power to thrust your
consciousness into the fleshy minds of others and pluck out their most intimate thoughts
only you could take something as beautiful and natural as telepathy and make it sound wrong
look look look okay voice up music up are you ready all right we can use that let's let's
telepathically let's uh let's see what stinky's thinking okay you make magma drama mind reading
targets by clicking and dragging with the mouse you always yeah yeah all right let's see mustn't
find out I wonder if they suspect anything what is he doing is he reading my mind right now
they mustn't they mustn't find out don't let them break you harry your name is harry moment
your serial number is two four eight three five six two your cell number is two one two five five
four eight six five your favorite color is taupe you have an infection of the lower hey that's
enough of that hey sam I got harry mole man's phone number nice work little buddy make sure
you wait three days to call or he'll think you're desperate excellent max that phone number might
be enough because generals couldn't copy locked the mole man's cell phone and other belongings
inside this container so you can adjust the volume on the game but can you backflip off of
the trampoline um maybe let's all go for a ride in my magical balloon and I missed the last
instruction because I was laughing at chat what does it want to do call moment can I sum up the
story um there really isn't that much of a story my they're pretty self-contained there must be
something here that'll help us knock skunky back into the penal zone hey brain aren't you hooked
into all the controls of this spaceship it max's president let's be a little more sensitive he
doesn't have hands what's he gonna do lunch me no hands okay so max is president somehow we we
won the election that's pretty much the only real major thing that happened oh and like aliens
came in and captured bosco and and then we went to the center of the universe and like put a
chicken there and then an egg came on and that's pretty much it we'd need more than just a picture
of a space bazooka to do all right let's do the turn max into a
bazooka see now the music's too loud I told you I told you guys all right let's turn it into a bazooka
work max now let's i'm a bazooka sam a bazooka oh just give me a moment to savor this oh yes
turned into a bop it oh uh-oh max careful with that trigger finger
say hello to my little body sam and max city you have just participated in a troubling vision
of the future the first of many such disturbing revelations over the next five chapters you will
witness things that baffle you horrify you even disgust you but you must not look away
pay close attention to everything that you see and hear his name because when our story reaches
its bowel tingling climax only you my friends will possess the ability to save the entire universe
yes easy that car we actually get an intro this time it's not just the silhouette
silhouettes were cooler i do like the silhouettes although this is cool too i don't know why my
brain is wired so strangely but i thought that that just said like written by like like directed
executive produced by sam and max like they made this i don't know hey sam this haunted toy i found
just gave me an uncanny vision of our violent future i know i saw it too somehow did your
version have credits it had a spaceship a friendly alien brain in a jar looks different evil space
gorilla trying to destroy the city what could it all mean the the mouth animations almost look
like that tf2 meme video we just watched like they made it a putty players is there a vignette on the
game i don't think there's a filter on here or something
creatures of earth i am general scone copy hear my words i have come to you with a message of peace
and love
sorry about that building put it on to the thanos voice means no no way on board that spaceship max
my friends you seem a bit confused but there's no cause for alarm we've merely let the story get
ahead of itself let's take a brief journey back to properly set the more time travel more going back
our story begins 25 minutes ago what on a street very much like this one
you've got a phone call this is sam and max freelance police the corn dog
commissioner no we're not in the office we're locked out of our building it wasn't my fault this
time came president yeah there you go people asking about the tlbr here is cracking the street
in those pansies from city hall shut down the whole block what's that commissioner so this is
season three wave of lawfulness and goodwill spreading through the city i feel like we're
getting a lot of did you forget who these people were exposition here more than we did last time
there aren't any crimes for us to solve okay then we'll be on the lookout for anything suspicious
there's a big time difference now that makes sense okay brain is dying
i'll take it back commissioner max has psychic powers now apparently that should bring us all up
to speed now what the fuck is happening something about a spaceship what could it all mean it means
we've got to find a way on board that spaceship max all right oh that i remember this guy what's
this guy's name home run something like that what's his name super super ball okay all right let's
take a look i want to let's let's take a look around first we got let me see worse news city
dirtification project a resounding success mayor credits new jersey's rich supplies of rust grime
crud and skank hi this is our uh jimmy uh two teeth up here what about you go down into the
subway all right let's start fresh sneaky's daughter how about you go slay some creepers in
minecraft the i mean the only way i'm going to turn minecraft on is if i lose a bet that's all
pretty much the only way how that works now ah stinky's diner the perfect place to catch
up with old friends and meet new ones like emergency medical technicians and the friendly
folks at poison control good thing you lose every bet oh really no never mind there's no coins in
here strawberry beet juice and ham i don't lose every bet beet juice and ham i just realized
anybody gonna eat this oh there he is is anybody gonna eat this can i talk to him this does control
this plays a lot different than the other ones jug jug barney and jug jug you're not even trying
with the names anymore are you barney look i've got a lot going on can i just give you your key
or your crystal shard or whatever it is you're looking for so you guys can go off and do whatever
it is you do sorry stinky we gotta go through all the questions oh by the way yes um whatever
she is like a cake right well we get like a mass effect style uh radio menu here all right how
about uh do you know the aliens have landed oh really i haven't heard anything about that at all
keep your guard up we're about 99.8 sure he's evil he's not even human uh tingy just gave five
community subs thanks a lot tingy tingy continuing the quest of of 100 million community subs thank
you so much tingy things must be easier now that grant is back oh yes it's heaven thank you thank
you at what he's doing to the place he's totally destroying the ambiance yeah this place used to
be an aggravated assault on all five senses now it's just a misdemeanor battery six senses sam
you always have the uncanny premonition of severe stomach upset in your future
how's the food let's see i'll take a double bacon cheddar butter deluxe heavy on the
wacky sauce that's not good jalapeno cheesy poofters wrought iron style now three okay three and let's
throw in one of the eight bean casseroles with extra onion rings and finish it off with a jumbo
size frosty banana mint pickle cyclone chugger with extra jimmies get the side salad please
oh and some bangers and mash hold the mash i'm on break see you again soon stinky yeah take your
time what does grandpa have to say i guess having just a jukebox wasn't loud and annoying enough
wait there were more options were there are you still here oh what happened to your fry
cook yeah what was his name sal or pablo or muhammad or something you boys must be mistaken it's
always been just me here working the kitchen no one else that's why i'm so grateful grandpa
stinky's back okay well hold on you and grandpa stinky should patch things up can't you see what
it's doing to max pretty good germa voice right there pretty good germa voice is going to be a
problem for much longer intriguing i signed us up for relationship counseling and a business
management seminar no now let's see you again soon stinky yeah take your time
oh slow down what about the pie ever since girl stinky took over the kitchen
stinky signature pies have gotten marginally more edible the insect bits give the dough that extra
bit of crunch gonna be eating insects in like 2050 hope you guys like the taste of crickets
because that's what you're gonna be getting at like taco bell demon broth oh you'd like to steal
my super secret demon broth recipe wouldn't you well hands off what i mean explain myself what
are you talking about don't you guys have any guys read the studies that like the only real
sustainable food source of humanity is going to be bugs in the next like hundred years
already did this joke this is not a joke this is me telling you what's going to happen in a
hundred years this is not a joke this is just what's gonna happen oh good you two are back
to barrage me with your inane questions we missed you too grandpa stinky did the health
inspectors ever make you wear a beard net i'll tell you type in bugs food source in the future
people way smarter than me have talked about this what's cooking oh you'd like me to tell you about
the demon broth wouldn't you so you can steal another patent come on you're not still angry
about that are you that was like 30 years ago and that's 30 years i could have been living off
the riches from a gooey molasses tar cake can't you hear at least on the joe rogan podcast you're so
curious about it pick up a can after i meet up so what selling it to every grocery store from here
to madagascar oh my god okay i need to like let's get off of this just no
that by 2150 there's gonna be ant soft serve machines and that's what you're gonna take for
your protein source it must be great getting back to work with your partner again i don't know he's
kind of cramping my style oh you were talking to him yeah never mind oh it's great she has me
working the register and making deliveries a master shape like myself that already is there
at mcdonald's already explained grandpa i just have to make it nicer so that it's um worthy of
your skills that's fucking funny all right okay all right let's like stay careful grandpa stinky
all right let's go you're doing the thing where you talk to chat and walk around in circles yeah
that's fine i i mean it is a point and click adventure game i just want to look around for
a little bit sheesh the mole people are taking their own sweet time getting our subway station
back into shape well to be fair they've been subcontracting to the mutant alligators union
those guys are notorious loafers okay let's go over here oh no let's take a look gumball
gumball machine always makes me wistfully nostalgic for earlier times like that time we
smashed this gumball machine that was great did i smash the gumball machine last season i don't
really remember doing that oh there's abe lincoln one of bosco's discarded giga guzzler soda cups
the only drink affected by the position of the moon four square and seven brides ago it's a
sculpture of abe lincoln's head sheesh what will it take to get rid of that guy he's not a real guy
max i can't be positive but it seems to be made out of pudding is it the annual citywide pudding
festival already i feel unprepared mole man construction worker either you guys seen charlie
he was supposed to be back by now charlie can't say i've seen charlie anything else
no i already did that they're the cartridges the whole people still haven't cleared away all those
old mime sweeper cartridges clear them away they're vintage collector's items mark my words sam one
day those games are going to be worth pennies okay uh let's wait wait wait carriage rosemary
keeps wandering off and leaving this thing behind i want some more coffee i gotta like brew some
coffee just regular coffee all right um so he's got that like demon water let me go back in here
and um not laugh at chat making references to ants let's go back and talk to you all right so
you got demon broth what is it now uh let's let me listen what's so great about that demon broth
anyway what's great is that it's nutrient rich that it's mine and i'm not letting you two parasites
anywhere near nutrient rich once i've perfected this recipe i'll never need to worry about money
again we're gonna make another person out of this broth isn't it kind of overkill to have a radio
and a jukebox anything to drown out the noise my granddaughter calls music it ruins the digestion
to be fair sam stinky's food does require you to be 100 focused on digestion okay you got more
station are you listening to there'd be only one station worth listening to in the greater new york
area wsnt listening to wsnt okay remember that station wsnt probably gonna need it
oh you and girl stinky will be working like a moment oiled machine in no time mark my words
for you boy oh did people really say that sam that woman will be the death of me that's the idea
can't you and girl stinky just get along all this negative energy is bad for my psychic balance
she's the one locking a master chef like me out of his own kitchen it won't be a problem after i
perfect my recipe and make me fortune i figured it out he's got a whipped cream beard on okay
grandpa i was trying to figure out what it was glad to see you back working in this diner again
after returning from a long time away to work with your granddaughter who's also coincidentally
named stinky was all that really necessary sorry max is all short-term memory i have to
bring him back up to speed every once in a while giant talking dog okay so can i use the
psychic powers treating you try let me try something all i can do just to turn this
back into a place that lures decent people into eat the carefully placed rack droppings are one
of those flourishes you don't notice until they're missing did you see all the decorations she's
scattered about rubbish at least then we had some customers i you really appeal to the lucrative
insect and talking statue demographic i'll give you that all right do you know anything about
skunk ape as part of the freelance neighborhood watch we're warning everybody about an alien
gorilla on the street general skunk copy we do well to have more of his kind in this neighborhood
instead of these shiftless layabouts loitering around until somebody comes to ask them questions
wow i never would have guessed grandpa stinky was so prejudiced against non-player characters
skunk copy is a true commander he's going places i could even see now are we gonna to the white
house are we gonna have to do another election thing most likely do we have to defend our
presidential championship belt just be careful around skunk ape ah you just don't trust him
because he's no human uh what he's welcome here anytime my granddaughter could do a lot worse than
to court a magnificent specimen like general skunk copy you gross okay so all right sam pull
out some of the uh what was that activate future vision on the demon broth right does he do it
ha ha so long suckers what about your super secret demon broth take it after today i never need to
worry about money again what does he bring hit the lottery or something we interrupt this program
for a breaking news bulletin officials for the city's 700 million dollar lottery jackpot drawing
have announced that there is one winning ticket sold to unemployed and somewhat pathetic molopolis
harry mullman okay so harry mullman we gotta get the ticket from harry mullman
and get here and then take the broth i was hoping you'd call no no no don't speak those detectives
are finally gone but someone might be listening in we should meet in person perfect i'll leave
right away what of course not and salmon max don't suspect a thing all right so first of all
we've got harry mullman wins the lottery in the future he gets the money somehow or doesn't care
about this anymore so now is there anything else i can do what's that all right what about you sam
what do you know would you look at that max amazing just press what button would you press
the button there's a button underneath i don't know there's a secret button all right so
okay let's get out of here i think i have to all right let's go find harry mullman
whoa a button yeah i know right this phone only accepts dutch gilder coins sorry sam
all i've got are some yuan a few euros and six bucks an italian lira where do you keep all that
change in my sock of course you're naked where do you keep your sock that's none of your damn business
all right appreciate aquarium i need to do that first you know now that i think about it i don't
think i've ever seen a fish in this aquarium they're probably just hiding from the stink
okay so i have one piece of the puzzle there we need a lottery ticket a winning lottery ticket
i didn't skip that so harry's not down there let's just okay we need to talk to this guy first
he's okay he's interviewing him there's like an interview going on no never mind hello sir
hello sir mr president president you are the ruler of this planet oh no i'm just president of the
united states we're only one of many united nations working together you can speak freely
oh okay yeah i'm in charge pretty much perfect just the one i wanted to see
see keep the hands where we can see him pal of course i have come to your pitiful beautiful
world for a peaceful exchange of technology all the wonders of the galaxy yours
what's the catch no catch all i ask in return is your help while my research assistant search for
an artifact of artisans to make demon broth
what's this about an artifact it is the eyes of yogsogoth one of hundreds of magical toys
scattered throughout the galaxy by the great comet it's believed to give the holder the power to see
the future what a coincidence i was just he was just saying how he wished he could see the future
so he and i would stop showing up to work wearing the same thing it gets pretty awkward
okay so we have it you're looking for the thing that we have so about this artifact yes you have
found it not as far as you know but just for fun why is it so important to you it's a legendary
treasure said to give the wielder the power to predict his enemies every movement manipulate
the economies and governments of weaker worlds avoid death bind complex solutions to puzzles
using unconventional combinations of everyday items and crush anyone who stands in his way
but that's all just a myth i would simply give it away to my nephew in canada hey all right just
wondering how much do you pay for security on a ship like that security you know laser grads
explosive time locks that kind of thing we're just curious my spaceship and the wonders aboard it
are open to all the feeble people we can go in this spaceship it's no fun when they don't put up a
fight need anything so we can just walk right on your spaceship whenever we want of course
the miracles of my technology are welcome to everyone especially to your planet's
mole people really hmm harry we're gonna take a vacation what's the story behind your whole
mole man fixation oh it's no fixation general skunk copy is a friend to all creatures of the
galaxy from the greatest ape to the tiniest most insignificant and pitiable mole man hey we know
the most insignificant and pitiable mole man on every planet i visit all of the local mole people
are invited to ride my fantastic gamma beam to a wonderful off-world vacation they'll never forget
it i don't kill them yeah i was gonna say what does that mean what's that supposed to mean
where are these fabulous off-world vacations exactly why any planets you can imagine
that's not a planet max it is yes it is nubile amazon priestesses bathing in rivers of chocolate
and toffee oh they made it a planet again sure why not didn't they go back on that
no it's not i thought they went back on that does the general want a banana
i see because i resemble your earth gorillas you assume i want a banana i'm glad to see that
earthlings are still so charmingly racist relax buddy we're just making sure you're getting enough
potassium you're not from around here are you guilty you could tell by the accent right
it no i have traveled from a planet hundreds of light years away from your own it was once
a beautiful swampy and muggy world the air dancing with swarms of mosquitoes the stillness
of the nights punctuated only by the mewling of infants and the drunken revelries of toothless
secessionists its name would be impossible for your earth tongues to pronounce but my people
know it as pensacola pensacola that's super ball as you know sirs when you appointed me
secretary of the posterior that placed me in command of the department of home world security
i didn't know we had one of those did you max heck if i know as soon as they gave me a button that
shoots ballistic missiles and a hotline to mila jovovich i lost interest in everything else well
i investigate visitations from aliens abductions violations of the time stream lost continents
myth and legends that kind of thing super ball what's the home world security threat level super
ball it's currently hovering between candy apple and fire engine red sir now keep you updated
so you're planning to just find your magic toy and leave the planet peacefully right the earth's
chamber of commerce has a selection of coupons for discounted dining and entertainment during
your stay find my toy and leave of course not
stay frosty max this is the part where he loses it and rips his mask off or eats a live mouse
or something roger that i'll get my video camera i would never leave without sharing the technology
of my world with your backward but fascinating people don't let him snap because yeah because
like you don't want to be like listening to music and i know what you mean by that
don't fucking we don't talk about movies all right we'll uh let you know if we find that
artifact after clearing it through the department of home world security first just a formality
go in peace all right let's get in let's go on the ship it's general skunk ape's horrible spaceship
good likeness oh by the way pluto is uh currently being discussed to become a planet again it's
like new from like january 2019 look it up this place looks eerily familiar check it out max the
control center for invaders from distant stars yeah yeah alien spaceship seen it i just want to
get to the part where i have those sweet psychic powers we just need our friend the brain to hook
you up and oh no he's dead didn't he look more moist in the future we've got to find some way
to wake him up so he can explain what's going on yeah i'm gonna i'm i live in vegas so i'm
gonna go down to the like casino and be like hey can i pick can i put like a bet down if
pluto is gonna be a planet again in like a year or two i'm gonna win like 100 million dollars
he died too soon i'm assuming how are we going to wake him up you must figure out how to do it
eventually sam he was awake in the future well that's going to be pretty clever of me
i wonder how i end up doing it hmm i want i wonder what was that dolphin
you did it sam and max you awakened me from the sleep of 100 deaths how did you do it
well that's encouraging so uh how did we do it i don't know we haven't done it yet i know
skip the whole game future vision on me where are you you did it sam and max you awakened me
from the sleep of 100 deaths how did you do it easy peasy all it took was stinky's demon broth
and mama bosco's futuristic power core okay well you heard the mean we got the material we've got
to find some demon broth and mama bosco's futuristic power core okay need what else do i need
is there so we just have to bring those two things in here what about that hey it's all my stuff
it's all my stuff okay what else is there to look at anything else we need mama bosco's power core
and the demon broth and we know how to get the demon broth congratulations
this is him going on vacation does he win the 100 million dollars and then okay congratulations
you're gonna get like sucked through a tube and be put on it it's definitely like they definitely
kill him or something has to be okay uh let's get back out of here let me look at this door
this door damn aside ladies big winner coming through let me big winner congratulations
hey pal we want to ask you i've been listening to suits like you for too long already
you can dig your own tunnels now while i enjoy you know expenses paid off world vacation
so long suckers yeah all right so they they definitely like a thing they yeah they like
grind them up into like power or something they get power from the moment and that is why we're
doing a staycation this year literally yeah well there's a mining helmet weird there's a hard hat
and some kind of vacation ticket all the personal effects confiscated from our fuel resources are
collected and donated to various intergalactic mole man charities what a nice gesture we should
leave it for when that mole man gets back sam i think he uh went to live on a farm to play
with other moment oh check if he left his wallet no such luck so did i get anything okay so i got
the uh the hard hat i got the off-world vacation ticket all right so i'm gonna have to give that
to harry are we gonna are we actually gonna kill harry that seems kind of mean i'm just
saving the game is it already that's auto okay there's an auto save i was making sure there's
an auto save and there is how about this it's empty nothing in it all right let's go back down
any other things in the spaceship should i put on the future glove the future glasses and
glow i was gonna say goggles but there are goggles put them on anything in here with the cell the
uh all right no no no what about down here you did it sam how did you do it easy of his i sure
hope that alien brain appreciates all the trouble we're going through to bring him back to life
easy you know how those intellectuals are they'll probably start bragging that he doesn't own a tv
worry that your future vision was just a big misunderstanding and skunk ape turns out to be
a good guy after all worrying is for lesser creatures sam i'm a highly advanced psychic
being the next stage in our evolution well when you put it like that i can't help but be even more
terrified all right let's keep seeing max keep in touch out the door so i need demon broth i need
mama bosco's core all right well there's a new development let me see can i can i go into bosco's
let's go check labs visit our new location oh so mama bosco's too good to haunt our street anymore
well this is kind of a bad neighborhood to be a ghost all the best cemeteries are on the other
side of town so let me let me future this up anything out here i feel like i should use it
here yeah all right well we got cybill's boxes oh okay i get it nothing changes they just they're
still here okay yes this i am using this in front of them the thing eventually takes off but hold on
what about what's this sam and max save earth from alien invader oh i gave away the ending
anything else to look at i just want to see it all
yep gee little buddy here in 2109 our street looks pretty much the same as it did a hundred years ago
keep moving earthling ever skunk ape the second has demanded tribute you used to be so much cooler
here you're not you when you're hungry have an ant snickers see wherever that is then oh my love
all right nothing else to see here pull it out so this is the new address visit us at our new
location fifth and 43rd d all right can i drive there well there's still more to do hold on did
you remember to feed the parking meter max i slaved all day over a hot stove for it and why
here one word of thanks can't do anything with the rats welcome to a bold new reimagining of
the computer obsolescent prevention society are they all just stuffed in here what are you doing
in our car i said you guys could hang out in our car until you found your own place but it's been
months now you have been randomly selected to enjoy a free trial of the crime hyphen tron xl
at no cost to you okay do you guys know where to find where's a power core power core
what's his problem we were forced to witness mama vasco tearing apart
circuit boards to construct her power core we prefer not to talk about it it was horrible
how are you guys supposed to help us fight crime yeah you're not even as powerful as a cell phone
max that was completely uncalled for with my one six mhz of raw power i am able to analyze data
at speeds rivaling the most advanced pocket calculators ow what do you do i'm a functional
telephone and that's about it all right what happened to that bluster blaster machine you
used to hang out with he has traveled with user vasco to las vegas nevada what's an outdated
arcade machine supposed to do in vegas he doesn't even have any money blaster blaster received a
generous workers compensation settlement upon his termination from kimplica we cannot comment
while litigation is pending he's here he's here now you guys should keep an eye on general skunk he's
right behind you he's evil that guy is the total heat sink a real motherboard he thought everybody
else liked them except for us his so-called advanced technology is going to make thousands
of hard-working computers and robots lose their jobs when buying technology look for the made on
earth label okay what's this business about a free trial you have selected to hear more about the
crime tron xl in a world where thugs and supervillains rule the streets only the most
technologically advanced crime stoppers will emerge victorian submit clues gathered from
your investigations and we will analyze the living hell out of them okay so we can try out the crime
tron right now we can actually put stuff in the crime tron xl may not yet be available in some areas
we are still recruiting members for the cops your japanese robot dog into this group we talked about
this that dog is straight up creepy can i drive the cars is great and all but could we have our
car back if you'd like to drive somewhere use the handy city map contained in the glove thank you
hey sam isn't our car still possessed by demons it is not so bad as long as you do not try to
run the air conditioner okay so give me the map i'm talking to you guys is great if you'd like
to drive somewhere use the handy city map don't have to like be out of this here cops end of line
time pull it out make a phone call drop okay drive somewhere all right bosco tech lab
let's go get that power cord so bosco's mom is here else is out here what's in the band name
bosco and science go together like church and state okay might as well take a look
oh there's a lot nothing over there what about the banner two in one blow and without any
significant injuries either two in one blow i'm being strangled uh well that knocked him out
cold i'm getting pieces of the story here in random order okay nothing else who's like just
floating around here okay now i already took care of that before we left i'll go this way
no no no post what you're knowing to talk no sheesh what a jerk there's stuff over here
can i go up okay i can go up the ladder wait didn't i put it on over here oh yeah i was just
gonna climb that that's what i was just gonna do i don't need you to tell me that future just climb
it but can i well look i'm gonna get strangled in front of no i'm not i saw the future and i
wanted to play out differently mama bosco get out of here it's sam and max hiya harry we were
looking for mama bosco do not be afraid mama bosco has passed on to the other realms but i
shall attempt to establish a link to there she is hey good looking should give him the pass
so he gets like liquidated or whatever they do to him bosco sends greetings from the ethereal
plains welcome to the labs you're my first visitor wait i was your first visitor right
oh no no i'm back he needs to win the lottery all right i got telephone games and say we got a
lot of grand things spider web spider webs and spooky houses go together like well-dressed dogs
and naked bunnies how many times have i told you not to use the b word sam
hello operator oops sorry you know how those spirits are once they get talking about the good
old days when they were alive i guess we can't make outgoing calls no outgoing calls all right
uh skeleton painting one of yan hooks for hands rare portraits he took so long to finish a painting
his subjects often died while posing okay anything else try turn on the future glasses not yet
thankfully i do have the item that he needs ectoplasm what's that hey need the eerie
oozing remains of mama bosco's ghostly visitations oh that must be ectoplasmic
jelly because ectoplasmic jam don't shake like that hold on did did max just say that there was
a difference between jelly and jim that jelly is not jim interesting wow i didn't even have to say
that can i take it can i pick it up charmingly outdated science textbooks from the earth to the
elaborate moon landing hoax it's mama bosco's dimensional destabilizer thing push that green
button what's the worst it could do tear a hole in the fabric of existence and bring the elder
gods back to this dimensional plane oh what happens if you double click it you get two of them i guess
all right look at weird i love that description look at weird ball thing that's something mama
bosco invented or an award mama bosco got for inventing something either way it's pretty
impressive if these findings are true then that would mean it's scientifically impossible for
max and me to exist oh no wait uh i was reading it wrong okay let's uh let's take out the future
thing future ectoplasm well harry thanks sam and max this is exactly what i need to turn my life
around there he's got a great big wonderful surprise waiting for him and to think all it
took was this are you sure you can't make those future visions last a little longer max that's
the car take all the fun out of it so the future vision seemed to be almost like the hint system
kind of because like i know i haven't got to give him the vacation card my missing power or
a lottery i knew you were the right one to find it flint paper i was nothing okay so flint finds
the power core my missing power core i knew you were the right one to fight yeah i was nothing
all right so that's that what about on mama bosco my missing power was all right so we need
to find a way to get let's just go talk to harry wait so long suckers prepare yourselves more women
of outer space the love digger is on his way
it's the card here come harry come here hi harry let's talk i'm sensing that you want to ask me
some questions that way lottery or vacation ticket because i need to get the demon broth
so if i just kill him right now he's just dead if money's tight maybe you should try the lottery
i've got a really good feeling about your chances this time and then he's he's going to have a
winning ticket on unemployed losers who don't understand how numbers work and then we liquidate
if you bought well no wait uh one okay the winning ticket is going to be in his personal
belongings so how do we do the lottery drawing though that's the question are you sure that
you're compatible with mama bosco of course i've been blessed with the unique ability to
communicate what the recently deceased only you can see me huh how many fingers am i holding up
only one see okay well you know harry we can all see and hear mama bosco that's just a manifestation
of the unconscious oh who am i kidding you're right i'm just useless come on harry you're not
just useless i'll get that lottery ticket you're totally useless what are you doing here harry
i'm working as mama bosco's lab assistant i never hired him and she says i'm perfect for the job
but you don't know anything about science or hygiene which means i'll never go mad and take
over the lab for my own twisted experiments i'm perfect that's not a you know you're not wrong
i thought you already had a job apparently there was some kind of power shakeup i got laid off
you guys aren't looking for another partner are you no we'll uh keep your resume on file
in case there's an opening let's liquidate him so when he has to hold on right i've got
yeah the lottery is just for unemployed losers who don't know so how many tickets have you bought
well no wait uh one yeah see what here you just want a vacation did you hear about general skunk
ape's fabulous off-world vacations what mole man hasn't heard about it it's the talk of the five
boroughs why don't you go try it out i was at a job interview and they gave out the tickets
by the time i got back it was already too late well i've got some news for you if you can talk
to the dead maybe you know about psychic powers sam's worried about my brain because i can see
the future now psychic powers there's no such thing they just made that up to sell documentary
tv series back in the 70s see sam there's nothing to worry about unless they're caused by a giant
deadly tumor okay see you around harry and cheer up you'll get what's coming to you that's what i'm
afraid of and ghosts kind of feel bad about this but uh here you go harry i'll take that lottery
cheer you up harry on all expenses paid vacation you actually have one of skunk copy's golden
tickets now that's a nice gesture but i don't take charity what i'd have to give you something in
return uh you wouldn't happen to have a lottery ticket would you oh sure i buy one every week
but it's worthless i never win anything i mean uh it's incredibly valuable to me i don't know
if i could part with it okay then see you harry wait i can part with it just give me that vacation
ticket so long suckers prepare yourselves mole women of outer space the love digger is on his
way all right we got the ticket let's make this happen use mole man tunnel harry must have dug
his way in here they say they don't like to be in bright sunlight but i say it's just an excuse
to do more property damage a brilliant excuse hey max why don't you hop in there and see where it
leads yeah sure crawl through a narrow tunnel to nowhere filled with hairy mole man spores
all right so you don't want to go in there all right let's go back to let's do the
give the ticket to stinky and then watch the fireworks because i can't i need to talk to
flint all right that's the guy that was here let's get out of here actually hold on i can
what just did i just go up twice it's gonna take some real detective work to track down
that missing power core let me yeah i'll talk to her crawl into the mole man's hole
what can i do for you boys all right power core do you happen to know anything about a power core
where do we get it where did you hear about that from magazines about pam flicks where's
you did who do you think stole your power core no idea i've got a um real detective on the case
though it's a good thing we're trying to steal it too or we'd be offended by that remark couldn't
have come at a worse time either i've almost got my dimensional destabilizer working but the
dimensional rift generator is useless without power man if i had a nickel for every time i
didn't understand what you just said okay what did this power core thing look like it looks
like a car battery question it looks like a power core you know that's like asking what a
bander poop particle emitter looks like what does a bander what is a bandicoot power i don't
remember even what you just said the new lab is um nice thanks for saying so but it needs work
do you have any idea how hard it is to find abandoned real estate in manhattan that's not
already haunted it is a dyer's market i had to start reading the exorcism listings in the paper
just to find a lead on this place okay where's bosco dr mama bosco your lab is actually pretty
impressive i don't know where he is bosco's inventions always kind of well uh sucked yes
well he was always a special boy i want to know what his favorite casino is because i'm just
gonna go there every day and like sit in the same spot and wait for him and then when he finally
shows up i'm gonna be like oh i'm gonna bump it hey whoa what the fuck boss bosco this is great
i'm on vacation right now have you heard from bosco he sent a few postcards he and that bluster
blaster machine finally made it to las vegas i didn't know bosco liked gambling he said he's
got a system plus 15 billion dollars left over from the money that some idiots gave him for
his inventions i'm sure those idiots had very good reasons okay what about the did you hear
about the alien gorilla that landed on our street yeah it came through on the news alert something
about sharing alien technology and ending all of poverty and disease on earth your bosco isn't uh
i'm sure he's fine i'm even gonna ask don't tell him help me finish my dimensional destabilizer
uh let's let's keep i'd be careful around that general skunk ape you too don't trust anybody do
you what do you mean by that yeah what are you trying to pull just wait till he helps me with my
inventions then you'll see he's not such a bad guy why didn't you just set up your lab in the
inconvenient store not everything happens on your street sam besides that place isn't zoned for
mixed use haunting they've got guys from the city coming by every day to evict me from this place
only way to get rid of them is by making the walls bleed how's the afterlife treating you mrs mama
bosco that's doctor mama bosco i spent the summer getting my phd online yeah i started to do that
but i kept getting distracted by all the funny cat pictures you don't know how to use computers max
what's your doctorate in mama bosco bridging the trans-dimensional gap to return spirits to
their corporeal form my masters was in funny cat pictures sounds like you're tired of being a ghost
oh it's not all bad i'm getting better at apparating and now i don't leave a trail of
ectoplasmic slime behind every time i leave the room that's better than sam can say but i'll be
glad when i finish my dimensional destabilizer and get my body back are you guys minus doing
things that i'm not saying yeah touching is my third favorite thing to do to things
uh in case anyone was curious second is licking all right
can we have a separate meter for the other guys here you're a doctor can you tell us anything
about late onset male psychic dysfunction psychic powers it's probably a melon-sized deadly tumor
probably well it could be mind worms of course but i don't want to be alarmist most likely it's
the deadly tumor couldn't max just have the perfectly safe kind of non-lethal psychic
powers oh it's max uh i'm sure it's nothing to worry about then could you uh i'm treating it
like reddit gold farther away from my machines though oh thanks for the gold are these psychic
powers dangerous for max at all well probably not if he's careful and only uses them responsibly
everything on this stream is my responsibility he'll overwork his brain so much that it catches
fire and explodes oh i have got to see that you can't see that max your brain will catch
fire and explode that's why you'll have to record it for me sam duh it is your stream after all on
the other side dr mama bosco not if i can get this destabilizer working all right so we were good
okay just mute the game every time they say a bad joke well the subtitles on you'll read it
every time they say something not funny i have to say something really funny and every time they
say something really funny i have to say something terrible so the score will even out completely
i'll work on it anything else in here are you guys ready to help us fight crime we're still on
a search for new recruits if you spot any new office equipment be sure to hook a brother up
oh wait wait wait what about the give me the jumping jumper cables neither of us knows how
to use them it's simple sam the red cable goes on the right nipple and the black cable clamps to
the other of us knows how to use them legally max i'm seeing too many plus twos for that
no i'm sorry guys i gotta bring this down that's not me i didn't do that
no no no no i'm sorry all right uh i didn't do anything yet all right the name bosco and
science go together like churches he cares too much about this all right so we two birds we got
two birds with one stone hold on air conditioner pretty cool not useful though let's put on the
3d glasses well that knocked him out cold that knocked him out cold somebody just said i i hope
his this his stream goes to minus a thousand one day what you you want me to have a really bad
stream what oh i you know it would be great if his stream was fucking terrible i can't wait till
it's awful what so i could take a bath later and like sit there crying you want me to have like
stress over like how bad my stream was no i'm not gonna sell oh my god why
uh uh journal wide about the clown car gave five community subs thank you for the five subs
this antenna is way too flimsy this is pure manipulation i don't even the score this is
this is an absolutely nullified score today absolute manipulation can i do anything with this
don't think so you guys have found out how to manipulate the market let's get it to a minus
a thousand i can manipulate it too just say i'm not i don't want to say that one i don't want to
say that word okay i got the jumper cables let's go back and do harry mole man uh turn off the chat
turn off the chat they're doing it on they're trying to do it on purpose how do i turn off chat
how do i do streamer only mode streamer only i don't want to i don't want mods talking streamer
only mode streamer only is there a way to do that how do i like is there a way i can turn off the
chat there has to be a way right no there's no way see they can't now like you know they're
keeping any mode only they can't minus two or closer right now but guess what i can hey mods
you want to do me a favor here just get it back up to like fucking 200 and where it belongs please
thank you oh oh what it manipulates the other way i'm upset about this oh yeah no i'm only
allowed to manipulate the score oh fuck i'm going to jail i'm going to jail for this all right all
right well that's fine that's fine that's good well we could uh we can never take it off emote
only mode apparently there's gonna be there's no way i can't take it off do you understand what's
gonna fucking happen if you take that off it's gonna be an absolute tsunami of minus two yeah
this is bad what do i do um fuck i don't know what to do i didn't think that all the way through i
got like 35 of the way through that one hey hey hey hey people can go through the filter
people but they have to pay they have to pay money
that's so stupid 25 cents people have subscribing and paying and doing plus two as well
your manipulation tactics won't work you're gonna break twitch settle down it's locked sam where do
you think that mole man went i'm sure is this is this the is this like the biggest long con
you've ever seen on stream it could be this could be the biggest like money con it's locked this is
gonna fuck up the bit reading at the end so bad i'm gonna have to scroll through all this
nothing hey hey what's going on hey hey hey how do i delete that a mod just did minus two that's
not cool but hold on for like the federal like trade commission i didn't make sure like i do
it too because like then they can look through the records and be like oh wait he sold in blood
oh my fucking god all right all right all right turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off
turn it up i'm willing to accept any responsibility here turn it off
okay all right i gotta what do i have to do okay lottery ticket i gotta give this to stinky
i really messed up yeah i messed up tonight today really might be the put it on like
six hour slow mode thing i'm thinking about it that's the only way i think this i can put
like i could put like a piece of gum in the hole of this boat you get to say one chat message
uh i'm gonna i'm gonna why do i have to pee so bad stinky's award-winning spaghetti
mentioned in the past five issues of the occupational safety and health administration's
journal of six hours slow mode mystery night you get one chat message all right yeah okay i've got
i'm gonna take i'm gonna go pee and then we're gonna come back and everyone's gonna be settled
down by then and we'll keep we'll keep going all right just everybody chill i gotta hold on
i know how to fix this hold on wait wait i can fix it i can fix it is it no clown videos on youtube
that aren't like evil and scary and like a blood in them what the fuck a clown on youtube it's
like oh i'm scary clown like comes with a chainsaw at me whatever i'll be back you know how i know
you suck because your username is i suck 24 7 oh you know how i know you sir because you're dead
did you just break your controller here we are 750 people at recording of this video 750 people
are now subscribed to the channel i have nothing to say besides thank you so much i was supposed
to do this at 500 but as you can see it's a little too late for that i i can't really do that now
so here it is for 500 subscribers even though it's way past that now here you go
it's time to get fucking huge these are bicep curls baby there's one there's two
three if you're wondering these are 35 pound weights let's really get this going come on
i need like
so here we are 750 people at recording of this video 750 people are now subscribed to the channel
i have nothing to say besides thank you so much i was supposed to do this at 500 but as you can
see it's a little too late for that i i can't really do that now so here it is for 500 subscribers
even though it's way past that now here you go it's time to get fucking huge these are bicep curls
baby there's one there's two three if you're wondering these are 35 pound weights so let's
really get this going come on i need like so here we are 750 people at recording of this
video 750 people are now subscribed to the channel i have nothing to say besides thank you so much
i was supposed to do this at 500 but as you can see it's a little too late for that i
i can't really do that now so here it is for 500 subscribers even though it's way past that now
here you go it's time to get fucking huge these are bicep curls baby there's one there's two
three if you're wondering these are 35 pound weights so let's really get this going come on
i need like so here we are 750 people at recording of this video 750 people are now
subscribed to the channel i have nothing to say besides thank you so much i was supposed to do
this at 500 but as you can see it's a little too late for that i i can't really do that now
so here it is for 500 subscribers even though it's way past that now here you go
it's time to get fucking huge these are bicep curls baby there's one
there's two three if you're wondering these are 35 pound weights so let's really get this going come
on
here we are 750 people at recording all right all right are we done how are we doing
how we doing on uh pluses and minuses here that's fine i was supposed to do this at 500 but as you
can see it's a little too late for that i i can't really do that now so here it is let's get rid of
that subscribers even though it's way past that now here you go close that please thank you
okay oops um okay uh we're back i sent my email uh i was sending an email so make sure that was
all right so let's get back to sam and max why is really really really you're not serious right
wow wow do i really have to turn it off no fuck it fuck it i don't care do it
keep doing it i don't care oh this is where he loses it this is where he loses his grip
he had he had chat in over the last few years he had his chat like you know behave and no like
spam and he did an all right job and then this is this is the stream where it's gone forever
you spammed us what all right i have seen that video in text format
6 000 times you saw it in video format like five times this is a big difference
all right so welcome back to sam and max everybody well people are really writing
emotes so if it's emote only mode right all right i thought it was over okay i gotta talk to flint
here we go okay hey it's flint paper here we are welcome back furry pals flint can help us with
our case sam anytime fellas except now would you look at that stinky's prize winning spaghetti
a private dick's gotta eat you know that's it do you know anything about a missing power core flint
give me a break sam i haven't eaten a thing since that yak's blood on my himalayan caper
and some gummy worms come back when i'm done eating would you oh shit people are getting
fucking crushed right now all right well easy easy easy hold on hold on i ask the king i demand
everyone stop don't people are getting like banned no no no more talking no don't ban anybody no
don't do copy pastes i i demand this as the king of this kingdom oh fuck they're ahead the doors
are breaking open i'm standing up right now i'm the fucking king okay and i'm like this is what
happens they're like they're at the front door like silence i command it silence i'm holding up
like a fucking knight flake quiet this is how you overthrow the king the king is just a guy
you understand oh my god people are getting like banned i i have like a few like knights that have
big shields and people are just sprinting just sprinting into the castle i'm talking like full
fucking sprint and just like body hitting into the shield and like and it's gonna like another
three or four thousand of you and the shields are gonna go down area does that imply that i'm
the alien in area 51 why do i have why am i the alien why am i the alien well you're never gonna
you'll you'll never get me yes yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah every time salmon max is
supposed to be like oh i have an idea how about i uh chill and play salmon max that's like a chill
game and people are banging down my fucking kingdom door this always happens when i play
that's like the outliers the catalyst how many people have been banned in the last 20 minutes
i'm so glad i got that i caught it thank god you didn't see that that was embarrassing was horrible
anyways um let's go back into let's get i need to get the power core okay here's what's gonna
happen let's here comes the treaty i'm gonna put forth the terms here's the terms i'm gonna make
sure i'm on camera for this this will get it's gonna it's gonna be it's gonna be it's gonna be
these can be good terms okay do what i fucking say when i say it
what i meant to say was when do uh do what you feel like doing but under certain rules
okay don't make me fucking use this some of the tourists give subs what do you mean no no no you
don't agree to those terms they're not agreeing to the terms you have to agree to these terms
otherwise we can't move on we can't move on with the stream i need to see at least 90% yeas
i don't give shit i'm still i'll stick around so i'm gonna turn it on six hour slow mode it's
gonna happen get your get your one chat message ready i'm gonna laugh my ass off if i do this
and then it's still that copy poster and then what happens after that is no there is no there's
nothing after that can we get some good conversation in here on the one chat
message that you get to have all right do it do it do it put it on six hour slow mode right now
do it what's wrong with me don't do that hope you got your chat messages ready because we're gonna
have a civil chat in here and then when that's done open it up i want to there you go 1800 second
slow mode hopefully you holy shit the power of some of you guys 30 minutes is the max really
what the it's all right you're wasting your messages you all right let it out let it out
let's see what they have to say let it open it up let's see what they have to say let's see let's
see you have 30 minutes no one's gonna be able to talk no one's gonna be able to talk then it's
gonna be hilarious because what's gonna happen is all this big flood oh like lol look at the
coffee pasta and then this is gonna be a 3300 person stream with like three messages in the
chat see some people are really smart about this this is your opportunity people are you're holding
on to this i'm not gonna say shit i'm not gonna say shit for like 15 straight minutes and then
i'll be the only person in the chat that's a really good somebody just said spaghetti what a waste
you wasted your you wasted it poopoo peepee that's another great one to throw in the trash
i want to see what happens in 30 minutes 30 minutes from right now what happens
what happened what oh it's got like i was like a fish on a hook
okay fuck that one i'm not reading that one okay all right look it was slowing down a
little we're starting to see the wall come in oh oh it's coming up oh oh oh oh look wait it's
normal i can see let's play salmon max remember to keep the webcam on i'll do it for like 15
seconds yeah see those here's the thing there are people right now that are typing up their perfect
chat message and there's five german wide about the clown car gave like 10 20 community subs here
didn't they like over the last like 15 minutes apologize to chat apologize for what having my
castle stormed this message was a waste i can't think of a good message it's all right you will
see in 30 minutes somebody just wrote quinoa all right what was i doing again what do we have a
timer when 30 minutes is up i'll know i'll know when 30 minutes is up because it's gonna be a
wave of the same copy positive that's how i know it's been 30 minutes i'm surprised that there's
still this many people able to talk all right here's a lottery ticket what is it now stay
cheerful grandpa stinky it's gonna take some real detective work to track down that missing
power core why am i not buff anymore uh because i stopped really going to the gym we're all torn
up about stealing your patent 30 years ago grandpa stinky maybe this will make up for it
a lottery ticket don't you know that nobody ever wins these students program for a breaking news
bulletin officials for the city's 700 million dollar lottery jackpot drawing have announced
that there is one winning ticket sold to unemployed and somewhat pathetic molopolis resident harry
mullman is just in in a surprising upset we're told that the winning ticket was transferred
to local diner owner grandpa stinky hey we transferred it on sorry harry mullman better luck
next time did you hear that i told you i would win so long suckers we've been hearing that an
awful lot lately what about your super secret demon brock take it you don't really like that
today i never need to worry about money again ever ever and i mean ever but pineapple on pizza
is fucking disgusting and like i don't know how do you guys feel about this but like it's it's
it should never be on pizza ever ever ever ever it's fucking horrible it's disgusting and like
you should like feel like like you should never order that shit okay well that's the quickest
way i was able to make people use their chat message that's good okay uh let's keep going
so now he now we get the demon broth right we better find a use for this quick max
i don't like the way it sloshes around in my coat it gets everything disconcertingly moist
oh sure blame the demon broth i got the demon broth i'm trying to think some other like opinions
that i might have on things um the witcher three is is not a good game at all i think
that should never have received even one award half-life uh by the way is like a four out of
ten i think at best half like one and half like two like i mean really that whole company in
general just made nothing but like four to ten games so i don't know how you guys feel about that
but okay what you can tell we're running low you can tell we're running low any idea when you'll
be done eating flint somebody right now heard that and they're like i can't believe you fucking
should that i wish i could say fuck you but i can't that's the point now we're down to less than
probably 20 people okay so i got the demon broth now i have to get the power core from you but how
do we get this from you big bits fifty dollars came in from colonel zero haha jeremy i found a
loophole haha thank you for the 50 bucks somebody says hey german just found your channel you have
a very nice community and as an aspiring twitch streamer i'd like to know how you have such a calm
chat well um well i mean hi welcome welcome to the channel uh thanks for joining us well we have like
a our community we all agree on the same things and um everyone kind of gets it here to just like
relax and take it easy we usually have like a pretty laid-back environment so um that's why
it's a little slower people are more respectful so that's why you're seeing that except i mean
some of the person that just wrote uh penis man that's you know sometimes you get a troll or two
you know something to get like that's a hater you know it's just a troll or a hater and um
that's like how it works so uh thank you germa is using a walkthrough for five community subs
thank you for the subs though appreciate it any idea when you'll be done eating flint heck i don't
sam husband time in the future all right this is like the i love this uh cab badger just gave
50 dollars thanks for 50 bucks and they say germa dumb stupid idiot but like the person that came
sometimes you get like a hater or two or like 50 or like 100 everybody you know it's a you know
whatever troll it's a troll that's a troll troll doing that all right i have to fucking let's go
i'm too focused on like people here i can't i'm too i'm too involved in you right now i need to be
involved in this stop they can't even talk anyways just who cares they can't even talk anyways what
does he say when you'll be done eating flint heck i don't know sam sometime in the future all right
so we've got to dump the demon broth into the spaghetti no this broth is too important to waste
um i can't look over a chat and see the answer because nobody can say it it's gonna take some
real detective work to track down that missing power core it's uh if i can do it on my fucking
i don't need any chat members to yell at me wait future what happens to the spaghetti del doris
sorry i wasn't more careful oh no his head now will never be able to find mama basco's power core
wow that looked painful somebody hits him in the head with an axe what's his button wow would you
look at that max amazing i can't believe chat is still moving this fast hey germ it's been a
while hope you're enjoying your stream today i just got here and saw how dead chad is right now which
is odd and they say anyways hope you enjoy your stream all right let me figure this out
i gotta get him i gotta hit him in the head with an axe all right let me
i can't it's hard i'm having trouble paying attention to this this is all your fault if you
think about it i miss grandpa stinky and his blasphemous recipes does anybody have a timer
of how long it's been communitron extreme 5000 with over 800 messaging features available
oh boy now i can finally set up my 24 hour adults only naked bunny chat line
we're sorry we've lost my manual for that feature can you make phone calls that i can handle
please say the name of the person you want all right let's get the call to
uh stinky's diner let's just get some let's call some
stinky's diner say it grandpa all right home of the colossal blooming avocado
taste banger 17 minutes okay place your order at the beep and one of our polite delivery people
will rush it to you if he ever gets the chance which he won't sit whatever happened to symbol
she's just gone now the phone's ringing in the box it was still on her honeymoon
kind of pointless to try and call her in retrospect
mr pizza i want an extra large thick crust with one half peanut butter and passion fruit
the other half with watermelon only you want cheesy dingles max you have to ask why was that
two no three orders of cheese why was that gouda no three right an extra fudge sauce okay thanks
how long till it gets here probably never max nobody answered
you've reached bosco tech labs the city's leading research facility for scientific breakthroughs
with a woman's touch science and woman's touch are two things you hardly ever hear together
i'm dead right now but feel free to call again later it's too empty it's too no so that's fine
that's why i have to keep this phone has been disconnected i feel like i have
two thousand of you in a jar keep it on keep it on don't take it off this is i need this
i need this all right um jumper cables hard hat demon bronf i need to get him i need to like kill
him who has an axe i've been down here let me go back down here how does it feel to live life as
a dwarf it's fucking awesome i'm like really really strong i'm really fun to be around and
i have a ton of gold it's actually kind of great so thanks for the uh question hold on what about
you i'm not supposed to bother the construction workers when they're on break which is always
am i going to shave my armpits no no i'm not going to shave my armpits i managed my armpits
why the this is what happens when it's too slow we start talking about this it's too far away to
see if there's anything interesting and or useful in there all right i don't know what to do i don't
know what to do i know i need to have an accident with the head timer time i miss grandpa stinky
and his blasphemous recipes booger check nope impending collapse in five minutes i'm i'm kind
of nervous i actually really am i'm like scared of what's gonna happen now i can't pay attention
i have to i'm like i know i'm like staring at the volcano erupting you know i can hear it and i'm
just sitting there going i'm close enough where that volcano is gonna fucking i is gonna land on
it's gonna erupt and i'm just gonna hit me if i start running right now as fast as i can
it's still gonna erupt and it's still gonna happen i'm what am i supposed to do
all right let me talk to let me talk to you do you guys mind i'm waiting for an important
phone call phone call well wait a minute haven't seen a futuristic power core gotta call her
what no of course not what does it look like futuristic core shaped kind of powerish
so somebody comes in and kills flint mama boska would know about that kind of thing
i mean i'm guessing interesting okay somebody calls we're gonna call you i gotta get you to
leave so i can press the button see you again soon stinky yeah take your time i got it should i call
but i just didn't i just try to call okay there's probably an axe that drops down
that like hits him in the head that from that button okay so let me try calling again or who
calls her the stream has been rad as fuck and i've been twerking i'm glad you're having a fun time
doing whatever dance you're doing let me talk about finding that artifact no but my best
minions research assistants are on the case have you seen it no but i've got my best max on the
case not to point fingers or anything but we couldn't help noticing that disembodied alien
brain floating in a jar on board your ship how much do you want for it joke sucks fuck you
that person just came out that person just came out of the death they were mad for 30 minutes that
means it's almost up that means it has to be up is all that remains of my colleague
gordon joe hanson son he fought by my side for many years and gave his life to find the great
artifacts he was a great warrior he really had an eye for toys and he was a good friend
it's 10 minutes all right i'm going to get i'm going to play again no there's no hope for him
i'm afraid remind me in 10 minutes this is making me uncomfortable okay what if what would i do
we're done talking now nothing else i can do over here what is correct it's been months and they
still haven't sealed up this crack somebody should do something about it i say we all wear
gray ribbons to raise crack awareness mods give me a two-minute warning i'll be looking for it
okay just let me know what the fuck do i do here examine this it's a couple of gallons of grandpa
stinky's nutrient rich demon broth will he eat it well somebody does somebody want to eat this
maybe i could give this to somebody here what about the hard hat i'm not giving this away to
the bad guy i'll save it for somebody who really needs it nutrient rich the brain i wonder if i
just pour it on the brain and bring it back to life it's gonna take some real detective work
to track down that missing power core i'm gonna try doing it for the brain eight minutes all right
let's see what happens nutrient rich broth on the brain right all right all right didn't even need
you don't have a nose because you smell delicious the poor brain's battery has run out oh i need the
power core that won't work until we get a power supply i need the power supply shit how do i gotta
call the phone to i'll get it the people that are paying money to go over the filter is
like i said is like the like ultimate like stream scam yep all right call the restaurant
can i get a warning here can i get a warning please anybody please say the name of the person
you want to come stinkies i don't have her number
two minutes i have to do i actually have two minutes somebody confirm that please
i feel like i've been stuck in a fucking just time vortex maybe back to bomb the boss go
seven minutes people are dm'ing me max kamara i need to like have you tell me something
where's max get over here what's flint paper been doing while our building's being renovated
somebody has to kill him busting up street gangs taking out mob bosses and now he's eating every
item off stinky's menu uh-oh he's crossed the line from reckless to death wish can i get him to like
eat something different these psychic powers of yours are pretty neat i guess it's just too
bad i didn't have him on prom night cheer up pal just think of all the destruction you can call
go back go back in the diner keep watching the sky something i can i'll shoot if they try anything
funny like give them more different food talk to i'm gonna talk to stinky here because seriously
there's like it's gotta be something in here i can do stinky's award-winning spaghetti mentioned in
the past five issues of the occupational safety and health admin okay yeah is there anything else
like the pie ever since all stinky took over the kitchen stinky's signature pies have gotten
marginally more edible the insect bits give the dough that extra yeah we already saw that
do you guys mind i'm waiting for an important phone call how do we get you to get called
see you again soon how do we call you take your time i need your phone number
how do i get this phone number shit the pay phone what about the pay phone the pay phone probably
let me go to the pay phone this phone only accepts dough it's the only the coins one
how do i get that fucking phone can i go i can't go in the kitchen right wait i can just go into the
kitchen walk from the inside it's just as well you're right pal i didn't want to go in there
anyway anything else i can do i need to like get that and press the button come all the coolest
stuff is kept behind counters it's like they don't trust us sam yeah somehow i don't see
us getting back there with all these stinky's hanging around and that was i'm stuck i really
don't know what to do i don't know what to do i would have thought it was the phone call her
phone but i need to maybe go back to mama bosco's maybe bosco's mom calls two minute warning this
is a two minute warning i'm sorry i can't i can't i can't stream with this i have to get ready give
me a minute i just like boogered out of my nose and it probably was on camera but whatever i just
typed in volcano erupt and it was like what if yellowstone erupts that's do i is it is it
happening no it's not you guys are freaking me out right now all right less than a minute oh fuck
is it time here they come here they come oh boy all right that was fun i turned off the
eruption before the eruption i all right turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off
turn off slow mode well no turn it off put it on like fucking something normal all right
are you guys relaxed now can we can we stop this nonsense now good i'm glad i'm glad that we all
agree let's go back to sam and max like we should have done and i hear i hear some some noise over
here but it's a it's not it's all right everything is fine and we are back to normal i'm gonna play
the game worst joke of 2019 well that was not a joke that was keeping chad inside of a of a
like a glass jar for a half an hour so they calmed down what happened what happened what
why am i out what happened when did i exit the game no all right all right let's go
well
it's what i mean it's loud
all right where's power anything about a power core yeah mama bosco hired me to find it
standard issue find the secret invention for the scientist before it falls into the wrong hand
stuff even you guys can do it yeah no offense oh yeah we totally know where it is we were just
testing you but i'm in the middle of a case that's one hell of a lot bigger big case big case you're
working on get ready to have your furry minds blown pals because this one goes way back
think about it what do we really know about this stinky doll well the story is that grandpa
stinky actually created her using some kind of demonic spell and she's been running the
diner ever since right some crazy story it'd have to be an idiot to believe right idiots so i started
digging around and i found this out back what is it stinky my queen i cannot wait any longer
i will be making my grandparents this afternoon you say they won't trust me because i'm not human
but damn the consequences we must start phase two of the operation now i will call your private
number with the details love s an inhuman monster in bed with stinky planning something big this
afternoon name starts with s you know what that means skunk ape oh well yeah that could be it
i was thinking it was you sam you think you know a guy i'm not angry sam just very disappointed
come on max if stinky's in cahoots with general skunk ape it may have something to do with that
missing power core good luck fellas i'll let you know if i find anything else stinky sam i may be
psychic now but i've got no idea how we're gonna find out stinky's private phone number
ps just to make sure your private number is still two one two five five five eight nine four two
isn't it we got it what do you know about this creep general skunk ape just that he tried to
hire me to find some missing toys for him i'm too busy with my other case so i said nothing doing
you wouldn't know anything about these toys would you i can't lie to flip paper sam i can little
buddy nope not a thing all right we got the number don't be too hard on stinky for almost
college i'm gonna call it i'm sure it was an honest mistake i just want to see the other
dialogue different kinds of toxins here they've got their own menu nice try fellas but she's onto
me i know it i'm getting too close on this big case of mine and she's trying to rub me out
i'm not gonna call that that's a fake number my eyes look puffy to you guys always i think i'd
better go see doris she's my allergy specialist man is she gonna blow her stack what she hears
about those peanuts here we go all right let's go call the number i'm so glad to have you guys back
if i play any instruments i can play the drums i actually can i actually can i know i can i can
if you gave me a drum set i'd be able to do it all right let's call the number
you look like a drummer what can i still do the person you want to call i was hoping you'd call
no no no don't speak those detectives are finally gone but someone might be listening in we should
meet in person all right let's food order check the baby have you checked the baby see max he's
fine i told you to stop worrying what kind of pretend mother would i be if i didn't worry
about our imaginary baby please say the name of the i was hoping you'd okay uh food order you must
have me confused with someone else oh fuck no i wanted one of your lobster-fed piglet buffet
platters to go please she hung up on me how rude please say the name i was hoping ah all right let's
be yes we should go to that place with the things that you like perfect i'll leave right away that
is the exact voice that i know of my love when i'm doing anything that's not one more thing
are you a corn dog yeah let me just tell you about this that's perfect what of course not
and salmon max don't suspect a thing well that's a relief ever since the dairy freeze shut down
stinky's corn dogs have been my only source of nutritious pig sphincters
so now we can press the button hurry up quickly let's take the desoto for a spin sam i want to see
what evil the cops have wrought we can in a minute i need to press the button if i take the money
probably empty out this cash register and no one would know god would know sam you're right max and
he won't stop pestering me about the 20 bucks he loaned me opens the oh all right all right okay
wow would you look at that max amazing it's a secret passage sam really not that big a deal
secret anything else back here no go down the secret passage get the power core hook it up
attached to the brain episode oh there it is big pile of low tech audio video equipment
tossed out like pianos from a falling zeppelin and it's still warm documentary filmmakers must
be lurking nearby some secret passage it's just a bunch of junk like this old scanner
that's it do we explode first attach that kind of scan what the hey look it's mama
bosco's futuristic power core what was it doing down here that's a mystery for another episode max
all right i got the power core i've got the jumper cables let's go back to the ship
and fill it in don't hurt the seagulls we talked about no no no no what just go in the ship and
go up the stairs connect this to that is this thing evil this is probably the evil thing right
this should give that brain the jolt he needs to face the morning now we just need some way
to hook it up jumper cables turn it on you did it sam and max you awakened me from the sleep of
100 deaths how did you do it easy peasy all it took was stinky's demon broth and mama bosco's
futuristic power core don't forget the jumper cable sam they were very important whatever the
case listen carefully do not trust general scone cafe he is he is oh something's happening toys
detected toys detected toys what are you doing brain cut it out i can't help it i'm
i mean what a pleasant surprise tell me friend brain where is the toy
two toys alive the weak can't trace brian blesses curses very well i'll find them myself
is he gone yeah the coast is clear what just happened i don't know i've never felt anything
like that the toys of this planet must have astonishing power where is skunk ape's collection
of magic toys he keeps them on display as a show of power i'm regaining control over the
ship's functions so i can reveal them to you behold no we just we are with us that's it
it's a toy that lets you teleport across vast distances in the blink of an eye harry's on
vacation he's over there that's not cool enough for you it's just we saw more toys in max's vision
more toys you must not have found them yet they must still be somewhere in this city you have to
find them before scone cafe does or he'll destroy us all all right i need the other toys i got this
the rocket launcher i need the i gotta get the telephone go give me the give me the phone
wait is that it can i talk to you anymore do you have any more dialogue
sam and max do not trust scone cafe his benevolent facade belies a heart of pure evil
oh yeah we kind of already figured that out the giant fang spaceship with disintegrator eyes
was our first clue are you calling me gullible what look i don't know what planet you're from
this one actually but on my world if an alien invites you onto a spaceship you don't just
assume that he's going to cut out your brain and keep it in a jar i guess we're just not
that cynical to be fair max your future vision goggles did tip us off you mean you wield the
eyes of yogg-zagoth but but that must mean you also have the gift is is max is gonna end up being
yogg-zagoth right something like that i could see that happening in the future you seem to
know all about max's psychic powers yes max is one with the gift the toys have great power but
only to those of us with a special brain well max does have a special brain that's what all the
teachers said well that and back back i cast the out demon you must use the gift wisely max and
keep it secret from general scone cafe the power is every bit as dangerous as it is wicked awesome
okay so where the what's that more processing room all about isn't it obvious general scone cafe
is illegally harvesting mold juice old juice it's the it's blood they they they're mammals there's
blood this is just okay what is skunk ape's evil scheme anyhow no less than domination of the entire
universe did he ever mention anything more specific he's traveling from planet to planet
searching for all the toys of power if he ever manages to collect all of them he'll be completely
unstoppable mammals not the only thing with blood yeah but i mean like a mole is a mammal they just
have red blood they have like human blood moles cows dogs humans they all have blood they all
have human blood we all have the same blood why did skunk ape come here to our street he's been
using my strange psychic connection to the toys of power to track them throughout the galaxy
something very powerful pulled me to this spot i can only guess it was max's discovery of the
eyes of yog sagoth and the future vision what's your story brain can we get you anything like a
spine no it's too late for me i'm afraid i can only help you put a stop to general scone cafe's
evil schemes by controlling the doors and the higher functions of this spaceship we must work
quickly before what is in this broth is that oregano it's delightful stay focused pal it's
demon broth okay i think i got it how did you get here i have found a mysterious toy and was using
my strange power over it to amaze and delight the ladies of my village it was then that scone cafe's
ship landed he was intrigued with my power and invited me on board his spaceship so you just
went with him he said he had candy how is i supposed to know he'd imprisoned me here forcing me to use
my psychic powers against my will okay where's your body what did you look like back when you
had a body oh nothing exceptional about 63 raven hair i had what you earthlings call a runner's
build i can read minds in the future you know all right fine i believe the closest creature you have
on your planet is called a platypus okay why are we supposed to stop scone cape any weaknesses like
he's powerless against the color yellow or he can't cross running water or he's powerless against
yellow water i know what you're thinking max and stop it well of course the toys of power are useless
to him without a gifted brain to control them so he doesn't have a different brand he always says
he has a weakness for potato chips and he has to eat the whole bag yeah that doesn't really help us
much sometimes when he's in the shower i could swear i hear him crying why do you think max's
powers are dangerous apart from the obvious of course general scone cafe can't use the
toys of power himself so he needs the brain of someone who has the gift he forced me to use my
power so much that i would have died had you not rescued me if he ever found out you have the gift
max he wouldn't hesitate to do the same to you okay that's all the evidence we need let's go out
and deliver some interplanetary justice max if you end up cutting out his brain i call dibs on
scone cafe's body yeah this is like this is the bad guy probably okay so now we gotta go
and we have a scanner and i somehow just clicked out of the window i don't know how that happened
play just dance spaceship is secure if i could have a moment sirs hello sam mr president if you
have a moment you need to be debriefed too late this may come as a shock but our intel indicates
that general scone cafe is actually quite evil no i'm pretty sure i never heard of a department
of home world security agent super ball established in 1901 by theodore roosevelt after president
mckinley's assassination by one of the insect doors of the nebulon empire i'm president of
the united states why didn't i hear anything about it it's explained in books sir all right
the other fucking 30 viruses i have they'll all eat each other until there's one that remains and
then i'll just remove that with a fucking fucking c cleaner is that why you were hanging out in
our office so much last season i mean a few months ago to protect max um sure wow i feel
really close to you right now agent super ball likewise sir a bit too close okay what's the real
story behind skunk ape general skunk cafe is an intergalactic criminal warlord there's been a
galaxy-wide gorilla haunted effect ever since he escaped from the penal zone oh i didn't talk
about the thing that i want to do it's an interdimensional prison for the most dangerous
villains in the universe are we supposed to get skunk ape back into the penal zone the united
planets have simple and easily reproducible failsafe measures in place to handle escape
convicts well that's a relief all we need to do is open an unstable transdimensional gateway to
the penal zone and his prisoner's badge will take care of the rest didn't they do this schtick before
a couple times where you you you do the end of the game and then they do go back and do everything
before the end of the game like they hey this is that very end and but now do the whole thing
they've done it like two or three times uh but anyways i was in the recommended channel a few
days ago and i saw an idea that looked really really funny i believe it was vr josh that had
this idea so you know whoever else contributed to it like props props to you um do you remember
when last week i showed that video and in the video the person it was somebody's music video
and they had hidden me in like a part of the tree if you weren't there but if you were there you'll
know so they hid me in a part like in one frame of a video and they were saying oh look you're
in this video and we couldn't find it so what the recommendation said wouldn't it be fun potentially
if i did a whole stream where it was just where's waldo people would submit images that i would get
to have a magnifying glass and try to find where they'd put me in the image i feel like it would
be pretty fun i get to have the only criteria is obviously there has to be it's going to be
completely vetted um so i get to have that little microsoft magnifying glass that's the
only thing i get and i have to stay a certain amount of uh feet from the screen so i can't
like lean the fuck in like this no i have to be sitting back here we'll have something to make
it so like i'll bump into it if i lean forward and i just get the microsoft magnifying glass
and people can submit it and put me obviously in places wherever they want
there'll be a lot of hidden memes that's where i have to be careful though because
they got to be really like cleanly vetted and if you put something fucked up in there
you're out like yeah like a like a hidden object game when am i going to do it i mean this was
just a random idea and i thought it was interesting so i would assume if it's something that i'll talk
to the mods about it and maybe we'll get a plan and then we'll open up obviously potential like
submissions i didn't notice skunk ape wearing any kind of badge or a homing beacon that's because
he wasn't wearing one sir i find it extraordinarily alarming whoa whoa whoa whoa calm down you can't
think with all your hysterics forgive me mr president but unless you can find general skunk
ape's homing beacon and place it on him we're powerless to stop him there'd have to be rules
where i would have to be a certain amount of pixels you can't just make me one pixel
and put me there no no no i have to it has to be solvable i can't be impossible what did this
homing beacon look like it's a standard issue intergalactic correctional facility in mate's
badge it can't be destroyed so the only way he could have gotten rid of it is by giving it to
someone else oh it would be a decent idea is to have a channel for this right at all right i i
just figured it out so to avoid like hey look i put a like little dick on the screen that you're
going to scroll over with the magnifying glass and it's going to be hard to like you know go through
it and screen it all and oh look you scrolled over the dick on on screen oh that's funny
to make sure that doesn't happen maybe have a chat in the discord open to have like ideas
and like designated people actually put it in the image you know what i'm saying
that's probably better a group effort where like only a dozen people have the key i think that's
pretty good yeah we have to open an unstable trans-dimensional gateway you must have lost
your senses man the odds against that are astronomical even if we didn't know what that
was the gateway is the easy part sirs dr mama boscow's reckless and blasphemous work tearing
down the fabric of reality could be useful that'd be fun give me the key give me the key
a school group project where one guy does all the work her dimensional destabilizer can open
a gateway to the penal zone anyone wearing a prisoner's homing beacon will be returned to
justice automatically and scientifically okay so we need to hope we need the homing beacon
we've got to throw it on a scungate back we can't track him without his homing beacon sir
this will require some traditional detective work all right what's reckless and irrational
detective work do because that's all we know i'd recommend starting with some of his known contacts
mama boscow what do we need from mama boscow her dimensional destabilizer can open a gateway to
the penal zone anyone wearing a prisoner's homing beacon will be returned to justice
automatically and scientifically all right let's go don't worry super ball we'll hit that gorilla
where it hurts the most right in the penal zone i get it sir okay wait nothing else with you
okay well give me the other uh the other item can i get this or do i have to open it or something
later max this unassuming telephone unlocks the gift of teleportation
using the power of your mind you can teleport yourself to any phone number you have memorized
oh boy i want to try it right now all right let's talk what's on of you teleporting off without me
you can go too sam max will teleport anyone he's touching watch the hands okay
where do i want to go stinky cell boscow tech civils let's get let's go into stinky cell
enjoying the ride sam i don't know it's so scary he's made it red
note to self when traveling through max's brain keep your eyes shut uh-oh my phone just started
somebody actually just texted me right now that happened that was weird it's stinky cell phone
but why would she have left it behind especially since she's got 18 months left on her contract
either there was some kind of struggle or it was left here for us to find and we're walking right
into a trap i got it she waived her early cancellation fees with a recommended device
upgrade just happened so now we know two things you're an idiot and this phone is going to lead
us directly to general skunking somehow what the fuck i can't win well now i have the phone
i got the phone the scanner the warrant what else do i need to find carmen san diego
let's teleport somewhere was that a cow civil where's her phone shouldn't i have been appeared
in the box all right we gotta go we gotta i got a scanner what's this it's one of those obsolete
all-in-one scanner fax copier juice maker machines can't interact with the rats have already tried
nothing in the boxes a good thing civil packed all our junk into these boxes for safe keeping
and i'm especially glad we didn't put it in a secure environmentally regulated storage facility
like she asked us to yeah this way's a lot cheaper and everybody gets to enjoy it
and then back there phones light up again uh hold on what about the phone in here are you guys still
looking for a fourth member well hello there beautiful were your moving parts properly
secured when you fell from heaven do not forget our seminar on workplace harassment
plus i called dibs when exactly did this get really creepy thank you for joining us in a
brand new style of 20th century crime play you can begin submitting clues to the crime
drawn whenever you find them i do have ideas on the case cops we're sorry we haven't been
paying attention i got a phone and evidence with the crime hyphen tron and we will track
down the villains without mercy am i angry angry what no it's because i'm in like a blue room
and i probably look menacing i don't want to toss this thing around i might break it
i'm inside of like the hold on i better keep this note there could be valuable information on it
that's not evidence wait the phone and this this is not evidence i better keep this note
there could be valuable information on it it looks like you're using the crime tron
would you like help uh sure i keep it short place any two pieces of evidence
two pieces of evidence excel multi-scanner if a piece of evidence is found on our database
you'll hear this noise if we cannot recognize a piece you'll hear this after two items are inserted
our exclusive clue match technology will scan for possible connections advanced data analysis
algorithms will compare the evidence against our 64kb database set up to one two calculations per
second you're not helping it's really not all that complicated i can also help organize your
compact disk collection if the crime tron can find the connection between the two pieces of
evidence then you get yourself a new location on your map yeah let's go item not found in database
really if stinky went somewhere to meet skunk eight she's probably got the number of a place on speed
dial that don't work so if stinky went somewhere to meet skunk okay she's probably got the number
of a place on speed dial so this is not it item not recognized come on i need another piece of
evidence i need the phone but the phone number is on there do we need two phones all right those
don't work so i need something else what do you mean wait wait what are you talking about this is
my gun if stinky went somewhere to meet skunking she's probably got the number of my gun so that's
not it general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could have at least left the forwarding
address or phone number i don't i really it's the note flint paper found from the mysterious
mister s to stinky that number and then the phone i don't want to use up stinky's minutes
what's in it sam you don't know how to turn it on god wanted us to use cell phones he wouldn't have
invented another piece of evidence that i need to find i can't use it it's stinky's newfangled
cellular telephone yeah that's it all right shoot the phone it's been months and they still haven't
i say we all wear gray ribbons to raise crack awareness put the stream on my other monitor
no i don't need to do that let me go back up here because i just ran the hell out of here right
after i right after i got done with you talking to you all right what's this water i didn't look at
anything down here i never drink when i'm on a case not even water okay i need something to
connect a cell phone to something else but i don't have that something else general skunk it could
be anywhere in the city he could have at least left the phone number can i go in the mole processing
center hey brain can you open this door for us you want to go into the mole processing room but
it's a horrible place official business besides it's for mole people only perfect we're part mole
man odd you don't look molish by marriage there were rituals very well i will try
there we go welcome reflection of screen in my eyes really you can that's you can see that
congratulations prepare yourself for a fabulous off-world vacation courtesy of
general skunk up a i'm very excited why aren't there any doors i'm gonna feel a slight tingle
as we take your personal items for safe keeping slight tingle well okay now that means i got a
pretty good hd screen this screw the vacation i want to keep doing this error cannot remove
inventory where do you keep your personal items none of your damn business computer
very well beginning mole man processing sam why is the floor so slippery with the comfort of
guests waiting outside please refrain from screaming or crying out please don't you
smell something burning sam why haven't we ever seen any mole people come out of here enjoy the
rest of your experience and remember that your sacrifice is for the glory of general skunk up a
sacrifice are we going to die sam depends on whether we can think of a way out of this
death trap little buddy all right think away out of the incinerator to the drain um get my items
oh no all my stuff is locked inside that container max pull it pull the whatever you have stuffed
wherever it is now where i don't know where to get it wait teleport out with the teleportation
goggles wait i want to see i want to see the future where do i want to go ops bosco tech
i think i'm just gonna i'm gonna be banana i don't like i don't think i can do anything with the
banana can i turn and walk the other way no i'm just gonna teleport out let's go to you're just
saying banana okay let's go to bosco tech i need evidence no visitors oh that part i remember
that part the strangle part hey you guys can't do that to me looks to me like we just did at
least give me back my sidekick you'll get the rabbit like once jerome's done working him over
max's teleportation power is pretty cool i just wish there weren't so much inappropriate touching
involved i don't have any stuff put on the goggles so he's knocked out do it again do it again up
the fire escape uh i just want to see how i died all right bye i'm gonna drop the ac on his head
just wait pretty cool not useful though can't do anything with this what about the band attack
he the way mama bosco hung that banner right over the sidewalk there there's a glowing there's a
name blowing uh bird on this together like church and state look at what was that it's kind of tacky
the way my blowing bird hung that banner right over the sidewalk all right pigeon hand over the
shiny thing and nobody has to get hurt that's not the sun hey careful will you drop that thing
can i jump down that's just a ring okay do a plunging kill the falling r1
all right shiny thing it's an engagement ring engagement ring i've got a feeling skunky picked
it up while he was out looking for toys oh there's an engraving hard luck classy evidence is that
evidence hey space gorilla you're kind of blocking the door there mind if we scooch on by we're closed
top rope kill here what about this you do me the honor scram geez buddy you could have at least let
me down easy well let's teleport out of here that was fucking terrible all right where do i go
bosco tech stinky cell stinky cell wait no wait it's inside the where is it right now
oh no no back up unauthorized agent oh he's in here he's inside he i just did it no no no close
yeah you better you went to skunk ape spaceship without me if you want to be the one who gets
strangled from now on go right ahead all right we did it all right so i have the engagement ring
now should i just go see if i can put that into evidence give the ring to max i'm not ready to
commit it doesn't do anything i can't look like i'm having too much fun all right don't look like
you're having too much fun jeremy like uh so let's go to the uh scanner oh fuck i need a cell phone
skunk ape got this ring from somewhere but the engraving just says hard luck i need my my stuff
how do i get my stuff back i have to like bring okay just go in wait just go and get collected
the units just go collect them just go open up the uh the personal item bin i didn't use the ring on
max what are you talking yes i did use ring on max i'm not ready to commit i what are you guys
telling me about what the agent i'm not ready to commit i got i got one guide right oh well
now don't even put it on 30 minutes slow-mo again i'll do it that was the look of he won't do it
hey it's all my stuff okay i got my cell phone all right hold on a minute here that's why i don't do
face cam that the last four seconds is the reason why i never have it on i'm not ready to commit
he's not ready to commit stop pressuring him into marrying somebody okay let's try the cell
phone in the ring or they're ringing the note let's see if we can get one otherwise i'm gonna
have to go back to let's just leave this word you have to use it on max outside i'm not ready
to commit mama bosco would be really helpful right about now if we could just get into our lab
i just got luigi now let's do note no the note is nothing but the ring in the cell phone
skunk ape got this ring from somewhere but yeah that's not he got this ring from somewhere
all right where did you get the ring from sybil's belongings right that's what i would think
mama bosco would be really helpful right i know i know i know i just get into it i don't really
want to get all right yeah i don't really want to get into mama bosco's lab let's get out there
strangle again no visitors so let me teleport you somewhere else i'm surprised like that didn't
work last time so teleport where's he gonna we're gonna get like stuck diner i feel like being in the
symbols let's just see what happens if we go to the diner
either that or the no hey next time you go to stinky's bring me back one of those salted
banana nut logs would you shut up all right well let me look at this because they get you get
he gets knocked out by the what the pole they both get knocked out out here what knocks him out out
well that knocked him out cold well that knocked him out let's drop the pole unscrew the pole
can we just teleport to here i wonder what happens if okay dude well i just teleport and like
telephragging no we'd be telephragging ourselves turn your lights on the lights aren't on do i have
to drop like a bowling ball off this or something i need that i almost think i feel like i need a
new location no it's crap yeah and then i can walk around out here teleport him can i put all
right can i put the phone down i gotta come on no really come on i thought this was gonna be it
put the phone on the pole and then teleport to the phone shit that's i have to put this
somewhere can i put this like in where do i put the phone under him can i like slide it under
him like a ghost trap stinky's phone but do it but what if i but if i don't put the phone down
they're gonna teleport to me and hit me let's try are we all gonna fall down two in one blow
and without any significant injuries either
i think he crushed my trachea
all right now let's go in to the lab that's a germa voice yeah see that's what i somebody said the
same thing i thought it was like prison cell like go to stinky's cell like oh she's in prison
because she got a torn up seat for something but skunk must have dropped it when he came through
here a clue i didn't think about store i didn't think that now from half a receipt little buddy
this looks like a job for all right we got a receipt crime tron receipt in the ring
all right let me see one of skunk ape's minions left behind this torn receipt from it
what does it say on it paddle paddle ball what else is in here can i use this phone
hello operator oops sorry you know how those spirits are once they get talking
about the good old days when they were alive i guess we can't make outgoing calls let's go
talk to mama vasco i yeah mama vasco what's going on here mama vasco help
thanks for getting rid of those gorillas sam and max all right what does that dimensional
destabilizer do exactly it opens a temporary gateway between one dimension and the next
which can pull someone from the spirit world into the real world or from the real world to
an interdimensional prison i suppose so we need that do you think that's what skunk ape was trying
to keep people from finding i don't know my money's still on the big screen thing that's
just cool well it's worth a try i built a remote control so you can open the gateway
anywhere it'll only stay open a few minutes so you've got to make sure you do it right
anybody holding something tuned to the alternate dimension will get sucked right in
okay max is confused about how that dimensional destabilizer works you just have to find skunk
and open up the gateway if he's holding anything tuned to that dimension he'll get sucked in
sucked right in the remote control for it is right over there get the remote he needs to have
something that is tuned to the second dimension they came in and took over the place right after
i told him about my dimensional destabilizer well that was uncalled for yeah i mean sure she's
really boring about it but that's no excuse for violence i'm pretty sure he was trying to keep
anybody from using my inventions against him don't make me do it did skunk ape give you any
idea what he's got planned nope he just told his guards to make sure nobody found out about my
inventions let's get on the other side dr mama bosco i'm not gonna do it again don't worry i'm
just kidding that's what i want you to think okay so let me get the remote thank you i have the
remote is this the remote control for your destabilizer thing mama bosco that's the one
make sure you don't press it before you really need to because you only get one chance
i'll fix the light don't worry too bright um two xbox i feel like i'm at an xbox booth
at fucking like packs uh no that's fine no that's like i look like i'm looking i look sick
no it's too bright that's better okay that's better dude twitch purple no i'm not gonna
twitch purple i can't even do purple it's a color that like somehow doesn't really work that well
all right so i got the remote i now need to put this on him we need to get the thing we need to
do the receipt and the ring i'm rolling now why am i from boston because my two my two parents
decided that they were going to live there and then they had me as a child what else do you want
all right got this ring from somewhere but the engraving just says
hard luck nothing how is that nothing that's a receipt in a ring it's not the receipt for the
ring is it a cell phone bill if stinky went somewhere to meet skunk shit general skunk it
could be anywhere in the city he could have at least left a forwarding address or a phone number
damn it i thought that was gonna be it do you think we have what it takes to join the skunk ape army
i think you could use a good stomach workout sam lose weight the stinky way
urging does tighten up those abs i'll give you that
civil sent us a postcard she and the giant stone head of abraham lincoln are still on their
extended honeymoon and you said their marriage wouldn't last actually i said it was a violation
of the laws of nature and most major religions automatically see you max keep in touch
we where would i find so this is one of skunk ape's minions left behind this torn receipt for a
toy store this is the note this is the phone this is the ring this is the just turn it off what
happens when you don't want to use that until skunk ape is nearby you can't hear me is there
can i is there anywhere else i can go general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could
have at least left the forwarding address my mic is not muted i can see it right here
literally i'm not going to sniff the webcam either so like get that out of your vocabulary
what else am i missing i feel like it's something to do with the the liquidation machine
can i like shut down the liquidation machine let auto sniff the camera no autos in bed
put the cam on your head like a gopro how am i going to hold it there am i missing something
in here anything at all should i like turn this on so you're suggesting we trap skunk
ape in our own building well kind of you'd actually be turning your building into an
alternate dimension so it won't really exist anymore how do we get into our building got to
get okay we're gonna get into our building teleportation stick it to the grease on your
forehead just ban that person for life please i hope they finish the repair work on our building
soon i miss taking showers we could just give ourselves tongue baths like cats and flight
attendants do well they're okay i guess just be careful around the back of my neck that's
where i'm most probably healthy skin that means i'm healthy that means i'm very moist i have lots
of collagen i've got lots of elasticity i'm very moisturized i think gee little buddy here in 2109
our street looks pretty much no no no no no max no not the chrysler building that sounds fun i
can hardly wait what the fuck are you talking about biting my lip again thinking too hard
all right i'm very obviously missing something important what am i missing where have i not been
i haven't been down here in a while i haven't been down here in a while yeah let's just see
see general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could have at least left a forwarding
address or a phone number you could be anywhere in the city rosemary keeps wandering off and
leaving this thing behind we've already seen this anything at all any wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait there's nobody there anymore as much as i'd love to get over there i'm not quite willing to
swim through the muck come on can i go in the hole and then walk down this way no i can't cross
the the game uh cartridges i don't think that can come down here but i can't go this way
either you guys seen charlie he was supposed to be back by now don't know where charlie is can i
let me look at the future future oh that's unpleasant well now i just want to know how
we get over there how do i get in there too knowing us it's probably something clever but
overly complicated probably you're not gonna know how we get over there
me too that's all i'm gonna get that we eventually just come out wouldn't you like to know
next train wouldn't you like to know so i obviously have to all right there's only two holes
general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could have at least left a forwarding address
or a phone number let's go teleport to but he didn't want to go into that hole the hole in
mama's box goes he's like i'm not going in there that sounds raw i don't want to be down there
right he said something like that no fuck don't do that no no no what happened but i have yellow
lights on right now i thought these were like green okay will you go in here now harry must
have dug his way in here they say they don't like to be in bright sunlight but i say it's just an
excuse to do more property damage a brilliant down there harry must have i'm gonna throw the
phone in there i don't want to toss this thing around i might break it general skunk it could
be anywhere in the city he could have at least left a forwarding address or a phone number
it's gotta be something with this thing it's too complicated i thought that was it i thought i
could throw it down there and teleport to it it's mama boss goes dimensional destabilizer thing
okay i can't collect the ectoplasm
nothing out here nothing i don't get an alleyway or something
i did i look everywhere it's not these two it's stinking went somewhere to meet skunk ate
give the phone to somebody should i give the phone to mama boss go i have no idea what it
wants me to do i'm missing apparently i'm missing evidence of some sort this is obviously the ring
that he's gonna hold on to this general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could have
at least left a forwarding address or if he's just sitting in the diner i'm gonna be so angry
he's just ordering food at the diner and i've been looking around for the clues and
shit trying to find him he's gonna be eating food at the diner i really thought that was gonna be
the thing not even the freelance police can put me in a bad mood today wait wait wait what's that
oh you think it is pretty cool isn't it but don't touch and no animals on the counter i need that
that's the homing that's the homing beacon all right thank you isn't that broach a little
fancy pants for your daughter stinky take a broach you cretin it's a badge of honor general skunk
copy was so grateful for my donation that he made me his second in command
that badge looks dangerous grandpa stinky you'd better let us have it let you have it this badge
gives me command over general skunk copies entire fifth legion and outer dominions i'm not going to
give it to the likes of you where are his outer dominions exactly i don't know he told me to
command them from inside the diner i think it stretches from alpha centauri to the andromeda
galaxy and brooklyn of course oh no i'm gonna yawn no why am i yawning that's not because of the
game i promise i i i just want to be i was that's not because of can't we just borrow your badge
even if you want a couple of shiftless ape traitors my captain ordered me never to take it off
and to keep at least 50 feet away from him at all times so if i press the thing will he get sucked
up how's life as a multimillionaire grandpa stinky so you're starting to regret handing over that
ticket are you i almost feel bad taking it from you but consider it a life lesson you're gonna be a
lot more clever to outsmart an old salt like stinky what are you gonna do with all the money
oh i already gave it away you what gave it away general skunk copy haven't you heard him talk
about the big plans he has for the planet exactly default pointing and since he made me his second
in command i never have to worry about money again all right you just gave away hundreds of
millions of dollars to an alien gorilla you make it sound like i didn't get anything in return
i got this badge and command of an entire alien fleet that is pretty cool sam that was a joe
joe pose especially if he threw in the badge we've had a sudden change of heart we think
skunk ape is awesome where do we sign up to join the skunk ape army you two in the skunk copy army
don't make me laugh we're really good at not making people laugh why can't we be in the skunk
ape army for starters have you ever actually hit anything with a gun of yours fido now that's just
not nice and as for harvey here he'll be a fine soldier until we run into a you must be this tall
to invade this planet sign oh you made him angry
now making a whole lot of noise settle down max you just gave away hundreds of millions of dollars
to an alien gorilla you make it sound like i didn't get anything in return i caught this badge
i got the badge and the command is pretty cool sam well yeah especially if you threw in the
i already had that all right so we we love skunk you really want to join the skunk ape army grandpa
stinky max needs to pay for calling why don't you ladies run back to your knitting and scrap
and leave the army work to the real men and gorillas that does it settle down max
skunk is a total dilweed grandpa stinky we're placing him under arrest well we're getting
around to it eventually traitors i knew it just wait until the general hears about this
you know where he is well no and i'm not supposed to go near him but you two are in for a world of
once he gets my memo where is he uh we have to play the back and forth here stinky let us
in the skunk ape army as soon as we drop the weight height and competency requirements
i'll get back to you take it back he's going after him again okay he's settle down max general
skunk ape's got you brainwashed grandpa stinky yeah and he hung you out to dry to avoid further
shrinkage you gentle free loving hippie peacenik types just can't appreciate a real
leader who's not afraid to use his weapons he really doesn't know us at all does he this is
your last one grandpa stinky we're taking down the whole skunk ape army don't forget who you're
talking to traitors as long as i wear this badge my loyalty is with the general flying thing hold on
okay this is your last warning for real we're taking down the whole skunk ape army don't forget
who you're talking to traitors as long as i wear this badge my loyalty is with the general
i don't think i can okay this is come on grip take it back here we go can i teleport no i can't
you know he's like touching me settle down max can't we just borrow your badge all hail skunk
ape beast through destruction i don't want to use that until skunk ape is nearby what are you
telling me use the thing what do you mean but i basically i can back out while they're talking
i thought it like that that's like this is part of a dialogue sequence why wouldn't why can't
i just use it here come on i should take it back i'd better get out of here before things get
violent yeah but i thought this was like part of the i thought this is this is all like enclosed
in a dialogue sequence i don't know that i thought backing out would just pull them out too
i thought that was just part of like this is you're in the dialogue sequence now backing out means
just walking away like but with everybody all right now let's um we should bring them
bring him to the tech room bring him to stinky put him in my pocket what happens if i do this
i mean you probably probably wouldn't just get them in the the cell phone has to be in the
let's see what happens let's go boss because i feel like do i have to put him in the machine maybe
jerks all right well we gotta we gotta go i think i have to bring him into the incinerator
and then be like give us the badge or you're not getting out that's probably that's what i'm
gonna try to do teleportation he's just mildly inconvenienced but we have to we have to go in
there first hold on wait wait wait i gotta do this in the right order right i need to go put the
cell phone in the thing teleportation so we have to go back to just because the phone has to be in
the thing i feel like that's not gonna work though i don't think that's gonna work but i mean whatever
i'm just gonna try it you can try it let's go put the phone in the thing bring him in there and see
what happens can you open this door again please welcome back we'll feel a slight tingle as we take
your personal items for safe keeping please do make a joke about the comforter get out and in
because the last time i tried to do this
the gorilla ran out i wonder if that happens here too
all right grab me let's make this quick come on grandpa stinky let us take it here we go
i'd better get out let's see if it works three two one action your hands off me
what have you done welcome back thank you for bringing friends along to celebrate the
benevolence of general skunk up a that's what i have you'll feel a slight tingle as we take
your personal items for safe keeping no one's taking my personal gold and griddles for the
comfort of guests waiting outside please refrain from screaming or crying out abort with a lover
skunk copy abort voice print verified skunk copy army sous chef eighth class processing
aborted sous chef eighth class after all i've done for that ungrateful monkey he can keep his
bloody hand full of my thoughts and he's not gonna remember that it's in there don't go in that case
i now have all the things i need we can end this take it all looks like grandpa stinky stuff got
mixed in with all of mine what does he got in his pocket his victory badge from skunk ape and
jackpot a collectible shot glass from misda pizza cool wait i actually need to use this
shot glass and i wonder what well now that i have this stuff let's go back what do i need
the shot glass for teleporting can i hold on this is important i've got the items i just need
let me see hold on wait wait wait let's see if let's see if i can do it where the shot i'd better
keep this it could be an important clue in our case no damn it where's it like liquid is there
liquid i can grab or scrape or drink or eat i got the thing not giving this away to just anybody
i don't want to use that until skunk ape i have so many of these items but none of them are together
shot glass receipt ring note liquid proposed to max i've tried it like 10 times it doesn't do
anything general skunk it could be anywhere in the city he could have at least left a forwarding
address or a phone number must have been in a misda pizza but how can we know which one
is this a pizza receipt no that's not a difference shot glass and skunk it must have been in a
misda pizza but how can we know which one shot glass pizza phone number from the pizza place
there's a pizza there's a pizza place i think he went somewhere to meet skunk
ape you just found a new location so all right let's go misda skunk ape was here
20 no 28 minutes ago he should really get more fiber in his diet there's gotta be some clue
telling us where he went next keep your beauty little eyes open pal so where at
misda pizza put on put the 3d glasses on let's see what this looks like okay here we are good
work max now let's see if we can aha a clue get on the roof step one step two leave the restaurant
were we supposed to be looking for clues or something step three good work max now let's
see if we can aha a clue get on the roof and swallowed whole i've never seen anything like
that before bird the bird eats something bird eats pizza out of the box so i'm gonna get a
throw pizza off the roof let's go in oh come on you can't get taste like that from real cheese
were we supposed to be looking for clues or something you wanted something disgusting that
i've been doing lately it's not even disgusting it's all right i don't do this every day but i
take uh you know that easy cheese from the can so what you do is you get the just standard regular
just orange easy cheese don't get the other the other ones get a bag of pretzels just the little
ones the little um like twisty pretzel things for like a little the hard ones you get at the grocery
store and then trace with the easy cheese the pretzel so it's coated eat it it's really really
good it's very good looks like this little fella's head is filled with mista pizzas rotting remnants
for one day can i poke his belly with a pencil and make him explode in a horrific shower of dough
and anchovies maybe later all right let me see the pizza box what a senseless waste of perfectly
soiled pizza boxes the boxes are the tastiest part we talked about this before with pretzels
it's okay same scenario just listen to me people are going to think i'm crazy and
people think i'm gross but just listen make tuna fish with like a tuna salad almost like mayonnaise
with the tuna take pretzels and dunk them into the tuna fish and eat them just do it one day
you're gonna wake up and be like you know what fuck this guy he's an idiot i'm gonna just do it
so i can be mad at him in the next screen do it i want you to do it and then tell me how it was
it's locked broken and doesn't go anywhere we want to go just like our socialite it's not i know you
might think it's crazy but it's not crazy there's something with the combination of the enzymes
in the tuna and the pretzel dough that makes it why i'm even telling you this let's just make a
fucking flavor out of it all right mr pizza for the unforgettable taste of old nipples
isn't that supposed to be old naples they had to change it on account of truth and advertising laws
all right so uh what about in the can't go in there i'm gonna go around the other side of the
building and get on the roof is there is there a fire escape room spend time with pigeon looks like
this little fella's head is filled with mista pizzas rotting remnants for one day can i poke
his belly with a pencil and make him explode in a horrific shower of dough and anchovies maybe later
all right what about nothing else i can do with these boxes have been picked clean
the pigeons carry the wood-like crusts away to build nests and primitive temples to their pigeon god
also no you know what you know i'm not i'm not gonna give you my culinary secrets anymore
why would i tell you that when you take a hard pretzel and you put it in your mouth and you like
suck on it for a second and then you smell it it's like one of the greatest smells you'll ever
smell in your whole life why would i tell you that because that's a that's a fucking culinary secret
looks like this little fella's head is filled with mista pizzas rotting remnants for one day
just do it just do it you're gonna do it one day you're gonna do it one day and you're gonna
knock me you're not gonna i don't care you don't have to say anything you don't have to come to
the stream and be like you were right and that was fucking really ridiculous one day you're just
gonna be sitting on the fucking couch you're gonna be eating a pretzel you're gonna go fuck that
boomer and you're gonna go oh fuck i don't even need to know i don't need to be there i'm fine
with that i just need to i just as long as i know that somebody's gonna do that i'll be happy i do
this can i put this in here hot and delicious dripping with rollover minutes and then the bird
picks it that's like this is also specific are you calling somebody swallow the hole
i've never seen anything the bird's not gonna eat all right not since we accidentally wandered
into that theater on time square that's that's reaching that is like reaching you believe in
time travel but you don't believe in a pigeon eating a phone no i don't i don't believe in that
at all if the pigeon was like fucking two three feet tall maybe good work max now let's see if
we can aha a clue oh that's one way to eat up data a vintage i didn't say that somebody who
collects old rare toys what's the address i don't know max the name and most of the address are
smudged out this looks like a job for the crime tron and pick up that phone max i'm not touching
it i got the toy receipt i've got the toy address look at that it's a vintage postcard from a
collector of rare toys but the address has been smudged out and i've got a receipt let's go
receipt and this this postcard is from somebody who collects and complete new location unlocked
pawn shop and live on tuna and egg salad those things are both very very good intergalactic
warlord business must be in a real slump if skunk ape is having to hit the pawn shops
he's tracking down magic toys max and he must have found something inside if he left gruesome
there to guard the door intrigue everybody also says that mayo is gross too what it's
i could go off on a long one here mayo is just fat as humans we desire the taste of a few different
things salt fat and sweet that's what you when you bite into like a hamburger or when you bite
into a piece of pizza you want that salt or that fat or sweet you have like three desires in your
entire life so mayo is just one third of all of your food desires in a jar but the but somehow
it's disgusting somehow what how does it make any sense you don't have to like eat it in a jar
what are we doing here oh yeah the collector of small goods and whatever it is punch up
would you like to know what magical surprises are in your future my friend here is a trained
psychic thanks for the biology refresher can i just like stick this in them let's take a look
with the goggles oldest trick in the book there's a lot of old tricks and lots of different books
skunk ape must have tossed it out when he realized it wasn't magical
we've got to find what store he got it from okay so he's got to get thrown into the sewer right
uh-huh a banana peel put him in the trash can all right get the banana peel from there
put it over here he slips down into the in the little i could have totally carried that heavy
thing a lot farther they just didn't feel like it i got it it's already done bingo i
guys trust me this looks entirely to say you and scoop it out i'm not whatever
you can spell it that's no you it's fine it's okay you're gonna do it at some point and and
i could have totally carried that heavy thing a lot farther i just didn't feel like it
i just tried it with a pretzel cracker it just smelled no no no you gotta do it with a hard
pretzel not a cracker huh a banana peel you know how good it's still i can't talk about
food i'll end the screen down with skunk ape aliens go home hey you guys really shouldn't be
surprised oldest trick in the book your ears would be ringing yeah don't litter
littering is actually bad don't do it this goes deep into the fiery bowels of america's filthiest
city you've been listening to my inner bathroom narration again all right so we can go in now
nothing else over here let's uh look at the pawn shop i think one of us should try to smash
through that window with his rock-hard melon-sized head and i think one of us should try the door
unless he wants to spend the rest of the day picking plate glass out of his partner's fluffy
white nether regions they've had an aioli before that's mayonnaise somebody just somebody's eating
like an aioli on their sandwich and they just spit it out because they couldn't believe it
paddle ball toy skunk ape must have tossed it out when he realized it wasn't magical
we've got to find what store he got it from now and now the receipt receipt and the paddle ball
what's my opinion on chili powder and lime juice chili and lime go together really well i'm sure
this receipts only got part of an address but not the name of the
success a new destination has been revealed on how much more is in this
these episodes feel longer are they longer yes they are how are we ever gonna find way longer
sam all these streets look the same shut up max huh they're completely different streets
it's mall men generals can copy is sweating mall man well you can delete 30 minutes warning harry
i put it pretty yellow that's how he controls you it's mall men generals can copy is sweating
all clues lead here but no sign of skunky where is skunky aha new york's lackadaisical business
win again what skunk ape will be back any second little buddy we'd better be ready
for him taco bell what are we gonna do once he shows up wendy's i don't know yet mcdonald's
talk about wendy's mcdonald's and then derek derek queen baskin robbins burger king
no shake shack shake shack taco bell shake shack five guys mcdonald's burger king baskin robbins
dairy queen when wendy's is up here do a tier list tier list is a website where i can
really oh that's right there there is like that tier list website all right it's locked skunk
ape's either waiting for this place to open or coming back with his never going to finish this
game how late to the bandwagon am i on doing tier lists on the stream am i like six months late
that's so funny always do things way after anybody cares about them anymore that's my motto right
it's the paddle thing in the future all these toys are still here unbought and unloved that's
kind of sad it's their own fault for not being more fun it's not a welfare state sam everybody
mute if you don't want to hear a spoiler mute mute right now if you don't want to hear a spoiler
don't mute i'll tell you no no no stay stay unmuted when i go like this that means it's okay
okay so i'm gonna give a huge spoiler if you don't want to hear a spoiler then no that's movies to
do i'll put it in another chat no that's not i don't want to do that so you have found me at
last freelance police that will make everything so much easier and you have brought the elusive toy
right to me yes yes i was actually gonna say like a bunch of spoilers
so you have found me at last freelance police
that will make everything so much easier and you have brought the elusive that was just happening
right to me yes yes that was just oh no they did the double bot
engines to full power yes destroy the city oh come back come back you're fine look familiar
i certainly hope that you are paying attention my friends because our story seems to have hurtled
to its inevitable conclusion no longer can you blindly mash buttons to unleash a torrent of
irreverent banter and comic mischief now you are all that stands in the way of the total annihilation
of the planet earth the villain has made his move the players are yours to command only you can
return general scone cafe to the penal zone take that die earthlings die i better keep this
throw it over to symbol that won't do any good stinky's right here with us we can't leave the
spaceship now there's still so much egg thwarting to do we can't leave the spaceship now there we
can't leave we can't leave that won't do any good full power to write mandible yes that won't work
drink the water drink when i'm on a kid sam and max hey don't tell me skunk copy wants you guys to
be his love slaves too you'd be surprised just how many fetishes there are that involves sam and me
what are you doing locked in here stinky i've got no idea i assumed it was grandpa stinky's fault
did you lose yourself
hang on a second i am your love monkey yes highest can copy i see you that's very clever
he's been texting me non-stop i tried to throw the phone away just to get away from it
can you call for help on your fancy futuristic phone i already tried that when you guys were
knocked out there's no signal off this spaceship no signal but throw that phone
throw that phone out there so we can teleport out of the cell yeah isn't skunk ape your boyfriend
you he wishes he is so not my type you only have to date an evil gorilla once to learn never to make
that mistake again just slide it up there and we'll teleport out what are we doing here how is this
grandpa stinky's fault he's been going on and on about skunk copy ever since he landed
that's the kind of gentleman you should get involved with he's got a future
how about skunk ape's the jerk stay away from skunk ape the guy's a total butthorn
you're telling me i was just going to meet my to meet a friend at the top of the empire state
building then all of a sudden this giant gorilla shows up and carries me off to be his queen or
something gee you think a hyper intelligent alien could have come up with something more original
i'm not buying this super advanced technology business if they haven't even mastered the
technique of margaritas and unexpected car trouble you know i don't think i've ever had
a margarita before in my whole life i think you're being too hard on skunk ape he's just
misunderstood oh yeah uh did i misunderstand this picture he sent me good heavens i think i should
put on some clothes now well skunk ape's got a lot of good points too name one he's got a couple of
good qualities he's got he's got his own spaceship i noticed that may impress you boys but the keys
to your cage so he could let you out but then she wouldn't be able to talk to us anymore
you general skunk ape we're all set max now we just got to get out of this cage so we can wrap this
case up reading take that die earthlings die game let's go plan well done freelance police now you
must place the homing beacon on skunk ape's back to trap him in the peel zone we're on it now light
up those toys the hell looking for these oh he looked through his 3d glasses and saw the
future has proven to be most enlightening here use it to witness how i'm going to destroy you
so what was that plan b again i believe you planned to turn on the dimensional destabilizer yes
luckily i have my own but i've still got the homing beacon exactly
can you believe that guy skunk ape knew what we were going to do the whole time he just wanted
to rub our noses in the penal zone from software end game level what do we do you're not supposed
to max it's a horrible plane of non-existence forever trapped between reality and unreality
yeah that and also that beeping noise is really getting on my nerves turn around max skunk ape
strapped an antimatter bomb on your back while we were out cold get rid of it what does it say
jeez what a jerk we've got to get out of here max pronto
we if i know my high tech futuristic explosive devices this is an anti-matter bomb that will
destroy the entire penal zone and anyone inside it and it's going to go off at any second really
sam any second well maybe i'm exaggerating hours but still best not to dawdle how did you land how
are you up there all right what do i do i have whatever items i got the paddle i've got the
homing beacon i got the shock glass you know unless you might as well what else is even over
here anything let's put the homing beacon onto the the explosive no let's not put the homing
beacon on the explosive all right that's not the right thing to do shock last i'd better keep this
it could be an important clue in our case how about um can i tell can i do i still have a
teleporter oh shit he didn't take wait wait hold on wait what about the future button
i thought he wouldn't wait i guess he didn't take it i just come back gotcha
welcome back sirs uh what just happened i detected a spike in antimatter radiation
so i locked onto the signal from your homing beacon and reversed the polarity of the dimensional
stabilization field to intercept yeah yeah just tell us how we can get back at skunk ape for crimes
against the freelance police and humanity i say let's cover him in candy bar wrappers and feed
him to starving raccoons you failed to trap him in the penal zone i wouldn't say failed exactly uh
maybe underperformed and we blew up the penal zone with an anti-matter bomb oh dear how can i help
sam and max doctor mama bosko has been granted the fullest security clearance possible for a
dead citizen mr president okay can't we just use that destabilizer thing to open up another
gateway not now that the penal zone has been destroyed how are we going to stop skunk now
with the penal zone destroyed we have no way to return him to prison unless you could make
another penal zone somewhere else i smell a convoluted plan coming on with a side order
of hand-waving technical nonsense extra crispy before i made the destabilizer i was working on
a dimensional rift generator it doesn't open a gateway to another dimension it actually
creates another dimension only problem is you'll have to find a nexus of ley lines somewhere for
it to work a place where the border between reality and nonsense has broken down there is
there happens to be one of those in the city man it's a 1313 straight street i was gonna say
address sounds familiar that's our building what if i put my minecraft bed okay how does this
rift generator work you just plug it in and press the pedal after that it works just like the
destabilizer if skunkope is wearing that homing beacon he'll get pulled into the new dimension
the trick is finding enough power do you have any more of those power cores lying around no i
never did get that back but even so it would have taken a hundred of those things to give enough
power to a dimensional rift generator it's over there with the other inventions that are a deadly
radiation hazard so you're suggesting we trap skunk ape in our own building well kind of you'd
actually be turning your building into an alternate dimension so it won't really exist anymore i'm
afraid it's the only way sirs and the plus side if it doesn't exist think of how much money we'll
save on rent we don't pay rent max can't we just use that destabilizer thing to open up another
gateway not now that the penal zone has been destroyed you'll have to use mama bosko's rift
generator to create a new penal zone see on the other side dr mama bosko we're doing a whole lot
of this today like put your fucking hands you know what's because there's a lot of breaks in
between using your hands in the game so i just i like moving around like a fucking magician
because i only need one hand to play this right we'll be careful with your rift generator mama
bosko just make sure you don't turn it on until you've got that homing beacon on general skunk
ape the fuck happened here it's like this is like i don't want no i don't want i don't want to
i don't want you to see what's under here guys my mother's that person that puts our name and
address as a fucking tag on everything that we own i can't help it on all of my nintendo games
on all of my fucking uh electronics i i don't just look what happened it's mama bosko's
dimensional destabilizer thing all right so i gotta do i got this thing gotta plug it in
turn it on bye guys i'll see you when i fix the fucking universe
we eat the rubber we're sorry we're not driving anywhere with that space gorilla on the loose
i just want to scan some data just teleport there if you're in such a day hurry to get yourself
killed all right well so i need to plug this into a power source and we got to go to the
interdimensional rift that's right outside the just go to sybil's and there's the
the rift there i just plug it into there what do we do now sam i don't know the powers out in
the whole building i know where to go do i'm doing
fighting
i actually have to dodge this stuff get him to blow so get him to explode something blow this up
got to get this homing beacon onto general skunky before we get accidentally incarcerated
out too and take this out too take this out bingo get in gee simple stuff is okay you live on our
street there's a good chance you're gonna get blown up she should understand that by now sam
whoa all right now the eyes there's gonna be a power source down here that he's gonna be able
to shoot through the crack down to the power source plug it in we go over here i can teleport
to the phone now just in case everybody was curious about what to do next all right then
ah i was hoping we teleport under an immovable pile of rubble and debris trapped for weeks we'd
be forced to resort to cannibalism just to survive you keep coming up with creepy disaster scenarios
that always end up with you eating me max it's getting annoying if you don't like it then stop
looking so damn tasty can you link me to the watcher you're reading yeah it's uh pc gaming
strategy it's a good thing civil packed all our junk into these boxes for safe keeping upstairs
can i go let's go in a mysterious town we're trying to save the planet here damn intruders
they've come to defile the toy box kill them no it's kind of cool brother look it is the dog and
rabbit justice prophesied on tablet 8 verse 32 uh excuse me i'm pretty sure you mean tablet 6
verse 24 heretic looks like another in a long line of wacky cults max we're in so many prophecies
we should start charging royalties you try and entertain the other wingnuts while i find a way
to power this thing up so the moles are an ancient group of old beings
who that's the most evil looking toy chest i've ever seen no doubt it'd unleash all kinds of
horrors if we ever opened it harry is it'll scrounge up some blasting caps no you mustn't
open it that would give general skunk up a unimaginable power to destroy us all
they're right pal we better get rid of skunk ape first all right well plug it in cable the workers
left some of the cable exposed when they were busy not fixing the power right in here right
yeah let's go plug the power cable into the boiler there's no place on the toy box to plug this in
i can't plug a rift generator into that why is it that's just like a jokey outlet over here
does it go in the outlet well it's plugged in but there's not enough power to turn it on
okay boiler controls
well at least the boiler still works uh all right so should i melt them what's with the creepy toy
box it is everything and nothing the power infinite oh well that makes sense we have guarded
and worshiped it from behind the shadowy veil of faith for generations we love the box so much
we've prepared a song about it that song is always the song the toy box cause it's really great
hey man the musical numbers have really gone downhill since we've been on break
some of us had grown to believe it was just an allegory i'm looking at you gemadaya but the veil
has been lifted there it is before us just as the tablets foretold what's inside that toy box
anyway no one knows no one has seen it for thousands of years there are those who believe
it contains toys oh right like the creator of all things it's really some fanciful box in the sky
filled with magical toys you'll have to excuse obadiah he's a fundamentalist
before it sounded like you were expecting to see max and me yes you're coming with foretold in the
sacred tablets and scrolls and yay the devil bunny knowing not his true purpose would unlock the
mysteries of the toy box hey sam it likes me you know what that means obadiah it's time for the
apocalypse what's that toy box got to do with max he must be blessed with the gift it will bestow
great power to the one who can use its contents oh and don't forget about the apocalypse you guys
seem awfully chipper about the end times it's just nice to be proven right for once yeah
suck on that barry digery who's wearing a stupid looking robe now on that pretzel chat
it's nice to be proven right who are you guys we are the boxists the last keepers of the true way
well our brothers have succumbed to the siren song of secular america with its basalt rich
tunnels and specialty coffees only we remain to act as guardians of the box
is there anything in your scriptures about how we can defeat skunk ape just that the box will show
you the way and then the devil bunny and his chubby sidekick hey broke down the wall and slew the
betrayer of mole men there's a there's a you guys stay crazy there's like an anti-matter
explosive right should we like take down the wall of some sort um let's see what this does
give up skunk ape you're under arrest so that you you're he's he's arrested under here oh it's
worth a shot hey max want to come here and ground me ground me yes okay we live in cool dark places
can i get them to be teleported into the the incineration room thing do i just have to keep
doing that until they get annoyed and leave let's see what happens if i do it like three or four
he's wrong with you oops sorry i better keep this it could be an important clue in our case
catch that and like the the sweat or something i better keep this well at least the boiler still
works um what about the plug can i put the plug down this is going to short out everything i can't
just put it on the ground i can't really move around try to plug this power into that power
i would try to just lay it on the ground well it's worth a shot hey max want to come here and
ground me you're pushing 40 in dog years you're not a very good detective and it looks like you've
put on weight thanks that should do it go that does not look like you should be able to turn on
that rift transmogrifier or whatever there's got to be something in this city with the unholy
power we need to power up this invention what's the point of having to be like
oh what's it for what is wrong with you oops sorry first i need to get this homing beacon
onto skunk ape or else i'll get sucked in again that twice in one day would just be humiliating
so let's teleport back to the ship get it on him he doesn't have the goggles anymore so how would
he know did you see that my queen not only did i defeat sam and max but i took care of the penal
zone in one stroke unfortunate word choice sam and max you survived have you returned with a
how do i put this tactfully better thought out plan to stop school cafe our last plan would have
worked fine if he hadn't changed the future yeah put this tactfully fight me you'll need to get
your personal belongings let me see if i can oh that hurts does everyone else taste butterscotch
thanks brain now we just need a way to get this homing beacon on skunk apes back without his
noticing i can't remember the name of my elementary school are you okay brain you're looking a little
green even for you the stress of powering the higher functions of this ship is proving most
detergent plus i think this broth is starting to go bad broth doesn't go bad how are we supposed
to stop skunk ape now i don't know something about a homing beacon wasn't it time and
oregano and stuff together brain okay bye now grandma
there's got to be something in this city with the unholy power we need to power up this
can you do that again please do that again that like oh full power to write mandible yes i want
to hit that again because that was the same exact noise as colossus from the x-men arcade cabinet
when you do colossus's super he does that he goes like it sounds insane things die you know you
just hear something you just takes that in your brain forever die earth things die no no no no no
where's the silly putty i need the the transform into any object putty
oh
you'll live to regret betraying us queen stinky soon you'll be serving time instead of serving
bad food in the penal zone you're no match for general stonkape sam and max when he's done the
world will never have to listen to your idiotic nonsense ever again nice performance stinky i
think skunk a believe it oh right performance there's got to be something in this city with
the unholy power we need to power up this invention what no no no put this away
don't you have planets to blow up or something thank you stinky hey brain can you give us a
hand here maybe cause a subtle yet stylish distraction i grow weak jamming tracks oh
fuck i'm gonna crash the game if i do that don't link my time in this wharf is drawing to a clone
but if i can prevent but one villain from massaging another appointment book my sacrifice
is but a small small bacon belt to pay right could you hurry it up max show some respect for this
noble creature sacrifice could you hurry it up please donut button sam and max donut button
till we meet again in the plaid
emergency engine failure emergency no no not in my moment of triumph sam and max must somehow be
responsible for this i must find them and destroy them going up all right out that's it little buddy
let's go take that step on the button suck them out let's win new rift there it is now
press on the button well played sam and max but once again i am too strong and you have only
seconds before wait it can't be the devil's toy box devil's toy box that's right jack
and it's ours yeah go find your own toys perfect you have led me right to the greatest prize of all
soon your bothersome dimensional rift will close and okay end of that episode then the next episode
they replay this scene and you see what happens so i can hold on click this link there it is how
did you find this why is there a twitter there's a twitter called colossus roar and was it just
he just roars at people no this move was so awesome but you could run out of it so quickly
when i was like when i was like 13 i remember mashing mashing the special button over and over
again even with default enemies and i i i spent like 20 dollars in one session i think at one
point i used all of my allowance money i saved up and i didn't even get to like the third boss
or something that's i'm that's burned in my brain from childhood just then you'd be completely out
of mana change your sub sound to that that would be so that'd be so annoying okay so next episode
we're back and i will take the toy box and the one who can control it yes think of something quick
sam i don't like the way he's undressing me with his eyes okay um skunk you're under arrest
ha ha ha under arrest by an earth dog and his pitiful inventions i have more strength in one
hand than in all the inventions of your planet's greatest scientists as soon as this case is over
i'm getting a gun with more gorilla stopping power it can't be that easy uh turn up the heat
turn up the heat it's gonna be too hot in here turn it off we live in cool dark places
can you take like one step to you to you i better keep this do it again it's hard to believe that
good old steamy has been sporadically keeping our building warm for almost a century it's even
harder to build there okay it's good how do i get him to move he's gonna slip on this right
just stop fighting so we can hurry this thing up already i got places to be
give up now when i'm so close to having all of the toys just take two steps nonsense
i'd better keep this pretty sloppy on you to miss this toy skunk ape it's the best one yet
nonsense it's worthless are you kidding me it's just dripping with psychic power right max
all right that one gives me the power to uh automatically calculate the proper tip at
restaurants nice one phone head it's a very practical power sam the kid i'll be showstoppers
give it to me now keep away from the big monkey no fair give it up save the cards
yes and so our hero saved the world once again our villain undone by his own greed it would seem
a fitting conclusion but this is not the end oh no but merely a beginning the overture if you will
of a five-part symphony of mayhem that will blow your ever-loving mind what is this mysterious toy
with its bizarre connection to max is general skunk ape truly defeated will sam ever find true
love will max be able to control his emerging powers but are his ominous visions of the future
a sign of tragedy to come i'll see you in the coming chapters to answer all of these questions
and more but for now i leave you with this chilling conclusion couch sucked right through
three floors in a septic tank there goes our security deposit i wonder if our building is
zoned to act as an interdimensional prison sam what are they looking at
holy heaping helpings of herodotus on base with marshal stacks and a wah-wah pedal is that us
imagine that's the only thing i've said this whole entire time
down there we go that's nice that's tuned down a little pretty cool what a jump in quality
yeah i mean the world graphics and uh lengthwise definitely i need to do my fast food tier
oh right um hold on give me a minute do tier lists that was fun that was um
a little different than the other ones they tighten the graphics up do a us states tier list
what like places that i've been season three following a more cohesive story than the last
two i've never known i've never played it i this is my first time ever playing these games after
credit scene let's see i waited i waited well there was episode one episode two will be on a
different day because if the episodes are i mean obviously like 40 minutes of that was
uh from the bullshit we did with chat and all the weird stuff we were doing earlier
if they're like three to four hours each or four hours four and a half hours something like that
then i probably do this on a different day because i know we're gonna be in there for like another
four to five plus hours he's ended this i'm not end of the stream voicing what are you talking
about what what why is stopping after episode one mean the stream turns off
what i'm gonna go pee i'm gonna grab a water i'm gonna come back and hang out and do tier lists
and something else i'm not leaving what are you talking about i'll be right back that didn't even
cover anything oh yes it did i'll be right back don't go nowhere unless you have to go somewhere
then hope you have a good time wherever you go