What is up guys, it's Germa here with another gameplay commentary.
This time we are playing as the Demo Knight, the Persian Persuader Demo Knight with the splendid screen and the Wii booties.
I know I said a long time ago I was gonna do a proper Demo Knight gameplay, and it just never happened.
So here it is, a proper Demo Knight gameplay. Using the Uber Update stuff like I said, this is on King of the Hill Nucleus.
Minicentury, get out of town. And now let us talk about a legitimate strategy when using the Demo Knight.
Did you see what I just did there? I was on fire, there were a lot of people around.
So I turned around like, oh my god, I'm gonna run away. And then I whipped around, charged, and smashed somebody in the face.
That is a legitimate great strategy to use if you're gonna play Demo Knight.
Make people think that you're vulnerable, like, oh I gotta get out of here, and then just whip around and charge them.
It freaks people out all the time. Nice kill on that scalp, by the way.
It's a great strategy to use, I hope you guys utilize that. You'll see me do it a couple times where I back off, like as if I need to run away.
And that gives people a false sense of security, and they go, oh, I can take my time with this guy, he must have some low health.
I'm gonna pull my secondary out, maybe I'll try and juke him a little bit, and they don't expect you just to come right back at them.
It's a great idea, please use it, you will get much more kills, especially stringing kills together.
I see a lot of Demo Knights just ram into somebody and then just get blown up five times in a row.
Like one for one, one for one. To get out of that one for one kills as a Demo Knight, you need to utilize some trickery.
You need to really mess with people because you don't have any other option. You have no other way to hurt anyone.
So if you're just gonna charge in and hit somebody and just start swinging like a freak show, you're gonna kill one person and then you're just gonna die.
Kind of, it's kind of weird for me to say this, but play the Demo Knight the way you would play a spy.
What I mean by that is utilize the same mindset that you play when you play spy.
The trickery, sneaking around, hiding, using things other than weapons to get kills.
So obviously you're gonna have to kill somebody with the sword, but getting to that point is what I'm talking about.
Getting to that point where you have to kill somebody is what I'm talking about.
And if you've noticed, I've stayed kind of in the same area for the most part of this gameplay.
Up near the right side of the blue team spawn, this kind of stairway over here, this is a great spot to hang out and be the Demo Spy.
It's awesome because they don't expect, when people come up here, people think they're gonna go around.
Maybe they'll encounter a scout. That's what goes through people's mindsets.
But people don't expect to see somebody at the top of these stairs because it's blocked out by a lot of things.
That right staircase, on our side as well, is blocked by the ceiling, the walls.
You can't really see anything when you come up there.
So I charged at this soldier who came up the stairs, didn't really think I was gonna be there.
I believe that was Chicken Fingers, and this is on Shibbi's server.
If you don't play on Shibbi's server, then you are missing out because it's a great time.
I completely missed that charge. I have the Wii booties on, but it's not enough of a turn radius to be able to turn and hit somebody, if you don't know.
The Wii booties give you the ability to turn while you're charging, which can help in some situations.
But for the most part, I put the Wii booties on for the extra health.
Now, it's also good, the Wii booties can be very, very good if you're going to use them with the regular Islander.
The Islander, if you don't know, makes your health go down by, I believe, I think it's 15 or 25.
I don't remember, but it's one of those two.
And when you put the Wii booties on, you completely negate that downside of the Islander.
So the Islander just turns into a 100% upgrade.
And I think I'm going to utilize that more often because I'm kind of sick of using this setup as the demo night.
Because ever since the Uber update came out, every single demo man is using this for the demo night.
And it's kind of sad because, I mean, the Persian Persuader is so good.
It is probably the best melee item in the game.
Of course, excluding things like the Gunslinger and the Spy Knife and stuff like that.
But for a side melee weapon for the other classes, this definitely takes the cake.
So let's get back into the gameplay now.
I get hit by something from behind, so I'm going to go up these stairs.
No, I'm not. Smash kill this guy.
I think that's Chicken Fingers again.
Sorry, Chicken, I got you.
Get the assist on that demo man and then smash myself right into a grenade.
But again, that's what you want to do as a demo man using the demo night setup.
You want to make people think that you're running away or make people think you're vulnerable and then smash them, baby.
So we have one second left and now there's overtime.
And we end up actually winning this. It is a great...
Look at this, just chaos on the point. I love chaos on the point.
It's a whole lot of fun.
Get a bunch of assists, get a bunch of kills in that little short period.
And now we are the winners of the game.
That is not the end, guys.
I know some of you might have thought that was the end, but it is not the end.
I have a couple of small bonus clips of me just destroying people as the Heavy,
using the killing gloves of boxing and the Buffalo Steak Sandwich,
getting the crit so you can crit, crit, crit over and over and over again.
And it was pretty funny. I played like this for an entire game for at least probably maybe 20 to 30 minutes.
This is all I was doing.
So I hope you enjoyed these bonus clips.
I'm not going to really commentate on them because it's pretty self-explanatory.
You'll get to see what I do.
You're actually seeing it right now, so I hope you're laughing.
Just absolutely crushing people, getting in front of a spawn room door and stuff like that.
Just one, two, three, four.
Let me just say this before this ends, before these little bonus clips are over.
Guys, this is actually a pretty legitimate setup.
If you can kill one person with these gloves, you will just go on a tirade.
As you can see, I'm not an expert at melee.
I just go on a complete and total catastrophe with these things.
And you can kill like four, maybe five people in a row.
You can kill like five people in one second.
Just by going one, two, three, four, and get a line of people.
It's like a chain stab.
But anyways, guys, I want to say thank you so much for watching.
You guys are awesome.
I hope you enjoyed this little goofy couple of gameplays of Demo Night and Heavy Freak Show.
So thank you all for watching.
Take care, everybody, and I hope to see you all next time.