Okay, sorry about that. I had to move around a bunch of stuff in my room.
All right, so what do you want to do for the next, like, couple hours or something?
Let's see, we got a dirty room. All right, let's, uh, let's get a pull-up. Why not?
Or maybe, uh, let's see, do roadblocks. Something relaxing? Yeah, we can, I mean,
we could go two days in a row doing something fucking wild and then just
fall on relaxation. I don't know if it's going to be Jump King. I don't think I can handle it.
I don't know if I can handle it. Nancy Drew? No, no, let me see what we got. Let me put up my
steam. I'm also kind of developing a migraine right now and I don't know if it's because
of this dream I had last night or I got a, first of all, actually, let's get on campus.
Let me just turn the webcam back on. This dream I had last night was fucking ridiculous. It was
insane. It's probably the most ridiculous dream I've ever had in my whole life. Uh, but let's
tell, I want to talk to you about it. And then maybe, um, I have Katana Zero. Is Katana Zero
like a super duper insane fast paced headache game? Yeah, it is. Okay. Watch me just open up
Jump King. Jump King is also a headache game. I'm definitely going to play that soon, but hold on.
Let me get this back on stream here. Oh, that's not in the right spot. This is my bomb guide.
So, uh, I had this dream last night and I'm going to do my best to explain this.
People are going to think that there's something wrong with me. There probably is.
So, you know, when you have a dream that just everything is so connected and just, it just
goes from bullet to bullet to bullet point to bullet point really fast. And it's as if you've
been sleeping for like fucking six hours, like you've been dreaming for six hours.
Oh, but it's actually in reality only been probably like 14 seconds. So I had this dream.
I actually wrote this dream down because it was so fucked up. I had to just rip off my iPad and
just start typing. So I'm sitting, I'm sitting on a beach, right? I'm on a beach and there is
a beautiful, beautiful beach and a huge mansion. I live in a huge mansion, apparently for some
reason. Right. And it's, it's like at least a 10 to $20 million house. This place is fucking huge.
And underneath there is this tunnel underneath the house. It's a big tunnel, huge, huge, huge.
You could be like a dozen cars can fit into more than that. So I'm sitting there and I don't know
why this big tunnel is under the house. It just is. So I'm swimming in this beach with this amazing
beach house. And all of a sudden I look up and a fucking an airplane, like a jet, a jet is just
screaming by and it's just like, that's getting kind of close. That's fucked up. Why is it getting
so close? This shit goes under my house way too close into the tunnel. It flies into the tunnel
and it's all, and I go, holy fuck, this is ridiculous. That I have, I have to do something.
I, this is ridiculous. It's going to my house. And I go under the water because I was like,
it's going to be so loud. And I plugged my fucking ears and I just hear,
and I'm under the fucking water going like, I opened my eyes and I could see dirt and debris
like coming into the fucking water and shit. And I'm like avoiding it. And I get out of the water
and I go, what the, what happened? And by the way, everything is normal. There's no,
there's no like wreckage or anything. It's, my house is perfectly fine. The house is completely
fine. So I walk, I've, I'm like running to the house and my sister and my fucking mother are in
the house and they're freaking out. They're going, what the hell was that? Yeah, that was a jet. I
don't know what that was. Like somebody did, was like a jet that just flew into the tunnel and it
like exploded. And I'm like, yeah, that's what the hell I got. We got to figure out what to do.
And I'm running by and there's, I have a big window right here, right? Huge window
out the window. I go, hold on. What's that? And I look out and there's like three,
it's my neighbor's yard and there's like two or three little dogs, little puppies, like little
tiny little dogs. And I'm going, oh, that's right. Those, that's the neighbor's dogs, the little dogs
and over perching on the fucking guy's wall is a tiger, a huge tiger. And I'm looking over going,
no, no, no, no, no, they're going to, they're going to kill, it's going to kill these geese.
He's going to kill those dogs. And my sister just goes, yeah, he's probably feeding right now.
And I'm just like, this is really bad. This is what we do. We have to do something. And we opened
up the sliding window and I screamed, right? I went like, and he freaked out and he ran away
for a second. And then my mother comes over, God bless her, right? My mother comes over and
like, it's like, okay, he got away. Let's close the window. And as she's moving the window with
her hands, it comes out of the frame and it's just, she's got it in her hands and she's like,
oh, the frame came out of the window. And the tiger comes back. The tiger comes back and he
like fucking looks right me in the eyes through the window, through the window. That's now open
because my mother, my mother took the whole frame off and I freaked the fuck out. I'm like,
mom, give me the fucking frame. Give me the fucking frame. We like sticking on the tigers,
fucking like walking towards the God, like getting really too close. And we get the fucking thing,
click it in and the tiger is still fucking there. We've just barely did it, right?
Right after that, I go, I gotta, I don't know what the fuck to do. I don't know what to do.
There's so much crazy shit going on. I gotta go get a weapon. So I fucking ran into what was
my huge like mansion living room and I grabbed a pair of shears. Okay. So I grab a pair of shears
and I flip them upside down to hold. So the rubber ends, I was going to like whack them
with the, with the other end. So I'm like, I'm going to go out there and like get out of here.
So, all right. I'm, I get that. I'll flip it around. I'm going outside. I hear somebody getting
mauled outside. Like, I'm like, someone's getting fucking mauled out there. So I,
I like go outside. I'm like, what the fuck happened? Somebody's getting
fucking mauled. So I'm out there and the tiger's not there anymore, but this guy is. And I don't
know if he was supposed to be my neighbor or I have no idea. He was just sitting there and he was
like blood everywhere. And he's just like, ah, you gotta take me to the hospital, man. And I'm like,
I don't know what to do. I'm like, stay right there. Just, just don't move. Don't move. Don't
move. And I fucking turned around and I'm like, I don't know what to do. And I ran back in the
house for a second. I was like, what do you call the police? And he goes, dude, are you fucking
serious, bro? I was like, I'm just trying to, I'm like, all right, let's, let's get you to the
fucking hospital. All right, let's get, I dropped my fucking thing. And I'm like, let's go, let's go
to the hospital to get in my car. And he goes, all right, sure. And he gets up and he's like normal
and he's like running and he goes, wait, wait, hold on a second. I can't go anywhere without my
cigarette. And he like went back to where he got mauled in the first place and like grabbed his
cigarettes. And then we ran out. And the last thing that I saw before I woke up was this fucking guy
putting a new cigarette in his mouth and we're running down the stairs and he's lighting it in
the house. And the thing that I, that out of all the crazy shit that happened, the thing that I
was most concerned about right now was you don't fucking, you're smoking in my house. You don't
smoke in my house. And then I woke up. Like you're smoking in my fucking house, dude. Like
kind of weird kind of like you think you can just do that. That was, it was insane.
And every single part of it was so intense. Everything I just described to you, each one of
those three different scenes was like living inside of a movie in three different occasions.
Oh, and I don't even know what that means. I don't know what that's supposed to mean,
but that was, that was, that was a wild one. It's been a while since I've had a dream like that.
Anyways, I just had to like vent that out because it was, that was seriously fucking ridiculous.
Anyways, we are going to do today, you know what, let's just, oh wait, what the fuck is this?
Jesus Christ. Oh, it's real. I mean, it is a real image, but not, it's doctored real.
And then of course there's
all right. What do I want to do? I'm like, I don't even know what I want to do. I want to like play
Jump King, but I'm not sure I have what it takes right now. I have what it takes last night. Go
back to the coin game. Uh, no AI Dungeon is not going to work. It takes, it's going to take too
long to set up. All right. I'll get a poll in here. I'll put a poll down. Why not play Neopets?
All right. Let's do, this is what I would do right now. Put that one on there. Put that one on there.
I need a third option too. How about, uh, no, no, Drew crew. Not today. What else can I put on this
list? Oh, this game looks like kind of cool. It's another cute game. All right. What do you want to
do? What do you want to do? It's a funny face stream. Oh yeah. That image just is still just
on there. You're right. Well, uh, I'm going to play Katana Katana Katana zero. Maybe just not
tonight. Katana zero is something that I'm going to do. Give us the king. Give us the game. I mean,
it looks, it looks like people, the majority want to see some Jump King. I can't just like turn my
brain off and let that just happen. It like just go as long as, like I said, I've developed a
fucking migraine. So it's gotta be something that's easy for my brain to understand.
All right. I'm going to close this. Jump King. Nice streamer bait game. Hey, I played Jump King
like two weeks ago, three weeks ago. I played it. We had, oh, I couldn't see any of the subs that
came in, if anything, but we did have a couple of big ones come in. A friend pal buddy gave 5,000
bits earlier. Thank you friend. Thanks for the 50 fucking dollars. They say bugleberry pottery was
definitely the worst joke of the year, but it was also the funniest shit. I also laughed my ass off
of you taking pottery lessons for it. Watched and loved the content for eight years. Keep doing you.
Here comes the jet from the dream. All right. Let's do some Jump King. I'm just, we'll just
chill for a little bit. I'm just going to open it, but thank you friend pal buddy. We also had 10
community subs from fluid mesic right now. Thank you fluid mesic. And I think that's it for now
because I couldn't see it. Put on some chill music. AI dungeon doesn't need setup.
Now I don't want to do that beta website one. It's not as interesting as the one from collab.
Jump King is the opposite of chill. Well, I'm not going to take it seriously.
I'm not going to take it seriously. We're just going to play it and relax. All right. Give me a
sec. I'll be back in one second while I set it up. Okay. Okay. That's not going to work. That's not
going to work. That's not going to work. That's not going to work. Jump King. I did save it right
before I got disconnected last night. I'm going to take it really, really just chill. You know,
I need my headphones. Yeah. Sorry for the large intermission here. I had my whole room set up
differently for, uh, keep talking and you're going to explode. What was the gift you? Oh,
that's right. Yeah. I can grab that after. Let's change this shit around. Stop talking.
How about just stop talking? That makes sense. Just we'll cut the book. Stop talking.
No talking for two hours. Okay. Uh, let's continue. There's a hot babe at the top.
It's too loud. Is it too loud? It shouldn't be. It should be fine. All right. What can I know?
Okay. Stop talking. I know, right? I'm not supposed to talk. What's up here?
Do the big jump. I don't even know what the big jump means. Stop talking. I'm, I have to talk.
That's a much, that's a bigger jump than it looks like. Shit. Don't go all the way down.
I got here last time and then I fucked it all up. Didn't I? I'm trying to sleep. All right. I'll
stop. Uh, my head on this. Wait. Ooh, shit. All right. Hold on. It's all right. It's all right.
Just go. Oops. Oh, fine. Fine. Fine. Ah, Dermis too hard on himself. What do you mean? Okay. What's
up here? Oh, I remember this part. This part sucks. This part actually sucks. Oops. Oh, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. I didn't see the lift here on the right. All right. How do I get up there?
Bounce off of it. Okay. Dermis so hard to do the, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. All right. All
right. Is this the second DLC? I believe, no, I believe this is the first DLC. Holy shit. Okay.
Oof. I was tight. Okay. What's up? Oh, I did get up here. I remember I got up here and I was like,
oh, this is going to be easy. Okay. And you can fall all the way down this right side too.
Okay. For now, it's okay though. Now we're just across. Did you disconnect your stream last night?
I actually have no, that was insane timing because I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything. It just happened. Shit. I was shorter than that one. Okay. Now what?
I don't know which way to go. Can I go? All right. I can go in here. All right. You didn't thank my
$300. Wait, that was 300 bucks. When was the 300 bucks? Oh shit. What? I was going to say,
what are you talking about? All right. How am I going to get up? I think I have to bounce off
of that and to there. Yep. What's up? Okay. Silver coin, silver coin, silver coin. Who cares?
No coins. I'm, I'm, I'm a non coin gamer. Okay. Again, or should I go, I'm going to go like this.
All right. Here we go. Okay. Now I gotta be careful. You're pretty good at this. I'm all
right. It's got, you gotta go right, left, right. You have to. It's all right. Fuck. Hmm. Oof. All
right. Oh, it's fuck. That's not good. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That jump sucks.
Oh, that's bad. That's really bad. Actually. That's the worst thing that could happen.
Shit. It's not a total catastrophe yet though. Hold on. Okay. Oh boy. We're good. I could go for
some pizza right now. Oh, could you? Oh, I'm not, I don't feel like a pizza right now. So you can't
grab me. Fuck. I think I lost it from last night. Yeah. Yeah. It looks, I don't know if it's gonna.
Yeah. Yeah. It's lost from last night. Yeah. I lost it. Fucking my headaches getting so much worse.
Why can't I just replace my brain with like a digital fucking computer at this point?
Like why? We want, everyone wants self-driving cars. No, I want a self-driving brain.
What? Digital computer. LOL. Yeah. I want a digital computer brain. It's on its way.
Shit. Okay. Come on. Give me back up to there. Too much. Way too fucking much. That's a tiny jump.
No. Forced updates. Yeah. I'd rather have, I'd rather have like a digitized brain.
That's better. Don't go too hard. All right. Slowly but surely climbing back up to where I was.
I don't know why. Just jump over though. Just jump over. Fuck.
Damn it. I'm telling you it's those 5G signals. I also have a doctor's appointment tomorrow too.
I'm bringing this shit up. No, no. Not the, not the digitized computer brain.
Hey doc. I've got something to tell you. You know, like when do, when are we going to have medical
procedures where I can replace my brain with a computer? That's not what I'm talking about.
All right. Back up. We go. Oh yeah. Okay. Hope it goes well. Me too. Me too. Easy does it.
Easy does it. Oh, I made it back. Well, not I haven't not yet. Okay. Good. Same deal. Get back up here.
Oh, come on man. Sorry to hear that you're being, you're being put down tomorrow.
If anything I can say about this stream, I'm so glad I got to tell you about that dream.
Seriously. I'm so glad you guys got to hear it. Too much. Oops. Okay. All right. I made it back.
A little too much, but it's all right. Oh, I almost didn't make it. Oh, way too fucking much.
Way too much. Shit. This is bad. What do I do about this? Oh, fuck. There we go. Oh man. What the
fuck was that? Get on there. Please. I'm begging you. It's so easy. No, no. I'll fall all the way
down. I don't want to fall all the way down. Holy fuck. All right. Now we go this way. I'm ready.
Here we go. That jump is fucking insane. But all right. If I go, if I go left instead, can I make,
can I make that with a full jump? I'm not sure I can. Can I? No, I have to get this one, right?
Man, that sucks. That's so hard. That jump sucks. Jump King sucks. Okay. So I've, I've overshot that
jump two times, right? So it's lighter than that, but fuck man. It's so hard to judge.
Maybe before this was a 12 hour stream. No, no way. Not a chance. All right. Here we go.
Got it. Boys and girls, we've made it to this next section. All right. Now what? What? Over,
wait, over there? Okay. Underburg. There's wind now. Oh God. There's wind. Shit.
Hmm. It's not that strong though. Is it? I wonder, can I, should I jump from all the way to the left
with the wind? I'm scared. Okay. I think I can just jump up and it'll take me, right? All right. Yeah.
I didn't know how strong it was. Oh my God. This sucks. This sucks. Oh man. Okay. Slow down.
I could jump up a little, but then guys, I have to, all the way to the left is not safe.
What the fuck was I thinking? Shit. Now I'm back here again. Damn it. It's okay. Oh,
no. God, it's so hard. No, it's so hard. And if you fall, you're fucked. It's the anxiety of
being so scared that you're going to miss it and go all the way down.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's go. Oh shit. Oh shit. Um, uh, I was on it. What the fuck just happened?
Slow down. I thought I missed it. Let me get up here and see what the hell this even is all about.
Let's get, okay. Um, yeah. Full jump to the left into the wind or full jump to the left with the
wind. I don't know if that's a good idea. Full left with the wind. I'm going to soar over this.
Hopefully this isn't up top maybe. Ah, shit. Okay. Don't, Jeremy. Oh my God. I hate this part.
It's freaking me the fuck out. Jump King and chill. Jump King and increase headache.
Why would you don't, why'd you tell me to do that? I was a full jump left. Can you see the wall?
What are you doing? What do you mean the wall? Yeah. I, I, I'm scared to do a full jump left.
I'm going to soar over the whole damn thing. All right. I'm going for it. Yeah. I know. I can see
the pole. I'm just talking about if I do a full left, I'm going to soar the fuck over the whole
thing. Fucking wind. I swear to God. All right. Here we go. Oh my fucking God guys. No, it didn't
work. Oh fuck. Oh, get back up there. You got to go softer than that. Very soft. Not very soft,
but shit. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. What's up here?
I'm scared to jump up there. Fold to the right with the wind. Full right with wind.
Oh, I don't have time to jump and check. Oh, I had to check. I had to check, man. I don't know
what's up there. I couldn't, I didn't even see what was up there either. God damn it. I'm going
for it. I'm just jumping up with the wind. Holy shit. Okay. I was supposed to do that. All right.
Now. Oh fuck. All right. Now. Um, okay. There's two ways to go. I could try right or just,
oh my God, damn it. Fucking Jesus Christ. I just, I didn't, uh, what just happened?
Glag. My controller unfucking plugged. Plug it back in. Plug it back in. Plug it back in. Plug
it back in. Plug it back in. What the fuck? Are you serious? I am so mad right now. You've got to be
fucking kidding me. What? I, it was plugged in the whole time. Ah, that's so stupid.
Fall right with the wind. I can't fucking believe that shit. Holy fuck, dude. Okay.
If you stand still, the wind doesn't, ow, my head. Oh yeah. Wait, I'm, oh, oh, I'm inside of a
building. I'm inside of the, I'm inside of a building. Okay. I'm inside of a building.
Don't you dare. What the fuck just happened? You fucking idiot. I got to jump in the air and let
it, ah, now I have to get across. Okay. Oh, I do. Oh my God. I think I have to jump straight in the
air. Okay. Oh shit. Oh God. No, no. Oh my God. It's so fucking stressful. I'll get it. I have to
jump a little higher. Now what? I can't see. Holy fuck me. Okay. And there? Holy shit.
Hello. This is my room. I'm getting tired just looking at you. Can you please leave? My fucking
God. Now what? Jump up straight in the air and carry to the left. The wind is getting inside,
but it's too much work to seal the entrance. No, I do know. Uh, where? Middle? Right into the middle?
But wouldn't that drop me down? I see over on the right, but how do I get into that room?
I don't want to go in the middle. That room on the right. I can't make that jump. Do I have to slide
off of the right side? Nope. Oh fuck. Oh my God. Where am I? What the fuck? Stop. Oh,
oh, this sucks. I don't understand. I'm in, I'm fucking, I'm screwed. And then it's full right
with the wind. Okay. I almost just missed it. So the middle, I, that's the middle right there.
You do know, you do have to go in the middle, huh? Shit. I have to go in the middle.
Fuck. What was I doing? Oh my God. I just like closed my eyes for a second. That just like hurt.
Oh my God. Try pick toe picks. No, I, uh, this sucks, but I'm going to have to turn my stream
off soon. Like the left side of my head through my eye. What a pain in the ass. What a pain in
the ass. I really don't want to, but fuck. And I have the doctor's appointment tomorrow.
Sorry. What was after this? Oh my fuck. Okay. Jump to what? Maybe jumping wasn't the smartest idea.
Uh, it don't matter. It was going to creep up on me anyways. Oops. Too much. You've been stressed
all stream. Well, no, not really. I'm all right. Just, it just hurts way too much again. Really?
That was like half the power. There it is. All right. Get me up here and I'm just going for it.
I'm going for it right now. I did it. I did it. I actually did it. Now what? Um, should I go down?
Oh shit. Hi. Hi. I need to do a little jump with a tiny jump with the wind because look at that
ceiling. Oh my God. Needed to be more than that. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. I'm going home. Oh no. This is
bad. Oh, this is really bad. This is game over. This is stream over. If I fall down even more,
this is stream over. Oh yeah. I haven't done this in a long time. Oh fuck. Oh well. It ain't over
yet. Not yet. It's still, I haven't fallen down too crazy yet. Too much. Oh bye bye. See you later.
I'll see you guys later. Nope. Not yet. I thought I was going all the way.
Munker Omega. I, I don't even know what that symbol is. How, how much power was that shit? What
fucking power are you doing? What the fuck? Fucking give me him. Easy with the power. Slow it down.
All right. All right. I'm good. End of the Jump King voice. Yeah. I don't know if I can handle it.
I knew that I was going to get crept up on. It happened a lot faster than I thought it was.
You know what? I'm just glad that we could play keep talking and nobody explodes
because that was the plan tonight and fuck me. All right. Oh, God damn it. That jump sucks.
That jump fucking sucks. That jump sucks, man. That's the worst jump.
Yeah. All right. We're getting, we're getting to critical eye headache.
It's critical. Yeah. It's critical right now. Oh yeah. It's over. It's over. We're at critical
headache. I think I'm going all the way down. All right. I'm going to try this one more time.
Oh my God. And I, I, I, do I have like a fever? What's going on? Am I like, fuck my body temperature
feels like it's like 5,000 degrees. Like what is going on? Oh, it's cause there's a bunch of
lights in here. That's why he's, he's dying. No, I'm not. I'm fine. All right. This is it. Last.
No, no, no. Last temp writer. If I fall down one screen streams over. Let's go. Let's do it. What
just happened? Okay. I think Mike, the controller fucking unplugged again. I fixed this shit already.
I fixed this controller like a month ago. That's a sign from God. Not yet. Pull right with the wind.
Here we go. I gotta go a little harder than that. Go get some rest. I will. Don't worry. So I,
and another thing too, this is why I was like, fuck, I don't want to stream for like two hours
today. Uh, there's no stream tomorrow because I have a doctor's appointment. That's going to
last a while. So I will not be streaming tomorrow, but I will continue the day after that.
And we'll probably, you know, we're probably gonna start Katana zero. We'll just do it.
That's like a five hour game, right? I just want to get up there and try one more time.
No, I just want to try again. I just want to save a checkpoint up here so I can,
oh, it's not fair or Kingsway Kingsway looks fun too. Oh my fucking God, Jeremy. What's Kingsway?
It's like a weird web browser, RPG pop-up window thing. It looks really, really interesting.
All right. Next attempt. Here we go. I gotta be a little bit harder.
Not too hard though with the wind. All right. Okay. Harder than that. I gotta wait. What's up
here? Oh my fuck. Oh my God. No, no, no, no. My God. Where am I? Where the fuck is my character?
No, you stop. All right. Last attempt and I actually have to leave. He's actually crying.
I just wanted to fucking be joking too much. Way too much. All right. Goodbye.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm saving everything. I'll pick it up another day.
All right. I gotta go. That's a fun game. It's fun. It's a fun game. I just, my fucking head is
on fire. So I hate fucking headaches more than anything. I would rather, I would rather shit my
pants on stream and sit in it than have a migraine on stream because one of them you wouldn't even,
you wouldn't even know happened. I would rather shit my pants and sit here in it. Like seriously,
I would then have a fucking migraine. But anyways, I'll see you guys again on Tuesday.
As of Tuesday, we'll probably go, we'll do at least two, three days in a row as of Tuesday,
because we did two days one day. We'll do two, three days in a row. Yeah, makes sense.
Either Katana Zero Kingsway or, or Heroes 2. Let's start that. Or a GameCube game. I don't know.
We'll see. Katana Zero. Yeah, we'll see. All right guys. I'm going to go through the bits.
It shouldn't take us too long. Thank you so much for watching. The earlier that was a lot of fun.
I got, I did some progress in Jump King 2. Keep Talking to Nobody Explodes was actually really
fun. That was, it was just all over the place. It's exactly what I thought was going to happen.
I guess we'll do that again and switch roles and see if we can do it. Am I going to do yesterday's
bits too? Oh wait, that's right. Fuck that, because I got cut off. I might not be able to
sit here for that long, unfortunately. Let me see. How many are, how many were there?
I'm sorry. I'm just going to be real. Let's see how many there were.
Because there's like a knife in my head right now. Let's see. From. Let's restore.
Yeah, I, I'm sorry guys. I can't sit here for this long. I wish I could. I really do.
He's currently getting a lobotomy. I will, I will do these when I come back though. And they're
going to be very irrelevant, but I don't want to just blow them off. Blame fucking shitty
internet yesterday. We'll do it. I promise. I just, I can't do it right now. I can get through
the ones from today because there's only about five or six of them. I do apologize though,
seriously, but I'll see you guys on Tuesday for those of you taking off. If you want to stick
around for the last bits of the stream here before I get out of here and like dunk my head in cold
water. I'll see you soon. Put this. Just do both next time. No, there's really only like six,
I think there's like six or seven here. Yeah, there's not very many. This won't take very long.
So earlier we had, we had a thousand bits from SSJ Mac. Thank you, Mac. Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey, German, thanks for making me laugh for like seven years. When are you going to bring back the
coffee commentary of justice and doom? Oh, I remember those. Probably never. That's just
every stream now. Thank you for the thousand bits though. Appreciate it. Sam of the freelance police,
thanks for the 500 bits. Hey German, happy 2020. You've been a constant companion for most of the
past decade. Hope this continues into this decade. I go to university abroad and your streams always
make me feel cozy and less alone. Please go back to the EU friendly schedule. I'm happy to be a
voice that you recognize and a voice that you are used to. That can either be in the background or
if you're completely attentive to everything going on in the stream.
Thank you so much for the support. And yes, I will be going back to one between one and
two PM Pacific starting in the next couple of weeks. I will make sure I let you know,
but I do want to get back on that. It was just a couple of things made it so I couldn't.
But yeah, thank you for the 500 bits. Nile Orion, thanks for the 300 bits. German is the Chris
Jericho of streaming. Wow. Effectator, thanks for the 250. German, you don't understand. I actually
obsessed over the bomb game last year. I learned Morse code just for the bomb diffusal and got to
the point where I could diffuse the first one before the lights came on. What? Oh my fucking God.
How do you do that before? How is that even possible? Don't the lights turn on when you
hold on? I'm confused. Oh, look at this. How don't the lights come on when you touch the
bomb? See what I'm saying? I thought when you touch it, the lights turn on. There's a brief
second of delay. Jesus. Yeah. So watching this stream, you must have been sitting there going,
I could do this shit in my sleep. Thank you though. We'll get better. We'll get better.
We'll get better. Morning Maple, thanks for the 300 bits. Mutilated man for next German rumble.
Make him have a floppy intestine dangling. I don't even know what I just read. I shoot. Was
that, was that a bad thing? I don't know what that I just read. Um, I don't know what that was.
But I don't know about that. Thanks for the 300 bits. Morning Maple.
Freudian weapon, thanks for 250. What the hell are you eating before bed that's giving you those
kind of dreams? Not anything ridiculous. Oh, from your dream. Oh, right, right, right.
I'm okay. I want to copy and paste all the text I've punched into the iPad because it is delirious.
I wrote it so quickly. I have to like pull that over here. I'll do that like in a couple of days.
I'll show you. But thank you Freudian for the 250. Also thank you to Cookieinva for the 500 bits. Hey
Jerma, my girlfriend recently ended our four-year relationship because she doesn't love me anymore.
I'm pretty down and you helped me so much. I met your YouTube channel in the old days
and though I can't sleep, I got to finally catch a stream live of yours. Sorry to hear that it's a
long time. Four years is a significant time and a relationship. But the one thing you can bring from
that that's positive, that really is positive is when you date somebody for that long and it
doesn't work out, just I guess be look on the bright side of if it lasted like another few years,
you know, then you're talking five, six, seven years. It's a lot longer and it's a lot more to
process. Four years is a long time but I am certain that you'll find somebody else
and it wasn't meant to be. That's all you can take from it is just know that it was not meant to be.
Eventually it will be to be. Much love to you though. Using somebody to teach math? What do you
mean that? What? Let's get the credits on here. Roll them. Short stream. We'll see you Tuesday.
Thanks everybody. Even if you subbed over the course of this almost just barely three hours
stream. It's a little one's compact money. Yeah it is. I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow.
Tomorrow the doctor's appointment actually is something I'm really looking forward to because
it is with a new doctor that we're gonna start to talk about what I'm gonna do
about my rib cage problem and my hernia. So I'm... this is an appointment I've been looking forward
to so I do not want to miss it. But thank you all of you. Hey Jamie, thanks for the 500 bits Jamie.
You could do a chill pottery stream sometime to show the pottery training you did for bugleberry
so it doesn't go to waste. Yeah it's uh it didn't take that much time. It took like three weeks to
get that stream set up. The whole thing. But the pottery it was it was like four or five hours.
Like four and a half hours total of classes. So it's not like I spent months or weeks preparing
for it. Do it anyways. You lied again. No I said it took away. When did I say I did three weeks of
pottery lessons? Oh wait maybe I did just maybe I was just fucking around. I mean I took pottery
lessons and it was like five hours of classes. Oh he's backtracking. Is that a lie? No I
didn't I say it took three weeks to get that already? Maybe I did lie. I don't think I did.
Hey grandpa pissed thanks for the 250. Just wonder what happened to the previous 984 germas?
Well the first like 200 were mixed up into a pot of uh fucking liquid and the 200th one
201st one drank them. Got all the power. Um I guess I don't know what else you want me to say.
Oh yeah that's right I'll show I'll show the cake Mario thing before I leave.
But thank you uh grandpa piss. Thank you Pablo for 500 bits. Happy 40 months nerd. That's a very
long time. I have to do new bit badges and sub badges. I gotta get on some of this shit for 2020.
I will I promise. I will get them done. Thank you for the 40 continuous months of supporting this
stream. Jesus. Gore grinder thanks for 300 bits. Uh I hope your appointment goes well tomorrow.
Thanks for a bomb ass stream. Thank you for being here. Thanks for watching. I do too. Hope it goes
well. The PC Int thanks for 300 bits. Hey germa I had a massive migraine two days in a row and lost
both days sleeping to try and get rid of it. Both days you cheered me up and made me feel so much
better being there streaming when I woke up and felt better. I appreciate that. I gave bits yesterday
but I don't know if you read them yet. I want you to say my name lol. It's Dejen. Dejen. Thank you
Dejen. And yeah migraines are the worst especially the worst migraines can just come on you and
there's nothing you can do. Even if you take Tylenol or Advil it just doesn't work.
It's just it's like a different kind of headache. It's such a pain in the ass. But yeah they are
the worst. Thank you for the 300 bits though. Appreciate it. Bdlujay thanks for the 500 bits.
I was in a discord chat with my friends while watching. Yo shout out to Alex and Keifer.
And we all had a blast seeing you and Joel yell at each other like idiots and also play
Jump King like a pro. I'm all right. Thanks for the laughs as usual. You always brighten my day.
Love you germa. Thank you. Thank you so much. You guys hanging out in a in a Skype call and just
fucking I love that. That makes me happy. Excedrin is good for migraines. Yeah doesn't
Excedrin have a shitload of caffeine in it though? And I take in a lot of caffeine anyways.
No it's just being a dark room and keep my eyes closed pretty much is how I get rid of them.
Thankfully they don't happen that much anymore. I think realistically only a few streams over
the last year have really been shut off from a migraine so that's pretty good. I'm just happy
about that. Doesn't happen all the time. Thank you 90hoo for the 500 bits. I made you a gift
of pizza before you go deep rain. No that's not it. Pepperoni pizza. Yeah he almost got me there.
He kept saying the word pizza and pepperonis and stuff and then I almost left. What'd you do to my
mouth? Why is my mouth so strange looking? Dobski dude thanks for the 250. I want to make a formal
apology. A week ago I tried contributing to the giant enemy spider meme but in the process I
accidentally brought the trick to you flog pyro joke back from the dead. It's already spiraling
out of control. Even Vinny is getting hit with the clip out of context. Now we have not one but two
five-year-old germa jokes running amok. Help one day chat can forgive me. Yeah this is rising of
the dead here. This is the second one. He probably just is like what the fuck is this? And that's it
guys. I will see you on Tuesday. Again sorry for the abrupt short stream that just turned off
but you know you do what you gotta do and I gotta do this. Thank you all again so much for your
support and it's Joel streaming right? Let's go say hello to Joel. Let's go Ray Joel.
We were playing with Joel earlier so yeah he's still going. He's doing Zelda Ocarina of Half-Life.
Plus garbage field leftovers. All right go uh go tell Joel. Say did go say Joel to blame him for
my headache. See like dude I do dude germa had to turn his stream off because of like you gave him
such a bad headache. Oh cake mario that's right hold on let me get it I'll be right back. Okay so
this is uh this is gonna go. I'm gonna put this in my bathroom. You ready?
This is going in my bathroom. Cake Mario. Stop hitting me. What are you talking about? What do
you think? It's like four versions of Cake Mario. It's ugly? What? What do you mean it's ugly as shit?
Who said that? That's not true. Is it? It's going to my bathroom. It's going right above my toilet.
It's going right into the toilet. Well not right above. It's going right above the toilet.
All right I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Let's uh let's raid Joel.
I love this thing. It's fucking all it's all the Cake Marios.
All right see you later. Here we go. Take care guys.