Split. Well, um, I mean, yeah, I could have done that. You're right. You are. You are correct. I could have absolutely could have done that.
I can't tell if this is the beginning of the game or if this is I don't know. Is this the beginning of the game?
Does anybody know where's the oh, there it is. This is where I left off. All right, good
We did it
We did a little pivot to hit man and threw some grenades at people and I went back to the quiet man
I just backed up into that guy and I heard him. Is the audio yeah
We have to explain to everybody again that the audio is like all fucked up
Yeah, see we had two hours of quiet man and then two hours of hitman and then like now two hours of quiet man
No, this this sucked. You should play hitman again
YouTube auto
No
No, let's just get through this game. I can't believe i'm still watching this
Don't you want to see how it ends?
We need to see how this ends
I feel like I was just in like a time warp
I just had like a hitman dream for an hour and 40 minutes
Still says i'm playing hitman. Oh fuck. I got a chance. This guy's not even functioning
I should get the quiet man's haircut. I already had it. It was great
God damn it. Don't do this to me. No
Not now don't do this to me now. Don't do this to me now
Okay, I fixed him. They can't be more than like 30 minutes in this game, right? They can't be
Golden this did not win a golden joystick award. No way
It did not
It did not it did not
What do I have to do? Please consider using youtube autoplay
uh
No, I can't get up 18 percent liked this game
All right. Here's the question. Do you think the viewer is going to go up or down?
What do you think?
Your viewers are going to triple
Well, it's been going down
Uh
Hey, well, by the way, germany is this weekend if anyone was curious. Hope you have a happy thanksgiving
It still says hitman 2. Oh, hold on. Let me let me just change that real quick to the quiet man
All right, and then the I changed the title title that makes more sense now, too
What is this pause screen? It's it's absolute dog shit. I have no idea why it's like that
Yeah, we went back. Yeah, I we we did the we I need to see how the sense we have to be close to the end
Blow up this stuff
Is this shit?
We're almost there
There's quite a bit left
And they can't be don't worry the fact that here's the crazy part about this the fact that there's no
Not even any any audio besides these muffle punches
And they keep doing this overlay
Covering the whole screen superimposing images. We've seen a thousand times already
Why do you keep showing us this?
Why do you keep doing that?
No, it's gonna explode
It's deep you wouldn't you just wouldn't understand
Play vacuum cleaner noises
Um, am I about to turn on that? No
I already did this
How about we just like learn how to speak a different language? How does that sound?
Let's get like rosetta stone
Rosetta stone. Uh, what language do I want to learn? I'm gonna I'll have a
How to speak
um
I don't speak french
A language poll. Okay. Yeah, you know, it's a great idea
Let's let's see what language you guys want me to learn while we for the next hour
french
Uh latin
Got Chinese
Japanese
Uh spanish
um
english
Italian
Italian uh
Korean
french
Klingon
We can't put like, uh, what's the one from lord of the rings? What's the one from lord of the
This is making me laugh so hard
Okay
That's good, that's good, that's good
No, i'm not putting i'm not putting dothraki on here
Oh
Klingon korean you guys it's coming down to english or elvish
Uh
121 to 132
People are gonna get so confused
They're gonna come to the stream. They're gonna be like, why is he doing this? Just
Is there any reason why he's learning a language and playing this shitty game? All right, we got
All right, it's you got you got you get 60 seconds here
Now I think it's getting closed
Oh, man. All right
I think that's it
Yeah, it looks like it looks like we're gonna learn elvish
Uh, we can learn both
Let's learn elvish and then english
Okay, how thank you for voting polls close we're gonna do elvish in english how to speak elvish
Oh my god. Okay
Basic vowels learn to speak basic elvish
All right. This one is this video is basic
These are vowels
Let's see
Okay, let's give it a try i'm willing to learn
Okay, here we go
I thought that in my channel, you know, i've been using some elvish words and
Perhaps it's time that I actually tell you what they mean and teach you a little bit so that you understand
What I am saying when I do my videos, I guess I jumped right in thinking that most people who would find my channel
Would already know
But if you haven't
Discovered elvish language then I will teach you a little bit. That's what we're here for
So let's start at the very beginning
So what you have to know is that the vowel sounds
Um sound so the a e i o u and then that will allow you to be able to pronounce words
So for a's it's always a long a so it has the sound of
Ah
So whenever you see a word that has a in it you can sound it out by using ah
So a is a
Next vowel we have is e and it's always a short e
and the word
The word that you can think of to get that sound is
Elephant or so l e is l so it's that
L
And if you don't know what a long and short vowel is, um, the long makes that long face. Ah
short is
And you can tell the difference in the way that you position your mouth. Okay, so
So everything is a and ah so far
And then the next vowel is i and that is a short i so it has that so it has
In
So i is
The i sound like that so if you find a word
Like mean mean lots of different, uh words actually have i's in them and so you're always going to have that short i
sound
Then the next vowel is o
Octopus
And then we have
You i'm not the birds. I don't have a bird here
Unicorn and glue glue
So it's always like a kind of sound you you you
So hopefully that will that's actually very informative
Announcing some of the elvish words and names
Okay, so let's start out with the very first thing that I always say in my videos, which is
My
Which means well met my friend sometimes I just say my
Friend but if you put that wait, I missed a reveal. This is a big reveal. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait
I missed it
My my
It's that ah sound so you always want to end that word with an ah, so
But it's that e so together it's my my
So just let it flow from your mouth, okay very very
Is that octopus sound and then
Try it with me
Very fast
Why is the game teaching us elvish and this is all third age
Elvish language. This is uh cinderella. So this is all of the walk in a corner, uh type of
Uh pronunciations that you would listen to in the lord of the rings
So this is all last stage lord of the rings all of the trilogy
This is this is the language that they use because there's a lot of different types of languages quinnia and there's uh,
The um cinderan can you believe that there's entire languages based on this game languages, but not this game
It's easier to research the ones that you find in the movie
But it's just really beautiful when you speak it. It's really fun when you start to do it
So just let that flow really easily
Okay
The next one one that I use a lot is hello or hi this quick reading is
Then do then do let's say say hello then do
Uniform that then do
Then do then do
very simple
The eh is that short e so that do
then do
And that just means hello
Use some times is
And it's just like that you pronounce the unicorn so
Ah that open a like father that's reading
Is another way that you can greet
I greet you. So this is another way to greet. Oh my fucking god
We sweet then I greet you
I greet you
Okay, so those are very basic basic things you can say when you meet somebody then
I will use these as good if I
So let's start out with the one that you
If you write anything on your computer, you need to get grammarly. I don't know. Don't get grammarly
Did he actually miss
At home
One where is jane?
She is in the living room jane's and what is she doing? She is playing the piano
Where is the car?
It is in the garage. Where is the dog?
The dog is too fast for me. This is basic english doing the dog is eating
At home
one
Where is jane?
She is in the living room. What is she doing? She is playing the piano
Where is the car? It is in the garage. Where is the dog?
The dog is in front of the door
What is the dog? This is an hour and 20 minutes
at the restaurant
This is a big menu. Yeah, what are you getting chicken peas and baked potatoes?
I don't know what to get. What a terrible fucking restaurant. I had turkey yesterday. How about steak?
Perfect. I'll get steak and mashed potatoes. What vegetable are you getting? I'm not getting any. I don't like vegetables
When's the baby due?
I have some good news. What is it? Lisa is going to have a baby. I can't keep up. I'm so happy for you
Me too. Do they want a boy or a girl? A girl. When's the baby due? In the beginning of september
I'm going to phone lisa tonight. That's nice. Say hello for me
Bus stop. Is that you at the conversation? Jean. Barbara, do you work around here? Yes, I work in that building across the street. Really? What do you do?
I work in a building across the street. I work in a building across the street. Really? What do you do?
I work in a building across the street. Do you work in a building across the street?
bus stop is that you at the conversation jean barbara do you work around here yes i work in
that building across the street really what do you do i work in a law office i'm a secretary
oh that's interesting what about you what do you do i work at duru restaurant are you a cook
what's new i'm a waitress that's a really hard job i don't envy you me neither hey what about
the baby in the bus now we're in the bus do you live alone jean no i don't i live with
how about you i married now i got married last year really congratulations who did you marry
his name is jeff hunt he lives in my building oh what does he do he's a doctor how wonderful i'm
very happy for you bus stop why are we at the bus stop so long do you work around here yes
i work in that building across the street really what do you do i work in a law office
i'm a secretary that's interesting what about you what do you do i'm gonna fucking lose my mind
oh are you a cook i'm gonna lose my mind i'm gonna lose my mind i have to stop it now job i
don't envy you me i'm gonna lose in the bus i don't care about the bus alone jean no i
don't i live with my family how about you i married now i got married last year really
congratulations who did you marry his name is jeff hunt he lives in my building oh what
he's a doctor how wonderful i'm very happy for you gardening your garden is really lovely thank
you i enjoy working in the garden do you do everything yourself i trim the bushes and weed
flower beds myself who cuts the grass oh it's so big that i hire one of the boys in the
neighborhood to do it for me well i must say he does a good job yes his work is more than
satisfactory gardening your garden is really lovely thank you i enjoy working in the garden
do you do everything yourself i trim the bushes and weed the flower beds myself
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die on stream well i must say he does a good job
yes his work is more than satisfactory a lazy boy i'm very angry no i'll get it off why what's
the problem he's not doing well in school that's a surprise here's a smart boy yes but he never
to his teachers yes i did what did they say he's the nicest boy
he's very lazy maybe they're right i'm afraid so have you thought about getting him a tutor
maybe that's a good idea i really want him to excel let's go look in the phone book now
phone book that's it a lazy boy i'm very my son harry why what's the problem
he's not doing well in school that's a surprise harry is a smart boy
but he never studies did you talk to his teachers yes i did what did they say
he's a nice boy but he's very lazy maybe they're right i'm afraid so have you thought about
getting him a tutor maybe that's a good idea i really want him to excel let's go look in the
phone book now i have to pause it oh fuck me man it's just like the being punched out of a
window he's a lazy boy we should get him a tutor oh my fucking god i just murdered myself
i didn't learn any english there at all i learned none i did not learn a single thing
oh my lord we're in a fire we're in a building on fire when did this happen
why did the building the building just burn what can you turn up the volume i can't it doesn't
exist he's a lazy boy they're talking about me this are you kidding me dropper yeah just put
her down and get him a tutor this stream has i'm sorry this has been such a clusterfuck
strangely enough i've been having a great time like
i've been having a lot of fun i need to learn english that's english conversation practice
you should open up the phone book i have no idea what this game is about
i don't i don't know either who knows i can't is this supposed to be mom or girlfriend or
can i drive there what time is it it's three o'clock oh no i'm late where are you going
to the dentist can i drive you there sure that will help that's the most like
cursed video it really is all right here comes the final boss can i drive you to the dentist
so he's a bad guy all along apparently he was he was the bad guy the whole time
there's so much of this he was such a nice boy but he this is the dentist he took me
to the dentist i wonder if they're speaking elvish oh my god he's him don't kill her no
don't do it we use grammarly inside or you motherfucker i'm fucking grammarly
will be dangerous please be careful i will by the way can i borrow your car
it's beginning to snow do you like snow no i hate it why snow is so pretty yes but i don't
like to drive in it well it's beginning to snow and i have to drive to work how far is it to
work six miles are we going to get much snow about 12 inches they say oh no driving will be
dangerous please be careful i will by the way can i borrow your car a house at the shore
when is your vacation it starts next week where are you going we're renting a house on the
shore that's wonderful yes we love the ocean do you swim a lot very much then why are you
going to the shore they're still talking when is your vacation it starts next week where are
you going we're renting a house on the shore not very much then why are you going to the shore
this is the way the game is meant to be played flash the nvidia logo
it's snowing but it's snowing but buddy you go to the shore i go to the shore to swim
but the shore is so far away how do you get there i drive can i borrow your car
what a strange way the two robots talk to each other looks like it was dad turn on the
dove again okay i'm gonna turn the dove back on because we all bought new swimsuits a soccer game
i'm going to play soccer who are you playing with some friends from work are you a good
soccer player yeah no it's not gonna work us but i'm not the best player on the team
what time does the game begin nine o'clock why don't you come with me i can't today i'm very busy
okay see you later i hope your team wins i hope soccer game
is this the actual audio i'm going to play soccer who who are you playing with
some friends from work are you a good soccer player yes but i'm not the best player on the team
what time does the game begin nine o'clock why don't you come with me i can't today
i'm very yes it isn't very large but there's a cooker and a fridge there are some cupboards
under the sink are there any any plates oh where the fuck are we yes there are good are there
any chairs in here no there aren't but there are some in the living room hmm there aren't any
glasses yes there are they're in the cupboard and where's the toilet afraid of flying
where is i wish they would speak your meeting in dallas texas how are you going
by plane do you like to fly sure it's fast and comfortable i'm afraid of flying
that's silly flying is very safe maybe but i don't feel safe in a plane
i understand a lot of people feel that way afraid of flying where is your meeting
in dallas texas how are you going he's lost his fucking mind plane do you like to fly
sure it's fast and comfortable i'm afraid of flying that's silly flying is very safe
maybe but i don't feel safe in a plane i understand a lot of people feel that way
i can't control it plane reservation okay let's we gotta get off the plane
messy writing can cost you primarily business focuses on commas spelling no no
no my money uh secret sponsor he's sponsored not me how long is this cut scene i have no idea
i know that's why i need a loan a car loan so is dad just gonna watch me fight
is that what's gonna happen a car loan a car loan is a boot to the head detroit become
boring he's very lazy i want to go to the bank this afternoon keep playing it i mean we're
already here i can't leave come on i gotta hold on a second this is important
hold on i'm ready i'm ready for the next cut scene that's it the chef is the only guy left
oh come on why are you like the hardest guy in the game all right knock them out
okay we good no we're not it's still going i'm so ready for the next cut scene i hope
there's like three people involved please tell me there's five people in this cut scene
okay
why is there a video of 12 hours of baby sounds now come on washing machine noises
into the dryer that was it leave it on why am i that's gonna hurt my brain that guy's gonna
bet this needs to be very i'm not turning this up very loud no way i feel like i'm stuck
somewhere like i'm stuck right now not in the game just in life i'm in this washing machine and
i don't like it i don't want to be in the washing machine anymore get me out of here
put in nickelodeon sound effects okay i like that better all right nickelodeon sound effects
okay let's see no this is that's not it nice lag i fucking died oh my god ed ed and eddy's
ed ed and eddy the ed eddy theme song
ask your parents
what's happening what's playing next no i don't want to play full episodes of courage the cowardly
dog i'm sorry that's not gonna happen i'm not gonna play an episode of ed ed and eddy in the
background guys he's getting away i'm not doing that shit do it cowl no what you want to play
copyrighted material all right i ren and stimpy oh my god somebody said this this is fit pretty
well this is 2011 i'm gonna lose again no the stream is not getting that derailed with derailing
i mean that's i'll do that that's funny no that's it this there's not that was it
it was one all right i get up this is the last part of the game i mean yeah we we are very
closely blocking the line of this is this stream is a shitpost we're getting there very quickly
it's happening this is getting real close it already is i i know that's why i got i gotta
put the foot down somewhere get away from me these guys the way that they swing uh
that guy just flew across the whole entire map play back home we'll play batman no we won't
we're not gonna play batman uh we're almost out of this don't you do it don't you do it
play flash games not yet just play audio from another stream i did uh this is painful without
memes well let me just get through this place oh my god and another one please i'm not playing
somebody's latest video let me just get out of this okay play my latest video in the background
my latest video is a spider-man update video from two years ago oh i'm overstimulated right
now anybody else overstimulated i feel i'm i'm gonna take a bath after this stream
i'm gonna put like epsom salt and coconut oil and i'm just gonna soak i need recovery after
tonight i i have been every emotion you know what i mean this has been a wild fucking stream
i've been every single emotion i was sad i was scared i was angry i was it was it was joy
ever every emotion has been touched stream the bath stream the bath i'm gonna get banned
if i stream me in a bathtub just wear clothes wear a swimsuit just keep all of my clothes on
i can't i can't do it i can't risk it that one random scenario you did it already yeah but
that was like a video i talked to mr twitch he said it was fine i regret wanting this game
to come back well uh oh uh just in case you're curious i cannot refund this game it's been
like three hours is he supposed to do something or all right give it to me straight here give
it to be real what um how much is left in the game for real and don't no joking answers how
how much is actually left in this game i don't know for real 30 minutes 30 to 45 minutes all
right we can do it we can do it what the hell are you doing down here dad maybe 20 30
we can do it here's the second to last boss one guy no there's no way there was a huge
reveal that these people that i didn't care about in the beginning are people that i still
don't care about in the end and they double crossed me for somehow through the beginning
of the game i don't remember what they double crossed me on it or they did it though somebody
was talking like baby talk it was an english uh tutorial that's all i remember because this is
one of the main characters here all right come on you can two drunk guys fighting
that's why did i go through him am i even connecting shots on this guy i don't think i
am i'm punching him and it's hurting me and there actually is no sun okay there we go i mean
that's a great idea hey google show can be dangerous nothing the history out the window
this is going to be different this is going to be unique
i'm scared
there he is
it worked
this match is officially underway i never heard the bell ring
they never got the door locked and cain why did i just lose that quickly this is like playing a
game on a school night and having the sound muted so your parents don't know you're still up yes
okay now the door is locked finally back into the cell and it's cain who goes on the offense
early and perhaps this is no accident understanding what the
lockers maneuvers like that 20 years of destruction for the undertaker looking to
continue it tonight and locking the door now these two oh the door is locked caged inside
hell in a cell and let's not forget cain did to the undertaker back and that just started
oh come on no
here's some destruction
a weakness in his brother the undertaker when the
undertaker showed some type of compassion to sean michaels at wrestlemania
and again this is a different undertaker that we've witnessed
there's a couple of weeks ago snake eyes vintage undertaker as he takes cain down
vintage under day oh there's down in a kick out a quick backstory paul bearer had
an affair with a woman in the bowels of the funeral home wait what was the dvc oh right cain
they're takering yeah knocked down to his knees after that punch
1990 look at cain now with the chair look at the chair oh i don't have a chair don't lose
here but let's humanize this for a moment i mean if the undertaker has ever come to
really fitting in a being of the flesh i may attempt that that humanity was revealed to be
a lie undertaker and he can't humanize under one of these individuals
demon a monster admittedly so cain has lived in his better more celebrated brother's shadow
for years that's what this is all about the father of destruction looking on man who please
what the fuck
gravitate back to paul bearer where the fuck am i the fact that the world's heavyweight
championship an accolade that transcends time the same way these two once in a lifetime
superstars will do is hanging in the balance tonight somebody just threw something at the door
under punishing a champion came in the early going got it placing cain's skull hanging over
the steel steps that are going to the poop by the undertaker the undertaker will use these
tools of destruction like no one else has ever been able to utilize such carnage
which one is the undertaker
it's now 20 feet high and this in perspective this is the 11th time
undertakers participated in this matchup the closest individual to him triple h
he's been involved in he broke him through the cell he wins my hallway
oh i can't take it anymore hey does anyone have a charger
here
oh no we're gonna wait for what's even going on keep it going
ah no no this is what happened this is a shit this whole stream is a shitpost
it just it is i've come to terms with that it just has been the whole time
that has not stopped for about five hours embracing it you have to embrace it
hey can we get some english lessons i'm not sure
hi this is gabe newell hi this is gabe newell
damn it that's gabe hi this is gabe newell i work at valve okay gabe n g-a-b-e-n
my username is gabe n
i'm done with this one i'm done with this one
oh my god
improved on perfection i think we've made it even more perfect come on joe this is the express
ready set go well kathy this is beautiful and it is ready look what we've done look what we've
done so i so i am the bad guy i or not no i'm not he's the birdman so i have to be the whole
game that was a huge boot where's that the whole game trapped here only five more out no
this game is over in 10 minutes probably i'm in slow motion get out of that slow motion man
come on really oh um remember to punch the guy in the balls you can't do that did i make this
you know what i mean i know you did you did right yeah i did okay you did i just was checking
i just i forgot i didn't know if i did or not i went like a countdown timer when the game is
over so i don't what the fuck am i doing that was a nice double kick no here comes another
five people i just asked a chat to count oh god that was a mistake i'm so sorry
i can't lose here though i don't want to do this again this is still coming in here
i mean what why make it that's just the same it's the same combo every time too
every single time nobody looked at it and said hey maybe we shouldn't just have the same
room and same combo you took out that center divider so now you have 25 more cooking area
so you can cook a lot of different things exactly right like how about pizza
it makes the best pizza i've ever had now this is my almost instant pizza dough and the
recipe comes with it all you have to just pop it in there and then put whatever toppings
you like it's a personal pizza so you don't have to wait for the delivery man pay extra
for all the toppings no tip for the driver either exactly now this is that reduced fat
turkey pepperoni you'll never tell the difference except it's not so greasy
we're saving a lot of calories little light mozzarella
here's the last boss bite i need something perfect i need something for this
i need something perfect for this
come on quick come on quick parry him i gotta parry if you're right
good parry that was a parry i parried him oh my god i'm gonna lose to gwen what you're about
to hear is encouragement and praise with cheering applause just for you acknowledging
you for a variety of reasons if there's a situation that does not apply to you
just listen and see how you feel so sit back get ready here it comes
we want to thank you for all your hard work you're the one who steps up and gets things
done around you keep your word deliver what you promise and then you go the extra mile
he's doing a great job a great job
if anyone asks we'll tell them a great job there it is come on quick doing a great job i am
i need more i need more i'm gonna lose it if i don't get cheered come on got it probably
wondering why we have asked you here today we want to tell you that we have faith in you
and we know you can do it we know you've got everything it takes to accomplish whatever your
heart desires that dream you're going for that career you want that recognition you're seeking
me it is yours
just listen everyone agrees
a great job here it comes we're on your side we're here for you we believe in you
we believe in you that seriously is one of the most unbelievably funny dvd cds that was sold on an
infomercial cheers to you is real this is not a joke that's not just some youtuber making a joke
you that was an infomercial you bought that and plugged it in and put it in listen to it
i can't believe it i wish i had bought it long time ago and you had one no no i
didn't remember watching the infomercial people used to be unironically encouraged by well good
because i hope they were doing a great job we believe in you what the hell why am i like
a supernatural now you're kidding me what now get 20 off clothing and outerwear at llv
find gifts with hundreds of five star reviews like our sweater fleece or our 850 down jackets
both their customer favorites don't listen to this make it an llv holiday and get 20
off clothing and outerwear okay start it over start it over start it over wait bring it on
nobody can be sand she's the hardest boss in the game what the
fuck was that the timing eat his face throw up why is this the coolest part of the whole game
so much we're doing jerma confirmed for 10 year old little cousin this was a request
this was a special request all right let's see how the undertaker he will destroy you
no man can match his free oh yeah destroy him give him the tombstone how many guys are there
when does this end how do you get this to stop this is never end all right hold on wait wait
wait i have to get the girl okay uh fuck is going on there was the time just rewind uh
i don't have i don't why did that happen didn't i just i just did this uh okay he wants to rematch
the undertaker now why would you want to fight me like this i don't think i'd want to fight
this guy he's gonna break the streak for need music need music all right sorry let me like
scheduling my shitpost street my god let me just get it like scheduled for you guys
yeah today's the uh wednesday night you know once once every two or three months
this is is this in my imagination do i just think i'm like a superhero or am i
am i holding him over the edge give us the reveal oh no what happened to dad don't do it
don't do it don't do it uh make your choice no come on no you don't want to reveal jigsaw
that's not his face you're kissing a mask i've lost control of the stream i actually lost it
probably three hours ago but you know i don't know who's counting he's nice but he's lazy
did i ever have control i'm not sure i don't think i did we already saw him without the
mask this reveal doesn't make any sense now this is is it like a twin it's a twin
situation right twin brothers one of them was evil and wore a mask and the other one was
putting the mask on to try to this two it's twin brothers see watch here comes a twin i called it
i fucking win i win i win here comes the twin brother no it's a dad why does everybody have
this mask i don't is this like the mask with jim carrey this thing just makes you go crazy
it brings out the worst or the most the most mischievous of people i don't understand
why wear it do i have to play as did you really just do like the rock
give him the people's elbow i'll try but i'm he's the rock i'm not the rock
all right i got it i got the people's elbow oh dad you suck oh that was a nice slide
does anyone want to watch all the dialogue of the game at like times 20 speed so we can just
figure out what happened just like yeah sure we could figure out what happened i'm not i don't
think it's impossible got it with a drop kick yeah that was pretty good oh we're in the hell
in a cell right here oh right up against the cage new game plus has dialogue but why would
you want to play through this whole thing again like the video game itself is just is just awful
right if the story was good you don't really you don't want to play through this again
if the game was a little bit more fun maybe but okay you could you could have a really
interesting story well though you have to play through the whole game and then play through it
again to be able to hear everything but like the the fighting has just been the same two
combos why are we doing like the dragon ball z we both fought for five minutes now we're
gonna have dialogue sequence they really are doing that it's like a smash brothers trailer
what the hell was that oh the double knockout the double knockout who is this they're not
she's not going to come over and put the mask on right is that like a who is this is that
the girl that was just standing there if she puts the mask on and i have to fight this girl
she's gonna be naked don't be naked don't go all the way here and just and be naked
or something don't do that i'm gonna do my best i'm gonna do my best to lip sync it
to the lip match
no you're ruining my immersion i don't want to hear it i've been so used to not hearing it i
don't want to hear it we're here for the ending credits we have to see it sing it
stars
this is one of those movies that you go see with a group of people
and you spend the money on it and then the car rider you walk out you know the movie ends
the credit okay everyone gets up silent on the way out you get in the car doors close close
close that's like four of you nobody talks it's dead silent and finally somebody's just like
so was the was the son the bad guy or was the mom and it was i don't i don't know man that was
whatever like nobody has any fucking idea it's in it's quiet for like 15 to 20 minutes until
somebody decides to bring it up because you all paid for it and you and you spent time there
you know what i mean yeah it was like a two or three hour movie nobody wants to admit that
that was a bad idea oh wow we all just wasted our evening no nobody what no so let me like
let me get this straight dude get rid of the whole beginning part and give me the
give me like the electric bird man stuff with all those cool moves
to two twins it's about twins it takes to make the break to show the twins on screen
don't even give me this bullshit it's this over 3000 people here 40 of you at least
are like actually kind of like this you're gonna add this to your playlist when you're
working out yes you will not a bad song see what's it called in the time that it takes
to show the twins on screen is that what it's called after you always stay for the after
infinity war credits push her off and this would be of two letter grades higher oh well here
comes another person to put on the bird mask is it dad again there's dad again dad's back
dad got up and
i want the main character to have a really really absurd voice
you is also what's happening to me like shut up idiot you're blinded by grief
me by ambition why is it so compressed audio
yeah
homeroom 201 it is the greatest performance of my career the night i was kidnapped
and the time that it takes you put songs of the world the time that it takes
one two three four one two three four one two three four 10 20 23 24 uh 50 49 cents
40 no 40 yeah 49 cents got it don't you just fucking hate the rumble feature
on controllers i wish they would just not do it anymore
uh
what the hell am i supposed to press a button it's not most people would have hung up by then
lava what the machine
no one hears me i don't hear me anymore i want to be taken away and just
just disappear i have absolutely no idea what's going on
please take me away
okay quiet man answer hey what's going on everybody it's uh it's bob from the dev team i'm gonna
answer your questions here as the game plays again so we decided to put uh the game in
reverse have you seen memento uh that goes in reverse too spoiler i mean it's a great
movie how do i turn it on didn't say it was in the options
yeah that is that really is a 2006 dvd menu i just want to see i'm curious got to change the
stream name instead of the quiet man the i can hear you now man the audible man loud man
the man just the man a man a man in the world let's see what i say here didn't we hear this
guy this is what this game makes no sense this guy we heard him in the beginning we heard this
shit before he see he talks why did halfway through the game we just we couldn't hear
anymore see why were we able to hear him do that but then 30 40 minutes later it's just
muffled sounds all right where's the scene that we need context you know what i mean
oh i can't i can't just skip all of them this is no sound though all right let's just
press let's get it over with yeah i couldn't use the top one separate progress yeah okay hold on
too late for a refund yeah that's all right i had a good time listening to music and putting
fucking weird sound effects over my stream we were all just sitting in a room and i was
pressing buttons and loud sounds and music was coming out i may as well just had a black
screen you know it gets to a point when you start to play the ed ed and eddie theme song
and then put and then a portion of an entire episode yeah it's you've lost control completely
and it's like the stream's off the rails i suppose keep the screen here
and it was that was a weird stream we started on this and then it got voted off the island
i got angry at my computer i i blew up a guy in hitman and then we went back and finished
that was this was very odd but uh i am not streaming tomorrow it's thanksgiving tomorrow
happy thanksgiving to all you the next time you see me will be either friday or saturday
germania 2018 is scheduled for hopefully sunday so i obviously want to give myself a little bit
more time to work on it so nothing tomorrow and maybe nothing on friday because i really
want to put time into uh the wrestling thing what was he you might see me again before saturday
but if not we're going to go saturday and sunday sunday being hopefully the uh you know
that game am i going to stream more red dead um maybe maybe that's what we'll do on friday
or saturday because i really am getting kind of an itch to play it again but there you go
thanks for sticking around uh i know people were coming and going during this nightmare
stream that's the best way i can put it it was kind of just like a bunch of dreams
mashed together but let's uh get to the bits and then the credits take care hope you had fun
i i mean weirdly enough i had like i had fun pretty much the entire stream i thought that
was going to be like a disaster no that was a boy i had a lot of fun i don't that was
great quiet man in germania yeah probably i don't see why not i'm gonna have to mute
the stream when it comes out but anyways let's go back a few hours here to just about four hours
ago let's go let's see what i got there we go is it that's my dashboard okay so thank you to
extra cheesy for the dollar 45 hey germbo you finally managed to stream some dead space without
it sucking completely oh damn man i only just recently figured out how to keep it from being
all stuttery i'm gonna celebrate by giving you money thank you extra cheesy it's a process as
uh as you saw during this stream sometimes computer problems and graphics and drivers and cpu i don't
have no idea what's going on with hitman but it just happens and you just kind of have to
try to figure it out on the fly or it's part it's part of the gig so i wish you luck
and thanks for the dollar 45 dude also thank you to timmy tim timmy tim tam for the one dollar are
you gonna go through are you going through a garfield phase again it's okay if you are we
support you a garfield phase what do you mean how do you about garfield phase oh lasagna that's
right that's the stream title was lasagna uh no there was a whole thing about uh this was
like three different streams i feel like i streamed that i feel like that was a conversation
we had yesterday this was really three different streams just mashed together in about five and a
half hours uh sorry for confusing people but it's all good uh thank you by the way speaking of
lasagna and garfield thank you garfield the monday killer uh for the one dollar germa i'm
stuck in feline penitentiary they got me now i'm in prison with you as well i'm not i'm not
in prison we're talking about well not you physically they just threw my phone in as well
and they thought it was you since that's what i used to show them on the stream these guys
hated my garfer graphs enough to keep me in prison so germa what's the game plan how are
you gonna break me out of here uh cyborg friend helicopter how is garfield gonna get out of
this one stay tuned for the next exciting episode uh i ain't posting your bail man i
would encourage no one else to as well what an asshole what no i'm talking about it like the
joke comedy cartoon land not like real life we're talking about joke comedy cartoon universe
betrayal is that a joke nothing is funny about putting cats in prison yeah but it's a
it's a comedy prison it's a joe it's a cartoon prison if garfield was actually in there all
he would have to do is plug his ears and blow out as hard as he could and steam would come
out of his nose and melt the bars and he would walk out it's the cartoon comedy land you can
do whatever you want he'll find a way out but thank you gar appreciate it dr clay thanks to
the one dollar germ i'm ready for phase one of boston out garfield i'm reporting to you that
we have two guards at the entrance and four at the desk if we want to get garfield we
got to go quick awaiting orders uh go to lunch and then go home thank you pilot guy for five
dollars save me some lasagna i will i'll save you lasagna don't worry you can get some but
thank you pilot guy thank you dark star 700,000 games for the one dollar oh he gave up on that
shitty fmv but not really fmv game thank god well i hate to uh cause you distress here but
you know you did say that four hours ago thank you the long egg for the one dollar the quiet man
made my knee even more swollen i'm sorry but at least we did it you can't say i didn't complete
that on stream i did put me on the list of people who i might who knows you find me
another broadcaster that's done the nintendo lab all of them uh sorry all of them on stream
and uh the quiet man i mean i got my hand up up on here looking over the ocean here i don't see
anybody you literally said you did one with kim off stream all of them except for that one
except for that one but that's that was just a little joystick one what i'm sorry so i did
95 percent of them on stream i did all of them except for the plain joystick fraud fraud fraud
it's outright didn't i guess tell you that 80 percent of the things i say are not true
thank you uh d jack for the one dollar hitman would be a much better game if the guy was deaf
and there was no sound i gotta figure out what the hell is going on with my cpu i might like
flash my bios or something because that made no sense because it wasn't just the fact that
the game was slowing down i was getting encoding errors on obs and i haven't had one of those
in at least two three years in my reading chat yeah i reach out all the time in fact probably
too much to my own detriment sometime uh thank you bro luck for the one dollar germ i just
realized uh your country has guns and like hitman or you mean like like the united states
yeah i mean that's accurate yeah make sure it's not just the game before you go yeah
that's true i don't know i'll do some tests because that was really weird if my cpu went
up to 90 percent when i installed that new driver that was very concerning that's why
i had to get out of there and i had to go i had to get out of there right now you know
what i mean i had to go i'll do a bench and just make sure everything's fine i wasn't even
kidding it's true but thank you uh thank you d jack again for the one dollar hitman is too
loud please play a quieter game thank you tingy for the dollar 50 cheering these bits to get
my new badge 50 is only the beginning expect expect much more from me thank you tingy for
the dollar 50 50 is way more than i could ever ask anyone to give this stream so do not ever
feel expected or obligated to do that but thank you we also had some gifted subs bet three we
talked about it already but bet three nice five community subs thank you you guys have
been incredibly generous with those especially lately uh bro luck thanks for the two dollars
here i thought i heard the delivery guy knocking at my door so i got up excitedly check to see if
someone was there it was a sound effect in your laggy stream uh my delivery is here now
you're forgiven well that's good you have to say laggy stream that's like saying
that's like saying shitty stream you know what i mean like hearts that's like telling somebody
that okay you go but you go over that house and you sit down and you it's like a friend
you know you're over a friend's house it's not like your mother's cooking it's not your you know
sister or brother cooking it's me and you're not used to it you don't like it and i give you
something that i worked hard on i put a lot of time into it was like macaroni and cheese and
you take a bite and you're like oh no this is disgusting this is gross mac and cheese gross
and i'm like i but i tried it's that's like saying i've had shitty mac and cheese tonight
in quotes this is a shitpost stream well but here's the difference though you came over
and you watched me put like random shit in the mac and cheese i didn't just make it i didn't make
mac and cheese tonight i took a box of mac and cheese and i said hey hold on a second
laughing the whole time i was putting cinnamon and like paprika and a random action figure into
it and put it in the oven we were laughing at it that's not my signature recipe that was
my just hey we're fucking around making gross food that was not my signature mac and cheese
recipe then what's the problem i yeah there is no problem then huh if you told me it was
gross then it would be like oh yeah it is gross we did we made it gross on purpose hey how dare
you did you say that was gross this cinnamon in there this dog pee in there it's gross
get out of here uh you guys are fucking awesome then there is no problem thank you cheesy hot
pizza for the one dollar how could you hate muffins you're a horrible person what i told
you my favorite muffins were cornbread muffin and chocolate chip muffin when did i say hate
muffins i talked about my love for chocolate chip muffins unless you put like a action figure
and pizza sauce in there and you did it on purpose uh but thank you son of jenova for the
one dollar i paul stretched a clip of you and star laughing during the bloody trap land video
it sounds like a bottomless pit of souls in pain what hold on what the hell is sin how do
i listen to it i feel like download this is like a weird website easy steps click start now
download on our website get free forums uh upload that i'll upload that to like youtube
and then give me a link next time that's a potential security threat son of jenova with
the sad face just play it through like your play through your headphones oh i'll be no
virus please 39 gigabytes of quiet malware play it through voice chat in the discord i
just said it don't do that don't do that don't do that just hang out here nobody go anywhere
don't leave i'll know you left oh why did i say what have i done that's how you repay it no
just put it on well just put it on youtube and we'll watch it on youtube i want to i want to
click a youtube video i'm scared of links they scare me 200 people is going to go do that
well uh don't do it how do i even open this did i download it did i get it
now that was that was terrifying thank you though thank you hawkeye of mine for 15
dollars 15 bucks from hawkeye oh man i'm going to texas for my 21st to remember the alamo so
i'll be missing the germania streams darn it well it'll be a great welcome home to see it
as a vod squad boy i had wrong inflection there but yeah uh that'd be 21st down in texas
hope you have a good time don't worry it'll be put on vod it'll be put on youtube eventually
as well so don't worry you'll be able to see it but thank you for 15 dollars really appreciate
it thank you and then right after that bet three gave 25 dollars 25 bucks from bet three
saying thank you jerma thank you i need i thank you for dropping 25 bucks on the stream thank
you bet three and you had community subs as well very generous uh thor facts thanks for the one
dollar dear video game streamer known as germa95 on the popular streaming website twitch the audio
of your game appears to be a little on the low side can you for the sake of your viewers
raise the volume level i went a little crazy tonight errorless thanks for the one dollar thanks
for the english lesson i feel learned very have luck thank you here it was uh it's weenie thanks
for the five dollars thank you it's weenie hey jerma glad to see you trying to expand your
horizons by finally learning english here's hoping you can learn spanish next since a lot
of fun music is in spanish you should try do you haven't embarrassed yourself enough so i
should try i said weenie thank you thank you smelly boy for the one dollar finished my essay turned
it in like 20 minutes late and i returned to the quiet game what the fuck well we finished
it and you can all say that you finished it too it was a giant terrible pizza that i forced
myself to eat but good luck good congratulations and good luck congrats on getting your essay
bet three again bet three another 15 dollars from bet three multiple large donations thank you bet
three just a durable heart on this one thank you big money bet three with the current number
one spot yep thank you uh thank you timmy tim tan for the one dollar better lose some weight
better lose some weight uh what is this we eat a lot did you see my car keys
they're on top of the tv you're right thanks where are you going to the supermarket again yes
we eat a lot do you want me to go with you sure if you can good the packages will be heavy
there is a new health store right up the road maybe since you guys eat a lot you should try and
eat more healthily maybe you're right we have all put on a little weight we eat a lot
but
but what the packages will be heavy
how do you know it's heavy
i don't know what's going on because i don't know what to do
just do it
i don't know what to do
i just don't know what to do
weight. but what the packages will be heavy? how much food do you buy? why are you buying 200 pounds
of food? thank you timmy. we eat a lot. maybe you should go there because you eat a lot.
thank you smacklesmore. smacklesmore for the one dollar. so i joined the stream a little late.
game looks pretty interesting but it made my brain shit itself. i'll have to ask my
tutor to give me a double lobotomy and suck a fart out of my ass to feel normal again.
thank you extra cheesy for the two dollars. you should have played this song during the fight
scene in the bar. i'm not playing the fucking youtube hilarious funny moments song. thank
you extra cheesy. thank you why do witches burn for the four dollars. thanks a lot. this is
literally all my bits just wanting to know this stream was so awful. my bones hurt. keep up the
good work. thank you. thank you for the four dollars. smacklesmore again thanks for one dollar.
okay what i said earlier turned out to be not turned out to not do any justice to the rest
of the stream. go sans undertale and thanks jerma for the laughs. hey thanks. captain
worgen thanks for the one dollar. finally figured out what owo means and it's translated
to business. business. weird. uh thank you jess. thank you jess for the one dollar. the fact that
playing epic music in the back was the only thing that makes this game engaging and entertaining
really proves that it was stupid to take the audio out in the first place especially when it
doesn't have a real purpose for the story. i think it's just they want you to play the
whole game again. but yes i don't i don't understand either. uh valuki thanks for the
one dollar. you should have used acid bass for that final fight but acid bass didn't make it
through the 2017 end of the year beginning of 2018 meme uh murder spree. sorry. extra thanks
to the one dollar. extra cheesy. though also this has been a good fight song as well. thank
you. would have been maybe. i don't know. uh mostly lost thanks to the one dollar. so i
actually did end up so i actually did end up lift driving this evening and somehow you
haven't given up on the game yet when i come back. i'm kind of impressed. no we had to
add some cinnamon. but thank you. welcome back. e half note thanks for the one dollar. hey jerma
i think my previous bits got lost in the computer crash. just want to tell you that
thinking about you in the raptor suit brought a smile to my face on a shitty day. so thank
you for that. thank you. glad you thought it was funny and it is the most embarrassing
thing i've ever done in my life without a doubt. um yeah can't wait to see what you
guys make. uh the rog. thank you. the the rogster or the roadster. thanks for four dollars. no
message. just four dollars. thank you. thanks for the four dollars. thank you. moo means moo
for the one dollar. your dog piss cinnamon streams are better than 90 percent of the
content on this website. that's very encouraging. thank you. dog piss cinnamon stream. is that
what we're gonna call them now? i guess. that makes i mean yeah i guess so. so anytime we're
starting to go off the rails just just bring up that it's turning into a dog piss cinnamon
stream and i'll know exactly what you're talking about. i'll now be like whoa i gotta pull the
rails. i gotta hit the brakes. uh thank you. errorless for the three dollars. really enjoyed
your breakdown of rat movie for vanity fair. will you be doing one for rat movie too?
oh my god. only 18 only 18 000 views. i'm just picking up on this. 7.5 million. a
million. 1.1 million. 18k. come on i can pull at least 40. okay i can pull at least like 43
thousand. i can pull i could probably bring up bring 150. more like 20.
oh thank you errorless. thank you dr clay for the five dollars. hey man this is a great stream.
the quiet man was a really bad game in my opinion. you'd probably be sharing the opinion
of a lot of people. i honestly have no idea what the story was or anything. i feel like
i saw the last episode of some anime without watching any of the previous episodes.
but with all the funny bits you really kept the ball rolling. i'm honestly glad this game exists
because if it didn't then this stream wouldn't have happened. have a wonderful thanksgiving
take care. thank you. thank you so much you as well. i'm glad we could turn it a cinnamon dog
shit stream into something that was a lot of fun. so thanks a lot. happy thanksgiving to
you as well. celebrated. thank you dr clay. thank you to albob. thank you albo or albob
for the one dollar. hey germo i know a lot of people say these kind of things
but i've been watching you for at least six years now and you're easily my favorite
content creator on the internet. i love everything you've done and you never cease to
amaze me with the things that you come up with. you've done so much for me mentally i
can't even begin on it. i even think you're too good to be true because of how many
idiots are out there. so hope you don't accidentally say something very bad one day or something.
no. no. i'm a what you see is what you get kind of person and i mean i'm just me.
bass is the worst instrument. but that was just an 85% cinnamon dog piss joke.
i just do this because i don't have any like ulterior motives or anything. i don't want to
you know sell you guys something or try to do something that i'm not capable of or
put on some kind of persona that's not real. i mean i'm like i'm like this in fucking real
life. ask anybody that i know that you know i'm i this is just i don't i it's exhausting
to put on like a personality or pretend to be somebody it is it is absolutely exhausting and
i do not envy people that do that because you end up having to put on a face and pretend so
often and so long that you have to it's it's it's step one to everything you do and say
he randomly uses his tuber voice it's kind of but like also remember i mean i am speaking
into a microphone right so i i wanted to so i guess it's impossible to 100% be the exact same
person that you are in reality because i have a microphone here and i want to make sure you can
hear it and and i'm i have audio set up and is being recorded you know obviously i'm
try to be as real as i can but no i don't i don't think you have to worry about me
trying to like put on a face or act in a different way i just hope that you still
think it's fun to be here i mean that that's the you know think about as a viewer right
some of you guys have been here for a very long time and yeah i mean yeah sometimes we kind
of i could see how some people after a while could be like oh it's it's germa again it's
germa again it's germa again and i don't know i feel like i'm trying to keep things
as interesting to have you guys not get sick of me you know because people have been around
for a long time i want to try to keep things interesting for all of us but thank you thank
you to chubby funster for the one dollar hey germ boy i recently lost my job i'm sorry dude
and i've been feeling pretty crappy about the whole thing but tonight's stream really helped me
take my mind off it not the game though that was fucking awful but you just shit posting
made my face hurt multiple times and i love you for it well i'm really sorry to hear about
you losing your job hopefully you can get back into a new job if you're able to take a little bit
time off figure out what you want to do and where you want to try i wish you the best of
luck and i'm sorry to hear that because you know i never want to hear about you know people
not feeling good people doing bad and we talked about this on the labo stream a little
bit but i'm rooting for you all hopefully you all can take care of yourselves you know
but thank you chubby funster good luck flank tank thanks for the four dollars flank tank
hey germy here's some bits i got a crisp clean 50 dollars i gotta save till you play
near automata like you said you would maybe after red dead 2 oh yeah i was gonna play that
that's true yeah get it on the list of video games that i'm gonna play
okay you're gonna you're gonna give me 50 dollars if i play damn yes
oh yeah obviously you gotta look into it yeah but uh we'll see if it's something that i
feel like doing most of the time besides some of the big plan streams the day-to-day on the
stream is kind of just like oh what do i feel like doing today what i want to do next week
or what if i want to plan to do next week and sometimes things just appear oh that yeah
i'll do that so we'll see uh thank you valuki for the one dollar i gave you a dollar you do what
i say play the game again and play acid base what no i'm not gonna play the game again why
would i play that game again play the fan-made bullet hell game oh man oh i'm gonna have to look
into that one and play that is that for real because like i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna look
into that in monster quotes you know what i mean i'd rather play that when more people are around
when it's like on like actual stream stream not like just hanging out at the end yeah it's for
real oh you bet your ass i'm gonna definitely monster massive monster quotes i'm gonna look
into that maybe i'll start with that next stream because that's really cool chill out
man i'm chill i'm fine i'm happy things are great besides the hitman technical problems that
made me a little sad i didn't get angry i was just sad i've had a great day today you know what i
mean but thank you to captain worgen again here's what owo means i know it's it says business
i don't know i don't know i'm not i don't know no it's not what it means
it's the thing it's the owl dick thing i know what it is i don't need to it's fine yeah it's
an owl dick and i get it it's two dicks richard and richard they're brothers okay i'm not gonna
get myself in trouble uh thanks uh thank you lazy luke for the one dollar you can read the bits
you lost from restarting your computer but if you don't want to if you were in the new super
spash brothers game what would be your special moves um i mean it would just be every single
direction like my let my side be my up be down be would just be the power of the sun
in a 600 foot long beam in every direction you just press side b and it would do like 40
damaged uh per tick you can just fill the whole screen and no one would ever touch me and i'd
win every time that's op yeah it is you think they're gonna patch it nope so guys bayonetta
was was impossible to play and play against bayonetta for the wii u version just beat
everybody and she was like an s plus plus plus plus tier you know the guy you know the guy read
the papers they're like i pay attention to the papers i wonder what they are gonna do though
because nintendo does not really at all like to patch games and fighting games in general
they kind of require balance updates don't they i wonder if they're gonna do that did they
actually patch uh smash wii u and do balance updates and everything they did have a patch
cycle no they patched it twice well ah there's almost 100 characters this time i'm sure there'll
be those i'm sure they'll be like the five to ten characters because when you make that
many characters it's like a moba you know all right welcome to league of legends there are
180 characters in this game but only play four of them five of them that are really worth
your time maybe seven of them out of the almost 200 characters in league how many of them are
actually worth going into lane with is it am i wrong saying that's like probably 20 characters
out of like a hundred and thousand about 50 about 30 how many are in the game 15 unless
you can one trick certain ones they're like 200 characters in league most of them are
actually played now really i remember hearing about people talk about uh it was there was i
mean maybe it's the game has changed or the better i don't know if you're bad at it like
me you can play whatever you want yeah you've even games like overwatch and that game had far
less characters a while ago wasn't there was the same two teams facing each other
overwatch meta l u l i haven't played it in a long time so i'm obviously speaking from
total ignorance but just play tanks i've seen a lot of people upset at that game but it's all
good as long as you're having fun playing a game then i'm glad you're having fun i'm not going
to be one of those people that's like well you know the thing is about league and dota
and think about uh smite and overwatch let me tell you whatever if you're having fun then
give us a fuck just play and have fun but anyways thank you clueless sniper for the
five dollars hey germa thanks for the great stream tonight i started watching your channel
in 2012 i got hooked watching your gta 4 videos and you've been a huge part of my life ever since
your contents helped me in more ways than i can fit into a bit message but being able to rely
on you for a laugh has helped me through some rough patches you're one of the most creative
wonderful people on the website and i can't wait to see what the future holds thanks for
everything yeah i hope you stick around uh i process these messages all the time and
stick around that should be a lot of fun shit more so than ever before so i told you before uh
starting with the green screen stream every like 30 to 45 days once every month or so once
every other month i want something that's we can all look forward to something that's not
just um anything that you're used to especially being out here it's going to be far easier so
i hope you stick around but thank you so much clueless sniper for the five bucks
and that uh amazing message thank you uh timmy tim ten thanks for the one dollar these english
conversations are fucking gold i can't stop thank you mr streamer uh thank the thank the
company that made those because they're absolutely gold thank you timmy tim tim again
for the one dollar i never drink coffee at night i never drink coffee at night oh god
oh god why are these so good a cup of coffee can i get you something to drink a cup of coffee
please with milk and sugar a little milk but no sugar i never drink coffee at night why not
it keeps me awake what do you drink with supper tea it helps me relax i don't like tea there
are so many kinds of tea maybe you should shop around and try to find one you like because
coffee is bad for you okay do you guys remember those streams that have the two robots talking to
each other that bounced back and forth off each other there was a popular stream for a long
time that's just this is what this reminds me of the two alexis having a conversation
that's a good idea a cup of coffee can i get you something to drink a cup of coffee please
with milk and sugar a little milk but no sugar i never drink coffee at night why not it keeps
me awake what do you drink with supper tea it helps me relax i don't like tea there are so many
kinds of tea maybe you should shop around and try to find one you like because coffee is bad for
you that's a good idea because coffee is bad for you coffee is bad for you is bad for you
you like because coffee is bad thank you timmy tim tim thank you also to moo means move for
the one dollar classic thought experiment you are driving a trolley down the tracks and the
tracks diverge into two paths one covered in cinnamon and the other covered in dog piss you
find the brakes and not functioning so you cannot stop before the just the diversion which of the
tracks do you drive down the one with the dog piss definitely uh thank you albo again al bob for
the one dollar hey what i said earlier wasn't supposed to mean that i'm getting tired of you
or anything i just bet i'm looking out for you because i generally think you're an amazing
person you're great at what you do and i'd hate to hear you did something wrong and throw
it all away also i hope you watch my green screen video and remember my name i worked a
little hard absolutely um i don't you don't have to worry about that thank you so much
for their concern don't worry everything's gonna be just fine thank you for looking for the one
dollar this is three dollars now you have to i'm not gonna i'm not gonna i'm not gonna i'm
not gonna uh parfolio mew thanks for the one dollar is acid base really illegal i'm so sorry
father no it's not illegal it's just it's it makes it room for some other songs you know
what i mean still a great song hey lawn two thanks for the one dollar here hey germa some
of the thrives in front of a camera do you have any advice for someone who has never been on
camera i'll be attending a big dota 2 tournament and i'm nervous that i'll make a fool of myself
on camera i have loved the stream keep it up um yeah i mean i here's the the best advice
i could give you but be in front of a camera you treat the camera like uh it's somebody you
want to talk to because you do you know the camera is an extension of of people's eyes
and i've always just kind of treated the camera like a friend you know somebody that i want to
talk to because i do want to talk and i do want to talk to it so you can kind of imagine
that the camera is actually a person that you're hanging out with and it's not that far
from the truth give it a try camera's a friend except cameras don't want to talk to you
yeah but the the camera is not a doesn't have a mouth that has eyes but hopefully the good that
helps you out good luck in the good luck in the tournament hopefully you do well don't know
much about dota 2 but hope you uh hope you knock it out of the park uh thank you so much
you know for the one dollar not a virus okay it's a youtube link so it can't be a virus
virus here's the chat bot thing to talk to a woman for a change so you don't talk with women often
that's right but there should be limits i don't know but it's the twitter people
who won't talk to me whispers why whispers i don't know ha ha ha crazy girl
okay thank you son of jenova for that
whispers uh here come the credits everybody we may have lost some in the first hour so
you all are amazing thank you so much the next line was the best maybe you're right we have
all put on a little weight the packages will be heavy there is a new health store right up the
road maybe since you guys eat a lot you should try and eat more healthfully some of these might
have turn into like a new subzone do you want me to go with you sure if you packages
there's a new health store right up the road maybe since you guys eat a lot
a lot you eat a lot like this one a lot a lot yes we eat a lot
peter peter i always get always gonna say i'm peter you know i think i'm going insane
uh lazy boy i've that whole segment was a fucking dream man i don't even remember anything
i was laughing so hard during that segment i don't even know what was going on on the screen
he's a lazy boy maybe with the tutor again yes we eat a lot
yes we eat a lot well thank you everybody again for coming to the you know the shitpost
fuck around stream happens every once in a while glad you had fun i had fun i will see you guys
after thanksgiving probably saturday yeah i want to give myself a couple days here to make
sure a germa rumble is locked in and ready to go for sunday yeah that's going to be the
end of the string happy thanksgiving wherever you celebrate it but time on sunday i'll let you know
i'll get it locked in probably around the same time as usual maybe three to two to three
something three o'clock uh pacific time oh yeah that's right i'm gonna take a bath i'm gonna
take a bath i am gonna take a bath thanks for reminding me and with that have a wonderful
rest of your night i'll see you guys in like probably a couple days holidays you know what
i'm saying holidays well we got hold on uh funny oh six one nine just came with a dollar
just nothing thank you so much funny and then flank tank with ten bucks ten dollars drop
right now from flank tank happy thanksgiving hope you and your family have a good one
i wish that for you as well and thank you so much for your ten dollar
bit donation see you guys soon thanks for coming out take care