Do you remember specifically when you were melee and we're in the fucking call and I told you I was going to a halloween party? What'd you tell me?
All right, it's november. Yeah, it's november. It's halloween's over. This is what this was your words not mine
You want to celebrate more halloween after telling me that I can't celebrate halloween a day after and you want to do it fucking?
Like three days after that's fine. That's fine with me. I'm not celebrating halloween
I'm playing team fortress 2. You are celebrating halloween. All of the servers are on halloween maps.
You want me to do the judge? I want the stenographer to read it back you is that the right thing a stenographer?
I heard is a stenographer like is that a doctor's equipment or is that like it actually i'm dumber than you
Well, i'm gonna i'm only gonna be ambassador headshot spy. All right be spy two then
Oh the present yummy. Oh shit
What?
I didn't have this achievement before
Oh, i'm it great no, no kill the engineer not me
Where are you? I'm currently running away from the dude the man the dude
The bad guy i'm currently running away from the bad guy. That's a head shot. That's a head shot
Can somebody please hit me?
What the hell was that?
Why did that take so long for me to get hit right there? Where are you?
I don't know. I'm in there. I'm standing at this pond door. That guy just died here
I like how you say you don't know but you do know. Oh, what's that spy cap? Oh, you got a taunt this guy
no
God damn it haunted house, man
He just ruined everything
The haunted house man. He really did screw. I would have capped it
I'm dead. I don't think you would have capped it. Let's play on how to reach over. What are we doing?
This is a good this is a good spawn to mark gonna snipe into we're gonna get it
One of us is gonna get it first person to get it gets uh 20 bucks
First person to get a machina like like triple kill double
So we have the first person to get a multiple kill with the first person to get the sound to play on the server
Okay, it's 20 bucks. It's 20. No, no screw that screw that
100 100 bucks first guy that gets it if you get it. I get 100 bucks if I get it
I get 100 bucks. Okay. All right
Who's giving 100 bucks? Did you guys hear that? I just I just said I get 100 bucks both times
Oh my god, how funny is that this get out of my no, no, no
I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get it. What we've killed the like people separately
I don't think uh, I don't think anyone's getting 100 bucks. Oh, dude. I'm tearing it up. I'm tearing it up as you sniper
No, watch it. Watch it
Please help me. No, no, no, no
I don't think it's gonna happen
What that's a spy
Of course the the of course like this the stupid how would I want someone to explain to me how that guy
What man I shot that sniper I shot howard stern his face twice and he didn't
I thought you were talking about the halloween man
No, no, I shot a sniper over there twice and one of them went right through his cheek and it didn't do anything
No, fuck you
Get out of here
I'm gonna get it. Not you. No, I'm gonna get it. Come on. Come on. Come on
shit
Get out of here
Got him
I need help
Can they cap the point already and come through here?
If you're spending all this time jumping in front of me, you're not gonna get it either. That's a spy
No, it's what that's me. That's me. No, it's not
It's the same name as me doesn't have my hats or anything for some reason
What the hell can these guys cap we're trying to get a mock at a kill over here
All right. It's got here it comes here. It comes i'm gonna get it
I want you to sign this hundred dollar bill. Why the fuck did I just fire?
We both shot them
Maybe we both cancelled each other out. That would be interesting
The other guy would have died
This is so laggy. This really is
If I only held on to that for like another three seconds, I probably would have had it
Somebody come behind this soldier. There's like these two scouts that are playing that soldier
I keep seeing and that's it. There are three people on blue team
Somebody just appear behind this guy so I can make my hundred bucks
Oh, there's a heavy there now. That's cheating
That's not
We're like the marasmus hat
They're all a bunch of drunk spies
Okay, so my paypal address. Well, you already have my paypal address. Yeah, you know where to send I'm editing it out of the video
You're gonna edit that out of the video, huh?
Yeah, oh, yeah
Oh, you mean me winning a slick to slick c note from star. No one's gonna know you did it
Oh really prove it. Oh, what if I wait you think i'm not uploading a video?
I don't think you are you don't think i'm gonna do that. I don't think you are. I just made 100 bucks
Everyone's gonna know it
I want I want I get 100 bucks. I want I want I get 100 bucks. I want I want I get 100 bucks
You did what?
I get 100 bucks