but that would be that would be you lying. You understand? Dude, the two best things at
BlizzCon were World of Warcraft Classic, something they did more than a decade ago,
and Warcraft 3 remastered a 16 year old game. And the third best thing is that Mike Morheim
stepped down before the company turned into a dogshit show. Oh my god. Dude, the mic is hot,
man. The mic is hot. You got a hot mic. What the fuck? Oh, dude. Everybody's already
saying that. Oh my god. Somebody says hot bod. No, hot mic. Oh, hi guys. You know who this is.
Sometimes it really be like that. Yeah, well, we're not playing a Blizzard game right now.
We're playing another game. You know how when you're a sweaty tryhard and you get like
gamer gunk on your controller. Oh, I know that. Tell me about it, man. I have about three inches
of gunk on this controller from all the Soul Calibur I've played. It is disgusting. I mean,
at what point do you just put that underwater and like shake it around with like soap and
stuff? Well, I stopped using it because I got a different one. But now that I like,
because I have to use this one for Lethal League, I've gone back to it and it's like,
wow. I think I could spread a disease. I think this could be ground zero. Oh my god.
What even is gamer gunk? Like, it's disgusting. Is it like sweat that just cakes on over like
years of time? Years? This took a few days. Yeah, but it wasn't, you didn't have gamer like
that. That was like years. These are my excretions. I like shake your hand. I don't
like that. Well, you know what? If we shook hands for like a day, you'd get all my excretions.
But I think one shake isn't enough. Did you make a tweet yet? I don't tweet anything. You
don't have a tweet yet about your story? I should, honestly, because I've people have
been asking me like every time I look at my chat for the past week and I said,
do you know Lethal League? Well, apparently you are stet abs. Lethal League with stet abs
then maybe Fred dead too. I don't, I auto, I don't know what happened.
Lethal League with stet abs. I don't understand. Well, then you're going to be germ bad.
All right. Let's move this over here. Are you like, do you even do like an intro anymore?
Or do you just say like, who cares play? What is, what is, what is it like now? Like,
how are you? Um, I gave up a long time ago. Let's go this way. Okay. Hey everybody. Welcome
to the stream for another edition of wacky Wednesday, where we check out the latest
goofiest games today. Lethal League. And boy is this one wacky. Oh, I burnt my mouth. Oh,
okay. Are you ready? So I, how do you, I remember we just did like, we did a test.
We did a test to make sure it works, you know, we did, we did it. And then you left the game
and I have to do it again. No, you're like, yeah. Like, are you, are you ready? Are you in
the game? I'm ready. I'm ready to be joined. So you should, should I give like a rundown of
what Lethal League is? You know what? Go for it. Tommy Pickles. Okay. So Lethal League
is a series of back and forth. It's a never ending struggle between two forces.
You've got the red team versus the blue team. Well, nobody dies here. Everyone lives. It's
just a game of back and forth and never ending struggle ball. You got blue team versus red
team. I'm on the blue team. He's on the red team. And there's a ball that signifies
a spherical entity and it goes back and forth between the two never end. Just press
press. I was waiting for the story. Okay. So there was, there is no story. I like it's called.
I just woke up. You wake up at 3pm. No, wait, no, wait. It's 1 30. I didn't just wake up.
Okay. I don't know how time zones work. Also you drink hot coffee in the desert.
Yeah. What's wrong with that? You don't drink iced coffee. I look, it's you save money. I
play ping pong. You save money. If you drink, if you make your own coffee, like I used to
drink a Dunkin Donuts every day. Good. Keep doing that. By the way, if you guys didn't know
what this game was the back and forth between two struggling places and whoever gets hit
first is the one that gets their health taken away. Hey, you're not going to get that one.
I'm sorry. It's about, it's about two struggling forces. It's so confusing when it's that fast
and you can also make it go through walls. Yeah. So everyone's got it. You've got a
special ability. Uh, his special ability is being a fucking cheater. What's that?
Is that a smash ball? Smash ball. It's a smash ball. Oh yeah. They edit power-ups.
What the fuck? I don't know what that is. What does that do? Oh, oh, oh, oh my God.
I don't understand what it's doing. It's, it's your superpower where it's going through walls
and now you know how confusing it is. Jesus Christ. I hate that ability.
What even, what is your, wow. Mine like curbs it and it's, it's not, it's not anything.
What, what, what does yours do? Like just that maybe curbs it. Show it to me. Show
people what that was. That was best special in the game. What are you talking about?
Ow. Oh, he's reading the summary of the load of the rings. Fuck one to find them. One to
bind them and one to shine them. The speed of the ball affects like hit damage. Oh fuck. Oh
my God. Oh my God. Oh yeah. And you can hit the people's dead bodies. Very important.
Oh, that's right. Oh my God. But like, but just for real though, if you don't know
what this game is, it's a red versus blue scenario where I'm playing by myself. Oh,
red, red communist China. That's why my ping pong pad. Wait, did you win? Yeah. I killed
you. All right. Now that we can explain what the game is. So if you don't know what the
game is for the next hour, I just felt fucking caught. I just got this fucking room. I just
got this room and I spilled coffee all over it. God damn it. Well, did it get on like
the nice walnut desk? Oh no, I'm good. We're good. He only lost because he spilled his
coffee. Who are these other characters? Should I be, should I be crocodile Dundee?
You still like crocodile Dundee. Did I? What is this special? I don't remember,
but I know he can, he can hang on the walls. Oh shit. It did get on the desk. Hold
on. I have a, I have a coaster here specifically for this. Oh, I got to take
my shirt off. Oh my God. Is this a web cam shirt off Jerma Stream? No shirt. No,
it's called, it's, it's called really like I spilled on my walnut desk. How much did
you pay for your walnut desk? It was at least like $400. It's a beautiful walnut
desk. I don't, don't swing that at me. I'll know you're going to do it. Okay.
That's good. I can put it back on the coaster. I'm not going to wash this again
later. I'm going to wash it. Okay. Now I got coffee all over me. I'll give me
one more second. You know, it's enough to fighting nations. Oh yeah. He like eats
it. His is really good too. Oh, I just heard you. I just heard you being me.
You're going to die, dude. I had my catcher's mid out. Oh my God. What was
that? You got double hit by it. We, uh, if you attack at the same time,
sometimes you, uh, you're like double hit it. What did I say? Nice for,
Oh, there's an emo button. I don't remember what it is.
Ooh, nice throw. Oh, I thought I had it. Tommy Pickles burst five. Whoa. That was
weird. That was a weird one. That is so strange when you do that. Oh my God.
Wow. What's the button? It's, I don't know. I want that to be my thing on my
screen. I'm not going to tell you. You always were a freaking selfish lover.
Oh my God. You've been practicing.
Wouldn't it be cool if Blizzard like announced this game instead of Diablo
Immortal and then lethal league blaze had a player base. Well, another funny
joke you could make is if Val bought this company and then put it out again.
What happened to PC gaming? What happened to it? Dude, I was saying this the other
day, um, 2019 and beyond get ready for the weird times where Val is going to
start releasing better games than Blizzard. It's about to happen. You
heard it. This is a new character. I'll try this character. Uh, I messed
with her in training. She like, she puts the ball in a bubble and slows
it down and then it, when it wears off, it speeds up again. Oh, that's
cool. Oh, for those of you, for those of you, German might on the German side
here, uh, we're going to be, uh, I got, I got a couple of bounces for you
here after playing lethal league. I'm going to give you some updates on the
green screen. Those of you, German might sit here in the German channel.
What the hell? Yeah, it's okay. It does a weird slow thing. It has like
three phases to it. Wow. Okay. That's pretty cool. I got it. I got it. I
got it. I got it. Why did I just do, I, I got it. I, I got it. I got it.
That just was, Ooh, that throw was actually pretty nifty. Oh, how did you
catch that? I just went the wrong way. I swung the wrong way. Did I hit
by that? Yeah. Oh, smash ball. What the heck? Come on. Give it to me.
Ooh, just homing missile it in. I'm Satan. I'm Satan. I don't know. What
does it do? I don't know. I think I'm Satan. Is it? Oh, I think it
changes too. What the fuck? Yeah, that's actually pretty stupid. I
thought it was a really dumb power, but once you get that fast.
No, it's my ball. What am I doing? Like cast. I'm like throwing confetti
at you. What the fuck am I doing? You're dying. Oh God. Not for long.
All right. Let's bring this to the stratosphere. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Some of this I saw in the sewer stage. If you get the ball a certain
speed, like a monster comes out of the sewer in the background.
Oh really? That's pretty cool. Oh my fucking God. That was the
easiest thing ever. I just lost it. Whoa. I'm doing it. I'm doing
it the wrong way every time. Fucking God damn it. I'm a football
player. Oh, that's weird. Oh my God. That's real weird.
I don't like that. Watch out. Oh, I don't know where it is. These
old man eyes. I think, I think for the, the sake of how things
used to be back in the good old days, the old stir, the old
German, I think we have to make a bet. Oh no. If you win,
I'll stop DDoSing you. Oh my God. That's like.
That's like, that's too close to home here right now. I want to
be the yellow guy. What about if I win? You just, no. Okay.
All right. If you, let's go to the, the pad room. Give me,
give me like a round of think about that. Cause you just,
you just gave me like an impossible scenario. No, it's
not. We have to get like five warmup rounds. You gotta learn
the game. Actually like on second thought. Oh, I mean,
yeah. Like we shouldn't do it this time. Why would you
stand in front of it? I'm dying. You need to stand in
front of it. Hold on. I'm dying. You don't even on
second thought. If I win.
Okay. This game requires so much concentration. Like there
is no like funny commentary. No, there is. Well, what's a
funny commentary? Yeah. The funny commentary is I think it
has made so much noise that I just shook the balls.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes. Oh, fuck me. Oh,
fuck me. No, no, no. Cause it hit the wall. It goes up
and down when it hits the wall. This is the scariest game
ever. It really is. It was like that before too. Oh,
no. Are you trying to hit me? No, I was trying to hit
it right when it came out. All right. We got just a
stand over there. Ow. Ow. All right. Well, I didn't want
you to hit twice. Go all the way to the edge. Let's
try to get the monster to break through. Oh, no,
that was only on the sewer. What? I don't know if the
other stages have anything like that. I'm trying to
speed it up. Oh, my fucking God. All right. We just
replay. Forget it. Let's give you a free kill.
Hey. Shit. Shit. I can. I can tea bag you. Very
good game. So let's explain the game. So pretty
much how it works. So you got two sides, right? You've
got red team versus blue team. And it's a red team's
goal to hit the blue team's player with this
spherical entity. It's a it's a it's a it's a big
it's a it's a large circle that there's probably
an easier word to say, but it becomes away from
me right now. It goes back and forth at pixels
on the screen and you have to try to hit the
other person's team with that. The protractor
when you when you take a protractor and you go
around in the circle with the I just said circles
and remind the joke is over. I don't that was
a joke. No, I was trying to not say the
fucking word ball or sir. I don't even know
what I was trying to say. I can't you
understand. It's like being speech jammed trying
to play this. No, I don't. I don't. I was
going for something and it just it just wasn't
going to work out. I summoned the monster. I
didn't see it. How did you not see that? Oh
because I was focused. You didn't see the
monster. Really? I was going to grab that
shit. You wish you grabbed it. Take this.
Sure. Holy fucking hell. He didn't come out
that time. He's he's picking up a little
bit. Oh, that was a good play. Oh, that
was a bad play. And that ability is a rough
one. Oops. The germamites. Haha. Ban that
guy for life by the way. I don't want to
die. Alright, so if hey how about instead
of like jokey like stick the knife in
and twist it jokes. Yeah. What do you
actually want to do here? I don't know. I
think everything in your life has lost
value to you. There's nothing I could
offer you that you don't already have.
You're such a big germa now. High in the
clouds with his head and his ego. What
can I possibly offer?
How about that? You know, I got a new
place. You know what I could use right
now? I could use some new curtains
here. New place. Yeah, why don't you
have your real friend italics get
them. Hey, you got a new place too.
Don't you need some new curtains?
But perhaps. But is this the curtain
battle? Yes. Okay. Okay. Yep. See he I
the candy man said yep like four times.
I thought you heard it. Yep. You're
cheating. Nice throw. The thing that's
different this time is both terrible.
I tried to grab that shit. Oh, you
fucking lobbed it over at me. You
fucking lobbed it over at me. I keep
doing that. Not this bullshit. I
remember this shit from last time we
played. You like then you then you
get out of the way. I remember that.
Come get it. That slowed down so much.
Why? Oh my fucking lord. What am I
thinking? What am I thinking? Oh my
god. So is that is that one curtain?
Two curtains a set? You get you get
one side. Okay. One side. What does
that mean? Did get one side. Yeah, but
you get a double window. That's one
curtain for one side. One of the double
windows. You always wear a cheapskate.
I want to summon the guy. So let's go
to the wait this one here? Yeah. Is
it this one? Yeah. No, not this one.
Well, it's too late. So you get
one side of one curtain. Oh my
lord. Aye yi yi yi yi.
Can I get can I get? Oh, I just got
mortal combatted. I just swept your
leg over and over again. I really stood
up into it three times. I don't know how
you control standing up in this.
Catch it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it.
Nice. Stop it. What's happening here?
You're a bull hog. I was just waiting
on this side like it'll come here
eventually.
What the fuck am I doing? What's the
taunt button? I don't know, but you
better stop pressing it.
It's too fast. I can't get it.
I don't like this game. Get him.
He just ayah. That makes me so happy.
Is it ayah? Yeah. Why does that
make you happy? Because that's
that's what all the old Chinese men
play say during ping pong.
Is it? Yes. That's why we play
ping pong. I played like a week
after I moved here and it's been a
while though. I haven't gone back.
My chat knows that I showed up. I
paid five hundred dollars for a year
membership and never came back.
Well, you sure you sure sound like
you know what the fuck you're
talking about.
Like press mute here. Let's mute it.
No, we fucking don't. Wait,
there's a store? What?
There's a store in this? I think
you can buy characters. I caught
that one on the edge. Oh, I thought
I timed that right. What a bunt boy.
Damn it. Oh, did I catch it?
Yeah, I did. Oh, God, I hate that.
Oh, my God, I got caught it. I
thought I thought I got hit. I got
hit. Oh, you did. You did get hit.
No. Oh, I thought you did get
hit by it. Sometimes your
character does this thing where he
crunches forward and looks like
it's hit. Yeah. Yeah. Sometimes
it'd be like that. You have fun
over there. What? How did that
hit me? Oh, oh, you don't know
nothing about curving the ball
and spin. Oh, you don't know
nothing about spin. That bounced
around. I thought I turned. I
turned. I turned around. That was
bullshit. What the hell was that?
I wish the other boys unlocked.
They have like the giant boombox
boss you could play as. I think
yeah, you get like currency
though, don't you? There's some
kind of currency thing. Dude, I
don't know. I'm going to go try
somebody else. I'm going to try
skateboard man. I've been playing
him a lot. Like we can unlock
different modes in the store
apparently. Oh, yeah. Remember
there was a big ball mode. Oh,
was there? Yeah, there was a
giant ball mode. My stream labs
has been turned off this whole
time. It's like I don't even know
how to fucking stream. Your what
was turned off? Sorry about my
stream labs. Oh, what is this
special movie? Skateboards
around. I don't remember. What are
these days? I'll get it. Oops.
Brain. Kick flip. Kick flip. Damn
that. Oh my God. When you all just
like jump around like idiots.
Wait, what is that? Hold on a
second. That's a different move.
One of them is throw probably. No,
okay. That's just different move
for a bunt for a second. I was
like, what the hell is it? Left
trigger. No, there's anything else
do anything. Are we missing
something like that? Like I'm
trying to figure out what game
and he just loves the ball.
Bunt hit throw in your special.
That's it. What? That hit me. Yeah,
nice internet man. My internet. Yeah,
I know it's not good. Well, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
that's not true. The internet is fine
here. It's a great internet. Great
speeds, fast speeds. It's just the
company that makes it. Well, they
don't make the internet. Nobody makes
the internet. It's like just data
that travels through tubes. But the
company that's responsible for moving
the traffic, the internet traffic is
having a little bit of a problem
right now as you can plainly see.
It's not good. There we've been
informed that it is going to get
fixed and maybe soon enough here you
will. You'll see it and I just
fucking won the goddamn game. I did
great thing. I swung in the opposite
direction on every ball
because I won the last two in a row.
Do I delete your curtains that I
gave you and then I just never
agreed to another deal? No, you
never agreed because we're going to
agree that I'm going to go to my
main.
All right, let's do let's do one
more and see if we can like get
another game mode.
Okay, like how much is another
character?
I think you might have to go
through the story mode to unlock
characters.
Oh, really? I don't know. This one.
No, I want to ready up. X. I tried to
click the ready button.
It's X. It's not X.
Okay, well never mind. You're X. It's
one thousand.
You buy characters with the sparks
you earn while playing the game.
It's a thousand bucks. So we're
almost there. We've played like 30
minutes.
A thousand bucks DLC. Oh, you don't
know nothing about the spin.
Oh, look at those omnics in the
background.
Oh, speaking of overwatch. So what do
you think about the new character?
I think it's just McCree without his
flashbang, which is how he should have
been originally.
Oh, you don't know. Not this time.
You're not going to go backwards
on me this time.
Oh, I don't know if I like this
character. It's the character. It's the
fucking character.
Oh, that's the character. No, the
character. This mallet's too heavy.
Yeah, the heavy. The mallet's just
really heavy. It's just heavy. It's slow.
And uh. Oh, please.
That's just. That's the mallet's a
little too big for me.
No, I mean. What if I. People are
going to take that. I'm going to.
Maybe we're going to like take that.
Like that's not what I meant. Like
people are going to take that.
So how often do you itch your nose?
Oh, do I itch my nose? Yeah. I don't
know. Maybe once every.
All right. Or wipe your nose.
Whoops. I quit. The host has quit the
game. All right. Well, fine. That's fine.
All right. So let's go to.
What is showcase? Characters. Oh, we're
like. We're like one coin away from
being able to get one.
How come I don't have 985? That
would have been perfect.
Okay. Well. And the modes cost like
400.
Okay. Free for all teams. Lethal
volley.
Oh, okay. This is cool. This is uh.
It's like tennis or like ping-pong.
Oh, dude. Leave the volleys ping-pong.
You know that. You know that. I'll buy
that.
And then because I'm going to. Do I have
to own it too? I don't think you have
to own it.
Dude, you have to pay to earn how to
play too.
That's why. Secrets that give the
game the competitive edge.
Or like volleyball. Okay. I'm in the
game. Join on me
and we'll play volleyball. Or what?
Yeah, but
volleyball is just tennis. They
dragged the poles up a little bit
higher.
Guys, tennis has been around for
like 2000 years. Yeah, I believe it was
that tennis. Tennis was invented in the.
That invented. No, it wasn't.
No, it wasn't. It was the fucking Ming
dynasty. They fucking played tennis.
Yeah, and when Plato traveled there
he came up with it.
There's uh. There's new evidence to
suggest that Jesus was Japanese
as well and he had a son
and his name was something.
What are you doing right now? I don't
know. I don't know what this is.
Did I just lose?
I. Yes. I guess you have to hit it over.
You can only hit it three times and it
has to come over.
Okay, all right. So don't like jump
around.
If the ball slows down it's not
speed.
You're losing the speed aspect of the
game.
Nothing's going forward. I'm pressing.
Oh, I would laugh if it just landed
right there.
You suck ass.
This is the first time I've ever seen
it.
It's so hard not to just hit it
straight down.
All right, I think we're getting the
hang of this.
But how does that make any sense?
Wouldn't it have just been a point
for me? Oh my god.
What happened? You can only hit it
three times.
Good strategy. I'm thinking I'm
picking up on this.
Stop. I just gave you a perfect ball
to spike.
Oh fuck. Yeah, like when you jump and
press
up you just slam it down into the
ground. Yeah, you just can't. Oh my
god.
You have to be completely under the
ball for it to even be remotely
possible.
Oh no. Can I grab the ball and throw
it at you?
Does that still work?
I think you can still grab here.
Oh, well I just saved that one. That's
what I call a fucking
save.
How do I dive? How do I dive?
No. Why did I jump over it? What the fuck?
I actually really like this game mode.
It's very awkward, but...
No, I just almost died.
I just called you dead. I swear
to god.
I'm just playing simple D. Just hit it.
You just hit it back, you know?
It's because I'm like my fucking
analog like spins me around in
circles.
I'll tilt like one direction and then
I rip the other direction.
Ripping this thing out.
The controllers be like that.
I'm fucking tearing this thing out.
I'm gonna plug in my steam controller.
Do you actually use that?
No, god no. Oh my god no.
Mad Kuzbad blaming the controller.
Yeah, I can blame the controller
because I know that
in my brain I've got these inputs
and this knowledge and this data
that's just like
flying around everywhere and it's so
intense. And then like it has to
translate through my hands
into a controller. That's just like a
middle man.
About how you're too fast of a
thinker and you're too smart.
Yeah, like it has to transfer through
like it has to go through like the
pipeline to my hands and shit like
god damn it. Like just hook me into
the fucking machine. You know what I'm
saying?
Oh nice nice get.
See the pipeline of my brain just
wasn't ready.
See that's what I'm talking about.
My brain's pipeline is just like if
you could just connect a wire to the
back of your head and just like
stare at the screen and like hit out
go go go. Like you have to transfer
of data through your hands to the
controller.
There's too many middlemen there.
It's three hits.
Stop asking what happens. I will
divorce.
Oh boy you're really unraveling here.
Remember everyone's going to keep his
off.
Good one.
Whatever. Oh my god that is so
annoying.
I just tried to like I tried to
like meet the parents here right
there.
I was going to just like fall on spike
it down into your head.
Oh that would I wish you would have
just fucked it up right there.
I'm doing great. See I'm trying I'm
over complicating it.
Oh it always
I did go up. Be able to hit it up
from the air you
goon. Oh my god. I'm gonna win
this. This is the comeback.
No it's not. This is the comeback. I
literally I literally 100% guarantee
you don't. If not I will delete my
twitch channel.
Oh my god. See that's like that's
like
that's like the deal of winking at you
saying the next hand is blackjack
for you sir.
It's like I'm gonna go I'm gonna go all
in. Rematch me. Rematch me. Next game's
blackjack. Next hand.
Next I see I wasn't in the right
skin. This is the skin that I need
to win.
You made that bet a million times.
Yeah I know. So which one let's go
to this one. Construction joy.
Yeah I'm not gonna lose a single point
this game.
Yeah go get it noob.
This is the skin. This is the good one.
Boom.
What the fuck happened with that one?
See you can't press the direction
when you're in the air. Otherwise it
just goes straight to the ground.
Oh I'm not gonna lose a single point
because of you.
Getting a little tough there.
No it's because it yeah it's with
neutral air neutral air that's the
problem. Neutral air is the problem.
I see that's how I lost every point.
No that's not neutral air.
Fucking Jesus Christ almighty.
I'll wait.
No it didn't it didn't go to the
right like I thought it would.
I'm trying to be fancy you can hit
it straight up so if you press up it
will go up.
I'm too scared to do that that's too
much for me.
I did it again he did it again.
See when when you wrote the script
before we started this stream
yeah you didn't think this would be
funny.
What this?
Yeah remember when we wrote the
script and we're like yeah let's not
know how to not hit the ball into the
ground for like 30 minutes and you
were like nah that's not gonna be
that funny.
What are you playing? Yes.
This script.
I swear to god I fucking had it I had
him right there in my grasp and I just
let him go.
Again shit okay I'll try that again.
Now it's tied.
Oh this is too much for me I don't
unravel here come on.
Whoo as as painful as this is and
how stupid we look I actually really
like this game.
I came all the way back there too.
It was the skin.
People were like on the sub reddit just
like in real time going like come back
of the century dude he's coming back
right now and I got like a rush from
it
on the reddit. Yeah like you refresh
like new comments like zero minutes
zero minutes zero minutes you know
I mean
fucking let them all down.
Everyone got banned just vote random
every time because otherwise I think
it makes us wait 10 seconds
for each person to vote I don't know.
Does it?
All right I'm gonna let's let's try a new
game mode after this one.
Get the reddit post ready.
Whatever. You just just whatever.
He's not gonna do it he's gonna fuck
up here he's too far away.
In the name of god was hat what
happened that you did your special
move.
Oh of course he wants to play with
items on.
It's a dead ball it just died.
Deflate bait.
That was Daria from fucking the Daria
intro.
You gotta be fucking kidding me here.
Oh what a recovery the reddit's gonna
be talking about this one for a year.
Oh no oh no.
You're dead.
You're dead buddy. What a fun game.
Oh my god.
That one wasn't a mistake like it
wasn't the same dumb thing we've
been doing that was I thought I had
it.
Oh my god the reddit.
My life for reddit.
A good thing that didn't hit it.
I swear to fucking god dude I'm never
I'm never playing that ever again
enough doing that ever again.
I've come to know how you're gonna
do that shit you can throw it over
every time that's how you do it.
See that's what he does. It's a good
move.
I died. How about a taste of your
own fucking grandpa's applesauce.
No.
I thought I would bunt it over I
don't think I pressed it right.
Oh that was a good recovery.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Every time in the fucking corner.
That was a that was a conflict in the
middle there.
One more point. You would have just
lost right there.
No mother. Thank goodness gracious.
It comes down to this burst 18.
Hot hot hot hot hot hot hot too hot.
Too hot hot.
Too hot.
Actually really again I'm a broken
record but that's really fun.
All right let's go let's let's give
you a character. Did you see how many
points we had?
No I got 1400. All right we got uh
we got all right we have Mega Man boss
Fat McCree and then like a
Dr Wily.
I want to play Doombox because
he's so big and that's how I am.
I just keep getting bigger and bigger.
So I'm getting Doombox. All right I'm
going to do the Mega Man boss.
This is like cut man. Told you.
Okay. I was seeing the game again.
All right so like I got this dude.
Okay cool. I could not afford a game
mode. We're just going to unlock it.
Now we can unlock how to play two by
the way. Yeah but I know how to play
two.
Oh are we red? Oh only three
costumes here.
Two three uh four. Let me be green guy.
What is what mode is this? I couldn't
afford another one since volleyball.
Oh well there it is started. Okay
that's a good start.
Oh I can't double jump but I get a
float.
What I'm too big. I'm too big.
Yeah your pit box is just weird.
Like don't even fucking. I swear on
everything that I've ever done
that that was like I was said I was
desperately trying to make that not
happen.
Oh god I thought it would bounce far
enough.
I got these big arms for nothing.
He's so he's too big for this shit. I
can't get it out of the corner.
I didn't even see where that went. Whoa.
I don't know what it does.
Oh oh can I test mine? Oh no I
can't. Yeah you have to build up
that many hits in a round.
It's gonna get over. Nope nope nope.
How many pickles man? I don't like this
character.
Maybe at least not for volleyball
because it's a piece of shit.
Did you break it? You stepped on it. I
just hit straight down.
Oh I was trying to play a little bit
fancy. My throw doesn't gain you
meter.
Holy fuck. I don't know what this
does but I'm gonna do it. No I'm
not. I spent too much time focusing
on the special and I should have just
won the game.
Nope. Shit. It all comes down to this.
No god it's so hard to not do.
I want to hit it forward now you
straight down.
He's kind of doing reddit. Okay let's
play a normal one so we can see what
our supers do.
That sounds a good idea. So do we
rematch or you just join again?
No just play. I can change the game
mode in here.
Oh okay. I can't press rematch.
What? I'm in the character slot. No I
think I have to just rejoin you.
Well no I can't even quit the game.
I believe I'm stuck here forever. It
works for everyone else.
What did you do? I don't know. There's
a countdown on my screen?
All right well what's the countdown
at? Oh it like
count it down you for not selecting
a character. Now we're starting a
game.
Are you sure about that? We're
starting a video game right now. Yeah.
Okay now I can only quit. So you're
going to want to alt f4. I took away my
rematch.
Come on. Son of a god damn. Oh yeah
striker is the other game mode is
supposed to be right here.
Fucking I I I forced quit OBS.
No that has nothing to do with cox.
Jesus god damn it man. Rage quit.
I like oh that's so that I'm so
I'm so angry that I just alt f4ed
OBS.
Like I alt I fucking force quit OBS. I
did like the task man.
I get it. It's not even on the same
window.
Oh can I can I just like lock a
window to never be like removed you
know what I mean? Windows 11
make it happen. I can't wait for
Windows 11. It's going to be so much
better.
Don't worry they're going to skip
two versions and they'll come up with
like Windows 15.
All right I'm back. I'm going to join
your game.
He what a noob. It's weird too for
having power ups on.
Like there aren't that many of them.
Oh yeah and there's a minimum ball
speed you can set.
All right so you you know what?
Yeah. All right coming in.
Oh good thing we're gonna have two
streams here now.
God damn it like such like a
bonehead accidental like just kill
OBS. Hey hey give yourself a break.
You've never streamed before you
know it's been a long time.
Yeah I raised the volume on music. I
saw people saying that they couldn't
hear it so I put it up a little bit.
I just listen I heard you say hit alt
f4.
What is that? Is that your special?
You turn into an electronic device?
I don't know what this does.
Oh I think I like I have no idea what
that does. It goes into my hand.
It looks like it comes back to me.
Yeah.
Well let's see what yours does.
Nothing.
No that must be like a proximity
thing. It must like knock me around
or something.
Maybe you can change directions. The ball
homes
into you apparently when you do that.
I don't I don't I guess I don't know.
Wow that killed me.
Yeah it fucking murdered me.
Do you have like extra speed on the
ball or extra power on the ball?
Are they like actual stats like that?
I don't think so.
Oh my lord. Oh my god.
Oh my goodness I didn't hit the ball
once.
Yeah I have no idea what that's doing.
Whoa whoa okay. Oh he's got like a hook
arm.
I hooked to it after I hit it.
Strangely enough.
Hey what the fuck was that?
I don't know. What did I get? What did I get?
What's my Mario Kart? Oh god.
No stay away from me. No. I'm afraid
to even go near it.
I okay I just get done. What happened
there? It. I'm confused.
It got bumped it somehow and then
when it hits the ground it resets
to me and I guess you didn't hit it.
Football's the worst power up. Is it?
Doombox uh. He seems very uh hard to
use. He seems like the worst character
you could possibly have. He's big
and everyone's saying his special is
homing so that just means you know
where the ball is gonna go
which is bad. Maybe. Come back to
volleyball.
Doombox special shoots the ball
straight at the enemy.
Yeah so that's what I'm saying it's like
you you know where the ball is going to
go so it's bad.
I think there's a there's a few people
that are telling you that you might
be uh wrong about this statement
because apparently he's very good.
Well you know what I'm telling you
is that um who are you going to
believe twitch chat or me?
I mean apparently the best player in
lethal league mains Doombox so
I I don't know I mean what does
that say? Because that guy is a
boombox and he just plays him
because he associates with the
character.
Oh we're doing this thing again? Yeah I
like this.
No I couldn't reach it. Oh my god.
He was a little sloppy he was a little
sloppy.
Oh he's getting a little sloppy. It's
because my ping pong paddle has horns
on it.
Well nice fight. He's getting a little
sloppy. I didn't hit it straight to
the ground.
That time I did.
Did I just re? No I didn't.
I was trying to knock it back. I wasn't
thrown to the wall where it just
doesn't even bounce.
Oh my god he's gonna fuck it up
again.
It's in slow motion. Stop with the
funky shit and just get it over there.
What?
Go straight down. Straight down.
Straight down. Not even at an angle.
Straight fucking down.
I don't even how is it impossible?
Oh shit. Oh there we go. You accidentally
pressed forward so you're gonna hit
straight down. Not even. Why did I set
you?
I was like he's not gonna expect this
button. Why would anyone do this?
Why would anyone do this? Okay.
Up. Up. No. Oh fuck.
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
Hey I'm ready. My brain is prepped.
Oh wowie man. Wowie. That was actually
really great.
That was a great volley. I mean it just
was. Nobody can say otherwise. They just
can't.
Oh that's not so much though. That one
not so much. That was not so much.
Nice. 600 experience points. I wish I
could have. I could unbind
forward. You might be able to.
No because I wouldn't be able to walk
forward. What's the uh what's the other
game mode?
Strikers which is you have to defend
against the thing but if you buy it
you have to be the host and I put it
into your game last time.
Should we learn to play again? There
has to be something either we don't
know. I'm buying it.
Okay but I'm saying how to play.
You're gonna have to be able to
host.
No well then just play another
couple because. Because I can't afford
it.
All right let's see what's what's this
uh learn to play two.
You do it too. I think it just
watch my stream.
Open up my stream. Watch my stream.
Teaches you the the ball parry.
All right so here we go. You can
bump by holding. You can you can aim
bunts by holding left or right.
Nice elaborate scheme to get one plus
one viewer.
You can also aim bunts down
advanced okay.
Bunt down by pressing B and holding
down. Okay nice all right you can
bunt down. You didn't know that.
I knew that. Hit the ball back and
forth at high speed.
Okay you probably didn't know you could
do that.
You can see when the ball would
release on the boombox.
Oh you probably didn't know that.
Yeah so you can see what the ball
would release. I knew that.
Did you? How come you didn't say
anything about it?
So I thought you knew. You can parry
if your opponent tries to hijack your
ball.
I'm doing this so you don't have to
pay for it. To activate your parry
hit the ball and press B.
You didn't know that. I told you that
before you started the stream.
You did you did not know hitting the
ball and then pressing B.
I've never seen you do that move one
time. Because you haven't tried to
steal the ball from me once.
This didn't happen. Look at this. This
like animation didn't happen.
You didn't even know that. When you
serve the ball it automatically
parries.
So remember it depletes your energy
bar in case you were curious.
So you can grab the ball by the way.
You're watching? Yeah I'm watching.
Okay so if somebody's parrying you can
pull the ball out of their hand.
I didn't know that. Well look something
else you didn't know.
Now you know. It's right stick to say
all the emotes. You were looking for
this.
Now you know. See okay that was
160 dollars.
I'm ready to play. And so are you. So
you don't have like we
you don't have to play for it now. I
totally don't have to play for it.
Okay join game. I kind of like the
cut man. Cut man? His special is weird to
me.
I don't see how you would use his
special in volleyball.
Oh you're really on this volleyball.
I'm on this volleyball thing.
Okay you really like this game mode.
Think of all the strategy. Think of
how hard you can hit the ball
straight down.
Ready. Oh home court advantage.
I'll try. I thought you had a
little bit of a different approach
there.
Oh that was a good one. Yeah reach over
the net. Good job.
Nice. Nice. See we're getting better at
this.
I'm gonna be best volleyball player in
North America.
Yeah I wish. I tell you know what and
that just you said you talked so I
couldn't play. Oh sorry. Sorry. I
won't talk anymore.
Okay okay Trolla didn't turn to the
other way. I was quiet.
Just just quiet. I was gonna hit it
straight down. See I talked and then
you fucked it up.
Damn. Let's roll. That was a that was a
move you did there.
Oh what? It sped up off the wall. So
weird.
That was weird. That was strange.
Back at your own net.
That you see if you that was a nice
move. You got you you
messed with my expectations there.
Trying to emulate what you did. Great
move. I'm gonna try it.
Oh don't you dare. I what it wasn't
close enough for that. I wasn't close
enough for that apparently.
Apparently. I don't use this character.
I gave up. I'm not using him again.
He's a good character. His body's too
weird for me.
This guy's body is just so strange.
His tail is all the way over there.
His face comes out.
He's like this Donald Duck looking
motherfucker like no I'm done with
him.
Really be like that. Wow. It made you
they make you even buy new songs.
No he's a good character if it's not
in that.
He's just too he's too long. Dink.
You parried me didn't you.
Yep. I thought you're being real cute.
Well the serve always parries.
You just read that. I mean I didn't
that was about two minutes ago.
Just reading it would be like right
now. Got it.
You ready for this play?
I heard that like a two seconds later.
I heard me myself screaming.
I swear to fucking god.
What is happening?
I just I can't I don't I can't do it
anymore. I like lost my mojo into the
game.
I think it's this character. I don't
think this character is very good for
this. No it's
it's this game mode it's like too
deliberate. Oh you have to like
you have to think. No.
What and and I hit I hit the ball
I hit the ball backwards to myself.
You hit the top of the net.
I you know what I like hit the ball
went backwards.
Went the other way there backwards.
I'm not sure what fucking happened on
that one.
I want I want to play the regular game.
Oh my god fine.
This is like this is like the star
game mode and you all know what I'm
talking about.
This is the star game mode where
after the stream
he's going to put like a hundred
hours into this game mode.
I left because I can afford the other
game mode.
Now I can't leave again. I don't want
to all tap
OBS and kill it. All right I'm going
to make this run into this real
slowly here. Well I'm hosting.
Hold on hold on. Okay I think I'm safe.
Oh it's it's the goddamn star mode.
Are there AIs in this? I think so.
All right coming in. Do we do you have
enough for the new game? Yeah yeah
I'm hosting already.
Oh yes I was gonna say that
striker's play needs four people
for it to be good
but I don't see where I can add AI.
He used to be able to I know that
because we did it.
Maybe I guess we could just do quick
jump.
Also the star wants to play with AI
instead.
I don't know if you're supposed to
beach ball if it's probably not.
So what is this? You're defending
your
your hole. Oh okay so
can you hit your own hole?
I'm sure we'll find out. Yeah um
because if you can put it in your
own like hole that would be bad. Yeah the
beach ball sucks for this.
Hold on let me see can I can you
can you put it in your own like
like I don't think you can. I mean
we're
kind of testing how these the game
works.
All right I get it. That's cool. No you
can't. Yeah
it's really good.
Yeah this is rough with only two
people as well.
What oh oh nice score.
What? Nice score buddy. What the
fuck happened there?
Oh no burst five. You kind of need
like a goalie huh?
Yeah. Where's where's your new best
friend italics?
Uh I think he's downstairs. I don't
think he has this game though.
But that would be three. Oh well then
I could get someone
else. I have friends I think.
I think I have friends. That would be
unfair.
How would that be unfair? Oh god.
With like a two.
How how does this not hit your goal?
I pulled it away right before he
hit it.
No. Okay that's freaked me out. The music
just stopped.
Yeah the music timed it perfectly for
like.
Don't you dare. The world. Why don't
you like you just block.
Oh that's what we call a super shot.
That's what they call a super shot.
I'm just like going don't you dare.
I'm just like posing in front of
you.
That super is really good at this.
Yeah it is good for this for sure.
Oh my god I was trying to farm super
to see if I could do some.
You're trying to do a super shot but
come on man.
Oh my god that is so good.
I fucked it up. It's all right.
What?
Holy shit. Holy shit. Oh you caught it.
Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Ah that was just too high for me.
Damn again too high.
It feels like we got better. Kind of.
No.
Tried to be fancy. All right trying to
see how it works with the baseball.
I can't believe those plays are legal.
I'll try.
He'd probably be really good here.
Yeah just keep picking op characters.
Uh see I keep just changing
characters but you're playing the
same character.
He plays ping pong. You're getting to
know every inch of that one character
where I'm spreading my knowledge
across multiple different people.
Oops that was. Wow that was a pretty
cool move.
I'll give you that. Okay I saw you.
All right I see what you're doing here.
That's an interesting little play.
Ain't gonna work again though. I
mean you know.
Offense defense. Oh my god that is
some bullshit.
I guess at that point I just need to
defend. Why is it still going?
It went over it. Oh my god.
Oh my god. I can't get it.
Oh my god. I can't touch it. I can't
touch it.
Holy shit. I tried to grab it too
but it said
it said no. You're lucky.
I was like holy shit what happened
there.
Oh good play. You gotta parry it.
Oh my god. There's the monster.
Goodness gracious.
No. Oh we got. I gotta cheat.
Oh fuck that was too high.
Burst. Nice save.
Intensity.
No no no no no. Damn it. Damn it. Damn
it.
Nice play. Oh my god.
I forgot about throws. You can do
them.
Uh oh. Good video game.
This is like. I love this game.
They're so hyper focused they can't
communicate.
That's the excuse I keep giving about
me and my wife.
Wait. Every time we do couples therapy.
We're just too hyper focused.
I'm ready. Actually why would you want a ring box on this?
I'm gonna hit it to you. He is bigger.
He is a lot bigger. No you stay with
the green.
No there was a raid came in. Who
raided here?
I did. Oh critical did.
Hold on wait. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Just pause the
game.
Thanks a lot dude. You still here?
Critical streaming. How's it going?
I did. I did. I did. Well thanks a lot
man.
We'll have to hit you up after this.
See how things are going. Wow. What I'm not allowed to have other friends?
No but like when you're on a date
with someone you really shouldn't be
looking at other girls.
Hey fuck you. Uh oh boy.
Oh you just went straight ahead. I was
like this one's coming down because
that's all we can do is hit it
straight down.
What? I'm just playing fundamentals
right now man. I'm just fucking playing
fundamentals.
Ah yeah fundamental that. Jet Set
radio up my ass.
I'm just gonna play fundamentals. It's
all about the fundamentals dude. You
gotta get back to the basics.
See and I thought I didn't play
fundamentals that time and you did.
Oh my god.
Oh you know what you know they say
this is such a germa game mode.
Oh fuck it's gonna do the thing.
Get in there. Nah a little early.
Oh what a what a germa game mode.
What a fucking sweaty tryhard over
there. This is germa game mode.
Hey let's keep playing this game.
Yeah okay let's keep playing this one.
We can do the we can do the other one.
No because you might have to think of the other one.
I'm getting this come back.
Just go back to basics. Come back. I
don't like her specialness.
Oh fundamentals it's all about those
fundamentals. I need this rematch.
Are we doing it again? I need this rematch on my main.
Okay. I'm with my my main skin and not
in your home character's stage.
Why not? That doesn't mean anything.
It does. Well then it's all random. I
didn't pick it. No you get plus 10
speed on your main stage.
You see you'd like that to be true
wouldn't you?
You would like that to be true all
those years.
All those years of star beating me
at everything but this not this time.
Hit it.
You gotta let them get one. Otherwise
we'll cry.
Gotta let them get two. Oh my god.
Look out. It's fine. Oh that's okay.
That's okay. That's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. Don't. It's okay.
It's all right. It's all right. All
right. Now you made it a fucking game.
Now you made it a game. Now you made it
a game.
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. I like
my run animation.
A piece of shit. Oh now you made it a
game.
All right. Okay fine. I gotta go
straight carry to the goal.
Oh shit's in my pants. That's where it
goes.
Oh my god. Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Oh you suck. Do I though?
I just I'm not and he let it go
through his legs in the world.
I planned the whole thing. The ball
went through his legs in the world
series.
No. Come on. Come on. Come on. Fundamentals.
And they blew into the world series.
Fundamentals.
God that got cocky at the end there.
Why beat you at your own game?
You gotta let him win one. I mean
he's won one in like four. I mean
come on. It was inevitable. He can't
be perfect every time.
You gotta let him get ten you know.
Just to build up his overconfidence.
That's how you hustle. Then you say
oh the rematch. We'll double
double or nothing.
Oh please. Oh please. Please.
Oh that was a freaky move. That was a
freak. That was a freaky. That was a
freaky eater. I'll tell you that.
You remember freaky eater? How could I
how could you forget? I don't even
remember talking to you about freaky
eater. Well you know my wife is a
freaky eater you know.
No. Oh my god that doesn't hit.
Oh good thing can't score on your own
fucking goal.
I should have ran back to my goal.
I'm just like a such a huge fan of
cheesy potatoes.
Oh you're cooking broccoli. Why are you
cooking broccoli right now star?
I tried to block it.
Harry fucking mayonnaise all over your
face.
You're doing shit.
Oh turning into Peewee Herman. Holy
shit I thought it was gonna hit.
Sometimes you gotta be aggressive.
Sometimes. Oh yeah.
Oh man oh man. I learned that from star.
Sometimes you gotta be aggressive.
Come back. Okay you gotta let them get
10 sometimes.
You let me get 10 I let you get 10.
That's how it works.
By the way level 10 that's a good
good comment you made there.
That's not how friendship works.
You know these guys are wind trading for
views.
That's what we're doing. Wind trading.
No that's that's what everyone's saying
over here.
Wind trading. I spell new characters new
character. What do you mean you spit it
up? I sped it up.
I hope you're ready.
What are you what are you doing? What
do you mean you spit? I don't know.
Okay excuse me here this is this is
not regulation. I mean even if I
lose this it's not regulation.
You can't just lower the hoop because
you're not good at shooting the
basketball.
Oh you cheat.
No please. How'd that not go in? I'm
going to start doing the Vincent
Price laugh here in a minute man.
Oh oops now okay now okay I gotta be
carefully because this
how this happens sometimes a star
gets to the point where he's
he needs to try as hard he's trying
to get this to happen.
He's gonna be totally silent he's
gonna focus he's gonna stop saying
anything funny.
I haven't seen anything funny in
years.
Feels bad man. You want to parry me? I
can go for a parry.
Oh it's so fast. It's like a bomb.
I don't know what to do.
Shit. I thought you were too high.
I was a little bit. Maybe not though.
All right all right.
Holy shit that moved around. Oh you
did a thing with that. You made it
oh okay all right I see. I did a
thing with that.
Oh fucking Jesus. God that's so good.
It starts off so fast.
No I have to double jump for that.
This is a very fun game. This is a
very fun game.
Okay I set it back to regulation.
Are you what? New characters. New characters.
Oh I don't know if I have enough
because I have to buy this game mode for you.
Oh it's shocker from spider-man.
Yeah I can't afford any walls. Okay this guy looks kind of cool.
I mean I think it's just because I've
been winning so much that it's just
giving me extra points.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Am I coming in?
Yep what game mode? Am I? The good game mode?
Uh I mean if you want to like take
the take this back and like start to
embarrass me again you could like
you could do the volleyball game mode
again. Yeah. Build up a little bit
more confidence maybe take us into
the next round you know what I'm saying?
Who the hell? What? Jack the Ripper? No
it's shocker from spider-man
with plugs on his hands. Hmm his name
is grid because he has a grid.
I didn't check the costumes. Oh that
was a mistake. Let's see.
Oh I forgot what I forgot what we
were doing. Yep. Okay this is the
this is the volleyball one.
Whoa that's weird. That's just I just
can't do this one.
I can't do it. Oh yeah. That was fancy.
Aye and I tried and I tried and I tried
and I tried. I got so far.
That's what I wanted to do. No.
No perfects yeah I can't get flawless.
No. I think there's one too many.
Yeah it's one too many.
Some things never change. I like this
guy's kind of cool looking though
his character design.
Shut up Jeremy shut up.
Stop talking. He's the worst character
design by far.
What what's wrong with his character
design? What you hate him why?
What's wrong with his character
design? He's cool looking. He looks
like shit.
He looks like corn somebody said. He does.
So he's cool. That wasn't too many
hits give me a break.
Corn he's a corn superhero what you
have.
That's it it's a corn.
Oh you missed it and I missed it too.
Fucking hell. Dude NA corn NA corn.
I press up. NA corn.
Oh you got me with that little back
and forth there. You got me with it.
He got me with it and it was
he got me with it. See you in the
corn field. You found a new outfit to
unlock for raptor.
All right let's see the outfits. Okay
so I can be corn.
Error texture on wall.
Funky. I think I'm gonna be texture wall
error. You kind of have to be corn.
Oh this one kind of hurts. Let's try
this one. I've been playing too much soul
caliber that they just look like bad
characters
people create it. Random grid thrown
on them.
Well it's not. I feel like this stage has
a higher ceiling.
And I tried to go I just like
cracked my neck so hard. I like almost
just this whole stage is just bigger.
Damn it. Damn it man. I just got no
patience. I got no patience.
And I try I got I got no patience man.
You got to do 100 000 miles per hour.
100 miles per hour or or bust.
Oh no patience. I had no patience on
that one. See if I just waited I
could have got it.
I went the wrong fucking way. I have no
patience. All right just let just let
him play himself.
Don't even move. What the hell. I tried
to press x.
It was too hard to press a different
button. I just my fucking fat fingers
went all over it.
Oh by the way um if you if you don't
know how the game mode works
and the game works. So there's two
sides. All right you got red versus
blue
and there's a ball that is just goes
back and forth between the two
entities.
Yeah that was a good one.
And I'm fucking just can't do this
like game mode.
I can't do it.
All right like all right let me
explain.
It's volleyball. No no but like the the
core video game itself.
It's like hey here's a porsche and
you're on the autobahn.
But please go 10 miles per hour sir.
It's like no you're gonna you're
gonna go a fucking hundred.
No. So what you're saying is you
you spent all the money on a porsche
and you finally you know you have a
porsche
and then you get there and it
doesn't even have internet.
No no you had you buy a porsche and
it's like oh by the way this thing
can go zero to a hundred and point two
seconds. It's like holy shit wow.
And then they put the porsche between
like one old lady in front of you and
one old lady behind you.
And so you can't go anywhere. You just
to go 15 miles per hour on the
autobahn.
What does that have to do with this
game? I don't get the comparison.
Because it's fast. It's a fast game
with like back and forth crazy
speeds and then it's like I gotta
drive behind an old lady.
What's the old lady in this
scenario? This this game mode
volleyball.
We're playing it again and then we
can play your stupid
casual game mode. Oh yeah.
Oh the casual mode. Game mode is an old
lady.
So yeah are you the old lady in this
scenario?
No you are. Because you want to go so
slow and I want to go
fast on the fucking highway. That ball
went pretty fast
right by you. I mean why even play
the other game mode if you can't
play the slow one? I think it'd be
too much for you.
Turn around. Psycho driver.
Psycho. Psycho driver.
What?
It's all about speed. That's gonna
keep moving around.
I man I saved you.
Just keep driving. I'm going too fast.
Out of the middle.
I don't like how the stage is
actually moving the camera.
Why did I hit it again?
Why did I?
Why did I do that again?
Why is it kind of good? I hit it. I hit it right there. It's done.
I did it. Okay I'm fine.
Wow. Turn around. You're jumping around
it's it's driving me crazy the way it's
moving the camera. Like this stage is
just like a pixel too big.
Oh look out. That's fucked up because I
have to jump then turn around in the
air to hit it but if you press
forward then it doesn't
it goes into the ground. Well I'm sorry
I have to move. You don't.
Yes I do. You don't have to move.
Don't you understand? Like I'm playing
better now because I'm moving
around.
We're not just going like this.
Wow really? Okay yeah that's really
dumb.
Nice game fucking shitty
developers. Got you.
We're playing on a stage. We're one
more of volleyball because I know
you're you're sad you're stuck
behind this old lady but we have to
play one more
and you're gonna you're gonna vote
for the
the white stage. Okay.
So screen doesn't it still is. Oh but
I have to admit you lost one game.
Like come on man.
Okay nice catch.
Did I just wait did I say oof? I did
not say oof.
Did I? No. Can I aim that down? I'm so
afraid to hit it down.
Got it. That was a great volley damn
bad.
I bunted and you just slammed it.
Ah I did it a little too far away. What was I
doing? What was I thinking?
See you did it too. Because you have to
turn around and you have to press
forward. I'm realizing where the suck
is.
Oh I don't know what happened there
but I'll take it.
I tried. I tried. Don't don't lose it
here. I lost it and I fucking just.
Silent tryhard.
What the fuck was that? What the hell?
That was just return that one.
And I'm ready for the ball. I wasn't
even ready for the ball.
I'm going to shake it off. Sometimes
somebody hits a home run pitcher. Come
on.
Curve. I went I tried to go up and it
didn't do it.
I can't even karamba. I can't even
karumba.
What? Did we both reach through the
you reached through the net. I blocked
you.
I blocked you.
I did it. I did it. I fucking was.
Spin around. You're good. Oh nice.
Good volley. Oh right on the.
I was too busy marveling over the
bounce.
I was marveling over the bounce on
the net and Eddie you did the curve
ball.
Okay what game mode do you want?
Regular.
Regular game mode. I can't rematch
again.
I have to force quit. Wow.
It's a shame. All right don't delete OBS.
Okay coming back. You have to rematch
before he changes the game mode.
Well coming back. Team reptile
joining your game.
I want to try this guy in regular
mode. Okay. I feel like he's
he has potential. Where are we going?
Have we even played here?
Played where? Here. I just unlocked
new stages. Oh okay. Is it still oh
it's still on like super fast mode.
Whoa. He teleports forward and then
shoots it.
I don't. It was because it was my serve
at auto parry.
Oh I was trying to queue up like a
huge one.
Oh I'm afraid you keep meter in between rounds on this one.
It's less climactic when it starts
fast.
Yeah it's a little too fast.
See this is the equivalent of being
on the highway and you. We're doing
tournament regulation.
Regulation tournament. Damn it's not.
Are you gonna main grid corn man?
Where's the other stage?
Um the street. The subway one.
Oh god that's a lot going on in the
background.
What the fuck? Ultra.
Oh god. It's what it bounced like
like three times behind me. Those
bounces didn't make sense.
I'm just gonna let it happen. You know
what I'm saying? Like sometimes you just
gotta let. Whoa.
What? I promise you I did that.
That is so confusing. Yeah that's
really good.
Oh shit I thought it hit you. Did it?
It did. Uh oh. Uh stink ball.
What? I don't know what happened.
You're cheating.
I didn't do anything. You hey you're
the one that you're the one playing
with items. Items are on by default.
Ah I was trying to invisible.
What am I doing? Oh is it invisible?
I guess.
That's weird.
Oh my god does he also say Cho?
Tournament standard regulation match.
Now who put items on?
Do I turn them off?
How is that standard tournament mode?
Because it's on by default.
Oh oh you're going for uh.
I'm going for big boy.
You know what you know what corn is
weak to?
Sound.
That would be crazy. Oh crazy if true.
Ow my head. Oh shit.
Oh where did it go? Damn.
Damn it. Oh my god it double tapped me.
It went bang bang.
Standing up is hard sometimes.
Oh you keep your health between rounds.
I didn't realize that.
Shit. What the hell was happening
there? I know I have a hover I just
okay I hold it that way.
Shit. All right this you have no health
man. I have one yeah I know I'm gonna
make it perfect.
I knew you're gonna do it. I knew you
were gonna do it. I just needed a little
tiny tap.
I knew it was gonna happen too and I
was trying to prepare for it and
preparing for it is what caused me a
problem.
Play this guy. Ready. Wow didn't you
dress up like that for Halloween?
Like this? Yeah with the claw and the
hook.
How would I dress up for a guy for
Halloween? I didn't know who he is.
You don't make any logical sense. I
thought you made this game.
It'd be so weird if I did. Oh what
happened? Did you seriously parry right
there at the end?
Yeah. Oops. Wait hold on wait wait
wait what?
I don't think you can hit it when
it's in the bubble. So what's in the
bubble it can't be hit. I don't think
okay.
That's interesting. That changes things
a little bit makes it that makes her
special better.
Shit. Oh man. Yeah it's pretty good.
That's tough.
That went so fast. I just threw it at
you.
Jumping into this one. Freaking noob.
Just using throws.
The bros. I can't parry it if it's in
there okay.
I like her. Game. Yeah I know what I'm
playing. You don't have to tell me
game.
I feel like uh I feel like star is
gonna play as this character
on his on ranked mode. I used to play
in the real world
with the the roller blades. Really? Yeah
back in the day.
That's pretty cool. Did you actually
roll it around? Do you know how to
roll it?
Yeah I was I went to the skate parks
and everything.
Fruit dooder. An itchy eye and it's
gonna fuck me up.
Itchy eye syndrome here it comes. Nice.
Um so now that this game's uh
like relevant again right
do you think something like this
would show up at EVO?
Um because that would be
how cool would that be? I would love to
see this at EVO but I don't think it
will.
I thought you were either gonna. That'd be
so fun. Just put it in like the
comedy slot right? Isn't there always
like a comedy slot
for EVO? Is there? I don't know. Is there like just a comedy slot?
I mean there's a lot of side tournaments
that are run that aren't on the
main stage.
So that they don't do like a four
fun like just little fun like
session it's all just all competitive?
Uh no. Like what if they think they
got like Burger King to sponsor it
and you got like
like three like meals for like a
week or something?
Free meals for a week. I don't know.
Stand-up comedy at EVO. Yeah. Who's the
best stand-up comedian? They already do
that shit. They do like comedy
of battles. No don't do it. Jesus.
Fuck. Yeah wowee wowee wowee wow.
It was my last life I've been on man.
Oh no.
Oh I don't know what to do.
Oh my god I jumped right into it. I
don't know. I like her but I also
have a much harder time.
I think it's the skin. Does Jerma think
EVO is run by Comedy Central?
Where's the comedy section? Look I I
know I
hold on. Wait let me like explain
myself here. I know that EVO is like
all the major tournaments is where and
all the big ones
and you got like uh Mortal Kombat um
Injustice.
That's the comedy section. Smash Brothers.
Yeah I did you know you don't think I
know this?
Yeah but like what are you talking about?
Like they don't have just like a like a
show match type
game or anything where people just play
for fun? Or is it only only only?
He said side tournaments. I'm saying not
every game is streamed
but there's still tournaments. I'm just
like
I'm just baiting right now. That's
what I'm doing guys. Like just
anytime you say something stupid just
like you're just fucking baiting you
know.
Doesn't matter you know what I'm
just baiting.
Just baiting. Me too. Every night just
baiting.
You really like you really okay it's so
it's been a while since you and I have
like really played a game together.
You've really like dialed up to sexual
humor a little bit haven't you?
You're like a second are you a sexual
humor comedy channel now? I uh
I go to EVO for the sexual humor
comedy
I win every year. Like I don't have a
star making like like like being at
like the sexual comedy show.
Nobody must
damn it. Nitro knockout.
Nice catch. Ah I thought it was gonna
bounce around the other side. Shit
I thought it was gonna go to the left.
Shit. Oh I'm in trouble here. I'm in
trouble.
Come on I'm on my last leg here. Oh
my god.
Ah quit quit hardcore
tryharding. That's what you have to do
in this game.
This is why would you try hard in the
comedy game.
That's what I don't get.
No that's not what I meant and you
know it.
I don't know what you meant still.
Quit taking my words out of fucking
comedy context okay?
Bam bam bam.
Ow. Shit it's always the worst when
you're right in the middle.
Or you can move. Oh you saw that
coming from a mile away didn't you?
Oh my god. What the hell what the
fuck?
That like did a full circle it came
backwards.
Who grabbed it? I did.
Oh I think I think gamer exhaustion is
starting to get in here.
I don't know what happened. I think you
grabbed it out of my hand. I caught it
like right after you hit it I
caught it.
Ow my joints. I need to drink a
stamina potion.
God if only those existed in real
life. Come get some.
Oh come on you bastard you timed it
you waited for it and you flicked it.
You flicked the button and it was in.
Yeah you got you got stamina potions
over there. I don't have any here.
Dude I took a stamina potion right
before this.
And you had the stamina copy. Did you
not? No but
but that but but caught the stamina
coffee puts you up to like a hundred
percent stamina.
But then you drain rate is like plus
a hundred percent. What are you?
So I I would have a hundred percent
stamina.
What? The German that lived in Boston
didn't do drugs.
Why are you bringing us back here? I
don't know. I have fun doing this.
Drugs are bad. I don't do I don't do
drugs.
Don't listen to this dweeb. Oh it's the
beach ball again. I didn't even
realize. I didn't mean to have a
beach ball.
You're not gonna like respond to the
fact that I spelled you dweeb. I
don't
have a problem with that.
Oh you dweeb.
Bunted it for you. Damn.
This beat is pumping. Can I score
a point
real fast? I can't. I tried. Should I
should you? I mean there. Yeah I let
you do it. I was like
I was like you know it's time for him
to get one.
Ah too bad it wasn't at the right
spot.
Ah. Oh fuck fuck fuck. Give me one
that's fucking to beat.
Oh going for a little move there.
Oh just out of reach. Fucking beach
ball.
No. I actually with beach ball I don't
like if you had two people I don't
know how you'd ever score.
That would be very hard. Nice. Unless you
have some
superb extreme donors spotted.
Nice okay he's finally getting into
it isn't he?
Oh that's unfortunate. Damn I was
waiting for the defense I couldn't
get it.
Shit I tried to blunt it up higher
so you couldn't get it.
Okay I jumped over just a little too
high. Oh
I can't believe you grabbed it a
second time. Oh that was it.
That was it.
What game mode? What's the situation? What are we
doing?
Um I don't know what do you think? I
like that.
You having fun? I like that. How long
have we been?
I mean my stream turned off. I turned
off my stream
accidentally so two and a half hours.
22 minutes.
222. You cheated super hard there
which is what because I bumped it.
I just passed it to you. This with four
people would be
I think actually really hard to score a
goal. It would be like just pretty
random.
Yeah it'd be a lot of like mashing
next to the goal post
and getting parries I assume.
It'd actually be kind of doable with
the baseball though.
I thought that was too low. Play lego
island.
What?
That's like just that's just too much.
I will somebody I will never give up
trying to get me to play
lego island. Can you guys play lethal
league blaze?
I don't know. Soon we'll play it
after this.
I'm facing the fucking wrong way. What
the hell am I doing?
I'd be down for lego island to be
honest.
Lego island. I don't think
I can even run that game on my
fucking computer.
Oh fuck whoops a daisy whoops a daisy.
Dinosaur.
Do it like you do drugs. Yeah like
when you get
next to the next sometimes it's hard
to even tell like what happened
there.
I thought you're gonna hit it up.
Oh okay all right nice.
Oh and he literally missed that.
Now that's he has a snort key mode oh
god.
I can't fucking break. So what's the
deal?
What's what deal? Another you want to
keep doing this one? I enjoy this.
Okay I'm gonna change character ah
never mind.
I'm not gonna change character. It's a
very it's a very uh
engaging you know tug of war. It's a very
engaging
game. Tug of war back and forth. I was
like trying to wait for you to do.
Yeah I was trying to wait for you
to do.
We're getting to that next level.
Ability sucks. You already had enough to
use that?
Yeah. Suck dude you suck. I'm gonna do
like the form
formation. Oh oh.
You suck. You suck.
Fucking move. I had to use mine more. That move is so good.
Okay okay see now that I'm now that I'm
close to losing everyone knows from
Soul Calibur then now now's when we
try. Now's when we come back we
kick your ass.
And maybe I'll go there and kick your
ass.
Here's what you know here's where it
really you know balls to the walls.
Maybe you'll see me on the
battlefield and smash to kick your
ass.
Yeah learning from the
learning from the master I see. Does
that thing just auto target?
No I have to I have to aim it. I
have to like actually aim the thing.
Press Q to make Candyman's mouth
move. Well I'm using a controller. Was
it on controller? Are you using
controller?
Yeah. Okay just making sure we're on the
same level here.
I mean you you could have used like
the I'm using keyboard and mouse like
to your advantage you know what I
mean?
Whatever. How would you play this game
reliably with keyboard and mouse?
I feel like it'd be very hard.
Just do it. Just do it. Nike just do
it.
Oh I gotta use that better. Really?
Oh oh shit. That's why we're playing the chief ass.
All right let's see. I gotta be
ready for that one.
And you're just going to teleport it
inside the goal.
No fuck oh no. Okay I gotta watch your
special leader.
Oh I let go of it too early. Damn.
Hold on. What? I'm trying to figure out
like what actually makes me
climb it. Can I do that? No it's his
thing. I think you think I can climb up
it but he like falls off and it's
really weird.
I don't know maybe I can't stand on
the scoreboard.
Okay. I don't know if I can even get it
from you
at that point. Maybe not. Oh fuck.
Fuck. Oh fuck.
No not this time. I was trying so hard
to pay attention to it.
Wow. No this is so stupid now.
It really is. We're just like doing
the thing to each other.
I'll gain meter faster than you'll
gain meter.
Oh it's too much. Oh no.
Almost tied it up. Come on now. Set it
up for me.
I did it the wrong way. I did it the wrong way. I did it the wrong way.
Oh shit I let go of it.
No. All right let's do it.
You son of a bitch. I should have
known you were just
gaming meter there. Oh you fucking threw me out of the bus.
Good game. This is all for the curtains? Yeah we gotta tally up every
single win and loss.
Well then I obviously win. Let's go with
who else would be fun in this mode? Are
we still playing this mode?
Um what's the other one that we didn't
do? Did we do all the game modes?
Maybe go back to original. It's dark in here. I gotta turn the fucking
lights on. I heard what Switch does but I
played him a lot before. There we go. Turn on the lights. There
they are. Hey there they are. All right is
this what we do? Is this regular mode?
We're doing regular mode? Oh yeah he can like hit it over
his head behind him. What was this thing?
Oh somebody said press Q? Well I'm not gonna do that. I'm in the middle of an
intense video game right now. I remember that.
Oh I just my brain just goes to it. I forget what Switch flip is even
doing. When you do a special what does
it do? Do you know? I don't know. Hey do you see in the back right at
the top of the screen in the background?
I know you can't look right now but TF2 play TF2.
Is that what it says? That's what it says. I've got the logo. Oh it's the
oh it's the Team Fortress logo. Is that what that is? Is that
like an is that an homage? What else would it be? I think you
may have found a fucking pretty cool homage dude.
Oh you see that blimp in the background? Please play TF2.
Tense but that's what the the aliens of the monsters the robots come out
of the man-averse machine. Oh my lord. Oh my lord I just watched
myself get hit by fucking four cars in a row.
Oh man do you see that baseball? Remember the Sandman?
No you have to make all the references to Fortnite now that's how
it works. Oh Fortnite? Did you just default Fortnite dance?
No that's been vetoed. That has been vetoed.
Good landing. Hey pick stage landing. Tilted towers.
That was a good initial. You did a good initial there man.
But was it enough? No I'm too big. I'm too big.
I would call it a perfect a perfect forward smash. If his super wasn't dumb.
Are you sure you're like doing it right? Maybe are you sure there's not
something else you need to do? Sure. Wow. Oh though he does get
okay I'm kind of understanding. Okay. Wait you can fly?
You can fly. I can fly. That's really weird. I can fly. I can fly.
Do you have to tap uh just tap A or anything? Just hold A and I'm flying.
Oh shit oh shit. Oh I got hit in the same head.
It's so weird though. Oh I didn't want to taunt.
Well here it is. Oh that was that was close. Can you parry without full
meter? Like I was worried about it. I was like wait he doesn't have full. I
don't know what the rules are here. I know it drains your meter but I
didn't know if you if you need to have the full one.
I don't know that's a good question. Um is someone's asking is there an
option for it to be one hit like the first game? Can you like
make it one hit and you're out? Or is it only HP? Wait what did you
ask? I said is there an option to make
it like the original game? Oh yeah there is.
Oh you can. Yeah. Would you like it that way?
Um we can do it after. Oh it's the rocket.
Ah my brain broke. It's the rocket. And he's gonna build it over there
aren't you? I don't think I like this man.
He's just not for me. He seems a little slow.
Holy fuck. Oh all right. So yeah it goes
just right to the other person. Yeah but people are telling me
that you can bump out of it so that you don't always know that it's going to
come get you and that that helps make them better.
Oh I was a little confused on exactly what happened there.
Oh oh good. We haven't seen this one yet. It's two balls.
It's two fucking balls at the same time.
Oh I'll see ball. Yeah I don't like he doesn't have a ping pong.
And I'll uh use HP turned it off. Somebody said there's a dev in the
chats. Really? Is that is that or are we just
getting named? Yeah no I made this. Don't you remember like the last couple
of months where I've been putting like dev updates to you?
I've been snail mailing them to you. Do you not read them?
Yeah. No I mean I just kind of put them on
like the counter. I think I opened one of them. I
thought it was just bills or something.
Oh he died. He turned it on. I told you. All right. Wow. Now we get to prove just how
bad we really are. Now we have to play like gods. Well I
bunted it and it immediately killed me. Bunt. Oh shit. Oh you bounced it.
Oh boy you bounced it. Yeah he bounced it man. Oh my lord.
What? I thought I had it. Oh is there like a delay after you throw?
Uh it's like a it's like if you do an actual throwing animation.
Ah damn. Okay I need the dev to confirm that my my character actually says
says Aiyah and Cho. Is he actually saying Cho or my hearing thing?
Damn and I tried to grab it out of midair and I was being a little funky.
What? You just made the eye got hit and died noise.
No I didn't. You didn't. I'm dead. Definitely saying Aiyah.
That's all I need to know. Never heard any elderly Chinese player say Cho.
Uh Cho is like good ball and Cho Lee is good ball again.
I hear it a lot in competitive like tournaments.
That's interesting. Like good point. Well game point match point here it
comes. Ah good game good game good game.
All right what do you say? What do I do? I like that a lot.
I just want to make it more points because it's quick.
Points to 12. Yeah I'm gonna talk about the green screen after
we play lethal league blaze. The new game.
New lethal league. It's very fun. I'm going to try
so hard. How much is this game? What's the price point on this one?
Uh I don't remember. I thought it was like 20.
Aye nice. 20 bucks. 20 bucks. We got a fucking endless amount of
activity here. Holy fuck that was much faster than
I thought it was. Oh my god I bunted it down just so you
could kill me.
Me too. Yeah just like that. Okay try it.
I'm trying to like legend of Zelda to you.
Oh my god. I'm trying to do the uh the link down smash.
What the fuck happened to me? Because I served it at parry.
I didn't even see you hit it a second time. I did my special.
Remember my special comes out and then comes back in. Oh
nice. Excellent work. What? Why? I don't know. I bunted the shit out of
that. That second was much faster than I
thought it would be.
Handcuff man. This guy's font man. Why is everybody saying spy party?
Spy party. Spy party. Oh my god. You jumped in. I was like he's gonna hit it
down. Uh like that and okay. Jesus
Christ. All right. Oh my god. She was like where the random
random xd. Oh I'm telling it's gamer fatigue. Gamer fatigue? No.
It's just. It's gamer fatigue man. The throw is weird.
You gonna let me pogo this? It's not mine. Oh my god. What am I doing over here? I'm
trying to like steal the ball from you. Oh my god. Are you telling me you really
aimed those? Because that's just like it feels like it tracks
exactly wherever I am. I just hook shot at you. It's called the sniper.
It's never like it's never slightly off. It's always just
right where it needs to be. Spy party. Spy party. Spy. I don't even
have a spy party on this computer. I had full meter. I think
if you parry somebody else you get full meter. I ya indeed.
This is why this character embodies me. Oh that was.
Ding. Boop. Oh it really is like a falcon punch. I get it.
Attention germ reviewers. No I'm not reading that.
Shit. I'm not reading that. Oh I didn't know you had it.
Yeah if you hit it like before you get the final one that counts as your
final hit. So if you run three bars the next hit will be enough to use it.
Damn I see. Damn he's getting on to me fellas. He's on to me fellas and lads.
Fellas and ladies. Fellas and lads.
Oh boy I'm just throwing. I'm throwing it here.
The bunting in front of people. Not a good idea.
Whatever that was not a good idea. I don't know it's gamer fatigue.
It's gamer fatigue man. It's fucking gamer fatigue.
Gamer fatigue. Gamer fatigue. Not just really fast.
Sometimes it throws surprise.
Oh what the hell was that? That was like a super ball.
Fucking I was trying to time it.
You just need one point.
I thought you were going to throw it. I thought you were going to do the thing
where you just try to blanket on me very quickly. I'm going to try to throw it back at you.
Is there actually the one character we hadn't seen?
Have we? I don't have.
There's one other guy right?
Is there? I mean there's this dude.
Oh oh yeah.
Let's try somebody else.
I'm gonna play baseball guy. What's his special? What is baseball man special?
I don't know. He spins and hits and then it does nothing.
Sounds fun.
I can't remember. I used to play him a lot.
So I remember being good but I didn't. I don't.
Yeah I think it just goes faster.
Jesus fuck man. I didn't know you were going to activate it.
My god that was the most embarrassing round.
Even worse than the volleyball earlier.
It's gamer fatigue.
I thought it was gonna.
I thought it was gonna get you.
That would have been ultra ultra gamer embarrassment.
Jesus.
Oh I jumped into it.
It was weird that you like hit it up.
What the fuck am I doing here?
Wow that was quick.
Yeah oh man.
I just threw you.
Yeah I didn't turn around.
I just threw you over there.
Nice.
Whoa I think you can just go any direction and it goes faster.
Yeah god damn it what the fuck am I thinking?
I just keep trying to go over that bonehead play.
Is Jermey even trying anymore?
Yeah.
Oh Jesus.
Damn.
You got that twice in a row didn't you?
I'm surprised I didn't get that.
Kind of right where I was swinging.
I was waiting for it.
Oh my god.
Didn't work.
Nice fucking play.
I was I knew it.
I should have just backed off.
Dinked him.
I'm trying to grab it in midair.
Nice.
Grabbing from a parry is more difficult than it seems.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Recuperate from gamer fatigue.
Recuperating from gamer fatigue is more difficult than it seems.
Come back to you.
Controller unplugged.
You can bait parries?
Yeah.
Yeah this is a lot trickery.
Do you remember what this girl's thing was?
You used her a second ago.
I don't even remember.
I don't think I even got a chance to use her special.
I was so bad.
Do you know that you can bunt out of your special?
Does it consume the special?
Yeah.
So while you're in the mid you can just bunt.
Interesting.
Damn it.
What the fuck is going on?
What happened here?
What? Are you still here?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Is that your is that your move?
Her move changed.
I remember it changes the direction a couple times.
No no I mean like there's like a dummy here of you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh well.
I thought you put a dummy here.
No.
Oh well.
Oh that's what it is.
Okay now you're off the screen.
That was a that was just a bad program.
It really doesn't feel like it didn't.
One of you hundred devs needs to fit a hundred devs.
Yeah can you believe they have a hundred dev team?
Damn it.
I'm so panicking over that shit.
Shit I'm holding it down now.
Oh lord I'm slowing down.
Yeah I'm slowing down.
Oh my god I thought I was you because we're both beautiful women.
I programmed the cars in the background.
Nice job man.
Stages like this I don't know there's some of the stages that
the wiggling back and forth is.
I can't I can't I can't man.
I don't like the stage wiggling.
Damn well you still just saved my life.
Oh cheese bag cheese bag.
Jesus.
I just want to get a hand on it.
I just want to touch it.
Oh shit I thought it was gonna go the other way.
Down instead of up.
Oh my god.
Sometimes you gotta I gotta just stop moving.
Just slow down.
It's like you know what people are like I don't.
Never mind just.
You might want to move a little bit.
Sonic boom.
Shit.
You fooled me.
Fooled him.
Level 23.
You fooled me.
Knock out.
Piece of cake.
What is wrong with you?
That's the that's the punch out.
It's only one good character.
Ping pong guy.
That's that was that was the when you beat somebody in punch out.
Look it up.
You beat someone in punch out.
Oh come on really you how did you get rid of that one.
You were you were doing it.
That didn't sound anything like it.
I'll play it in a second.
What the hell why was it floating to me.
It floated to me.
Because after a second it floats to you.
Come on bro.
What's happening with my body.
I think it was.
Oh I was in the middle of a special.
Yeah you were in the special so you still had a lock on it.
All right.
You're just like binding of Isaac me.
With the fucking item that's like aerial of you know what I'm saying.
No I have no idea what you're saying actually.
You walked into me with like band-aid girl.
Oh.
See that's like what.
What the fuck man.
I'm gonna stop doing that to you.
Try it.
It's pretty rough.
No that sucks.
Oh here I come.
Yeah.
Orbitable damage.
Orbital damage.
Orbitable.
When does the binding of Isaac come.
Expansion coming up soon right.
When does Diablo immortal come out.
I can't wait.
Who knows.
When does 2B come out.
2B?
2B in Soul Calibur.
Wait we're playing this really really just boring aren't we.
I walk ball into you.
I would probably get you a ball.
Hey I'm playing a win.
Oh my god that fucking throw.
2B or not wait 2B from near Autonomica.
Yeah near Autonomica is gonna fight Geralt of Skyrim.
Wait Geralt is in Soul Calibur.
Yeah.
Is he really.
No be honest with me here.
He is yeah.
That's pretty cool.
Wrong direction.
You'll see.
No I can't add it.
Oh my that is so deceiving.
Why is the second throw like 10 times faster.
It just is.
That was the cheesiest shittiest game ever.
That's why you have to regulate it and play volleyball.
All right well how about let's do one more volleyball.
And then I need to talk to my stream about green screen stuff.
Okay.
Yeah okay then I need to talk to my stream about.
Are you going to go to Soul Calibur after this.
I wasn't going to stream today.
Oh let's get it.
We're just going to talk about cute boys and.
The star guys if you just don't know.
His YouTube is twitch.tv slash s-t-e-r stirb.
Um he's he's available um for parties and.
Remember what game those rates are pretty good.
I remember I know.
Okay as long as you know.
Are you sure you know.
I was very slightly off.
He does bachelor parties.
Got it.
I love his jump.
Wow.
Candyman has a has a more downward angle I think.
Well.
Fuck.
Oh no.
Damn it.
Yeah that's how downward your angle be.
That is very downward.
Downward dog.
Yep yep.
Candyman.
Downward dog.
Could have just well I could have just downward on you right there but I didn't.
I love his walk he's got the best walk.
It's at the road runner.
No.
Right into my trap.
Right into his trap.
Keep forgetting that you're going to do that.
I was trying to do it the whole time.
Uh oh.
Oh whoa whoa wait oh oh.
Let's go again.
Oh I hear some smashing of stuff.
What is he doing right now I can't.
What is he doing.
I'm going again.
Are you on cam right now.
What are you are you on cam bro.
I'm going again.
You're not going to do a single point.
All right buddy.
Hey.
Nothing like a funky beat.
Oh yeah.
Did that go in my side.
You're going to try and do some goofy shit.
That didn't that was.
Let's fucking go.
Yeah you just like broke open you're like fucking vase.
You got like the adrenaline right now.
I got to break something too.
No fuck this man I got to get ready.
Yeah you angry.
Okay.
I just broke I broke a piece of cardboard.
I'm going to break more shit in a second.
I spilled shit.
My hands are wet.
Okay.
Oh I got a walnut desk here.
Dude I can't fucking break anything.
I got a brand new desk.
This isn't that piece of shit that I had my other place.
Nothing in my life matters so I can break whatever I want.
No.
Come on come on make a break something.
That was on who's what happened.
I was like what the fuck.
Yeah you lost it appeared on your side and then.
What the fuck man.
No that hit the ground.
I heard the explosion too.
No fake anger.
What crap crap.
Dang it.
Oh wild.
Then you can stand up to me in my own court.
I did like I like drop a piece of like cardboard here.
Is it all right.
What about over here.
I'm gonna have to get like a quick towel over here later.
Hey I got noise clone.
All right I think that's that's a good one to go.
No it was the no it was one to one.
You beat me I beat you.
It's one to one kidding.
I'm kidding don't make.
Oh I was about this is full of like water I was gonna throw it.
What are you doing why are you doing that.
So you have a new place too what are you thinking.
Sorry somebody we need to like give you like rubber glasses and shit.
Okay this is this is it's one to one right now that's what you said.
Okay let's get angry you wouldn't like me when I'm angry I'm like the Hulk.
Oh sorry that's all right I mean I got a little nervous when you said that.
Holy fuck that was pretty sick.
It's pretty sick my brain locked up my brain just locked in half.
That was me no right through the legs.
You're in my head don't lose it.
What it just makes up physics for you.
You got the fucking dev in your stream.
Wow he's putting glue on my freaking controller.
Hey maybe if you cleaned off the fucking gamer gunk.
This wouldn't be a problem.
Nice job dingus.
I did this yeah I know whatever.
Let me just let me just give you some points how does that sound.
Sounds great.
This one's for all the marbles.
Eat it eat it eat it eat it and you know what I'm referring to.
Careful careful it's almost over careful be careful.
I just wanted you to feel better about yourself.
Well that's crazy how this was a best of five.
That's crazy yeah when I was looking at the rules.
It was weird it's officially notarized rule set.
Let's go it said the rest of the three that was stamped by a notary.
I don't know but watch out I know where you live.
Play ball.
Dink check out this dink.
What was that a dink I heard I heard it on the other side of the net though.
Check out this strange it was weird check out this thing.
Okay weird check out that thing I heard it I heard it.
That was bullshit that was over the net.
You wish it was over the net lucky.
I thought you were gonna do the thing where it spins around goes the other way.
Thought you're gonna do your special.
You're gonna go where you're gonna go.
I only had one hit there's no way to get it over.
Okay you're gonna be like that and I'm gonna be like this.
All right okay all right okay.
Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho.
Oh I thought you had I thought that was the no yes.
That did not bounce how I thought it was gonna be.
All right I'm trying to bait you out there it's fine.
Holy fucking hell oh you didn't do it.
Oh what I thought I had super it didn't do it.
I should have been able to use it.
For the likes.
Come on come on.
What here it comes.
Can he win it will he win the world's next game.
It's crazy how this set was the best of seven.
You're gonna have anything left in your room before we're done here.
It's actually insane how the tension is boiling in this best of seven set.
You're gonna have anything left in there.
You'd be surprised how little you need.
You need food water and winning and bread and winning.
I'm done taking it easy on you.
Look at him wiggle look at these wiggles.
I can feel you.
It's not activating my super ever.
I could I could like smell it.
I almost want to lose because I feel like you're gonna like sledgehammer your computer.
Yeah just play it off like you want to lose just play it off.
Yeah that's what that was so you want it to lose.
Yeah you just want it to lose huh.
Yeah.
Yeah you want it to lose right.
That's what's happening.
Well you're gonna get it be careful careful careful it's hard again.
I was trying to spike it on you.
All right come on now.
Oh you gotta be kidding me with that bullshit I've never seen it before.
I've seen it before last time you were trash of this game.
Oh yeah I've trapped this game.
Yeah I let you win those just like you're you are.
I think I should let you win because otherwise oh you're in danger.
My controller.
What oh that's excuse that's excuse man.
Controller oh god.
Oh you can't fool me with that bullshit.
You're not gonna.
Bullshit oh that's bullshit.
Oh what the fuck dude my controller.
Oh looks like I won seven for everyone keeping track at home.
It's like I'm ahead by four.
Got two free points it's still lost.
Hey it was a series I won the series two times in a row.
Three times in a row actually.
Best out of three best out of five.
Well that's that's seven.
Looks like I'm in the lead.
If it's best of seven I have to I've already won.
I've already won he's like it's already it's already over.
You know what just fucking water all over me.
Same.
Fucking you see you're dumping water on me.
There's like you're not gonna recover from this shit.
No way.
He didn't turn.
Because if you try and turn too hard you just slam it into the ground.
I was so good that was so good and I fucking flew it at the end it was so easy.
What the fuck.
Okay best of seven come on now it's gonna happen here.
There is they know by the way there ain't no such thing as
ain't no such thing as best out of 10 or best out of 15.
Doesn't matter what sport even it doesn't matter.
Oh you gotta be kidding me with that.
Snuck it under there like a little fucking mouse.
It was still counting as my ball too again.
Okay oops a daisy parried him.
This game blows game was made by toddlers.
This game's great.
Gamer rage here comes the rage.
Okay so we're even at three to three.
The next game wins.
I quit.
I don't know how many series I have to win when you keep extending them.
I mean it's just it just comes down to just
getting in the right moment in the right mindset.
Timing your shots carefully fundamentals.
He left the discord by the way he's gone he's he's gone.
He's not here.
He turned his stream off.
Wait what.
What is.
Why did you turn off his stream.
It was a very good intense series.
Hey you probably won more games total.
See you in another year.
Well that was a star by the way a star twitch twitch.tv's flash stir.
Welcome everybody from hi hi stars switch twitch channel.
So here's what we're going to do now.
Is I'm going to go take a pee and grab a water.
And then from there we're going to talk about the green screen.
I'm going to update you guys on the green screen.
Which is happening very soon.
Because there are some changes to be made.
So stick around.
I'll be right back.
Pee break.
Water break.
You know the deal.
See you in a bit.
Okay hello.
So let us discuss this out of the way while I listen to music.
This is from lethal league.
Lethal league blazes soundtrack.
It's very good.
Highly recommend.
Okay so you want to see just how much this game takes out of me.
I'm like so sweaty and greasy right now.
It's like unbelievable.
Turn this on.
Let's get that off.
I'll take this out too.
Like look at look at this shit.
It's insane.
Take a look under them.
I am.
This is just this is water.
That's not a shadow guys.
That's that's water.
Look at that.
This is like heavy under here.
It weighs a shitload.
Check out this side though.
It's like I'm just sitting here like I'm wet.
I worked out.
I could walk like when I talk to Kim.
I could tell her I was like doing push-ups in here for like fucking three out four hours.
And she'd be like oh wow wow you really look like you've been working out.
Don't even need to go to the fucking gym.
But anyways let's get this back off.
And let me transition.
Well actually I don't think I can just keep this on.
So let's talk about the green screen.
Those of you that don't know just like I'm just going to be this cube in the middle.
Yeah that's fine.
I don't want to use too much internet.
So for those of you that don't know there is a thank you for sharing.
You're very welcome.
So next week I'm going to do a stream where I get in front of a green screen.
And I'm going to do potentially 150 to 200 separate actions.
So originally the plan was I was going to have a voting period.
And it was going to be secret where I didn't know what you guys were suggesting.
But I've changed the rules a little bit because it's just not going to happen.
There were like I think 1500 plus different suggestions in that channel in the discord.
So it was like there was no way I was reliably going to just be like oh hey mods.
Hey can you do like fucking if there's props involved I need to know what they are so I
can buy them.
You know what I mean?
I need to know what these things are so if I need to know what they are so I can buy them.
I need to know what these things are so I'm able to do them.
So what I did is I went through myself and I did a pre-screening.
Essentially I went through every single every single submission in that channel.
And it was oh we're going to make a poll.
We're going to make a voting.
There's not going to be any voting for all the actions.
I'm just going to take the ones that I like.
The audio is out of sync.
Oh it's because of PlayStation 4.
Here let me do this.
It is because of the PS4.
The mic has been out of sync the entire stream hasn't it?
It had to have been.
Yeah no there's no way that it wasn't out of sync the whole stream.
Was I like responding to things Star was saying like two full seconds before he said them?
So wait hold on a second.
I've been I've been like a full second behind.
It was fine.
All right it seemed fine.
All right well that my microphone was 650 milliseconds behind.
So he would say something and it would take me almost a full second to respond to it.
But as long as it uh as long as it wasn't that noticeable.
It was just stuck there from the PlayStation 4 when when it did Red Dead.
It still seems off.
It should not be.
Yeah I'm at zero here and the camera's at zero.
Is it?
Yeah it's fine.
But anyways uh the let's go well hopefully that wasn't fucking horrible to watch.
Uh sorry about that.
I you know it's been kind of crazy here with the internet.
So I saw green and stepped on the fucking gas.
Didn't even think about it.
It was just like green internet screen go.
So sorry about that.
Anyways uh talk about the green screen right.
So instead of having it be a period where everybody votes and I don't know in secret.
I just I went through and I picked out the ones that I think I want to do.
And I narrowed it down to about 120, 130 plus actions.
There's going to be one poll.
So the poll is going to be what meme shit you guys want me to do.
Because there was just a lot of meme shit.
And I don't even want I don't even want to talk about them.
So there's going to be a poll with all the memes on it.
I've already vetoed three of them.
So you'll you'll get to see it over the next day here.
So I'm going to put a poll in the discord.
I'll give it to one of the mods.
I'll put it in the general.
That's where it's going to be.
I haven't made it yet so that's why it's not here.
And there's no more suggestions as of tonight.
So pretty much by the time this stream is over five or six hours later.
I'll probably till like midnight.
Pacific which would be 3am eastern is when it's going to be just completely closed.
I'm going to then a couple days later figure out exactly how I want to do it.
What I want to do.
And then you guys are going to be a poll that's going to be up for like three or
four days before the stream happens.
From what mean is three meme shit that I get to do out of like 20 different options.
So we'll go we'll touch on that later.
Police temple you chose where there are a lot of great ones.
There are a lot of odd ones too but you'll see soon enough.
And because I got a little bit of time here to be able to actually explain all this.
After the poll is closed and after it's ready to go.
It's going to be the after the stream happens.
There's going to be like full two full weeks before we even do anything else.
So you'll have plenty of fucking time to be able to put together whatever you want.
And the rules for that.
I think I won't even talk about them till later.
What's my personal favorite one.
There's two of my I'll tell you that my two personal favorites.
Because I just can't even imagine how stupid that it's going to be.
Personal favorite number one is.
Go limp on the ground hear something and pretend to be a toy from Toy Story.
Like that's like what that's fucking ridiculous.
Go hear something and go limp.
Like I don't even know where you're going to put me there.
And the second one is.
Be in a bowl of cereal and avoid a toddler eating cereal from the bowl.
Like what how am I supposed to even do that.
There's hundreds of guys like you think that that's it.
And people were concerned though.
I mean let me let me squelch these concerns right away.
A ton of people are like oh man we're just going to get like a bunch of fucked up shit.
Not going to be able to use oh no no I'm.
We're doing a full spread here man.
I am doing like standing.
Blinking walking running dodging getting hit getting hit in the shoulder getting hit in the arm.
Getting hit in the shin getting hit in the face like this is going to be a full nine.
It's not going to be like oh I'm just going to like eat fucking bananas on stream.
And then that's it.
There you go meemers like no.
We're doing the whole thing.
Like oh react scared react scared plus react scared plus plus you know what I mean.
Like there's going to be plenty of options for you.
And there's a ton of random fucking things that people have suggested that are going to be funny too.
Sprites essentially I'm making human sprites that's right.
And then a couple weeks later we're going to do it might even take two streams in a row.
To do a night where we sit around and we just hang out and we just play them.
And they will be rules by the way based on that.
I'm going to assume it's going to be this is not set in stone so it's not quite ready yet.
But up to two minutes and at least 10 seconds.
That has to be there because like I said I was talking to the discord the other day.
I ain't going to have like 400 submissions that are just like up.
Like no that's not like it's got to be at least 10 seconds or up to two minutes.
You know what I mean.
Those actions are funny but do we have anything to really add the green screen.
Oh there's a lot of things that are going to be worthy of the green screen.
There's at least 60 of these actions.
They're very very going to they're going to be very fun.
When was the sideburn patch.
I fixed them.
Look see right there.
Right there even I fixed it.
See I fixed it.
I told you guys I was going to fix it.
Can you do 10 bups?
Sure it could be like but I mean is it going to pass the pre-screening.
Because all these members.
Here's something another thing that a lot of people might not understand.
There's going to be a rigorous pre-screening on every single one of these submissions.
And you only get to submit I would probably assume we're going to have a limit here.
You can only submit like two or three submissions because people will just
diarrhea in like a hundred fucking submissions of random shit.
So we're going to have very strict rules and if they don't follow the rules
Strictly strictly they're going to just get thrown out.
Because I cannot have a scenario where it's like do you know.
What oh guy stands in front of green screen.
You know how fucking easy it would be to do up all kinds of fucked up shit.
No they're all getting pre-watched pre-screened not by me.
I mean maybe I will do it.
It depends on how much there are.
So there's going to be laws here in this lawless country.
There's going to be laws.
Should we put a cap on the amount of videos total.
Um I don't I'm not sure because it really depends on how many submissions there are.
Because if there are like let's say 50 to 100 really great submissions
and they're up to two minutes long.
I mean that's not very long.
You know what I mean.
Like that wouldn't take a long time and plus if we do an entire stream
a full three four plus hour live stream maybe two streams maybe possibly.
Then they would have to be hundreds of submissions that get through.
If you take back to the emote contest.
I mean the emote contest had a ton of submissions and a ton of ones got pre-screened.
But it wasn't like an outrageous level.
I mean there's 3,000 people here now.
But I don't think this channel is quite at a spot where it's unmanageable.
You know what I mean.
Up to like three four five hundred submissions then going through them
and bringing them down to like a hundred or two hundred.
I mean if there were like two thousand submissions then this would be impossible.
Right.
What is this contest?
It's not a contest.
This is not a contest at all.
This is just a fun thing that we can do just to make some weird shit.
And see what you guys can come up with.
Because I also I was talking to Star about this earlier.
It's going to be kind of fun to essentially bring in some people to do them.
Right.
Like I'll have I'll see if Star wants to do an edit.
He's already talked about it.
Like italics might want to do an edit.
Bring in some more people to like do edits and like show theirs on screen.
You know what I mean.
Hit up some people see if they'd want to do it.
Am I going to be doing a fortnight?
No that was already vetoed.
So see like if I just see if anybody was interested in doing it.
But is that a dong on the door?
That's a fucking creeper man.
Come on.
You guys have played that game.
How am I going to veto the default dance?
Because I get three vetoes and I don't want to do it.
And it's it's actually kind of funny because I didn't do the veto thing.
It's just there kind of for fun.
Because I vetoed a lot of fucking things that came through there.
I vetoed almost 90% of every submission.
So that's a creeper.
But it should be fun.
There'll be way more.
What's with the shitty wallpaper?
It's it's just like regular wall man.
Shitty wall.
There's no there's no wallpaper on this wall.
Wallpaper.
Three vetoes is bullshit.
Three hold on three vetoes based on like 1500 submissions.
And I pre-screened them down to like 200.
Three vetoes out of 200.
You're lucky I don't veto 50 of them.
Let's see what's what do you mean the drink?
This drink right here.
Will I pretend to be a rat?
It depends on if I want to put it in there or not.
I got a whole list and it's pretty much ready to go.
After tonight I'm going to do one more pass through tonight.
And see if there's any new ones or any good ideas and we'll go from there.
But this is but what's today?
Today is today's Sunday.
So I would assume based around the fact that closing it tonight.
Maybe gonna give myself like three days or so to like.
Well remember I have to buy props on Amazon.
So at least two days.
I would I would probably say that by this weekend.
Like this next like weekend coming up here.
We'll do it on like probably Saturday or Sunday afternoon.
Is what I'm going to shoot for.
And after that two weeks later there'll be all the footage will be available.
Whether you want to pull it from Twitch directly or.
It's going to be difficult for me to put it all up raw.
I'll have to find out if I can do that.
We'll see.
But expect it at some point this weekend.
Is this still a one dance limit?
There weren't no not very many people did dances.
Not very many people were putting up dances.
They were doing the people would to give you guys a lot of credit here.
You guys were trying to at least put some interesting shit up there.
It wasn't just like total nonsense.
You guys did a pretty good job.
I'm not going to use more than three vetoes.
I already have.
I've already done it.
You want to tell you what the three vetoes are.
Fortnite dance dab and reenact the gnome video.
That's an automatic veto.
I ain't doing any of those three things.
Reenact the gnome video was suggested like six thousand times.
Then it was upvoted like a thousand times.
That's a veto.
Well let me just give you a little bit of a consolation here.
Oh no the gnome is not selectable in the meme poll.
But run as Sonic and say Sonic's the name speeds my game.
That's not fucking embarrassing as hell.
That's an option.
Are you kidding me?
You could be known as the gnome.
I don't want to be known as the gnome guy.
I don't want to be known as the guy that's like the annoying dude that
I'm the new gnome video that people start to put into the other gnome videos.
I don't want to be that guy.
I'll be the guy that people will hate me for that.
People will be very upset.
Streamers, YouTubers, friends of yours.
People like random people on like Overwatch lobbies.
People are going to be like that guy sucks.
Why did he make this?
He made that.
I didn't make it.
I don't want to make it veto.
Vetoed man.
No way.
But anyways it's going to be a lot of fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
All the props that are there.
I mean it's going to be hard but I'll try to do a full figure skating skit.
That's going to be fucking hard but it's going to be funny.
I'm going to put like fucking fake blades on my shoes.
There's so many fun things.
I don't think you guys understand.
There's a lot of interesting potential things here.
Could you say something for a senior quote of mine?
Falling down hard through the ground.
Eventually you end up standing up because you go through the earth
and you're on top of the world in China.
So move to China.
But you just moved to Vegas.
Yeah well I'm moving to China now.
I'm going to China now.
Take a new balloon.
Is the sip part of the quote?
No.
Help me come up with a wedding toast.
Okay.
Hey everybody.
Good to see you.
For those of you on this side that don't know me.
I'm Greg.
Little bro over here you know.
I'm the little bro.
I've seen some of you guys.
I've met some of you guys.
And first of all I gotta say,
Kristen you've been like a sister to me so far
over these last probably 15 years or so.
I really didn't think that it was ever going to happen
because obviously there was all the issues that we had
as a family.
But we love you.
You're a sister to us now.
I just want to say that really quickly before everyone is clapping.
Everyone is clapping.
Dude man I gotta say something.
Put my little bro over here
because that's the man of the hour.
There he is right there bro.
No no this is for the green screen.
No this is for the green screen.
I have to be standing up in a suit for this.
Save it.
You have nothing else to do?
What?
Can you help with the funeral speech?
Hey everybody.
So for those of you on this side of the family
that don't know I'm Greg.
Met some of you guys already here.
But before we get started I gotta say Kristen
it's been a pleasure having you as part of the family.
And it's just too bad you're down there.
Down there now.
But it was it was an absolute fucking honor.
No no.
It's been an honor going down.
Funeral wedding.
Wedding slash funeral.
Now you see the move to China as we've all seen.
You made it right to us when you get there.
Same event.
Oh anyways we talked about the green screen.
Now I'm going to move some stuff out of the way
and I'm going to open another game called Red Dead Redemption.
It's a fun game.
You can last out people.
You can shoot people.
It's probably the most fun I've ever had in a video game.
But I don't know man.
It seems like it's going to be pretty hard to do with the internet and all.
What's the matter?
I don't understand what you guys are talking about.
Okay let's go.
What a bad internet joke.
Uh I need to put I actually have to desync it again
because I'm opening up PS4.
Sorry guys here comes the desync.
The door behind me looks mildly shocked.
Fuck.
Damn it.
Almost puked.
All right let's go.
Is it even turned on?
No it's not.
Whatever.
Uh I gotta update the...
Hold on let me get off the camera here
because I don't like how ugly I am.
But by the way Lethal League is very good.
Very fun.
It's a lot like the first one.
But the first one was also a ton of fun.
So doesn't surprise me at all.
I need to move through this.
That's all good.
Okay.
By the way during the gamer try hard moment
KingLam gave like 10 gifted subs.
So thank you so much KingLam.
I'm just microwaving some food.
Okay there we go.