Secret stream. Well, I'm hitting you with the uh, I'm hitting you with the extreme reverse delay.
This is extreme. The sus said Thursday. It's Tuesday. What an extreme reverse delay.
Anyways, how are you? Hope you're having a good day. So is there no stream on Thursday? Um,
there probably still will be. I don't know. It depends. Does the music sound weird?
Uh, shouldn't. Surprise stream. Yeah, technically. Does the music taste weird?
But yeah, if you're curious, um, why I turned the stream on, I'm just going to play a game and chill.
I think I talked a little bit about a few weeks ago as we went into 2023.
I want to do much more stuff like this, but we're just chilling. Doesn't need to be anything crazy
going on. Doesn't need to be anything elaborate. I'm just going to play Plants vs. Zombies and
Hangout. I think there were a lot of people over the last year or two that have been like,
you know, I really miss when he just fucking relaxed and played Plants vs. Zombies.
I feel like a lot of people have had that opinion. And I, I join your opinion. I think I kind of
missed being able to chill and hang out and just do whatever. So they're coming back. I promise
there won't be any McDonald's rants tonight. Well, I can't promise that, but you know,
how long are you going to go for? I think that's the other thing too. No, uh, no time limit,
no kind of rhyme or reason to anything here. Just going to play a game, hang out, talk.
This is going to be 15 hours. No, I don't think I'll ever go over 14. Also too,
there's not going to be a cam tonight. I'm going to try some, go back to kind of the way,
if you don't know, back before 2020, 2021, 2020, I never did face cam. It was something
that was very rare. So we're going to be doing less face cam, but no, I'm just not going away.
Let me be really upfront. People be like, wait a minute. Why is he taking the face cam off
permanently? No, it's just when I feel like hanging out and chilling, it's not going to be on.
That's right. I get to be naked again. It's awesome. You know how a lot don't, I'm not
going to rant about anything. It's a chill stream. I've been waiting for the opportunity.
No, I'm just kidding. But yeah, well, I don't really have a plan. The plan was, uh, I was in
offline chat, just kind of hanging out for a minute and gave a few options. Like let's just
play plans for as obvious. I don't think I ever beat this game. Maybe we'll beat it tonight.
Maybe I'll play for an hour. Maybe I'll play for four hours. Maybe I'll be here all night,
but let's just relax and have some, uh, have some fun.
Breath of the Wild, Breath of the Wild is going to, it's going to be funny because
it's the first like six Breath of the Wild streams where there's a lot going on. It's like the second
part of the Breath of the Wild series is going to be so much more like chilled out and kind of
turned down a lot, right? You're going to get to the second half and be like, wow, he must have
really, what the fuck I have to do. But anyways, yeah, let's, let's open it up. I hope you guys are
doing well. I know this is going to be new for a lot of you, but it's something I wanted to do this
year. Spend a lot more time just doing stuff like this. Let's go. Is there anything weird that I
need to do? Plans for zombies. It's been so long. Do I have, is this the right version? Like do I,
did I get the wrong version? Are you on your iPad? That'd actually be kind of funny.
Fuck, this looks old. Well, that's because it is old. It is very old. When did plans for zombies
come out? I don't remember. If make your own zombie, what does this mean? I don't know what
this means. Make your own zombie. I clicked on this and it was like, I had to like agree to terms.
What's this? I had this on my family PC. Yeah. Fix the aspect ratio. Uh, I don't think that's
possible. Wait, so I can make a zombie? Is this what they look like when they come down the lanes?
Oh, okay. Do I have to unlock these or are they just all available? Just the first zombie with
the flag. Oh, okay. Oh dude, look at this. Look at this character creator. I like that. Use plenty
of sunflowers. I used to be pretty damn good at this game. I don't think I ever beat it. How long
is the campaign? Oh, definitely that. It's like 30 hours. You could probably finish it in one sitting.
30 hours. I don't think one sitting, that's a long time. That sounds like a while. Uh, hold on. Let
me move my chair. I got a pretty good tea here too. Okay. Oh no. I put my cord underneath it.
What are you doing? I'm moving my chair. Yeah. No, no. People are asking. No camp tonight.
This is a relaxed night. What should I be wearing? Oh, I got an orange spice tea, by the way.
Very smooth clown costume. This song is comfy. I'll do the clown. Oh, these are teeth. Okay.
White collar, gold teeth. I think play insane aquarium. I think I did a long time ago.
Remember, this is pre-recorded. You might think that. It says probably feel that way.
What do we got here? Gold teeth. Okay. It's an AI generated stream. I'm just testing the waters
to see if you notice. It's an AI generated stream. I'm just testing the waters to see if you notice.
It's an AI generated stream. I'm just testing the waters to see if you notice. I'm thinking this.
Uh, I like the gold teeth. They'll stay gold. Hey, just because I'm relaxing doesn't mean I'm
not going to be a weird. Oh, that's right. Somebody said this too. The last time I played
this game, it was, I couldn't beat the tutorial during the Halloween special from a few years ago.
That's right. It's just, there was no attention there at all. Zero, zero attention. So let's see
if I can, uh, fix that and see if we can actually beat the first level. That'd be great. This is
fine. Be sure you're done creating your Zompatar. If you wish to make any changes,
you'll need to start over. So what? Your Zompatar has been saved to your desktop.
Why did it do that? It's weird. That's weird. I don't like that. I don't really don't like that.
Where is it? Hold on. Is it actually on my desktop? Yeah, it is. That's strange.
Okay. Oh yeah. I have to capture the, sorry. The window needs to be captured. There you go.
You can't capture this game as a game. It has to be a window. All right. So there it is. Cool.
All right, let's go. Make that your Twitch avatar. Oh, this is a replay of the last game that I
played. Look at that placement. I can't lose the tutorial. I mean, there's no way, right? How did
I lose the tutorial? I should probably turn it up, shouldn't I? No, I'm like actually genuinely
asking. How did I lose the tutorial? You can't. There we go. Is that better? Yeah, you put it
back here. And you always want to have the sunflowers in the back row. You might remember.
Did I actually lose on this level? I cannot believe that. It seems impossible.
It was this screen? You lost to one lane. How? You can't. This, ah, this, I forget how cool this
game was. I forget how awesome this game was and I forget just how much I was so sad when the second
one came up. It's too loud. How's that? Is that better? How is that still too loud? Come on, dude.
There we go. Play the YouTube video of you ranting about the in-game currency.
The one thing that I remember about Plants vs. Zombies 2 was that. It was the fact that
some levels, it was just like, oh yeah, there's like electricity lightning moves.
You just put your finger over it and you just destroy every single enemy on the screen.
And it was, it cost money to do it. There we go. Make the music and the sound effects the same
volume. Okay. We gotta get the perfect, it's gotta be chill. This is not chill. This is chill. This
is not chill. I think it's in a good spot. All right, yeah, the sunflowers go in the back row.
You guys gotta help me with decisions though, because I know that eventually you can buy
things. I don't, you guys probably know a lot more than I do. Yeah, this feels pretty nice,
doesn't it? A lot of people probably think this is a joke. Like, ah, no, I like this. This is cool.
So I used to do double sunflower, right? It's like kind of overkill, but I used to like it.
It was like, yeah, give me the double the power. Some people are against the double sunflower lane,
but I always wanted extra power. I'm probably going to continue to do double sunflower.
Hey, when is the bit going to end? Oh shit, yeah, you probably, a screamer is going to show up in
about one to two minutes, I think. I have it programmed so that like a screamer just goes
right in the middle of the screen. How pissed would some of you be if that happened and the
stream turned off? I feel like a lot of people would be really mad at me. Do three rows of
sunflowers? Nah, now you're just asking too much. Can you ever make the cooldown faster on these?
I don't think so, right? This is a chill grandpa stream. Yeah, that's what I like to hear.
Best gamer moment, beating the tutorial. Oh, look, there's our guy. Dude, he was so cool.
I don't have to do anything else. Oh, I remember this. I support grandfathers across America.
So is this a lane or is this just the air, like just a small area? I forgot. Didn't know the
chili pepper is the lane, right? From what I remember. And why does this game have a 3D
acceleration option? What does that do? It's a three by three square, so like all I remember
about this is at every convention there were those cones were on everybody's head. If you went to a
gaming convention between like 2011 to like 2014, it was like that was that was like a fashion
statement, wearing one of these cones. I feel like you're lying. No, no, I'm going double. I
got to go double wrong. Come on. I feel like you've said that before. Probably double row.
Look out for that zombie. I got plenty of time. Don't worry. If Jerma doesn't respond to this,
then it's pre-recorded. But how do you know that I didn't make sure I specifically addressed
comments like yours in the pre-recorded video? Look out. What? I got it. Actually, it might be
kind of funny if I just respond to stuff that's not there. Yeah, maybe I'll do that for a minute
or so. What's my favorite kind of steak? Um, I'm not really a huge steak guy, but I like it kind
of a medium medium well. It's like a like a flat kind of iron, flat iron steak. Oh shit. I gotta
be careful. Oh, come on. I can't get, I cannot have any of my flowers get touched once in the
first zone. That would be embarrassing, wouldn't it? You're making up stuff. Uh, hold on.
Is your favorite pizza? Standard pepperoni is pretty much how I like to eat my pizza.
I fucked it up. I fucked it up. I'm gonna lose. Type mustache. Is that, is that a cheat code or
something? Look at that placement. Awful. Is it going to give you like unlimited money? I'm not
going to do that. I wonder how this game gets actually kind of difficult, doesn't it? It gives
the zombies mustaches. Technically. Yes. Does it add money or anything? I don't want to hold on.
No, no. Why am I doing that? Save that. I always want to get a row down first. I'm going to do
double row until I can't. That's the screamer code. You type mustache and it just goes, don't
you dare. Good guys. I always want to make sure there's at least some one person in each row.
Please type mustache. No, no. Would I rather eat a burger or a pizza? I think that's an
impossible question because there are some days where you really feel like a pizza and
there's some days where you really don't feel like a pizza. I think honestly though,
if I had to delete one of them, if I had to delete pizza or delete burgers from earth,
they would just gone. They would just Thanos snapped out. I don't know. What, what, what do
I care about more? Do I like pizza more than hamburgers? I probably, oh, that's hard.
Pizza is better. Pizza is better than burgers. I would probably say pizza probably is better than
burgers in most cases, but if I feel like a burger, like if I really feel like a burger,
I don't think it can match like the taste of burger. Pizza is very versatile. Burgers are
versatile too, but I feel like there's a lot you can do with the pizza. If you delete burgers,
the jazz won't exist anymore. I think they could, they could eat pizza. They would be happy with
that. Oh, hold on a minute. Am I deleting like beef or just like the, how you make a burger,
like the bun, the cheese, the Patty, am I deleting beef? Cause I don't, I would not do that. I don't
think I would do that. No, just burgers. I think I could live with that though. Deleting beef,
the difficulty you want. I don't think there are other difficulties in this game.
There he is. I need you to clear your lawn. Use your shovel to dig up those plants.
Okay. What is it? What purpose is this a serve again? Do an impression. Okay.
I'm not doing that one. I'm not doing that one either, but here you go.
There's a chill stream. There's a little weird voices. Hey, I, that's not what I said. All right.
I remember now. Oh, wait, is this, Oh, wait a minute. That's right. Okay. Was this
explode or not? Right. Okay. I remember kind of like a puzzle. How's the music this good?
All these old PopCap games were, I don't, I don't even know what happened. PopCap made
banger after banger after banger. Oh, yeah. I'm going to get that sometimes.
Don't let any through. I don't think any will get through.
What? I have a really important question though. What actually happened to PopCap? Are they still
doing anything? I mean, uh, Peggle two was the last, God, that had to have been at least five
plus years ago. Wasn't it? It was all mobile.
Oh, actually might be in trouble. Yeah. They got bought by you.
Oh, the garden warfare games. That's right. You know, I actually heard those games were pretty
fun. They are played them, but I actually liked them. I feel like that's the kind of multiplayer
first person or third person shooter type game that I probably really actually would like.
There's a couple of them, right? There's a garden warfare, garden warfare, two garden warfare,
uh, neighborhood or something. And they're like a few of them. It's very similar to TF2.
Really? You would be acid bowling. Let me be really, really honest with you though.
Be real. And I want you to be honest. How many of you, how many of you ones in the chat, if you
actually can reliably get a strike in bowling, I don't think it's anybody. I don't think anybody
does. No, you cannot come on. And I'm not, I'm not talking about just a strike. I'm talking about
like, and it curves across the whole lane and boom blows up all the pins and you can do that
more than once or twice in a row. I don't, I don't believe you. I can bowl a 60. Is that good? Oh,
look at how big that is. You can tell the resolution is really small just because of how
huge that was. That was gigantic. That might've been weird placement, but I think it was good.
Max is 300. Throw up mashed potatoes versus mac and cheese. Mac and cheese gets to stay.
Oh, oh, I have to panic here because they can jump over the these things, right? Can they jump over
these? You can jump over those. Oh, don't you dare. Don't. I have to go flawless. Come on. No.
No, you have to, I have to be flawless. No, no, no. Oh, this is actually kind of bad.
No, stop eating that. No. All right. I got to get it. I got to get it right. I can't have a lot
more happen right now. Oh my God. What do I do? Oh, he can only jump once. All right. Okay.
How come you panic so easily? I don't know. All right. You're going to jump that.
Fuck. You're not going to make it faster. I got doubles. Yeah, there we go. All right. We're good.
Everything has the right amount. I have my explosion. I'm going to use it probably over
here. I'm going to use it right here. We're good. Okay. We're fine. He's still doing the Elden Ring
stuff on the weekend. Oh, yeah. 100%. Bro does not have a green thumb. I was actually, uh, so
stirs playing Neo 2 right now and I just was catching a little bit of it and I was, uh,
I was laughing because somebody in his chat said, uh, what was it? It was like, dude, you're going
to do so good. You're going to, it was like a little paragraph. It was just, oh, hey, man,
don't worry. You're going to learn this game and you're going to make it rain on these enemies
and do it like a boss. It was, I just loved it. It was so funny. It was like, it was like one of my
favorite comments. Dude, you're going to make it rain like a boss. It was like all the little tag
lines from that stream. Like in one comment, it was, I loved it. All right. Maybe the strategy,
wait. Ooh. Okay. I got to rethink my strategy. Okay. We're not going double lane, but we're
going to do one row. I'm putting this here because I don't want to deal with this yet.
It's like Jerma is streaming from his alt account. I mean, I just, honestly, I just kind of wanted,
I want to do more of these. Not every stream we got to be fucking crazy. You know what I mean?
You double lane. I'm going to leave the opportunity to, does this dude do more damage than this?
Cause this is a slow, right? Yeah. Does it do more damage? Yeah. We used to do a lot of these. This
was something I've been, for the most part, the stream back in like 2016, 2017, 2018. There's a
lot of stuff like this and I really kind of want to, I really want to bring it back. Cottage.
Can I do a second lane? I don't think, no. Yeah. Come on. Let's go. Should you do a flappy bird
stream? Maybe I will. What are my thoughts on Greek yogurt? It's good. I will say I don't like
plain Greek yogurt unless it's put in a swithy or something, but it's good. I like vanilla Greek
yogurt. Okay. This is, I have to read this. Nobody goes, what are your thoughts on Greek politics?
Oh, yeah. Let's, let's transition to that. Let's, let's talk about that now. Hey dude. Yeah. What
are your thoughts on Greek yogurt? Hey, what about Paul? What about Greek politics? How do you feel
about ancient Greek? I wasn't there. So I don't know. I know this is not, this is not aesthetically
pleasing. Is it not lined up correctly? They're haphazardly placed. I know I can do better.
Every lane needs one of these. I wanted you to jump over that. Exactly what I wanted.
Fell into my trap. Stupid. I don't think you can ever take this off. I really don't. I think it's
way too important. It's overpriced though. Oh, I think 150 to be able to clear potentially
a half dozen enemies. I think it's pretty good. It's also instant too. This makes me want to play
insane aquarium. It really does. That game is so good. It's not even funny. What are your
thoughts on wireless toilets? What does that mean? Like you flush the toilet with your phone?
I don't understand. What an extra step that doesn't need to be there.
Oh, I got a flush. Hold on. Let me open up the app and then go to like wait for it to load and then
touch flush on the app. I don't know. Sometimes I like the way that like tech is going. Why do I
feel like that that's something that would happen? Well, you don't understand. You see,
it's on your phone. If you have wi-fis out, I can't flush my toilet. This is why we hold onto this.
You know what my favorite item in the game was? The triple shooter. I always want to eat people,
right? It takes like a minute or so to chew them up. Garbage don't use it.
Why is my game lagging? Yeah, that seems like you think this is expensive. This is way too
expensive, I think. Yeah, I'm keeping the original crew here. Copper's good. Why can your PC not
handle this? What's your favorite veggie? This is the first stream I've ever been to. That's an
actually really important question to ask. Um, probably broccoli. Mayonnaise. Yeah, my favorite
vegetable is mayonnaise. Broccoli's great. I actually, I like raw broccoli. I actually prefer
raw broccoli to cooked. I like the snap. Or maybe, maybe very, very like steamed very slightly.
Come on. Yes. I don't really like really cooked broccoli. It kind of falls apart and it turns into
weird mush. Especially if it's, I don't know, I don't like mushy broccoli. I much prefer cooked
broccoli. I like it gently cooked. All right, now we go blue. Prepare with, you know, put a nut here.
Prepare. It's kind of funny because I prefer raw carrots too. I prefer most of the vegetables raw.
Carrots raw. Broccoli raw. What else? Radishes. Just kind of clean them up. Eat them. Yeah. Is it
gonna work out or what? I don't want to use this right now, but if I have to, I will.
I'm actually not a, I don't really like potatoes. Have I talked about my kind of
love-hate relationship with potatoes? Baked potato is not really that appetizing to me at all.
That's an L take. Yeah, that's okay though. All right, this is the big one.
Whatever you say, broccoli boy. That's pretty clean. Ooh, this is the double shooter, isn't it?
Risk it on a baked potato? That's an AI strategy. I don't think so. What the hell are you guys
writing for business? Oh, it's a dream. Okay. I was like, what should I do? What happened?
Something about this loading screen. It doesn't like, uh, definitely this. And I'm, I'll tell you,
people are going to be like, bro, settle down. This is a bad idea. Let's see. Is this the first
loss of the evening? Is it a bad idea? Each one, each row has to have one of these. Oh,
oh, this could have been a huge mistake. Pretty greedy. It is, but it's all right.
So much greed. Yeah. It's a lot of greed. I'm thinking about going even further with it.
No, no, no, no, no, no. There it is. All right. I'm in a good spot. The love of God,
goddess Athena, please purchase a chomper for the love of God. I love how you, you clarify
goddess Athena, just in case we were, uh, we weren't sure. All right. Good. I'm glad he's there.
All right. I've got my two rows. I'm good. I ain't fucking around there. Just love of God,
goddess Athena. You're going to make it rain like a boss. Once you figure it out,
we're doing fine. Everything's good. The double shooter. All right. Good. We've got our base here.
Now we go with the freeze. I've got my wave one coming. This is not gaming. You need to be sipping
on a big gulp. True. Worth it. Look at all. This is clean. Look at this. This is very nice.
What does it say? Downloaded vampire survivors on your recommendation.
Now characters like music will play on my phone. I deleted it. You just made this up.
Hey, if you don't mind, could you please type mustache real quick?
Yeah, let me type in mustache. No, don't do that. That's stupid. Nothing's getting by.
All right. I'm ready. Is there anything missing in this row? I need something, right?
I'm going to wait for 200. Every row is protected. Every row is good to go.
I've got all kinds of explosive everywhere. Everything is good. I'm going to hold this.
Wait, wait. Easy. Simple. All right. Now that's essentially the tutorial. The tutorial's over.
Hello. We're about to launch an all out attack on your house. Sincerely, zombie.
No, it's another one of these. I actually am really not good at these levels,
but I'll try. Let me assess the situation first. Okay. Okay. Obviously they just,
they don't go off the screen, right? They just kind of stack. Every row needs something.
Oh, chopper row. Right here. Have I ever used this thing? Thank you, goddess Athena.
Yeah. I got an orange twice. I might pick another one too. Do you play Hades? Yeah, I, I, I beat it
once or twice, right? But I didn't really, that's like saying I beat Binding of Isaac because I
killed mom's heart once. Right. That's not accurate, but I did complete the game in quotes.
Play it fully then immediately. This is a victory. Play the Sims. I'll probably go back to it at
some point. I almost have too much stuff. I got three bombs. They're just waiting a party.
Do you think you can get, I don't remember how much was in the game. Cause this is the last of,
how many zones are there? All right. Don't go too crazy here. I don't want to waste all these.
These are, Oh, that's right. There's a bonus. There are the bonus stages.
Hey dude, I love you. Can you type mustache real quick? Yeah. Type it real quick.
All right. That's a really long word.
Okay. Pretty long. I can't even place anything. There's no, I got to wait till something dies
like that. This isn't even the big wave. I mean, you might as well just replace these with better
ones. I'm ready to pop this. Oh, that's right. Nighttime. I forgot about nighttime. Yeah. Nighttime
you ha you can't use plants. You have to use the mushrooms. Uh-huh. So are they limited or I forget
how it works. So wait, I can still do this. Can I? These, wait, this is, I don't remember.
What do I do? No, I can use those. Can I? All right. Okay. All right. So let me do,
I definitely want to bring you, bring you, you, you. Yeah, they work. Yeah. Okay. Um, just get,
from what I remember, you just got to get these out quick, bro. But I'm fine. It's really short
range. That's okay. I'll just make sure that this thing does. This bro has no idea. I know what I'm
doing. Just wait till I get my full row. So these dude, these are just a deterrent from me. It's,
they can go right through these, right? Can they be dug up? Okay. There we go. You got through?
All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Ooh, money. Okay. Oh, his pants, his pants come down.
Oh, right. No. Oh, I thought his, no, he drops his new, I thought his pants came down. I was like,
oh, he's like, oh, my pants. And then I saw the underwear. I didn't really look at, I thought I
didn't look behind the newspaper. Bro, you must be high as fuck. No, I'm fine. I want one of these
in every lane. It was a little sloppy, but I think it's fine. I still have the, the bombs here.
I see this. I see this as an, I see this as an issue. Don't worry. You're doing everything
wrong. If I was doing everything wrong, how did I just beat the level without a single lawnmower
being used flawlessly? There we go. Small sun at first and normal sun later. Hey, you've collected
$270 in coins and you collect 750. I'll sell you something really neat. You want to make it big in
the plants versus zombies world. You need to get it together. Jump. Okay. So should I just go all
mushroom? I'm going to try it. This is probably dumb, but I'm doing it. That's not bad. You should
play slots. I don't think I'm going to do that. Double row. I'm doing double row. So it's two
spaces. Okay. Three squares. I just found a shard of bone in a sausage I was eating. Holy shit.
Careful. Be careful. Somebody just said, I think he's watching a long play and commentating.
I was just sitting there watching a game play. I got my arms behind my back, like by my head,
just sitting here. That's exactly what he's doing. When's your next physical? I actually
probably really should get one. Not to get too depressing or real or whatever, but I kind of
hit a point a year or two ago with all the medical shit. I kind of just was like, fuck whatever.
And I just, not that I stopped going, but I had so many, back in like 20, I want to say 2018,
2019, I had probably, I don't even know how many. I was like scanned a fucking hundred times. Like
almost every single part of my body was checked. And in my brain, it's almost like, you know what,
I spent so much time with the doctor in like 2018 through 2020 that they scanned everything.
So that would be, I think I'm all right for a little while. It's always a good idea.
Get checked up on. I shouldn't read this, but I'm going to. No, I mean, it was, hold on,
hold on, hold on. I can't, I'm supposed to, hold on. Wait a minute, wait a minute. This is important.
I actually like this room. It's cheap. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on. Come on. Damn it. Oh, this is bad. This is actually bad.
Oh, I'm in trouble now. I'm in real big trouble. I'm in big trouble right now. I don't know what
to do. I'm in huge trouble right now. I'm in big trouble. Uh oh. It's okay. It's all right.
I fucked it up. It's all right. It's okay. Everything's fine. How did I not have anything
in this whole row? All right. I really thought I could arm it fast enough, but I couldn't.
This run is dead. No, it's not. I should have took the bomb. I think that'll be armed. Yeah,
I think I'm all right. No. Oh, what did I do? I think I really fucked that up big time.
Wait, what do you read the message? All right. I got to pay attention here. There's a, all right,
there's a walnut in front of everything. Yeah, we're good. I lost the lawnmower. That kind of
sucks. Are your late night streaming issues fixed now? I got to be really honest. I have no idea
what the hell is going on. Those of you that don't know, randomly sometimes between like seven and
eight o'clock my internet would just die. I died. I'd never figured it out. There was never an
answer. There was never a reason. It could have been Twitch. It could have been my connection to
Twitch. It's really possible. It's fumes that can pass through screen doors. Is this any good? I'm
focusing way too much on this. It's making me save too much money. I don't like it. How many
squares forward does it do? Shit. I wanted that here like four. So like one, like one, two, three.
I should put it like here. One, two, three, four. Who's your favorite actor? I kind of think that's
impossible to answer because I really don't know. This is a better start than last time. I thought
they could shoot down the whole lane. It should be a better start. What's your favorite plant in
the game? The triple shooter. All right. So I want to put this thing here. That's one, two, three,
four. Okay. Why is this a fake stream? No. What are you talking about? All right. Right here.
How much damage does this do relative to everything else? I'm very concerned about it.
Uh oh. That's why. This shoots through screen doors. All right. No more of these.
Got that. Good. If you could be any plant from Plants vs. Zombies, who would you be?
Um, no, probably the Walnut. I feel like you're really strong. Or I don't know,
maybe one of these mushrooms. They're pretty cool. Who is saying these messages? I don't know. You
are writing them. You are writing them. There's a lot of messages that go by. Okay. I want one of
these in each lane. Now we're doing freezing T-shooters down here on every row. I don't want
to hear how it's a bad strategy. Oh, we're not going to have enough time to do that. Never mind.
What time is it? It is 8, 18 p.m. Pacific time. We're good.
I think this is fine, right? What time is it in ancient Greece? Well, you're asking what time is
it in Greece right now? And I don't think I'd even answer that if I tried. Could I even answer that?
Let's see. Greece is Pacific time. What is, like, London is, what, eight hours ahead?
Ten hours ahead right now? No, what time is it in ancient Greece? What does that even mean?
What does that mean? Is an ancient Greece Greece? Wouldn't it be? It would be the same time.
Why would the time change? It's not like time. Was ancient Greece on a, like, four-hour clock?
What are you talking about? Ooh, seven seeds. Should I do it? Why not? Now it's 5,000.
What about the continental shift? I don't know. What about the continental shift? I actually like
this. I'm going to use it. I think I like this setup. It's a lot cheaper. Well, ancient Greece
would be in the past. That's right. That's true. Who's your favorite ancient Greek philosopher?
Oh, that's easy. Any of the ones that have their arm up and they're wearing, like, a big,
you know, they're wearing, like, a toga and their arm is up and it looks like they're,
like, almost singing, like, as they're talking. Who is that? Like, they have the big elaborate
arm is up. They're like, oh, like, there's like a big elaborate arm up in the air. Like,
they're, like, presenting something. Who is that? All of them. Yeah, that's Roman. That's okay.
I know this is risky, but it's going to work. It worked. That was dumb, but whatever. Okay,
okay. Don't, don't do that. Get up. Nice. Okay, good. Not a bad thought. I just gotta,
I gotta get some walnuts down. Give me a good toothbrush strat. Uh, don't go too hard. A lot
of people like brush the fuck out of their mouth and it's just like, dude, yes, you're going way
too hard. You want small circular motions on the teeth and don't just like, don't just grind out
your gums and shit. Don't do that. All right, we're good with this. I need something here.
I need something here. I think that'll do it. Don't you dare kill that. That was expensive.
Don't kill that. This feels like one of those phone game ads where someone's intentionally
playing bad. Yeah, you used that one a few days ago. That one doesn't work two times in a row.
I see. Yeah, you said that a few days ago. I don't don't work two times in a row.
Give me a hundred. It's kind of like a Minecraft zombie. It's your opinion on blue cheese. I think
it's one of the best things in the world. Genuinely. It's one of the best things in the
world. People really hate it, but they love it. I don't know. I feel like people give blue cheese
a really bad rap, but they eat other shit that's way grosser. That blue cheese, it's, that's
absolutely disgusting while they're drinking like kombucha. Really? Hey, to each their own,
whatever. If you don't like it, you don't like it. I think blue cheese goes on. It goes well
with a lot of stuff. Does every row have one of these? No, it does now. Am I safe here? I think
this is okay. All right. This is a good setup. Buffalo and blue cheese. If you would ask me,
if you say, Hey dude, what, I've probably said this before, but whatever. If you asked me, Hey,
what is the best flavor in the world? The best taste in the world? I would probably say
blue cheese and hot sauce together is probably the greatest sensation on earth.
Like blue cheese and buffalo chicken, like buffalo chicken with blue cheese.
I don't, I don't think there's anything that tastes better than that to me. It's just like,
it's the best tasting thing in the world. I think that, or if I don't know, I'm trying to,
how can I rank this? A really good piece of salmon. And I'm talking top tier restaurant
salmon. That's close. Roasted garlic. Very, very close. Oh, cool. I don't know. Blue cheese and
buffalo chicken, or just that blue cheese and hot sauce flavor. I just don't, when I, okay,
let's talk. So pizza. Hold on. He's talking. Okay. So they can come out of the ground,
right? Yeah. Wait. Oh, I just have to actually click them. I'll just start with this. I get,
I'm a click master. No one's getting by. You know, I'll do this. I'll put them at the very end,
just in case something happens, something crazy. Don't ask me why I'm clearing all these. Is there
a benefit to this? Whatever. I'll do it with my, just with my hand. He's been hardened by years of
iPad gaming. This kind of is a lot of iPad games. Yeah. Yeah. I know what you mean. No, iPad games
have come a really long way. You got to give them at least a little bit of credit. Come on.
Are you on the toilet? No, not, but get rid of those grapes. Is there even a big wave?
No, I got this. Dude, you installed the wrong aim lab. I feel like this is pretty good. All right.
Here we go. I don't need anything. Nobody does better than me. Oh, cool. Oh, speaking of iPad
games, the, the pine tar poker dev, uh, was really, really nice on Twitter. They were like,
Hey, you've mentioned pine tar poker. Oh shit. Um, it seems like you're really cool, dude. Uh,
I like the mushrooms. How good is this? Is there no audio? This should be. How far does this go?
Is this a whole lane or is it, do they have to touch it or something? They have to touch it.
Don't you dare kill that. Come on. I need to do this. Hurry. Come on. Come on. What the fuck
are you doing? Okay. We're good. Sound effects are a little loud. This is bad. Are they fine?
Okay. So this should go up front then. Should this go in the front row?
The crunching noises are loud. I don't know if I can turn those specifically down. This is a problem.
The one time use. Oh shit. I thought he was, I thought he was just going to start walking
around the battlefield, like attacking people. Okay. Nevermind. All right. I get it. I get it.
That was a pretty big waste. Yeah, it was. It's all right. We get what this guy does.
What the hell do you do? Are you just wrong? You're just wrong. That thing actually. Okay.
Think about it like this. That's 75 cents to make somebody turn around. I actually like that.
I'm going to hold it. The bed's fine.
Up there. All right. I'm ready to use it. What, uh, which lane should I use it on? That's the
question. Where's the, I need somebody who runs up here, right? Oh shit. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Okay. I'm going to do
bomb right here. All right. That worked out. Get out of here. Dude, you're a strategic genius.
I'm okay. I'm okay. Ooh, actually someone did say that. Well, I didn't read that shit.
All he's saying. Nobody said that. Nobody said that. Somebody in chat said, actually somebody
didn't say that. I feel like every single loadout has to have this. What do you guys think?
Do mushrooms only? I think that's what's about to happen. Is this your first time playing it?
Uh, I played it a long time ago. I think I got like the third or fourth world. I don't think I
ever finished it. Maybe I did. It's been a long time. I'll try this. So these things are long
range and they duck down when they get close. Oh shit. This might be bad. I love how cheap the
mushrooms are though. All right. This one's going to be hard. I gotta be, I gotta prepare this one.
I should have brought the grave thing. Yeah, this is going to be a problem. I think I can do it still.
Restart? No, I don't have to restart. I think I'm fine. You gonna play anything else tonight?
Um, I don't know. I'm kind of just going until, you know, just whenever. This new thing of,
I talked about it before earlier on the stream, but a lot of you showed up a little bit after I
talked about it. But chill out streams are going to be a lot more frequent. I kind of miss them.
I like just kind of hanging out. Doesn't have to be crazy every time. We're going to get a rock
outbreak. What about the speed runs? Hey, you're talking, I'm sorry, but you're talking to the
seventh place Bob the Builder PlayStation one speed runner. Just remember who you're talking to
when you approach me. How much damage these really do. This is really bad because I got no
opportunity for these. This lane I don't like. I should, I need to put a walnut here. Do you play
magic or anything? I'm excited for grotto beasts. Um, I'm not really, I wasn't really like a card
game fan or anything. And it's interesting because the grotto beast is sort of a,
I mentioned it a little bit briefly, but it's like, it's like a decade of stream references
and like YouTube references and stuff. And originally it was no game. It was just,
oh, maybe we fun to kind of do like, whoa, you can open up and get like a holographic
glue man or something like that. That was like an interesting concept to me. Um, like just like a
physical card, just trading just for fun, just merch, right? Um, but then we got this game
designer who is everything. He just like, Oh, what a thought about this and this and this. It's like,
Holy shit, this is actually trying to be like really, really cool. So hopefully a lot of you
guys like it. If you don't buy, you know, it's no pressure, right? But it's definitely one of
those projects that it's been kind of a long time coming. I know people, you know, Hey, do I have
to like, no, do I have to like play magic, the gathering type games to care? That's not necessarily
the intention. It's just, I've always thought of years and years and years ago. Um, it was like,
what if, what if we did like cards or something, like get like a bunch of artists to do it and a
bunch of cards and you can open them as packs. And it was like a kind of a fleeting thought years ago
and decided to sort of kind of capitalize on it and just do it. Yeah, there's a game component.
If you just want to get packs to do it, if you want to get the starter kit and just be able to
have it, it was in my brain, it was merch that was, Oh no, where can we get some more t-shirts? Can
we get some more of this more of that? I'm just thinking, what about just like a bunch of cards
with a bunch of references and shit? I feel like it'd be fun. There are 200 cards. I think there's
like over a hundred cards that have some type of screen reference, a screen character on them.
The NFTs? No, it's more akin to like Pokemon than it is like an NFT or like, you know,
Magic the Gathering or something. I got too cocky. I got too cocky with like a thousand gulls.
I think I'm all right. Oh, do it. Shit. I missed it. I missed it. No, I don't know what to do. I'm
freaking out. He just completely blew it. No, I didn't. I'm fine. I mean, the end got a little
messed up, but it's all right. You think Grotto Beast will be competitive? I don't know. I mean,
that wasn't really the intention. It was just like some fun merch for people to collect if they
wanted to. And the way it stands out right now is we have, there's a starter kit that'll have two
decks in it with like some dice and some other cool stuff. And when that, when that actually gets
time to kind of talk about it, I'll go into way more detail, but each booster pack is going to
have one guaranteed rare and one guaranteed hollow. So you'll be able to kind of, if you want,
it's just so cool. There's like a hollow and a rare in every single pack. Years ago, there was
this, like I mentioned earlier of like, imagine if there was like a holographic blue man that you
could get in a card pack. That was like interesting to me. It was like funny to me in a way. Like,
wow, that's cool. I actually kind of don't, this thing's okay. Because there was always the question
of how would people in the community play with each other? Not really sure, but I'm sure some
people maybe, I mean, I'm sure a lot of you guys at this point know each other. I think there's a
lot of people in real life that know each other just over the years, but that's, you know, that's
just extra awesome shit that's on top of the project. What is this? It mobilizes all zombies
on the screen. Is it worth it? I'll try it. Oh, what the hell am I thinking? This is, you have to
have this in every single loadout. I really think so. Oh shit, the grave buster. I have to rely on
this though. I need it. What's the prices? How much would the cards be? We're trying to make it so,
because it's, it's tricky because I really don't want to charge some crazy amount of money for
this stuff, but because it's a, it's a limited amount of cards and we have to essentially
kind of commission up the manufacturing. We're trying to make it affordable, but also, I mean,
I don't want to just kind of blow up my bank account. I think this is okay. I'll go with this.
There are some prices we're floating around at and I'm trying to keep it reasonable if I can.
Is it going to be under a hundred? Yes. For the starter kit starter kit has, um, I believe I don't,
and I don't want to give any wrong information, but starter kit is going to have two full decks
in it. I think a couple of booster packs in the starter kit, some placemat, some dice, custom dice,
and it's, it will be under a hundred dollars. I can promise you that well, well under a hundred
dollars, not like 99, 99. Oh yeah, guys, it's going to be, it's going to be well under a hundred
bucks for the starter kit. Yeah. Like 97, 98, of course, like 90, 99, 98 and trying to price this
stuff too. We've had tons of conversations about it. I don't want to make it so expensive that
people just can't fucking afford it. It's like, wait, should the starter, how much should the
packs be like 15 bucks? 20? No, I don't want to do that. Even though like even with manufacturing
costs included and everything, what does that do? What is going on here? I need the explosion. I
don't know what to do. See, this is a crutch for me. I'm just, okay, no, that's fine. See how much
I need that? Imagine that wasn't in the loadout. And there are a limited amount of them. So we
don't really have, oh, it's this store and it's just the way to have some kind of agreement where
it's just going to be printed forever. That's not really the case right now. We're trying to gauge
how, how many people actually want to buy it or how many people actually would purchase something
like that. Because it's asking a lot. It is. And I understand that. And I want to make sure you guys
get that too. That even if I try to get like a starter kit somewhere in that, like under a
hundred dollar range, that's still a lot of fucking money to ask somebody to be like, hey,
spend like a bunch of fucking money on this thing. I don't want people to feel like it's
not worth it or something. What are you talking about? I'm talking about the router piece.
And the idea is to make it so, to make sure people can get them if you want them. Perfect
opportunity. Can you tell me why that? Can you tell me that this shouldn't be in every single
loadout? From my understanding, we're going to make sure that whoever wants to get them,
will be able to get them. If you know what I mean. Could you play Grotto beast on the toilet?
I think that would be very, that would be impossible. I think how about international
shipping? We, that was a question we've recently asked to the, our fulfillment people.
And I don't think it's going to be anything terrible from what we were told, but I want to
make sure you guys get the right info. And I don't, I mean, this is obviously, I'm just like,
Oh, chill stream. We were just talking. I don't want to just give you wrong info.
Can we buy boosters with channel points? No, you cannot. Doomshroom. International shipping
is always a nightmare. Yeah. And unfortunately there's not much I can really do about it. It
just kind of is what it is, but I don't think it's going to be terrible. I'll try the Doomshroom
for the different rarities. So there's, there are common cards and there are rare cards. And
then obviously there's hollow versions. I think of everything. You get a hollow in every pack.
You get a rare in every pack, but what those are, that's all kind of random. You didn't get
the grave buster. Shit. It's all right. What about anything digital? It's, it's really tricky
because I don't, I don't really know if I even have an answer to that question because we have
this plan of like, we have this limited amount of these cards and these kits. That's what we
got. And that's what we're going to do. All that stuff would have to come later, depending on
how many people care about it or buy it or, and all that stuff. Don't eat that. Are they standard
size cards? I believe they are. Believe they are. Will it be possible to collect all the cards with
it being limited to that? I don't, I don't know. I don't think so. We still were talking about like
what happens after. How do we handle something like that? Cause at the very, very end of the day,
it was sort of just a, it was sort of a project that was based around, Hey, what do you get in
this pack? Oh, whoa, cool. What did you get in yours? Kind of thing. All right. Like don't tell
anybody this because it's a secret. I thought about putting in like golden tickets and like,
there's something like, what the fuck is this? But like a hundred golden tickets in packs or
something. I'm going to lose. Okay. Hold on. I thought about like, Oh, what if like this just,
I don't know. Me giving like, like the middle finger in a Polaroid, like wrapped in a golden
foil or something in them. But I was like, Oh, we kind of, we probably can't. I got to use this
right now before I lose. Oh fuck. Hold on. I was talking. But like, I don't, I don't want to do
that. That's probably a bad idea. Reset, reset, reset, reset, reset, reset. This is, I fucked it
up. Reset. This time I'm taking this. All right. I think that's good. This sucks, but it's okay.
My child bought a pack. Yeah. I, that's, that's what I mean. I want it to be very just kind of
general audience. Like it doesn't matter. I kind of want like some little kid, Oh Grotto beast.
What's this? And they open it. It's just me with like a cigarette in my mouth, giving like two
fingers. No, that's not a good idea. That would be bad. Don't ask me why there would be a cigarette,
like a cigar or something. Cigarette comedian. Yeah. Have you thought about Kickstarter to do
anything more like this? I've thought about it, but I don't want to do it. I would rather need to
be sort of, I would rather need to answer to myself and have to answer to a bunch of people
is money I took. I don't, I'm, I don't know if I'm completely comfortable doing that. And there's
not, I don't have anything, something wrong, I don't think with something like a Kickstarter, but
just personally, I would rather be the one responsible for it because who knows, right?
And look, I am not, I'm not certain how well or how poorly this project is going to do. I don't
know. I would rather just be able to exist and be like a fun thing that people think maybe for a
little while is cool. And maybe, maybe not. Maybe if you really like it, but I would rather be
beholden to myself with that and not be like, yeah, everybody. I want to do this project called
Grotto beast. Please give me hundreds of thousands of dollars and yeah, let me, uh, cool. And then
it comes out and what if it's not, what if you don't like it? I don't ever want that to happen.
I really don't. I would rather it be something that I did than something that you had to pay for.
This guy's English is terrible. My English? What do you mean? My English? What do you mean?
My English is bad. Are you in bed? Yeah, I'm lying. I'm lying on my back right now.
I think I'm doing it. I'm going to do an explosion over here.
Pairing for it. Stop yelling at me. Stop yelling at me. Oh, he's got a huge raid coming in.
Box box. What's up? Welcome all box box viewers. Chilling out playing some plants versus zombies.
Hope you had a good stream box box. Good to see your name. Yeah. Just chilling out. No camera
or anything. Just relaxing. Oh wait. No, this is fine. I have a lot of money now. Let's get rid
of some more of these. I think I'm safe. I need to start replacing these though. That's okay.
Oh, I don't even want to deal with it. It'll probably respawn by the time I'm here, right?
Better. I didn't want to put it there. I'm annoyed by that. Okay. I think I'm in a good spot.
There we go. Good. Everything is solid. What about are you doing anything about scalpers?
So because we have a limited amount, it's not just like, oh yeah, there's going to be like
hundreds of millions of packs are being created, right? We're going to be doing a system where
I think we're going to, and I don't want to get this wrong, so it could change,
but there are things we're going to be doing to make it so whoever wants to order them can be like,
I want these and I want this many. And then when the limited run is over, that's kind of it.
That's pretty clean. Something like pre-orders. Yeah. We've talked about like stuff like pre-sales
to kind of be like, all right, who's buying this? Yeah, I'm thinking about it. It's something,
because like I said, I want to make sure that it's like a fun thing for the community to do,
because that's what it is at the end of the day. It's sort of that 10 plus years of references and
stuff. And it's kind of like Omega merch in a way. What about stuff like tournaments? I really,
I don't know. I think I really, we really kind of need to see what happens, like how people
kind of consume it and what they think about it. And I am much more concerned with people being
like, this was fun. I enjoyed this. No, that's okay. I think that kind of stuff has to happen
after, later after the fact. I really like this chill stream format. Can you please do some back
flips and jumping jacks? Oh, I'm all right. Yeah. There is a, you can follow the Grotty Beast
Twitter. You can sign up on the Grotty Beast website. What if I just do this? Okay. That
thing's insane, but I can't put anything else there, right? A lot of these. Are you ever going
to get a tattoo of your channel logo? No, I'm not. I don't have a plan to do that. I just hope
people like it. A lot of the concerns that I always have with anything, whether it's a show
or a stream or like if people genuinely think that was like, hey, or cool or fun or whatever
goes through my mind a lot. Freeze them dummy. I got, I'm going to hold on to my freezes. Oh
shit. I'm out of room. Hopefully this. Okay. Oh, that's a lot of money. Come on. Come on. Come on.
There we go. Do you have any life-size cardboard cutouts of you? I do not. Sorry to disappoint.
There was hesitation in your voice. Uh-oh. Look out. Hold on. We're going to do this.
Freeze. Oh, this is the second area done. What about the Battle Axe stream? Yeah. Battle Axe
stream has changed a few times. I made it way more elaborate and then I simplified it and then
I made it way more elaborate again. It's my own fault. Indecisive Andy. Pretty much. Oh, I missed.
Sorry. Just die. Your face is all smushed up. Just die already. Die. Die. Why is he still alive?
Fine. This is going to be huge. You have a bunch of dooms? Yeah, I'm going to use them right here.
Check this out. While you save them. That was cheese. Do you plant non aqua? Oh, okay. Right.
Oh, they introduced this stuff. I forgot about this. They need to put the lay pads down. Well,
I mean, that's incredibly important. Do utility first. Uh, the pool stages are the best. How come
you said that like this was a recent update to the game? Yeah. Oh yeah. The most recent patch.
They probably last patch and plans for zombies one was probably like 2012. What should I bring?
It's pretty standard, right? I'll just, I'm going to be greedy. Yeah, let's be wicked greedy.
The last patch of the game was the steam update. Oh, then like actually porting it to steam.
What is the oldest reference in grotto beasts? That's a good question. I wonder. I'd have to
look up. I'd have to look into it. Get armed, please. It's I'll tell you a little bit of lore,
though. There are a couple of cards that are referencing a stream that never happened.
And there's a story there. I thought, okay, so a stream was going to happen
that ended up not happening. And there are grotto beast references to this stream
and it never happened. So people are going to be like, what does this even mean?
Why is this a card? Cause I thought it was going to happen before grotto beast came out.
Come on. I know you can do it. Come on. I know you can do it. Come on. I know you can do it.
Come on. I know you can do it. Come on. I know you can do it. Come on. I don't care.
Still putting sunflowers in the back. Wait, what? Sunflowers should go back here to protect them.
Dude, don't get me started. I might do a triple column. Do not blow up from that.
I mean, I'll be pissed. Will it happen in the future? No. That's the, that's the interesting
thing. No. What stream was it? I wonder if you guys maybe we'll figure it out. I'm curious if
people know. You will know. It's referencing a couple of direct jokes from this, that stream
that was going to happen. I think they were pretty funny, but that's just me. No, it's not
the hamster stream. Well, you're talking about the hamster stream. Like that was a stream that was
going to happen. That stream was not going to happen. They haven't even come close. There we
go. Was it Mr. Green's casino? Yes. Yes, it was. I guess what I said, the stream's not happening
anymore. So why don't we just talk about it? I was going to do a stream kind of late last year
where I got in as I'm talking like Jim Carrey Grinch level prosthetics and painted myself green
and ran a casino and invited a bunch of streamers to it. Yeah, it was going to be
fucked up too. It was going to be fucking wild and there's going to be all kinds of fucked up games
like, Oh, there's blackjack. But what the hell is that over there? It was because of the gambling
ban. Um, I'd had some to do with it, but I think just logistically, it was going to be hard to do
at the end of that year. And there was a lot of other stuff that I wanted to do at the end of
the year. It had a little bit to do with it. I think, wait, this thing is actually kind of good,
isn't it? Yeah, I was going to walk around. There was going to be like four assistants behind me,
you know, doing those kinds of routines. If for some reason this ever does happen for any reason,
which I'm telling you it's not, there is some stuff that's really fun in there. I think why
won't it happen? Cause it's very expensive show. And I learned that too, through the process of
trying to figure out how to do it. That's a, that's a show that's, um, very expensive. We will pay
for it kicks. No, no, no, we're not doing kickstarters. Um, I like this thing a lot.
Yeah. Kickstart, kickstart me to open up my own casino. If you came across that on Kickstarter,
I'm pretty sure you would immediately click the X in the top right corner.
Imagine coming across that at the squash is okay. In fact, I'm going to use it probably right now.
Wow. Only 50 cents too. I think if you had the money, it would be easier. Um, sometimes it's
really not about the money, about like how logistically they even get it off the ground
in the first place. We're going to be just utilizing this. It's not about the money.
Is this game easy? I would say this game is, I don't think it's really hard. It's more just kind
of fun. It's relaxing. It gets, I think it gets really hard eventually. It's casual. It's a casual
game, but you know, we played those. Nothing wrong with that. Would it be more expensive than
Yes. At least that was the thought process. Do not come close please. No.
Ooh. Present. Mini games unlocked. Cool. Um, okay. I got to thank God for the squash.
Something else that's important too. And it's kind of a real talk stream maybe in a way too.
I also don't want, I don't know. I kind of don't want to fly too close to the sun in a way.
Okay. It's just like, Oh, look at all these things to do. Look, all these ideas,
all these things. So maybe I'll do this and maybe I'll do that. I really don't want to,
you know, what, you know, go too hard on something. Uh-oh. Oh my God. I need to do this right now.
That's okay. Oh my God. I'm not even paying any attention.
Let's real talk for a second. I'm not playing the game anymore. You can very clearly tell.
Somebody just called me Icarus. What is Icarus? You don't want to overexert yourself.
I feel like I've had so much fun and so many of these projects have been so much
just fun to work on. I guess like there's a little bit of fear that I'm, if you go too hard,
too much, I got to go bigger. I've got to go better. I've got to do more. I don't want to
fuck it up for myself in a way. I'm kind of forcing myself to do like a huge thing. It's almost,
I don't know. You just referenced Icarus? Yeah, I know. Did I? You're uneducated. I just heard,
I've heard that term before. Oh shit. I flew too close to the sun. Uh-oh. What happened?
Little bro doesn't know the myth. What? I, I feel like I've heard it on like TV before.
He can't be serious. That can be hard. He probably thought it was from kid Icarus. You know,
I was going to ask. Oh, you mean, hey, they ain't even coming close. I think to finish that thought,
one of the reasons to bring streams like this back. So I don't do that. I don't kind of just
fly into outer space. I think streams like this bringing these back are kind of grounding for me
in a way that makes sense. It wants us to lower our expectations. If that's how you see it, then
that's probably what I mean. One winged Andy. Ladies and gentlemen, the play through has just
begun. This is my favorite plant in the game. It's so expensive. I like the double flower too.
Oh, the shop. That's right. There is the shop. Can I do it from the main menu? Wait a minute.
Is there, how do I get there? I haven't unlocked it. That laugh. I don't need this anymore. I'm
going to use this. Go wait. No, I need this. Oh, after beating three, four, you've set it for
Pikmin four. Nobody tell them. Do you guys remember the Pikmin streams for the Wii? I, I got so
irrationally angry at that game. I don't even know why it's, it's just kind of, I mean, it's not,
that's not a relaxing game. You're against the clock. I complained about the Wiimote and this
is not an exaggeration. Probably, probably 30 times over the course of what? Two, five to six
hour streams. If you break it down, it's like, I complained about the Wiimote once every probably
12 minutes. And we're not talking about very, no, the Wiimote stinks. No, it was like, like,
fuck this whole system. Like I hated it for a while. Right? Like I was embarrassingly angry
at that game. Come on. No, what did I do that for? It's all right. It shoots in three lanes.
I fucked up. Good thing I have the crutch. I wanted to cover the whole pool, but I forgot
what I was doing. There's a 32 minute video called Wiimote woes. Yeah, I'm sure there is.
Look at that. Look at that coverage now. You'd be probably asking,
what about this spot, man? This guy who cares being doing shit.
And he said, bro, what? I'm fine. This is, I'm, I'm, I'm teching right now. Don't you understand?
I'm teching. What you got? See ya. I'm teching. It's getting overwhelmed there.
My teching is almost done. What does teching mean? It means when you play an RTS, right?
And you don't do anything but build all like the upgraded buildings and just hope that nobody
comes and attacks you in the first like 30 minutes of the game. Plans for zombies. You
don't have to tech. Yeah, but I want to look and now the huge wave is going to come and I've got a
lot of stuff doubling up here too. All right. I think I'm good. A lot of coverage. Nice. Yeah,
we're good. Look at that. How can you put a three shot in the top lane? Um, yeah, I messed that one
up. That's on me. You're nothing without your bombs. That's good. I like that.
Quarantine that pulls a zombie underwater. Nice. What flavor deodorant do you wear?
Deodorants don't have a flavor. They have a smell. Hey dude, what flavor deodorant do you have on?
Oh, it's a green apple. Um, I, I'll be honest. I don't really have a preference. It's just whatever
is whatever the first thing that I see that smells remotely. Okay. In like a drug store
or something. Is there, okay, that's what I'm going to do. I really don't like the
deodorants that have that heavy, heavy smell. No, it's not for me. All right. I gotta be careful.
I don't do too much like, you know, tech. This is a lot of utility and not a whole lot of damage.
It's all right. I'll just tech. I'll be fine. I'm just going to, yeah, I'll be fine.
Let me do a regular though. There we go. No, don't you hate when that happens. It's okay.
I don't like the start, but it's okay. Why are you throwing? I haven't wig up. Look at all,
we got plenty of time. I'm the no rush. Oh my goodness. Thank God. Hey, we need to do that.
This is not throwing. When somebody jumps in the water, they're going to get pulled down.
Need to get something out there. Your Elden ring streams were more children. I, uh,
I disagree. I don't think that's accurate. I almost like bit my camera during those streams.
I, I think you're, I think you're wrong on that one. Start. Oh, you tech. Look at that placement
too. Oh, you just, you dream of placement like that. All right. See, this is why I did this.
I need, I want one here and one here and then I'll stop with the triples. My favorite item.
Of course I'm going to use it. Would you say that you're the Jim Carrey of streaming? No,
I think comparing yourselves to other comparing yourself to other people is always a kind of a
recipe for kind of disaster in my mind. I'm just trying to be, I'm just trying to be this dude here.
You know what? Okay. Let's go even more. I'm like, how do you even make that comparison? No,
I wouldn't. Would you say that you're the German nine eight five Twitch? Yeah, I'm not. Yeah. I
mean, that's close. I think maybe this is godly placement by the way. What do you think you're
doing? Oh, it's okay. I'm neglecting the top and bottom row, but it's all right. I didn't miss
money. They're impossible. These things are useful. I'm all right. I need to slow down with these
things. You missed money. Oh shit. All right. I got like, I got like five grand down here.
Pretty good. Taking a lot of hits. Got one more big wave. You know what? Let's see. Let's just
triple up on it. Let's go. Just like swallowed that word. Replace the P shooter. No, nothing's
getting for this. Are you kidding me? Good carry bomb. After this, I'm going to take a quick break
here. Otto, he wants to go outside. You can now visit the shop. Cool. My car keys.
Ooh, 20,000. Um, all right. Let me look at this first. All right. We're just going to,
I'll take a quick break. I'll be right back. I'm just going to let Otto out. Let me get some more
tea. I'll be right back. Let's keep this music. It's fine. He's just been talking. He's just going
like, stop this mad man. He's just been talking to you. Cancel Dave. What the fuck? All right.
Let's keep going. Dude, your channel is going to get banned. Okay. So I have 600 bucks. I get the
rake. Oh, this is a consumable. I don't think I want this. Ooh. Yep. I'm saving up for that.
First thing I want to get the pool cleaner. Yeah. The pool cleaner is important. This is
the most important thing. Yeah. I'm not, I don't want to defend your shins a little. Oh,
very pixelated. Double sunflower is mid. What? That's not twice the sun.
I fucked it up. It's all right. Is Dave a mog like, no, I wouldn't say so.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. I have to.
It's 1153 where I'm from. Did I drink a coffee? 1153 PM? Or is that AM? AM or PM? PM? I'm not
going to tell you what you should and shouldn't do with your life, but I feel like that's a very
late. Well, when did you get up? That's another question. Did you wake up at 1030 PM? That's a
question. Are you on like a reverse schedule right now? These are all important questions,
Dave. No coffee past three. I would tell you that, but that's a lie. There's tons of times
you've seen me stream past five, six, seven o'clock where I've had coffee or something.
These bomb placements, they're just so good. Yeah. Also, what's your relationship with caffeine
too? That's important. Crying with laughter. Wasn't it good though? Wasn't it funny? Wasn't
it funny? That's going to die, right? Yeah. A nice like, a nice cappuccino is nice though.
Cappuccino is a nice kind of night coffee, afternoon coffee, I think.
Espresso and shit. Cappuccinos are fine. I'll order a cappuccino at a restaurant just to kind
of make people think like, oh yeah, of course. Any desserts or coffee or anything? Of course.
I'll take a cappuccino. Oh, okay. That's what you're ordering. Yeah. And then when I get it,
I hold it up and I take a little sip and I go, perfect. I don't, I don't actually do that.
You psycho. I don't, I'm kidding. I don't do that. I actually really liked this one. All right. We're
back to, wait, wait, wait. This thing runs over plants, right? Is it two hands or one on the
coffee? I'm imagining both hands holding it from the bottom and slowly dipping it up and
it might like blink, blink, blink, blink. Eyes going up, blink, blink, blink. Oh, it's so good.
You're going to spill it, dude. Yeah. All right. What do I want to do? What the fuck are you
talking about? We're talking about drinking cappuccino. Guys, the last time I drank cappuccino,
I don't even, there's no memory. I know I've done it like three times. This needs to go here.
Oh no, no, no, no. All right. I'm doing a new crutch. It's the jalapeno. I think that's a new
crutch. Why are you drinking coffee? Looney Tunes style. That's a great comment. Someone said,
don't use lilies at the beginning. You're ruining your economy. I think you're actually right,
but it's in my brain. It's kind of wired there. I got a plan. Don't worry.
Look, my economy is doing fine. I almost did it. See, I thought about what that
person in chat said. I didn't do it. I thought about it. I need some big ones. All right. I need
some triples. Was it waste? Maybe for you. It was. It wasn't for me. This is going to die, right?
This is going to die, right? All right. This is where it begins. We did our teching in the
beginning. Now it's time to really, really let it all lose here. Come on. Now I'm going to put one
right here. And we just steam roll. Everything's fine. Did you just make the whole area sunflowers?
I mean, I was loose. Maybe you'd think it was funny for a minute. Can that hit more than one
person? It can. Holy shit. I didn't know that. Going down the middle again. Come on. Be enough.
I missed a gold coin. Oh, fuck. It was a big one. Pick up the coins. I was picking up the
fucking sun. 1 a.m. plans for zombies goes pretty hard. All right. This is it. I think I'm good.
I got everything I need. Let's preemptively. All right. I'm preparing. And I think I'm all right.
I'm going to drop this right here. Ready? There we go. You lost the symmetry. We don't need
symmetry. So is this like damage over time? I think somebody's asked me about my viewer
count or something. I try not to pay attention to it because view count is one of those things that
you really kind of get in your head. I really don't want it to. We make jokes a lot of time
of like, oh, my God, a bunch of people left. But, you know, I mean, I'm just I don't really
I don't want to pay that much attention to it alone. Every single zombie is my enemy.
No, this thing's probably bad here. It's a lot of water, right? How much is it right in the middle?
Is that worth taking? I'll try it. Why not? How could I forget my favorite? Does anybody else
have to line them up correctly? In my brain, this is the correct order. All right, let's try it.
I'm not going to do it this time. I'm going to skip this. I'm not going to put two of these
lily pads down. I almost did it while I was talking about it. You can't play plants versus
zombie without beatboxing once. Dude, come on. Why is that accurate, though? It's funny. Remember,
what's a nutmeg? I have no idea. I just know you grind it against like a shaver thing and
you put it on stuff as a nut of some kind. I don't have any idea what it is. Spice? I mean,
what the hell even is it? It's a nut. Yeah, that's what I said. I said, I don't know like what
deal is. I just know it's a nut and you shave it on to make like things tasty.
Yeah, speaking of that, you guys ever seen how weird chocolate is?
I'm convinced that aliens fucking put chocolate on this planet. It's literally like alien eggs.
Have you ever seen what it looks like? I got like a cocoa pod. It's fucking insane looking.
Here we go. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Yeah, hold on. Hold on. Hold on a second.
Now that's right. We're gonna relax. There's no reason to talk about aliens. And if they may or
may not have landed here and drop cocoa pods with like alien fucking fluid in them. You know what?
Let's try this. I'm just curious. How does this work? I got some more tea, by the way. Anybody
else get any? Autumn row? Yeah. Good. I'm gonna put a triple here. Is it chamomile? It's orange
spice. I don't know exactly what it is. That's probably nutmeg or something fucking weird.
Shave the nutmeg in it myself. I need a triple here. Yeah. Yeah. I didn't get this, but I might
not. And it's making me very concerned. Yep. I'm just gonna go for it. It's all about the tech.
I kind of like these. They stick around forever. Can anything break those?
It's just a nice little bit of damage before they get over here. Uh, there's gonna be only
breaking. Too much nutmeg can actually poison you. Really? That's terrifying. I feel like a lot of
things are like that though. Too much of anything will kill you. Yeah. That's why you just gotta
follow that philosophy. Too much of anything is gonna, is gonna kill you. Just do everything
in moderation. Put a little bit of nutmeg on it. Not the whole bottle, but I don't know what
this conversation is. If I'm honest with you. Uh, I want one here. Symmetry is broken here,
but whatever. What about too much germa? Yeah. I would say that too. Die. Come on. Come on.
I've been holding this tea in my hand and I haven't taken one sip in my, I was like,
why does my arm hurt? It's because I've just been holding it up in my hand. Pretty clean.
One more wave. I gotta defend the top and bottom rows here.
I kind of feel like that you kind of want to play this game from 15 feet away. I feel like
that would be easier. I feel like I could see more if I would just sat like 20 feet away.
Just old? Yeah, that's true. Penses. Guys. No, the symmetry! No!
Feels like watching a VOD from years ago in real time. Glad you're bringing these back.
Now I'm glad to hear that. I hope that's um, I hope it's been like a chill time.
So many games to play. Just hang out and do this. Expect way more of these. These streams are wicked
chill, man. Check the shop. Ooh, good idea. Are these actually worth it? An extra line of this.
Should I buy it? I want to save up my favorite thing. Would you play old school RuneScape?
I'm going to save. Oh, these things are awesome. I'm going to be, if I take this, I'm going to be
such a tech idiot. I'm going to spend the entire first three waves just building out this tech.
I don't care. Should I even? No, I need. I think this is good. I got a lot of things I can do.
I'll try it. Okay. Let's tech. Play OSRS. You have no cheap attackers. Sorry. I got this. I got this.
I just need to get to a point where I can do one of these downs. Like Garden Warfare. I'm up for
anything. I really am. See? Check this out. We good? He's not even close. That's actually a pretty
good idea. Just playing something like a Garden Warfare. Like, who cares? All right. I'm sure a
lot of you guys probably join in the games and stuff and whatever. It'd be fun. Oh, I actually
blew it. I blew it. Maybe not. I blew it. I blew it. I blew it. I got to restart. That was my own
fault. No, I blew it. I shouldn't have put the lily pads down. Let's try that. I won't fuck it
up this time. This is a hard game to take a sip of a drink, by the way. Like, my finger has to
constantly be on the mouse. Because if I miss clicking one of these, people are going to
omega-lul. I'm going to be incredibly embarrassed. No more. Just wait. Put one of these down here.
There. I think the crisis has been averted. I'm getting so greedy. I had to. Oh, wait. I don't
have my smasher. I'm nothing without the smasher. I have to stop doing this. I'm just obsessed with
it. I'm obsessed with sunflower money. You're so tan today. Thanks. I'm getting some sun.
All right. I've got to focus on this. Fire goes here. Please kill that.
You should play Viva Pinata again. I've actually thought about playing something like that again.
All right. Hold on. This is important. This is super important.
Oh, important. Important. Okay. This is my opportunity here.
There it is. All right. I've got to get two triples down here. What the hell was that?
I thought that was a monkey. Oh, okay. Hold on. Oh, shit. I need my smasher. I'm nothing without
the smasher. I really am. I'm in trouble here. I have to do this. Here we go.
Kids are losing at a kid's game. We're good. Where are you going? Where? Right there. Got it.
Okay. Got it. All right. This is a big deal. Use the spikeweed before the walnut.
Shit. You're right. Hold on. All right. That should be that. That should take care of the middle.
You jumped over it. You piece of crap. We're good. Cool. Watch your language.
I have a big one. Yeah. Plans for zombies. When was the last thing they released?
Is Garden Warfare 2 the last thing they made? We've got these dolphin assholes.
So I need to hold these for when they show up. They're making three, but it looks soulless.
Oh, that's unfortunate. If I remember, you don't take both. You take one or the other.
I'm going to take this one. I need this though. You saw how bad that was. Play something in the
first lane so the water ones jump right over it. Good idea. I'll try this. I'm okay with
this for now. Dolphin can't jump over the tall nut. Ate out the dolphin with a lily. That's true,
but they're the same price. I guess this is on cooldown. Okay. This is a big one. Save money.
Squash is my favorite. Yeah, I think it is. Very useful. Let's get one in there.
Probably shouldn't have done this yet, but it's all right. Stare? Fuck you.
I just said fuck you. What is stare? What is that? Is it an emote? I can't see for some reason.
I don't know what to do. Wait, I have an idea. No, I have to do this. Oh shit. I was paying. I
just restart. I'm so mad. I was looking over at chat and somebody said fuck you and it made me
laugh. So I forgot what I was doing. Let's try that again. This is too expensive for now. It really
is. They're going to stop using it. Skill issue. Yeah, it usually is. Is it a tech issue? No,
I think it's pretty good. Got to use these quick because then it'll go and recharge immediately.
This will be charged by the time it gets down here. Here we go. All right. This is much better.
I got way more money coming in. Good. Done. Okay. We're going. We're on it now. Again that. I'm
going to put one of these in every single lane. Just you watch. His brain is fried. I'm fine.
His brain. I'm just chilling, man. Don't jump over that. Jump on his head. Yeah, two of us can do
that. Can't jump over that. All right. This is so much better. Now we load these all up.
I'm going to be sick. Big wave. Oh shit. Come on. I'm not ready. I have the cherry bombs. All right.
Okay. I'm strong. Go. All right. We're good. I'm going to put one of these here
and then I want to put a big nut over there. That we go. I think this is a win. Yeah,
this is much cleaner. Nobody's getting by this shit. Look at that. Look at that unbelievable wall
of defense. You'd be full of shit if you think you get over that. Two more big waves though.
Not that I'm concerned, but it would get ugly. How are you still here? Really? No, don't do that.
Kidding me. Why does he make it that far? I know that's stupid, but you know, whatever,
I don't have very much options right now. I should have put these closer forward, but it's all right.
It's all right. It's going to be fine. I understand that I screwed up, but it's okay.
I have bomb here. Get that shit out of here. Get that shit out of here. Okay. I don't know
what that was, but I'm glad I had this smusher. What? Oh my goodness. That was a whole bobsled
team. All right. I need to, where do I put this last nut down here? Probably. Yeah. Like right here.
Excuse me. Why can I? All right. Come on. Pray. Okay. Come on. I think I'm all right.
Smush. Best thing in the whole game. Without a doubt. Praying. Do you feel it? I kind of did.
I heard you were having a pool party. We think that is fun. We'll be right over. I'm probably
going to screw this one up a few times. We'll see. Is that enough room you think? Oh, give me
something to work with. What is this? Give me something to work with. Give me something to work
with. Give me some, give me something to work with. You gotta give me something to work with.
See? Look, it's random. It was a terrible RNG. Give me something to work with. I think I'm okay.
I see the vision. Yeah. Coming together. Give me something to work with. Fuck out of here with
this shit. Okay. I get squashed. I can't even get close. It's worked out. I need another
pulley pad here. We are doing this down here. Sorry. All right. This is working out. I need
some more lilies. I need three lilies right here. A lot of the top and bottom. Yeah. Not until I get
everything squared away here. I can't even see where the mouse is. These run over the, wait,
they can run. They run the nuts over. I didn't know that. Give me another lily pad. What? Because
I said I'm going to run my nuts over. All right. Here comes the big wave. I need to just, all right.
I gotta place them. I have to, I have to put these down. Finally, bro. What? I'm doing fine.
Look at that. We're good. Aquatic plant that shoots short ranged spores. Cool. You know,
they used to call me fog man because I would hang out in the fog and jump out at people.
Those are the days. Get out of my face. Okay. This is nighttime. What is this? It's been 10 years.
Okay. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Wait, is it, we still, is there a pool still? Is there still a pool?
No, we're not in a pool. Is there still a pool? There is. They have to be in the correct order.
I'm sorry. They just have to be. Let's try it. I just put a lily pad down here. Wait, wait,
I'll try it still. I don't need lily pads. Not necessarily. Oh, the sun shrooms. That's right.
Come on, hurry up. Okay. I know I can't really see, but this should be all right.
I got to move stuff up even though I can't see. What's with all this? What do you do?
I forget. What the hell does this thing do? What does it do? I don't even know what it does.
You'll see. You'll see with like a little like hee-hee-hee face. I didn't even use any of these.
I don't even have enough time to, on these early levels, probably shouldn't even do a second row.
Kind of unnecessary. I think I'm good. I don't like the fog though. It's annoying.
Assuming that's to get rid of it. That was too close. That was not close. Hmm. Okay. Explosive
surprise. So I'm assuming if he plays the whole song, then it'll blow up. You'll see.
All right. So what did I do wrong there? What can I improve on? Tell me. What can I improve on?
I think I'm doing one column of that. These things are just too important.
Anyway, I need the lily pads. I like these. Don't take the water shroom. Squash is important. I
need to take the lantern, right? I don't want to just have no damage though. I feel like this is
not enough. Is that not enough? Maybe just a regular peace shooter? Don't take any lily pads.
I'll try no lily pads. Just utilize this stuff. This is... I'll try it. I'll try it.
You're getting less sunlight. You should do the walnut. That's a good point, but let's try it.
Bold move. Yeah. I need that lantern. Okay. So it's only an area. Still helpful though.
How are you going to attack the middle with my aquatic sea shrooms? Something in the water?
Don't eat that. You piece of shit. Stop eating that. Yeah. I should have listened to that shatter.
That was the right call. I fucked it up. No, I fucked it up. I'm just going to reset. I played
it before, but not really to this extent. I played the second one on iPad and horrible experience.
Was the second one too hard? The second one just... It was just kind of annoying. It really,
really kind of encouraged me spending a ton of money on it. Some of the levels were so,
so hard that it had these pay mechanics where you could use these certain currency and buy
like a lightning move. It just wiped out the whole screen. And I'm talking like wiped out
the entire screen. You get the fuck out of here. I just got like so pissed. I think I'll do it,
but it's going to be ugly. It's going to be very ugly. I might lose the metal. Have I played
balloons? It was that time years ago when we did a community balloons, but you guys picked every
single spot because I was too dumb to do it. Where are you? Just die. I think we're okay.
I don't think we're going to lose. We might though. Play Temple Run. Is it fun? No. I'm seeing a lot
of nos. I think we're good. Yeah, we're good. What about subway surfers? I feel like I would
get bored of those games pretty easily. Would you stream balloons? What did you say? Would
you stream balloons TD six for a year straight? I don't think I'd want to ever do anything for
a year straight. Ooh, do balloons with click maps again. That was really fun. Yeah. The click map
streams were, they were up there. Do you guys remember that was such new, cool shit on Twitch
back like five years ago? I used, I overused the hell out of that. Like maps were just such
a wild concept. I used them almost, I think I want to say once a week at one point.
Um, not quite there. Okay. Act this. Why is that up there? Look at this. I really like the fumes room.
It's pretty cool. Are these, is this a sunlight plant? Can I use this here? You need the cactus.
You don't need sunlight. Okay. What about Peggle? I wanted to play Pegglin,
that like Peggle kind of game, right? That looks fun. Peggle is, yeah. I've never,
did I play Peggle 2 on stream? I don't think so. Uh, this is, I'll take the small one.
I feel like this is, I need the lily pad. I do. All right, let's go. Pegglin's a lot of fun.
I played the original Peggle. It's kind of sus. You didn't take squash. Oh, you're right. I didn't.
This could be a problem. You're right. Let's see what the hell's going on here.
Nobody down here, I guarantee it. What about Deep Rock Galactic? I'm down to play pretty much
anything. True, that's okay. It's pissing me off, but it's okay. I don't want to do this,
but I might have to. Oh, I have to, whatever. It's a terrible place for that. Oh shit,
I gotta pop that. Uh oh. Uh oh. Oh no. Well, that doesn't help. I'm not restarting yet. I
was about to, but I'm not gonna. I didn't know what this thing did. I want to restart so bad.
Yeah, I'm doing it. No, I'm so. Pull the bandaid off. Let's go. Okay, I need to get the lantern.
I gotta get this thing down first, because that thing flies across the whole lane. Nothing can
shoot it. Embarrassing. Now, frankly, that was embarrassing. Could you please abruptly end the
stream? I'm kind of tired. You should go to bed. You don't gotta stay up. That's the problem.
Squash wasn't there. All right, this is a terrible team, but I don't care. No, it's fine. There you
are. Shit. All right, not bad. It could have been worse. Why did you move from Boston? Um,
I kind of wanted to change. I'd been in, you know, New England almost my entire life. So,
like, at that point, it was a lot of, I want to do projects and this big stuff that I want to try
to do. And it just felt like being on the west coast was easier just because, wait, LA is right
there. Vegas has a lot of cool stuff. There's a lot of resources and opportunity and stuff out here
for like the entertainment industry. Like, you know what? Why not? But I didn't really want to
live in LA. I didn't want to be like in California, really. No, let's just put this down now. Oh,
I need one of those poppers. I need a pop. I need you to get popped. Come on. It's so close.
You fucking asshole. All right, pop. Does this still shoot? Thank God. I didn't do that bad
damage either. They didn't get through, right? Where do you shoot it? Hope nothing comes down
this way. All right, this is it. Where is the pop person going? That's not cool. Oh, that's not
cool. Wait a minute. Come on, squash. You can do it. It's all eyes on you. Oh, fuck. Fuck. Hold on.
I have an idea. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Squash is almost ready. I need some fucking damage right
now. All right. All right. Hold on. Okay. Oops. Please heal that. Thank God. All right. We're good.
You really should play Sly Cooper. I think I would like it. Nice. I'm eating my greens.
What do you got? Kale? Spinach? Lettuce? What do you got? You said wasn't I going to go soon?
I think I missed that. That was a really stressful Saturday night.
Blows away all. Oh, that's cheaper. And fog. That's pretty good. It's only temporary.
It's only one time. Lower is actually better than the cactus. You got to try each one at
least one time, right? All right. I'm seeing dolphins and I'm seeing balloons. So definitely
need to do this. I think I'm okay with that, but we'll see. If you got invited to something
like Comic-Con as a guest, would you go? Um, I don't know. Maybe, but if I'm really,
really completely upfront with everybody here, probably not. Why not? Uh, I don't know.
I don't really have a great answer. I think I went to a lot of conventions pretty early on
in the YouTube arc, if you want to call it that. I went to PAX East, PAX Prime, E3. I went to all
of them every single year. And I think I've, as I got a little bit older and as I kind of went to
a lot of them, it just started to become something that I didn't, because what used to happen was,
and obviously that this is not like this anymore, but it would be kind of takes a lot of time.
Like you kind of dedicating a week to go travel and what are you going to do is you're going to
stream anything during that time. I don't really do IRL content really at all. So it's not like,
oh, I'm going to go to like PAX East and stream. I'm actually much more comfortable just kind of
in my own space, if that makes sense. It's funny because I'm, I'm an incredible extrovert
very selectively. It's kind of weird how that works out. You're a popular loner.
Don't eat that. I know I wasn't supposed to do that, but I did it anyways.
Funny Ludwig said that exact thing about you. Really? That's funny. Oh shit. Atriarch, what's
up? That's it. That's a meaty Atriarch raid. What's going on? Currently in the middle of
playing. Holy shit. Why did I do that? Oh, did I waste that? Oh, the recharge is insane on that.
No, I'm good. We're good. Yeah. I'm just chilling out playing some plans for zombies. I played it
before, but just relax. And on this Tuesday night out of here, this thing's actually awesome.
I like how it disappears, but disappearing is actually perfect. Are you, are you zonked?
No, no, no, no. This is way too many mushrooms. It's way too many. Yeah. Atriarch is awesome.
You don't follow Atriarch. What the heck are you doing?
Uh, I don't want to lose this. Come on. Hurry up. I really like this thing. I think it's really
useful. He is zonked. He put the sun shrooms in the front. You don't really want me to put
them in the front, right? I feel like that's a bad idea. And look what happened when I missed click.
Sorry. Double defense. Please do your Mitch McConnell impression.
You know, it's making me laugh about that. It's like, dude, it's, it's like, what time is it
where you are? It is 11 15 PM here. I wonder what time it is. Are you tired? You want me to do Mitch
McConnell right now? Isn't it kind of late? It's like too late for that. It's late at 11 15 PM.
Give us a Mitch McConnell.
I'm not going to do a Mitch McConnell. What I'm going to do, we're going to have
plant versus zombies and I'm going to play it and I'm playing it well.
Worst impression.
I don't want to hear anything about the stimulus stimulus. Yay. Voices. Hooray.
You're throwing right now. I don't think I can throw. I think I'm in a good spot.
When was Mitch McConnell elected? Imagine like looking over in chat and it's like, you know,
like Mitch McConnell, like 96, just like, fuck you. Oh shit. Oh my God. Oh God. I don't have
anything here. I had no defense here. Well, we're going to lose the two. I don't know. Whatever.
It's okay. It's okay. It's all right. Wait, it hasn't happened yet. Can I push him back or
anything? It hasn't happened yet. I'm still okay. Should be fine. Everybody relax. If I get this,
it's going to be good. Oh shit. Hold on. Oh, I got it. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. I think it's still possible. It's definitely, I got it. Yeah,
I'm good. Nice. Now do foghorn leg horn. Just rewind two minutes and pretend that's what I
was doing. A thousand bucks. That's an old pop cap sound. I haven't heard that in a while.
This is what I want. I told you that's what I was saving for. Cattail. Cattail is going to
attack any lane and really, I kind of feel like I should have bought that. I feel kind of stupid.
Do your best second term impression. No, I'm done. I'm not. Is that close? What is this?
This is courage. The cowardly dog. Yeah. Break it. We're going to base to see what's inside.
Ooh. Oh shit. Hold on. You just woke everybody up. I probably did that as look at, do you see what
just happened right there? That was perfect. Wait, they disappear. Please type mustache. I'm about
to fucking explode. Okay. Don't break them too fast. Get the fuck out of here. They do disappear.
They do exist. Try that again. Do it one row at a time. That's the strategy. There we go. Okay.
Very cool. But what's wrong? What the fuck? Why? Why? I'm seeing a lot of question marks.
Why is everybody? Why the question mark? Go. I'm going to turn. He's going to kill that guy.
Why you've bonked out of your mind. That's the worst strategy I've ever seen. It's called the
quick strategy. It's called the strategy that's fast. Just sped it up. You're definitely zooted
and naked. What's that tweet? That fake ass tweet that somebody put up of like I burnt my nuts with
a blunt or something. That was a fake ass tweet by the way. I didn't really, I didn't write that.
That's not real. This goes forward and backwards. Nice. Yeah. Smoking butt naked and just dropped
the blunt on my balls. I scrum so fucking loud. I didn't, I didn't say this. That's not real tweet.
Yeah, dude. That actually happened. You just said it though. Yeah. But come on,
you should just tweet that now and pin it. You know, if you, if I editing tweets, like if I could
edit tweets from like years ago, part of me just wants me to go edit one from like six years ago
and just make it that. Whatever. Scrum. Okay. Uh, this is still nighttime. I want to use this.
This is a fog. I hate this fog. I want to get rid of it so bad. There's no balloons, but this,
I like this. You know what? I like this better than this. This is not that expensive and you
can just get rid of everything. I'll try it for now. Take the little green one. All right,
let's go. How many, uh, worlds are there? I want to say seven or eight. There are five. Oh damn.
Okay. I beat this night. He thinks he's going to beat it tonight. Why'd you take the two headed?
Uh, cause it was new and it looked shiny. So I picked it up. Play the mini games too.
I'll try them for sure. I'm tired, but I don't want to miss the rest of the stream. What do I do?
Well, I have good news for you. If you like this stream, if you're having a good time,
there's way, they're going to be way more of these. Don't worry, you can just catch the next one.
You're just messing up my aesthetic and I hate you. Like he, you know what I mean?
I, that was perfect symmetry right there and he just messed it up. No, not, I wasn't saying
that to that person. Oh, you're really messing up my aesthetic right now. What kind of horseshit is
that? Can you imagine? What a dumb thing to say. Like I, you know what I mean? I, that's not what
happened. Oh shit. Okay. That's why you need to have this. What the hell? Okay. Well,
get rid of this, get rid of this fog for a second. I didn't see what's going on here.
You're eating my shit backwards is annoying. Vibes are officially off.
Yeah. Vibes are fine. I'm not having a vibe issue right now. It lasts a long time too. I
like this thing a lot. I need some more stuff down here though. Look at the bottom,
driven the bottom. I'm good. Okay. All right. He picked the same row, which is good.
Safe. I want one of these fumes over here. All right. What's this thing?
You should definitely get the cattails. Star fruit. Shoot stars in five directions.
Should I put that on a lily pad in the middle? Like right in the middle?
I feel like that's awesome. I think that's the play. Yeah. And that's the strategy I'm going for.
I need my lower, maybe one of these. And I think I could work with this. It has to be in the right
spot or I'm going to lose my mind. Okay. There is. Okay. That looks all right. What are you guys
doing that face? That's acting weird. Why are you acting so weird? What happened?
Lillipad going right here. After I set up, after I do some tech. I feel like I want a lot.
Like this is going to be kind of hard. Who's shooting? I can't tell who's firing.
Right here. Okay. Yeah. Right here. Just tacking it. Just getting it ready. Okay.
Who's shooting? You are. All right. Star is going to go here and star going to go here.
I'll be two stars are going to go in the middle like that because there's a shoot behind too,
right? Theoretically. Is this a good spot? Kind of. That's works out pretty well. If I do another
one here and here. Nevermind. He's a stupid nerd. What? What did I do wrong? Oh, why did you say
that? Now I am a stupid nerd. Look what I did. What happened? Oh, that's sad. These things are
awesome. I'm never, I'm going to only make these. Do they have to go on a lily pad or can they go
on anything? Anything, right? They can go on anything. Nice. Okay. Two more here. I don't
want to neglect the bottom and top. Probably should have deleted this. It's okay. I'm gonna.
Oh, it's this. The star has that face. I haven't seen you play this game since you
food yourself. What? What? Then what are you talking about? Oh, that's okay. Oh, yeah. That's
right. During the Halloween stream. Yeah. Now I know you can. Um, can, can you stars shoot this
boy, please? They're all missing. Are they not hitting? How come they're not hitting this dude?
He just screwed everything up. That was a, that was a disaster. They don't hit behind themselves.
I think I should still make it though. He's scrum and shit himself. God damn it. It's okay.
Whatever. I miss clicked. Is anybody going to kill this guy? Protect plants that are within the shell.
Oh, it's like a personal walnut. That's cool. It's still nighttime though. I think I'm gonna do the
same strategy. There's no, uh, there's no pickaxe people here. So same deal. I don't think I even
want one of these. I feel like I can cover it with the stars. It'd be wrong. We'll find out.
Sure. Why not? Star fruit sucks. I think it did pretty well last time.
Does the pumpkin scale with faith Dala decks? You didn't even ask that question.
You didn't know that read the game manual, dude, with the rest of us. Can you, is soup a drink?
Dude, I don't know. I have to restart the, I didn't see this guy soup, a drink. This is the,
is a hot dog, a sandwich shit, right? I guess kinda. Okay. You know those, um, like when you
get a ramen, like the, like the cup of noodle thing, it's like the cup and you put the water in it and
eventually eat all the noodles out of it where you're just kind of drinking it. You're just
kind of sipping on it. I bet those of you that have had bone broth before you just heat it up
and you sip it. That's technically a soup, but it's, you can sip on it. It's kind of a nice little
thing. You guys ever had bone broth before? Yes. You can drink a soup, especially if it's just a
broth. I think that, I think that makes sense. It's good for you. Bone broth is, bone broth is very
good for you. Yes. It is very good for you. Just be careful with the salt though. It could be high
in sodium. Just be careful. Okay. This is also important. Are chips dinner? No. I'm going to
have to agree with your mother on this one. No, they're not. Wrong. Wrong. Wrong. Is this
all right? What did I screw up last time? I don't remember. I screwed something up,
but I think this is all right. What about nachos? See nachos are not just chips. It's more than that.
Nachos have sometimes cheese, salsa, sour cream, meat. It's not just a tortilla chip for dinner.
It covers at least a few food groups. For me, dinner, lunch, dinner, whatever needs to cover
at least two food groups for it to be like a meal. It has to be at least two food groups.
So if you had chips and like crumbled on top of the chips was hamburger meat,
that's not a great meal, but it's still, that would fly for me as sort of food. If you had a hot dog,
just a single hot dog, I don't think that's a meal. Hot dog and bread. There you go. Cheese and chips.
I mean, nachos kind of, I mean, technically I just lost again. Actually, no, I didn't. I think I'm
okay. What about just a steak? No, I don't, I don't find that to be a meal. If you're just going to
eat a steak and just nothing else on the plate, it's just a cooked steak and that's it. No,
like mushroom risotto. No, um, you know what I mean? No, nothing else. No, I don't think so.
Oh, no, like broccolini. You got to have something. What about water? Don't think that's,
I wouldn't say that's dinner. Please die in this. So I don't have to, you know what? I need to see.
I got my setup here. What are you doing? Um, you just jump over shit and I've, it's okay. I don't
care about this. It's fine. It's fine. I'll be all right. We don't need to get a hundred percent on
every level. Who's being eaten? Waste, wasteful, very wasteful. That's okay. Partably wasteful.
You're not going to actually die. All right. Okay. Careful. That was 3 a.m. Yeah. I don't think I'm
going to go much longer. See if I can maybe get to the last zone. Maybe I'm going to say I was
about to put that down. I think I'm good. Yeah, we're good. Don't let that guy win. Keep streaming.
Ooh, that's nice. Don't let that guy win. That guy is probably going to bed. It's probably like
five o'clock in the morning or three o'clock in the morning or something. Don't be a coward.
No, I'm good. I think we'll probably beat it tonight. At least get through the fifth
zone. They just said it was 3 a.m. Aren't you the guy that eats mayo from the jar?
Um, I don't. I like mayo. I think it goes great with a lot of stuff, especially with tuna fish
and pretzels. I wonder how many people actually think I'm a disgusting piece of shit. And then
they go, you know what? Just for the meme, I'm going to do it one day. Just for the meme, like
all of you guys are hanging out. There's like a thousand of you. There's like a hundred of you
in this thing. It's like, I don't know, fucking dance hall or wherever you are. And you make a
big vat of this and it's like, oh yeah, remember when he said this? We're going to do it for the
meme and it's going to become your favorite snack. And you're not going to, you're not going to say
shit, are you? You're not going to say shit. You're going to be like, oh, it's delicious,
but I can't say that. Make tuna fish with mayo, slop it, you know, slop it up a little bit,
get it in the bowl and then get pretzel rods, dip it in, dunk it like a dunkaroo and bite it.
And I want you to report back. I really want you to report back. Tuna. I already, there's a
lot of people writing. It's guys. Nobody said, why the fuck are you eating gruel? You don't,
is that what you think about tuna fish? You think tuna fish is gruel? Come on. What? It's not gruel.
All I'm saying is give it a try. Look, if you don't like tuna fish, then you're obviously going to
hate this. I grew up on tuna fish. I grew up on tuna fish sandwiches.
Shit. I sound like I have a shit face. You kids don't always like, I grew up on tuna fish sandwiches
and they were fucking delicious. Look how I turned out you little shits. Okay, let's go. This is the
last level. Should I take the smush? I don't really like these, not for here. I'll try this though.
Tuna sandwich and a can of ginger ale, mega comfort food. Leather jacket said that. Oh man,
that sounds pretty great. A nice fresh ginger ale tuna sandwich with like a piece of Swiss
cheese on it. Even a tuna melt or something. Tuna melts. Oh, maybe a little bit. Maybe get a
little wild, put a little bit of avocado on it. You know what I mean? Tuna melts are really good.
I know there's a lot of people that really don't like fish at all and I get it. But to me,
tuna fish is barely even fish. Maybe it's because I was just so used to it growing up eating it.
I had it all the time. It was not, oh this, it's fish. I know that sounds weird to say that,
but it doesn't feel like it's fish. It feels like it's just like food. I'm explaining this really
wrong. What about pickles? Yeah. Who's spiring? Okay, you guys are fine. It tastes like chicken.
Yeah, it just, especially when you, if you add a little bit of no pickles or relish or something,
a little bit of cheese. I think people, tuna fish, obviously you don't want to eat it all
the fucking time because tuna has mercury and can't have mercury. Can't have too much mercury.
You get it. But it's really easy. You can get a bunch of tuna and then here's the good thing
about tuna from like can, right? Just regular, just regular ass tuna. Nothing crazy. It lasts
a really long time and you can just get a bunch of it and you can make a full meal with a can of
this shit. I gotta be ready here. Don't eat that. Where are you? Okay, this is all right. How about
this? Get that hat off. Wait, how close does that have to be? It's not metal? Oh, I thought it took,
I thought it was metal and hats. I thought it was hats. It's plastic. Yeah, but I thought it
was like removes hats. Should be all right. This middle row. I'm good. Oops, sorry. Take that hat
off. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Can he float over that?
Wait, blow away. What am I thinking? What a waste. I'm sorry. That was dumb. I'm still fine. Gotta
take care of this bottom row here. Take this hat off. This is, this is metal. This is made out of
fucking aluminum. I think it's so good. So many of these assholes too. I started, yeah, I started
pretty late. No real plan with this one. Just kind of felt like turning it on, which expect way more
of these. I know I keep saying that, but I really like this shit. I do. I did miss it a lot. Don't
eat that. I put in here to get something in the way. This second to last row has nothing on it.
I'm going to hold that for now. You got to be close. Jesus. All right. World four done.
Look at that. Only one more world. Yeah. This is your mother. Please come over to my house for
meatloaf. Leave your front door open and your lawn unguarded. This is not the zombies.
I think it's so dark. It can't be good. Oh, well hope you survive the night.
Do you guys like meatloaf? Meatloaf sucks. Unless your mom makes it. That's just a fact. I think.
Come on. Let me see. Okay. It's right there. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. I said the same thing
five years ago. It's true. This can go anywhere. Don't crunch. Oh, I hear the crunches.
Oh shit. Motherfuckers down here. Oh my God. Dr. Clay just linked a fucking sandwich and the thing
looks awesome. Holy shit. Turkey sub with everything on it. Oh, that sounds awesome.
He goes, Oh, whoops. Sorry about that. No, that's not good. With everything on it. Oh, you know,
when everything's on it, that's going to be, you know, it's going to be good.
Get that thing stacked up. Lettuce, pickles, mayo, cheese and shit. Get everything on that.
And I want it to be, I want the lettuce to be falling out of the outside of the bun.
It's fucked up. What happened to that one? What? A lot of these lily pads. I don't really want them
anymore. Okay. Not a bad setup. Yeah. I don't think there's anything better. How should I use this?
Maybe flying right now. Use the blower to get rid of it. I missed it. Hey, he's dead. Okay.
Is there any space for anything? Show me. Shit. This top water lane needs a, give me a blower.
Give me a blower. Give me a blower before I'm in trouble. Give me a blower. Give me a blower.
Place it. Yes. I got it. This is almost a full stack of shit here. Any more flying people? No.
Ooh. A cabbage thrower. What was that achievement? Or else cabbages at the enemy.
They even found a way onto your roof. Those are some persistent zombies, dude.
Use the cabbage pulse. Okay. You can finish the game in one sitting.
Yeah. I think that's probably accurate. I don't know what that thing is, but it's kind of scary.
I'm going to drive people crazy with this, by the way. I'm only taking this,
and I'm going to drive some of you crazy. Okay. So we got cabbage, triple shooter. Does this work
here? Squasher. Uh, boom, boom. Uh, boom, boom. Um, boom. No, boom. No. I'm already getting
luigied. Yeah. That's what I want to do. I was just joking around. Oh, right. You have to put it
on a sunflower. Oh, yeah. Oh, I can only put it in this many slots. This game sucks. Oh, Megalo true.
What? Oh, that's annoying.
Cool. I know people are going to say, stop doing this. Just let me do it. I want, I want a million
sun. Okay. Almost. All right. Now we double all of these. Oh, fuck. Right. Oops. I think it's okay.
It's not okay. What's that?
That same enemy is in Sekiro. Can you shoot? Is this working? Is it hitting the ground? Oh shit.
I think it's hitting the ground. Can you only use the cabbage?
Oh shit. Okay. Well, that's good to know. Is there any way I can stop that from happening? That sucks.
Shit. I want to get all of them. Well, now I know. Extra pot. You don't have lawnmowers.
Interesting. I get this. Only losers get that. What did it do? So it's only the cabbages can hurt
anything. And the squisher. These can't shoot up. The cat is OP. The front most plants can attack.
Then let's fucking go. Pumpkin will protect the grab. Oh, good. That's good to know. If I don't do
it this time, I'll do it. We're going to hold off. I got an interesting plan here. That turkey
sandwich looked fucking awesome. It really did. He loves tuna sandwiches. Oh, sorry. No, no, no. I
got the squisher. This is why you bring the squisher every time. There's no reason to ever
take this off your loadout ever. An instant kill and it's only 50 cents. So good.
Landmine is better. The landmine is a little cheaper, but it takes too long to arm if you
really are in a pinch and you really need to get out of there. Squisher is your friend.
This is definitely pre-recorded. You're definitely naked and watching the VOD right now.
Like with you guys based. What you guys don't know is at the end of the stream,
I forgot to like make, I forgot to make sure the stream turned off. I fell asleep here
and the video just starts over again. Okay. Let me get this right. I'm not going to let you do that.
Wrong lane. You idiot. I thought it was. Oh, I thought he was at the top. Shit.
This is why the smusher is the best thing. Look at this. He's not going to let you get by.
Get out of here. It would be way more effort for you to pretend to play than to just play.
Yeah. That's what I'm saying. How much of a fraud do you guys think I am? There we go. Perfect
placement. I'm good. Detective stream was a neat idea. You know, that's one of my favorite streams.
That's one of my favorite things I've ever done. I had so much fun on that night.
I don't know if there's not a lot of people that don't know what we're talking about, but
five years ago, we recorded a whole stream and the whole goal was I had a bunch of fake accounts
that were me and I was just typing in the chat, watching the VOD with everybody on fake accounts
and every like 30 minutes or so, every 20 minutes, the video would stop and an alarm would sound and
everybody had 10 seconds to guess who I was in the chat. I don't think we could do that again.
I think there's too many people here now. That was back. That was where there a thousand viewers or
something. 1500 or something. I don't know if that would work very well now. Like three K.
Leave my shit alone. I had a great name too. One of my favorite names. What was it? Binary Man
0010110001. I forget what some of the other ones were. I had like seven or eight, didn't I?
Oh, corn. That's the worst joke of all time. I don't think so. I thought it was fun.
I'm happy with this. Even less. That kind of sucks.
Everyone, you did a rebroadcast of the Simpsons hit and run.
And I wouldn't just let it play. I kept showing up and pausing it and being like,
oh, let me tell you about this. I remember people screaming at me, just saying,
get the fuck out of here. We're trying to watch this corn go first. It's just the butter, right?
Or is it, is it butter or is it kernels? Find out. It's butter, right? Oh no, it's kernels.
I thought I had like a pad of butter. Oh, it is Baltica. You're going to eat the pot?
Get out of here. You just made me waste 25 cents for the pre-recorded webcam bit from Hotline Miami.
Oh yeah. Yeah. I don't even remember what that was. You kept talking while you were drinking.
Oh, that's right. Yeah. Cause I recorded like 10 minutes straight of webcam footage
and just looped it in the corner of the screen. What the hell am I? What the hell is wrong with me?
Don't. Did I just really kill him? I did, didn't I? Come on. What the fuck? This guy's super human.
You're super human. Why are you still alive? I'm going to die. And then the next one I'm going to
get killed by. I don't think I'm prepared, but we'll see what happens. Is this too much corn?
Are you sleepy? Um, I don't, I'm a little bit tired, but I'm okay. I figured a bit,
probably at the end of this, I'll maybe try a mini game or two and then take off.
Did I miss a dime? Whatever that is. I'm just doing all corn, corn only. You know,
actually I'm not a huge corn fan. I love, I love the corn is in something, you know, like corn meal,
like corn tortillas, but I'm, I don't know. I'm not like a, just an ear of corn.
I have to be really in the mood for it, but that's not good.
Corn on the cob can be good, but I need to really, really want it.
I just don't like what it does to your teeth. It seems like every single space between every single
tooth has like paper stuck in it after you eat corn. It's just like,
I love the way it tastes, but it's just kind of annoying. I don't know why I just did that,
but okay. Why is this ladder still here? Nope. What? You didn't even climb over the big ones?
Yeah, I didn't know that. Then they can climb over them. That's annoying.
Washroom to wake it up. Wake it up. I mean, I can use, oh,
kind of like the setup I had. I don't think there's anything I really want from here.
Bring the magnet. Yeah. I don't think I want to do that. I'll stick with what I was doing.
I think it was better. Oh, that's right. No squish. It's okay. We'll deal. We'll deal with it.
Magnet is a shroom. Oh, that's right. I'll deal with it. Does the cabbage do more damage than the
corn? I have to imagine it probably does because the corn is a slow stun. I probably need a few
more of those then. I did way too much corn last time. It does pea shooter damage.
Good to know. You got to go. I don't have my smush. It's done. Done. Done. Nice. Done again.
It's done again. Yes. This has got three. This is going to be tricky. This game won a Grammy
for its soundtrack. I mean, the soundtrack does go really hard. It's a really good soundtrack.
I got to have at least two in each row. Bro, why are you streaming right now?
Just hanging out. I'm going down here. It was unironically added to the Library of Congress.
Didn't you guys give me shit for that before? As you said, that CARS 2 is in the Library of
Congress and there was a bunch of people laughing about it. I made some arguments saying, no, no,
you don't understand. This is in the Library of Congress. And people were like, yeah, bro,
CARS 2 is as well. Done. Can we get a stun? Everything is in the Library of Congress. It's
true. You know what's funny? I've never seen a single CARS movie. If you said I'll give you
a million dollars if you can name three characters in that movie, I wouldn't be able to do it. I
wouldn't be able to name you two. I think I can name you one. I could not name you more than two
people in that movie. I've never seen any of the CARS movies. None of them. All right. This is
where I got to be prepared. Pretty good setup. Some, uh, walnuts here. Ah, give me that.
He's dead. Nevermind. Would you rather be the head of lettuce or a raw ear of corn?
Is it a raw ear of corn hard? Maybe that kind of hurts. Break your teeth or something. No.
Oh, they're like really kind of like so fresh and frisk. I'm going to have to disagree.
Sorry. There's a whole nother wave coming too. I think it's just protect and that's it. Can I
put a pumpkin on a walnut? I can. Okay. That's cool. Oh, give that to me. Oh, I got really,
oh, I got really cocky. I got really cocky. I have to replace this shit. Come on. It's okay.
Just kill them. Dude, you're not actually going to fucking asshole.
You get out of here. He's ruining everything. They're all getting through. How are you still
alive? This is making any sense. Die. Oh my goodness. Oh, suck that thing out of his hands.
Oh, this thing is a mushroom. I forgot. Oh no. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Uh, I'm going to, I'm still going to be fine. Oh fuck. Oh shit. Oh shit. Everything needs to
be clicked on. That's all right. I don't care. I don't have to 100% it's fine. Get run over.
You'd be really bad at Starcraft. Yeah. I'm never going to play Starcraft, man.
That sounds like a bad idea. Now you can play Zen garden mode. A couple of sprouts.
Money. How much should I do this for? Can I just do this forever? It's 10 bucks every time.
Your plant needs fertilizer. Visit the shop, pick up some fertilizer. Oh dear. That's pretty
good. I mean, I feel like I don't want to buy that right now. Nah. He gave me some for free.
Zen garden is pretty nifty, huh? You can visit it at any time from the main menu.
End your house. I have to warn you. You're going to hate this next level.
It's nonstop bungee zombie after bungee zombie. I hate those. All right. So I need the strategy here
is. Oh, okay. I have to use it. Oh, I can do this. Chopper.
Is he going to be chewed by the time he gets over here?
Oh, my goodness. You just eat him already.
They have bigger range. Hey, cool. You have bombs. I'm saving them. Hey. Oh, they get eaten though.
Look at that guy over here.
Somebody eat him. Somebody eat him. What is happening? Eat this guy.
That's the strategy right there. I'm going to do that. Yeah, I got this. It's in the bag. It's
already. I win. I had to do that. Everything's good. Okay. This is where I go. Boom, boom, boom.
Three times, four times.
Looks good. One of you has to stop chewing here in a second, right?
All right. Here we go. Here we go. Nice. They really be crunching.
Convert zombies into other lanes. Catapult zombie. What the hell does that mean? I got
fucking golly dude. Come on. All right. Just that. I'll try it. Convert into other lanes so
it'll move up or down. Does it choose a path or do I have to pick it? Oh, he said it. He said the
thing. It's random. Put them all the way at the end. Two tears of double sun. I feel like I'm
probably going to need that eventually, but not immediately. Maybe like the next three levels at
the end of the game. Dude, you're totally gaming right now. Yeah. The garlic in the top and bottom
row, like all the way back here as a defense. You have to eat it. Oh shit. I'm going to do three
cabbage and then one corn. I think that'll be good. Are you winning son? Yeah, dad. Oh, good.
I need three rows of cabbages or I'll quit the game. That's what I require.
This is stupid. Was it dumb to like tech this whole time just to get cabbages or is that?
I think I'm all right. I don't know what this thing, what this guy does though. I put it,
I'm going to make, I'm going to put it. Should I squish him? Found a solution. Kill him. Come on.
Kill him. He's not going to kill my sunflowers, right? You are such a dick. I can't believe that.
That was 150 bucks. That's a, that's actually bad. It's going to set me behind.
Okay. I got all the rows. I want a cabbage. This is where I got to get ready. It might just be,
I'm going to do one row of corn. That's it. What's the difference? Corn does less damage
than cabbage, but has a random chance to throw a big thing of butter, which stuns them like that.
It's pretty useful. Stun him. Stun him. Stun him. Sorry. Not that bad. What are your thoughts on
corn? Corn is really good. Yeah, it is. Ah, I see. It buys you a little time too. It's good. I'm
going to sneeze. I'm so sorry. I probably woke up like a thousand people. I'm sorry.
There was no escaping that. It was just coming out. I tried to look away from the microphone too.
I, this is supposed to be chill night. I just probably scared the shit out of like a million
of you. Ooh. Okay. Protect nearby plants. Is that, do they have to be touching or is it just in a
square kind of adjacent squares? The three by three. Okay. I'll try it. Order. Come on.
I remember when he said stimulus. That was a little more put together though. That was not
quite it. Final three levels. Let's go. I didn't tech last time and I think it was a problem.
I'm going to focus on that right now. We're doing double lane of flowers by the way, even if it
ruins everything. Cause I can kill this one and I can kill that one and then go forward from there.
Yeah. Now this is going to be unbelievable. I'm going to stack at least a few of these
and I'll be in the money. Look at this. This is going to be awesome. It's going to be good.
Your economy is doing great right now. Thanks dude. No, no, no, no, no, no. Okay.
Come on. Where's my economy? Where's the economy? Get that shit out of here. Placement.
Look at all this money. It's just piling in right now. Come on. Die. Die. Jesus. Okay.
He's blowing it. No, I'm not. I'm good. I'm not blowing it. I didn't blow it. There's so much
damage here. Look at this. An unbelievable amount of damage here. I'm doing fine.
I'm like, I'm running out of room to quit shit. You need to optimize your strategy. I'm
looking, no one's even getting close. No one's even come close. Look at, I got a thousand bucks.
Go ahead and take it. What is that? Oh my God. It's a thousand dollars. Wait, why did I preemptively
say that? Oh, cause I had a thousand dollars. Right. No, I want you to hit this guy. He must
be pissy in that. Oh, what the fuck? More money than you could even count.
I got care. I've got $800. I don't care. All right. Big wave coming. I don't think I need to do
anything. You know what? Fuck it. This one, I don't even need it. Damage only. That was clean. Very
clean. If you were a plant, what would you be? Um, like Olivera. Gives you silver and gold coins.
Oh dude, you're dead. I don't think so. I'm happy with that strategy. I think it works fine.
Smush. No, I got to work on the economy first. Especially with a big guy like this.
You would be a cactus. Probably. You're right. All right. I think this is good. Let's go.
Only one more level after this. Damn. All right. I'm going to beat this tonight.
I feel like I've been playing pretty well. I feel like I've been pretty locked in.
I don't think I failed one mission. Maybe one. Look at this economy. The restarts don't count.
No, they do. Economy. I had a huge economy last time and it was the reason why I won.
Come on. This game is really fun. Why didn't they just make more of these?
I feel like there's so much more they could have probably done with this franchise
in this way. Not in the FPS way or the shooter way. I would have loved to have done
late like Plants vs Zombies again. Yeah, I mean Plants vs Zombies 2 got a bunch of updates and
stuff, but it was just a regular standalone game. Okay, let's go. All right. Time to go.
There's not going to be any real rhyme or reason to the placement. People are going to be pissed
about it, but it's okay. Just as they come up. I have a lot of money. It's coming up.
Symmetry is going to suck, but it's okay. Same damage. Same stuff happening.
Did you get it out there? Bottom row. Come on. I got to quickly get this built.
Draw a dick with the pots. Have I just started doing that?
No, I'm not going to do that. Get over here. Get rid of him. First test. Okay. What is it?
Not bad. Not a terrible wave. Oh, big guy. Oh, shit. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's going on over here?
Uh-oh. What? No. Okay. It's fine. Come on. Come on. Come on. We're good. Nice. Don's cap on.
I saved that. I didn't. No one more has got hit there. What are you talking about?
Holly can't sleep because Gerva keeps playing TVC at full volume at 1 a.m.
I'm being really quiet though. Okay. Here it comes. All right. Wherever the big guy is,
that's where I put this thing. Where's the big guy down here? He squished it.
He actually smushed it. Oh, my God. Oh, shit. Come on. Damn it. Die. Oh, no. Crash him. Yes.
Five, nine. Coming up. Heavy damage to groups of zombies. Should I just only do those? I think
I'm just going to go ultra tech and only do watermelons. Watermelons and corn only.
It's pretty pricey. That's what the corn is for. What am I doing? Of course. Okay. Here we go.
Let's go. This is it. I think there's only one more level after this and it's like a
minigame level, right? If I can make some money early, then this should work out fine.
This is the original Plants vs. Zombies. The second one is the Game of the Year edition. I
don't know if they added anything or what that means. All right. Come on. First economy. Come on.
That doesn't mean anything. I didn't expect it to. Just more content. Will you play Zumbinis ever
again? It's funny you say that. I think I have it installed right now. Play it tonight? We can play
Zumbinis again if you want. I'm down for that. Sure. Not tonight, but eventually. All right.
We got a row of corn. Row of watermelon. There's no way they can buy. Remind me to protect the
watermelons because I will forget. Need something down here. Where the big wave shows up. Here we
go. Nice. Okay. Not a bad spot. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. I need to get at least three
here. There it is. Nice. All right. Right in the middle. I'm going to do another row of corn.
No. No, not. Only watermelon. They can't even walk up here. Hey, can you please react harder?
Sorry, man. Another row of watermelon. I have a little bit of time. Protect them first. I will.
Look at this economy back here. That's not happening. Sorry. Don't you dare. Took so long.
Please. Shit. Right at the end. You piece of shit. Whatever. It's fine. Good luck getting
over here. All right. Big wave. I need this. No. Okay. If I get two rows of watermelons,
it's game over. It just is. Getting watermelon launched to your head must really hurt.
Yeah. Big watermelons are doing way a lot. Get him out of the way. All right. Get in there.
Okay. That's it. That's it. No more upgrading. All right. Good. Hey, German, can you crush a
watermelon between your thighs? Sorry. Sorry, dude. I don't think that's happening. All right. This is
it. Come on. Launch. When he launches out, I'm going to crush him. I did it. All right. Now,
it's the wind. I already come on. Keep them frozen. Keep them frozen. That look. Oh, shit.
No. Come on. I'm not. My click speed isn't fast enough. Yes. The clutch. Squash with the clutch.
Homeowner, you have failed to submit to our rightful claim. Be advised that unless you comply,
we're forced to take extreme action. Please something. Your home and brains to us now.
Sincerely, Jean-Pierre. Uh-oh. He's here. Ready to get ready. Every one heck of a fight. His
weakness is even the pancreas. Dave. Uh-oh. It is Dave. All right. All right. Here we go.
It's the last level, right? No. Use it early. Use it early. Use it early so I can get a good,
you know what I mean? Use it early. Watermelon going right in the middle. Perfect lane already.
Not dealing with that. Not dealing with this right now. What the fuck? Should I attack him?
Wait. Freeze. Ooh, that hurts a lot. Okay. What do I do about that? What the fuck do I do about
that? What the fuck do I do about that? He just crushed everything. What? What the hell? He just
rolled a fucking like blueberry snowball at me and it killed everything. What the hell happened?
I need to use fire. Oh, that makes sense. Okay. I've got a pretty good thing here. But this works.
Oh, slowest clicker in the entire world, by the way. Not putting up with that. All right. Focus
fire. Freeze. I need ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice. Now what? That's unfair. It's kind of a dick move.
What bullshit are you going to do now? Fire, ice. Yeah. Almost halfway. Didn't take any
watermelons. Good. Kind of running out of. Wrong. It was a waste, but it's okay. It's not a huge
problem. That's okay. He should die right now. We got fire. Probably should just freeze him again.
Hey, that was fucked up. That was annoying. What the? Freeze. I need some more shit. Dude,
come on. Give me something besides the hot and the cold. Oh, Jesus. Okay. What are you going to do?
Ice, fire. What is it? My teeth just came out. My fake teeth just came out of my mouth when I said
that. My dentures just flew out. There's nobody even in this lane. Shit. Freeze, freeze, freeze,
freeze, freeze. Oh, goodness. I hope you don't. Oh, please don't do ice. Fire, fire. Oh, I can't
click correctly. I can't. I can't click correctly. I can't. I just, it's like,
it's okay. I'm so close. No, this guy died already. This is the wrong lane. You don't.
All right. Put your head down. Oh, come on. Oh, I did it. Cool. $8,600. Cool.
Okay. You win. No more eating brains for us. We just want to make music video with you now.
Sincerely, zombies. Cool. I should probably turn this up. I don't think I can though. Let's be quiet.
Two, three, dark and dead. We're going to bite all the petals off my head.
Flashing me. That might be the worst enemy in the game. They're probably the hardest to deal
with at least. Playing it now. The cat jams. Dancing. Cool. Hey, there it is. That was fun.
I do it real quickly when I just want to see the mini game stuff. Yeah, that was cute. It's been a
long time since I played it. It's actually been on the list for a while of just play this game.
And I'm sitting there going, Oh, how do I play Plants vs. How do I do that? But I think we just
do what we did tonight. It's just hang out, play a game. Can you do more late night streams?
You're going to see a lot more stuff like this this year. Very cool. Game of the Year content.
All right. Mini games, puzzles. What's a mini game? I'm curious. Oh, what? But if you guys like this,
I'm happy you did. Because I don't know, a lot of times when I'm thinking about what to do for a
stream or something, it's like, Oh, what's it going to be? It's going to be something fun or
funny or crazy or wacky or no, I don't think it has to be. I really don't think so. I think I'm
changing my philosophy on what it means to kind of stream the Twitch and stuff. And there's gonna
be more of this shit. It's fun. What about what's happening right now? But I need to actually get
free. So what if I don't get anything? Can I get anything? This is kind of, this is kind of
fucked up. I'm not going to lie. Okay. There we go. Dude, you suck at gambling. I'm trying as hard
as I can. Oh my God. It's late. I just realized it's like almost two o'clock in the morning Pacific.
What? I didn't know it was that late. It's still a lot of you here. Jesus. A lot of people probably
fell asleep. Oh, here we go again. Eastern time. Almost 5 a.m. Eastern. Late night crowd is usually
pretty chill from what I've seen. Is he afraid of us? No. I'm surprised I'm still doing fine here.
Do you still get up before noon? Yeah. I've been starting my day around like nine, nine thirty,
ten. The last probably a couple of years. At least last year. Uh oh. Uh oh. I, uh oh. All right.
What else I got? That's pretty cool. Um, classic walnut bowling. Jesus. Click on the right spot,
please. Okay. I got to leave. I was trying to click here. It's fine. I got enough.
I tried to do it again. See, look at, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look,
look at my fingers. Look, look, look, look at that. Look at my cursors. Look at that. See?
That's in the square down here. That's in that bottom square. This is actually really fun.
I can see why people like this game mode. That didn't hit.
Oh, shit. Get the cat. You have a lot of money. Uh oh.
I think this is where I lose.
Not quite. This is like a clean Dr. Mario or something. A Tetris. I hate this.
Oh, I don't hate this. I just hate that feeling. Oh, it's over.
Actually, as long as I get a bomb, I'll be fine.
Shit. I thought I could get out in time.
Okay. Is it RNG? I haven't seen a bomb in like, in at least two hours. Where are the bombs?
Where are the bombs? Yeah, there really hasn't been a bomb
at all. Look at all this junk here. How am I supposed to hit this? I need a bomb.
You have to save the... Ooh, presents. It's over. Well, maybe not. Hold on. Thanks for the bombs.
Finally. All right. This has to go right there. That didn't do anything. What? That hit two people.
That hit two people? There's 10 people standing here. What? Okay.
Yes, this is GG here. Yeah, that's still fun. Unless I get some insane luck right now. I think
I spammed them too much in the beginning. All right, that's cool. Looks like there's space for
way more of these. That's a lot. What is this? Oh yeah, I don't want to do this one. Yeah, no.
No, thank you. They attack back. No, that's too hard. Oh, I don't have enough. All right. I'm
going to call it here. Thanks for hanging out. We'll see you again. The next time I'm going to
stream, I planned on streaming on Thursday. We'll see. If not Thursday, then maybe because
Ster and I are going to do Saturday, Sunday with Elden Ring randomizer co-op again. So just keep an
eye on the sus. If you don't see anything in the next few days, the next two days, then expect
everything on Saturday, Sunday. But I might just show up and do what I did tonight. I was really
actually, if you want me to be real, I was kind of going, how are people going to react to this
stream? I didn't know if people were going to be like, you know, this is, I don't know, I don't
like this or something. So I'm glad that people seem to have a good time. So that's great. I'm
glad to see that because that means I'm going to do way more of them. Get hydrated. I've had,
I've been drinking tea. I had some water a little bit earlier too when I went downstairs. It was
good. Why do you, what are you so worried about? It would be terrible. It would be
terrible to have a random stream on Friday, my birthday. You didn't even type mustache. No,
I didn't. I really didn't. That's okay. Any news on Grotto Beast? I actually talked a lot about it
earlier at the beginning of the stream, the first hour or two. It gives them all mustaches. Yeah,
keep an eye on the sus. I'll see you this weekend, guaranteed. And then maybe, I don't know, maybe I'll
show up again before this weekend. If not, then expect Saturday, Sunday with a good old stir,
or Elden Ring. I think we're going to beat the game this weekend. I really do. But have a great
night. Have a, I mean, good morning probably for some of you at this point. I'll see you really
soon regardless. Get some sleep if you stayed up. I don't want to be the reason why you're
going to mess up your sleep schedule. Basically morning, yeah. I think it's morning for everybody
at this point. Too late. Should have said, yeah, I should have said that way earlier.
Hey, it's six o'clock in the morning. Hey, don't stay up for my sake. Bro, I'm on my like third,
I'm on my third Pepsi. And it's like 5.30. All right, good night, everybody. Drink some water.
Eat your vegetables. Call your mother. You know what to do. And I'll see you soon.
Keep an eye on the sus. Take care. See you again.