Hey, what's going on? How are you? Yeah, I didn't want, I wasn't supposed to be late.
I don't know what the hell was going on with Steam. Steam was, I couldn't connect anything.
About, about to do an Elden Ring PC Steam PvP stream and they turned this off for maintenance.
They did that because I was streaming. That's why they did it. All right, so here's what we're
gonna do. Are you guys ready? Cancel the stream? No. We got an, this is exciting stuff today.
Today we're going to do Elden Ring PvP, but it's going to be a little different.
How it is different is I need to find champions. I need to find people that can fight
for this community and that can represent this community in a very meaningful way. Because in
a few days, tentatively, still ironing out the details, Ludwig and I are going to do an event
where we do a trial by combat. Ludwig is picking somewhere around five to seven people from his
community and I'm picking five to seven people from my community. And we're going to battle you.
Yes, trust me when I say I've been, I've been looking for the barf drinker. We may have a lead.
We may have a lead on the original barf drinker. I'll tell you right now, there are two slots that
I already have reserved. I just don't know where to find the other one. Then the problem with Elden
Ring, especially the multiplayer stuff, is if I ask, oh hey dude, who was this person in that stream?
5,000 of you are going to go to Rhea Lucaria and you're going to change your name and your outfit
to be that person. So this is going to be interesting. So what we have to do here,
this is the plan. These are tryouts. I have VR Josh here. He's in the game right now.
We're in the game. We are going to be summoning people. Sometimes it'll be a 1v1 scenario where
you will fight me. Maybe you'll fight Josh. Maybe we'll summon someone else and you'll fight each
other. I'm going to decide who I want to represent me in a few days. I'm ready for the guild tryouts
and not just me. I think you guys deserve to have a say in this too.
So we're going to pull people in and you're going to show us what you got.
It's either going to be yay or nay and then you're out and we're moving on to the next one.
Is this pre-recorded? Why would this be? What? Show me what you got. What's the rune level?
I think we're going to shoot for 125 probably. Your rune level doesn't matter right now.
As long as you're over 120, if you use the password we're going to give everybody
and it doesn't matter. But the nature of this stream, by the way, keep in mind,
I'm not going to summon the same person like three or four potentially times.
So we're going to go from here. If you get into the game, I know this is going to look,
there's probably going to be hundreds of signs down and I'm not going to get to them all.
So this is just going to be for fun. It's not meant to be taken seriously,
but I can assure you we will find a group today. How that's going to happen. Excuse me.
You are going to come into the game. People are asking, how the hell are you going to keep track?
Elden Ring does not keep track of that. Well, VR Josh is. VR Josh is going to have his recent
Steam players list. If you are to be considered, VR Josh is going to reach out to you and confirm
who you are in Discord. And obviously he's got your, you know, Steam profile, whatever.
That's the way we're going to do it. That's the easiest way. We were talking about like,
oh, should we just have people take like a screenshot with their hats off and like
hiding behind a cemetery or something? But people could just spoof that. So what about
reserves? Oh yeah. There'll be reserves. I'm going to pick 10 people today or maybe like seven. And
you're just, if three or four, you don't show up on whatever Friday or Saturday, whatever we
decide to do this, we'll try to make it so it can work with everybody. That's the plan. That's the
plan. Do you need my blood type? No. Are there Elden Ring spoilers? I haven't finished. Oh,
I can't even show you the screen. Um, that person, I just want to let you know. Yes, leave now
because I just looked up and this is what I saw. This is, yes, yes, absolutely. Um,
this is what I literally just saw. Hey dude, it doesn't happen to be Elden Ring spoilers.
Is there? No, not really. Ah, I wouldn't say so. I mean, I don't know. Come on. Nice hair. I have
to comb it. All right. So we're going to do a password. I'm going to tell you what it is.
I'll put it on the screen to make it easier so we can get started. We, we are currently in front
of the Church of Vows, the front door. I'm going to be putting down the, a, not the password we
were using before. This is PC. I'll make sure to put it in the, you know, in the list there.
All right. The multiplayer password is going to be no spaces, no capitals. Uh, trial by C.
Trial by C. Trial by combat. Trial by C. Don't worry. I'll spell it out for you. Trial by C.
Dr. Cheese is not what we're using today. I'm in front of the Church of Vows. Let me,
can I just comb my hair real quick? Is VR Josh even still in the game? Where is he? Josh,
you still here? Oh, Jesus. Okay. You are. All right. So we need, I need, I need gold signs
and I need invasion signs because how this works is there can only be two of each.
So right now Josh is an invader. So I need another invader and I need another gold sign. So
put down both. Messy hair. It's, I need a haircut. That's a problem. Uh, uh, mods.
Will this work if, uh, yeah, you should, you're still here, right? This should work
if we change the password. Soul level. Summoning people with a password doesn't matter. So level,
but for the actual tournament, we're probably going to say 125. That makes the most sense.
All right. Let me use this item. I'm not going to send him out. Am I? No. All right. Should I
be seeing signs or what? Do I have to do, do I have to take any other item? 125 is too low.
Is it too low? We'll figure out 150 is the new PVP cap. Oh, I need to take one of the fingers,
right? How come I can't take it? 150 is not. We'll figure it out. Password password's trial by sea.
Yes. I have to kill. Oh, I'll use the tongue. That means we can be invaded. Uh, is this, am I
going to be able to even have, I might have to just summon Josh, uh, with the same password, right?
Yeah. I'll put the password on screen. Good idea. Good idea. Is it cross region?
I think it's currently set to cross region, but I'm really going to have to disappoint everybody
here. I think, I think I'm only going to be picking North America. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
In fact, I'm going to have to turn that off now. I'm so sorry, everybody. Like we got,
we're going to have a tournament here. It's, we're going to have to be able to connect to each other.
Should I leave and rejoin? Yeah. Try, try. Let's, uh, leave and rejoin. We'll see. Let me just, uh,
got it. Okay. So yeah, this is how it's going to work. Why am I wrong? Like, okay, there we go.
Uh, let me change the region and I'm going to reload the area too. So hold on. Let me do a cross
region off. I'm sorry. I know. Oh, it's already off. Okay. We're good. All right. So I need gold
signs and I need, uh, regular signs too. See if I could find Josh again, that's going to be hard.
I can do some trial, uh, trials by myself, but I really need to have that recent steam players
list. I have a question. Uh, go, go gold, Josh. It's all with the password, right? It's not me.
I'm gold. Hold on. Hold on. Yeah. With a tournament like this or having like a community fight a
community, I feel like we have to have it be no lag. If someone's just teleporting around,
I'm going to be like, what? Oh, we can't even do it. I'll put the info on screen. Bear with me
for just another second, please. Thank you. Okay. Uh, password is trial by combat and
rune level one 25 to one fifth. I, we haven't figured it out yet. It's probably, I gotta talk
to a lot of people. We're not sure yet. Uh, you see, all right, let's see if I can get Josh back
in here. Once Josh is in here, then we can really get going, but he really has to be in here first.
May restart it. One 25 is PVP one 50 or players who were too bad to beat the game without
over-leveling. Oh, stop. Stop it. Please. All right, Josh, where's your, uh, sign? It wasn't
there. All right. I got a question. So for me to see recent players that I've played with,
I can't see it. Is there a re what do I have to do? This person is just me. If I can find you here,
shift tab, like, okay, but you can't see it in Elden ring. No, you can. You can. We confirmed
that you could just do level 70. Yeah. Recent players does work now, but I can't see them
because it has to be like, why don't you just use it? Yeah. That's what I was going to say.
That's why I was trying to get Josh in here so he could see it. But trying to get, we thought
we could get Josh in first and then switch the password. Well, here's where, okay, I gotta,
I got a solution. What do I do? We think about this. I'm just not going to tell you what the
password is yet and get Josh and why would we not think about this first? That was like the eat.
What are we crazy? All right. New password. I'm just going to give it to Josh first.
What the fuck am I doing? What do you mean? I'm dumb. You didn't have the idea either.
You didn't have the idea either, did you? I just should have left it at the other one. I don't know
what the fuck we were doing. All right. New password. I'm typing it to Josh right now.
I don't want to show you this. How, guys, how are we going to do this? I don't know. I got to
get Josh in, then I got to change the world and I get what? Just the easiest problems have the
whatever. It's the most difficult solutions have, I don't, whatever they, you know, the quote from
that fucking movie with the guys in space throwing lasers and shields and stuff. All right. Let me
turn this off. Okay. I'm going to put that. I'm going to put the password down now. I'm excited
for this. I don't. I'm very ready for this. Why did we fucking do that? What were you doing?
Why would there be a separate password for Josh to come in? Okay. Yeah. Josh, we're going to change
that password again. Mine was too long. That one's the one we're using. That's the one we're using.
All right. Are you guys ready? Let's go. That's not the password. I could change that too.
All right. Here we go. Takes a little bit of setup. We're good. We're not ready. Yeah. I know. Hold
on. Let me just, he's in a weird mood again. I, yeah, I am because I'm excited. This is going to
be fun. All right. Looking for your sign. Where'd you put it? So here's the plan. We are going to,
we are going to do this for a little while. After we pick a few champions, after we get who I think
is, should be there. I'm going to play Closing Shift. It's a horror game. It's area game. It's
everybody make coffee or something. All right. I can officially now show the password on screen
and I can. All right. We're good. We're good. It just takes a minute. Everyone just relax. We're
fine. Password is not trial by combat anymore. Password is frogs LUL. That is the password.
Good luck everybody. What the fuck? No, wait, why are we getting invaders? Why are we getting
invaders? I got a password. All right. We got to kill this guy like quick. Josh, try as hard as
you can and kill him now. Get this guy. Get him. Okay. All right. Okay. Why can't I see anything?
Where's my HUD? Why is my HUD off? Who turned my fucking HUD off? Why is my HUD turned off?
What? Who would do? Why would that be turned off? Oh, right. I did. All right. Here we go.
You guys ready? Our first contestant, Goob. Welcome Goob. Goob, we're going to have you facing,
let's pick another one here. Passwords don't affect invasions. I thought you had to take the tongue
because if you're, Oh, right. Anyone can just invade the game. I forgot. Welcome Goob. Let's
take a look at you. See if I think I would want you as a, as a champion of mine. Rivers of blood.
Rivers of blood. That's an automatic disqualification. Um, thanks for playing. Josh,
if you could take care of him, please. Oh, you're not an invader. All right. You're going to be
going against, who's this? All right. Wrangledorf. Wrangledorf. I should turn off the HUD. Why is it
on? So these are our first two. Remember, I'm looking, I'm not just looking for people that
can play the game well. I'm wait, don't, don't, not yet. Oh, I'm not looking for like, Oh wow.
What a gamer. I'm looking for people that can, you know, be able to, it's not just about like how
many times you can hit R1, right? Where is, um, look his HUD. All right. Now I want my thing.
All right. So here we go. Let me take a look at you. Not bad. Hey, don't fight yet. Don't fight.
That's unsportsmanlike conduct from Goob. And I don't think I'm not, I'm not happy about this.
That's unsportsmanlike conduct. What am I doing? No, I want to look, where's my binoculars?
There it is. All right. I want, I, uh, first of all, Goob, I don't, I'm not, I'm not entirely
happy about what you just did, but I'm ready to start the fight here. If you guys could,
this is a, to see who may or may not be moving on. I'll consider everything.
You can go ahead and fight. You can go ahead and start now. I'm looking for a lot of different
things. I'm looking at the comedy. I'm looking at the skill. I need to back the camera up.
All right. River of Blood is banned. If you come, I'm telling, I'm going to tell you right now,
if you come into the trial by combat tryouts with Rivers of Blood and you kill the guy in three hits,
you're banned. Rivers of Blood's banned. That was cool though. That was pretty cool. I like the
armor. I like the getup. I like the idea. Uh, but we have, I mean, we have to find someone that can
get rid of you. All right. Drew Crew for life. You've, you got a catchy name. Rivers Crew. No,
no, no. If you, I, you, you, you're trying to impress me. I'm sorry, but you don't impress me
by hitting L2 three times, but wait a minute. It could be some redemption here. You forgot to call
us Drew Crew for a year. Okay. I'm not against having somebody with Rivers of Blood by the way.
Okay guys, go for it. Let me see what you can do. Let me see what you got. I like the weapon choice.
Oh my goodness. Crawl. All right. Okay. That was actually amazing. Congratulations. You're the first
person that's being considered, but not quite yet. We're going to have to have the, we're going to
have to have the chat vote on you, I think. All right. We need, uh, we need another gold sign.
We've got Drew Crew looking good. We need some gold signs. I might need to, uh,
okay. There we go. Who's this? Okay. Anna. Anna, go for it. Put on Tekken music. And by the way,
the environments are going to change too. We're not just going to sit here. Like I have to see
how people can handle this. Uh, yeah. Can we please keep, um, like, can we please keep the Drew Crew
for later review, please? That's for later review. Okay. Anna, let's see what you got.
Please help. That's funny. Uh, you two can go ahead and get started whenever you want.
Good. Oh shit. Fire move. That move is sick. What just happened? What the fuck was that?
Okay. You killed me. No, no, we have to redo this. No. I have to, I have to re-summon Josh
with a new password. All right. Put that one on the consideration list. Put that one on the
consideration list for sure. All right. We're going to move area. Drew Crew is currently saved.
We're going to pull them out later too. Uh, Drew Crew, if you're here, I would stick around. Uh,
but I need to make a new password and we're going to move area too. Uh, let's go over here. Let's
go. What's a place that like not a lot of people will be that's like kind of open in the snow area?
What about, yeah, what about like right here somewhere? Lindell? Outer wall of Lindell?
Yeah, that's probably not a bad idea. Like you mean like out here? Like at the rampart?
What do you mean like in here somewhere? Is 156 a room? Look, the room level doesn't really matter
that much. We're, we're trying to find some community champions here. Play Radegon's theme
during battles. Okay. I like that a lot. At least for a few. Uh, the one left. Okay. Let me get a
new password for Josh and then that password's changing. All right. New password. It turns off.
The one left near the outer wall. Do I even have the outer wall? Okay. Yeah. Outer,
outer wall battleground is where we're going to go. I gotta get a new password.
You killed me, man. I'm not gonna have to consider that. It's so funny because there's no way we're
going to actually get like, oh yeah, let's get like some like people to do that. I'm just picking
like the five like fucking biggest dickheads and like that's who's going in. It doesn't really
matter. It's just for fun. All right. New password. I got to change it. I don't want you guys to see.
New lake of rot. Yeah. Guys, I'm, trust me when I say this is going to be very, very,
we have to consider a lot. Once we narrow down some people, we're putting them in weird scenarios.
We're putting these people in strange scenarios. So don't worry. I, I gotta give Josh this new
password so we can log. Um, this is fine. Okay. That's the password, Josh. Use it. I'll get you
in and then I'll show it on stream. And I am right here, Josh, by the way. This is an interesting
place because there's a lot, this, um, verticality here, this area right down here. I think it's
perfect. You can be outside of it by a few levels. Uh, all right. I need to wait. I need to press the
button. Yeah. You can be outside of it. Where is, where's your sign, Josh, the fire, get the right
password, right? I hope I have the right password. I sent it to you, right? I need to reset it. Yeah.
Hey, you love the drew crew. Not yet. Hmm. Ah, no. What? I rewrote it. Let's try it again. If there's
no boss, you need a red summon sign first. Really? Oh, I didn't know that. Uh, Josh, it's
going to be red. And then I need to summon a red and a gold. That's a lie. Rest until night, but
until like noon or something. Oh, that is true. Okay. That was a lie. I feel like it's not a lie
because I can't see his sign. Use the finger. Didn't I already do it? I was reset it. Why does
it hate this place? Why does it hate this place? Maybe I gotta move. All right. Well, it doesn't
like this place. Um, how about up here? Will this work? Consecrated Snowfield? I can't believe I
fucking killed. This should work, right? Or the Radon Festival. Oh, that's a great idea. Yeah.
We'll go over there. You leaked the password? No, I didn't. Yeah. We'll go like right over here.
That sounds good. I pay a laugh. I can't summon here. What the fuck? All right. So what's the
thing to show the PVP areas? You, you're lying. It's like, look, what do you mean? Just go to the,
yeah, we're just going to go. All right. We're just going to go to an area where you can actually do
it. Church of vows is, it's kind of cramped. Academy main gate. The Academy main gate is
going to be so flooded with signs though, but sure we'll start there. That's a guarantee that
we can at least do it somewhere pretty early might be helpful for new game plus. That's true. Not
with a password. All right. Let's go to the, let's go to the main gate. I wanted to like do it in
interesting places though. All right, Josh, put it down on the main gate. Maybe an isolated merchant
shack. You need a boss to summon golds. I feel like I need a Wikipedia to play multiplayer in
these games. I always liked that. No, I already did. Okay. Sign should be done. No, I killed the
bosses that were in, um, in front of the church of vows. I, I did everything there. This isn't
new game plus or anything. I don't think. Let me see if I have the password right. I'd like a team
of 10 people to help do this. Yeah, that's the right password. No, no caps, no spaces, just that
word. And then that number, it just works. I have no idea why it's not working. Maybe we have to
just do it at the church of vows. I, it's, I, I don't get why I wouldn't, why I was working there.
All right. We're just going to go where it worked because it does not work here. I, for some reason
let's go back to the church of vows. Why would it work there though? That's weird. It's because of
the, I didn't kill the boss. There's a secret boss here. Oh, what the fuck? Okay. I'm very irritated
by this, by the way. Very irritated. I just want to play multiplayer. What the heck is going on
here? All right. We have to do it in a place where I have not killed a boss. Apparently there's a boss
here at night that I didn't kill yet. Holy smokes. Haven't put a red down. Yeah, that didn't work
either. Why was this working flawlessly last time we did this? All right. There we go. All right.
Let's go. All right. The password, the password is cookies three. Okay. It's fucking cookies three
from software. Jesus. So we need gold and red. Whatever you want to put down, please do it.
It gets cut off. No, it doesn't. Cookies three. What do you mean? All right. Who do we got? Oh,
here comes, here comes cinnamon. What? The three is cut off. How would the three be cut off if I
have it right here? What? Oh, I'm mad right now. All right, Josh, we have an invader and they're
going to fuck this whole thing up. So, uh, are you, are you, okay. Point to the ground if you are
wanting to be considered to be a champion. Josh, get him, get him, get him. This is random invader.
Get him. Don't let him screw this up. How are you? Wait, what? You can't find the emote.
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let up, let up, let up, let up, let up for a second, Josh.
Point. Okay. Point to the ground if you want to be considered. He doesn't have the emote. How do
you, don't you get that in like the first fucking 10 minutes of the game? All right. Do an emote
if you want to be, there we go. All right. You want to be considered. That's fine. Let's get somebody
to fight you. What do you know what your name is? Cinnamon. All right. Do we have a fire, fire, fire,
fire? I'm interested. That's rude. I don't know. Somebody could just invade and kill us both and
we have to redo the whole thing again, man. Hey. All right. I wish you both the absolute best of luck
and get started. Pretty cool. Oh shit. That was fucking pretty cool. All right. Stick around,
stick around for now. We need some red signs. This camera work is why you'd never worked out
as a wedding photographer. Listen, I, I just imagined like, I don't know why somebody would
have like, like their wedding video would have the Radegon theme for some reason.
Like you really like this game. All right. We need some red signs. What do we got here? Who's this?
Storm blessed. Maybe, maybe metal mesh. Zeke. Maybe there's Wrangledorf again,
Rachel convo breaker. Hmm. What do you guys think? Convo breaker sounds like a good idea.
All right guys, let me get a good spot. I need something like kind of high up, like up here.
Can I get like up on the roof somehow? Up on the rock. All right. Don't do anything yet.
I'm going to get up on the rock. Maybe I should get on this rock over here.
I love, we got to, we got to take a look at you. Hey, going on convo breaker. You two, uh, currently
this is a pretty interesting consideration here. Give up the hillside. All right. Follow me. This
is where we're putting the signs down now. I'm going to get up here. That's way better. Yeah,
that's better. All right. Once you start hearing the music that you guys can start to get started
here. Good luck. Congratulations. Uh, have a good fight. Oh, they, all right. They both have
similar moves. Oh, that was huge. Nice job convo breaker. Fire, fire, fire. I want to put you on
the considered list though. Excellent work. Let's get you in again. I want to get another look at
you. Are potions allowed? Yeah. Fuck it. Yeah. You can drink potions. Who cares? These are triodes,
right? You can drink potions. Yeah. Just chug them. Who gives a fuck? By the way, uh, convo breaker.
Um, we're going to eventually, we're going to, when we narrow this down a little bit more,
we might be in contact. It was like a fucking college application, like a job application.
By the way, we'll be in contact shortly. Potentially. Maybe not. Don't call us though.
We may get in touch with you. We're thinking about it. Be aware. We might reach out. What the fuck am
I talking about? I need some signs. Gold signs. Let's see what we got. What's your name? You got
a pretty crazy setup. So I'm going to, we'll go ahead and say, yeah, we'll call you. Don't allow
healing. No Estes. No, anything, anything goes. Stay in one spot. Well, I don't see any signs here.
Hey. All right. Come on over here. You're going up against convo breaker. Uh, come a little bit
further back. The rock. Estes isn't fair. Uh, yeah. I mean, we're not, um, we're trying to see how you
handle certain scenarios, scenarios. Okay. Uh, good luck to you. We'll get you the music. Once
you hear the music, you go ahead and start. Got a gun here. Not a bad start. That's the spinning
wheel, the pizza wheel. All right. We've got, we've got a contender here. Uh, I think we have quite
a contender. Use a controller. Yeah. The issue is it's like alt tabbing. What does it shift? How do
I like make it so I don't have to cycle, right? The person that stays has less Estes. That's true.
If tab, right? Just don't alt tab. But I need to play the music. All right. Let's grab another
one. Uh, any signs over here yet? Not really. I think they're all going to concentrate over here.
I'm telling you right now, uh, convo breaker, if you go three for three here, I'm going to have to
very put you at the top of the list to wildly consider it. Your own battle music. I mean,
three for three. That's a big deal. Um, I don't see any more signs. Reuse the item. Uh, I think
we have to refresh after this, which is fine. It looks like we're bringing in Zeke. Oh, no. Hold
on. Yeah. All right. Zeke, come on and play the flute for battle music. It's this is Zeke, the
freak plays Shito. I don't even, I don't even know where she is. All right. Come over to the rock.
All right. We got convo breaker versus Zeke, the freak. This is to solidify. Convo breaker
is going to be absolutely considered. I'm very curious about it. Let's see. Good luck. Somebody
has to, uh, no, no, get that shit out of here. It's going to kill me. Get that out of here.
Get that out of here. Oh my God. Convo breaker might actually be unbeatable. Josh is just running
back and forth. All right. Zeke convo breaker. That was, that was quite the display. I wonder
if there's any more signs. I never told them to start. I said, what's the dog doing? Oh, wait,
hold on. We got some more. Hold on. Wait a minute. Scum. The fanatic. Somebody has to beat convo
breaker. Can we just put signs down? Yes. Uh, people are wondering where we are. We are in
front of the church of vows. So level one 25 to one 50 ish. I mean, it really doesn't matter that
much. All right. Scum. Scum. You are, first of all, you've already got the look down. You're like a
weirdo. So you've already, where are you? Where are you going? Oh, okay. You're going the right way.
Don't go yet. All right. It's kind of a weirdo. Where's the barf drinker? Where is it? Where is
the barter? If you're like looking for Batman or something, like where is Batman? All right. Hold
on one second. You know when to start. You're going to start when the music starts playing and
hold on. I'll tell you when that is. That's going to be in about five, four, one, zero convo breaker
is three for three. Can scum drinker be able to do it? Badness. Oh, shit. Oh no. They're too far.
Oh, did he get him? Oh my God. Nobody can beat him. He's scared. Nobody can beat him.
Nobody can beat him. Somebody said I can beat him. We need gold signs down with that password.
Cookies three convo breaker. Um, we might actually have the first champion looking good so far.
We don't need the telescope view. I, yeah, but I like it. All right. We've got Xena of dragons
possible. Young replica. Villabalt. Arcturus. All right. Xena of dragons. Somebody has to be
convo breaker. It's starting to get to be nightfall. He just walked past my sign. I don't
worry. I'm going to get as many people as I can. All right. I'm a breaker. How do you feel? I need
to turn this music down. We've got our own music. All right. Come on over here. Xena of dragons.
Welcome to the tryouts. I think you understand the rules here. You're going up against the
strongest champion that's shown themselves so far. That is convo breaker. I will get up here and
I'm going to tell you when to get. Uh, come a little bit closer to the rock to start. Yeah,
you can be like 150 plus. It don't matter. Turn on cross region play. Uh, back up a little bit
towards the, uh, towards the rock. Keep coming. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up.
Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. They're just going. They're going.
I don't know what happened. I don't know what just happened.
You did it. You killed convo breaker. That was a false start. Josh, you look fucking crazy.
All right. Let's get, um, we need, uh, uh, that was cheating. All right. We got invaded. We got
invaded by trash. Everyone be on your absolute lookout here. Be on your absolute. This three of
us just be aware. This person might not have any idea what we're doing. If we could get a confirmation
from trash that they are here to compete in the competition, that would be fantastic. If we could
get an emo of you pointing down. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Come over to the rock.
Nobody start yet. If you start, you're disqualified right in front of the rock.
Those bugs look up with the bugs. All right. Oh, come over to the rock. Close to the rock.
Guys, I'm trying to. All right. You can now begin the battle. Good luck to both of you.
I can't see anything. All right. I can't zoom in anymore. Wait, maybe I can. How are you killing
people so fast? Here's the issue. The issue is it's like 0.0.02 sensitivity. How do I make it
faster? Can I make the sensitivity faster for the camera? Yeah. Like, come on, dude. Like,
what the fuck is going on here? That's better. All right. Finally. All right. Zena now is currently
in the lead. Lock on to one of the fighters. Can you move when you're in this? Yeah, I can't move.
I can't move around. Well, not. There's no lead. Yeah, there's no such thing as a lead.
Okay. Sanders. Sanders. Come on in. See if you can beat Zeno and let me turn this off because
it's annoying and makes loud sounds. Yeah. I want to be like not even here. Isn't there a
weapon that makes so I'm silent too? Isn't this something that makes you quiet? Okay. This one
here. Okay. So good luck to you, Sanders. Good luck to you, Zeno. Both of you are in it to win
it here. You can go ahead and get started whenever you both comfortable. Oh, my God. Good start.
That thing is instantly killing it. I'm on their team. It's okay. All right. This is a bubble
character. Oh, you're dead. It's over. Oh, no. You definitely rotted by now. Fucking move, dude.
Is that ever going to hit? Oh, man. Okay. Zena now is really difficult. Sanders is dead. Nice try.
What level is Zena? That's a good quick. Could you be like, it's not possible for Zena to be
like level like 500, right? Oh, yeah. Let's go. Nancy Drew. I need Nancy Drew's fucking theme song,
whatever it is. Ladies and gentlemen, you're competing for the first time.
Nancy Drew. Hey. Okay. Nancy Drew, meet Zena, the dragon, who will win this Nancy Drew,
just a detective, just a detective in high school or a dragon warrior princess. Good luck. Begin.
Oh, that's so much distance. Come on, go over there and solve the mystery.
Nancy Drew. Just that's like a fucking leg of a chair. Oh, shit. This is all that's in Nancy
Drew's inventory. I've got a piece of a fence. Nancy Drew's dead. All right. I think Zena's got
to be considered. Looks like she couldn't solve that mystery. No, nobody's got to come in.
Is Zena over leveled? I don't know. Maybe. I don't know. Magic is good. Put HUD on for damage
numbers. How do you check level? Is level scaling if you use a password? Apparently,
she's level 125. Yeah, she's not over level. She's not 713. All right. Any more signs or we're going
to have to refresh? Oh, there's a bunch in here, isn't there? This is PC. Yeah, we need to refresh.
It should scale. All right. Yeah. So we shouldn't be a problem then. All right. We're going to have
to refresh. Zena, please take Zena's name down. They're going to be considered. Considered.
You have no U.S. friends. What? Okay. Zena, you're going to have to help her. Minus what?
Tip? Should I put clothes on? To the right, to the right, to the right. Good sir. Are you here
for the Tournament of Champions? All right. Let's start this. That was like a little kid
just wandered over. That was just like, what was that? We were like, we were like, some just kid
just walked over. He's like, what are you guys doing over here? What the fuck was that? Disqual.
All right. Stinky. I got high hopes that Stinky. Where's the barf drinker? We need to put a bat
signal up in the sky for the barf drinker. Do you want me to DM barf drinker? Yes. All right, Stinky.
Good luck. Come over here. You're probably going to die in one hit. That was so funny.
This shield and sword didn't even die. We couldn't even say hello. All right, Stinky. Let's go.
I'm very curious. Let's make it happen. You are going up against the strongest character so far,
besides Convo Breaker. I don't think you're going to win. I don't think you're going to win. All right.
I'm going to tell you guys something like, I understand the comedy points work, but when you
come in here with like toys and you're going to get killed. This guy's using a sticky hand
from one of those quarter machines. Wait a minute. Don't speak so soon. Watch out for the... Uh-oh.
I was facing the wrong way. Easy. Stinky. This has been the hardest fight so far for Zena.
What the hell was that? Holy shit. Stinky, you got it. That's unbelievable. Nice job. Zena,
nice job to you too. Stinky, let's see what you got. I'll keep Zena's name down as well.
Stinky did Estus three times. Not a good showing. I keep thinking about the Linus guy.
He didn't even have a chance. All right. And we need a, uh, I need a gold sign.
We're going to have to refresh it in a second and, uh, bring in some new people
because I want to get a cycle. Gold sign right here. Okay. Well, we've got, we've got a, um,
what we have here is we have Frosted Flakes and then next to Frosted Flakes is the off-brand
Frosted Flakes that, that nobody buys. What's going on? Except, hold on a second here. Some
of those off-brand cereals that come with the huge bags are better. Buy like a lot. They're
gone though. I don't know where they went. You could buy like a year's worth of cereal.
How come their sign is gone? All right. Puke Peddler. Let's see if, uh, hold on a minute.
Are we really going to take the off-brand, uh, barf drinker here? What the hell is this? All right.
All right. I, I, I've gone over this person's sign like five times.
Hud for damage numbers. Put the HUD on for a little bit here in Cross-Region. All right. The,
hi. The reason why Cross-Region is not on is because if you're, if you got like a thousand
ping or something, then it's not going to work out for the tournament. I'm sorry. The way it is.
All right. VillaBalt versus, uh, Stinky. You guys can start whenever you feel comfortable. Good luck
to you. Uh, VillaBalt has, uh, he's like a merchant. He has all the items in the game
that, uh, he's probably going to block everything. Holy shit. Oh my God. This is going to be close.
Uh-oh. What is, what is he wearing on his back? Oh no. No. VillaBalt. That was so close. That
I went and put him down. Put VillaBalt down. That was actually pretty, that was cool. All right.
Where's Puke Peddler? All right. You've had a little, let's see what you got. Like I deserve
to lose. He was using an exploit. Oh, by the way, when we actually do this, we're going to
put rules in. So don't worry. This is not the Barf Drinker. This is the Puke Peddler. Oh my God.
So, yeah. Can we do a tag team? Um, it's going to be difficult. You do versus me and Josh. Yeah.
All right. Good luck. Puke Peddler. Let's see what you got. Oh, it's this move. This is the
biggest spell. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Stinky is a very skilled player because what I'm noticing
is a lot of, uh, a lot of consumables being used. Although Puke Peddler is coming up with
the lightning here. Doesn't look good for Stinky. Stinky's in a lot of trouble. Oh, that's it.
Puke Peddler. I've got to say that was a pretty good attempt to this pretty good display.
My only issue with you is a big issue is, uh, the Barf Drinker was the pacifist and used magic
tricks and, um, didn't like want to hurt anybody. And you just go right for the lightning move
and you're using his name. Oh, good job. I'm just kidding.
Everybody get out. Everybody get out. Quick. Leave. Run. Run. Run as fast as you can. Get out.
All dead four. Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave. Everybody all dead four. Quick.
All right. How do I do it? How do I all dead four? All dead four. I'm up.
It's like a fucking tornado coming in. It's like, it's like, did you see the tornado coming?
And it's like, whoa, look, there's a tornado coming. It's like a hundred miles away.
Whoa, it's here. The tornado's in front of the house. Okay. That was fucking crazy. I'm so scared.
That was so scary. I don't want my computer to crash. How do I all dead four? I don't know, man.
I'm fanicking. I don't need to back up my save. All right. So let's go back. What just happened?
Well, uh, that person that invaded may or may not have been, uh, somebody that didn't come in
and hack, uh, be a hacker. I don't know. It's so funny how everyone just like
scatters. Like everybody scatter quick. A tornado is here. Oh, that's so funny. It's like seeing
Slenderman, right? Like you're just like, oh my god, like two notes. That's cool. I got two notes.
And there he is. It's just like, wait, oh God, there's this thing here. I gotta get out.
Okay. Let's, uh, so we're gonna, um, okay. So the plan here is we have to get two invasion signs.
So, uh, Josh, be an invasion sign, please put your red sign down. I'll give you a new password.
I will check. Oh yeah. Let's go to the freezing lake. Wait, didn't I kill the boss? The freezing
lake. I think I killed the boss here. It doesn't matter if the boss is dead with the pet. Yeah.
But how come it wasn't working before? That's kind of weird. Stay where it works. My game is offline.
What? Hey, uh,
monkey ass. What are the 500 map markers? This game is huge. You didn't know. How did I know
was a hacker? Uh, last time we did this, uh, he came into the game and did like a bunch of
explosions and it was like exploding and scary. And I thought my computer was going to crash or
ran. All right. So, uh, let's make it a password to, uh, you, Josh. So let's see red signs and
gold signs, please. No, not Jesus. That was, that was a different person. What's a good,
let me think of a good password. I mean, that's an easy one, right? Yeah. So I want to see red
signs if you could, when you eventually have this as your password, which you'll get it in
just a moment. I'll change it. I'll update the screen to red. We need red and gold from chat.
Yeah. All right. So the password is I can see, uh, Josh's symbol. So I can do this.
Password is chair nine is the password. And you see red signs and gold signs. If you could,
that'd be fantastic. Chair nine. I need red and gold, please. Any red signs, any red signs.
I need the, you already have, oh, I need to do the tongue. Right. You can't summon two reds.
You can't. I thought you could. Oh, I have to do, I have to use the tongue first. Right.
Will I be able to see the signs on the ground or will this just let people invade?
Invasion timer is also literally zero. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. I mean,
I need to see some red signs. This one here, you peddler. Oh shit. We're literally being invaded
again. Oh, this is bad. Oh, this is bad. This is bad. I think this is bad. I think this is bad.
Why can't I see red anymore? So I'm going to gold. Okay. Well, this is, this is somebody else. This
is Zed. Okay. I think we're all right. Wait, what do you mean run? Okay. Who's someone in this guy?
All right. Zed. Why this is coming. That's my favorite part. All right. Follow me.
Host of fingers. Lasher the lame. All right. This is a double whip. All right. Back to the
fighting area. Please follow me to the fighting area. Good. Lasher the lame is over leveled.
That's why he has the thing next to his name. But yeah, but doesn't that mean he looks like
he's getting scaled down, right? It says down, right? How is he the host? Yeah. What does that
mean? It makes no sense. All right. Good luck. Let's see what you got. Lasher. Double, uh,
what are they supposed to say? Giant crusher? Zed versus Lasher the lame. Lasher the lame is not
flashing. Whoa. Actually was. What was I switched? That was a quick switch. Oh no.
Zed is going to take this one. Unless, uh, Lasher does something very, very interesting right now.
All right. Oh shit. This is, this is a good fight though. I'm enjoying this. Damn. Oh,
actually got him. Nice job. That was a really close one. Very close. Yeah. Why is Josh flashing?
Okay. So you are technically a, okay. You're technically a, um, gold, right? So I need to use
the thing and then bring in a red symbol. Camera work was better before. Do better. How come you
don't grow a mustache? I can't, dude. I can't have a mustache. It's not going to work. Okay.
So I need red signs. Put them down with that password. If you could please. I need to see
red signs. Any red signs? Do we have a confirmation from the bar of drinker, by the way? Is there one
right here? Did we actually get in touch with the bar of drinker? All right. Well, juggles,
juggles the great just came in. This would be interesting. Okay. Okay. Well, I'm just going
to say that I'm already very impressed. I'm incredibly impressed. So let's go ahead and
let's put some music on for this one because, uh, I think this is going to be a big one.
Don't fight yet, please. You're going to need some good old cartoon music if we could get it.
What was that cartoon music? I want like cartoon music, cartoon background music.
Why are they all like, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run. Why are they all
that? You know what I mean? That like run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run. Emotional cartoon music.
All right. We're going to do the how it's made theme song. Okay. Don't start yet. Do not start.
I want no HUD for this. I don't give a fuck if it looks stupid.
This was a, this is, this is a big deal. This one's a huge deal. All right. Who's who where's juggles.
All right, my god. All right, begin. Holy shit. Oh, he's got the he's got the silly hand
Oh
Shit. Hey, you guys won't go up on the rock. You guys won't go fight up on the two on the top of the rock
Will you you guys won't go fight on top of the rock? Will you why do they have the same items?
all the
Did he win I don't even know who's winning. Oh be careful careful
No, he's dead no juggles. Oh, I you know what put juggles down. I'm serious put both these guys down
That was a good one
The falling off. All right, we need a more red signs
We have confirmation by the way just to let everybody know just to make sure everyone's aware
We have confirmation that the barf drinker is not ready, but they will message when they are
Interesting the barf drinker. All right. I'm looking for red signs. Somebody has to take the lasher here if they could
This is pretty good display by the lasher. We need a red sign. So let's see some red signs, please
You home depot next the blasphemous barf drinker. All right, I think there's like 10,000 people
Invading at the same time. So we just got invaded by John Elden ring. Hey, what's up? John Elden ring is here
Lasher could you DM Josh with your steam name like your steam like ID profile and whatever
Just trying to keep track of everybody
Okay, so come on up to the rock, please. Welcome. That's the John Elden ring
You don't have to fight on the rock home depot music for this one. No, that's like annoying
How about just like Super Mario one? All right, where are you? You guys want to fight on the rock?
I mean that that's extra points if you can do it. That would be extra points. Oh
Creams going down extra points. Oh
Oh, what the heck? What the heck? It's not it's not the home depot. Am I my stream dying right now? You're at low FPS
I mean, it should be okay now
That was odd. All right. Yeah, everybody hang out. You're on a slideshow. There was a hiccup
I think hopefully brush your fingers that doesn't keep happening. All right
So what's it? What's like a good soundtrack for these two? You guys want to fight on the rock?
You can if you really want to fight up here you can I think we're okay
All right. Um, what's a good fine? I'll do the home depot theme. I'm only doing this one time
I'm not do this again. This is like a horrible thing to fight to. All right guys. Good luck. Oh
Good dodges up here. This is actually both of these guys a phenomenal job. This shows skill. This shows patience
I'm very impressed
Sorry, I just like got the rage in me nice dodge
Using the tyrannium advantage. Good. Good. Good. Very good work
Actually hit him with that. This is it. This is where it ends. Oh, it's none of how either you not falling off
That's impossible
Got him. Nice job. Wow
Nice job
I'm not kidding. That was impressive
Dodging around up here while you're fighting somebody and not falling off. Yep. Yeah
Well, hold on now. I want to see what you can do. Let's get let's get another gold sign in here John Elden ring
Very good job. I want to see what you can do. This feels like a classic video. I'm just I just think it's fun
It's just fun. I don't know. This is like I this is cool. I like this. I need gold signs now
Right. Do I have to refresh anything? Should I turn this off? Alright, cool any gold signs we refresh the area
This is fun. No, it is. It's I like doing stuff like this
I mean
We're kind of just sitting here watching people beat each other up and obviously I mean
I'm not gonna be able to get to all the people that want to participate but just fun to do
It's two invaders technically right or Josh. Are you gold? Turn the lowering thing off. Oh, you're red
Okay, so now I be able to see signs now, right or is because there's two invaders technically
I can't sign pull another one in I should be able to pull somebody in put on yakety sacks
Somebody needs to die turn the tongue back on
Hmm use a finger. I can't use remedy remedies. I can't it's great up
I think somebody has to die
John Elden Ring, I'm sorry, but I think we have to kill you and the tongue back on
Okay on this back on
Yeah. Oh, there we go. All right. We're good. No John. You're fine. Don't worry. You're good
Cory thinking about it. You've had a little we saw it. We've got you already
Zeke. All right, I might need to okay. I might I think I have to reload the area
I'm seeing the same like four or five names. I'm seeing the same like five names
We'll try Cory, but then I think I have to like reload the whole area as I keep seeing Zeke. I keep seeing
It'll about I keep seeing the same like three people. We'll do a reload after this like some boss music
What's a good? What's good boss music you think?
How about one hour of epic boss music walk? I feel like that pops people say dude block put block boss music
All right, sure Ross region East Coast. I don't think that's how it works
All right, you guys ready? Good luck to both of you. The music's gonna start in a second here. Go for it
Both of the same weapon mirror match. Holy shit. This is fucking this goes hard
nice
Imagine shooting the referee accidentally with an arrow good fight so far. Oh
Is that a stagger nice
That's a good fight. Good fight. Very good fight. All right, John Eldering you
I'm liking what I see so far. Who is this? I like what I see so far. All right, I have to do this twice
looking for gold signs
I'm gonna see if I can get one more person from here before I
End it up. We'll reload the area. What was that? It was an explosion, right?
But yeah, you know what? Maybe I could refresh it by doing cross region
I wonder what if that will do anything well that like look refresh everything actually might I'll try it
When you load in you have a pool of summons about 20 that fills up a resets when you reload the game
Really I have to reload the whole game. I'm picking from a pool of 20 people out of like
15,000 it's alright. It's what it's doing. This is fun. I'm gonna read we'll reload it
I will reload the game and I'll reload the area. So it's somebody said I have to reload the actual game
John Eldering, that was a great display. Thanks for playing. I got you written down. See if I can
Remove this
Made me I mean to reload the area. Okay. Well, that was weird. All right, I'm gonna reload the game
We'll get another pool of like a hundred people or something. Why can't I quit the game? Why am I stuck here?
Oh, what's happening right now? What's my even am I awake?
He just did the okay
Whoa, that just opened a bunch of stuff up. Is it the same people though? Oh, these are different people
These are these different people are these all different people I'm never gonna be able to get Josh
Well, I'm lagging. Why am I lagging so bad? I I'm gonna reload
I'm gonna do what that person said. They feel like that's my like actual game is lagging too, like hard lagging
Yeah, we'll do new password
How about alright so log back in? Okay, let's go use finger turn tongue on. All right
This should be this should work now use finger. Oh fuck. No, I need to
Goddamnit. Oh, I just so can't summon to brain. Well, I would write a summon. All right. Well looks like you're playing use finger
Fucking from software. I swear to god. It's like I need to like like be upside down drink milk
Pat my head blink ten times to play fucking multiplayer. All right, let's trans German
We're gonna bring in this person to fry finger, but whole I it's come on
I'm just trying to summon people were you in the game already boomer Andy. No boom from software is boomer Andy actually
Playing multiplayer with people with mechanics from like 1994 is boomer. That's boomer Andy
Wait, who's this? Who do I who's this?
Yes, I didn't I didn't summon this person. Uh
Well, I didn't even get Josh in here. No, no, no, don't just run away. Don't just run away. All right you two
France German and and
Wrangledorf go for it. You need to use the tongue very carefully. Okay, and because the tongue right? All right up to the rock
Wait, what what's going on? What happened? We can't even keep track of who these people are. All right me strong and
Wrangledorf go for it. I was gonna watch where do they go? What is going on? Oh my god. All right
I'm just fucking I'll be back. I can't even quit the game. I can't even set I have to go find me strong
I don't even know where they went. They literally just ran away. I
Don't know where you are. Okay, they all left. Well, how come I I can't I can't quit the game, huh?
What the fuck is going on?
Fucking please. No, I wanted you to kill me. Somebody kill me. Where's okay
We're gonna reload is this is fucked up turn off the tongue tongue is off. Okay, dude. There's a clown behind you
All right, let me get Josh back in here
We'll do this for a little while longer. I want to play that scary game too. Let me get Josh back in
I think if my games fucked up again. All right, I'm reloading one more time. Yeah new password. What's the scary game?
The what's it called something? It's like the coffee shop one. What day you guys do in the tournament?
I don't know if this might take a little longer than I thought closing shift. That's one. Yeah
I want to play closing shift. We do more of these fight clubs in the future. I love doing this
I just really wish there was a easier way to do this or how fun this is
I just wish it wasn't this much of like a panty ass. All right new password. You guys can't see right good
Okay, I got a password for Josh
private lobbies would be good too. Yeah, so the way it would work right is
I summon somebody and then somebody else so if I summon someone can someone else summon somebody else
What do I have to summon everybody Josh needs to be yellow for no invasions. You have to summon everyone. Okay
You just filtered by inscription. No, I didn't my plane closing shift today. Yes
Immediately after this front of the church door. Okay. All right, Josh is coming in the password
By the way is changing the password is now puke 30
No spaces no capitals summon me then summon a red then use the tongue for one more red
I think that's how it works. Yeah, so then the two reds will fight each other that makes sense
Yeah, this is PC. So now I need to see some red signs
Lowe some puke eater. Yeah, I I hopefully we can get confirmation that the barf drinker can participate
Okay, well we got invaded by by busting by me I think they're probably a participant I would assume
Now I gotta use the taunter's tongue. There we go. Okay, so
bonk you'lls
Let's do like I imagine just people are just invading. So can't summon red
I have to imagine if there's so many people just invading so here's the question then I got a really important question
If me and Ludwig were to do this, would we actually be able to do this?
Would we be able to actually summon people privately?
commander Hark
No
Kinda probably not you would need to have some you need to summon
Yeah, I would summon Ludwig as a cooperator like this and then summon an invader
But then we would need to summon another invader. He's called me a bandwagon normie. Well, what did I do?
Just don't leak the password
Secret passwords for all contestants. I think we lost somebody
God ended up without stream looking to know you started
I think we had the issue was trying to be able to reliably find participants. I think I have a few ideas
Maybe it's easier to just kind of pull people. I think what's gonna have to happen is oh
My god, did you see that person? That person was ridiculous looking. All right. Well, it looks like you two are fighting
Yeah, look by the way Ludwig is not doing what we're doing right now. It's just an idea that we thought would be fun
If it won't really work logistically then whatever we interesting to think about
All right, so come to the rock, please do not use tongue use gold for Ludwig then red and gold for combatants
But the issue is can I even do that because I I can't summon more than so when I summon Josh
Will I still be able to get to see gold and red on the ground?
Even if I summon another gold or another red that yes, okay. Okay. All right, that's confirmed. It's possible
All right, cool. All right, so let's go. So go to the rock
You guys ready to do I like the spear. I've got Quinn stinks and then busting in me
What what what weapon is that? I want to use that the weapons cool. What weapon art is that? Oh
Oh
Oh, he went for the triple poke went for the triple poke and it won
Good job
That was he that was amazing the tech chase
The tech chase
Caught every role nice job busting excellent work. So if we have private passwords, then we can okay, I get it
Yeah, all right, then we still we can do with fun
The issue is that there's just everybody knows that we're doing this right now
But people would know that during the stream day too, right?
We wouldn't we run into the same problem get away from it. All right amir versus uh,
We go busting bimmy. Let's do it. Just don't use the tongue
And only change location every time we might run into the same problem. We don't have to do a little bit of testing here
All right. Good luck guys
Lots of moving lots of movement
Flare I always do that. I was like go with the move. I'm always like
Very vulnerable, but still got out of it
Who won? Oh shit. That was close. Very nice job
You can play wobble dogs again. The reason why everything worked last time is because I used a group password
Aren't we doing that right now?
Can I change the group password to something pre-recorded on an undisclosed day? It would work without invasions
Huh?
And then broadcast it out
That might work. It does. Yeah, the group password doesn't do a
matchmaking
Three it would be an actual pre-recorded stream that would work
Yeah group password is only for I believe
What let me see. Well, you look cool. Hold on
You look really cool for dan and the bow armor. Very cool. All right, let's go for it
You too, and then after this I kind of want to just fight people
I'm I like I want to get in there. I mentioned to play
I'll do like five or ten times and then we'll do the scary game
Good luck. I definitely think I know at least one or two competitors from this stream
And the barf drinker, of course, obviously
What we might need to do
Is we might need to hold some of these offline
Not on stream. I think that would be interesting
Have like a night where whoever wants to participate we kind of just have a group password and just see if we can find some
people
Because doing it on stream is actually probably a lot harder
Yeah, i'll talk to ludwig about it. That was actually pretty plug pretty plug
Twin blade andy over here get a load of this guy
What's wrong with twin blade andy? Very good job. Very good job
All right
I it's time for me to get in the ring
Yeah, there's a there's a lot of people actively doing it. This is a good this is a good trial run though
Because I really do think that if we just have a group password in the discord
We can have some people kind of we can have people playing i can have maybe a couple of the mods or something if they're still playing
Keep an eye on it. See who's like doing well see who's like, you know playing against each other
Might be able to find it from from there
There's definitely at least one or two people that i'm pulling from this stream without a doubt. I gotta take a look
I'll talk to ludwig to see if he's uh, still interested
I'm putting together my pvp build right now. See we already got mods ready to go. All right
I'm putting some gear on and then i'm gonna fight and i'm gonna do some one-on-ones
I don't think I don't know if nancy drew is gonna make it. I'm sorry guys
It was funny, but I I don't know
What have I picked up linus?
Yeah, if you guys want to kill each other you can while I put some stuff on
What was I wearing before the royal armory? Okay, let me put on the bastards. Didn't they buff this?
Oh my goodness
That has some tag teams. I wish man. I wish
I wish they would I we could do so many things
Where the hell is the bastard stars?
Who the fuck is this thing?
Wrong hand and my staff. Okay
That's it. I haven't played in a while. It's been a while. All right. I'm ready to fight
Who wants to go you?
All right, mommy gonna go. Let's go
He basically wants the new wrestlemania on elden ring. I kind of do
Wait, I need to heal. It doesn't matter
What the fuck just happened dude? What the fuck was that?
That was 10 sec
Kill this thing
Am I lagging? I'm not even lagging though. I've crossed region on oh, that's right
All right. You want to heal up?
Nice fight
All right. Amir you want to heal up and uh go one v one and then josh i'll take you one v one, too
Oh, no, never mind. We can oh, you know, no josh. Why don't you one v one?
Uh, i'm here
That sounds good
Everybody say thank you to vr josh for being the um camera slash
uh
list
keeper
Really appreciate it. We'll pull a few people from this if we end up doing it
It's a good experiment. I think it's worth trying
All right. Good luck. What is josh using for a weapon? Nothing. He's gonna get killed by that
Nice try nice job. Are you gonna end the stream without the barf drinker barf drinker was uh unavailable today?
The barf drinker is uh was uh unavailable
Trust me when I say the barf drinker is team captain. So if we end up doing this
The barf drinker is the team captain no matter what it's just the way it is
And I would like to set up a stream
Where I I just follow the barf drinker around
Yeah, like just just follow the barf drinker and I go on an adventure with the barf drinker
All right. Let's go. You ready to go. Let's do it
Hey, oh
Follow them. No, like I bring them into the game and me and him go on an adventure
All right. Good fight. I got fucking destroyed go to the academy. All right. I'm gonna do a little bit of pvp
Thanks everybody. Thanks everybody for participating
I'm gonna turn off cross region. That's a rage quit. No, it's not i'm i'm going to the pvp area
I want to do 10 pvps. That's so I need nine more or maybe five more change the title. Uh,
That's true
Password is still the same by the way. All right, let's go up to tarnished barf drinker might be putting down a random sign
Uh-oh. Hello tarnished. Hi dirty rock. Ooh, didn't expect the founding reign of stars. Did you?
Ah shit ran out of stamina nice fight. Did you just rip a dab pen?
Barf drinker might be putting down a random sign really summon the barf drinker
I mean if the team if I can see the team well, i'm not gonna call barf drinker the team captain
That's only if they okay. I mean, yeah
Still using baby rattle. I like it if barf drinker wants to be team captain if we do this
You can give a password really. All right. Hold on. I'm very interested nancy to revenge. Let's go for it
Uh-oh, nice job nancy drew. He said he'd rather just put his sign down for now. All right, so as an invader, okay
barf drinker barf drinker
We got him. Is this the real barf drinker? Is this confirmed the real bar? I am like starstruck right now
I want to see this guy so bad, but we have to oh, okay
Is this the is this the real barf drinker? Is this him mods? It's a fake. He's a fake
He's actually a fake this is a fake wait, is it hey, is it a fake we have to see the behavior everyone just
Everyone wait and we have to observe the behavior. I don't know if this is the real barf drinker might be real
But did the barf drinker have a dash help him barf drinker take me wherever you want to go
I feel like i'm observing a wild animal apparently okay
The first one had a hyphen and the second one did too. Is this the real barf drinker?
It is the real one it is what do you want to do? Okay, what are you doing?
This is this seems pretty barf drinker behavior, by the way, ladies and gentlemen your team captain for maybe this coming weekend
depending if we do it
Hold on. He's trying to speed run warp technique. All right. This is the real barf drinker. I think he's trying to
Speed run warp technique. I love this guy. All right new game plan. This is what I want. Can I uh,
Josh can I see a list of the people that were I want juggles. I want barf drinker
I want I want a list of maybe I want like four of them
I want to get a little party together and I want to go adventuring with
With the group because I need to be able to see if I can gel with these guys
We need to go to like a dungeon together. I need to see if uh, because I have at least the three or four in mind
Can't do that. Why not? I can do two. Yeah
All right
We're gonna do a password for the barf drinker and for juggles the great
Those are the two that I want to do a dungeon. What dungeon have I not done on this character?
Whatever this one is here
You're gonna do two and you're gonna get invaded. All right, fuck it. I need a password
We need to get a password to juggles and a password to uh barf drinker and i'm gonna do that dungeon over there
I'm so he was trying to warp his skip. That's so funny and it was even funnier that he didn't get it
That's the best part
Is he was trying to get it?
That's such fucking that is such barf drinker behavior, I love it so much
All right, we're going down here. I'm gonna do a dungeon with these two because I want to see if I can confirm
This is hard. Wait a minute
Okay
All right
Barf drinker is an actual chat. I mean
I I agree
All right, let's get where's the entrance to this place?
Have I not done i'm dead. Okay. I have not done this place
Hila annex tunnel
Okay, so let's go ahead. I'll put up i'll give you a password
Uh, I can do two golds, right?
It's got to be something hard. It's got to the password has to be something because nobody's going to guess right?
It'll be kind of complicated kind of like this. Yeah, how many can what's the uh, let's see
How many characters is going to be one two, three, four five six?
Seven eight characters one two, three, four five six seven eight nine characters. Okay
So that's going to be the password. You can see your screen. Yeah, I know i'm gonna take care of it in a second
So this is this is gonna be fun. I'm very excited about this
Do you have any idea because i've been thinking about the barf drinker since we did that stream last time
I can't wait to play with this person. I actually am starstruck right now. I'm not kidding. I truly am heavy
I can't wait to do this
I'm so happy we actually tracked him down to
This guy I can't wait
This is gonna be so much fun
This whole stream leading up to this was worth it just for this one moment. Okay you guys
Uh
Yeah, vr josh is going to
Uh message you juggles and barf drinker to let you know
So do I need to do I have to go down there or does it can I actually see their signs up here?
Do I have to go down first? Okay, they both have the password. Oh, yes
Okay, put your sign down
Should I not have done that? I am at that
uh
What's this place called? The yil yil yil
Doesn't do anything. Okay, let's just play yellow at annex tunnel. It's in the
Go my map. Oh, right. I'm right here right here. You go down
And put your summoning sign down right here. There's one for the barf drinker. What's up juggles?
You want them both co-op or do they wait it has to be red. Jesus. There's one right here
Why can I do it? Oh my god
And we got invaded already. All right guys, we have to defend defend everything don't let don't let this person fuck this up
Barf drinker is gonna be summoned and get killed or unless rob. Are you? Oh my god. Get him. Don't let this
He just came in and started screaming
Barf drinking you're gonna actually fight him
All right. Are we good?
No barf drinker. We're not going barf drinker. We're not going that way
I love how barf drinker just showed up and was like i'm doing that too. What do you want to do?
He's still warp skipping. What are you? Where is he gonna go? Is it not working?
This scared the shit out of me. All right, we have to complete this dungeon. That is your task
We've got the team captain barf drinker
Uh second in command juggles and then like literally i'm third in command
Got him. Nice work. Just want to make sure they're dead. That's
10 out of 10 tactics by the barf drinker. Can we not even get in here? What do we how do we get in?
Oh, wait guys
We can go this way
I did that as a stupid joke, but i'm alive. Thank god
Oh
Everybody heal up. Don't
Where's the okay? We're good
Okay, nice. Good work. I don't know how we all lived. Were we supposed to do that?
All right, go on barf drinker lead us. All right. Be careful. Don't
I'd say we should go across and explore over there first. What do you think?
He's like i'm contemplating where to go
Careful juggles
Good work the golden rune here. All right, let me get this item first
They added the three stooges to the to elden ring. Yeah, it kind of feels like that doesn't it?
Where's the barf drinker? Where's the barf drinker? Oh, wait
Wait, he already went up
Watch your health there juggles
Nice work. I thought they were going to fortnight. No, it was elden ring. It was different. I need everybody in here
All right, go for it
barf drinkers
He's gonna die over there. I don't even know what's happening over there
Do we get him?
All right, we got what was that?
All right, how you guys doing on health you guys? Okay, dude, you look like a beat
Like a beat the vegetable beat I look like a beat god, there's the shortcut what's in here. Where's barf drinker?
Where's barf drinker? You go in where is he? He got the zip. Wait, what do you mean? He got the zip
Uh guys, I hear him. I hear somebody juggles. Where oh, there you are. What are you guys doing?
There's an invader here. I just want to make sure
Yeah, let's wait for him. He's gonna come up the ladder, right?
Let's make it so he can't come up the ladder barf drinker if you get that that would be insane
What wow you actually did it that was terrifying I thought wait they they can come through the other way
Nice job guys. Excellent work. Very proud. Where's the music? I'll give you music. Let's go fight the boss barf drinker
Let's go get it done both of you juggles barf drinker. Let's see it. Good luck. What the fuck
Oh my god, it's one of these
Where's the barf drinker? Oh, he's just coming in now. Okay
What is he doing?
Oh shit, oh no juggles is going down. Come on barf drinker. Let's go. You got it juggles is doing work in there
Why he just ran the whole perimeter
I love the barf drinker so much. He's the best character
help
You got it come on barf drinker juggles is the tank barf drinker is the is fucking bard
No
Come on barf drinker, how many weapons does is a bow and arrow?
How is juggles still alive man, oh i'm gonna get hit by this
I'm, all right. Everything's fine
Watch out for that teleport. He's gonna grab somebody
I can't believe how good juggles is at this game
Watch out for the meteors
Meteors coming
Oh shit
Everybody. All right
Get in there you can do it
The little pebbles
Watch out. Watch out meteors again
Oh fuck. Oh, no
We can still get it barf drinker down
Oh shit
No
Dude
Oh shit juggles is dead now. Wow
No, i'm dead
That was awesome that like and the arrows just like falling over
Okay. All right. That was that was the one for cinema. Now. This is the one to win that was for cinema
Oh my god. I loved every second of that. The best part of that was the barf drinker doing like the perimeter
Just checking the perimeter juggles had no
blast and
Didn't get hit one time for like five straight minutes juggles carried the entire fight. Oh, man
I love that's so funny. The best part was definitely the arrow volleys. I just thought I couldn't fucking do it anymore
It was just too funny. All right, uh same password guys. Let's put the put these down
And barf trigger has like
10 weapons
I need to use the remedy. I don't want to leak the password though. Did you miss the tourney?
Yeah, I mean I I gotta figure out what I want to do about it
because
There's just so there's so many people
Trying to connect that after a while
It was just hard to kind of keep track and the invasions and tons of people trying to invade
It's a fun experiment. It's a fun idea, but I think we might need to do it
Offstream some too have people sign up through the discord. Yeah
It's probably a lot more of an undertaking than
We think what's up juggles. All right, i'm at we'll go for the win this time. Okay, i'll bring the uh you back
Just you know, just elden ring with the boys not a big deal. I'm gonna actually i'm gonna put on the moon veil
Let's go try hard mode here. What the what's going on? Who is this?
I got we got invaded watch out watch out. Watch out be careful
The partridge has got the big shield get him boys
What is happening right now?
All right. Nice job. Nice job. That could have been a disaster. All right, make sure you're all healed up. Okay
Quick little pep speech here quick little pep speech. You know what I mean? Not a big deal
What I want you guys to do is this?
everybody
Needs to focus a little up. Okay
We might not be the smartest
We may not be
The healthiest may not be the tallest we may not be
All right. We may not be the strongest we might not eat very well. We might have
Uh, you know, I microwave at least three or four dinners a week at least
Some of us may have had to go to the bathroom for the last hour
Number two and i'm holding it and it might be diarrhea but together we are strong
Don't let anybody tell you differently and the three of us are going to go in there right now
We're going to beat that god damn god daemon. I'm going to do it first try good luck. Ow
Whoa, this three. Oh
Oh, no, juggles is going up
Watch out barf drinker
All right, heal up good good good good good good
the arrows
Shit. All right. Watch out meteors good
the music
What's wrong? What's wrong with the music?
What's wrong with the music?
What's wrong with it? It's a bug
Who just did that? Holy shit. Nice job
Watch out
Careful the grab watch out for the grab careful the audio is scuffed. That's it. We got it
Meteorite of astel. Hell. Yeah, nice job guys. Oh, I missed them already
Okay, so I never did that don't cry because oversmiled because it happened. No, I want a clip so bad
I know somebody's got it. Oh that the barf drinker volleying the arrows and i'm just going like this
This is so funny. Oh
That was awesome. Does everybody have it? I need to see it like right now
This is like my favorite clip ever
This could be like my favorite elden ring moment and like I beat the game like fucking two weeks ago
What the fuck? Oh, it's right
How many weapons this is a bow and arrow. I love this so much
What's wrong with the music
Why does it sound like somebody's listening to this on the subway next to me?
I fucking love it so much
Yeah, why does it sound like somebody's playing that like through like a school pa system? What was that?
Oh
Help me with godfrey again, please can we we could also summon the barf drinker dude?
Oh man, this is such
It's so fun
Okay, so
Uh, I think this room
Uh, you want to help with godfrey?
Like horror loo. Okay, let's uh, let's get I don't know how we're gonna get you the password dude
The first full night with them. I don't know if we're gonna be able to do uh, get the password to somebody
It's two more caves in the snowfields. You don't have um, that's all right me strong. I'll handle it
You have a parasocial relationship with the barf drinker
All right, I think I I want to play this horror game, but I definitely want to do this again. It is discord
Uh, this was a good experiment, but I want to I want to do this horror game
I think there's a good I think there's a good place to uh pivot
That was uh, that was a i'm glad we ended on that note. We have the barf drinkers
We have the barf drinker. We have we know who the barf drinker is
We know juggles is there's plenty of opportunity to do more of that. Oh, what a great character
Uh, thanks for playing in the pvp. We're gonna move on. We're gonna play a horror game now
We have everybody who yeah, we have pretty much everybody that was there
Barf drinker juggles. Thanks guys. Thanks for making the stream like funny fun
Appreciate it. Let's think about it. I I didn't do that. That was the barf drinker
That was juggles that was me just like laughing and having a good time. Well, that was that was all them
So thanks guys. It's a lot of fun
So we're gonna move on i'm gonna take a quick break when I come back. We're gonna play uh, the
Closing shift taking a brb. Anyways, i'll be right back closing shift. See you in a minute. Maybe it'll uh be fixed when I come back