Hello, should I leave the title as buying and selling organs? I feel like that's uh, kind of morbid for the next game we're playing.
What are you- what are they doing? What is- what is the chat doing right now? What's the meaning of this?
I broke the chat? What'd I do? What is- what are you- why- why are you revolting against me? What are you doing?
Put us back in emote only mode. I will. I'm gonna drop this volume a little bit. What's- what's this little-
What's this bit that they're doing? Is this like a- what- what- what little routine is this?
Capture this game? What- what do they add? Is it actually like a big substantial update? That's pretty cool.
I love this game too. Video quality, uh,
Super computer. Looks fine. Mouse sensitivity, bring that down.
Leaderboards, I don't need the leaderboards. Who cares? Do 90 FOV. I do need to do this.
I remember this- I remember the sound effects were very loud. Turn that up. Okay, go back to the organ game.
I'm- I don't make me scream into my monitor. I really will. Okay, so I think I'm just gonna
just do the, sort of, birthday mode, because I just want to play the new stuff. Survival takes a little too long, I think.
Click play. Oh shit, that's cool.
Yeah, let's just do birthday mode. Go back to the organ game. You guys-
You guys- stop being such butt heads, okay? You guys are being butt heads. I'm gonna tell mom.
This is like the I'm telling mom. You're like holding your finger and putting it in my face, like I'm not touching you,
I'm not touching you. I'm about to yell for mom. All right, here we go. So what- what are the- what's the additions?
Which, um, arcade should I go to? Did I shoot myself in the head? I thought it was-
No, what do you mean, new text message? Happy birthday, kid. All right, I got 200 bucks. The bullet went backwards.
Go to the-
Please don't listen to chat. Don't change the title. One-Eyed Billy's. Oh, okay. I forget where One-Eyed Billy's is.
Larry's Pawn Shop, Larry's Arcade. Isn't it down on the coast somewhere? Oh, we'll find it. This is very loud.
This is exactly what I was talking about. The outside of this arcade looks like a strip club.
I do appreciate the GPS that's here now. All right, One-Eyed-
Don't hit me again, please. Okay.
Stuff it. Where is One-Eyed Billy's? Did they add another arcade or is it they add more machines to- Oh, One-Eyed Billy's is this way.
Oh my god, dude. There's a whole new arcade?
What? Holy shit, dude, you wouldn't believe it. The Oregon game just got a huge update. You should check it out.
You dick.
How do I reliably get over there? I guess I have to run.
Remember, your stream gave me acne. I didn't do anything.
Eden Animals, that doesn't work right now. All right, One-Eyed Billy's is right here. Let's go check it out. I'm actually very interested.
By the way, I'm just realizing, aren't I like 13 or something? I feel like this would be incredible. Where are my parents?
This would be really dangerous. All right, One-Eyed Billy's. Adventure and Fun Center.
Celtics lost. I have not seen a Celtics player shoot a basket in probably like 11 years.
I have not watched a single game. I'm sorry. All right, should we get a pizza?
24-hour delivery. Earn money today. Pirate pizza. Wait, what? Deliver pirate pizzas. Click here to accept a delivery.
Fried baked pizzas. Pizza delivery. Seven dollars. Wait, did I just buy a pizza? Why am I purchasing this? What?
Why did I have to buy this? Who am I delivering this to? Who is supposed to be getting this? Oh my fucking god.
Where's my car? Where's my car? Where's the car? Did you expect it for free?
I don't expect to pay for a customer's order and then bring it to them. The customer pays for it
and then I get paid to bring it. Why do I have to pay for the customer's food?
The sound just got removed. Can I just run there? I definitely can run there.
You look out your window, like you order like
Uber eats or something and you look out your window and there's a guy just fucking
sprinting down your street with a bag of food in his hand.
He's in full stride and he still comes up as a car on the app when you look at the app and you know
you can see where the car is going. Oh, where am I? Where am I? Where am I?
What I don't what what where am I? Where am I? I don't know. What am I? Where am I? I'm the red?
Is this their house? Oh pizza. How do I get my inventory?
Hey, don't call my limo. What are you doing? Where am I? Did I just? No, I don't care.
I don't I want to go back to deliver that pizza. No, I need to take me to the place
I just was. I need to go back and deliver that pizza. I need to buy limo. Can I take it? Where am I? No, wait
Oh, for the love of God. Okay. Hold on. Wait. I have a car. Don't I have a bike?
Don't I have something to I don't have a car or anything. Okay this way. Oh, it looks like my
Uber Eats driver is right down the street. Let me open up the the blinds and see sprinting down the street
He's got a bag in his hand. He's here. Oh
He just got hit by a car. I think I hope he's okay. No limo just pulled up
He's standing outside the door. He just got in the limo left. He's back running. Okay straight. All right, do I flashlight?
I thought I did you're not gonna make it. Yes. I have a hundred and twenty four seconds. I'm running a hundred and twenty five miles per hour
I'll be okay. Which house is it? It's this one right here. But where's my inventory? I?
I haven't played this in a long time. I have my credit card. K is inventory. I don't think so. It's on the watch tab
All right, where the hell is this place right ahead? It's not this building. It's building right in front of me
I need to take it out golf cart Beach Billy's warehouse factory. There it is. Which house is it? Is this but okay?
It's right here. Where where is it right here? Oh
God this one. Where is this house?
What's happening? Is it this house right here a dollar tip and he's slim. I actually just got one dollar tip
Okay, there's my limo in here. Let me in my car. Why can I not get in here?
I locked myself out of my own car. I can't take this off the card in this lot. I go to
One-eyed Billy's already not impounded. It's fine. Drive your car up here. It's not even that steep, please
You're me you should play at least the pain playing the painful is an arcade machine here at least the painful
All right. Finally, let's play some of the new games very excited. There are no breaks. I don't have breaks
I don't have breaks
Randomizing the play tables and coin. What do we play tables?
Well, you said there was a new boat ride to take which will do that sounds like fun
I want to do this. This is fun. I score is 175. I think I've done this already, but I love this game
I can't do it by a I got my 80s just freaking out. No matter what you guys. I can't trace anything
I also can't do this either. It makes me like want to puke. Oh, I did it. Oh
You play against another person. What's happening? Why am I getting attacked? What was that? Who just did that?
I'm gonna fuck with me again. Oh hoops. I gotta get it in the spot a little higher. Come on
What's the point of a backboard? They always say aim for the backboard, but you never see like NBA players do that
They always just swish it or dunk it out and do but not really Mountain Dew
Oh, what's this one? You see these in like Dave and Buster sometimes you always wonder there's so much room
This is such a huge gigantic machine. It's so unnecessary
And this is by the way, this is one of the worst machines in the entire arcade. This thing sucks
Nobody likes playing this I've never seen anybody have fun playing this game. They always like swipe their card
They press it once they go. All right. This is right. What's over there? What's that over there? Is that a time crisis?
Nobody likes this game
And by the way, this game is always one of the most expensive ones in the entire casino 50 tickets. Hell, yeah
30 tickets. Oh, yeah in the middle what I get. What was that? What?
559 I got the jackpot. Oh my god
Fake I'll give you another one. This is roulette for children. How many balls do I get tickets? Awesome? Yeah, I'll do it again
Say how much this sucks again. I think I just did it again. Holy shit. All right, I'm getting really lucky
Mystery, what's the mystery? Wow, that's a lot. I mean, this is a really good return on my investment
Turn it up a little bit. It's kind of low. I do it again. What is wrong with me, by the way, okay
I'm just gravitating towards this. This is all the little kids at the skeeball machine. You just open up Chuck E cheese and it's just like
I
Just keep it go go go go go go play skee ball skee ball skee ball skee skee skee
I think I might this might be broken. I'm not sure what to do about this. I take my tickets
Think I might as a leave and come back. All right. Well, this one's broken. Just like at every fucking arcade
I'm not let me tell you at every arcade I've ever been to
It's always like one or two of these are just not working and they always have the best prizes in them
Is that some kind of crazy conspiracy?
It's always the ones that are not on that have the best prizes inside
This one's kind of cool and what they should do is take the prizes out of the one that's broken and put it in the
One you can actually use
There's a fidget spinner in here. These my tickets. Oh, those are 80 tickets. All right. Okay. I want the fidget spinner
I'm gonna get it. I
Like the golf balls is cool. Is that money? I don't think I can rotate it settle down. That was way off
I think I got it though. Oh, come on. Was it a razor?
Good again
What's the biggest prize I've ever won?
Um, I'll hit the flaming finger. He doesn't want to talk about I think I goes flated finger get your flame on and you have to
Go like with your finger. It's a trace inside the lines
I've beaten that one before and I got I think like a thousand tickets whatever the jackpot was
I actually beat it. I made this up. It's an actual game. I won't hold on. No, I'm not done. I want that
Whatever it is
There's a strategy with that though is you don't it it's you get friction if you use the pad of your finger
So you have to use almost like the top of your nail and the the top part of your finger
So you use almost your fingernail and the small part of the pad at the top right where the fingernail reaches
Like right where your fingernail touches your pad of your finger is that's what you should be using to play flaming finger
The money. Oh my goodness. Come on
What is flaming finger flaming finger is a arcade game?
You have to trace inside of a gigantic maze in five seconds the whole maze
Is that not in?
Arcades anymore. I feel like I've seen it. Oh my goodness. Please just give that to me. I
Need one of the fidget spinners. It's this why is it swaying so much? That's how they get you stop swaying
Give it to me. You're doing great
That was makeup on that's what the face came isn't on. There you got me. I don't want movement
I see I can't see from the other side. Oh my god. Stop moving around so much
All these golf balls are messing everything up. Just just leave I'll come back later
Just leave I'm done. What's this one?
Fishy fishy. Ooh, this is cool. This is definitely wasn't here last time now the crane
I wonder how much better this just you know, let's see. I'm going with it for the
Flam the shell whatever it is right in front that one down right there grab it
Let's see it first try. Come on
Oh, yeah
Give me another one. I think I got this one. This one should be easy
Oh, yeah, if that grips. No, it's okay hit the snail
I'll get it. How much is this worth?
Probably sell that I want to play the air hockey. I play against someone
Oh, okay
What don't laugh at me?
You guys have to understand the strategy with air hockey
As you just stay completely still right in the middle and your friend will fuck everything up
You just don't have to move. They're gonna try to be like
It's gonna bounce all over the place
Well, this was an ai
Your goal is you want to go straight forward let your friend just do a bunch of crazy shit. They're gonna screw up
Because they're always gonna bounce to the edges
Just defend this middle part and you'll be completely fine. See what happened
Is a crowd forming
This like four or five inches right here is the only thing you should be concerned about at all
Just wait for your buddy to rear back and go smash and then it bounces king king king king back and hits him in the fucking finger
And he's gonna go. Oh shit, and it's gonna be inside. It's you don't have to do anything
Varying speeds too. That doesn't make any sense. This is one way for my body
That doesn't make any sense either
Get over here somebody else
Or you know what another strategy is and i've used this before too and it really really pisses people off
Is you just go like this
You just go back back back back back back back up up up up up up up up up
Like that, I mean it's gonna make you sick if I keep doing it, but you get the idea
And then they'll eventually score on themselves
That's classic. Oh, yeah
I'm the you hold on. I am reaching that far
That seems like too far to reach
Why is it a yo-yo? I'm not doing the strategy. It's not working. That's a new game idea. That'd be really dangerous
I don't think that'd be safe
I'm gonna get hurt
You know what? I also think too
I also think that these paddles should be heavy
They should be weighted
and i'll tell you one reason why
the amount of people that get on these machines and act like absolute assholes
And just swing as hard as they can and smash this shit across the arcade
if these things were like
seven to if they were like ten pounds
And you had to like drag them around and actually you couldn't like swing like crazy and knock it off the thing
And they should be attached
These should be attached to here
This should be on a track. That's literally here like this
And it should weigh like fucking five pounds
Just make it. Yeah, and somebody is every two other people
No way. I have to let me rephrase that
It should be
tethered
To a wire or something that can only move like this far
Right. So not like a track but on a tether so it can move like this, right?
On a wire or whatever the tether it has to be on and it needs to weigh like at least a few pounds
Are you losing to a little kid?
I'm barely even playing the game. I'm explaining how to make this game better
I think I've mentioned this before but uh, you know lying on top of one of these things
Just letting the air hit every fucking pore of your body. That's like
I like want that
I want a
Um air hockey table in my house not to play it
To be have to be a relaxation zone
Is that weird?
Let me say that in the middle of like the hottest days of summer when it's 110 115 plus degrees here
lying on top of one of these and having
Hundreds of little air jets hit you in every corner of your body
I wouldn't even play this thing
And get one just take a shower
But I don't want to get wet. I don't know who's winning right now. I can't even tell
Is this supposed to be a little kid?
I'm talking about your fetishes
That's very specific
Yeah, I see what happens is I get off to uh lying on my back on an air hockey table
I'm letting the air hit me in the back
Good luck finding pornography for that. There's probably three videos on the internet where that happens
You know, you're not gonna you're gonna have to cycle before like two videos
You could just corner the market
I don't I don't think there's very large market for that
If you're talking about uh, like a business expense for yourself
I'm not sure you would ever recoup the cost of the table
Does anybody else think this is getting a little ridiculous that this is still going?
And I have to admit this happens when I play regular ice hockey not ice hockey, uh table hockey
What the hell is this called?
After about five minutes neither person wants to play anymore, but nobody wants to back away because this was four dollars
I won I just kicked his ass
That's pretty good tickets
I am not kidding. I have left games without being completed
There have been people waiting to play air hockey sort of another like couple group or kids or something that I and
And i've gotten like two to two
Like one to three or something versus somebody
And we just leave
Like oh that was fun. I know you guys can just take it
I actually in fact will say I think air hockey
is
The worst thing that's in the arcades because it takes up so much space and I find it to be
After five minutes a game. I don't want to play anymore
Like not even two minutes
I would rather there be
I want more games like video games and not just the same video game
Where they give you a machine gun a plastic machine gun to fire at aliens. I'm sick of those, too
arcades nowadays have seriously become like 10 plastic machine gun shooters 10 car games and then a bunch of like
Coin pushers was the mortal combat
They tuck that shit in the corner
Where's turtles in time they put that stuff in like the jokey retro section where there's three cabinets
They're covered in dust. Nobody plays them air hockey's fun game
I don't get I don't know. I think it's uh, I think it's taking up too much space too much space
Go to a retro arcade. Yeah, but those are so few and far between
I think it's fun, but please remove it from all arcades
I didn't say remove i'm just talking about there's usually like four or five of them
That take up the a huge amount of real estate because you have to have a huge amount of real estate to put them down
Then there are these things
Do you know how many simpsons arcade games could fit just right here?
eight
You could fit six arcade cabinets one, two, three, four fives
How am I supposed to get it down all the golf balls are in the way
Dave and busters is all that we have. Yeah, I think that kind of
I don't know. Here's the weird thing about arcades nowadays
Is all these companies bait
everybody now with nostalgia
Yet no one will make an arcade that has the old games in it and then really have it be like a big business
Like they just pull on all of our nostalgia heartstrings
But they won't put any of these like old cool arcade games
Dave and busters is just like
The same this kind of shit everywhere
There's there. Yeah, they exist but it's maybe one in one every major city maybe has one
maybe
Round one does do it round one does it to an extent?
But I really do kind of miss just like the old just arcade games where you just the cabinets
You just played a game
And you had to put you know coins in for lives and stuff. I miss that
Arcades are the way to go
That's true
That's true. I'm just trying to get these golf balls out of the way
There's not a market for it anymore
Yeah, but that's my that's that's my point though. There's not a market for it anymore yet
They keep remaking video games and movies and stuff
I think there is it's just nobody really wants to put the time and money into doing it
I so badly want this fidget spinner old arcade cabinets are hard to maintain
Yeah, i'm just a salty old person
I will get this before I turn the stream off
I promise
In fact, i'm getting it right now
No, i'm going too far up. I'm convinced anime conventions have big arcades
I remember
I think like some of the packs at some point had this old retro arcade room
It was awesome
It was like 50 cabinets old like donkey kong like joust and all that stuff. It was so cool
And that might be it
There it is
Hold on a little longer stuff swinging around so much. Yeah
All right, let's go
Where is it? Um, where's my fidget spinner? It was just five dollars
Oh, what's this? What is this time score? I have to shoot like a water cannon. This is cool
What boat am I what am I supposed to do pick up the
Oh, okay. I have to pick these up
Oh boy. I have no idea where I am
earn
I'm blue in the corner. This is cool
I love those old midway games too. We have to spray the water into the hole
If I was ever a billionaire I would just I would probably lose 50 000 a day on this project
I would love to just have a huge awesome arcade that had so much of this stuff
All the old classics just like a hundred plus old, uh retro arcade cabinets all the old stuff remembers
I would probably just lose money every day
I can't tell even what direction I am. Can I turn around?
Rent out an arcade instead
Say toy boat toy boat toy boat that was cell phone did
Honestly, the way that that boat over on the left was I thought it was spongebob in the water
Vegas is probably the place to do that
That was cool. I got tickets for that. How do I get off?
Oh, that's a lot. It's 600 tickets
Did that one? I got that one. I beat that one. This minute did I oh this mini golf
I don't think I did mini golf. Did I?
Last time I played it
I got I've got to put all the new viewers. I gotta impress the hell out of them, right?
How could I not impress the new viewers with this?
You know when I got this it was like five or six times in a row
Ah, come on this was the ayaya game. Yes it was
I gotta get it twice in a row
Come on apologize apologize apologize apologize. I am so sorry. I am so sorry
What was this what I just got distracted get out of here
Come on three times in a row
Oh, I forgot about this you can just keep going
Let's try to crash the whole game and just try to fill this entire arcade with tickets until like everybody has to run out
This is really loud. You're right. It is
Now what what's going on here? Come on. What happened to the organ game?
Um, I got two endings
and
I thought it was a really fun game
But I realized that coin game had an update I didn't know about
And now chat was very very, uh excited about it
Incredibly excited about this update
So I was like, you know what fine we'll play this too
Organ dev. Thank you on twitter. It was really sweet that game was
Very very very fun
That was like I would give that at least
I mean something high that was fucking really good. I might play it again on my own time
He got bullied into playing coin game
This game is really fun too
There it is. Finally. All right, I got three
All right one more
One more jackpot and i'm done
Come on one more. Come on
You gotta play dizzy bird. I'll play dizzy bird
I've lost my magic here
There we go. Don't break my shit
So much dopamine. There really is dopamine. I'll play this one too. This one new. It's not bad
2500s on there too. Holy crap
I never play these when I go to the arcade. They feel too random
I feel like I have no control over what's going on right now. The organ game actually updated for you
No, they did not the organ trader dev actually updated the game to spite chat what
No, they didn't hold on. What was the update?
No joke. Hold on. What what what was the twitter again? I just I just
Moved out. I just closed out of the window. Oh, hey chat. You got proof
Okay. Okay. What was the update? He said I do not fuck around update queued. Wait, hold on. This is this is actually hilarious
Okay, let me read this he found his connect he read the tweets live on stream like my parents on christmas
Nerma putting even more cash into x cormac's remnants to drive down his average price paid and justified in his investment with a big
Meme face he gets it portions of the chat kept asking for a different game
So often that he switched to emote only so they'd shut the fuck up and he could concentrate on trading organs
That might be the best endorsement i've seen of the game so far. Holy shit
He was holding his urine for four hours to keep playing
Building and uploading a new steam version specifically so that the chat isn't gaslighting germa about a new
Update anymore. Are you kidding me? This is that's that's actually hilarious
one guy
In this chat said hey dude, go back. They updated organ trading simulator lol
It's like aha. That's funny. They they go and update it and like you you actually were correct about that
That's a pretty huge one guy moment just to spite the chat. That's that's more. There's an update actually queued for it
That's so funny
That's too funny
Well, they said thanks for playing the game. I mean the game's great
You should be you should be uh, very proud of what you've made. It's very fun
Give me my cards back. I like playing these. These are fun. Did I get the bonus?
I always like to I queue up the coins. I don't like doing one and then wait. I just at the arcade I go one
two
Three or bonus five bonus six bonus seven bonus, right? Then you stop see I got i'm throwing off
Where's dizzy bird? I want to play dizzy bird after this. Okay. Well, I that was I think the game was broken. That was weird
Oh, give me this
Flying around this place
Why am I larping here? What am I doing?
We
Yay
Let me put the oh
I remember watching the critical video where he just literally won this every single time
The videos that video is actually like an s video s plus first try. Let's go. How much is that 2 000 tickets?
I'll take them
You have to understand something. I watched that I watched that critical video. I can beat this every time
I think these are new. I don't remember these being here
They left and yeah, this is definitely new stuff
and I
What networking andy? I said I was a fan of critical's videos
That's not networking any that's that's recognizing a good content creator
Pinball machine drops frames. That's all right. It's fine. Oh my god. Why do those exist?
Biggest scam in the pinball industry ever is having that spot on the left and right where the ball just drops down
It's so dumb the pinball game is supposed to be about skill and what the hell is the point of those?
There's nothing fun about the left and right traps
Nothing nothing fun about
Pinball in general like I don't even know why I play it because the game it's literally why would I play pinball?
Oh, what what is this space invaders?
This is so cool. The dev of this game seriously put so much time into this
What are they like up like 60 or 70 machines now to play maybe more. I don't even know
There's a lot in this game
This is like the fourth plus I think fourth or fifth time i've played this on stream. Just keep adding stuff
I'll get it. I'll get it. I got it. All right, come on these little popcorns
What are they do mini golf? Yeah, i'll do mini golf after this. I can I forgot this
I thought this is a different day and I was under the desk with that hair
I thought that was four days ago. All right, you gotta use defense here. Oh shit. All right, I lost
Now I don't want to play this anymore get in. Uh
What do I think this is? What what? Oh, no, i'm trapped in here. I can't grab anything. What's wrong with my arms?
What let us peep the horror. Oh, i'm busy the third time i've said that today, isn't it? All right
Cool. What else is here? That's new. Ooh
Oh shit, all right. I get it. You just don't want to get it in the big ones. Okay, I say I want to spin
Hell, yeah, let's go. What do I get? Give me the whole 3000. That's all right. It's not bad. That's not bad
It's not bad. I think that one was here. These three definitely were not this shit
Not this again. I was obsessed with this now. This is the children's roulette. Yeah, I had it wrong
I'm not gonna spend time here. Don't worry. I'm out. I'll do mini golf. Should I count my tickets?
How many tickets do I have? What is the ticket counting machine? All right mini golf
Uh, i'll play 18 holes that might be way too much. Oh boy. That's probably I made a mistake nice vans
Hey, thanks the depart too. All right, let's go. It's out hole in one hole in one or I will gift 10
Dollars
Lotto or a new toy. All right hole in one right here. I will never mind. Those are the real stakes
Does anybody else not have the patience for mini golf at all?
There's nothing in this world that infuriates me more than this game because once you go over three or four strokes
You just get pissed and kind of embarrassed
Especially if your ball bounces out the play field and then you end up just dragging the ball over into the I used to
Hate mini golf. I really did
It's kind of weird because I really don't like mini golf and I don't like bowling either
I just get frustrated and annoyed and impatient bowling is sick dude. I trust me. I know I like watching good bowlers
I don't like to bowl myself. I just can't this one. You want to go on the right side? Come on, really?
That's it right there. That would have been great too hard. See right now my lips just went like this
Okay, if i'm if i'm actually in the mini golf place, my mouth just went like this that happens like my lips go
Mm-hmm go right up here
Okay
If I get a hole in one at any point during this course and i'm gonna eat a pepperoni pizza tonight
If not, then it's all salads. We're talking kale
spinach
radishes
So maybe some red onion. No, I I want a hole in one i'm gonna get a pepperoni pizza
Or have to eat a gross salad. Oh, I was gonna say it's pizza tonight
No, I don't want to eat a salad. I like salads, but I don't want one for dinner. You are so dumb
Why would I go with it?
Salad night tonight and it's looking more and more like a salad night. This is my chance
This is yeah, this is my chance right at the end right there. That'll do it
Oh, no
It doesn't want to eat vegetables golf sucks. I hate this sport so much. You know, it just it
Perplexes me it intrigues me. I don't I don't want to play this. All right, you want to have a round of golf? No
No, like can't we play frisbee?
That sounds like more fun
I don't want to play golf once you hit like 35 years old or like 30
It's almost like you're supposed to like this. I don't and it's treated so
Like oh my god, it's the best. It's so much fun. It's so incredible
I don't like I don't want to walk around and chase balls
I don't want to take like a big drive into the ball slice across it. No
It takes so long. It takes an entire day to play
It takes way too long to play and you can't play three rounds. You can't do three holes people be like
No, I want to do nine. Let's do nine. By the way, let's wake up at four o'clock in the morning
What are you doing? It's like everything I hate about the whole universe wake up wicked early
Walk around like miles and
Swing and try to hit a tiny little thing
It's like all my least favorite things in the world
I don't like anything about it anything about it. Why is your name gas can easy to remember that counts
I get pizza that counts. I get pepperoni pizza tonight. I like this a little lightning they're doing here
I don't mind golf and it's like it's so asmr
They do like golf is the original asmr
Looks like he's uh gonna be at the he's in the sandpit here
See if he can try to get his way out of that one small little swing will do it
I think why don't they just put the announcers like why is it such a big deal?
We have people that go up to bat in baseball games in stadiums full of 60 to 70 000 people screaming
Everybody's gonna be shit. Everybody's gonna be so quiet at the golf course
He's gonna swing and hit this thing
They have to swing and hit things in baseball the things that are coming at them 100 miles per hour
Imagine a stadium for golf that I actually would probably like it a little bit more
I'm not kidding if there was like a putting competition and everyone was just fucking chugging beers and like freaking out and screaming
I think that would be so entertaining. I think that'd be so funny mini golf. Why is there not a mini golf?
Stadium event. I think that would be so awesome. You need oh don't even please don't give me more ideas
Can you imagine how dumb that would be if there was like a stadium with like 40 000 people in it?
It was just a mini golf course and the mini and the course was wicked fucked up. It's crazy shit happening
Let me do baseball first and then we'll see now. I'm obviously just messing around golf is fine
I just find it to be boring. I mean we got everyone's to be quiet
Wait, somebody said viva labam did that in 2004. Did they really?
How do you remember that?
That's so funny. You're describing. Holy moly
Wait a minute. I I'm I'm very curious at this point. What is holy moly?
Holy moly show
Uh-huh. Oh everyone wants a burger mcdonald's the first big mac and after their first big mac
Oh delicious madhouse pop pop mcdonald's chicken. It's nugget. This is a real show. I can't believe this is a real show
Holy mo is it bam margera?
Welcome to holy mo. You might think i'm just another celebrity cameo at the what?
Way more involved in it. They get celebrities to do this
Maybe sit back and relax. I don't know
I thought that was a big mac for mcdonald's. I thought there was another ad playing or he was in this or something
This is holy moly
I can't believe this is real
They came in twos from across the land to do mini golf battle one-on-one the most skilled competitors on the planet
Competing on the most epic mini golf course. Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me
For glory, why do they have to do this? Why have to go up the aggro crag? What does this have to do with mini golf?
25 grand it's ninja warrior most extreme elimination challenge wipeout and golf
And yes, this is literally a mini golf competition and yes
It's on prime time with an absurd budget, but is this on tv still this is june of 2019 is this trailer?
He said no shot no shot. Hold on. Let me see. Holy moly cancelled. Let me type that holy moly
Cancelled holy moly has been renewed through a fourth season season 3 will debut june 17th
2021 still on the air. Well, never mind there goes that idea. It was a good one
I just accidentally just did that to 12 000 people. I just gave you an advertisement to go watch that show
Well, let me know how it is
All right. Hey, I got a hole in one that means I get pepperoni pizza thousand tickets. Holy
Holy, I gotta go to mcdonald's first. You need to go to mcdonald's to get yourself a quarter pounder with extra cheese
Why do you keep doing that? Oh now I want mcdonald's
Why does all advertising work?
Don't spray me. I love these little things nice right there get that rat got it. Would it land on 10 bucks?
I think I got them all
I'm all right the title. Oh the title is buying and selling organs
You're right. It's all right. I don't shoot again. Where's my mouse?
Uh, I lost my mouse
This is not good. Where'd my mouse go?
mouse
on the screen
uh
This is bad. Okay. Did I see everything in the update?
I can't get out of this
I have seen okay
I got to alt tab. All right, we're gonna go we're gonna go, uh just chatting for three minutes
I want to make this really good. That's bad. I mean we've been going for like five hours. I think we're okay
I did what I wanted to do. We're gonna just chatting for like five minutes
Because I need to have it be over five hours. So it makes it look like I streamed for five hours
Very important before anybody leaves. I know i'm saying all right, that's it. But listen here is very important
The new year's eve show is happening on new year's eve
7 30 p.m
pacific time
We're gonna do the rumble just like we did last year
We're gonna do the rumble and we're gonna do the categories. So three or four categories a match three or four categories a match
Three or four categories a match
And then do that until we get to the rumble. That is the 31st the next time I will be live on new year's eve
7 30 p.m pacific
Go vote on the poll if you want to have your vote count
It's there's a lot this 26 categories half of them are dog shit, but that's
Kind of the way it is
We have about 15 real categories and then you know, there's worse peter is on there. So good luck
And I will go uh, i'll go irl. Well, no, i'm not gonna go irl. I'm just gonna go like this for a minute
What's up? All right, my lips are like purple. I think it's a white balance. Yeah, the white balance is so off
What did I get auto for christmas?
This this little carton. It's a little milk carton and there's cookies in it
He can fish out the cookies and they're tethered to the inside of the milk carton and they squeak
This is a reddit shirt. Okay
Is uh, there's not many things that I get upset about but this is an andy mark shirt and andy mark is uh,
You do not talk about andy mark like that
How dare you?
This is an andy mark shirt. You just saw like this top part
And if you don't know andy mark is responsible for the carnival robots
And they're also responsible for putting
almost the entire
Uh dollhouse set together and all like the little uh, kind of toys and tools that went into that
But also with like a set director too. So or a set designer
They pretty much were responsible for almost that whole thing
Andy mark, we love andy mark here. We really do. Are you gonna stream any more monster rancher?
I want to stream more monster rancher, but i'm just other things come up
I did promise we would beat s rank and i'm going to adhere to that promise. I promise we will eventually
What do americans eat for christmas?
Um, it depends
ham
mashed potatoes
corned beef
a big like corned beef and cabbage
hot roast roast beef
Yeah roast beef turkey. Bring me whatever you want. Did you get any tool? Uh, cool toys for christmas
Somebody wait. Hold on. Somebody said please never do a best aaron category again. It causes me physical pain
What do you mean?
I'll take that feedback
I'll take that feedback and i'll uh process that feedback
Do you eat liver and onions liver and onions are disgusting liver is disgusting
Liver is such an incredible thing to eat. It has like the most iron your body can possibly get it's so dense and nutrients
But it is revolting. I find it to be disgusting. I don't like golf and I don't like liver
Sorry, so fuck you. I love liver
All right, i'm out
Thanks for watching. Uh organ trading space warlord organ trader was a blast
Coin game update is awesome. Both of these games go support them
But support these devs that make these awesome things please and we'll see you guys on new year's eve
I'm excited. Should be a good show
No, dizzy bird. Oh shit. It's okay. Don't worry. I play coin game the same amount that I play house flipper. I'll be back
Raid. All right, let's raid somebody. I haven't raided somebody in a while. Who should we raid? Let me see who's live
I'm gonna take a little peek. I'll take a pic
Who is alive right now? Let's see
Um, who is alive?
Go to my page here
Uh, there is there are quite a few people live right now
Uh, we just raided neanderthals last week, but she is hysterical
Let's do
Uh, oh, I never know where to go
Charlie critical. Yeah, we we I mean I did win that first try the lock game because of critical
Yeah, go say hi to critical. It's been a while. Let's see up to games and demos
Playing horror games as he's playing horror games. Is this um, laser fear?
Something scary looks interesting. All right. I'll see you guys on new year's eve. Have a great night
Go, uh, go show some love to critical. See you guys later. He's gonna go and leave and watch xqc vods
All right. Good night. I'll see you later. Have a great evening. See you new years. Thanks for the subs everybody
There were a lot of community subs, too. Thanks a lot and good night