It's Spy. Spy.
Who's that Pokemon? It's Spy.
Spy, I choose you.
No, if it was like Ash, it would be like...
Oh my god, come on, Gerudo. Go get him.
Gerudo.
No, pull back, Gerudo. You can't do it. He's too strong.
Spy, I choose you.
It's you.
Use Bakespade.
It's super effective.
Oh wow. Spy, that was fantastic. I really love you.
Who's that Pokemon?
Hey guys, I'll trade you my holographic Charizard for your holographic Shpee.
No, that's not worth it.
A holographic Shpee is worth like $500,000.
You're gonna try to rip me off right now?
There's only one in the world, but I've got the one with Japanese text.
Do you really? Do you seriously have that?
Did you guys ever like play Pokemon trading cards?
Do you seriously have that card though? Because I kind of want it with the Japanese text.
Oh my goodness, man. Are you okay?
That went right into his mouth. Dude, are you alright?
Please get me to a doctor. I'm sorry, just chill out.
I gotta pull the arrow out though. Hold on, just don't talk.
Just don't talk. Get it out of me, mate. Come on.
I'm trying to. I'm really sorry I did that.
Oh my god, fucking help. Guys, help, please.
Fucking murdered this guy.
Turbo, where are you?
Gotta get you away from the scene of the crime.
I wanna see your trophy.
Oh, he's gone. It's too bad.
It was absolutely heinous looking.
No. Was it a sniper?
Yes, it was.
Man, that took a lot to do that.
That took a lot to do that.
Alright, I found nobody.
Nobody scared the spy. I found a spy.
It's guaranteed that he's a spy.
Where are you? Just don't scare him.
He's in the wild right now. He doesn't think I know he's a spy.
I don't know where you are. He's the scout.
Don't kill him. Howie?
Oh, you're right behind him. He's right here.
He's gonna backstab you, boof.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I saw that.
I didn't know you were playing that heavy.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, I'm playing shithead Natasha Gibbous heavy.
Oh, boy.
Watch out for these shtickies.
Don't do what I was gonna do to you, you punk.
What? Why?
Who did I just kill?
I'm so confused right now from that.
Scout on the point. Scout on the point.
Scout on the point.
This will be the last time you do believe I'm on fire.
Screw to the poop. Pyro on the poop.
Peep on the poop.
I can't stay here.
Come on. Use your rainy unusual and kill that person.
See Ted.
The Ted trademark. This guy has a trademarked name.
I'll give you a trademark.
You can shove that trademark right up your ass.
Oh, Pyro. Don't do it.
All right, gentlemen. I'll be putting up a dispenser up here.
Don't worry.
Let me get this thing up here. Don't worry about that.
I'm just gonna get some stuff up here.
Barack Obama plays engineer.
So what's your favorite class, Barack?
So the thing is, let me be perfectly clear.
As the engineer, I want to give everybody a shot.
And, you know...
They're fucking spawn camping us.
I see that, yeah.
People love America. I have arms to solve your practical problems.
Actually, Barack Obama's voice kind of does fit on the engineer.
If you replace the engineer's voice with the Barack Obama lines...
How are you even back...
And you're telling me that wasn't a headshot.
I don't know what language in what world that's not headshots.
But I'll just die again for like a 50th time.
If I get an Uber, I'll give it to you.
If you give me that Uber, you're gonna be very sad.
Just gonna let you know.
If you give me that Uber, you are going to cry.
Oh, turn around. Holy crap.
Don't die.
Body shield. Sniper body shield.
Alright, you want to go meet people?
Wait, I'm gonna grab this health and that'll be it.
Alright, do you want to go like metaphorically and physically meet people?
Yes, let's do it.
Alright, we're gonna go meet the red team.
Oh, you actually have meat. Okay, let's go meet people.
Let's go meet some friends.
Alright, let's go meet this engineer and this whole team.
Meet the sniper!
Chop chop, mate.
Oh crap.
Hey, chop chop, mate.
Damn it.
Well, that's where I...
That was one of the better Ubers I've had recently.
We actually killed people that time.
We actually got a couple kills.