You see what I got a rush and get a get up there now.
Yeah, wait, so it is your so that's your fault.
But but hold on though.
But I didn't I said you good to go.
I'm going to take a shower and get set up and you said yeah,
you were awake.
Yeah, so you were you were you in like a full-on panic when you
said yeah, I was a little confused at first and then I realized
I like checked my phone and you hadn't sent me a discord
message.
So I kind of just laid in bed for a while.
Anyways, how you doing?
You sound a lot louder today.
I did adjust my mic a little bit this week because I heard that
I was low on yours and I always I don't know.
I feel like I'm low a lot of the time.
You definitely I just I turned it down.
You're in a good spot.
Good.
But yeah, hope you're doing good.
You I heard and I did see that you were playing Neo 2.
Is there any assessment you can give us I can give you an
assessment because since I talked to you about Neo last
week, I have 40 hours played and I can tell you that this
morning.
I was really excited to play Elden Ring with you and a little
bit disappointed when I realized it wasn't Neo.
Wow.
Wait a minute.
Hold on a second.
So you're this why me just mechanically speaking the combat
because Elden Ring as you said kind of is just attack with
weapon.
There's like no nuance to a lot of the stuff that you do.
Yeah, there's a lot.
I don't like about Neo the first 10 hours were like grinding
your face on a cheese grater to try and understand all of
the different words where you need to charge up.
You need to gather enough anima.
No, I still don't even know you need to gather enough
Amarita to charge up your anima to get your Yo-Kai shift
ready.
It's like nothing was designed for a human to understand.
But you've kind of grown accustomed to that and you actually
prefer it now.
I would say mechanically combat is a lot of fun and I was
even thinking in bed last night because I was like, you
know, he's going to ask me like how would I rate it like
Elden Ring is obviously it's too good.
You can't compare but then I was thinking about like the
last Dark Souls like Dark Souls 3 and trying to compare to
that and I realized is it just me or was Dark Souls 3 not
memorable at all?
I actually went back to try it again the first time in a
while and it actually I found myself saying more often than
than not going this like sucks.
I don't think it sucks, but I was like, you know how you
like think back to Elden Ring you can think of like Millennia
and the boss at the end like all the shit like even Dark
Souls 2 I have so many memories and I was like, okay,
well, what are the zones in Dark Souls 3?
Yeah, there's like the crab in the swamp is like I was
really blanking for way too long and it is a great game.
Maybe that's just like the sign that like it's out of my
memory and I could play it again, but I'm going to have
to probably do a serious reassessment of where I put
from software games because I did play some Dark Souls 3
off stream like I don't know last year at some point and
I really did it seemed like every single area.
I think like Holly was sitting next to me on the couch
and I'm just like fucking stupid like this area is fucking
dumb. A lot of the game is set up to like piss you off.
I feel like I took a little bit of a she's like, do you
first she's like, do you like this game like I thought
you liked I thought this is like one of your favorites
and I'm like, yeah, it is.
I think they blur together to like some of the areas.
I'm like was that Dark Souls 3 the like the like frozen
area with the invisible enemies.
I don't remember playing through Dark Souls 1.
I think I did it sort of in the same period.
Dark Souls 1.
I hate with a passion two or three spots in Dark Souls
1, but I think as a whole I think it is.
It's probably just better than Dark Souls 3 and I had
it wrong.
I had it flipped.
Who knows?
Anyway, dude, I could go back like a year or two from
now do it play through it again and have the completely
opposite opinion.
That's just how these games work.
I feel like around that time was over saturated with
like souls like and I played so many and by the time
Dark Souls 3 was there was like this was good.
But played so many I feel like I know what about
secure.
I feel like I'm secure.
I just completely just wiped it from my memory and
like it was good.
But like I it was it was though.
I remember it was like really really good.
It was pretty good.
This game is very loud.
Actually, I at the time I was a I was a secure non
enjoyer, but I think I've come around.
Yeah, you were a secure row non-enjoyer for a while.
I can't remember.
There's like one simple mechanics that pushed me
over the edge of like needing to farm for healing
or like just in general like you could only use your
your arm moves a certain amount of times and you
have to like collect arm oil or some shit.
Yeah, why would you gate the like fun mechanic around
like I need to farm enough resource to use this?
Yeah, it's just all these games.
You just like flip on them every like six months.
I have a different opinion of each one of these
games.
It's weird how that works.
I swear.
I promise you.
Well, the assessment is Neo 2 I'd say was better in
Dark Souls 3.
I have a lot of fun.
The level design is actually crazy good.
It has like I wish the areas were a little bit more
interesting like Dark Souls environments really can't
be beat.
Yeah, but like once you finally get over the hump of
these mechanics like do not make any sense and they're
basically non-english.
There's a lot of fun to the game.
I I'm willing to try it.
I probably don't think I'd want to scream that game.
I don't think you would I think not streaming.
It is a great call.
Okay, I have never been backseated with like such
like crazy such as just Determinated backseating.
Yes, you're not going to understand what's happening
and you're going to get frustrated because the game
has a lot of frustrating shit and you're going to
get like mad and you're going to look to chat for
like some sort of like we're in this together like
that fucking sucked and chats going to be like you
need to keep pulse more often like dude, you're so
bad like it's me.
It makes me angry.
Hey, so so can I get some support in here and you
just look over and it's just like like the people
have like the stream muted like the mute thing.
Just like oh, okay.
You're not listening.
It has like new content for like new game plus one
two three four like it has a lot of content.
So I think there's some people that have spent like
thousands of hours in the game and then they really
need you to just be better.
Okay, so let me ask you a very very important
question.
Yes, if I got over the if I got over it the first
10 hours would I like it if I kind of understood it
like you do know that what you know about I think
the parts that are thrown in your face of like the
stance switching and the key pulsing you kind of
naturally you kind of get after a while after the
first day like it kind of just I don't really even
think about it anymore.
Okay, but it's also really not as important as
people would make you think okay, because there's
tons of times on my stream where it's like I would
attack something like dude, he's never people.
When is he going to do the key pulse to get his
stamina back, but it's like they're going to die
anyway, that doesn't matter.
Like yeah, it's just like whatever.
Yeah, it's like I feel like the same thing would
happen.
I don't know random comparison slay the spire.
We're like, you know, you have lethal next turn.
So you just sort of end turn even though you could
have ended at this turn, but they can't because
you have armor hold on though.
I played slay the spire until it got too complicated
where I was like, I don't care anymore.
What once it got to be like I had to do five
different math problems in a row.
I was like, I think I'll just do something else.
I think I'll play something else think we'll play
some vampire.
I think I unlocked I love how that's an insult now.
I mean just you know, I don't really want to like
do anything after I unlocked the poison.
There was a poison character and that was really
fun.
But then the game got like really hard and I was
like, yeah, that was fun.
I like completed a few runs and I'm kind of done.
Well, that's what I mean, you know, like you can
poison the enemy and you have a they're going to
die to poison is your thing on the ground.
I don't even have a game open.
Mr.
Rush rushing to get ready.
He's not in the game.
I'm not rushing.
I thought you said you rushing.
I thought you said you like jumped up and like
panicked and were like, I got to get on there.
I got to get my stream ready.
That panic is over.
Oh, okay.
So now you just chose a while ago.
Yeah, then I realized that was an hour early like
an hour and a half early.
They you if you were really early at that point.
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
Whenever you get your sign on the game with the
mod that I did thing.
I was very prepared.
Hey, dude, it's not even two o'clock.
It's 154 right now.
Oh on time with some with some pregame and I said
this to you the buttons for dodge roll is like
switched in Neo and it's like hard switch like you
can't.
Oh, that's right.
You said hey, dude, like please like make sure
you play well today because I'm not going to even
know the buttons of Elden Ring.
That's what you said.
I'm a little concerned that I'm going to be trying
to keep all some stuff.
So I maybe I do just like get some magic and watch
you for a little bit.
Well, I think we're all right.
Our characters are pretty beefed up now.
Let's give a quick recap.
So I can do that because you've played a different
video game for like 50 straight hours since we
last talked.
So we were at the Volcano Manor.
We were rousing around doing a little bit of you
know, an investigation to see where we're going
to go next and I think we ended up saying that we
were going to do a right card, right?
That's the next plan.
That was the goal.
So to get we never found Volcano Manor.
We don't really we were kind of on our way there.
Yeah.
So we're in the vicinity and I think the last thing
that happened is you laughed audibly laughed at
the character.
That was the the mage character that you thought
was a randomized character, but it's where you
get the Comet Azur.
I think that's the last thing we did and I forget
what that is.
Is it see the water terminus?
I think I have no idea the words you're saying
Subterranean Inquisition Chamber.
Yokai shift.
I opened my way.
I where are we teleporting and then you can join
me.
We are seriously what button interacts with the
bonfire.
What why what it's why is going to be oh, no, he
doesn't even know the buttons of the game.
Okay.
Here's the thing though.
I get exactly what you were you coming from though.
It's it's just on the controller for like an
Xbox controller B and A are reversed and for the
first like two or three hours and you know, it's
like I hate this.
So I have you played a high five rush by the way.
No, okay.
A lot of people wanted me to play it.
They like stream it stream it with they don't
know is like I got game pass and I'm already in
it.
It games fucking incredible by the way, but right
bumper is dodge in that game and because I've been
playing that right bumper.
I kept trying to hit B and it just kind of doesn't
work.
So I might be in the same boat for a little while.
Okay.
We'll see how our dodging goes.
Yeah, my brain got reprogrammed game pass seriously
Xbox ever I'm ever like a few years ago during one
of those conferences when they were just talking
about this thing they wanted to do.
Let me just go over it.
I know people can say oh he loves game pass.
He's a game pass Andy Monster Hunter rise high
five rush and Goldeneye have all come out in the
last like two weeks on game pass.
That's fucking ridiculous.
That's that's actually ridiculous.
Like what that service is unbelievable.
What is there a Goldeneye like remaster or something?
Yeah, they did like a Goldeneye HD kind of remaster.
Oh, I thought I know there was like a fan version
at some point.
I never heard of this one.
I'm just I'm just saying I'm just saying it exactly
the way that I see it Xbox everyone Phil Spencer
was on that stage.
Everyone was like oh game pass.
It's gonna I resent anything I ever said negatively
about I respect anything he says because he is the
most rectangular man I have ever seen.
Is that I don't even know what that means.
He is fucking squared off.
You know what I'm saying like because of Phil Spencer
I started calling myself the cubic man because I
aspire to be as square as him.
I want like you know what they go for the measurement
of like one cubic meter of like I am one cubic
meter of man.
I am the exact measurement or well Phil Spencer is
but I want to be like him.
All right, but yeah, I mean I would say yeah my you
why are you talking about him like he's a Minecraft
character.
He is what wait my cameras stage presence dude.
He walks on stage and there's cracks in the floor.
What's wrong with my camera?
There's a gap left to close.
Oh, sorry about that.
How did you even see that what but anyways game
pass they got this cloud gaming thing and it's so
I'm telling you I would not be saying this if I
didn't fucking believe it game past is legit.
It's the real deal.
It's the real deal believe in believe it.
Can you not afford games?
No, it's just look I have this problem with video
games.
There are a lot of them.
Okay, there are a lot of video games a lot of
stuff releases indie games triple-a games.
It's like I don't fucking even know what the
hell is even I don't even know what I want to
do.
So what happens is game pass just dumps once every
couple weeks.
Sometimes it's one week.
Sometimes it's three weeks, but at least once a
month at least once or twice a month.
You like you get multiverses on that.
Holy versus is is free multiverses is already for
free.
I didn't know that.
All right.
Well, yes, you can but anyways having the option
just to have like hey, there's four or five games
that are here right now.
Open them right now.
One just play one right now and just with the
cloud shit just open it.
You don't have to install it.
You don't have to like, oh, let me go read reviews.
No, no, no.
Oh like for instance, like, oh, I don't like it's
like a shadow play.
You don't even have to download it.
You you can that's the best part.
If you open one of these up and you're like, you
know, that was actually really fun.
I like that just hit the install button to set your
save file continues.
You don't have to worry about like, oh, I got to
start over.
No, you don't.
I'm telling you I will I will be an Xbox game pass
fan here.
You can be a fan.
It's cool to like things.
Yeah, but I will say it's definitely one of those
things.
It feels like a Netflix like I can just get on there
and be like, what's on game pass today?
By the way, there's like a hundred plus other games
that just are on there permanently.
Plenty good ones.
You should be getting paid for this.
No, I don't.
I shouldn't because I just I just like it.
What we said any good ones lately any like you you
tried something on game pass.
You wouldn't have tried but you actually liked it
a lot.
Yes.
And it's not like a mobile game called like tar
pit or whatever.
Gunfire reborn.
It's pretty good.
Gunfire reborn was just on game pass just opened
it.
I was like this is kind of fun.
I played it for like at least for probably four
or five days gang and also Monster Hunter rises
on there.
I was actually kind of thinking about starting
that engine back up.
Oh Monster Hunter.
Wait, really?
I'm gonna open it.
Okay.
Fuck it.
What who cares?
There's no pressure.
Just open it.
Who's going to stop you?
Usually pressure.
Who's like, excuse me, sir.
You cannot play Monster Hunter rise today.
But Monster Hunter really he's not going to stream
it.
Oh, maybe I will.
I don't know.
All right.
Are you like have you opened the game at this
point?
Yes.
I said that I put the thing down.
You can join me.
I've just been fucking walking around the bonfire.
All right.
Let's go race the grace.
Excuse me.
Honestly and high fire high fire rush to I that
was just a surprise launch.
They were just like, oh yeah, by the way, this
game exists.
Okay, and it's here now stir-take for now.
No.
Yes.
I was reading all the reviews of high fire rush
and all of them like, can you believe this like
silent drop it's crazy.
This is silent silent drop Bethesda's like official
game conference.
They're like biggest thing that they do to like
announce all our new games.
They announced it at their biggest conference.
How is that silent?
Did you watch the Bethesda conference?
I did well silent in the way that there was no
release date and she's like, oh hey, here's like
the gameplay launch trailer and you can play it
right now.
I think that's immediate.
That's why the English language is very different
very specific.
Yeah, but that's cool though.
Okay.
Look maybe not like, oh wow, what a silent stealth
launch.
Do you think it's cool to have a gameplay trailer
like a launch trailer and they like, oh by the
way, you can download it now.
Okay.
So like if you didn't announce that you were
going to do a scream stream and one day you just
show up and you start screaming.
Is that a silent drop of a screaming stream?
Well, that depends.
Did it take me like three to four years to prepare
the scream stream?
Like how big is that?
Of course not.
So I don't think it makes no, I don't think that
works.
I hold up.
How do you run?
Fucking what?
All right, dude.
I mean, I know how to do that.
No, seriously.
How do you run?
I'm not joking.
It's B you hold B.
Okay, he's not pretending.
How do you get on the horse?
Oh, that's a little more complicated hold Y and
then you probably have a map to one up down left
or right on your d-pad.
Okay.
This is going to be a I can't believe I deleted my
entire memory of like how to play this dude.
It is gone.
Your memory.
It's gone.
I know we were going up left and there was the
lava Lake there and we were I think there's a
yeah, we we actually need to we need to go back.
I think we need to like actually wrap around here
like we're on the right side, right?
Thought it was left.
I don't think we got up left where we left off.
Can we get up here this way?
Just quietly looking at our chat.
Hey, do we get up that way?
I want to go.
So wait this one this one down here.
Do you see that dude holding a shield in front of
us?
Do you see the shield?
The big like look at the shield.
It's not finding Nemo where the straight straight
one walking straight towards him.
There's a bug.
Oh, that's a bug.
I thought that was a guy's holding a shield.
Okay, I'm want to like start this back up tomorrow.
Are you good?
You want to start this up tomorrow?
Looks like Nemo.
Oh my god, dude.
Did you get any sleep?
Tell me the truth.
I didn't know you he didn't get any sleep.
There's a all right.
How about this?
This is what we're going to do.
We're just going to chill out.
All right.
We're going to just chill out for a little while.
We're going to like just relax.
We'll play for like we'll play for like a few hours
and no, no, no, I'm good.
It'll just take a second.
Trust and follow me.
Oh, no, I don't know about this.
I don't know about this.
I know where I'm going.
I have memory.
I just don't like my muscle memory of buttons is off.
We need to go to Primeval Sorcerer Azure.
I don't want you to I would okay.
I would not be following you right now.
No way.
I'm not going to follow the sleep deprived guy.
That's like, yeah, let's walk.
Let's walk through the fire on the ground.
Yeah, we killed the thing.
We killed a boss.
You're the Mariner.
No, we got to go to the sorcerer person's body.
No, no, no on the other side.
Come with me.
Oh, no, no, you're following me.
I'm leading.
I'm the commander.
You don't have authority here.
Okay.
You were the sub.
So here's what's gonna happen here.
This path we were going to go.
Do you drink coffee, bro?
Like do you drink coffee?
No, you don't.
I don't.
It doesn't even drink coffee.
I like what do you drink tea?
Time we get you like a nice green tea brew.
I take caffeine pills.
No, you don't.
What?
No, you don't take caffeine pills.
You don't take those.
Jerma like an old man.
I literally have in front of me a Monday to Sunday pill holder
and there are caffeine pills one for each day.
All right, but hold on a minute.
We need to do we need to do a little maybe we shouldn't do
this assessment on broadcast.
That's fine.
Okay.
How many milligrams of caffeine are in each one of those?
200.
Okay.
But I've heard the it does not feel like 200.
Like the like digesting it like that.
It's like if you don't take it on an empty stomach, then you
don't get like a full powered.
All right.
But you don't like you don't you don't you just don't like
the taste of coffee or like the way or like tea or anything
like that you have tried to get me to drink coffee before
like you ordered me your like favorite drink at Duncan.
Yeah, like one time in Boston.
You fucking hated it.
I did I hated it.
I've tried a lot of different coffee.
It's all just like it's all just why did you guys burn
the shit out of this?
Okay, so we I think we're guys up here.
We are going the absolute wrong way.
I'm just right.
But you got to watch out because they like they have more
stamina than a yokai around.
There's you look in a dead sleep and you like ripped
yourself out of bed to come over here and talk about how
you like eat caffeine pills every day.
The block was different too.
I'm just randomly jumping people watching my stream.
Like I entered combat attacked jumped back stepped like
I don't know what's going on.
All right.
Hey listen to me.
I want you to open up your menu and I want you to go to
Prime Evil Sorcerer Azure.
That's why we're going this way.
Okay, but in a minute we're gonna we're gonna go to donkey
let him cook.
Are you sure about that?
I don't know about that.
Let me cook.
What the fuck I mean if I die before you do that's gonna
be embarrassing.
I could be you.
What like right now?
Yeah, what you were gonna give me an assessment.
Okay, my assessment is so is that the only caffeine you're
taking in a day?
Yeah.
All right.
That's okay.
But there are some teas and there are some you can like
there are like drinks you can drink that aren't just like
200 milligrams of just caffeine.
They got like vitamins and like hydration and shit if you
really want to.
I have I have matcha tea this morning.
Okay, green tea.
All right, big fan.
I used to make it myself, but then I got lazy.
Well, that's exactly what I was just going to tell you to
do.
Yeah, I would do I would drink a few matches a day rather
than take you a day.
You know how much caffeine is in a macho not 200.
Are we like 40?
I'm telling you the 200 is fake.
Let me take it's not real.
It is 200 but like I'm saying like it's not it's not real.
It's not true.
It's not real.
I will rest here.
We did a full circle also if I literally take one sip of
like a five-hour energy.
Hmm.
That's what happened on myriad day.
I won a little sip of five-hour energy like like 1 20th
of a bottle.
It it fucks me up and I'm like wired and can't sleep for
a day or two where we're going.
Yeah, I I don't I one of the reasons why I can't drink
stuff like Red Bull really or five-hour energy or pretty
much anything that has the like just caffeine in it.
We are going the wrong way.
I yeah, but it's okay.
It's all right.
No, we've already been we did a full circle.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no trust trust cook.
They say cook keep cooking.
All right.
Well, then the other one that's at the stove.
Let's go.
Okay.
So everyone's like, what's the Duncan order?
What's the Duncan order?
Is this what I know we've been this way because we fought
a fucking great putrid slob up here.
We did and we're just going the long way back and around
in a complete circle to that sorcerer who is up here and
we could afford it there.
But you were at stove and I just kind of let you go.
I was serious thousand souls.
I feel like I should spend these.
All right.
We'll spend your souls.
We have we have switched personalities like for real.
All right.
So now we have to go like around this way like around here.
That's correct, right?
We go like around this right side.
That's correct.
I will follow you anywhere we go like, yeah, we want to
go like around let him bake.
Baking does take longer baking takes a little longer.
That's right.
Well, you want to go down into the fucking heroes grave.
We could the worst Dungeons and Elden ring.
Wait, is this the one that with the lava and the chariot?
I think this is actually yeah, this might be like one
of the worst most painful Dungeons in the game.
Yep.
I don't want to do it.
You're really going to nope out.
No, I think this is the worst Dungeon in Elden ring.
It's absolutely this is the worst Dungeon in the whole
game.
I think what with me randomly jumping and backstepping.
I think we can I think we can do it.
I think the last 15 minutes of this stream starting has
proven to me personally that we should not walk down
this hallway.
What if the chariots are randomized and like we don't
even have to worry about them.
All right, let's do it.
That actually that was enough for me to say.
Yeah, let's do it.
People watching my perspective seriously take note
of how many times I jump.
I have not done it on purpose once.
Oh, I thought you were just doing the thing where you
like jump around Ironforge.
No, every time I jump.
I think I'm running.
I think I'm doing something else and if I ever do this
sword, I think I'm blocking.
So what you're saying is now you have a great excuse
when you go back to Neo 2 after playing this for a
while, you can do like a 30 to 40 minute complaint
stream in the first 40 minutes of that stream talking
about how you relearned these abilities.
It's genius citizens.
Oh, all penis.
No, it's not there.
Okay, by the Duncan order.
It's a it's a large blueberry iced coffee with only
a few sugars.
Wait, wait yours.
You were gonna you said you were going to assess me
and your assessment of me was telling me to drink tea.
That was it.
That was I just want to go back for a second.
My assessment would be to tell you to stop taking caffeine
pills.
Okay, but what if I stop and then I like don't feel good
because I haven't taken one.
Well, okay, can they be can they be like cut in half?
Yeah.
All right, so I'm gonna have these before.
Yeah, so do that for a while and do then cut that in
half and then once you get used to like that 50 ish
milligrams, I think you're good.
Just drinking tea, man.
You don't got to do you don't gonna be caffeine pills
or watch out.
Oh, yeah, I forgot why did we come down here?
I don't know.
You want to be said it was gonna be randomized.
Oh fuck.
Do you not gonna make it you're gonna get fucking squished
to get on the way back.
How do I heal?
It's X.
How do I how do I equip it?
What do you mean down on the d-pad?
I'm jumping.
All right, you have fucking me up so bad.
You have no idea.
Did you just run you over again?
No, I don't want to lose my Amarita.
Are you down here?
I'm coming.
Yeah, you freaked me out so bad.
I didn't know what to do.
Yeah, because you were like freaking out and you were
all like you were like caffeinated and ran down here.
Okay.
I think you're weird that you drink more than one coffee
a day.
Coffee to me.
I'm not gonna lecture you in front of like all your fans
who are gonna like back you up and make me feel like.
Look what you've done.
We're good.
Okay.
Where are you trying to remember how to heal?
Okay, where do we go?
We're gonna go this way.
I think I don't you can go all the I went all the way down.
You can go down further and there's like cool items and
shit.
But I don't like we really care walk in the lava.
Yeah, I think if there's like a spot you can go down there.
Let's just go this way.
Is the chariot not one shot anymore?
I don't know.
Maybe we're supposed to be I do remember killing like I'm
surprised we live through one.
Yeah, that is weird.
But anyways.
Drinking coffee for me is this is kind of wow.
It is an important stone.
Coffee is more of a thing to kind of dip and relax within.
What is it?
I've never played a game worse on stream.
Every time I went to block.
I just drank an elixir.
I drank like three blasts to fight a rat when my health was
full.
So you really weren't kidding when you were like, hey, dude,
I really don't knock under the buttons help.
It's worse than I thought.
Wow.
I have like a good talent.
I'll say normally a talent for absolutely discarding any
information the moment I just like not useful.
Like I just started out during it's in the fucking recycle
bin.
That is really interesting.
That's how loud a little loud.
Why is it so loud?
Wasn't like this before.
All right.
But yeah, why is it so loud?
Okay, that's better.
Yeah, coffee.
I drink coffee not necessarily for the caffeine.
I like just kind of like sipping on something just like
a hot beverage.
You're like, oh, yeah, that's nice.
But most days it's whiskey.
That I'll be honest.
That's like another reason like oh whiskey.
Oh, I'm just gonna like that.
Whiskey.
I'm gonna drink it about loud.
What that did it that was I was a pretty loud for you.
Usually they're not that loud.
Really?
They hit me weird worse.
No, it that is.
Yeah, hit me weird.
You're farming for worse noise again.
I am actually like in real life did like Sonic damage to me.
Okay, you're fucking me up so bad.
I've drank more flasks in this dungeon that I have like the
entire time of playing Elden Ring.
Did you know you could do that?
Yeah, he didn't.
What now?
Dude, I don't remember.
Watch out the fire.
Oh, it's my little fire away.
Okay, watch out chariot.
I think we can we can follow this one up.
I think we wanted to but I don't know.
I'm afraid that's my fight the boss.
Okay, I'm gonna die.
Oh, that's not where that is.
Let's just leave.
Are you dying too?
Okay.
Yeah, let's let's fucking let's go.
I thought that you know that level where the this you can
go inside and there's like the two little places on either
side of the chariot that are down and you go in and I thought
it was right there.
Yeah, let's get the fuck out of here.
Like immediately it was the right place, but it was the
wrong side.
Oh shit, whatever.
But yeah coffee is more of a sipping thing just like this.
This is like hydration.
I just like I got to move my hands around.
I relate to the move your hands around but not the put it
in my mouth part.
Well, the thing is it's really good that I and like I know
that like obviously like cigarettes are one of those things
a lot of people go like yeah, I just always I kind of wanted
to have something just like in my hand and like something
to do with my hand and whatever and I'm so glad that I
never ever ever thought to try cigarettes because I probably
would one of those be one of those people that was like,
oh, yeah, I just needed to have it in my hand just something
to do.
I'm glad I never fucking ever thought to ever do it.
You gonna kill this crowd?
What are you doing over there?
It's worse than I'm self-aware.
It's like the self-consciousness of what I'm doing is making
it work.
I'm giving myself a headache.
You sure those are caffeine pills?
Something else?
I just cast bops barrier like six times and tried to cast
a face thing with my staff like for this thing is actually
kind of hard.
We need to be careful.
He's taking mystery pills.
I got it.
All right.
Hey, all right.
It's all right.
Here's what we're going to do.
You just go.
I got I got it.
You know, what's probably better?
I got a suggestion for you.
I am trying to keep home.
What if you went into and change the key vines to make it
just Neo 2?
No, you sure?
I'm sure that's not a good idea.
That's actually a really good idea because then you don't
even have to think about it.
Run is the same button.
Jump is the same button.
Swing is the same button and that thing is actually pretty
good.
Isn't it?
I don't I don't I don't know.
This sounds dangerous.
What do you mean?
Oh changing.
I don't know why but it sounds dangerous and I kind of want
to overcome it.
This is like the getting over it that kind of game.
Well, there's a time for you to do it.
It's definitely right now.
Okay.
So now make sure we're going the right way.
I wish I could see the freaking map.
You just I'm going to see I need you to lead for a bit.
Now we take a left back you up.
There's a boss up here.
Isn't it?
Let's go.
There might be an item up here.
Can you handle climbing this ladder?
We'll see you want me to go first.
I would like for you to go first.
We're all good.
Part of it was hoping that you were going to get sniped.
I am good.
Like if we go into a boss fight and you die, I am going to
try harder than I've ever tried of the game to like beat it
anyway.
Just just so I can be the winner.
That's fine.
It's a good thing.
That's good.
So I may be completely incompetent, but I have the like
the burning desire and that usually works for anime.
Oh, okay.
Keep going.
Let's do a race.
Wait ready?
Hold on.
We didn't do it.
You're going to win any race because I'm going to jump
instead of run.
That's better jump.
It'll be funny jump.
I almost just did it.
I was thinking it was weird.
My whole body was like I'm going to do it.
Kill yourself.
I was like, I'm going to jump off that for no reason.
Watch out that I thought he was going to walk off.
No, I'm here to game.
Are you going to stacking bonus for the amount of things
that you kill before returning to the shrine and praying?
So I like don't want to get hit.
Is that oh, that's a as a neo reference shout out.
I'm just going to brace the jumping.
Are we going uphill?
Excuse me.
I'm walking in my we have gone around like we need to turn
way to go like on the road.
I know.
I got an epic.
Did you epic?
Hold on.
I've got something that you are going to want to take a look
at.
I got the staff that I used a lot of the game.
It's really sick.
I don't I have every staff in the game and one spell.
I have gravity pole or whatever.
But this one is the one that makes your spells cast way
faster.
This is the Azores glint stone staff.
It reduces the casting it.
All right.
Yeah, you can climb that tower and throw it off.
It's like just javelin it over the edge.
Yep.
All right.
There's a boss up here.
Yeah, are you prepared?
Hell, well all the way over the top is normally the
meteorite meteor man and for us, it's going to be redone
now.
It actually would be really bad if it was like Eldon Beast
if it okay if Eldon Beast is in the middle of this.
I'm going to wait.
You're just going to go to bed.
I'm going to go to bed.
No, I'm you're going to die and I'm going to focus so hard
and you're going to see me jump and cast stops barrier at
nothing.
But I'm still going to beat it.
Okay, it's going to be you.
Oh my god, please don't say that.
Are you prepared?
Huh?
I'm keep holding it.
It's rough.
I'm sorry.
All right.
I'll get over saying it soon.
You're supposed to dodge roll in this game.
Okay, you know when you were asking me about Neo, I think
this is actually the best comparison.
Your first couple hours are going to be like this.
I'm dead.
I just saw you jump over that that actually helped you
you jumped over it.
You didn't dodge it.
Oh, I've got him now.
Oh my god.
We are so don't die.
This is so fucking far away, dude.
I can't die.
Got him.
Holy shit.
This is so far away.
Sorry.
I looked over your chat stir not even helping the chimera
is dead.
Yeah, well you took you have like a legend next to your
computer of like all the buttons written down while I
was dodging and attacking and fighting and he was kicking
the shit out of me and you looked at your legend of moves
you could do and then like 15 to 30 seconds later you
decided to help I kept there was a giant great wolf those
wolves die in one hit.
No, that's one of the big wolves.
It took a lot of hits.
Are you climbing you coming back?
I don't think you understand how far away I am.
I am at the Gellmer's hero grave.
That's the last bonfire we got.
Oh, I thought there was a bonfire right here.
Did you get it?
Because I didn't get it.
May just be up the hill a bit.
I know there's like a midway point.
All right, I'll be good.
Okay, you'd better be good.
I'm on my way this time.
I'm just going to get right over there.
No stopping at the maps.
Yeah, that's I don't know that I think that might be a
little much for stir right now.
We'll get this one at least and wait.
I've never played Elden ring.
Can I get a spoiler warning?
Oh shit.
Yep.
Stir will write it on history.
What does that mean?
Someone was wanted a spoiler warning because they haven't
played this part and I said that you would just put it
on yours.
Okay, that's on mine.
My stream has the there's the twitch plug-in where anything
that you haven't seen before in a game is covered with
like a black box.
That's so stupid.
Oh, the spoiler extension.
Oh, hey, welcome back.
I'm back good of you to show up and finally start helping.
I know.
All right.
So we just got to get her.
I think there's a bonfire somewhere over here.
I just finished making a cardboard cut out of you and
watches me when I sleep.
That's not strange at all.
I thought there was like another ladder here.
You should jump you thought I was going to it's the last
thing they would expect.
All right, so we got it.
Let's go over this down here.
All right.
Well, I think we keep going on the ladders right the ladder
right here.
Right here.
I know.
I know, but I think I think there's a bonfire though.
I knew where to go.
No, it's up here.
You're wrong.
I knew where to go with those coffee.
Drank is kicking in.
I swear this one like right here.
Yeah, I think it we are going to go up one more.
Oh, this is just ladder zone.
I like it.
You need to help your friend.
My friend.
What I said you need to help your friend.
I'm beyond helping you need to help him.
No.
All right.
Watch out.
I think we yeah, we go.
I can do it.
I think you're all right.
I think you just maybe were a little nervous that you had
to relearn and get the game.
Everything seems fine.
Do you have some enemies special enemies got some
Herba do you need any Herba is already something like
shooting this from a mile away.
Oh the flower beware.
I thought that was actually like falling stars in the sky
and I was like, oh, that's that's a cool environmental
effect.
I should grab me.
I thought I could hit it.
You're so dead.
You're I thought you were getting pelted by everything
kind of was but I'm all right.
We fighting this.
Oh, I mean no, but that's destructible.
This thing is that these things are so annoying.
I say no.
Just get the heck out of here across the bridge and then
there's a bonfire right here.
Yes, there is and then we fight whatever is up here.
All right.
Let's both take a guess and if one of us gets this right
then we all the other one 50 bucks.
It's kind of weird that you like booted up your game early
just to see what was up here pretend.
You don't have any of these graces for $50.
Yeah, I'm gonna all right.
I'm gonna say it's gonna be we haven't.
I'm just saying I've said for Don I don't think it would
be it would be in the lore for him to be inside the crater
probability wise.
We have not seen really that many ulcerated tree spirits
and there's like 10 in the game.
So I'm going to say an ulcerated tree spirit statistically
speaking.
That's where I have the most odds.
It's oh that way that could have an urge tree avatar full
grown or tree avatar though.
Yeah, this is a safe bet to this in the ulcerated tree spirits.
We've only seen like two of these.
I know a lot of hell.
Oh shit.
I tried to dodge that didn't time it right.
That was weird.
That was really weird.
I did not appreciate it.
You know that you you dodge faster if you're in low stance.
What the fuck did I just get?
Yeah, I got a I got a weapon blue feathered branch sword.
I've never seen this item.
Are you going to take a look at this?
That's pretty rare.
Well, you thought he was drinking a flask?
His staff on my screen went like behind his body.
So it just looks like he put his hand to his empty head.
I was like he's drinking.
God damn it.
I don't want him to heal.
That would be so funny if they could do that.
All right.
Hold on a minute.
What did I just get?
I got like a weird rare key thing.
Is it a weapon?
I think I got a pot.
Was that actually a sword?
What the hell was there?
It's a talisman.
Raises defense when HP is low.
And then the other one was a talisman too, wasn't it?
What the hell was that other thing?
Did I get this thing?
I think we're in the fire zone though.
I think I'm all right with this.
Omen burn.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's a key though.
I don't even know what that thing does.
All right, cool.
I know that we're looking for like smithing stone fives.
It's my my breakpoint.
Hey.
Just want to let you know what take a look what's on the ground.
No, seven.
I do smithing seven on the ground.
Yeah.
No, I need sevens.
Oh, I thought I was helping you and have those back.
No, let's go.
Are we going?
How do we get to Volcano Manor?
All right.
Now we continue this way.
We have to go over like here.
Oh, yeah, there's like a walkway over here.
It's not it's like over here.
Old needle gravity stone fans.
Oh, yeah.
So you said you do not care at all about about magic anything,
right?
I would like some magic to cast potentially because I have a
couple of talismans that you probably want to have smithing
stone sevens.
Maybe I do.
I feel like you looked a bunch of times last dream and didn't
take a look on the ground.
Oh shit.
Who's your who's your favorite friend?
I see you.
Okay.
Yep.
No, no one else has given me smithing stone sevens, dude.
You just got frenzy flamed by the three fingers.
You just got fucking three fingered bro.
No, that's an e3 fucking presentation.
This is the e3 co-op presentation.
Dude, you got three frenzy fingered by the three fingers.
Whatever the fuck you said that was the e3 presentation.
You watch out you're gonna get frenzied by the three fingers.
You're just trying to distract from the fact that I don't know
any of the buttons and you've died more times.
Yeah, but I have to like help you.
I have to like guide somebody is lagging the game by the way.
Somebody there's like DDoS.
No, there's another one of those like look over here and the
game goes to 10 FPS creatures like a like a look at me.
Yeah, there's a look at me.
All right.
Let's are you are we going?
Are we wait?
I'm not the one who got three fingered.
You being like delirious tired is making me delirious tired
and I had a full night's sleep.
I had like avocado tacos.
I had like a nice coffee.
I have a foot fully hydrated.
I'm fully well rested.
You're turning me sleep-deprived.
I wish I had a knob that I could turn and just become sleepy
or like, you know, like a mood controller.
I wish I was a robot.
You know, I'd sell my soul to Ubisoft and they could plug me
in, you know, how just how amazing that would actually be
if you could truly control just like, you know what?
It's time for me to go to bed.
I can like go up into my internal like hard drive up here
and be like turn off and turn back on actually every terrible
what if like it was like an emergency yourself.
Yeah, I need a quick reboot guys.
Yeah, my like Wi-Fi is off.
I could go for some like mind control slash like invasion
of privacy like give up all my data type of situation
if it meant that I could be sleepy when I want to.
It's an avocado taco.
It's just a taco.
Like I would take the risk that the communists could totally
like activate me at any time as a soldier if it meant that
I could like control my my being.
It's like I know the communists.
All right.
Isn't it one of these illusory wall eventually all the way
down at the end here.
You have to go in one of the rooms because you can't even
I think we have to talk first.
We have to like say, yes, we're here.
Well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
this is the guy upstairs who drops the thing if we could go
kill the guy and see if he drops on Elsa.
I don't know if you want to do that.
I like this outfit.
You got to join the manor.
All right.
So we join the manor.
She gave me two golden seeds.
Join the manor.
I'm having twins.
And a bell bearing.
Nice.
All right.
And then we go upstairs.
Yeah.
And there is that person to fight.
It goes
just like Bloodborne.
You get invaded.
Oh, Amidala or whatever.
He says, you know,
Oh, Amidala, have mercy on the poor boy.
Of course, for some reason.
Have mercy on the poor bastard.
I think that's what it is.
Why this?
This guy has like 10 million health.
What is going on?
It has a lot of health.
No, it's being healed.
Oh, because he seems to have the beast magic.
There's a beast heal.
I'm just seriously jumping everything.
Magic.
Beast magic.
Can't hit me.
I'm a jumper now.
Why is my stamina going down when I keep hold?
I've helped.
You're not helping.
All the help that's been taken off in the last 15 straight
seconds has been me, not you.
I'm doubting that.
Oh, dude, look at that.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm going to use it.
Ready?
Oh, you're good.
Oh, you're going to want to take a look at this.
Yes.
You just clean yourself with soap.
Yeah.
First shower in months.
Okay.
So now we wait a minute.
Don't get mad.
I was very excited.
Okay.
So the door should be open technically now, right?
One second.
No.
Oh, this one is.
Do you have to come back?
No, you got to, you know, yeah.
We do.
I think we have to reload the area.
Oh, you might be right.
You didn't get the drawing room key.
We don't have the key to get in here.
Oh, right.
She does give a key.
Oh, yeah.
So we don't have it.
So now what?
That's a good question.
I know there's multiple ways to get in there.
There's a different week.
I think we can go like around here.
Let's get the map.
I think we can go around the whole thing.
Take the teleporter at the bottom of Ray Lucaria.
We did that.
Yeah, we did that.
But were we supposed to go a different way from there?
Yeah, we got we got killed at the bottom and we we have a
teleporter down there.
Is it safe to drop down here?
No.
Oh, I want to do it so bad.
I'm just so lazy.
It's too far.
I was testing it.
That was a good test.
I'll wait.
Ready?
Be careful.
I am ready.
But that's how it went for you every time too, right?
I can't remember.
Give Bloodborne on PC with a new DLC and a bunch of new weapons.
Oh, that's so that's one of the so-called fall jokes.
Interesting.
Are you studying my stream?
Why are you studying me?
Well, apparently you're interesting.
There's a replacement German every now and again.
Interesting writing notes.
Okay, so I gotta go a long way.
Fine.
You still haven't killed any of these invisible dung beetles.
I haven't.
I haven't killed any of them.
This one is so easy.
Isn't it?
Let's get it because it could be something cool.
Well, you're you're lingering flame.
You put on the ground.
You could just like put that in the path.
That's a good idea.
Where is it going around you coming down here?
You missed.
Oh, it's just like impossible is like one pixel.
Oh, that's why you do it.
That's why you do it.
I just got the black knife.
I've had that you're lame.
I got Elden ring the Elden boss remembrance.
You've got the Elden beast remembrance.
Yeah.
Ooh, see it was worth it.
Now if we didn't do that you what's worth it.
See you can also jump across the volcano Manor interior from
the place you get teleported to if you do a running jump.
Really?
Let's see what happens when we go this way.
What's going on?
I got another smithing stone 7.
Oh, yeah, I can get big pluses.
Give it to me.
Give it to me now.
Drop it.
There's no opportunity to do that.
We're trying to get the map piece.
You're trying.
I know what the map looks like already.
No, you don't.
I've got fucking IGN calm open.
I drop it.
There's there's a boss down here.
There is it was patched.
Oh, I should let me wait a minute.
Hold on this 35,000 souls on the ground.
I think over here that I yeah, I'll be right back.
Yeah, that adds up because we killed that boss.
Yeah, where the fuck is it?
Is it where I fell?
It's kind of strange that you left without giving me the
smithing stone.
I'll be right back.
I feel like that's kind of selfish and you're showing
a side of yourself.
I didn't know existed and I don't like it.
We'll fucking deal with it.
How's that sound?
Yeah, I'm glad people finally got a glimpse of what you're
really like during the Christmas stream.
No, you're being recorded.
Where are these?
Where are they?
Oh, yeah, that would have been awful.
That's 35,000 souls.
There's a lot.
I'll come back.
I will drop the stone.
Well, then we have to we got to travel.
We have to move.
Into where I can Smith.
Okay, we can get that.
I need my smithing.
Okay.
Here is the do you have any somber smithing stone?
Eights by chance.
I believe I do actually if you like something I recall having
in my inventory.
Let me one briefly moment.
Take a yonder look over into my sombers.
I have an eight.
Dude, then here we go.
This is fucking perfect.
I discard.
Wait, which was which one?
Okay, I'll just you know, we just picked them both up.
All right.
I'm putting mine over here.
Okay, I can go to plus nine now.
So now we're going to be unstoppable.
We are going to be genuinely unstoppable.
Now, let's go Smith.
Where is there is actually fucking insane true.
I don't think so.
Oh, cuz you want to be like the insane guy.
I'm taking like street cut away from you.
I was saying to my child, I don't even remember what I was
saying that you're like, I don't know.
You're trying to I don't know.
There's a conspiracy where you're trying to poison me, but
it backfired because it made me weirder like you want it
to be weird.
I don't know.
Are you talking about?
There's a conspiracy that I poisoned you.
Yeah, what's oh explain this conspiracy there that I poisoned
you last time we played Elden Ring.
You're like damn stirs like kind of funny.
Like I feel like I'm losing some cred to him.
When we're like co-op.
Oh, I thought you meant like there was a point in the last
like decade that we've known each other or I just trying
to poison you.
Oh, okay.
No, just last week.
Yeah, just last week when I hold on a minute.
I got I'm almost a plus 10 with this thing.
This thing is beefy now.
Do you have any of the ancient dragon smithing stones?
Some of the ones you actually have one of those.
Yeah, I'm plus 25 on my sword.
They would give me that somber ancient dragon smithing
stone.
I will be plus 10.
Mine's mine's a hollow here.
What are you giving me?
Better not be a staff.
Hello.
Thank you.
Yeah, I treated you would know that has sentimental value.
It does me strong just traded you his club.
That's something that that's that's a trinket.
That's worth isn't isn't a club.
Just a staff plus 10.
Let's go.
I mean, that's something that that holds incredible like
generational sentimental family value and I just let I just
gave it to you.
It's wrong.
Club.
Okay, where we're going get back to where we were.
There's a boss there.
Yes, I don't remember the name of it.
It was I was up here.
It was the ninth Mount Gelmere campsite.
You sure I think it's the road of let's let's get this
right because if we can't get in there with the key,
what is the best way for us to get there because we can't
go to the manor because it's randomized.
So we can't open the door.
So how the fuck do we do this go to Seathwater terminus?
That's there that has that that has that has to be it.
And also, I don't know.
Apparently, we have to go through Ray Lucaria.
We cannot get there any other way.
We did that.
So we should have the way points from down there.
So we did that.
So let's get back down there.
Wherever that is was it subterranean inquisition Chamber
should be this pre-recorded.
Why would it?
Why would it be you managed to stir?
If I was like, hey dude, like I don't really feel like
streaming tomorrow, but like let's like scream for like
seven hours right now, like pretend and then I'll just
upload it tomorrow.
I thought about doing that a few times never done it.
Something about it's funny to me that I could be sitting
there watching my own stream and like laughing and
enjoying my stream with everyone else.
You got a stream on an alt channel of me watching my
stream reacting to my stream.
I guess we have to jump from here from the teleport.
Are you going to do a jungle gym stream?
Who said hello?
Oh, I don't people look like that's people.
Okay, I have no idea who that was.
Wow, that's a diss.
You don't know who that was.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
I feel bad.
Wait, I wasn't even paying attention plate again.
I can't it's random.
Hello.
That was not the same person that just did that.
Exactly.
That's what I mean.
You don't get a redo.
Okay, so we're not in the right spot.
I think we have to get to where we get to ported to and
then jump from where we get ported to.
Well, that was further up.
Have you played this before?
Yeah, but I've like had the key to open the door to the
manor not jumping from a weird port and breaking all of
my characters.
Okay, like legs and then I lose all my souls.
I haven't played this before and I don't know game is
like enemy placements are like really weird.
Okay.
So where do where's that spot that we are at when we
teleport here from Ray Lucario?
That's where we need to go and we need to jump from a
spot there to get into the manor which is cheating by
the way.
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
I am I am with it.
So where is it?
I am we have to actually get eat.
We have to get eaten again.
We may have to get eaten again people have keep saying
patched, but we don't really have very many options.
Do we why did they patch everything fun in this game?
Oh true wielding jumping attack and patched so bleed
patched.
So if it is patched then can we just not do right card
and we just have to just keep going ignore them.
We're going we go again.
Okay, so we have to go do that Ray Lucario skip again.
Yeah, sure.
So that we have to go die down there again, which I'm
going to lose 22,000 souls by the way.
23,000 souls.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to how much is it to level up?
You're a baller.
That's nothing to you.
I don't want to lose them.
I have a briefcase full of money.
I'm not just going to like open it up and dump it on like
the fucking just side of the road.
This is like, oh, yeah, dude.
I'm a baller.
I don't care.
Just like yeah, ban out like a million bucks on the fucking
road.
I think they're also saying patches gives you something
but I think that item would be randomized use a twig.
Oh, I do have those.
That's a good idea.
Where are those things?
Oh, it's a talisman, right?
Okay.
I'm ready to do whatever you want to do.
Let's go.
Are we in combat?
No, it says I'm in combat.
Oh, it does.
Well, then we're going.
Are we doing Ray of Lucario?
We have to do that and then we go to the schoolhouse classroom.
This is such bullshit.
Like why didn't they like think to make the game like completely
accessible to people that are like breaking it and like using
like fucking mods and cheats on it to ruin the whole thing
and like randomize everything like they didn't they didn't
think about that before they made the game is that bug where
you like block a few times and backstep and teleport across
the whole map is that still in I don't know.
It was a speedrun that could beat this game in like two or
three minutes right because of that.
I don't know if it was that fast, but they did get pretty
it was pretty damn fast.
It was like less than five minutes.
I think eventually no.
Yes.
No.
Yes, no one.
I mean if that's still in and we can't jump across a ledge
and that's all I'm saying.
That's all I'm saying.
I got to say somebody I was watching you play Neo for a
little bit the first time you played it and I already said
this on my stream, but I have to say it because it was on
your stream.
Somebody had an amazing comment on your stream.
You were trying to learn the game and you haven't like
trouble and you like all the buttons were so hard to
remember and just get to getting used to it and somebody
wrote dude.
Don't worry.
Once you get the buttons down.
You're going to make it rain on this guy like a boss.
They said like everything that you had said the other day in
one sentence.
It was like one paragraph.
It was I like loved it.
It was like my favorite comment.
You don't worry.
Once you learn the buttons, you're going to make it rain
on this guy and then like a boss.
You'll take down the next enemy.
It was just like perfectly crafted.
All right.
That is how it happened.
So we're going back down.
Shut up.
Once I learned the buttons this game.
I'm going to do it too.
You coming are you I'm coming down right now.
I'm coming down right now.
I was killing the hand just go just going down a lot of
ladders and elevators today.
Okay.
So is it still work?
We just die down here, right?
Yep.
Just die.
Okay.
Hey, you pretty good at that.
Actually.
Hold on.
Let me pick up that item.
I never got.
Oh, right here.
Right here.
This guy sucks.
Why is it always like this?
Yeah, these things murder you if you fight them.
Yeah.
If you actually play the game fight them minus 26 K.
Nope.
I put on the talisman.
Okay.
So there's a place we have to jump from here.
Like over there.
I remember I remember you spawning in different location
over here.
I think it's over here.
Is it this?
Yeah, I think it's this way.
We make this I feel like I would with the horse.
It's a bit further ahead.
Oh, no, we're gonna no, no, no, no, we're about to just jump
off and die.
I believe I know what they're talking about.
But I just remembered you spawning in this area in a
different spot in mod chat.
Wait, the mod mods playing game form again.
I mean they had the helping it is over there.
Yeah, it is that spot and we have to do it from.
Oh man.
Okay, hold on.
We got to do it from like back over here.
Where's that from?
Like right here.
This shit out of the way.
Wait, what is it?
It's right here, right?
Right there.
It is patched.
Several people are saying it's patched.
Wait, that's not it.
Is that it?
Yes, it is.
So it's like right here.
Fuck my souls.
That was close.
Oh, you respawn here.
Spawn right here.
I think what about like from here?
Got it patched.
Okay, we're good.
It's that there's a little lip that you have to land on.
Yeah, it's tricky.
There's like a little extra a little bit to the right.
You're a little extra on the top one or the bottom one.
So do you okay where you are right now?
You see what that little that rock Juts out just a little like
a hair extra.
That's where you want to jump from.
You're better than me.
It was not it was I got it in the right spot.
It's actually really tricky.
You have to do that thing.
Like, okay, imagine you're playing Legend of Zelda, you know,
in Legend of Zelda it jumped for you at the last possible
frame never played any of them.
Hold on closer closer.
Yeah, it's that I've got this next one.
It's almost you have to step off of the platform.
Yeah a little and get that last hair that last you got a
wind walk on the Wind Waker.
There's an earth tree avatar over here and it's messing.
Okay.
I be careful.
I don't want to have to do this again, dude.
This is actually really bad.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is there a bonfire right here?
Because if I just get the bonfire, can't you just port
to it?
No, no, you can't I hit it.
That was very very close, but you got to land on this
like edge.
I have to I have to land on the other side.
Oh, I didn't I thought I was going to the lava.
No, no, you took what?
What do you see where I'm standing?
Okay.
No, now that I know that wait, you thought you were jumping
into the lava.
What if I take off your equipment?
Maybe this this is a I got to tell you this is not even
the hard part.
Really?
No, because we have to get by a like one foot hallway
where an archery avatar is just sitting there and it's
like we're going to fall off.
Maybe they patched it on your game.
Yeah, because I'm the host.
Oh, wait.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So like not the lava like where do I land?
You want to land on the rock where I am?
Okay.
Oh, that was it right there.
I was on it for a second.
Use his controller.
I we can't do that bro.
Can you take the controller?
I can't do that bro.
Take it bro.
All right, just easy.
Okay, I got it.
It let me hold on as yet and you're like not even you got
wasn't connected when you did it earlier.
I wasn't connected though.
You didn't even jump at all.
I wasn't even connected.
Hold on.
Can you plug me in?
Yeah, that's Wi-Fi.
Okay, that's the wireless.
Something there's something wrong something wrong with
your controller.
Okay, give it back.
Give it back here.
Just take it back.
I have a fucking headache now.
Thanks.
You control your your your B buttons like sticky.
I don't know what the fuck you're eating.
It's different.
It's different in Neo fucking headache.
No, I fucking hate it.
We're going to be here all day VOD viewers.
You can't skip.
Yeah, dude, you should disable disable timeline skipping
on this VOD.
Oh, you have to do it at a 30 FPS because if you jump in
Dark Souls at a high frame rate, it doesn't work magic.
You could do that.
That's that's a real Dark Souls.
No, no, no.
I mean like make it so people cannot like skip through
your VODs timeline.
Now you have to watch.
Sorry.
You have to sit here for this like 20 minutes.
I got it.
Are you serious?
That's very close.
Do you see where you okay to on your left?
It is a piece that juts out a little bit further.
You want to land on that like little piece that's jutted
out a little further.
It's like very very nuanced.
Yeah, you got to go a little more to the left.
This one's for all the fucking Wolf Boys in chat.
Okay.
All right.
Don't seem to care about them really at all after that.
This one goes out to all my scaly brethren.
Okay.
I missed I'm getting worse.
All right.
I'm going to stand where you should be.
I have so many debuffs.
I'm concerned that even if I make it I will die because
I have like no health.
Whoa, okay.
Never.
I don't care.
Just do it.
I was going to stand.
Okay, you need to land like here.
Okay, I'm aiming.
Okay, no stay there.
No, because you're not going to be able to land on it.
I think that's it.
Wow, you guys really stand on it.
This is kind of embarrassing.
He really must hate those skillies.
Oh, I don't yeah, I don't he's fucking take a while.
That's all right.
I'll be here when you guys are ready.
Hey, big fan of you two.
Can I get in here?
I'll switch friend code by any chance.
Is this your lizard voice?
Are you mocking lizards?
No, it's all good man.
Well, no, it's good.
Keep trying.
No, me and the urge ray avatar are hanging out and having
a conversation.
Hey see your way out of it next one.
I have it next one.
I have it 100%.
I feel like I just connected the dots.
You're going to come down there and help could you maybe
you could I'm just kidding.
I'm gonna kill you.
God damn it guys.
He's so bored.
He's doing fits.
I'm fucking up everything.
I was pretty like aggro him down here.
Oh, you made it.
All right.
Good luck because now this is the hard part.
I actually have so many debuffs.
I have no health.
You are guaranteed to die.
I'm just telling you right now.
Don't be upset.
Hope you got that down because there's no way you're getting
by this.
What did you just do?
I use the rune arc.
It didn't do anything.
All right.
We have to go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
back up, back up, back up, back up.
Where are we going?
Where's the correct path from here?
We can get on the rooftop to the left.
I don't like where are we go to the left or up?
Where's the way to get a bonfire quick left?
It's one for all the Wolfman out there.
That's okay.
You got this jump first try.
They were just like bugs in my clothing.
There was so many bugs.
Fucking God damn it.
Now we're going to sit here for like another 10 minutes while
I do this.
I did it first try.
Dude, my stamina bar is like the size of my right here.
It's like right there.
I have to get it in less and I have to get in less than five
tries so I can prove that I am better than you at this.
Okay, there was no doubt about it.
But I think also you left your souls.
I'm so angry at you.
This is your fault.
This is your fault that that happened.
I didn't in three tries.
I'm better than you.
Let's go left.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to jump off again to prove that I can do it
in three.
Wait, no, you don't do that.
All right.
I have no idea what we're doing here.
We need to be careful because the firing lasers over here.
What's that?
This way we jump from here.
Okay.
I guess we're all right.
Don't die.
We're in we just have to find the right bonfire.
Why am I mad that I killed the pot?
Oh, it's all right.
Oh, there's a dog.
There's a dog.
You don't want to get the item over here.
I jumped across a weird way.
There's dogs growling on me.
Oh God, he gonna get me.
No, no, no.
I'm good.
I can't lock onto him.
Just I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Just focus.
Got him.
I do no damage because all my curses.
Okay, we don't go up.
I thought you did that.
Oh, no.
What are you doing?
Shoot a fucking beam at him or something, dude.
What the hell?
I don't do any damage.
I'm out of magic.
My magic bar is like a centimeter.
All right.
We how we can't get up there.
No, not one more fucking Craig.
All right.
There's an elevator.
We tell you we want to take an elevator up currently.
I know there's an item over there, but I'm telling you it's not
worth it.
We need an elevator.
Elevator is across the lava.
I think over here this way.
We have to go.
Where do we go?
Oh shit.
Go on the rooftops.
I'm dead.
Oh, no.
Go left then elevator up the lava just slows you mostly.
If you have to quickstep you can make it walk on the lava, please.
I can't I don't I don't have enough health if we have to walk
across the lava.
You actually don't I seriously have like a centimeter of a health
bar.
So all right.
So you talk about like down here walk like in that way a walk
like down this way down like there.
You mean right left need to hide here because I cast this bullshit.
You're going to have no health bar.
I think we should leave.
Yeah, but we like we're so close.
So what about like you come up this way like over there?
Well, can you just do it and then get a vote to teleport like
this?
Yeah, I think you jump in between that area and then you turn
you go right not well, we're going for it now not like this.
Yeah, flash.
I think you can still make it.
I think you missed it.
Where where where you got to go back around around this octagon
into the hole into the gap to the right in here to the right
right now where oh now what all right.
Oh my god, just don't die.
Where's the bonfire from here?
I forget it's like I told you the wrong way.
It's okay.
That's like a joke.
Oh, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
Then there's the thing you go up.
She says you died.
All right.
Yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup,
yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
Is anyone's cat like looking?
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
Is that like a cat?
I don't know.
You just make weird noises.
That's not a typical like come here cat noise.
So I noticed that my wife Ashley she always talks to her dog
exactly the same way as the rest of her family.
They like, you know, there's like a dog speak where you like
change your tone of voice.
You know, yes.
So I was like you like exactly like your sister exactly like
you all talk to your dog the same way.
I was like, that's kind of weird.
And she was like, oh, that's not weird.
That's just like we're a family.
So I was like, oh, well, you there's like plenty of ways
you could talk to your dog.
And let me give you an example.
Our dog's name is mouse and I just got really weird and slowly
started hovering down to it going a mouse cute dog.
And she got so fucking scared and like was panicking to get
away from me.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I don't.
Apparently you need the fucking like psycho.
You need to like do we like anime or whatever voice?
Yeah, how's that anime voice?
It's I don't know.
Everything is like a little like a few pitches higher.
I would say that's more Muppets than anime.
That's more like Sesame Street than anime.
Do you like sesame seeds?
Yeah.
All right.
They don't have any flavor and they get stuck in your teeth.
The bridge is up.
So that is complete.
Now we just go this way and I think we can open up this back
door here, right?
And then this is here.
It doesn't open from this side.
It's okay.
This whole thing was for nothing.
We have to beat this boss in here.
Find a different bonfire.
Okay.
All right, please pray to the randomizer gods.
That you just keep dying that in here is like mad soldier 2.
I'm almost there.
Can I like peek in here and see who it is?
Oh, is that the boss?
Oh, yeah, and they would glitch that door.
See the bro.
It's bad soldier.
I think it's mad soldier 2.
This is huge.
I think that's just a shitty enemy.
Isn't it?
I think that's a mad soldier 2.
I think wait a minute.
No, it's not.
Who is that?
Do I have binoculars?
No, I don't want to die.
Got to do it eventually.
Everybody dies once.
Is it blade from Mortal Kombat?
All right.
So but I think there's a just go go go.
Is it Gideon?
I'm just going who is it?
It's blade.
I think it's millennia.
It runs over did the runs over the runs over the runs over.
What the fuck we're not going to do.
I'm not going to wait.
There's no it's impossible.
It's you got to be not going to have a face to you got it.
Wait.
Yes, she is.
Yeah, she is that half health as long as you're good at the game.
You can win.
I haven't played against millennia in a long ass time and I have a lot
flawless just watch out for when she swings the sword.
A lot of people thought millennia don't know the sword hurts swords
where the damage comes.
I have like no stamina.
It was the sword.
It's the fact that it's the fact that I have fucking like half of my
HP and half of my stamina bar and it's millennia and I hate this motherfucker.
Yeah.
Well, I can't take one take of lava damage and I'm back here.
I'm in hell.
Okay.
So here's the plan.
I can't believe millennia.
I really hope there's no face to all right.
So here's what we're going to do.
Follow me ready.
I can't take any.
All right, but me raising the bridge.
Jerma Jerma.
Look at this.
Okay, we have to leave.
We have to leave.
We can't stay here.
We have to we have to leave.
Does anybody have a solution?
You can get to it from the rooftops.
Okay.
Let's see if I can fuck did why why are we here?
Just to suffer.
I think I should we just go to the Altus Plateau.
There's so many different things we could do go through the caves.
There's a bonfire over there you bozo.
I mean, it's I don't remember where all this stuff is.
Is a grace in the town.
I'm going to I'm going to save us.
Okay, I promise.
I'm going to rescue us.
You know what you should just sit down at a bonfire.
I just didn't okay.
I'm going to save us.
It's going to be all up to me.
Your health bar is going to look like mine.
It's not great already.
All right.
Nice and watch this the ledge master.
There's a gargoyle following you.
But oh fuck you guy.
He he that was very impressive.
I don't know why he's still here.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to find us a bonfire.
Ah, stop calm down.
Okay in on this.
I think this one in this town somewhere hanging out like in here.
You're right up the ladder.
Hold on.
Let me just be smart about this.
Are you watching?
I'm the best I can.
I'm so nervous.
I don't know what that was, but it was big whatever it was.
It was a huge where it looks like the Great Wolf from the classroom.
Okay.
Well, this ladder is the ladder somewhere right here somewhere.
Where's the ladder?
I don't see it.
I'm looking for a ladder.
Fuck.
Where's this ladder?
Help me.
Somebody help where it was right there.
I don't know.
I don't know where it is.
Dude.
I where is this a ladder?
Where is this fucking ladder?
It's next to the gunpowder enemy.
You're just panicking.
That's a giant dog.
I got us.
I got us somewhere.
I'm going to rescue us.
Just relax.
All right.
Where is this fucking ladder?
I'm so mad at this game.
I hate this game.
Don't you fucking kidding me?
Yeah, Neo 2 has to as a co-op.
Why is that dog down there?
It's not fair.
What would the developers thinking putting that there?
What a dog in the lava?
Dude, I actually don't have health.
If I all right.
It's one tick and get I'm getting some conflicted info that even
if I use the ladder the doors locked that I'm going to get to that
correct.
Am I being trolled right now by 600 million people?
I pressed it but that is correct.
Okay.
I don't think we can physically do this area unless we kill
millennia.
I believe that's true because I know even speedruns would kill
that boss and they want to not fight that boss.
So if there were a way around it, they'd probably do it.
Okay, this time I'm going to wait for you to do nowadays.
We just like like can we even warp out and just get some hit
points?
I'm going to try this one more shot here.
I was so excited to play Elden Ring today.
We're okay.
I'm taking so much more damage for tick.
Okay.
So before I run in here, there's a ladder on the right.
You don't even fuck you.
You came over here because you knew I was going to be here.
Now you sit there looking at me.
That's bullshit.
Do you know it?
It's up the road.
I am up the road.
You see look at the clip that doesn't do anything and just
waits for the protagonist to come back to like initiate a
new conversation.
It's okay.
Hold on.
Yeah, it looks like the great wall.
Okay.
Yeah, I see it.
But okay, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's behind the big gargoyle thing.
Okay.
I know where it is.
No, but can I even get there without getting attacked?
Oh my God.
Please don't kill me.
This is kind of fucking impossible when that dog is there
and so much shit.
Okay.
I banished you which clears the debuffs.
Oh, that's smart.
So we can like, I don't know if you want to we can try on
our own.
If one of us gets to the Millennia we can fight Millennia.
Oh, that's actually wait.
What did I just get ported to?
Why am I here?
We have to get killed at the karya gate again.
Oh you do.
I first tried the jump.
I'm going.
All right.
Well, let's see if you can get there in the meantime.
I'm going to relax.
I hear that.
There's a dog.
There is and it's awful.
You don't need to you can just go to the place.
We cannot get the key.
None of the doors open.
This entire zone is closed off.
I think we have to kill Millennia.
One of us does.
You can skip Millennia, but it's hard.
But your drink sounds like a Minecraft skeleton.
Go through Volcano Manor normally.
I that's not possible.
I don't know where I am up the ladder.
On the normal exit.
I'm going to set up the ladder.
You can jump to the right onto a ledge and then open the door
from the inside.
Okay.
Let me see if I can do this.
I am I'm cooking.
I'm cooking.
Did you get the ladder?
I found I went all the way around a bloodhound steps.
I just dashed the lava like way way away to the back and I
found one of the elevators.
Okay.
Do you have a bonfire?
I got hit out of the elevator by the one enemy that's in this
area.
So you didn't make it.
I'm I'm currently in the process of making it.
Okay.
Well, just you focus don't even talk to me.
Just do it.
I made it.
I know where I am.
Okay, so you made it up the ladder and you made it up to
the place we need where we need to be.
Yes, join me.
I don't appreciate you making fun of me.
Say less.
Oh, it gave me all the debuffs again.
Once I opened up my world.
It did it did so maybe I should close it.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on.
I'm just going to try and find a bonfire find a bonfire.
That's the most important thing.
All these motherfuckers just waiting for me.
Whatever.
I was gonna wait for you to do it and then I go up this
elevator the dog.
Just wait, you know, I'm gonna just lose the dog is going
to kill you.
I went a different way.
I skipped the dog.
I did dog skip.
Oh you did dog really?
I'm at the gate to Millennia.
Okay, so just be on the lookout for a bonfire and just
sit on it when you get there.
Can you still do the bridge jump?
I said you can but it's really really hard bridge jump
is not as hard.
I remember when they patched it and then I also remember
people still doing it the same day.
But it did look very hard.
How did you do dog skip and you didn't climb up the
ladder?
I went all the way to left through the lava.
I bloodhound steps through all the lava didn't go through
the town.
I was gonna kill all these motherfuckers.
I'm gonna kill the dog come fight me over here.
Do I hear a bonfire?
What is shooting me through the fucking wall, dude?
That was so stupid.
Why did I do that?
This is the worst place to fight this fucking boss.
This is such a shitty place to do this.
He's like
he's just fucked up.
Oh no, that's the bug.
Why did I jump down?
Because I don't know.
I was just like too lazy to I'm so done with this area.
I just I'm just waiting to skip over Worcester is the dog
enemy does that thing where they jump in the air and they
just like leap across the whole game and he's just doing
that in random spots where there's like no way to go.
I'm killing this dog.
I'm killing this dog right now.
I'm clearing this entire zone and then me and this stupid
ass dog are gonna have a fight.
I think I'm near a grave, but I can't remember exactly
where it is.
I'm scared.
I'm stuck now.
I think it's like in here to the left.
Somebody shoot me from arrows of across the whole game.
It's almost like this is completely random.
Who would have thought?
I could just equip my ninjitsu.
I run fast.
Fuck this.
Fuck albanerk throwing fucking Krillin's Destructo disc.
Yo, I know there's one down here.
I'm so glad you're as upset as I am.
I'm just so lost.
I feel like I've walked past like three bonfires.
Get up here.
I'm not fucking around right now.
I did it.
I got a great.
No.
Okay, I'm opening my world to you.
It is super incredibly super laggy here because there's
another bird with her head in the ceiling.
And I just imagine all the birds are girls.
I don't know if that's like a problem.
I don't know if like that's something I need to take back.
I'm so fucking mad right now.
Jerma Jerma you just got exercised Jerma.
I am joining your world right now.
Okay, I'm concerned because there's been a couple times
in recent history where you like don't hear anything I say.
All right.
Here I am.
What's up?
Oh, thank goodness.
You have no idea guys.
Welcome back from Elden Ring gameplay me and that dog down
there.
I've got a bone to pick with that dog.
I'm just saying I we need to go kill that dog at some point.
I think I open the shortcut to the dog to our right.
Oh, this is so bad.
Yeah.
What if something's here right to our left?
There's a that bird has its head in the ceiling.
Okay, please go away.
All right.
So all right, that was fun.
Oh dude, he's three-fingered of the frenzied flag to you.
Did you see that?
That's really cool that you would take my joke.
Yep.
Yeah, I think if you really want to kill the dog, it's the
shortcut door what they were saying to climb the ladder,
but this door was closed.
This is the ladder.
And this is the ladder and this was locked.
Yeah, dogs down there.
So I was doing that for pretty much no reason.
I would have had to go around the whole thing.
Oh man, no, then you come in here.
Do you want to fight the dog?
Do you not care?
Do you like killing dogs?
I'm going to give the dog a name.
That's Ralphie.
Oh, that's cool.
No, I like Ralphie.
All right, let's go.
Yeah, Ralphie just like he was protecting his area.
But now that like he knows you he like warmed up to you.
It's left this way other way.
Oh, that's a cool dog is Ralphie.
Yeah, talk like it.
Yes.
I love that character now.
I don't even I have no problem with that character at all.
Now this guy's name is Craig and he's a fucking tax auditor.
What?
Wait, who when you're fighting right now?
No, the guy you just killed.
Oh guy.
I killed his Krillin wannabe Krillin.
Yeah from Dragon Ball Z.
No, this is barf drinker.
He was throwing the light disks.
I've never seen an albino do it.
I don't know why he's doing it.
Destructo disk.
So this character's name is where did you go up the stairs?
Okay, this character.
This is it.
This is glow blob and Snaily and their best friends and they
are doing come up with a better backstory.
Not cool.
What did it be really epic?
No, I thought this guy's a statue.
What would be epic if I could take my hat off and use it like
a shield?
That would be pretty cool.
Oh, I got lightning Ram.
Careful careful.
I ran this whole way.
You did you need a better backstory for that hat stir.
Yeah, I don't know why this is a foggy because it's one of
those keys.
Oh the kiss me keys.
Wait, why can I not attack what a coherent array of enemies?
Oh my god, I'm gonna fucking die.
Guy has like a super sword.
You just hear a car horn.
I think it was somebody blowing a horn up here.
I thought like I heard like a truck on the highway.
So there is an item in here, but I don't know it was worth using
the key but none of these gargoyles are worth using keys
on because I got the painting.
I got the dragon scale blade.
That sounds pretty cool.
Yeah, I don't I don't remember that item.
Okay, so millennia I guess is the plan.
I am millennia blade of Micola.
Now that's not good.
Just kind of came you look like you came out of the actual
stone from the wall.
He's not doing anything.
He's got a lot of health.
I don't it's not worth it for the fucking bin beast bones.
We're gonna get for killing this guy.
Coward.
Okay.
I actually I don't I don't like this.
I'm dead.
I was there was a wizard behind me.
I don't know where he came from because we cleared everything
but I turned around and there was a wizard isn't that much
health but don't think it's worth it.
But here I am.
Nonetheless.
Oh, it's this one.
Oh, never mind.
I don't want to fight this fucking thing.
This is the other this is the second one when there's a
little lightning moves.
Dying.
Uh-huh.
Don't die.
Just don't do it.
Okay, just say no.
All right.
I'm not going to die.
I'm dead.
I mean, it's kind of not.
I don't know.
Why did we fight him?
You were so you wanted to fight him so bad.
I didn't know there was a wizard.
He is a wizard.
I'm holding this deep off because I was coming back to
help.
Oh god damn it.
The fucking big turkey thing is back and everything lags.
Yeah, and then and then you rest it.
That's real cool.
You would you would rest.
I just this place sucks.
You're fighting a turkey alone.
I have to kill this thing like I just do right.
Yeah.
Okay, it's dead.
All right.
I have I don't it's I have not burned into my short-term
memory where to go at all in this fucking goddamn maze
of a place up the stairs.
And then you're basically there being gate kept.
He's going after Ralphie.
Don't say that.
All right, let's move.
All right, squat up.
We don't want to get three-fingered.
I went right by my head, dude.
Please watch where you're casting your spells.
I didn't mean to press that.
I don't know what I pressed.
I just turned to you and looked and all of my eyebrows
were gone.
Like Mike.
I just turned and looked as excuse me.
It was right by my face.
Oh shit.
He's back.
I forgot.
All right, just leave just leave don't even fight it.
Okay.
Oh, I know it's annoying from downtown.
I was trying to lose him up and you can't be serious.
I refuse to die from that.
I don't know when he's going to cast this thing and it's like
I can hear it.
It's like fucking sizzling like bacon in a pan.
It's like and then it happens.
I don't know if there's a closer rest, but that's millennia.
All right.
Hopefully it's just a phase one.
Hopefully it's just a phase mom.
It's just phase one.
Then we should be all right and you very famously beat millennia
without a problem at all.
So I'm leaving this up to you.
You'll be my mimic tear except worse.
I'm so slow.
I still have the debuff.
Oh this thing.
I'm dead, dude.
I forgot she could do that.
Yeah, I really haven't seen her moveset in a hot minute.
It is just for Neo.
I would have fucking rolled her.
I hope this is the phase two then we're in a lot of trouble.
It actually might be impossible to dodge it in this room.
I have a new strategy.
Here's the strategy.
You hear me loading a new strap.
We get there.
We don't have a debuff because I was like, I don't know.
I had like a move speed debuff.
So all my rolls were like slowed behind the pillar when she
winds up with that actually stop her from attacking him.
She could get stuck on him.
Yeah on kill the lag bird.
There's got to be a closer bonfire.
It might not be.
I think lifting up the bridge is like the way to do a short
cut here.
Just do a kite around the pillar.
Yeah, I was thinking just DPS.
I was thinking just just R1 R1 R1 because she staggers.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's fucking Barry.
He's blocked it.
Or whatever his name was Barry.
Clamula.
I don't know.
I didn't give them names.
You killed them before I could.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It was named it was like slimy or something.
I don't know the elevator cage will get back here faster, but
we're not going to have to worry about it because we're going
to finish it right now is the strategy is seriously just like
one try millennia right now.
I kind of think it has to be because last try doesn't count
and people think it counts and that's kind of weird.
But like we had debuffs and it didn't count if there is just
a phase one that would be huge, but I don't think it is.
You've never even seen this boss before.
What is it?
What did that to me?
What way he's coming?
He's got.
Oh my God.
He is that was such a horrible feeling.
He's been that close the whole time and we didn't even
we were just nonchalantly just kind of running.
All right.
Come on.
Let's do it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait saying
The this is faster apparently and we don't have to worry about that fucking horse guy
Is it faster though? Get in here. Is there a bonfire down there? Oh, it's there get in here. Get in get in
There I mean, I'm this is down. Oh
Yeah, oh, I know what they mean. We would go down by the dog and then run up here
Because we open the shortcut by the ladder
Okay, then you run up around this way and you avoid
It's still pretty not it's still pretty it's comparable
Back by the bridge. All right. Well, let's do it. I just win just win. Aren't you like big into parries?
Yeah, you want me to parry her? No, I know you're gonna start and you're gonna be mad because I told you to do it
You'd be like you told me to parry and I haven't practiced
Get these benches out of the way so we can actually when she goes in the air just hide behind a pillar
We just use the pillars regardless just hide behind them. Why'd you tell me to parry? That's what I'm saying. That's a don't
What the fuck?
You good
She went for the grab to grab you and she grabbed like the side of my ear and fucking skewered me
I hate this boss so much. I think on a good day. I wouldn't be worried. It's not a good day. I
Want to block everything she's doing and you're not allowed to block in this game
I'm just so paranoid that she's gonna do the stupid water dance. It's gonna one-shot us. So I'm just playing so timidly and
Then she grabs you by my ear and just picks me up and sticks the sword through my stomach
It's only one phase though
Out this way and then we have to go I forget
Boogers just came out of my nose
Boogie boogers just like shot out of my nose because it's like this is we're picking to go this way
Deliberately and I don't know why because this is gonna be way worse than the other way
This is wrong. Look at how much worse this is. It's just Ralphie. I
Just don't know where to go. Why did you go this way? Why did you go this weird-ass way?
Which way you supposed to go?
wait
Well, I don't know you decided I didn't want to come this way I was like, oh, I don't think we should do this
Oh up this way. I don't want my dog. He's a nice dog. He just doesn't know you
Actually, this might be better. I don't like the synchronized elevator. Yeah, that's gonna mess us up at some point. I think I
Spent like four hours fighting millennia at least
This is this is like a thing. I don't ever want to see again
I think I actually said after I beat millennia see in the regular game
I was like, yeah, I'm never doing this ever again
I would beat the whole area cuz like that that Halleke tree area is pretty cool
But before getting to this fog gate, I would just leave on any other playthrough
Well, it's not any other playthrough
It's the playthrough. It was way more than four hours. It was like 14
No, it was not
Yeah, I don't even know what buttons
The strategy good strategy careful get back. She's gonna go in the air. She's gonna go in the air. I had behind a pillar
Nice. Nice. Just keep doing wait. She's gonna go up here. She's up. She's up
She's gonna come for you. She doesn't give a shit. It kind of works. It kind of works
Not doing it again. Are you how many fucking times do you do that? It works though? It works. You just can't get close. I
Just can't even drink out of my fucking flask. I
Hate this boss so much just delete it from the fucking whole game. It works. It works
I mean, I thought we were gonna fight her you were hiding most of the fight because and I survived but then
She did that thing where oh you have you taken some damage, bro. Don't worry. I ain't gonna let you do shit
I'm just gonna be like right like right behind you the whole time and I'm gonna be swinging like every you know, one two
Three four one two don't you can't drink in this game. No, of course you're fighting millennia
Like just fuck just just turn around and run around just run away
We have the debuff. Did you sit down?
Do we think so when we both die? We don't get one. Oh, okay. I think we have no we don't
Fucking one guy. I hate millennia's entire move set. Oh my god. I've already wasted flasks
Reset it's a skill issue. I don't care. I don't care. Fuck that boss. I
Despise this boss. I hate this boss with a burning passion
It's the worst boss they've ever made. It's worse than better chaos. Come on. You hit me with that
All right, we're in worse than better chaos, dude. You okay?
We're winning you're gonna fight her and we're gonna win me and better chaos like smoke a blunt together and hang out and shit
Like me millennia. No, don't call me. I don't want to hang out. She can call me
Okay, let's do this, please
Nightmare blunt rotation
Whatever you're gonna fight her dude, I'm waiting for the opportunity you why did you jump?
Mode I'm on block her attacks and jump. All right, listen when she does the dance thing. Don't go too close to the pillar
It's just enough to like like keep it right here. Oh
No, oh no, the solution the solution's over. Oh, no
She was in the right spot. Can you play your own game and take your own advice next time dude? She was
Excuse me. What's happening here?
She from where she killed you she kept doing that move across the whole map
She did it backwards
It doesn't work. It does but it's you got to get it right her attack has that
Spot in the middle where it the circle has to be right in the middle of the pillar
I don't think we have to kill this bird if we go the other way. Maybe all right, maybe call me crazy
Let's just let's just attack her and just don't even let her do any moves
Dude I can't like this fucking way such asshole. It's do we just jump down into a rave
See what I was doing my only only jump attacks, right?
I
Rock to run around the pillars and just wait for you to do something. Can you scoot up a little I feel like I'm gonna fall
Okay
Jump attacks only I'm thinking and just try to get the stagger and then one of us does the attack
Let me put on that thing though. Where is it?
Okay, try to get the stagger. Don't even think about it. It's not even think just just going it kind of worked
God, dude
What the fuck working? It's working
That's mommy time. It's working
lagging
Like oh don't say that now
lagging I
Why did I do that? What the fuck was I thinking? I could have jumped. Why did I do the fire move?
I wanted to be so flashy for no fucking reason. I don't know why you would use the fire move. I
Just figured I had an opportunity. I had isn't you could you got it. You got it
You got it. You're like that guy that killed millennia like 30,000 times that what the let me solo her
It's just channel that energy. You can do it. Okay, we strayed from the plan. I needed to run
I needed to just go into light stance and start running and get the better dodge
We had the strategy and it worked. I have a question
We took her down to half health with jump attacks and she didn't get staggered once what's going on?
Oh, you mean like neat like on the knee stagger. Just like boom. How come we can't get it?
Oh, yeah, and you have to parry her three times to get like an actual Barry
You oh, yeah, like yeah
Fuck that. I love going this way. You actually do and it's like it's annoying. I
like running
Nothing attacking you and just like watching your health bar
It actually works out sometimes though. I'm glad you expected me to be right behind you. I looked behind me
Without even turning my head. Okay. I am
millennia killer blade of Micaela killer
Let's just go I kill her
To do it when she goes up in the air. We are full sprinting to the other side of the Coliseum
Okay
Watch that stamina burn. Yeah people she cheated that was cheating. Oh
No
Whatever happened to run across the game. I mean we were both in the middle of attacks. It's fine
I've seen you do this once I
Never saw it actually
Watch out for the sword
brilliant brilliant
You did it twice in a fucking row that move is such horse shit twice in a row two times in a row two two
We have it. I feel like um, you know before when I called the jump before I made the jump
I feel it in my soul. This is the one you know, I'm saying that was bullshit
No, I want anybody and don't even talk about it. We don't even do that patience. Keep hitting her
You know, she when she's gonna go up we just run
I got distracted because she got she went down on her knees and she was like, please please kill me and like I
Couldn't say no, but now I know better. She didn't do that move twice in a row. I beat her I
Was in the zone. It's cuz we missed the stab
I thought you were gonna get the stab and then she was up too quick. Yeah, it's too quick
But like this time get a safe distance before you heal
Well, the problem is when she does that move twice in a row
She covers so much ground that even you just don't know what moves coming next
So you think about what what does she have in her arsenal and she just did that move?
So in your brain you go that's not happening a second time
She's gonna do something else
But if it happens twice in a row it throws off your brain and it's just like that's not good
I was nice you never expect the same move to happen twice in a row. You always like oh, yeah
I just dodged that so what's the next one? Let's go. Let's go
Jump jump on her
How did I jump all the way around her?
Good good. Good. Be careful though. I
Don't have enough 30 run. She's behind filler. Keep her there
Stop making funny references careful
You're probably gonna go up
staggered staggered
She could end this right now if she goes up. So just be very careful. Let's just play like a coward. Seriously
I
Know what I know she was gonna do it
There's some advice for you
Holy shit. You got him. You got him. All right. All right. All right. All right
We did it what? Oh
It's the second phase. Oh
No
What there's a cutscene how come how come how come oh
She's up
It's gonna happen
Yeah, she got me. It's fine. You can do this as long as she doesn't do I kill you
I've got fucking rot in two seconds, dude. I
Already have it there's over with rot too. No, no fucking way. This is literally fucking impossible in this room
Runs over runs over that pause. That's the only boss so far that has actually like regained health and gone to a phase two
Oh we can use
We can use spirit summons. No, you want to just like ding-a-ling-ling-ling and bring up
You will you will lose all respect from everyone who ever respected its randomizer. That doesn't matter
Dude, I'm telling you I think I think we ding-a-ling two teachers in here and we just fucking destroyer
I mean, that's your call if you want a ding-a-ling. I
Love how we spent so we spent the last two hours straight. I'm trying to get here
But we don't even have to do this this is optional
Yeah, we could probably do it. How much do you care go again? Okay?
We had we just weren't like mentally prepared for a phase two
We actually were not our mental crack the moment. She like teleported into the sky. It's very true
Phase one's easy as long as we like respect the you die
Millennia is a horseshit. You need you should just ding-a-ling this
You need you should just ding-a-ling this you should both use the boys so you get 20 people in the room that actually really funny
Fucking millennia, of course, you knew she was gonna show up at some point
It's just this is a really bad room for her to be in
Alright, what room would you have liked her to be in something that has?
a hundred percent more area to run around in
Alright, let's do it. Oh my god. I just fucking hate this piece of shit so much
I fucking hate this boss so much. I hate this place. I hate this boss
Okay, then your call like we can run away. We can come back later
We can get plus 50 swords
um
We're trying to like this. Let's go play truth or dare
All right, let's come on. I'm doing it like this. I feel like looking at it from a different perspective. It's a good idea
I'm gonna play upside down
Dog got me dog got me
God
All right, this is the last attempt and we're just going out splato
Okay, it's so close to hitting you
You're too slow
your host
I meant the guy who tried to scare me
I'm gonna save my dingulings for phase two
Smart. Oh, that's not good. She's coming for me. I'm dead
Like we're hitting their same amount and before she was staggering
So i'm kind of like expecting the stagger before she goes sicko mode and we're not getting it
I need you to there's no way I can do this alone
Although
Okay, kill it kill yourself. Hold on unless you feel the vibe literally. I need one more
Okay
I need one more. I need it
This is the last one no matter what as long as we're careful when she's at the the doomsday threshold
What am I sipping?
This is a green tea
Uh drink powder. I like it a lot
It's yummy
It's got a little bit of caffeine to give you a little bit. It's tasty
It's good
I read that. Um, the green tea the powder comes from like they grind up goblins
I'm gonna fucking die to this
I'm fucking gonna die
Goblins, uh
I don't think that's how it happened. I think it's
Hold on. What is it?
It's a tea leaf
They grind that up. Have you ever seen someone do it?
Yeah, actually
Like the actual leaf
I yes, i've seen it
Okay, first person to get first person to get hit by milania. What was the other person 20 bucks?
Why do you just keep like trying to financially ruin me?
I'm just saying
Well, that's gonna make you play like a little baby boy. We gotta get fucking in there
Get her
You owe me 20
I'm trying to lighten the mood man. The mood is light
Light her up
There's a lot of damage. I'm in the camera. I'm expecting it. Yep
She snuck around
It's okay. Sorry. She snuck around it
I don't go up again. I feel like she's going up again. I can I can see it in her eyes
You're just paranoid
Oh my god, you're making me scared and I don't think she's gonna do it again
Just do single hits right now like single jumps and back up
Until she shows her her true side
her fucking sicko mode
red-haired
Is she doing it? Nope. She's probably about to
Every time I jump in she jumps away
It's if it's happening. It's gonna happen very soon
Can't see what where'd she go?
This is between two pillars
Always keep a pillar between you and her
Here comes
I knew the moment I jumped on her that she was gonna do it
And I immediately started running and it was still too slow. Hey, let me cook for a minute
Okay, I thought it was I thought I could drink. I thought it was over. I thought the combo was over
my problem with milania is just
Knowing when you're just so scared of one of her moves that it's almost like a combo will happen and you'll go
Don't fucking do it. She's gonna do the water dance thing. Everyone is freak out and then it doesn't happen. But then it does
Undercooked learn to dodge that move. I know that this technically like a two frame window
to go like
I don't know it and it's gonna take a fucking a million years to figure to get that correct
You're supposed to dodge through it, but there's a window you can dodge through it
But if you want to dodge through it, you better have it right because you're gonna die if you miss even one frame
But chatter, how do we learn? How do we learn it? Do we do we fight the boss?
To learn that no, we have to go there's a training mode where you can just select any boss and oh
So we should close the game and open up the training mode. It's elden ring
training area
Okay, so we shouldn't fight the boss to learn it
Towershield is good. I think you can
Inhale it pretty much right?
I think the
and people were saying the same thing when I played the game for real in fought millennia and it's
You can dodge through but the thing about dodging through it is you'll dodge through it and then you don't know where she is
She's behind you somewhere
And it's like you have like one second to really figure out exactly how to dodge through that second and third attack because she goes
Away from your screen
So it's tricky. It's hard
It's very tricky
What do you mean?
Oh, come on really
That was really early and I was really hoping we'd get the stagger. So I used all my stamina
You want me to put anything in the oven here?
All right, probably not
And that's too to it too too immediate
All right, like I don't even care if I lose so maybe that means i'll win
He has nothing left to lose. I don't even like give a shit like who cares if I just lose right now. Yeah, I don't care
Can you please do the neelix voice? I have the boss scrumptious cake captain captain
Do you think we could have some scrumptious cake? There you go. All right, three two one
Are we leaving the area one more? I have the strap
You have a new strap. What is it? I have the new strap. Let's go
Can you tell me what the new strategy is? You just keep doing what you're doing and stop doubting
All right, but what is your so fill me in on what the strategy is so I can make sure I know to do no
No
As long as you do your best
honey
We're gonna do just fine. Okay
No help
Just do your best. So you but you are approaching this differently is what you're saying a little bit
What but what okay if there's a point in like phase two and there's three hits left and you're like
You need to do this do this do this and you didn't tell me what it was. No, you just need to do your best
I need you to focus. I need you to think right now
If we lose right now, uh-huh
We have to do it again
I want you to be like no i'm gonna be cautious and safe and just kind of like hit her here and there jump in
Well, make sure she doesn't go up
I mean stir. I am stir. I've been you've you've been the one you've been the one dying
But I've had to wait around you
Wouldn't it be better if like oh she's been waterfowling at me
You're just gonna say i'm the one dying because she's attacking you're not hiding behind
You're not using the pillars. Are you fucking shit?
I really hope this strategy is gonna work out for us
Are you serious?
Okay
One more how about this i'm gonna beat her right now
But see but you're not wait
You're not
You're not even using my strategy
Too focused to remember the pillar
No, I just wasn't in the right spot. And even if I ran behind the pillar, she probably would have gone around it
All right, so this is one for real I just I did
We're gonna be stuck here for like four hours
Stir you realize that we have like good weapons
but I
We are like potentially
like
Like 40 levels to like a 50 levels too low for her
You know that right?
Yes
So I I am aware that we shouldn't be insta dying the moment she touches us because we should just have like more health and stuff
It scales no should let us have this
It's scaled. It's scaled. No, no
Let us have this
How come the streamers can be fallible but the mod can't be and the scaling can't be a little off for milania
Copium overdose they messed up the code on milania. She's not scaled
Oh, I did hear about that. Yeah, and then it's in the patch notes. Yeah, it was like patch notes like uh, one point
uh, two point like uh three b
It was like having tons of trouble with with milania
It seems to be she's doubling her levels and the scaling doesn't work and she's doubling levels not scaling down
So it's like yeah. Yeah, I mean we're we're I mean if we beat this it's pretty good
And it's a little bit harder without the great run
Actually true though
That's the only thing that like the copium overload is like that's what you're saying is actually kind of true
This isn't a bad start. It's all right hold together
Don't you dare kill me? I will scream as loud as I can good. She's close
Keep your stamina
Nope. No, why did I why even attempt it? This opportunity is so small. All right. Yeah, be careful
It's coming
Keep a pillar between the two of you
I am here it is
Holy shit, are you fucking you're good? You're good. Hey, hey, you're fine. You're fine. It was only a little bit of hp taking off
You're fine. That was insane
Not a bad attempt if you could do it again, just be careful. Yeah, i'm i'm i'm envisioning it my game
a game like stuttered
I'm envisioning i'm envisioning
Please lock on to it. Okay. All right sicko mode. So just get out of the rot
Oh, it hit us both. It hit us both. Did it kill us both? It killed me
It scarlet rot at me. Oh
I was just wedged up against the fucking wall. I have no healing
Oh, that sucks
I thought we were in totally different spots, but then we kind of just ran together
Uh, it's weirder because like she would normally always go to the center of the room, right?
I know see the okay. Yeah, what happened there?
Because when she did it at first we were kind of confused and she went right in the middle
But she usually dives on top of you, right? I thought in the real fight. She always lands in the center
Wait, maybe i'm crazy. I think you are right
Doesn't it? Yeah, she lands in the middle. Why why did she jump on top of us? No, she dives you
Oh, yeah, she does
Okay
We are trying to get a pillar between her again
That's a good idea. I'm just trying to roll
You fucking hit ralphy. Well, I mean ralphy's completely in the way
Psycho
She dives on you but after the cutscene goes to the middle
All right, this let's
Actually last attempt because you know what's gonna happen. We're gonna we're gonna get to faith
We're gonna get to phase three
We're gonna get to faith
We're gonna get halfway through phase two and she has new moves in phase two that we're both gonna go
Oh, what is it?
What does that move and it's both gonna die to it and then we're gonna put our controllers in the air phase two
Easy. No, she does that weird ghost attack thing when she goes in the air and like 10 ghosts come out. Yeah
Yeah in here that's gonna be hell
But whatever well, it's all right. Those are excuses
Oh god, damn it. That's really unfortunate
Yeah, it is
I don't think we're gonna do it
Uh when I was first playing this boss
I remember thinking
I'm not gonna be able to do this and i'm gonna have to tell the stream that i'm just not doing it because I
Don't think I can I really didn't think it was possible for me to do it
I was trying to figure out like how am I gonna tell everybody that I can't do it and i'm like i'm just gonna give up
That was actually that was actually going through my mind for the last like two hours before I beat her
It's like, oh, how do I like say? Hey guys, like it's not fucking happening. It just isn't
third fucking time
Can stop doing this move stop doing this move, please
She wants it
It's the only move she has
All right
i'm just I
it
I hate this boss so much
Want to go fight bed of chaos?
I would rather like become roommates with the bed of chaos for five years
Then fight this piece of shit five more times. That one was really close though
This summon we could all right. This is the final attempt. This is the real last one. No more
No more fucking around before I before I like
Let's go somewhere else
We're going out to plateau right now. I'm just gonna teleport there without you. I'm just gonna go there without you. Okay. All right
Yeah, I I don't know. I have a lot of life
But every time she dives at me
I don't even have a chance to like dodge the second hit of uh, the waterfowl like it just fucking kills me
I don't know if because I have like no armor on or what my situation is
I'm just a dead boy
Like and i'm imagining a scenario where like the bed of chaos is like fucking dirty laundry is everywhere in the house and shit
And just like pots and pans go
Uncleaned after he cooks whatever fucked up shit that he cooks
Just constant issues really loud at like two three four o'clock in the morning. I don't even care. That's okay
I'm not fighting millennia again. Well, just decide where you want to go. Where do we we want to go to the okay?
if we go
Here
Right. No. No, we don't have to lift do we?
I'm fighting her right now. It's awful
one more time
No, no more times
No, there are no more times. All right, let's why am I always in combat here?
Where's the place to go to althus plateau?
We can come back. Uh
Well, what great rune bosses have we not done we were going to do ricard
Ricard is off the table as of right now. We did godfrey
then
I think we're done
Can we just like walk this way?
like here
Where that kind of burnt urn tree is that top where the bridge is can we we can get up there, right?
We can go to moag if we go to the uh, oh underground city
We could do underground
That sounds good to me. All right
Pull me back in let's go underground
Uh, what teleporter is that?
uh
We have a couple of them, but I don't know if that's the right ones we have to go
through
Yeah, I remember like the path to get down there when the ground is destroyed is really awkward. Yeah
underground sucks, you know
randomizer well
I'd rather go back to millennia when we have like a level 100 and I like all the stuff that we want
Not like it's gonna help
uh
I have opened my world to wanderers
Do we need to just go down to like the co for riverbank or there's a different way to get down to like actual
You have to go to the just come come to me come come to my world
sewer pipe
Yeah
Where all the omens are something like that. Okay, you guys are writing. All right following you
Why did it have to be millennia?
It could be any boss, you know
That one random room
Hey, it could be anything
So that means it could be millennia
I know but like I really wanted to see if like we have to use the spear on whoever replaces right card
I think we could do it eventually
We just gotta like
We just gotta go for it
It doesn't I don't know. It depends when she's looking at me, but it doesn't feel great to do on a caster
Yeah, that's also hard. It's a
slow
If one of us was like a dex user, I feel like that fight's easier
Everyone's gonna write omega lol dex in chat, but it's all right
Yeah, oh we had to jump down on the other side
I think I don't know this I remember like in my first playthrough just walking around this area for like an hour being like, huh?
Yeah, you gotta go like down
There are a couple things to do down here. I almost just didn't make that
with a double jump
I I spell
It's cool ancient city of wonder
What could lie millennia?
Is it possible for duplicates? It's not right
I don't think that's where millennia is that's where millennia will stay. Okay, that's all right then a little bit of a fall joke
See my issue is i'm like rushing
I like I still feel like millennia is behind us
And i'm at the fucking volcano manor
Uh, I could probably just go grab the bonfire and vote
So I remember not getting a bonfire for a while down here
I can't really leave because I would port you out
Okay
Just chill for a second. Take a breather millennia is not behind you
Wait a minute. She's behind you
I don't know somebody is believe that somebody is behind me. You're just playing vr in your game
guys come come to my stream if you want to see his perspective like of just him in vr and like the actual inside the
Helmet view is um, I mean I I can banish you and you can just join me again
And then you'd be with me. That's probably easier
You know, I I like items down here. I can just I can just do it
You keep playing let's get up
Okay, i'm going to try to join you again
If I walked off
I got michaela's needle
Looks like I beat her
Cool. All right. So
What are the actual bosses that are down here? There's another one of those
the mimic spirits, right and the big no cron dragon man and
Mog if you get really far down is down here, right? I think we need a certain item or something for mog mog
Like yeah, I don't know if we can actually do
There is a mog like down here though. I'm just gonna walk out of this room
Okay, glen stone stars. Do you want it? No, there's like crucible knights down here. Usually
There are but it's randomized. So I doubt we'll see them. But yeah right down this hill is the mimic
Tear I don't know what boss would be in here. Uh, that's like the first enemies we've killed in like three hours
Uh, hey
millennia is always gonna just make a like
Six hour gap on any stream where somebody's playing it. This is the way it is. You're not gonna even get the item
I mean
It looks like a dumb lame item shattering crystal. Do you want it?
somber eight
And the mantis blade
I think the only spells I really want are like the beam ones
That's hurt a lot
Well, these guys are empowered by
Mog
What sort am I using? I'm using the magma worm sword
I'm using it's called the magma worms scale sword
All right
Runoc
I do wonder what we're gonna do about acquiring great runes
Didn't you say that there's a thing with this randomizer where oh
If you want to find this specific item you can or something
Yeah, there's like a cheat sheet notepad where you can look up where stuff is and I think also the merchants sell
Uh hints
You go. I'm scared
As long as it's not a dragon or millennia. It's just a misbegotten. We're good
It's a mimic misbegotten
Yikes
That's so much easier than millennia
Memory stone
I I am still I don't know what it is. I'm getting golden seeds from every boss. It's good
Do I have any not really I feel like it's time for a change of clothing. Oh, there's also the
The deer
Yes, if we light all of the thingies
Which uh, I know kind of a tired statement. I never did it
I did the first year and then I came down in this area and I was like
Getting shot by people who had bows you oh you didn't do this one. This one has I moved on with my life
The deer boss is really actually pretty cool
I enjoyed fighting the deer bosses. I think they were fun
Damn, that was a triple item drop
I didn't mean to do that. I thought it was an enemy
I was living jaw
Okay. So do you want to fight the um, yeah, whatever's here? Yeah light that flame
There is four twenty. I think there are six, right?
Oh 20 wait you
Are you hey you 420 you like 420?
No, i'm relating
420. All right
All right 420
Now just if you do
Recreational marijuana and it's legal in your state or wherever you are
Cool in moderation. Be careful. Don't do too much. It's not like just
Just treat it like anything else that you know, any more too much of a good thing too much of anything is bad
Shut up, dad. No, i'm serious
I'm serious be serious about it. They say even too many oreos
Yeah, it's true
Uh, you just have to touch them, right?
Yeah
That looks really weird
Elgin lord braces
Oh, wait, isn't there like a mini boss over here too inside this little area?
I think it's just an item
It's just an item but it's like we'll go get it jar. I think it's a it's a chest
If you go up all the way
Yeah
It is a chest but there is an opportunity for something cool to be in the chest
I really don't also an opportunity to like jump off this map. I don't want to be the one to do that
So i'm gonna be careful
I am the one that would do that
Watch out. It's being guarded
by the fucking gruesome slob
death root
You really are taking your time
My controller unplugged
It's control the vibe was off my controller unplugged
Look, can you not get out of here without teleporting?
You actually might not be able to get out of there. Yeah, I don't think you can
Do you want to just pour it?
Yeah, hold on. Let me turn this one on
I can do it too, right? Yeah
Uh, if you if you pour it, I will say yes
I already voted
You did i'm in common combat
I mean, hold this. Let me just get this one
Oh, no, you can get out. I'm good. Are you good?
Yeah
Oh, you did get out
We need what two more? I got one just now
I think there is
one or two more
Looks like anything happened to let you know, you got them all
I don't remember probably
I don't think so
We need let's see
We get this one. We got that one
I think we got them all
Unless there's one more somewhere
Did we get them all?
Oh god
That seriously killed me
There is one there's one more
one remains
What's my favorite pasta shape? Um, probably penne
or spaghetti
I'm getting where this last one is
I feel like it's deep
I got it. Yeah
It's a good thing I died. I never would have came back here
Our gathers. Oh, yeah. There we go. I have a debuff
Uh, do you want to just sit at the barn fire? No
We're doing this boss hard mode
We don't even know what it is. What if it's hard?
It's gonna be super easy boss
We've had like a really rough start to the stream just like last time where we decided to like
Run our heads into placid u6
And we ran our heads into malania
And jumping off a cliff, you know what I mean? Okay. Well give them a minute to uh vote
Never mind. Whoops. I goofed it. Oh no
I still don't have to go in. Yeah, let's see. Do you think we'll beat this first try?
Uh, this is gonna be the putrid clown
The putrid clown putrid clown juggler
All right. It looks like a lot of people think yes
A lot of people are saying yes
What they don't understand is behind this door
Is hold on if it if it's like rodon the stream is just gonna end it might probably enough
All right, let's go
Uh
No
well
There's a lot of mini bosses there. I gotta say for us to find like all of the end game bosses
Thankfully, it's in an area that makes sense
for this fight
Where are the beams? Don't they come down?
They should maybe they hit the ceiling
I forget this whole fight
Same
I haven't gotten next to it yet
Oh my goodness
Yeah, this first try easy
Hit it
And then it's gone
Eat shit
All that fucking hurts
Oh god
It's not going well
It's not going that badly either though
I don't have a lot of flash right now
I think it's just a game of patience
Where am I?
He's doing triangle mode
I think what is triangle mode? Oh, you have to jump over it, right?
Oh my god. Okay. Well I baby
I baby no, I said I maybe I don't know
I think we're okay, man. I think we're just we're thinking way too deeply here
It looked like he was swinging at you. Um, he is now
I have one flask remaining
I I so wish this was an arena where we could use a fucking horse. I didn't dodge that
But I did look like I did
He's just running
I think we're all right. Just play it safe
Oh this fucking move
It's it's on you
What the hell? Oh, that's this thing
Stop yelling. What is it making make it a youtube video or what?
It'd be a sick video if you were
Uh-oh, he's doing triangle mode
or circle
man
Get out
Okay, he nuked me
Stay alive
Wow believers
Hey, congratulations for the fucking millions of points. You probably just got
I got great rune of the unborn
I got a stone sword key and a bell bearing and the glint stone wet blade
And a bell bearing we sure i've got a few bell bearings. I don't know what's in them
We should go check
I'll be really honest though. We lucked out big time
because
If you put the elden beast in a room that's small like that millennia room
I don't think I we probably wouldn't to fight him in a small room. No, I don't think you know, you're not no
I would all those moves are so they're just aoe spam moves that we wouldn't you wouldn't be able to do it
Well, I would love to like for the experience to see what that fight's like if you're not constantly running across a football field
Like how are they gonna let him run that far and not give me a fucking sniper rifle in this game?
Yeah
So we did that
What else is down here? There's uh, then you drop down here and you go to uh, oh where the double gargoyles are
Yeah, we might get some
That's gonna be fun. Whatever. That is
Rip 15k imagine all the emotes with glasses I could have had with that much money
that's so
uh, that was
Emotes with the glasses I have no channel point shit like really at all. It's emos with glasses
I mean there aren't a lot of options
Some people have millions of points here and it's like, uh, it's like you 100 put glasses on the germamoon emote
Nice. There's a guy behind you
Oh watch out. It's you. Oh, it's you
Crab look at all those glasses
So many glasses emotes
What does the glint stone wet blade even let me do
I believe it lets you imbue weapons with the magic damage ash of war stuff
Oh, yeah
but it
So you can scale off of intelligence
With pretty much any weapon
I was I was thinking because I already do that but i'm using glint stone pebble to do it
There's another somber ancient stone. I've gotten a lot of
Bell bearings it really might be worth after we do this to go check what's there
Oh, there's a legendary over here
Legendary legendary legendary legendary
Lord of blobs bro
Where is it? Oh, I got mogs
Bro, I have the twin darmer set for this apparently
I got a I got a pose
Okay, nice. Who is that? Uh, that is the other that's the twin brother. Oh, this is bad
I don't think we need the spear
but but also we could be wrong and
Just die
Um, okay. There we go. We got the spear. We have the spear apparently
Where is it? I hate when this happens
Where is it? I hate when this happens. There it is coming slow. Don't panic
All right, we can I think we can do this the technique where he never attacks you
We don't have the oh you have to weapon art
If you can stun them, you can keep them stunned forever. I think wait
I
Am confused
What do you mean? How do you how do you do this shit again left trigger?
Yeah, mine doesn't have a wind blade
Only you can do it my chat saying
I saw so many speed runs this part that I know you can literally just keep them in like a loop
You really wanted to
Well, it's not worth it. I can't help
Does this thing cost mana or no?
Oh, they patched it. Okay
It's good to know
Oh, did they find like something that was fun?
And then they like patched it out. You need mana to do this shit. God damn it
I'm helping
I'm overweight with this
I wish I could see
I got him
Frater Raikhan
All you do is eat the gods and then you
I have no more mana
Uh, I guess I could just attack like this
Please don't die. It's only you
I'm not gonna who said I was gonna die
I'm just worried because I can't help
No phase two. No phase two. No phase two
No phase two. Don't do it
Yeah
These quotes are approximately correct
It's like you told an ai to do the the ryckhardt lines
Okay, good fight
I have to level up
Yeah, so so the next elden we're gonna do elden ring two
dark souls four
And uh, there's totally gonna be like a sword that shoots like wind
There's gonna be one boss
I have a question for you. Then there's gonna be a swamp
I I want I want the actual stir take because I don't know if this is just stupid or not
But I was thinking about this
Do you because eric look?
Everybody loves the from software
RPGs like this, right? We're not talking about any of the other games they've ever made not like armored core. Whatever this
Lower left of your screen that looks like this in like five of their games
Everybody loves these with the stamina bar and the you know dodging and the pairing they call they call them souls. So sure
Yeah, do you think it would be cool?
It they kind of just and look i'm not complaining. I love these games. They're amazing
But like each one of these games is like the same kind of game in a different setting with some slightly different changes, right?
Yeah
Would you pay like 15 bucks a month for a?
Souls like mmo where they just kept fucking adding stuff to it
They're making them anyway
god forged
But made by from software not like oh something in this world. No, I mean like the next whatever they do is just like, you know what?
We keep making this type of game and everybody loves it. So let's just like have one go forever
I mean, honestly
That's what neo feels like
It would just not with the emma like the actual online I would love the actual online
but
but comes with a big but that this would be being made by like
a japanese company
And it would have a whole bunch of like gacha mobile. Well mmo i'm using that term wrong
Not an mmo, but just like a like a constant
Like they make dark souls one dark souls two dark souls three they make bloodborne. They make elden ring
You're just saying live service dark souls
Yes, and it's just like that. It's just you don't have to worry about it
Oh, when's the next dlc like it's just gonna happen
It's gonna be like a wow patch like every like four or five like three or four months
I think on paper that sounds great. That's what I mean, but I think it would actually be fucking awful
Yeah in practice this it would be probably terrible
But I don't know. I just feel like I I I love these games
I feel like they wouldn't be able to execute that without completely killing the vibe of like hey for halloween
We got the new update to souls 14
That's right guys are gonna get like oh wear pumpkin hats and like there's like just like all the weird themed cosmetics
Everyone be running around. I didn't think of like fucking bizarro. Yeah
I didn't think of the it's christmas time
You dress up as a tree and transform using your talisman into a fucking present
I forgot about the the octoberfest update that would happen. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
but I mean like in theory if that if like without the pessimism of it being bad because
I feel like there's a two percent chance. It makes it through like all of like
The business dealings for them to get like the money grant to be able to do some live service multi-year thing
Well, hold on get through all that and it's not many dlcs to dark souls 2 have
Well, it was a bunch wasn't it like four
uh
two three
Two or three. Yeah, so there were three dlcs for dark souls 2 and people always go. Oh man
It's awesome that isn't one of the things you say that one of the reasons why you like dark souls 2 so much more
Than the other ones is why?
How much content how much content there is why elden ring is pretty great
But isn't that kind of that that doesn't like I think you might get what you're saying
Within a couple years of like elden ring was like crazy financial successful raised a bunch of eyebrows
People are like, oh souls games people have been playing for like 10 years time to like come in and ruin it
Yeah, somebody made a good franchise long enough like we're getting dangerously close to like man. I miss the old from soft
I don't want it to happen. That's true. And I hate like if i'm jinxing it my bad, but like
These are the good we're in the good times and you gotta appreciate somebody said
It's actually kind of a good point is like art is finite
Should be kind of in this world and I think if you don't let a game like this be finite
Then you maybe are going down the road where it just ruins everything and where are we going?
How do we end up at the end of a ledge? How do we end up here? I don't get across somehow
I agree on that like everyone got to play through the same thing at the same time and get excited about the same stuff
Yeah
And at the moment that it does become like mmo
Everyone's like what's the quickest way to end game because I just want to like grind millennia for millennia's god-sent set
Yeah, that's true
Yeah
I think it's just like it's a it's such a good thing and it's such a it's such a unique experience that it's almost
You sit there and go god damn it. I wish I could have that unique experience again, but it's here
It already exists. You already had it. Fuck fuck dude
I'm just excited to see them explore like different settings again and see how armored core turns out
I never played any of the armored cores with any were they fun?
Well, what kind of I don't know what kind of games they are
I believe we had this conversation and yeah, I love like armored core one and two were amazing
I went to go get an item and I got
Annihilating fortunate. I'm awesome. I mean like I just thought like we're all doing it. Everyone's doing it
I'll just drop 60k souls real quick
Yeah armored core games are really good. I think they got like early on it was like slower more dark souls like slow big mechs
If you put on a whole bunch of armor your mech would like be slower
And it started to get towards like three four five
It got a lot more anime and I didn't really play those and i'm kind of hoping
And assuming it's going to be a little bit more like the older ones. Yeah
Uh, yeah, you uh because lightning coming from I did the mario thing
Where you jump like you freak out even though you make the jump you still jump a second time third time because you just don't
You thought you were gonna miss the edge. Is that three fall jokes today? Is it a little bit played out?
You think well, I mean you did miss that jump in the lava place like 40 or 50 times
So I think I can fall a few times. Ooh, whirl of flame
Okay
At like e3 comes around it's like june
And there's like a dark souls or like a bloodborne announcement like bloodborne moon rising
And like holy shit that like it's just like a cinematic trailer looks amazing
Looks so and at the end when it says like what consoles and everything it's on it's like, okay
This was made by nexon. How are you feeling after that?
I don't know about that
Well, I think I think that goes back to what you were asking. Yeah
I think
Yeah, I don't know about that
What if I told you that this game was ass and there's nothing you could do to convince me. Otherwise
I would tip my hat to you and say good day. Good, sir. We have different opinions. Um,
Enjoy the rest of your evening
I got the magma whip candlestick
I think uh
When someone says you can't change my mind about this. Yeah, that's like that. Oh that i'm not going
I'm not gonna try
You really expect me to do anything else other than not talk to you anymore. Yeah, it's like hold on a minute here
Listen to me. Let's talk about this
You've already you've already given me no opportunity to uh to give you an argument
I would just say yeah. All right
I have have a good day
It's like hey
Hey jeremy
Pizza is disgusting. I think it's fucking gross
What do you say about that? Do you think you think you're gonna convince me to eat pizza?
No, that's more pizza for me
Can't convince you though something you already don't want or don't like
You already um, you've already made up your mind
And it's almost like you want me
To argue with you so you can argue your points back to me
But why you think i'm wrong you're trying this is a your wrong scenario and I want to prove why
Sorry
I'm not gonna give that opportunity to you
We can go over to the tree that's over there because there's usually a crucible knight and item or we just go up to uh
giant dead mermaid
You make the call mermaid
Which I this is not how you get there. I I don't think it is
I know this is a really really stupid question to ask but you definitely didn't do like the secret boss
That's up here when you fight. Um
the deathbed companion all of her champions
No, I did that you did that's actually surprising. That's not really a secret
I mean that's like you have to do a very specific amount bunch of shit in a row to do that
I don't think so. You don't I don't have to do her whole quest line
Um, I thought you just show up
Oh, I thought you had to do her whole quest line
Coke zero or diet coke neither
I don't like either one of them
Just give me a smaller regular coke so I can so all right
I would rather drink less
Regular coke than more coke that doesn't taste that good
Just I want to drink less of the if sugar and all that and calories or whatever is what you're concerned about
I would just I would just I don't I don't want to drink like a full 12 ounce can
If you get a two liter just have a little bit
I'd rather have the full flavored one but less of it. I really don't like I know a lot of people
Love the way the diet coke tastes
It tastes like flavored air in your mouth after and people go. Yeah, that's the point. That's why I like it
It's like okay
And i'm telling you right now you are not going to convince me otherwise that diet coke is good
Go on. Come on
I mean, I I don't
I don't have a stake in this
Uh, where did you where are you? Did you go up?
I went up
It's moag
Did you just seriously spoil my?
It's fucking boss here
I mean you're talking about drinking air. I
Wandering around it's because coke diet coke when you take a sip out of it
It kind of disappears in your mouth and leaves this
It leaves this weird like air flavored flavored like sugar air
You don't know what i'm saying people the people that get it get it
Magicians actually use it when you take a sip of diet coke. It goes like
And it's this and it's this weird like
Like someone breathing in your mouth. I'm telling you it's
Why do I have so I just got so many
Shit keeps falling off the trees. I just yeah, what the fuck?
That's got like 15 000 souls. Wait, did I I didn't just activate that right?
Aftertaste it's but it's an yes. It is an aftertaste, but it's like an airy aftertaste. That's what i'm saying, dude
Hold on a second. I'm getting another I just got another 10 000. Yeah same
Let's hold on
Respawn everything. Yep. Cool. That's got another 11k
All right. Let me level up one more time. The last time I got this much shit for free. It was on game pass
Yeah, I mean it
I could believe that
Considering that in the last like two weeks load monster hunter rise came out on game pass. You can just download it
On top of that
Hi-fi rush comes out. It's on game pass. Just you can just get it golden eye remaster. It's on game pass
It's like a hundred fucking dollar value
You've got to be kidding me like just actually kidding me
It actually is mog. You're right
Um, so do you want to fight him solo?
You want to fight him solo?
Well, no you because he's like your favorite and you're you're like wearing his outfit
You like are showing up to the boss in his clothes like look. I got it, too
I'm showing up to like comic con
This is the i'm in the meet and greet line
That's my move
Is he gonna like count down and
He's probably gonna do the thing
Sorry, just be aware of it
I forget how that works and if we need an item for him to not
Murder us. It's a flask item, but you can heal through it
Oh
You got me with a backswing. I'm doing a challenge run where I have to get hit by every attack
I was gonna say I've heard you scream like a lot
Fucking die
Oh, that was quicker than I thought it was gonna be
He's gonna do his thing and we need to heal through it. I got one flash
Maybe he doesn't do it because
He should have he should be doing it now
Wait, this might be the other mug the fake mug. Yeah, it's the fake mug a different mug like no
I know actually doesn't he have a different name?
Other than bog, I think it's omen. I thought he had a name like underbelly submissive boy
Uh
I don't um
Just beat the boss already
Hey, remember when you made that joke about me fighting the boss alone
Yeah
Hey, i'm fucking doing a lot. You just don't know
Oh, you're so cool
I'm such a huge fan, by the way
lord's aid
You know what? I I was gonna respect to like the faith support character. I'm I feel like i'm playing so bad. I really just should
What's your drip?
This is what you needed all the question for afterwards. You talked to her to do plastic do six
But the initial fight I think is uh always here
um
What do we say? That's right
To be a mother so it is I must bear
Bottom one
Oh, I think I just ruined it
Because we uh, i'm disbanding
Oh
I want to spend uh
Quick amount of time. I am gonna do the respect
Am I okay?
I can still choose. Okay. Good. Wait, you you let her hold you. No, that's you're supposed to so then that's how you fight
Plastic do you think you sick fuck? That's how you fight plastic do six you fucking horn dog
Uh, I could just go back there deathbed companion
Loathsome dung eater
Horoloo chieftain of the badlands and who could forget
The all-knowing
It puts me in combat every time. I can't leave this area. It's annoying. Can I take one of these things to like go back?
That's not good
even
How do I get out of here?
I can't
I don't want to run through all this. I know I just whatever but what if I miss i'm gonna
I'm okay. I can make it
Why am I alive?
I don't know, but doesn't kill you instantly. How come it was killing us instantly?
What the fuck? Wait, what the that was weird?
Like we already did this. My brown hole is invaded again
It might just keep doing that
maybe
They died in three hits this time
Wow a hundred souls, thanks
Oh, yeah, check your bells
Bells your bell bearings. Oh good idea. I want to just teleport out of here
Did I go the wrong way?
I mean, i'm just trying to get far enough away from where I was to teleport
Golden order seal boost fundamentalist incantations. Do you remember what those are?
What counts as fundamentalist? I think
some of the big fire spells count
Is the the black flame stuff I think the holy light one. Oh, it's lightning. Okay. Do you have any seals?
I only have a golden order and dragon communion
I
Do have some seals
I have dragon communion and I gave you the other one. Whatever it was. Yeah, that's the golden order
I guess i'll use that one
Okay, just really get the hell out of here. It's not open in my goddamn game
What do I do now?
You went the wrong way rest go down the ladder
I just want to pull the fuck out of here
uh
Go into the castle
Read chat i'm staring at you right now. It's just read
Chat read chat is is there are there are 5 000 messages, which one?
read
Chat i'm just gonna go this way
I'm gonna die in
I'm just running around in circles until I figure out where the hell i'm supposed to go
That's a bunch of garbage my bell bearings are all
Ball lakes
I think I can go through here
Can I go through here?
What are you doing right now? How does he not remember doing this multiple times?
Um, because this area is fucking enormous and there's so many random ass places to go
That and they all look pretty identical. So they're all the same place in my brain
Where are you trying to go? I'm just trying to get to any grace
But I can't go anywhere
Oh, you're trying to get a closer you're trying to millennia right now. I'm trying to get the hell out of this area
But it won't let me
Uh, then inside the building to the left and you go down the stairs. That's where I was thinking of going
But there's somebody scary there
Uh, that's fine. That's where we were spawning earlier with the bird in the way
That's what I just didn't want to get blocked by that
and then down the stairs here, right
My uh finger reader receive equipment of champions she's got ash of war kick
Wow, this guy's just gonna fuck it all up for me. I know it's gonna chase me
Okay kick is op
Is kick I mean kick is actually pretty good
Yeah
Is it?
Bro, am I even going the right direction?
Yep, that bird wasn't even there before when was that bird here?
Lightning isn't faith scaling. Yes, it is
Wait non lightning is dex
Yeah
I got lightning ram and it's dex
I don't have the only thing i've been missing is I don't have a single faith ash of war
I wish I could drop them because I think I have two or three of them
I don't think I have the uh
The thing to make them faith
Oh the actual doors are open now
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
The dragon communion seal scales on arcane, right?
I could do that
Wait, I could put it on a weapon and drop it really
That's kind of cool. I didn't know that
Okay
Let me see
I have um sacred blade
And I think I can put it on a weapon and just give it to you
That's actually a good idea if I gave you my long sword. Yeah, and I could just put it on and just give it back
I'm thinking uh, because I have actually a whole bunch of stuff that scales with a cult. I could use the dragon communion
um
But does that scale just as good as the other?
seals
I think
the dragon seal scales
He said with arcane
But it also just can be used as a seal for every other spell. I think it just depends on what the spell is
Yeah, I just want to make sure i'm not like screwing myself in some obscure way
I don't i'm gonna i'm gonna do arcane. I should have another larval tier i'm just gonna go arcane
Which is also good because that's a magic vine for items and it's all random
So maybe we get more better stuff dragon communion scales to s with arcane at level 10
Apparently, is there any other fun stuff that I want to use? Maybe i'll be like a
Maybe i'll do the bubble thing. That's kind of fun. Then that's the play
Do you guys want me to level up? Uh the big bubble horn? Uh, do you have a smithing stone?
somber five
I probably do let's see what i'm missing. I have a somber stone five
Do you have a nine is there a nine or does it go straight to dragon?
There is a nine and I also have a nine as well. Okay, I need a five and a nine
I can give you both of those. Okay, then i'm gonna go
Respec again, I guess oh the bearings. Yeah, I do check your bearing shop if you haven't yeah, I did
When does she go sit? Oh, you have to get her. Yeah, her shop will be randomized too. Won't it?
Doesn't does she have a shop? I think she sells some random shit doesn't she finger lady?
Oh, the finger lady does have a shop not just remembrances. Ooh
This thing is pretty cool
This is like fire. It's like a blood fire colossal hammer sharpened
Yeah, volcano fragment. I mean, it's 1800 i'm gonna buy it
Weapon rewards will be randomized if you bring the remembrances to her
Worth looking. Okay. Cool. Now you can finally play as me strong good point
very good point
Wisdom of the two fingers have you then I've been I am known as a tarnished eye onto us
We're a stir. We're in separate worlds just getting our shit together
Yeah, I gotta I gotta pick up my order. Do you I don't know. I can't drop this. I don't think
The litany of proper death creates an image of order to deal. Holy damage
Holy shit. I have so many
I have so many bearings
Holy shit. All right, we're gonna be here for a little while
Um god, can you try joining my world because i'm like bottlenecked until I get that and i'm already in the round table
Just a moment
Uh, oh you're in the right. Can I join you? You should be able to
love so you need a
nine
end of five
There you go. What the heck is braggart's roar?
Why is your door closed but mine is open? I don't know. That's weird
Oh, wait, let's see the dung eater. What are you dressed like?
All right, let's go over all this new shit that I have
the death root
Hi, I have it
Okay
Now we need
No, no, no
Do you have any faith talismans?
faith talismans like the stuff that boosts
Faith magic or anything weird like that that you're not using
Oh, let me find out
I have
Uh raises maximum fp raises decks
I don't think I have anything that boosts faith
I don't you can only see your other bell bearing shops because you used them in your solo game
Oh shit. Well, i'm leaving for a minute
You got the items, right?
Yeah, good
Oh shit, we're duping
golden land
Oh shit. I'm a cheater
I got rot breath with a plus 10 dragon seal
See how millennia likes it already used this one before
Eight thousand come on
Is that all the bell bearings I had
I feel like i've seen all this stuff already
by the soul
Hmm
I don't think I really want anything. I think i'm ready. I think i'm done. I need a you know
Like a new outfit to like impress you
I never will no matter how cute I look
Get the millennia sword
Where's the millennia's weapon? Oh this thing, right?
Oh 48 decks i'm never gonna do that. Yeah
i'm
Pretty much ready, but I am gonna do this because people are gonna be mad if I don't use this weapon
Okay, I need to get it ready. I did give you the stones. I gave you the stones and I really needed them
Um, well, I gave you stones earlier. So it's only fair
You want to be fair right there
All right. I'm ready. I'm gonna join. No, I probably shouldn't join you here. This has problems
Yeah, where are we going? Well
We could go we did this. Do you want to go do the um
we're
Placidusix is supposed to be that other dragon
Uh, do we have that quest on that quest? I don't know what we're supposed to do. Can we actually do it?
I doubt it of four to sex, right? Can we do four to sex? You gotta have the item
Now you need the finger slayer blade
We could go we could go give some death root really we both have a few that we haven't given
I have a great rune
So i'd like to go somewhere where we can activate it
one of the towers, um, which one is it the
Unborn
That I have the finger slayer blade you do. Ooh. All right. Well, then let's go back and do the fiaquest
So we need you to go. Let's just go do it, which is which teleport?
Uh the roots it's where we would just were right before we left that root place
Now you have to give the finger slayer blade to ronnie
Oh
Uh, that's right. So go to ronnie. You don't need the blade. I need the curse
Yeah, hopefully if you get it then I can play too need death mark. Not the blade. The blade is for ronnie
Ronnie is just like jealous
All right. Let's go
to
Ninth mount gelmere campsite and we're going to go back and we're going to run into altis plateau
Are you okay with that?
Uh, I need one second
Yeah, every quest is going to be a huge pain just because everything's just so everything's randomized
We might just we might just get stuck somewhere and have to turn around you get the death mark from killing millennia
But it'll be random every if we kill millennia. She'll give us like fucking dung
I am I am doing some nasty shit with fear right now. Um, are you ready to play the game?
I saw somebody in chat said hey dude, like i've been sitting here for like five ten straight minutes
I've got a big bunch of snacks. I got popcorn. I have like nachos and cheetos and shit
And I my popcorn is getting cold
I haven't been able to take one bite because I was waiting for you guys to start to do something
They're furious
He said he said he's holding it in like big like holding it all like popcorn
How come how come you got to be embraced by fia and I don't how is that any bit fair?
Okay, where where were we meeting? I was just seeing if I had an item the uh
Where are we meeting like where are we going? Like what what's happening? Like who are you aldous plateau?
So we're gonna go to the nine nine mount gilmer campsite and then from there we're gonna run to
Aldous plateau. Okay. Um, I believe my world is so we are going to this way. We want to go this way five
Three join my world now
Dude, I need to poop and I i'm not gonna read the rest of that. But okay. Oh you look different. What did you do?
All right, it's a race to get there go
Hey, how about the first person that gets there owes the other person?
20 bucks thousand dollars. I don't know where we're going
Uh, we're just following
First person to get there also follow me not that way
Weird like this is not where millennia is
No, it's not
another point
Okay, you know we never did we ever fight the way that um, like the meteorite
Demon thing was we didn't go all the way up there. Did we?
No, we didn't what was up there the tree spirit. Oh, this is tree spirit. That's right
You know what? We haven't done the dragon in the starting lake. It's true. Okay, continue
Going keep going
Hey, look at this grace right here. Yep
It's crazy
It's pretty crazy. There's also items galore first boss here is
you get
Uh like invaded by
Um, what's his name there?
Market, right?
Uh, oh we're going in the city
Well, isn't it right when you get through the front door of this, uh, alts plateau. He shows up, right?
Yeah, and he's like you aren't good enough
Okay, how do we get down? I think we have to go over here. I think you just jump
I think you go this way
It's your squid in a chair
That is a squid sitting in a chair
I'm beating you
It's not over yet until we get into alts plateau
It's a long ladder
Yeah, could you just hold b?
Hands kind of hurt when I do that
All right, watch out the lobster
Another dragon heart. Okay. Here we go
And your winner
Uh, how do you get down to the where mog is I thought you did that from no crone you
It's like a teleport from somewhere. I think oh from the
the four ways
Teleporters or it's yeah the the place with the blue keys
blue stone sword keys
Good theory
Okay
uh
Let's let's explore
Probably something interesting down here
Actually pretty useful
Is there ruins that go down here?
crab crab crab watch out crab. I see it
There is over by me
It's probably a bad idea to just walk up there with the horse
That's one of these guys. It's a mog like
I don't know. Is that thing bigger than normal?
But this thing is just right in front of me how
Why did I just hear is that a dragon? That's me. I'm dragon boy. I did no damage with that
Which is kind of surprising
Just lagging my game
All right, just come down here. Oh
Wait, no
Yeah, that's sad
We got a boss in here. You have to hold it
Oh you went downstairs
There is a boss
All right, something easy
Something simple you first
Who is this?
Oh, it's one of the invader like the bell-bearing invaders
Oh, no, no. No, this is somebody this person's in that castle
Now I don't like being in this corner
game
Lacky whenever boss
true
oh
Annihilated thanks for the heal. Hey, no problem there pal
No item
Out of this door. Oh poison bloom crap. Okay, we continue to progress
All right. I think we get invaded here by
Margaret
That's way later
Up in the castle is it I thought it was like right here. Look all that castle all the way up on the right past the urn tree
Yeah, you go there. Yeah, and that's where margaret is
Oh, let's kill these. Let's do it
I'm i'm initiating the pact of let's do it
I turn around just being killed by a dog
Well, you know what they say
Why are we killing these?
Because they got the item
Yeah, we can just go in the back
No
This dog's gonna kill me
It's a random group of fucking enemies
That's a big ant
It's a crazy big shield. It's holding
Yeah, you were on crack in the very beginning of this stream. By the way, i've mellowed out a bit, but I really
You know it happens
Don't get rot, please
All right. What do you got?
Oh, dude a blessing of the ancient old ones. I got a grape
Really?
I just have to start you would love crack
I've never tried it. Uh, my game's lagging right now. I don't know where you are, but i'm just kind of going forward
Do you want hamburger helper?
Um, uh, dude if I could go for like, uh, like a man witch
That's a good
I don't know. You're a fan of floppy jose
I am come up this way. There's the uh, the god skin noble who's probably like
I don't know. Oh the windmill
I love sloppy jose
Same
I never I don't really happen that often though
They're incredibly hard to make
It takes a lot because you need to be like a professional chef
Um, i'm kind of you lagged out and I don't know where you are
I'm at the windmill you can teleport here if you want i'm at the bonfire at a windmill game is putting you in many different locations
Yeah, if you don't simmer it just right
Then it can really ruin it
Are you mocking me?
I mean i'm making just like a general joke about making a sloppy joe. Are you are you mocking me?
I'm mocking just making sloppy joes, which is I like them. I'm just we're making a funny joke that like oh look
It's it's a lot of work. I'm not laughing joe
You know what? I think you would like crack too
All right. This is a really important question for you stir. Do you put cheese on your sloppy joe? Yes or no?
Like on the bun. How do you smoke it or do you inject?
Cheese on my no. Okay. No, that's a good answer
That sounds fucked up. Like what was the point of making like a messy disgusting thing and you're gonna like
Some people put like a slice of like american cheese on it
And I don't agree
No, i've never had cheese on one. I feel like it's enough on its own
Yeah, i'm glad we agree
and the boss is
A free sentinel. Hopefully I think it's just a regular one
Yo, hold aggro for a second. I've got a big spell I can let loose charging up my spirit bomb
I can't lock on to him because he's a fucking you're dead
I know you're just talking and all I could think of is you speaking. I can't lock on to him
I just heard you say hold on take aggro and i'm just like i'm just gonna let him talk for a little while and then
I just got out of the fucking plane. I lost it
I was doing fine until you started like yelling commands
Ah, we've got this boy. You suck. Oh my god, dude. You just got hit. Do you want me to do it?
You're not gonna be able to
You're just not gonna be able to
Nice misses
That was so awful holy again
Wow
See see what happens. You see chat. You see see how fucking how it feels. You see how it feels chat
It stinks. Can't lock on to him. You don't understand. You can't lock on
All right there pal. Just take aggro for a second. So i'm charging up a big attack
So when stir gets hit and he looks over at the chat and he sees so bad omega lull terrible. Wow got hit
see
Are you just spectating? I'm here
You just obscured my vision to a bar. I didn't know when he was swinging the sword
I'm sorry alarm. I'm sorry
Yo, first person to buy buys the other person a cheese first person to all right first person to have a fucking sandwich
Uh, it gets 20 dollars sent to their
I'm having a sandwich right now. I got one in the fridge
Yo, I got you go in i'll heal you
I hit again
Dude, you almost got hit there
You almost hit you you're so bad it almost hit you
Dude, you fucking sucked that fight
Dude, you oh nice. I got a uh, isn't that good?
That's one of the good ones, right?
It is okay. I need to mix that
All right, cool. I don't need to heal. Actually. I didn't I want to level up. Does urgent heal not apply to other people?
Urgent heal does not heal other people it only heals. I have to I have to great heal you
Yeah, great heal will heal everybody in that circle
Nice. I don't know why but like your outfit it looks like you're a participant on the masked singer
Something about the way you look right now
He just doesn't stop
It's like the big cape the the regal like I don't know ornate shit you have there the big mask
He doesn't let up. All right, like, uh, where do you want to go then?
Okay, so that was fun
Let's get a map fragment. Let's get this map fragment
So let's go
Sloppy joe though
I'm telling you if you keep saying that then the stream is gonna end because i'm gonna go i'm gonna want to go make one
Do you have it?
Come on, man
You don't have a can of man, which just ready to go under any circumstance. Well, that's I wish you're making a big mistake
No, I have a whole bunch of like pre-made meals left in a backpack
Hold on left in a backpack
What do you mean? What do you mean? I have to explain that because I that just I did not expect a human to say that
Well, is this like daisy?
What do you mean? There's like food in your backpack
Uh, well my wife's in the chat and she's crying because I brought it up again. So I don't think I can talk about it anymore
Oh that kills you don't do it
Okay, you already did this once with the fucking zelda clip again fall joke is overrated
I didn't think that was gonna actually kill me. I didn't think that was gonna actually kill me
I thought it was that didn't look that far that looked fine
All right. Anyways, what were you saying?
I
I don't got nothing to say
All right, you can tell him do it as a warning. I the short version of the story is
Me and ashley went to the grocery store yesterday to get food like a whole bunch of like the prepared grocery store meals
Okay, I was like, i'm i'm lazy. I just want like a whole bunch of these to eat. Okay, you mean for me
But when you say prepare it you mean it's like, okay, there's like a salmon in here
It's already seasoned and howard he has the stuff in it. You just put it in the oven
It's just like a cold cuts a pork chop with like some potatoes and green beans like ready to go in the oven. Yes
Yeah, nothing wrong with that. Yeah, and we walk we don't drive so it's like all in a backpack so we could walk back with it
and uh, you know just
I went to go eat them. I was like excited like oh shit
I've got so much food and I went to go get and there was uh, you know
It was all still in the backpack
Like the next day so you just had a bunch of fucking food
Oh, that's one you ate one
Stirrer, I ate one stir. You ate a backpack meal. That was like raw food in a backpack. Yeah
24 hours had gone by I you're saying it like I didn't cook it first
I did cook it and it wasn't it was maybe I don't know it was overnight like 16 hours
I think you're missing a lot of the finer points here. I don't know dude
Have you ever watched one of those food time lapse videos?
Where it shows like one hour two hour five hour six hour and then they fucking ants to start coming in and grubs
Well, it is sealed inside of a thing. There's like not ants getting in it
What kind of food was so you took so this was uh, so you opened up the backpack and you were like
Oh like oh like you must have stunk
It honestly didn't and then I unsealed the wrap on it and I touched the meat and it was like a little cold
And I was like, hmm like it was colder than my my hand was you know, it felt a little cooler touch
So then you were just like, you know what fuck it i'm just gonna put this in the oven like if I die
I die and how long ago was this?
Is overnight like got it at like 8 pm at night and then it was the next day at like 2 pm. Okay
So, how do you feel right now?
Uh, I ate it yesterday. Uh, I gotta say I felt a little weird, but i'm good. You feel a little weird now
Um, I think i'm good. Are you coming like i'm at the castle i'm sorry
I'm can't tell you that i've been paying that much attention to the game when I heard that you ate food
That's been in a backpack for a fucking day
It looks fine
No, the fucking bear grills is like eating his own shit. No, no, no, no
I'm telling you right now you're I know you're about to go down this path of oh, what are you talking about?
Like you probably would no
No, I would not if if I had like a pork chop that was raw that was on the counter for 16 hours
I would not eat it
But there's like no other food because that's all the food you got for yourself. I would figure something. I would figure something out
Yeah, I would something out. I would eat anything else anything else. No, that's not happening
Especially if it's like raw food that's just sitting there
What is the the this of the what's the time? It's two hours, right?
Two hours is like when bacteria really starts to grab a hold of food, right when it's out a bit of bacteria is good for you
It's four. Okay, so four hours went by
Okay. Well, hopefully you don't have any issues. All right. I don't know where the fuck i'm going right now
Stuart can we teleport back to the windmill village and can you help me this fucker's judging my fucking backpack?
Raw meat meal doesn't even know where he's going. I gotta say though. Actually, I was kind of dizzy yesterday
Bridges didn't exist for thousands of years in human history. Yes, but they were curing their meats
It's not the same. It's not it was
That's stirs fucking musty ass backpack is not a curing environment for for food
That's not okay. I ain't gonna have that happen
Do you want to I mean you'll be proud of me at the very least that there was coconut shrimp in there. Ooh
Everything we talk. Yeah, you're absolved of all these crimes
Okay, well I was just gonna say I didn't eat the coconut shrimp actually was like that's fish and I was like a good argument
Good point. Oh, yeah, don't eat that
But somehow eat what was what was the food the actual food you ate the actual food was pork chops and potatoes
That's just that's just as bad
It's not fish raw pork is arguably probably I would even say maybe even potentially worse
Fucking it was like eight bucks, dude
Fucking for real right now
Uh-oh, look out
They don't even shoot raw fish is sushi though
Well raw fish is sushi, but it's not sushi. That's been sitting on the restaurant table for 16 hours
Yeah, we left the sushi out overnight in our backpack
Fucking disgusting
Honestly, what do they do to sushi? No, but hey, hey, please people are telling me that I have this wrong
We're not talking about a tv dinner. We're talking about it's it was raw food that you had to put in the oven and cook it
Yeah, it was just like raw pork chop
See, it's it's not like a tv dinner. It's not like stoffers
Just like in them in like an aluminum tray with like uh plastic wrap around it pork chop
I
I actually can't believe you ate that
Honestly same though
So what was the scenario? You're just like, you know what? I don't care what happens to me
I'm just gonna eat thinking about it for like a day and I like had no other food and I looked at them all
And I was like, you know what?
Well, if you feel
There he is
Oh shit
That was he's not really that scary actually
Hey, honestly if I were him too, I wouldn't say anything either
You just shut up and disconnect as quick as you can. Yeah, just just literally pull your ethernet cable up
And make a new account
It's like what are the signs that like if I have worms?
um
Probably gastric upset I would say probably number one
uh
Is that a talisman not what the hell is that?
gastric issues
I would say
diarrhea
How have you been?
You think I'd feel a little tickle?
I would imagine you would feel quite a few gurgles if it were if it were me answering
so
I know that like everyone whenever they're talking about hand
uh the thumb
is always the uh
Kind of the hero of the hand everyone's like, oh that's a human hand the thumb
How do you feel about like I I feel like fingernails are kind of underrated
Not even remotely close to thumbs not even close. In fact, I think I think the raw pork is is mutated your brain at this point
I think the raw pork is mutated his brain
You think that an opposable thumb is not as important as your fingernails
Can you imagine not having like fingernails and just having like just like normal?
I think these these are the worms talking
I yeah, I think scientists have said that eventually we might just evolve them out like they just won't exist anymore
Really? I think so. That's that's been a debate. I
I use them so much though like
You have to like really pick at something on like um, like you drop something between your keyboard
Like how are you gonna get it out if you don't have fingernails? I mean
That's one tiny shitty little thing to you. I mean you could use like a
That's like we're we're using them
I don't my fingernails are used i'm trying like scratching my ass
I think i'm just all i'm saying is I don't think fingernails get enough credit because the thumb
Takes all the fucking all right. Give me a fingernail tier list of things you can do with it
That's what what are you saying is like, okay number one
Do you not?
Because picking up like a coin on your desk if that's s tier for you. I'm sorry that that is a good example
Thank you. I didn't even have to come up with that one
That's like d
You ever like scratch a dog?
Yeah, that's gone. If you can't like really get underneath the like the fur and like give them a real good scratch
You can't do that without fingernails. All right, we like we're just walking in circles
I think you could still get like friction
Hold on a second
Your dog would know the difference it still works. What about peeling an orange?
True you never never
I uh when I was young sorry for uh, you know, uh sensory overload alert don't listen
Uh, one of my my big toenail came clean off
And I gotta tell you uh, certainly appreciate it having toenails after that. I can only imagine for fingers
Every single person in the whole world that's here. Just all of us went
I gave the sensory overload warning. It was fair game
Um sensory overload I think is like if you were to dance while singing
Not like hey, this is disgusting. I just got right. Oh, I got a rune
Great rune of the unborn. Oh, that's um, very lucarious, isn't it?
I got dragon cult prayer book. What do you do with that? Because i'm kind of
Using the dragon thing
I think you can now
raft stuff
All right. Where is this? Uh
Oh, yeah
Yeah, maybe like a gross out warning not a sensory overload
I gotta say I feel bad that everyone is upset that I told them something bad happened to me and not like
Sensory they don't they don't feel bad for me sensory overload here about it
No sensory overload is if you were like, hey, just want to tell you sensory overload. I got a story to tell you
So when I was uh, again, you know what I mean? That's that's sensory overload
You didn't see what I did
But that to me is sensory overload
Where the fuck are we going? Where's the entry or like if you started like doing like spells and like flashing a bunch of stuff
On the screen and if I started doing spells
Yeah, if you were casting spells and like and they were like screams and like sound effects sound effects sound effects
I use the wrong term. Hold on this
Come on here. We have a problem. What we have a double boss scenario here. Oh god
I think we focus the one on the right first
Uh there the boss does not care that we're doing this
Okay. Well that was good
That actually saves us a lot of pain and suffering
Did we get any other guy we could just I can hit him with a dragon breath
Okay, go for it. Oh my god
Insta-dej, I never even got up
Where the hell did I just end up?
It's okay. We can serve him from the spawn
You just like you just changed you just changed the weather and it just fucked me up so bad. Oh, sorry
Really
No, it does not are you serious
Are you serious? I don't want to laugh because it's like kind of like not good if that's happening to you
I don't want to like laugh. But are you all right? I don't have uh,
I don't have anything else to eat
Dude you all right. Can I tell you what you really should do tonight?
just
Like make some like just rice just make some rice
And eat a little bit of rice and like some toast and don't eat anything else
Don't eat any more backpack daisy food
Whoops, but I rest it so I probably reset it. I don't know where you are. You did
Oh great. I don't know why I didn't spawn at this long
Because I definitely
Dude, you were fighting the whole time then you were like doing good. I actually was doing well
I had him down to like 40 34 35 percent. Honestly, we have to fight him fight them both again
We have to kill this. How about we just don't
This is a boss. You should like heal
Don't worry about me and worry about the fucking like diarrhea. You're gonna have in 40 minutes
Beware of the scarlet rot
Wow, you're not doing too well
Have I died?
I don't see a death thing on the screen
Well, congrats
You were just waiting just you were waiting like is low
Mo like is dead
All right. Oh, okay
Wow
Oh, that's what that is
Am I not how am I not hitting this person because uh, because he had made a grab animation so you can't oh
He was using he was like he's like using a door
I could reset it again. I we're not quite dead yet
It could be it could be much worse right now
It's a really bad place for him to be doing this
Come over here. Come over here. I had I got the heal ready. I don't
It's just
I'm helping i'm helping come on
focus
You're not focused
I gotta get that down. He keeps doing it
He's doing power
Watch out for his ultimate power
Oh fuck he comes down with it
I'm gonna go reset it
We haven't lost yet
Yeah, but this isn't going well. It's we had he's at 50 percent. It's we're okay
I mentally give up
Mentally you can't give up
Don't give up
Don't give up. Don't give up
Sora
Just imagine this is millennia
You know what I mean? This is my millennia
I hate this enemy
All right. I'm gonna be honest if I had like
Stir with 10 fucking effort. We would probably have already beat this
That's fucked up
How do I get out run?
Fucking sigma
You reset I had
you
Okay, I only had like a few I had you reset it and I was still fighting the enemy
So I lost out on like four heals because you reset it the first time
Okay, we'll come back
I can't
So you can't no
Then why was I able to come back?
Maybe you're the host
You can do it
I took this boss's health down
like
70 percent
Yeah, but he just like spams
Like he doesn't even play the game like right
You know what I mean? Yeah, that's definitely like a like a soul caliber fan take
Okay
That missed me and you saw it you saw that it missed it actually kind of looked like it did
Okay, can you take this seriously?
He's also I guarantee you this dude's gonna drop nothing
There's a there's a if you look down at your controller
As I um
I wasn't doing this for a little while the first like a little bit that I was playing but if you look down
There's a red b button and if you press that you dodge
um
You should press that when there's like a right at the moment right before you get hit
I just didn't know if you know i'll try but my game crashed
Fuck so bad. My game crashed mine's crashed too
Well, let's try it again last time somebody gave you that advice germa. You growled at them. Yeah, I know
Why that's why I thought it was
No, I really did
I was fighting that lightning tree sentinel outside the city and I was having some trouble
And the person's like what they say was hey, dude
I don't know if you know this but the horse has a dodge and I just I just it just did it
I just I went off
Uh, I think my game is actually broken
Uh mod bat. Yep, not the that's the one I just did
Well, I'm in it's almost like the process is still going hold on. Yeah. Elden ring is still technically running
Coming back. I'm sorry to bring it up again, but I really gotta say
I feel like I ate that pork and I got away with it and there's kind of a thrill
Okay, uh, you say that now and in potentially a few hours from now
On your fourth vomit into the toilet. You're gonna be like that was a dumb thing
I ate it yesterday afternoon. I think if I was gonna get sick, I'd be sick by now
that's true
I really feel like like I fucking
You know like
I played the gamble and I won
Don't get used to that. Don't get used to oh, yeah
You know what? Uh, if I that means I could probably do that again and be completely and totally fine
No, you lucked out big time. Wasn't there some youtuber who used to like eat shoes?
I have no idea
that's
I don't know. That's your justification for this. It's like no, no, no, no
You see there's a guy that used to eat shoes
Uh, what is his name?
What's his name shoe night?
He named himself after what he ate
All right. You ready to fight? Yeah. Yeah, let's like like focus the guy the easy guy in the right
Full he says stir you could have worms and you might not know it
You know, hey, do you like fucking cooked it? Do you doesn't matter? Do you like garlic?
Are you telling me that worms are immune to heat?
Worms don't like garlic is the thing i've heard. I don't know. It's I think worms actually don't like garlic
That's real, right? I heard worms don't like your fucking stream, dude
Let me heal you. You could save flasks. You know what I mean? Like a greater heal right here
Hey
Hello
How did I get hit by that? How are you 20 bucks?
You just randomly like yeah 20 bucks
Where is he going?
Can you hold his aggro for a sec it's it's happening right now do whatever you want to do
Okay. Well if he hit me
He's looking at me
You hit him harder. He's like doesn't care that you're doing this
How much do you shut the fuck up?
Hi up
Dude, look at this dps. We've already done
I ran in front of him
No, he's angry with you. Oh
Ace two ace two dude
All right, dude, we got this
Just saw a fucking strategy guide on this shit
They said it's actually
You gotta avoid you gotta like there's a dodge button. It's b on the controller right before you get hit
You gotta press it
Oh, look at that. I did it
Where the fuck is he going?
This is I
I think he's stuck
That's actually he's kind of bad because yeah, he'll do that
watch out
Dude, he's coming for you, dude
You get some hips in while he's focused on me
I'm gonna get hit by this but sorry
I went in the wrong part
Why did that take me so long to get up?
Uh, it hit me really weird. I don't know what happened. The choke is real right there. You're running. There's one ahead of him
Oh my god
He's gonna grab you. No, he's not you dude. You're writing his fucking ma dude. He's got you with the next one
You're so fucking bad
last hit
easy
Hey, by the way, you're
You are so fucking happy that this just happened because I just got an ability
I got a thing that you
Are going to be obsessed with and by you. I mean me get an item
This is probably the best trinket in the whole game
maximum hp stamina equipment load
Disgusting. Oh dude, is that the fucking the one with the talisman with the thing?
I get plus two equipment load plus two stamina plus two max health
best trinket in the game is
Stir whatever you do. Don't put the garlic next to your butthole. The worms might crawl even deeper
I didn't say that on my stream. I just want to make sure everyone knows you didn't okay
All right. So so true my friend
we
Getting into the capital is interesting from here. I hope I hope they respond
They actually might
Okay, so there's a few ways to get into the capital
But we could also your favorite you want to let's do the archery
Go to the outer wall battleground and let's do the archery. Actually. Yeah, can we do it from there?
Why are all these hills so dang close range?
Because it'd be really powerful if you could just do that and heal everybody
Sorry, I assumed you didn't know tv dinners were pre-cooked. I thought stir was just eating a soggy hungry man. No
No, that's not. Yeah, that's
In fact, I would I don't think there's anything wrong with that
Like that's all right. Why why would it be a soggy hungry man? We're like like I would still cook it
All right, let's do the archery soggy cooked. Yeah, i'm saying that that wouldn't be that big of a deal
That wouldn't be a problem to me. You're talking to somebody that actually really genuinely does not
hate
Those salisbury steak tv dinners and I talked about this already and everyone was like what the fuck is wrong with you?
There I they're okay. I don't hate those
That whole meal is soggy. Do you like sushi?
Very occasionally. Yes
Wrong I like
I
Hey, hey convince me. Otherwise
Can you convince me? What what do they do to sushi?
they
Cut it up and they put it over a thing of rice or in a roll. They don't like they don't do they don't do anything
Some depends some places do correct me if i'm wrong. Some places do like steam it right for like a certain amount of time
um, if a traditional sushi is just they
just fish
Sometimes they'll freeze it
Like if I didn't want to cook I wouldn't eat
You know what I mean?
sushi is
Okay
I don't like eating a lot of it if you get oh, this is a salmon roll
All right, cool. Let me let me have one. Ooh, that's pretty fresh. That tastes really good
Okay, wait, but what's up? You got a spicy tuna roll there. Oh, no. Yeah, i'll take one. That's raw. That's gross
I'm gonna eat like raw fish
It tastes good. I can't cook a pork and you can eat raw fish
um
If you it's not about the foodborne illnesses that you can get from sushi as long as it's prepared correctly
It's yeah, you can
But the difference that you and you trust the sushi guy you go to at the mini mall
I'm not going to a mini mall to get sushi. Where did you get that from?
a mini mall
the fucking
the uh gas station
No, i'm not
Okay
I know that there are people that say hey do not do not dog. Oh my again. Oh
My vorus my least favorite enemy
I'm stir
Yeah, look who's on the ground gift shit, oh having a good time down there
Are you?
Looks like someone's trying to kill you
I'm alive. Don't worry
Hey worry about yourself
Okay, i'm gonna go over here and worry about myself then I thought we were a team
Uh, but sushi
What sushi no, I said, but sushi
It's good
It's good, but I have to really really be in the mood. I'm only gonna have a few pieces
I know some people that are like, oh, yeah, like give me like five different roles. I'm gonna eat all of it
No, i'll have some not that much
Really like to hit you with that but whatever
Oh my goodness
He was targeting you with that at first
He did
You hit me with the first two. This is so
Unsatisfying to not be able to keep hold right now. You have no idea
I just want to keep hold
You say keep pulse one more time
And I swear i'm going to
Leave this fight
Who needs you?
Oh looks like somebody got hit there, right?
Looks like somebody. Oh somebody got hit twice. Oh, I wonder if you're gonna get hurt time
Maybe three stars third time to charm out. No, look at you. Look out for that. Hey watch out
He's coming in again
Don't worry star. Don't worry buddy. I'll beat the boss for us. Don't worry
I'll be back
You so badly want me to lose so you can scream at me. I can feel it. I can feel you just going like
Boy, i'd like my 20 in ones, please you beat it. Is he still here?
Have you beat it? I beat it. Okay, cool
I have one in the bathroom. I'm feeling so good. All right, let's go. Oh, I got 80
Pick up your souls. That's 80 000. All right
I was talking to you the whole time too. Did you bring your headphones to the bathroom? I mine are wired
I don't want the government fucking listening into my gamer talk. I was talking so much shit, dude. It was
I was like, oh, yeah, what about this? What about that? You were just gone you left
Yep, you know that goes with the uh, the good old saying how do you get bullied on the internet?
Just fucking turn the monitor off. I didn't even know
You were just talking. I actually was talking to nobody
I wasn't even talking to chat. I was just like
I feel like that means I win
It kind of does mean that
Yeah
No, that's all right. I still beat the boss
It's called a uh, that's called a parry reversal
Do we need a great rune to do this?
You cannot proceed without more great runes
Oh
I'm doing plus one more great rune. Do we actually need more?
Yeah, I believe we need two
We both have one
Can you drop them?
And just the same one I just I got the same one you did the unborn
Yeah
Okay again, I think we actually have to go back to millennia unless we could go
Where could we go?
What about k-lid is there anything in k-lid we could do
oh just random like tomes and tombs and
It's just random, right?
It has seemed like this run is weighted a little bit to drop better stuff at more important bosses
Oh, that's right. They're a tree. Let's do the ear tree
the
One tree the one that's right here
Okay. Hmm
the ronnie quest
Also, I have like all the ronnie items
We could have a little doll ronnie. I have the finger blade. I have
The servetus helmet. I i've got so much shit from it
I don't know
I don't know where it's used when it's used why it's used or what the fuck she's talking about and why she wants the world
To be in darkness, but I am there for it
Um, I feel like every few months I try to remind myself exactly what the hell is going on in this game
And I always just kind of get stuck again where I go. Wait, what actually the fuck is happening?
And then I watch uh baddie videos like three hours and then I go. Oh, that's right
I know everything and then I forget all of it in like a week
Uh, all right. So yeah, that was never a boss down here. It was just I guess technically it's just this group
And the stuff in the
And
alo scythe
That's a good item
carrion glint blade staff
Oh, I found a faith talisman
Plus 10 mine i'm not doing it again. Oh, no, this is potency of incantations
I think that actually that i'll take that i'll take that I can't I don't think I can drop this
All right. I don't think you can drop these drop it drop it
Drop it drop it
I can
You're welcome
Ooh, whoo. Who's gonna wear this I think
This is how I already had one. I already had one and it wasn't equipped
Nice. Oh, isn't there a cave like right here? I think there is
It is somewhere here, where is it check the cookbook recipes
Yeah, but we can't craft anything without the crafting item the thing that you get in the first minute
Crafting item they don't seem random. They all seem the same
It seemed like the uh, the first guy at the church of ella was selling the crafting thing no matter what really
Yeah, I bought it from him
I have a voodoo doll of you. What should I do? Um, can you just like I don't know
Put it in front of like the air conditioner on like, you know, like 70 degrees and just let me just chill there
Come on, man. What are you thinking? Oh, it's a view. I don't get one
typical
Just make speaking of him instead
Okay, can you open up my voodoo doll and like see if there's anything in like the stomach?
Yeah, can just like yeah open up the summer part. See if there's any worms in there
but like carefully
Ow you popped your pimple you
Say it that dog is very angry
We uh, I mentioned this before all right story
So if somebody was casting like negative magical spells against me
But there were other people casting positive magical spells against me. They kind of just run into each other, right?
They run into each other like it's I mean if somebody's doing like magical spells to make me feel bad
But people are also casting magical spells to make me feel good
Wouldn't it just be the answer? The answer is very obviously
There's gonna be 99 dudes casting positive vibes on you and the one dude's gonna cast negative and that's gonna be like a critical
No, I don't think so
Ooh, that's good. I have so many comments azor
Those are thing i'm faith now that dude
Give it up. Give it up. This is the comment of the year so far. We are describing
YouTube comments
Yeah, that's what that's what I thought it was like in reference to no, what do you mean?
I thought you were doing like a like my twitch chat like sends posi vibes and some people send no no no no
I'm talking about like actually casting spells
Oh, well, like what kind of spells are they are they pagan rituals? I don't know
Uh, are they a cult? Um
Something else demonic in nature. I could help you with this
But I need to know specifics
So what what should I like wear to like get the negative spells away again?
It depends what kind of spells they are just like okay, let's general like
General negative spells what you should you should wear. Um garlic
Uh, i'm gonna say old navy. All right wear of ruin of protection. Yeah, the the infamous curse this
Penis curse
I remember
I was pleading with chat to have the whatever
pleading with god
Take it back. It's so small. Why didn't you just make me a woman?
Do you do you ever hear that story when I was getting cursed? No
Somebody somebody somebody came into the chat and they were like, hey dude
I'm like casting a small penis curse against you and I was like, well, all right, somebody's cast want to make it bigger
It's all is that what this is trying to see if it's like evening out and I was like
But then I was like wait half of you shouldn't half of you do want because what if it goes too far
What if they're like, oh we all have to do this because we have to help him
That would be bad
Uh, I don't know if I can help you with this
Just sounds like this just sounds rough rough situation to be in
Any like updates on how it's been going? I'm just saying what spells they're casting at me
All right, are we?
are we
You can like open up my character sheet and see what like I have against me right now
I don't like this slob
I don't think this one has very much health
Does not
You would think I was getting hit less if my character didn't scream so loud
Actually kind of true
Like why doesn't your character like scream at all?
And my character is like a 13 syllable scream. I think my character does just not as loud
Well, all right, so we need to figure out what the hell we're gonna do here
I'm just following you thinking about I don't know if I could help you with this curse situation
We need another great rune
But doing even doing ronnie's quest will not give it to us because it's probably gonna be a random item
We need to just find random shit
Hey, dude, are you gonna shove an entire remembrance up your ass? Uh
I don't want to give that meme any more attention that I already have but like that was
But like that was like humorous enough for me to read it
All right. What about we go in this cave?
Anything for you in my leash? All right teleport to the outer wall phantom tree
You've already voted to warp to this destination and we can kill we could try milania again
But I feel like that's gonna give us
both headaches
Um
I'll heal you. Okay rewarp. Try it again
Bye hints. I'm not gonna cast any spells, but instead i'm praying for your salvation and hopes our lovely lord above will forgive you
And well, I appreciate that though like that's
That that that should help right?
I wasn't listening
No, thanks. Thank you
All right
All right. So from here we're going down
To this cave just because I feel like going
Hey, hey, buddy. Hey
Yeah
For the guild for the guild
I got the flame of frenzy. I could do it if I wanted to
I have enough faith
Get three finger me
I could
We gotta go down there
Don't jump. It's gonna get you hurt
What do you think about uh
Go to milania. No
Do you know what I think?
And I don't think I ever saw this in like an elden ring video
But it always it's always the thing that's like, huh that has me thinking
Yeah, is that the uh
So the giants don't have heads because their faces are in their bodies
You're dead. How did you die? I don't I honestly don't even fucking know what happened
I guess I just got
Electrocuted like over on I don't know
Okay. Hey, welcome back. You're talking about giants. Yeah, so the giants don't have heads their faces are inside their stomachs
Okay, and then I I also had like this weird thought I was like, okay
Well, what if their brains in a different spot and their brain is in their hands?
That's why when you hurt the giant's hands, that's this weak spot
Because like the three fingers and the two fingers is obviously like it's like a giant sized hand
I was like dude, what if these are just like giant brains?
They do have that they do have heads
Uh, I mean the two fingers and the three fingers obviously a part of the same hand
I think that's you could probably argue that
Uh part of the same hand that maybe split up and oh we have two different
Philosophies or something. I don't know the whole hand. Maybe the dlc will put the hand together possibly
Maybe there'll be other full hands hands are a big thing in this game the hand enemies and stuff
There are other two fingers, but that they're probably maybe the other three fingers
They were probably all i'm just saying normally enemies weak points is like hit the enemy in the head
But the giant is like oh shit hit his hand
Hey, easy shield enemy. Oh head
I've got a special special enemy down here
What's your favorite haichu flavor
My favorite haichu haichu
Flavor the fuck are you saying? What is your favorite haichu flavor?
Can I get an example?
You just okay. So the the answer to the question is i've never eaten one of these before
Like haichu like you're sneezing like my favorite sneeze mine's mango. I like peach
Haichus suck
What do you know? They don't height to me and I gotta i'm a big fan of this company
I'm a big fan of these but haichus are if starburst gave a shit you come down here
I'm just saying and I love starburst. I love to go to anime conventions and eat pocky
Those are good strawberry, uh strawberry and cherry
uh starburst
Our our s plus
But i'm sorry
I feel like they haven't innovated in the game at all
The classics need to innovate. Well, hold on a minute. Look, what about what about rices?
Look at all the different rices there are there's so many different innovative new rices and they're actually pretty good are there
Oh, yeah, i've never seen one think of all the innovations that have happened in rices
like what
Peanut butter rices that's that's a big skeleton rices thins
That is a huge skeleton. Let me see if he's paying attention
Hey
Hey, who did that?
Okay, how come he doesn't lack the whole game?
What the birds do? Um
We need to get out of here
Who fucking hit him?
I don't think we fight this. I think we just go
One little bone
on the tree branch
Let's go
Do you know what else is really interesting about elden ring lore never hear anyone talk about this? Sure
You know a lot of people pronounce the word three and they can't speak english. They say tree
So anything it's interesting they have the tree fingers and how important the uh, the urn tree is
Wait, did you go say that again? I just I
You you say
What tree?
Don't worry about it. It's kind of above your pay grade
Um, but okay, but what about gideon?
What about him if gideon said three fingers he'd go. Oh, you've probably seen the tree fingers
What are you talking about? Well, not everyone pronounces it that way
Like some say cost some say cost cost some say cost
Grand does eyes grand does eyes people say three and some people say tree
Like you once did for the vacuous rom
the oh
Knowing armor
Okay, we need to go through
Got him. I did so much damage
Why don't we just do the thing just drop down and kill him from the top?
This is like the easiest way to kill these
Do it then
Can you like move him a little bit towards you like aggro me over?
Hey, did you know if you hit the top of it? Yeah
Just pull them this way
I'll get him i'm stuck on this ant. Why do you look like a half-cooked hot dog?
Um, I don't know bro fucking fuck off
Whoa
I got him. Oh i'm doing so much damage
Hey, hey, hey group up guilty guilty group up
Good always gonna make sure you that you can be prepared for anything. So that means you're pretty good healer
Yeah, okay. So we got a
Is there another wall shadow priest?
There's another wall somewhere, right? There's gotta be another wall. There's always another wall
Found it
Watch out slugman
Oh, isn't this where the big ass little thing is?
This one here isn't this uh, isn't this the well in dark souls, too?
uh
No, I would make this more aligned with the um, the big tree in dark souls one
The big tree the tree what's it called? Yeah, no great great something great the big tree
Yeah, I missed that area. No, you didn't i've like watched you play it
I act the the like those like secret tree area. That's like it's not even secret way off to the side
I I played and saw dark souls one so many times before I realized that area existed. I'm like
I'm telling you i'm a fraud
I think you just
Want to beat stuff so quickly that you just don't care if you miss something
No, it's not you're you're misrepresenting me right now. I could take you to court. Yeah, but what would you even what would you sue me for?
Defamation watch out big guy in here. This is the isn't this the right? This is the same
This is the correct enemy that's supposed to be in here
Is it?
I think so
I'm pretty sure this is what's actually in here. I thought he was gonna kill me in one hit
He's got so much lighting on him. It's hard to see where he is
Nice
I got the glaive of gilgamesh
I got the seedbed curse
Stay away from me
Ah, I got a remembrance actually did you really that's good. You know the omen king
You know him, you know who that is the omen king
Uh, is that bog?
Or is that margott?
You really you need to go watch three more hours of videos
I believe you're talking about morgott
I feel like i'm hitting you with lore that you never even considered before
And you're just you don't even remember like anything. No, I i'm telling you
I was obsessed with all this game's lore everything about it. I just loved every second of it
You got me wrong
And you never even considered it was the tree fingers
Okay, just go do double get double teach and kill millennia enough to level up. Okay. Well, this one doesn't open yet. All right, so
That's how we get to here
This thing doesn't open yet
We can't get into the capital
We can't we have to beat millennia
We have to
I mean, I guess I think we're kind of have to just I think we have to kill millennia
I think we gotta kill millennia unless we just did random like catacombs and stuff to try to find a run
Uh, what's um
You know the whole like upside down tower ronnie's quest thing thing. Yeah, I I have the device
You want to go to it we kept saying we have all the ronnie shit and the finger blade
All right, i'm mark to ronnie. Yeah ranala or remi. All right, what does she want me to call her?
Uh, let's go to ronnie's rise. Yeah, is she even there? Do we have to talk to servetus man?
Um, I don't does she move because she goes to sleep forever and she's just totally just like this part of the game's boring
Wake me up when it's over. I don't know. Yeah
Uh, can we do that funny thing that we did before where we pitch our voice down one tiny notch
Keep it on permanently until like people just leave
Yeah, uh sounds pretty good. Okay. I think you're pitched a little bit too a little a little too low
Yeah, a little higher than that. Um
Uh a little higher no lower. I mean then it's not on at all. Okay, so I I can do something
Wait, oh, I don't I don't want to do that. I almost just ruined our whole playthrough
Did you just like hit her in the head with a sword? No, I almost just did the
Weird quest thingy where like isn't that I don't got administered drought. What's that?
Like you give her like a fucking poison. I yeah, I think I could like kill her or something. Okay
I'm not going over there. Okay. She uh, do we get on stairs and blade is like you took my waifu and we kill him
I think it happens later
I think that happens after you burn the tree and I can we get your best like wolf snarl
That was a bird but it was a decent attempt. All right. What what did she say?
Uh, she says she also has to go on a journey and she I think she gives you the doll
I think we gotta go talk to the other tower guy. Don't we have to talk to the doll at a certain place?
underground somewhere
Uh, yeah the other like nocturn sit dude. This quest is so fucked. What do we have to do for like why are we doing this?
Why did I bring this up again?
We're trying to get a rune trying to engage in my interest. I was just he likes pretending to be like a wolf
We can't what if I give them like an easy one? It's probably the wrong one. There's another one, right?
Or is it there is the third tower?
Isn't that the one is the three tower sisters? Oh like the three fingers
Remember?
Yeah, I do the three fingers
Do you think there's any significance?
Um, I don't know. Do you want to like no clip and fly around this area for like 16 hours? Let's kill those dragons
Oh, here's here's the land six. Is that someone I should know? This is one of the other
Dragons that you fight secretly. Oh, who is this one of the other dragons?
This is the placid eucach's
I don't know. I don't I don't know. It's one of these like the blood. He's just one of the dragons
Jumping he he'd teleport it
To where I don't know. Is this like monster hunter? You got to go like find his next area
I mean the help are still on the screen
Oh shit, just got the urn tree great shield. I think he's gone
No, is he only here like at night time or something? They have like a day change make him go. Bye. Bye
He's about to respawn
Go to the entrance of the three sisters
I actually don't remember
Not over there
Butthead. Oh, I found the service man tower accept the task
He handed over the potion in question, which was three smithing stone
And then you need nefali to drink the potion. I actually have the potion. I think I have denied it
She was like, I don't want to drink that I'm I'm fucking gluten-free or whatever
Oh my god, he looks fucking
He looks like shit
Okay, thanks for the golden rune, okay, I have that potion yeah
Okay
Rock blaster
Explosive ghost flame
Ooh night comet night comets actually really good. Isn't it for you? I'm not doing magic anymore. Oh
Yes, so i'm gonna kill this guy kind of a dick get it. Oh, this is where petri dish is
Uh pidea
Great rune really? No, I was gonna say come on. Why didn't I get none?
All right. Well now what?
Reload the area. I'm talking a pity. Um, I don't we don't gotta kill the dragon
Did you go down here did right? Did you go down? My minimap is my map is wrong, man
Oh, I think you're inside here. We can just teleport somewhere. I just wanted to see what he was selling
Why are you doing that? I ate this weird raw pork chop. I heat it up
Was there for like 16 hours?
Oh, haha. I figured it would be all right
Living my life story now
All right
We need to go somewhere and we need to figure out we need to get a another rune or we need to actually just go
Let's go kill. Let's go millennia. Let's go
Let's do it. Oh, he said let's go
Millennia, let's do it millennia
Where's the right bonfire? Let's go get millennia. Where's pidea? Am I in the right spot for pidea?
I was just kind of jumping around
No, you gotta like fall off the edge. There's like a
Castle. Yeah, somebody behind you
Behind here is right here. I know this item's
Behind one of these could be a great run behind I never found this person
Really? No. Wow. What a loser you are. I thought you played this game
Yeah, how does it feel? Pretty good
Dude i've never been down here. Holy shit
Cool. All right. Are you ready to fight?
Millennia and have us both rage quit the stream in about 30 minutes
I say that we um for the prediction. I think we could do it in like 60 tries
Do you have any runes? Yeah, I need 4 000
Hey you your runes
Give them to me. Yeah, it's kind of just like gold farming
You should be you should pretend to be mad at stir
He'll hear he doesn't pretend
All right. You ready to just kind of bang our heads against the wall for a little bit?
Okay, if we do it
We just I think we've been playing for a while. We warmed up a lot
I mean this was six hours in if we're gonna do it. We're gonna do it right now
I actually know how to dodge now
All right. So where is the good place to go to?
Uh, hey bro, did you forget the whole game too? Nice. Yep. I don't know. I feel like one of these
Yes tall
Will they beat millennia in 10 tries?
Hmm I that's possible. I wonder we'll see let me make sure I got the right gear on millennia is slash, right?
I believe law of regression heals all ailments that should get rid of scarlet rot in case we get you know bad pickle
Is all gonna be heavy
All right. So points are in we have 10 real attempts. Are you ready? Yep. All right, let's go soldiers for the guild
We've been trying to clear this raid for a month
We have the big guilds have already done it
We're the last ones. We're not trying to get world first or anything. We're just trying to just participate
They're out gearing us
Which is making making them they're getting more loot in the chinese new year event
They spent plenty of time developing
Okay, just to get dropped from china. All right. All right. All right. Are you ready? You're right
Wait
Waiting i'm hitting her
You are
Every time I jump she dodges
I i'm fucking i need a brain for a second. I'm stuck in a fucking lamp post
I like glint stone pebble better here
She can go up anytime. Yeah
Oh
Excellent. Good job. Excellent
My fucking button clicked in this stupid button the button clicked in and it's a crouch
literally
the
worst place for a fucking crouch
I
Left stick push in his crouch. Do you know how much people grip this fucking game and they like, you know
How many times that happens?
Just just trying some stuff seeing how it goes
learning
Didn't you rebind it? Oh, yeah, this is a whole nother game client
not the
Original game client. Oh and I gotta go unbind crouch to the left stick
Do you ever have that problem?
No, where like you you're pushing down on like running around and you and you click in the left stick because you're pushing down hard
And this bullshit happens never done it. I've been there somebody says it
I believe that it's a thing
And what these controllers really need is a mind detector
We could just get a little bit closer to the user's intent. Hold on a second. This is all fucked up
Okay, that's better. I feel like switching to faith was a meme
Okay, i'm better
And I am objectively worse than our last fight
I don't think so. I think we're okay
You're doing pretty well
Until I press the fucking left stick in
You know, it kind of reminds me of when
hitting
uh
Light attack and forward was kick in some of the other games
Yeah, I did that quite a bit
in my personal opinion
Get anything bound off the movement button
Okay, that one was uh, it was a good attempt. Yeah, we're good. We're good a little bit of a controller issue didn't count
Oh, you would just go for the caster
Wow, that was my bad. I didn't even realize that at first that you changed targets. That was not a good attempt. All right
Dude, like glintstone pebble
It's the best spell in the game
What are you using now?
Now I got like lightning bolt and she can actually dodge it because it doesn't track at all. So glintstone pebble is
gone
Uh, well i'm faith skilled now
I distinctly remember us having an argument about this very subject
Did we?
edgar alan poe
I distinctly remember
us
Squabbling over this very very subject
He's disassociating
So that's a fight for Lydia
He thinks he's gonna play
Maybe it'll help did we I don't remember talking about it
Here I am hit me
Let us go up the elevator
Brother there's an arrow in your back
Hello millennium
I'm here
Excellent first maneuver
Although I seem to have dodged quite a few of them
Pressing the attack I see
That I didn't do it
Yeah
Yeah, you did
Yeah, it also did more damage
But what that buffered so hard
We do so much less damage now because it's because she's scaling no, is that what it is? No, she's scaled to
The room that she's in i'm just saying that my lightning deals less damage than my glintstone pebble did and it's harder to hit her with it
She's gonna dodge it every time
Unless she's a big dumb dumb
Let her get me
Be scaled to have lower health if anything
Phase two is is if phase one is giving us some trouble already phase two is gonna be such a pain in the ass
Um, I think i'm bad
Uh, and i've got 100 fizz mitigation shield was letting me just live through the uh, the flurry
So maybe I should put one on too
I figure even if she hurts me and she does heal from hitting you but like as long as I don't
Fucking insta die
I'm just gonna i'm just gonna sword no magic
I can use my greater heals. Actually, let me go back. Oh you already jumped. I mean, I thought I thought I was
Holding you up
I have a few magic flasks. You know what? You know what? Let's yeah, let's just reset it. Let's go. No, no, no
No, okay. Yeah, let's just let's just reset. Let's just reset
Reset it. I gotta move some gear around
That doesn't count. That doesn't that's not a real attempt
Yeah, our reset doesn't count. That's not fair
We have to traverse the fog door for it to be a real attempt
I called it before I jumped down
Sour boys
Because I have three fucking mana flasks. I don't need
How heavy is it?
It's way too heavy
I think I just had to be good
Okay, you ready?
I don't know how many weapons you've like considered using and how much stuff you've done and i'm seriously still like
How we just happened to work?
I don't know that did a lot of damage here. I'll use uh, I have the healings still equipped
I can use before the door
Yeah, don't heal yourself
I think the dog is
Right behind us
Thank god
Did that not get you?
I think it did I can't tell
dead
The other one was the lord's heal
Lord sworn
Okay
No disrespect to the battle mercies out there, but really let's go balls out
Don't waste all your stamina bar. She could go up at any time
Let's go
Hi
Fucking i'm
What what was that?
Dude that okay. Somebody help me that like
Like how do you do you dodge through it or to the left right? How do I do get how do I do that?
That like da da da da da da da
So if you dodge forward to the right or forward it's in and then to the right so it's forward right
Right and then back. I think it's in yeah, it's in and to the right
Wait
I just saw you
Kicking up a little a little flame there. It looks like you were doing are you going for some parries here?
Are you alive?
Yeah, I don't know. It is
I forget like what she does that you can parry
And then you still have to parry her three times
You can parry waterfowl
Good luck. You did you die? Did you actually just do that much damage to me? We're just trying to get by man
We're just trying to get by
How's that not hurting her it's being real weird
She could do it
Be aware
I'm so paranoid. Yeah
Easy easy, dude. No fucking damage
What really?
Jumping me nice dodge get her
Watch that she could go up
Where's the stagger? All right. Oh, what the fuck
What the fuck we're good. Watch that rot. She's being extra careful. She's on me
What the fuck is my character doing?
dude
She grabbed me from fucking behind again
She was going for you and she fucking grabbed me
I rolled like into it. It's just there's so much shit happening on the fucking screen
I just like forget that she even has that fucking move
This character sucks
Uh, she heals when you block by the way, apparently. Yeah, I I know
She kills you when you don't dude
I in my I told you my normal playthrough
I killed her with mimic tear and the whole time my shot was like dude
She heals when she hits the mimic tear and I just fucking just kept jumping on her until she died
Sometimes you gotta take the l to get the dub. I beat her with tish. I just let tish fight her
I was like, I don't even care you saved stir. That was literally a get down. Mr. President
Oh my god, dude
I can't I can't i'm stuck. I'm stuck. I can't I can't anakin. I'm too weak. I can't
All right, dude, are we ever gonna be able to do this?
Yeah
I mean we're good until you got one shot by a grab. Hey, but you what I stopped you from getting one shot by the grab
I don't think it looked like that on my screen
because I I
Don't feel like I was in danger
You know, maybe i'm wrong do you need a great heal? Oh no, you're in there
Okay, I mean we're either gonna do it or we're not I don't think the extra 20 15% health is gonna be a problem
I mean if you had a little bit more health last time
I mean she did it was like almost 100%
Heal
Yeah, i'm gonna start hitting her right away
And she's probably gonna go from here
Yep
Oh Jesus she went to you. I'm good
Afraid that she's gonna do it. That was a weird jump
Oh, come on
Come on we gotta do this to the fucking guild
You know, you know what?
I think fighting together makes it harder because it's almost like she's going after you
But like I get hit by her hitbox sometimes
Oh, I was wondering why I wasn't healing. I was praying. I was pressing the neo heal button from like the last 20 seconds
Now germa's blaming me what it is. It is kind of fucked up that you're blaming me. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
Don't let chat tell you something that didn't happen. I just said that it's almost like fighting her solo would be easier
So do you want to you want to take turns? No
I feel like that is saying that i'm it's my fault
No, no, no, i'm just saying that that I by my presence is making it harder for you
He's dragging you down, dude
I mean i'll let you go in
Solo for a bit
All right, let me go in in solo
And I will tell you if I need your help, okay, and then you can come in full health and shit
Wait a minute. This could be genius
If you need me, but you won't need me. All right, so if I need you
I'm gonna call you in you're gonna be full health refreshed
Yeah, all right. I'm just gonna be in the locker room
All right
I'm going in
Okay
The forces of diablo grow stronger
Hey, yeah, I was in just a bad spot for it. Um
Oh, yes, come on in dude
Yeah, I got this
I was just in a bad spot. Oh, good luck. Let's try dude. I gotta get a shield on
Just block the first one roll the next one. She's an idiot
Who cares if she heals a little bit chats could always be like, oh she's fucking she dude. No, she's she's healing
Yeah chat
Why is she? Oh, okay
I mean, I don't think I i'm gonna do the whole place like solo though
Uh, dude, I think it's time. We just bring in two. Oh mega spirit summons and just who gives a shit
Let's get let's get out of here fights yet and you're giving up
I don't why do you want to fight millennia this fight sucks absolute balls like you don't who wants to play this?
Nobody wants to fight this character
Let's get the summons and get rid of this motherfucker
But she heals off the summons
All right, not until the bed. That's fine. And no more screaming. I'm not gonna i'm not i'm not a scream streamer like youtuber. Come on
Settle down. I have a strategy
What if we like
What if we like both fighter?
Yeah, that works that way we can we can try and keep her staggered for longer
If like both of us are hitting her. I mean i'm just saying you you give me the go-ahead i'm going back to the spirit summon
Trainer and i'm just gonna get tish to like plus eight
Who is she? She is the probably the best summon in the game
it's just
Such a good she's so good at everything and she literally killed millennia on by herself. I didn't even do anything when I played it
Okay
Let's let's just try both like to see what happens if we both fight her
Which we've never done before i'll go in first usually you go in first and like curse it
It's true
I don't have a fucking spirit bell
You're playing around with your fucking bell. I thought I thought we were doing this together
I actually thought we were doing this together and like we would stagger her and you wouldn't miss every swing
I didn't even get dude. You went up there and just fucking died. You went up there and died dude. I didn't
Because you're trying to look in your fucking back pocket for queen latifah. Let me out here. Let me out, please
Somebody please let me out
Just fucking kidding
Oh the fight begins
Oh, I feel so alive
Jerma what you don't understand is it's a dance. It's a dance
Which is not even rigged on to beat her
dance
Yeah, how come I don't have a spirit bell because it's an item you gotta get do you have a spirit bell?
How did I not get it?
I mean, oh, it's it's just random that sucks
I think it probably counts as a key item and you could probably get it from somewhere. Hold on. Are we sure that I don't have it?
Wait, wait, wait. I have that rot thing on
Why do I have we both died? Why do I have the wrong thing? That's weird. I just don't have enough mana
That's probably not gonna happen
Just don't die to her like spaghetti
Okay, come on ralphy that's fucked up
Um, where are um, i'm going up you you blocked me
Uh, wait, I can't get it back. Hold on
Hey, you know what? Just reset reset. We gotta no going going going going i'm in
This is coming in too
Here. I got uh, I got the spell. Let me use my spell
oh
So fresh one more one more you beat this game. How are you so bad?
dude
I'm gonna respond to that one real fight real focus if you lose this auto gets it. I'm day
I'm going in i'm in i'm already in where are you?
If she's she doing some jumps going in
Every time you go to attack
She moves the other player
Easy
Yeah, she is kind of easy, huh?
It's very actually very hard. Where were you looking?
I'm, all right, but that was very annoying. I'm incredibly annoyed by it
Okay, hold on. Oh that's what she's doing
Dude, what is she doing?
What is she doing?
I saved you
Little bro doesn't even have his controller plugged in
What are you talking about talking about me man last heal besides slow heal
Damn, she really sick with it
I gotta save him
This is the weird ghost shit
I'm dead. I'm on my head
Dude, i'm going out. I'm going out
I expelled all the air out of my body. It's just fucking I saw stars for one second
It's so hard
Best one yet. That was pretty good. Try your l2. It takes so long. It's not worth it. That was a good attempt
Is it what so the ghost move I somehow dodged every single one?
I don't even know how I did it
She attacked me with every single one
It's just the pillars were in the way and I had no idea when she was casting it. You were in the flow state
You hit trance
You know what i'm saying? I thought we had it there
I know what you're thinking, but it's probably whatever you're trying to say skip the ladder all together
Actually, probably a good idea
I do have the boiled crabs. I feel like it's time to we got to use these
We picked up I used one that fight. We just we picked up so much random shit like it's um, how do you even remember?
I guess i'll put them on the bar
uh
Okay
I tried to hit b to back out of the menu and you saw it happen next. Yeah, you know naturally that's naturally that's how it happens
You just you know, you're pressing b
Can I get one of those heels when I get back up?
Sure, all right. Let me actually put them on the bar because i'll use them and I'd eat them both at the same time
Okay, I have been using my wondrous disease
Remember the one I was gonna go. I was gonna go as long as it took. Do you want some crabs and
Whatever. These are do you want some? Uh, I don't think I need them. I uh, I already had, you know the whole eating, you know
Are they raw?
No, they're boiled. Let's go. I don't want I don't want them
Melania
It's time for you to pay
That was unfortunate, but
My game was lagging so bad during that. I was worried
Oh my god
Thank you. Yeah, that might have just saved me. I was just so
I'm so desperately trying to make it so you all right. I don't want to die here
Okay, i'm coming
Oh god
She turned around to do it to you. I need a second. I'm not with you
All right, be aware of that
Oh fuck
Nice one
She went down
Get her. Okay. All right. All right. Heal up
Heal up and get ready. Heal up and get ready
What wait? I don't she needs one hit
Yes
Okay, uh, I don't have any mana for
repeal
What the heck I dodged it quiet
Let's show her why we're the actual rot boys
I'm covered in rot. I'm covered in rot. It's bad
It's real bad
I'm all right. I'm just eating food over here. I'm buying time for you. I'm not let's go
I would expect the shadows. Yep
She's chasing you hard. Yeah, there she goes
You just run far enough away. It won't get you
I don't think that's accurate though
I can't see shit. Where am I? Yeah same god damn it lock on
Oh, she's doing this bullshit again
She should full heal during that
Oh, no, I didn't know that's what she was doing. I thought she was going towards you with the
Oh, man, I didn't know she was doing that
Fuck. I thought she was doing the thing. She puts the sword in the ground. It does the explosion
Well, good luck
Whoa, wow, what the fuck that's what I thought she was doing
Always assume it's waterfowl. I also
She was aiming at stir figured I could get in there
I got no more heals. This is it. Yes. No, I got one more. This is rough
She's she's just healed
The l2 is insane damage
Yeah
I just I did it once and I must have pressed it again because I did the second part and I really didn't want to and that's
More kind of fell apart for me. That was a really good attempt though. It's unfortunate
Yeah
Or should I have like any other weapon for this? I have a dagger that reduces max hp. What do you mean?
Didn't you have some like fully upgraded faith sword?
Wait, i'm not even faith. Never mind. What is this?
What do you mean?
I use this this is good with no upgrades. No, this is just gonna have to come down to us being gamers. I think
Is it a debuff? I mean, I I don't there's no harm in me keeping it on I could try it see what it does
I'll try it. I went the wrong way. All right, I will tell you i'm getting a little bit of gamer fatigue
A little bit of gamer fatigue. I'm getting a little bit of gamer fatigue
And that's understandable that was just unfortunate what just happened
I mean, it's like it's fine because we're gonna win this one
Make sure that guy with the spear on the stairs
Can you please just like walk a little bit further? I did
I did this fucking worms in you dude. You are you are gamer fatigued
Wait, it's not yes. Not you
we're
What we're what the fuck I was doing a thing where I was gonna come back down and bow to you
All this too, right?
Wow, that's a big heal. Why is that so bad? How much faith do you have?
I have the arcane scaling
Oh
I think told that that would work
Arcane doesn't enhance faith incantations
Okay. Well, I feel like I was asking a lot of a lot of people said yes. Okay, let's see what happens here
Holy shit
Um, excuse me
You wait a minute you mean to tell me I could just sit back and just do that
Oh, you got like the moog sword
It's just doing this weird like dot
How long does it last?
Holy shit. That thing is fucking disgusting
Okay. Well, I didn't that's cool
full weapon
She might go sicko mode soon
I would expect it
Give her her space. She needs her space
Holy shit
I expect it like right now
I can't believe she hasn't done it
Oh my god
What chat doesn't understand is that she's also god-skinned. All right, here she comes. Oh my fucking god
Okay
That's um
That's a full sprint
Fuck
This sucks. It's so fucking hard. I remember hating this just as much as I did before on the regular game
Delete this delete this character from the game delete this character
Uh, I can upgrade the dagger
I really need to switch off faith
I it was it was a bad call. What does this scale with?
It's it's just faith index
Try just go pump this up like crazy
Uh people how much faith do you have? It's you have arcane. Don't you I have like 50 arcane
Yeah, so that way this wouldn't work with you
I'm gonna go upgrade this thing
And i'm gonna
You know what?
Desperate times desperate measures
Here's what we're doing i'm gonna just take a shitload of mana potions i'm gonna go upgrade the knife
And i'm just gonna be a coward dot loser
Okay, i'm gonna go respect back to magic and get my glintstone pebble on because it actually did damage
I need souls though
I could probably sell some shit. I also thought we picked up the uh
Like the blast ray whatever and I got excited but I I don't see it in my inventory
I don't know. Well, I don't have to fight this. Okay, this is kind of your tiring
Yeah, i'm getting the same thing
Oh, it's so spooky
Okay, so
How much better it'll be when it's leveled up
All right 480 I don't care doesn't upgrade the dot do not do this upgrading the dagger does not increase the dot
Come on Miyazaki why did everybody let me do this?
Wait, they told you the faith stuff scales
Wrong like afterwards. I thought the l2 was gonna
I feel like everybody was right, dude
Maybe i'll use this weapon frick
Well, uh, never mind
I'm ready
The l2 will stun lock millennia
That's true, but I can only do it a few times before I need to drink and then I might just die. That's right
Oh frick
Bleed is really strong against millennia. Yeah
What is this?
Weapon that I have big what is this thing? Is this bleed?
Now it's fire
Do I have a bleed weapon?
What a bleed dagger in your other hand
I don't know if I even have one
scarlet rob
um
This thing does it's not too slow though
This would be great
I could do a wheel
Respec a real one. I'm gonna go respect
How many of those tears do I have?
Just because I this is a really dumb idea
I have one I really thought I got the laser beam
I'm doing it. I'm gonna have to live with my what I do here
I'm doing it. You have rivers of blood. I sold rivers of blood for a joke because I said look what i'm doing to the op item
Is it thy wish?
Oh, hold on. I would but
Is this standard?
upgrades stones
Is it somber?
I have one two, three, four five six seven eight. Okay
I can do it. I can get update. I mean uh plus nine
Or plus eight
Why do you keep play this game? It's taking you like a year to complete it
my friend
That we're doing a random. I
You you you responded
um
Uh, uh, geez, um
Oh geez
Does this scale more with strength or dex probably strength? I would imagine 28 18. Okay
Oh, yeah, I forgot that I had the true counter
We win now need arcane
No, I don't
No, the thing already has 70 bleed. It's quality scaling
Was that all right? No, no arcane
Did I put the other two in so I do 22 or?
Go like 30 27. It's quality scaling. Then this is fine, right?
It scales d and both
You're so fucked dude the dagger you dumbass I
We're not we're going for a new strategy. I'm going for just pizza cutter
To see when it's okay. So then this is yeah, this is fine
Like that, uh now I can just go like this boom boom boom, right?
That's fine. This is fine. Hey there pal. Do you have any smithing stones seven?
I probably do
This is uh, this is fine help germa because he's dude. There's fucking like
Thousands of people trying to help germa. I I got nothing
He doesn't need my help. You got this king fucking sleigh
I'm ready
Now I upgrade them seven fuck out of this thing and i'm gonna go
And i'm gonna millennia is gonna turn into swiss cheese
Okay, I need to just get some souls real quick. Where should I go?
Where's that place do we get 10k for doing nothing?
Oh by fia underground let this guy fucking knead his dough
Millennia you don't stand a chance
Millennia you are gonna die
in minecraft
Absolutely power this thing up. What? Oh
Uh, so for this next fight
I was thinking of hiring someone off like a
Like a gamer website to like use like, you know, take control of my pc and play for me
And then you can act like you're doing it
But I just want to let you guys know I decided not to
Very good idea
I actually have a bell bearing to look at
That gamer website
I am i'm ready unless there's a smithing seven
you I
Cannot help you out there
I have up to six just wanted to go the long way
Okay
I wonder how much better this is gonna be. I feel like it's gonna be people are giving me shit for this
But I feel like it's gonna be better
320 this thing look at this
269 119 already
Hold on. Yeah, i'm gonna put the hp flask back in
All right people gonna be really upset with me, but I don't care
Hey, if you're ever indeed of ruins
Just go to where fia is
Walk forward like not towards her but like the other way two seconds you get 11 000
Just reset it and you do it as many times as you want if I ever need runes
I'm just gonna kill milenia
I just wanted to get it easy
first try
All right. I am moments away from being ready for you to put your thing down. We'll try this again
I've got to say maybe maybe like four or five more attempts before I need to eat food
And I need to oh relax and go to this guy fucking eats
food
Okay
All right. All of a sudden you're like into like do a somber smithing stone nine
Uh, that's the ancient one. It is not
Isn't it though? It's not
I don't you have a seven
I don't have a seven, but I am ready for you to put down your thing
Okay, i'm ready
I'm traveling
The manner please come to my world isn't your food gonna taste so much better after we are victorious
And you sit down and you put that fucking that hot cake in your mouth the crab cake
Okay, you got it done
Yeah, he's done
No, no more time for conversation. It's game time
I'm wearing a green shirt today and people will freaking out
All right, look at my new toy
Look at my outfit
all right, uh, I
After seeing that well, I wish us the best of luck
Coming. Yeah, I just I don't even know what the move set is
Neither does she
Look at how much more health I have though
Oh my god
I do miss the uh
I think i'm gonna have time to calm it as well
Oh, I don't even have mana. I didn't get myself mana potions
Exeter's hat
What about my hat?
Uh who wore it best?
You want to go again or with like what's going on here? I'm fine
I've
Haven't fought this boss before
Maybe our worst attempt yet
Just keep her in the corner
i'm dead
Surely it gets better
This thing's fucking awful. This thing is bad
I want her to heal
Yeah, I expected it to deal like
Damage, uh, I don't have any more larval tears. We said this was horrible. Well, okay. Hold on. I feel like this would be really good
If we could coordinate it
So like I go in there and I just start like grind grind grind grind grind grind grind and you can just get in there and just
Attack with all your most powerful moves
You grind her and I common azor
I mean
I wish you had it
I do you do
Yeah, I mean we could try to be just wacky
I I don't think it's gonna do that much. My staff isn't
Upgraded as much
Watch out bad guys
Let's get in the vader
What if we just like hit her?
Maybe that would work too
This thing does pretty good damage though
I was doing like a 1100 to swing right there
All right, let's go for it. I think it's a little slower than the thing I was using before
Dude, all right. Okay
Not bad not bad
Fucking god. Damn it
I had a aneurysm and forgot how to switch to my shield
I can't if you have to sprint away during that move
Don't laugh i'm doing all right
You're grinding her off. She's just like fucking punching you in the face
It's a lot. It's just a lot of stamina
Is that okay if you were alive, but we put it up with pretty good
I messed up bad
I had a goof moment
Like for like a brief second when she went up in the air
I could feel that I was in the matrix and I kind of doubted the reality. Yeah the
The l2 is not really can I do any moves from l2?
I wonder let me check
You cannot
Why everybody does that anytime you like look down to look at something down your like sure to you touch your eyes
You just everybody goes
Why?
What was that?
What is what?
They just like make up new enemies down here
i'm dead
What is that dog? Is he up there coming boss? Hopefully this time the sky like doesn't fall on me
Use the black knife. I don't think I can anymore
I needed 18 faith which eight points to be able to do that one move is I don't think it's worth it
Keep her in the corner
There's a closer bonfire. Yeah, i've heard people say that
But we're in we're in gamer fatigue mode right now
I don't think you can you wouldn't be able to direct us to where we need to go
That guy is sick of getting killed. He's left over the bridge
Maybe we'll give it a look
That was not worth the man. Not really, but it was very good knockback
Oh, that's fucking fantastic
We got our locks in we do
Okay, easy easy
I can't believe I didn't
No
No stamina
Just getting ready for the next phase
What was the stagger on that shit?
That's the first time I got hit by the second part. Oh fuck off
Stop losing fucking lock on
Come on you piece of shit
kill her
Can I do a fucking move in the fucking video game?
Dude, you just you can't even swing at her. You can't swing the fucking weapon at her
She's just constantly doing a move
Huh stamina was almost out. It's just I feel like she's just going like this. Can I play can I from software?
Can I play the game? That is the game. It's a dance
Yeah, I remember
Dude, it's a dance. Uh, well, can we just can we like
Can we do like can we fucking floss or something?
You shouldn't use this your weapons too slow
What it would just have to delete a whole class of items to play against millennia
The omen killer. I feel like the omen killer was was slower
All right last attempt last attempt before we put a new seed in and delete her from the game now i'm angry
Hopefully not too angry
Not just angry enough to fucking like
Go hard. Oh, i've been hard
Uh back to one
Oh, because I don't have as much stamina or fucking health as I did before so I don't even think I can do that anymore
Sorry, sir. This is personal. No, that's cool
my bad for
Yeah
for existing
Fine. Fuck you. I thought I dodged again
But like what if we did like one more I didn't get a fair I do I she had more health than when you fucking died
I fought her for like an extra five minutes. Yeah
Yeah, you know what they say can't win them all change your weapon. It's over
I can't the only way I can change this weapon is if we randomly get another larval tear
Somewhere I have one you do. Yeah, i'm not honestly not giving up on this yet, though
I actually the bleed is really good when you get it to go off. I don't I don't I think it's okay
I don't hate it that went real quick from if we had a larval tear to
No
It's really not that bad
Stagger is good anything out of this helmet
I I fucked up my respect because I have less health and less stamina
it's just well I
got
Shit on a lot quicker than I thought I was I just want to smoke weed with the better chaos like I just
Really want that
There you go. Yeah, let's go. Let's go and the bleed to play an extra safe play safe
Yep, exactly why we just did that
I got caught on a fucking you're good. You're good. You're good. You're good
No, you're good. You're good. You're good. You're good. Everything's all good, man. We're good
Could do it again soon
Yeah
Good very clean so clean well diddled
sucks losing the
nice
Paranoid all right eat whatever you got eat whatever you got. No i'm in the run. I'm in the run. I'm coming out here
Well, that doesn't reach
No
I'm gonna die. That's fine. She won't leave me alone
I mean, I I have rotten she puts it was in the worst possible spot
No, it's over man
as she landed I dodged it and I was just in it I was trying to get away from her because of
Oh, this is such fucking hell in this room
That was a really good first run
It's just the second round is just it's just like fuck. I mean you didn't really even get to do the second round. No
You walked back into it. I know but it's like it's just i'm trying to get away and
At the uh at the cross of the church if you go into those like big extra areas
She can never land on you if like we're close enough. We weren't really
I just
It's so hell bent on eating that I just forgot I did it was like it was just like I just forgot
That this is the worst boss they've ever fucking made and that's just hungry
I just forget I forget sometimes this is the shittiest thing they've ever created
I can't wait to smoke a fat fucking blunt with better chaos. I'm telling you it's gonna be so good
I don't know. I am gonna vent I am gonna vent
At the bed of chaos we're gonna be high as fuck and i'm just gonna be like, let me tell you something
Let me tell you from felania
He's venting
All right, easy
Oh, that's unfortunate
I don't even
Do it as you don't even I don't even know where the fuck I was. I was stuck on two pillars
I think i'm still old. No, never mind. I was gonna say I thought I was still in a plus one flask
What what plus is your flask gap?
uh 10
What the fuck? Oh, no, no, no, you mean how much actually healing? Yeah. Uh, let me see. I mean
Uh, anyways, it's a plus six. I have a lot more health. Yeah
Um, can you use the black knife?
Um back in
Do you have do you have any faith at all?
Nope, no, um
Only in our next attempt. Do I have faith?
All right. Let's try this one more time
Put on the lead grease just to keep it going
I don't have any lead grease
Skip her. Uh, we unfortunately
can not
And there's a bunch of other shit we could do but she kind of is
We need two great runes to go further in leyendale
Wait, there's another way in there
What's the other way?
Are you coming from like the catacombs? I think we're astell is
I don't know now. She won't drop a great room, but the game progress is through here
Because we kind of I don't know if there's any other game progress we can really do this is kind of the wall right now
uh, can you
Take tish and I drop it for you. Let's see. I cannot drop it. I don't have a lot of mana either
This is optional, but I thought there's no other aren't we kind of locked out or we can't go to the capital
I mean we could go can we even get to mog?
I think so
We could do bog maybe
Not tonight, but there's tons of shit we could do
The shit that we want to do was fast here, right?
What is she gonna do? Yeah
No, please don't do it. Oh, please
Oh, please
That's rough and you handled it like a champ. Thank you
Your chat would be parking
Positivity was I hope they are
That's rough
Careful. I sense it
There's a disturbance. I was gonna say that but I was too concentrated
What the hell did she just do whoa she's behind me
I don't know. She was there
She's definitely gonna fucking kill me
She's mad
Yeah
Okay
Camp oh she's behind the pillar for me
She's up
Oh motherfucker
Yeah, I didn't realize she was gonna instantly go for that. I thought it was the other one
The hell
Let me swing my weapon
never mind
It's I just got no I don't I think you got this
I have no heels
Do you need them? Good point. Yep, try attacking her when I swing one time
She swings five and I die you need a katana telling you this game should have a sniper rifle dude
I'm pulling the plug in like in five minutes. If only you had a faster weapon. Why do I have to play with it?
Didn't we didn't we talk didn't we argue about this?
Why can't I play with the weapon? I want to play with why do I have to play with the weapon that you're supposed to play
With to beat millennia not fair
Well, if you beat her with this weapon, then you would have beat her with a weapon
You're not supposed to use to beat her true. You just have to beat her
Like just do it
I don't like her over here
can't hide
True
And I god damn I have so little health after the respect
All right. I'm gonna find like an exploit
I I don't know be a racer. You're just a leader
Uh, i'm just gonna die
Black knife I we only have one larval tier and stirr is talking about how his build is not very good
No, mine is great. It's just I need a little more life
Uh, you can you can take it. Um, I am so scared to like you
Go back to faith
I I don't think the pizza cut is the problem. We're doing a lot of damage
All right. We're doing one more attempt. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I i'm done fucking
already left
I mean we could just go explore other dungeons to try to find a great run. I'm gonna i'm gonna goofed
You're right. Yeah, I used the the remembrance I had to get enough for a level and i'm a little bit short
Uh, I unfortunately don't have anything. I got enough. I got enough. Oh, yeah. I'm missing a lot of points
Like down 10
Put on more armor, I mean I have left this armor is heavy as shit
Disable her healing like i'll just go like full dps and you can res me
I mean the knife was really good. It was doing
Like it was just taking damage
It didn't seem good
It was but I mean
I would have to go back to faith. I really thought that bleed was gonna be really good
I mean, we're doing a lot of damage. We're getting through phase one pretty pretty much
Like 60% of the time very hard for me on this low of life and stamina to survive a waterfowl
So we absolutely could just do other stuff and level but either way, I think
Probably done it for the night. I mean i'm probably gonna eat my keyboard if we do this for like another hour
Oh risking it she going to go crazy
Oh fuck I got stuck. Oh fuck
Oh, man. Oh boy
I'm doing it again. Are you? Oh, that's not good
Two in a row look at our health. She's like back to full health. She's taking like collateral damage
Oh, yeah
I'm dead. I yeah, I we we would have to do other stuff. I I just don't have enough health
What if I beat her right now though?
I mean do it
I'm all for it
I was trying to jump
This is exactly what we did to plaster do six by the way. What do you what do you mean?
Well, we fought last to do six for like a whole night and he was destroying us and we're like, okay
Fine, let's go do other stuff and then we came back and it was like wow. This is really easy
Uh, I would rather smoke fucking three blunts with plastic do six and do this
I fucking hate this bus more than anything
All right
What do you say we cool off for a little bit and we go?
We go and do a little dungeon or something. Just just like cool off. Let's cool off in a dungeon. Let's cool off
Okay
Oh
I know some content that we can do. Mm-hmm. Uh, it's millennia. Hey, let's do six. Hold on passing
Hey
Anybody want anybody want millennia here? Yeah. No, no way. She sucks
Mm-hmm. Yeah
Button I voted you did. Yeah, we're going to limb grave tunnels. Yeah, I voted but it won't work
Can you do it right this time?
Now we're going up up take a nice little little little chill detour
The final boss is equally as hard as millennia
What is it? What have we seen this before? What are we doing?
We're doing a first dragon
Oh, this sounds pretty relaxing
Look at that big boy
Look at that big old chonker
That guy's massive
Now this is the now this is content
Ah shit, he's almost got me. Watch out
Claus beware
But
I don't think we got it
What if you dropped a great run?
I would say then that's great because we don't have to fucking play that other dumb stupid fucking part of the fucking game
Oh fucking stupid fucking goddamn fucking stupid fucking thing
Come here
He's delaying it. He's delaying
He disappeared. He's right about he went back. All right, great rune of rodan
I got uh the glaive
I didn't I didn't really get anything
That was nice dude sick. That was that's um, that felt pretty good
That was great
Okay. Wait, what about some of the jails?
I know there's a few we didn't do
There's a ton we didn't do we did like two jails in the whole game did we do this wait can we even okay?
Wait, we'll look at some jails
This is her tree over here. We didn't do
Let's go
All right. One more relaxing battle
Wait, let's turn the death road in we might get a great run
Every item is just one item the next one that next one
Wait, is he gone? No, i'm here. Oh, we're not doing hero's grave. No way
I didn't get anything
Cool. All right. What is something else we can do? All right, there's the other route that goes into lane dell
from below
Which is astel?
uh
Totally don't think we were done with nocron. We could go kill the big dragon the big sleeping dragon
Just like a free hundred something thousand souls
Also true. Let's go do that
What if he's replaced?
might be
Uh, do you get there from here? Yeah, you do. Yeah, you can get her from here
I don't know where you want. I see let's walk
stir
I've uh
Stir I got we're good
What run saved?
Actual run saved. I just got the key to the manor
I just got the key to the fucking manor
Was it at this tree? It was at the tree. I've told you to pick that up like twice you have
This fucking guy. All right, but hold on. Oh, okay. We're good. Let's keep playing
Hey, i'm gonna go turn into a death root if you there's like a tree down there and you've been getting like good items from
the trees
Let's um get him to quiet and then
Uh, let's fight this dragon
Let's get into quiet
let's
Um, I don't think i've stood up in eight hours
Yeah today like i'm surprised you didn't even ask for like a pea break or anything. Yeah, let's do that
I haven't stood up in like seven. Holy that's actually bad. What time is it?
9 30, I feel like I feel like legitimately, uh, this is gamer addiction like a gamer health alert
uh, I need to get up tomorrow and
Yeah
Hey, I got it. I could play a bit longer, but I got a proposition for you
Yeah, I know that we were gonna go tomorrow, too
but
Do you want to you want to do it on monday or tuesday instead?
That works for me. Okay
Because there's a couple things that I probably need to do tomorrow
so
probably
um
Let me just make sure I get it. All right, you want to do it on
monday
Yeah
Yeah, this is we got the key
At the very minimum before we leave let's go kill that big dragon
We're already here. No, they're dry another dragon fight. We're gonna get like rot it. This guy wants another dragon fight
We just killed the strongest dragon in the game. Well, I mean, I don't mean this one
I mean the big one but this one this one's got way too much health
Oh, oh, yeah, let's go to the big one
This guy's freaking out. He's gonna smoke weed with the bed of chaos
Yeah, I got plans
God, I fucking hate millennia. Hey. Hey, remember when we first tried elden beast
That was actually pretty good
We got uh, we got gargoyle down here if you want. I think it's a good idea
Just can you just like remember for a second when things like
When things were nice good times
Hey, i'm not having a bad time by any stretch of the idea. I just millennia just just makes me irrationally upset
I don't like this area. I'm in where like everything does 75% of my health and damage and I can't heal it in one slap
Should probably get um, the horse is feeling easier run away. He relaxed man
nice
That seer that one shot me
At the hell I was at I I goofed
Okay
Why can I not lock on anymore?
Weird can't I I cannot lock on to this enemy
Whoa, that hurts. I thought it was just like I'm angry sound
me mad
Not locking on it's driving me fucking nuts
I just couldn't lock on even off the horse. Let's go to that big dragon and then i'll level vigor
Like two or three times
Even off the horse I couldn't do it. All right, let's go kill that dragon and just take the free souls
Did you respawn at the bonfire?
I did not
Well, okay. Sometimes I forget
How long it takes you to spawn?
Okay, the big dragon is like over here, right?
I don't know. I always get lost
I think it's down here
here
Where are you going?
I don't know. I think we I think we have to go over here
That's not that sounds right
There's a bonfire down here. I know
There was a type of guy to put gold sheets on his food fun. No, no, I wouldn't why don't we just get 62 000 souls for
Uh, I I I don't know you got you got lobstered you're getting lobstered friend
Oh getting you're getting
Bye
Just leave just leave without me
Okay, where did you go?
I went down the hill
The dragon fell off the bridge. Holy shit
Okay, let's kill this dragon get the souls level up a couple times and then i'll see you monday
oh
Okay
What level are you?
Okay, we're actually pretty close. I'm a 79er
All right over here somewhere
Uh, the game fact says that a lot of people don't fight millennia until they're level 300
The worst fucking boss ever made like yeah
I would want to go in there at a level of thousand and just click just hit her once
Okay, where is this?
um, I think
He he's not here
Where are all the yeah, all the dragons are gone, too
Yeah, he would normally be here
Just kick me
I where isn't where is i'm
He's not here. He's not here
Okay, I had this jail change of plans
Yeah
jail
I don't know where the fuck you are
I'm gonna say there's the castle at the top that has the uh
The dectus medallion and maybe that item is a good item. Oh, I don't know where the hell you are
Uh, i'm at jail
Over here. Where are you? Oh, there you are
you have to
You are very far away from me. Holy shit. How do we get so separate dragon is?
Oh, well, come over here man. We got some cool shit going on
You're on the other side of the fucking like chasm. Yeah, I I knew there was no dragon. That's just testing to see your
Gamer skills
Here I come here I come they're saying the dragon is not randomized
They can say that all they want but it's not there
Okay, here we go
100 there. I was just up at the fort
I hope this is easy because I have 63 000 souls
God free the battle mage
You ever just wish you could roll up into a bomb be like a roly poly
Actually be kind of cool
Like if you come across like a big hill, you're like, oh that's fine. I could just like turn into a ball
Can you hit him like it's some it's some aggro
I've been hitting him this whole time. Can you hit him like four more times?
He just really does not like you
I hope you're uh
Let them have it. Oh nice bleed
Where is this not in this front?
Oops
What's this? Wait battle mage go defroy
Wait go
I thought it was
Is that how it's spelled there? There is a god free that normally appears in one of the jails
I don't know. Maybe they call him goad free
I feel like you just made that up. Yeah, we got like the grocery store toy version of them
It's the mini boss version. Okay. Okay, cool
You should look at the cheat sheet in the randomizer files
It will tell you where some of the stuff is
Now that we have the manor key, we don't have to worry about it anymore. Not for at least a little while
Welcome to fort far off where the big dragon is
yeah, and
at the end of this we're going to get a great rune of um
a mesquite
the x-men character
Will you get away? Oh, thanks for the meat. Do you know the secret place to get the uh,
the trinket here
the secret place
No
I left when you guys discovered you needed the key watch the entire royal rumble pay-per-view
And first thing I hear when I come back is we finally have the manor key
mogues great room
Really? Actually. Yeah. Oh, thank god our next play our next time we turn this on is gonna be so much better
Which also we could get into landale now because yeah, i'm pretty sure the mod makes it two great runs to get in
That's a bit of a mogul like that's a great moment. I think it happened in the last
Five ten minutes of the stream. We spent we spent 99 percent of the stream fighting. I don't know what I just did
And then we went and did one other like side quest and like, okay, we got a great rune. That's what i'm saying
We're gonna go we're gonna like play for a day
We'll like on monday and at the end of the day at the end of the day on monday we fight malania
And it's gonna be like we're just gonna fucking
Shit down her blouse
Oh, you did the same thing I did you did the same I figured solidarity. Ah, thank you
Makes you feel better
All right. Well now that was fun
We we made a lot of progress
I actually think here's my prediction
because
We've got we've got to kill whatever is in rykar's room
And then we do the capital
We could potentially
Beat the game on monday. It's possible
Uh, I think it'd be pretty easy
because like
the only like
Terror that we have not seen is radon. Yeah
So if like the elden beast or any of those fights isn't radon
And just go fight
You know like the main quest stuff like that could be a mad soldier at this point
Who knows it really could be where the elden beast is and where horror lu is
It could just be something so simple. It could be like an ulcerated tree spirit
Yep. All right
Well, no, that was fun. Um
Millennia sucks just want to say that again
um
We'll beat her though. We will
I i'm confident
I'm also confident with like
10 more levels. I think we would
It would be so much easier with like 10 levels
It would be
Uh, right
Do not banish me yet. I know you want to but hold on. I mean you're banished
Don't do it. I'm serious because i'm about to get the treasure chest
The treasure trashed
Okay, you can ban me now
I can't believe that was actually a great run
I'm now alone
Well, we killed ryckard. We killed the weird version of ryckard. We didn't kill the actual ryckard
We killed the well we
Phase one ryckard technically
Yeah, we killed ryckard in the valiant golem
double fight
Which i'm surprised that wasn't two enemies
Yeah, I don't think I have anything else I can do
Why all there is to do
Is stand near fia's entrance
And get 10k souls
Could do that
But yeah, i'm going i'm going i'm really tired and I uh, thanks luster
I've just got some like backpack pork. Yeah
Go go relax. I feel like you have kind of a stressful last 24 hours. Go chill
Yeah, all right. We'll see you soon. We'll see you monday. Yeah, okay. Yeah
Yeah, see you monday. Yeah
All right. Yeah, that was uh, we made some pretty good progress
We were on millennia for like three hours three and a half four hours
It kind of par for the course. I think it
Before I go is anything else I can just I don't think so great stream. I didn't get too angry
I don't think I think this pales in comparison to when I actually played the real millennia
Yeah, we'll see you monday
Same thing. Maybe we'll beat it. Maybe we won't if we don't then we'll finish it up a day or two later
Imagining maybe the maybe one more weekend. Yeah, I think that's good here. I'll just call it right here. Thanks for watching
We'll see you on monday. Have a good rest of your weekend. Uh, there's still sunday left. So have a good one
and then after to after monday
Probably do a uh, I don't know. There's a lot of things I want to play monday at
Let me talk to stir probably gonna just ask them
Assume somewhere between two and three pm specific. That's where we'll probably end up in but yeah, take care
See you guys later. Uh, this stuff we still can hang out for a second. What level is my character 84 and I believe stir is 80
I'm gonna do some more chill stuff. Absolutely
Like pentament in your spare time. It's a little slow at the start
I think I actually tried it for like an hour and I it was a little too slow for me and I was like oh
This is for me
But I feel like I kind of didn't give it the right amount of time
What dead space?
I could probably play dead space
Put it on the list
Is the is the remake any good i've seen a lot of people playing it doesn't know if it's any good or not though
It sounds like I fucking smashed something in my room
This the cams off nobody can see me and i'm just like
This goddamn game
What about hi-fi rush? Hi-fi rush is i'm playing it just kind of hanging out off stream
And I will tell you it
It feels like it's going to be one of the one of the great ones this year
Yeah
Take it easy. See you guys later. See you monday. Have a great night
Take care of yourselves. See you soon. Goodbye and good night