Ooh. Oh, he got me! He got us! Hey, happy Halloween.
How are ya? Uh, those of you that are trick-or-treating,
aren't you a little old for that? Go back inside.
I'm five. Well, you're a super genius. How did you find this stream if you're
five? Same, same, same. I got recommended this
channel on Roblox. Oh, nice! What is this? 8 out of 10
germa? What is this? Do I need to watch this? 8 out of 10
germa impression? Wait, why can I only get this through one
headphone? All right, hold on. Let me listen to this.
Okay, what is it? Is this like, is this like your stream?
Am I able to like listen to a clip of your stream?
Link it to me? I can't see it. I don't even like it. It scrolled by too fast.
It's Ster. What the fuck did he do now? What is he trying to do?
Why can I not hear this? Okay, you can hear this, but I can't.
For some insane reason. It's not going through my like
Vive headphones. Well, now what the fuck happened? I just broke everything.
Now I can't hear anything coming through here. Hold on, open up my mixer.
What the fuck? It's not, it sounds not coming through my Vive headset anymore.
Now it is. Oh, here we go. Okay, here we go. What does he say?
2020. Okay. I don't think I can stream for four months.
He doesn't even get it. He doesn't even, hold on.
I'm putting this on stream. We need to break this down.
That's not even why that happened. Ster's impression of Germa
in the year 2020. I don't think I can stream for four months.
Yeah, he's a funny guy. Yeah, nice form by the way.
Nice form by the way. Almost saw your balls on Twitch. Almost just got
permabanned, Star. Real funny. That was real close to a
ball sack on stream. It's close. Was it still funny?
Yeah, it was pretty funny. All right, why don't I come over so you can
you can see this. This music is, why this,
the scary music makes that so much worse.
This is like found footage of me watching Star
start making fun of me and then what does he like stalk me and murder me?
It started with one video clip. Bugle, we need Bugleberry.
I'm sorry to say Bugleberry actually contacted me.
He was just rambling. He said that he's not into Halloween anymore.
He said he's different, he doesn't want to do it anymore, he doesn't want to be a
one-trick pony. He kind of went all over this. I was like,
what are you talking about? He started rambling about
different recipes he was working on and hams and turkeys and shit and I was like,
I was like, dude, just call me later. Like, you obviously kind of, you're
fucked up right now. Maybe I'll talk to him tomorrow, see what
he's up to. Anyways, yeah, we're gonna do VR tonight,
Halloween VR, which, no, don't turn it off, don't turn it off. I'm here, I'm here.
No, don't beep and turn it off, you fuckers. Don't.
Why? Don't do that. Okay, so. All right. Why is it the wrong hand?
Stop opening the door and trying to kill me. Wait a minute, I need to make sure
this is on the right hand because I, if you don't use VR for fucking 10 minutes,
it turns everything off. All right, we're good. Let me, hey, let me, why don't we just,
I'll just show you. What's up? You like my Halloween costume?
I can't do a Halloween costume anymore. I'm 35. I can't, that's when you're not
allowed to wear a Halloween costume anymore. I just have to be MrTwitch.tv guy.
You're a man-child. No, I would be a man-child if I was in a
Halloween costume, like of Sonic the Hedgehog,
right? No, I'm a professional Twitch virtual reality streamer. Yes, I was
Naruto last year, but I was still in the 18 to 34 drop-down bracket.
I can't do that anymore. See you next year when I'm dressed up like a fucking
pineapple. Happy Halloween. Let's go. You ready?
Clip that. Good, clip it. I'll be a pineapple next year.
Did I gain weight? I gained a shitload of weight. Yeah, thank you for asking. I
gained about 20 pounds. We relax and we just wait until we go
into a live stream, okay? Especially if you, you know how it's
like. I know it's a small window. I'll fix it.
Full screen. I know, I will, I will. Motherfucker, we're gonna do like five or six games tonight.
It's gonna be nuts. Starting with, what's the name of this game?
Affect the Manor? Affected the Manor is the name of this game.
This game's apparently only like, it's loud.
Uh, this game is apparently only like 20 minutes long. It's just a haunted house.
So we're gonna do Haunted House and then we're gonna move on to Hospitality VR
and then we're doing Five Nights at Fucking Freddy's VR.
It's all VR and it's all scary. And then if we're gonna do Walking Dead VR,
we're gonna do, there's a lot. I'm going in. You guys ready?
You need anything else from me before we start? This is why I wanted to start a
little later too. I wanted to be like night time.
Put it full screen. Yeah, I got it. See? See?
Um, is the space game too big? I've gotten a good spawn.
Underwear. Those of you that were in the pre-stream chat, we were talking about if
I were to walk out here, be on stream like this,
and be like in VR. Oh, what's all scary? Look out!
Oh, I got it with the lightsaber, right? And then after like 40 minutes, I back up
and it's just fucking white underwear and bare legs.
I wanted to, I did be like, I would do it. Well, I can't. Like, I would get, I would
get thrown off. And then like, I would look at the chat
and everyone would be like, dude, underwear, what the fuck?
And I would, and then it would cut to a pre-recorded video of me waking up
in a bed and being like, oh shit, what a nightmare.
But yeah, I didn't do it. And then I like get out of bed and like come in here and
I stream. Another time. Low effort streamer.
And maybe the last month. That's not even true though.
He's getting drunk? I have like three of these.
This is like, this is the equivalent of drinking one beer.
I don't, I'm not gonna get shitfaced off of three beers.
I'll get very talkative though. What am I drinking?
Uh, a thing that makes me an evil, an evil mastermind.
I'm just gonna switch between all the seltzers. That's like the new thing that
I want to do. Not White Claw. This is truly the same
goddamn thing. Just different companies. Okay, I, I, okay, I had the Xbox. This is
the PlayStation. What's the Nintendo switch of the like
weird gross seltzer companies? The Bud Light one? I don't know. I
know. I feel like Bud Light would be Xbox. Truly, this is, this probably is the
switch. Oh, so I got it. You're drinking the Luigi of
Drinks. It's, I actually don't even hate it. I,
look, it's, I know, it's fun to make fun of truly,
right? And like White Claw. But look, if they're on sale,
you're gonna get them, right? If you're of drinking age and you want to drink a
couple, if they're on sale, why not? Stop buying fancy Instagram drinks and
upgrade your PC. This was like four, this was like three dollars.
It's like, it's like six grand for a PC that I want to make.
Seven grand. It's fancy Instagram drink. I bought this twice in my life.
I'm getting a 3090. I'm getting a fucking 32 core PC.
I'm getting a fucking case that can embed into the wall.
I'm gonna get wireless everything. Wireless mouse, wireless keyboard, wireless
microphone, wireless headphones, wireless
motherboard, everything. And I'm also, I'm gonna get a desk that can go
right here. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, it's gonna be
fucking incredible. Please don't waste money on a 3090.
You know, I actually heard that. I heard that like, don't buy a 3090. What are you
stupid? It's like, it doesn't do anything. But I
got, I want to get it for the, the Nvink, the codec. I want it to be
rendering the stream at like fucking 1080. Instagram drinks. Do people like post
themselves drinking these on Instagram? Why? What? It's like, this is not, this is
not cool. This is cool. Am I cool for doing this?
Wait, hold on. Somebody get one of these. I'm gonna get an image of this.
And I don't want you to put it like, I want you to put like the Instagram like
like and follow button and shit down here. And like put a filter on me. Put like a
bunch, put like six filters on me. I shouldn't have done that. I shouldn't
have done that because now like, okay, I have nothing to do with this fucking
company. I just bought this because I want to drink it so I like it.
I want like all the, like the dashboard of Instagram.
Stop advertising. I, I, but if I drink a Coke on stream, you're gonna see Coke. If
I drink a fucking Sprite on stream, how's that any different? It's the, it's
the same thing. Don't I just put tape on this? Cover it up.
Go put electrical tape on this. No, if I put electrical tape on this, this is not
truly, this is like some kind of weird fucking potion that I made.
That's like dangerous. All right, let's go. No more Stalin. Let's go.
That's cool. VR sucks. Okay. All right, so thanks. VR
sucks. Oh, by the way, I'm ready to go tonight. You know why?
Can I show this? I'm just gonna show a little bit, okay? Just enough for you to
see it. Where is it? Just enough for you to see.
I'm taped up today. I'm taped the fuck up today.
I'm covered in like, in this like, in this fucking body tape and I'm ready to
take on the entire world. I got it going across my back. I go wrapping around
here. Like a diaper. You have a colostomy bag on.
Why is he taped up? Because it's like body tape.
It's to like support your like muscles and back and chest. It's like, it's
support tape. Got it already? All right, look, when I
go in, I don't come out. All right, this is not the filter I was
talking about. This is not, no, I didn't want it to be like,
like a, like a nuclear bomb going off. This is like the sun exploded.
This is the last thing I do before the sun explodes.
Gotta get those likes on Instagram before the sun like takes over us all.
Hey, ah, sun just exploded. Might as well enjoy it with a fucking truly.
There's no way that I could get 2,000 likes on Instagram. What are you talking
about? I could get like 50,000. I'll show it,
I'll show you. What do you mean I can't get 2,000 likes on
Instagram? Are you kidding me? If I had an Instagram, it would be
loaded with likes. Every like would be, it would be, it would be double liked.
It'd be 10,000. All right, I'm ready. Let's get, I'm gonna,
let me just try to finish my fucking blueberry and I almost just dropped it.
Does Bugleberry have an Instagram? No, but I'm gonna be here for a while, okay?
This is all I got going on tonight. I'm not, I'm just, I'm gonna,
you got me tonight, okay? Dropped all of his loot.
All right, let's go. Already stalling. I'm not stalling. This, this game's only like
10,000. All right, I'm ready. This is called, uh,
affected it the manner. The reason why this is like five times tighter than it was
three days ago. Why is it so tight? What happened? Oh shit, it's because
of this. I didn't do that. All right, that's better. Okay, let's go.
This is effect, this is a haunted house. You go through it, it takes about 15
minutes. Almost as long as I've been stalling,
drinking, truleys on stream. Right or left? Just make this shit green
so I can fucking see it. Okay, you ready? Well, this is, this is
horrifying. This is really scary sounds. Okay, this is
scary sounds. This is what you guys have been hearing
this whole time? Okay, I wanted to, where do I go?
Stop, gauntlet. Can I take a candle? I think I have to go this way. Here we
go. Your pants are falling, you're on. Okay,
here we go. Haunted house, haunted media. Happy Halloween everybody.
Warning, this experience is intense and uses jumpscares, loud noises, and
flashing images. Do not play if you have any known health issues or
nervous disposition. Your discretion is advised.
That's, wait, I'm getting the don't ride this if you have a medical condition
thing? I mean, I have a few medical conditions.
Fucked. Don't die. Okay, that's the house. Can I go any faster?
Fast as I can go. Oh, I already don't like this. I already hate this shit.
You guys know that before YouTube and Twitch,
I did not ever play scary games because I can't play them and I hate to play them.
I am of a nervous disposition. I don't, I hate this.
Damn. I have to be strong. It's Halloween night.
I think I need to wipe the lenses. What the fuck are you doing?
Right? That's it, right? What? That was good.
That was really good. You know, I know that was good. You can,
you can minus two it if you want. I don't, I wasn't trying to be funny. I was showing
you how good I was. Alright, Satan door. That was, uh, I'm
not ready for this part yet. I'm not ready for that yet. Is there
anything else I can do in here? Let's see what's behind door number two.
Oh, I don't want to go in there.
Ass cracked? Fuck off. What? Alright. In the house. I went through door
number two. Can't go up there. Imagine doing this in
real life. Why would you ever do this in real life?
I feel like ghost hunters and shit. Stay fucking home.
Stay home. That was horrible. Oh my god. I felt like my whole
house exploded. Seven? Alright, this door is number seven. Remember that.
Like who cares if the place is haunted? Don't you think that's a little condescending
to the ghost that's there? Like the ghost is just trying to exist
in peace and you're in there with like your fucking ecto meter.
Hey, can you hear us? Like yeah, I can. Please get the fuck out of my house. I am
on the nervous disposition. That was a kid laughing in reverse.
God damn it. For me it's a big brave adult man.
Thanks dude. Going deeper down into the house.
Shining. That's some shining little shit right here.
Fuck. It's okay. What time is that? That would be
that's a six down there. Seven. That would be eight. That would be oh no. That's not
pointing that way. That's uh that would be one.
That's one ten. Come on. I'm kidding. It's fucking ten
o'clock. Ten ten. Leave me alone. Hey. I'm so jumpy tonight. Oh it's a
fucking Ouija board. Great. Fuck you. Don't do that. Okay if that
happens you can't blame that on like your drunk friend.
Ask it a question. What's your name? B? Holy shit the fucking things have
flyed out. That's what I'm gonna look like in an
hour when I take the headset off. It's Abraham Lincoln.
Oh don't come out of the painting. Don't come out of the painting.
You were gonna come out of the fucking painting. Actually pretty fucking scary.
What? I didn't get to play this thing. Orgrab.
It was kind of a lore grab. And face. All right I'm going left hand.
Put it down. It's like interference. This is a microphone.
Don't literally pick a microphone up next to the speaker. What are you
supposed to be the audio guy? Fuck off. All right I can't go that way.
This sucks. It's already gonna be in the bed in about five seconds.
I'm so I'm so glad that there are like 70,000 people here watching this.
I know that you're here with me so like it's not as bad. Hey
I see a shadow. Is that my shadow or is that their shadow?
Find out. Is that? Is it painting? I don't. I hate. I want like a gun or
something or like a knife. Give me a weapon please. It's gonna
change. Uh don't. I'm waiting for it to change.
No please. Why would you have this shit in your house?
All right I'm sorry. Is it weird for me to say that if you have paintings like
this all over your house you're a fucking psycho.
Like these are fucking psychotic paintings. You can't you don't relax in
this house. Who relaxes and eats dinner here?
Like you get chicken and rice and you sit there with like the pictures of
people's heads being torn off. If you own pictures like this you keep
them like in a vault or something. You don't show them in your house. You're
gonna scare the fuck out anybody that you can't have friends over with a
painting like that. Because they're all gonna come over
they're gonna be like oh dude nice place cool.
Oh what is this hardwood floors? Oh uh nice man. You know what? Yeah I'm gonna
order a lift. I'll uh I'll meet you guys at the bar.
Don't that's an uncomfortable painting man. Oh what's this shit?
Oh I don't know is that your grandfather? No no I just collect old photos of
strange people. They're scary people. Oh hey you got a daughter?
You got you got a son? Cool hey my name's my name's Mike.
I'm your dad's friend. No no don't go up there don't go up there.
Nah it's not good man. I'm checking out your place dude.
Hi. Well these little dirty books. Have those to be scary. Old ass tv.
Oh can I go somewhere else? Holy fucking shit okay. My face don't be my face.
It's gonna be my face. Turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it
off turn it up turn it off turn it up turn it up.
Oh
All right I've had enough of you. This is a true
this is true monkey ass. I don't know why they gave that warning of like hey if
you're if you have like a heart attack while you're playing
you don't sue us. I'm sitting on it. I have a question for you guys all
watching. At what point do you leave? What's the point that you are like I
want to I'm gonna leave the house now? I think it's it's now by the way.
It's right now. I'm just gonna start I'm gonna turn around.
I'm gonna knock this fucking dresser over. I'm gonna smash it.
Everything behind me is getting thrown behind me. Like whatever I walk by is
getting ripped behind me. I'm just gonna stop pissing. I'm
gonna start making like a piss stain like piss spots or like just slip on it.
I'm doing everything possible dude. I'm gonna I'm telling you I would freak I'm
not I'm not getting killed. We're talking Mario Kart level shit is
what I'm gonna do here. I'm doing everything possible to get out of this
house alive. Like I'm grabbing candles and the stove's
got burning. You gotta go full chaos mode to get out of here.
I'm going in. Don't hurt me. No you don't. That's a movie that's Mark Ruffalo did
that one. No you don't. He's behind me.
Ayayay. Uh I said ayayay not ayayaya. There I know I'm turning around.
Oh a map to the treasure. Can I take this?
Baby are you all right? Where's the baby? Baby? Oh my fucking Jesus.
God damn it you piece of fucking shit. Oh oh quick piss and run.
But then as a thing I would be like okay it's time to get out of here.
All right what? I would fucking my keel would go up and I'd let out my back
and then she would just eat my soul. I would home alone myself in that
scenario. Hey look how hard I can five more months of what? Just dying in a pool
of his own piss. I don't dream of that I'm just saying that's a realistic
scenario. Phone in the bed?
Shut that up. That's horrifying. Why do you have all this?
You're fucking scary. You're scary if you have all this stuff.
I can't turn it off. Get out. I'm gonna I think I'm I think I'm
gonna need some truly power after this. I suppose it's to be a little girl you
know? It's never just gonna be like an armadillo or something like a dog or a
cat. Could it be an evil cat? A very little girl.
Oh I hurt myself. I just hurt myself. I hurt myself.
I hurt myself. I hurt myself. I smashed my fucking thumb.
I'm gonna have I got I'm hurt. I got hurt.
I got hurt because I'm wearing I'm holding two giant ice cream cones. I
don't know why they made them like this in the first place.
Why did they make them like this in the first place? It's like why make them
just huge fishing rods? I gotta get the index controllers.
Bad. Because if you get too close like this you're gonna smash.
I'm holding my hands out wide like this from now on.
It took my what? Why did my flashlight just disintegrate?
I don't have any defense against the dark hots.
Yeah come on down to my man cave. I've got a stadium seating.
Yeah no don't mind all this shit. Yeah no that's all good. This is just books
about like witches and murdering people and like burning
like children and stuff. No no that's right. That's just my great uncle. Don't
worry about that. He was a blacksmith. Yeah come on down
though. Yeah yeah yeah. Patriots are on in 10 minutes.
Come on down. Let's go. Who has a house like this?
Those are my those are my hands. That's gonna look at me.
I know you're gonna look at me. That like fucking Napoleon statue is gonna turn
and be like I knew you were gonna be there. That's why I didn't like that.
That's why I didn't like that. Don't move.
Yeah just just a little further. Yeah I swear to god I got an 80 inch tv in here.
All right don't worry about that. Fuck all that stuff.
I gotta get the cleaners in here. Would you have all this?
And like that big fuck is gonna do something.
Oh the joker. Oh this is a really long hallway.
You know how I can tell this thing's mouth is gonna open because look at
the like the animatable lines that are right neck on his mouth.
One two three don't do it. I'm just getting hit with various pieces of wood
into my back. That's what this game is. I have a
blindfold on and somebody is going to my back and say you ready?
When I don't know it's gonna happen they count to three and do it on two.
That's not a bad picture whatever. This house is huge.
Come on piano. Gotta save us here piano. Gotta save us piano.
You can go harder than that man. I can take it. Are you sure?
Yeah yeah I can take it man. I did that pretty fucking hard Jeremy.
Fucking do it again with veiny arms. This blood is just
fucking flowing through me right now. Oh stop. Get out of here. Go back to that tv
show that ended like 15 years. What was that show with the
I wonder what it was. Just flying whatever. Go back.
Go back to that tv show. Pretty cool. I just gotta make it to the door.
Make it to the door. Make it to the door. I gotta be ready. Here comes like up.
Did you open? Oh you you dropped all the stuff.
I don't have a flashlight though. This is bad. That was the playing music in the
beginning right? Oh tense. That's just too it's just my
whole body is in contractions. I'm having contractions.
He's gonna be pregnant. Get the fuck out of here with this
bullshit. Get out of here with this bullshit.
If I was pregnant I would get Disney World. That's how it works.
You guys ever heard that weird like conspiracy theory?
Yeah somebody has. It's an urban legend. Right yeah yeah.
Not consi- well whatever. Open. There's nothing else at the end of this.
Get the fuck away from me you're gonna. Oh I know what to do. I just closed my
eyes and you guys won't even know I'm closing my eyes.
That's a huge big brain moment. I could just close my eyes.
When I know something really scary is gonna happen I'll just close my eyes.
One of these is gonna take them. Take them. One of those is coming off.
My body is so hot and sweaty right now. You know that one of these is coming off
and they're gonna drop at me. Did I lose? Jesus. What the hell would
the gauntlet be? No one survives this way. The gauntlet
just various jump scares that scream like at you. I'm just curious. I just
want to know what it is. What's the gauntlet? It's gonna be just
screams in your face. Instructions. Hold the trigger to
accelerate. The longer you hold the faster you go. Your speed and the
amount that you scream will be rated. Please make sure the microphone is on.
What? That's really what this is. It's not on.
It's not on. Hold on. How do I turn it on? I'm
it really is what I said what it was. It's just screaming in his face.
What is this? Come on. Get out of my way. Oh shit. It's gonna be a light.
It's gonna be an electricity puzzle at the end of this.
What's my rating? An A plus? Hurry. This is what's like
running out of this guy's house. Get the fuck away from me.
Oh we got three mystery doors. Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one?
Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one?
Left. This sucks.
This is like kind of better than the other game.
He was just trying to kill me. Move. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
Come on. I lost an ear. I lost an ear. I lost an ear.
Idol. That's just that's just all of my streams.
All right. That was ridiculous. Cool. All right. Well that was uh
affected the manner. It was that was awful.
Not awful in like oh the game was bad. It was just it was fucking too much.
And you know how you feel when you get off of the scariest ride in the theme
park? The one with like a 300 foot drop and you
get off and you're like holy shit that was horrible.
I had fun but like that was terrible. I don't ever want to do that again.
Did you get back in line? All right. I gotta come out for a sec.
That sucked. No more. I'm not doing that again. No.
Hope you're good. I'm good. Idol screamer. What's this link?
Rick look at the link. I want to make this really clear that this is this is
satire. This is a joke. This is not real. This is satire because I I'm not this is
not actually real. What is alpha gamma beta house?
Just shit myself. I don't think that's going to get you
very many likes. All right let me get out of this.
The next one is going to be a quick one too. Next one's called hospitality VR.
I think this one is you just this one might just scream in your face.
There's another link. Well I'm not going to show that one on stream.
Enjoy that one on your own. Link I I saw I've seen it. I'm not putting it on
stream. What does the pregnant Disney think?
If there's an urban legend that if like if a man was pregnant then he got Disney
World. I don't know where where that came from.
I swear I don't know. I this is like a weird urban legend. Yo what the fuck. I'm
this is just I'm just telling you this has been an urban legend from like 30
years ago. Why do I have to click on all these
bicycles, Google? What are you talking about? Click on the bicycles to verify
you're on a robot? Yeah Walt Disney's will the first
pregnant man snopes.com. I'm telling you yeah. Why would he
want that? I don't know. I didn't make this up. I
this is just something I was like what the fuck what does that mean?
It was debunked. Okay well it was debunked.
Whatever. I'm not saying that this is a factual statement.
All right should I just move to Five Nights at Freddy's and just say fuck it.
All right we're doing Five Nights at Freddy's. VR. Let me just
okay I I don't want to break this. I've broken it before.
Okay how do I okay quit. I gotta do it in here.
Every time I try to do this I break it so I'm not breaking it this time.
We're doing Five Nights at Freddy's Help Wanted. That's coming up next.
I have to go so I don't break anything. I have to go to the home.
So I have to go to home. Uh exit game. There it is. Five Nights at Freddy's.
I don't have to I don't have to exit anything. We're still in VR.
I practiced this guys before I turned the stream on like three days ago.
Next up is Five Nights at Freddy's Help Wanted. Here it comes.
Nice. All right that was easy. Am I still streaming? What the fuck happened?
Wait what? Let's go. I gotta change. Hold on. I gotta change the uh
I'm gonna change the game we're playing. Is this game actually any good or is this
a meme? Is this just a meme game? Tell me now. All right Five Nights at
Freddy's VR. Why's my computer crashed? Uh Help
Wanted right? How many Five Nights at Freddy's games are
there? There's a Minions game? Minions Five Nights at the Despicable
Hospital 3D. What? Why is that on Twitch's
directory? Should I play that? Five Nights at
Freddy's Help Wanted. There it is. This doesn't have an icon. Five Nights at
Freddy's Help Wanted. Did it change? I want to make sure I'm in the right
category otherwise I'm going to be in big fucking trouble.
All right we're good. Let's go. Five Nights at Freddy's
VR. See you in the game. Wait I need a little bit more uh I need to drink a
little more. I like this because it's fucking disgusting.
I'm sure it is. Uh this is the first time I played a Five Nights at Freddy's games
uh since Demon Lord Zaraxos made that awful video that I
refused to delete for principle. This is the first time I've played one
in a long time. Okay hold on. Are we good? Help Wanted. Shit I forgot to drink.
I need like a helmet that feeds it to me. All right let's go.
I thought that said bad game. Let's do it. Minions Five Nights at Despicable
Hospital when? Never. How do I walk? General. General. General. Subtitles on. How do I walk?
I can't like this is in the wrong. I'm hitting the microphone.
Um the legs are broken. Can I not make this move?
New game. Uh uh hello. Hello.
Is this cringe?
Oh Freddy!
Freddy!
That's not Freddy. That's a guy.
That's Happy and Hoppy.
That's Foxy.
Put a Truly. Put a Truly over there and put a filter on it.
That's the same picture I took.
It's mostly just legal mumbo jumbo and isn't at all based on user experiences thus far.
Volumes low. Injuries associated with testing. Just touch the button to agree
and then we can jump right into some harmless fun that can't harm you at all.
I got you. Thank you. I got you. I got you.
Knowledge that fast fair entertainment is not responsible for accidental digital
consciousness transference real world manifestations of digital characters
nightmares night terrors night sweats.
Oh no the nose thing is fucked up.
Five nights at Freddy's one.
Use the console in front of you to navigate the menu and pick one of the
frightening experiences available. Okay night one.
More will become available. You'll see plenty of familiar faces
and some new ones as well. Let's grow taller. Stay a while
and have a good time and remember despite the temporary horror you may
experience this is a completely controlled environment
and you aren't in any real danger. Fast fair entertainment not responsible for
real danger unless you're using the ice cream cone fucking
Vive controllers. Can I move? How do I move forward?
This is not right. Don't. I have standing room only selected from my Vive.
Why did I go forward from here? Have to get like all up in your face?
There's no moving. Okay how about uh candy. Okay show time. What's this?
Night one? Night one. Whatever let's just do night one. Five
nights at Freddy's one. Five nights at Freddy's push buttons.
Okay push buttons. Wait this is this is he's gonna do it.
Oh fuck I don't I oh I don't want to do
wait I forget don't touch anything right how do I turn the cameras off?
Oh door no light no I I play this game with both doors closed
permanently. I've never won five nights at Freddy's
because I don't keep I close the doors permanently.
Where is he? Where's Freddy? Where's Freddy?
What's happening? Close the fucking doors keep them all closed.
Dude why do I have to get so close? Oh there they are.
That's not that's like Ernie. That's not Freddy. That's Ernie.
Where are the others? This is just the kitchen is disabled. Why?
Oh shit he's right there. Good thing I have the door closed.
He's literally right here. Purple guy. What? What? Is he there?
All right what time what's the time? What time do I leave? All right I gotta
shit. Get out of here. Get out of here. All right I'm safe.
What the fuck are you doing? Get out of here. What time is it five a.m. right?
Just five a.m. Here it comes. Somebody's coming.
Somebody's coming. Somebody's coming. Somebody's coming. Somebody's coming.
Close the doors. All right six a.m. Five nights at Fast Bear's.
I did it. It's gonna be six a.m. No power night one.
I haven't told these shitties right there. I haven't played this game in like
seven years. Look at me. I did it. Name your prize.
Oh I got a chicken. That's cool is that like is that like
uh is night two. Five nights at Freddy's. Wait how many?
Item two. Three. Dark rooms. Parts and services. Vent repair. Night
terrors. What is all this? Prize counter?
Is this every game? It's actually kind of cool.
How many coins do I have? All right what should I get?
Four. I don't have enough for anything. Okay we're gonna do
we're gonna do night two.
Blush trap. Dark. All right let's just why don't we just go in order?
Night two. Five nights at Freddy's one. I get it now. I get it. It's been a while.
Here we go. They stay backstage. They move around. There's like
okay there's that. I don't spam buttons either.
They do? Is that somebody? Is that here? Somebody I think somebody's here.
Somebody's here. Somebody's here. Somebody's here. Somebody's over here.
Hired code. What happened? Oh shit all right you're in the supply room. You're
fine. Where's the chicken? Okay there's Freddy.
You're back there. Where's the chicken? All right chicken's coming down the hall.
Chicken's coming down the hall right now. Chicken's coming.
Who are you? Chicken coming. Chicken's coming down the hall. Where's Freddy?
What do I do about that? What do I do with that? The alien. What do I do with
the alien guy? Holy shit they move in this one. They move
and they it's Scott Cawthorn actually animated them.
They actually animated in this one. They're not just like fucking bitmap
images. Okay that's scary. They're right there. Get the fuck out. Are you
still here? What's his name? Shit I'm running out of power.
I think I can open this. Yeah is chicken gone?
Chicken's gone. Open that back up. Chicken's gone.
You here? Where's the chicken? Chicken gone? Where's the chicken?
Who's over here? Can I hear you? You're here?
3am we're good. He's right there. He's right there. This motherfucker's right
here. All right chicken's coming back. Chicken's
coming back. He's right there still. Fuck this guy.
What was that? What was that noise? What's that noise? What's going on? Who's
moving? Hello? What was that? Left? I heard somebody
ram into a door. Shit you're right here. Get away from me.
Don't move. I think this is safe to open. Keep this one closed. Keep that one
closed. Is he here? Freddy? Freddy? Freddy? Freddy?
Okay I got 5am. Just leave me alone. 6am.
6am. I hate this game. I just spit all over myself
because I didn't know that he was going to be up under my face
and in my nose. I thought he was going to jump this way so when I was looking
down like this and he was here like underneath like under the water
peek into the hallway and peek down the hallway. Holy shit really?
So that's there so you can't cheat. Molly. God help us.
I'm gonna need a second. I did not think that was gonna happen.
Down the fucking hallway. My god. Scream like a monkey. That was that was
the worst RNG you possibly could have gotten. What?
It was RNG. No that's like a you're peeking you're cheating so we're gonna
end the game. What? What do you mean no it's not? It
wasn't even two seconds in the first second level
of the first game. Go in again and find out.
I fucking knew it. I knew it.
It's bad RNG. Do it again. I don't want to do that one anymore. I don't
like this. I hate this. It's too stressful for me. I want to do
the other ones. Where's the one with like the others? Let's
do Five Nights at Freddy's 2. Oh this one's even worse.
I'm gonna hit the desk.
Oh this sucks.
Don't you have to like wind up a toy in this? Don't I have like a mask I can put
on? Where's my mask? You actually have to put
the mask on. I'm gonna smash my hand.
Yeah I have to wind this right? Oh this is the- hello!
Oh this is the bone, the foxy bone one.
That's this little weirdo, the little weirdo jumping guy.
I hear something. I hear something. Why do I fucking hear something? Oh shit!
Good night. First thing better be getting like a thousand dollars an hour.
So they're up? Where are they? There's two missing. Okay where are they?
Two fucking people missing right now. God. Oh my god.
Get the fuck out of here! Yo! I'm one of you though! I'm one of you!
You gone? You gone? I think- are you gone?
Okay I'm fine. What about- hey! I'm just one of the- one of you! One of you
fucking monsters! Take it off! I died the first night. I hate these
games. I don't like them. I fucking hate these.
No go back to the menu. I want to do two. Two sucks. Two's hard.
Oh no I don't want to do two anymore. I hate these.
I hate it. I'm like one of the most neurotic people you know.
I can't- I don't do well in these scenarios.
Event repair? I will. I'm gonna do them all.
Why did you take the job? Okay so this one, two,
three is bunny, chicken, bear, and then there is-
who else is there? Bunny, chicken, bear, faceless bunny,
and then this toy up there. We move it down here. That little shit
right there. That's the one that runs at you.
Hang up. All right they're on the move. All right bunny's on the move. Where is he?
Where's bunny? He had to have been in here somewhere. Where is it? Where the
fuck is the bunny? He has to be in here. Where did he go? Where's that fucking
bunny? He has to be in one of these rooms.
Didn't he leave from here? Where's the bunny? Okay bunny and chicken are both
gone. All right chicken's up here. Bunny where are you at? Where's this bunny?
Where's this fucking bunny? The bunny. Chicken. Chicken up here.
Bunny right there. All right I got some. Okay wait chicken?
Where's the chicken? Where's the chicken go? Where's the chicken? Where the fuck is the chicken?
Where's the chicken? Where the fuck is the chicken? Where's the chicken?
Where's the chicken. Where's the chicken?
All right there's a bunny. Bunny right here. You're coming down here, I see you.
Okay they're both creeping on me. They're both about to fucking creep on my ass.
I got you. I got you, you can't come... Okay you're moving. On the move. Where'd you go?
You're on move. You're in the vent right now you're in the vent right now. Where
are you? You're in the vent right now get away.
Get away! You're in the vent right now. Get away from me.
You're in the vent! When did you come in? Get fucking out of here.
Where'd you go?
Oh, there.
I lost the headphone.
Where's the chicken?
Where's the bunny?
Where's the- where's the bunny?
Bunny's back!
We're good.
I don't need to enter anymore.
The fuck is going on?
Oh shit, you're in the back- okay.
Come on!
We're good.
I want to drink that truly so bad right now, you have no idea.
Are you having fun yet?
That's great to hear.
That's pretty good.
It's actually pretty fun.
If you like Five Nights at Freddy's, I mean, this is just that, but ten times worse.
I know, I would say a hundred times worse for your, like, anxiety.
That's what I'm doing- look, I'm never going to beat night two with three.
Sit down, dude.
It's way better.
Uh, I mean, that does make sense to sit down.
I know.
Look out for Foxy.
He'll sprint out here.
Uh, oh.
Come on, do it!
What do I do with Foxy?
Shit, I lost the chicken.
Who am I missing?
Where's Foxy?
Hello?
Am I good?
Are you good?
We're good.
Okay.
Chicken's coming down left hallway here.
Hello?
What does that mean?
It's the balloon kid.
Alright, balloon kid is currently in the bed right now.
What do I do about- shine a light in his eyes.
Is that what you do?
What do you do?
Do I shine a light in his eyes?
Can my ass go work on?
Hey, you little fuck.
Alright, he's gone?
Is he gone?
Get back on!
Where is he?
What?
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Get her in the fucking bed, too!
Away from me!
Okay.
AHHHH!
Away from me!
Leave!
I saw somebody else!
Shine a light in his face!
Get away from me, Freddy!
Is he still there?
He's fucking still there!
Freddy!
Leave me the fuck alone, Freddy!
Is he gone?
Why would you leave me alone, Freddy?
Leave me alone, Freddy!
Hey!
Where the fuck is he?
Where is he?
Okay.
Wait!
Hey!
Alright.
No.
I can't put this thing...
Hello?
Ring it.
Holy fuck.
I didn't even mean to do that.
I won.
Gamer instinct.
Stick of butter.
I don't know why we have a stick of butter.
Game for babies.
Uh.
Night 3.
Do I dare even attempt Night 3?
Sure.
If I'm gonna...
I mean, I'm gonna go...
This is where the game gets real.
Right?
I'm now out of the tutorial.
I know how it works.
Hot damn stone cold.
This is where the real game begins.
Yeah.
Take a look.
I think so.
Oxy did appear in the hallway.
Chicken's already gone.
Where's the chicken?
Chicken in here?
Where did you go?
Get out of here, man.
Come on, man.
Dude.
You?
This person there pissed me.
Shit.
Where's the bird?
Where's the...
Yes.
Yeah.
You.
Oh.
Chicken?
Yeah.
How did you get through my shield?
I had a shield.
What?
What happened?
How did he get through the shield?
Oxy is defeated by the flashlight.
Oh, right.
You have to like...
And he'll go away.
All right.
Let's go back to the basement.
Every jump scare, I get electrocuted with 200 volts.
That's just what your body does.
I've been...
Fuck.
I'm gonna change the title of this stream.
Watch a guy get electrocuted over and over again.
You know what?
If anyone wanted to make like a compilation of all the jump scares, but put like a...
Like electricity noise before it.
Just guys shocking himself.
What happened?
Oy vey.
From a race car?
I don't know what that is.
Get me out of here.
Shut it down.
No escape.
Would you recommend it against sleepiness?
What?
Did it break?
Shut it down.
How do I leave?
Restart?
Oh, okay.
Start it?
Restart the game.
That button.
Where's that button?
Where do I restart?
Library, store, exit game and then just restart it?
I lost you guys.
What?
Shut it down.
Exit.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
Just open it back up.
Hey, there we go.
Turn off your PC.
What's wrong with this chat?
What do you mean?
Wait.
Launch.
First gamer moment of 2020.
Why?
What do you mean?
What happened?
Yeah.
Relax.
What?
You actually did it, Omega Lowell.
What are you talking about?
What did I do wrong?
Continue.
All right.
Let's try the other ones.
So that was two.
This is three.
I have this weird memory of Five Nights at Freddy's 3 being terrible.
This is the one that sucks, right?
Yes.
Kind of.
Well, you might as well see it.
What's the one where you're in the bedroom and you're like the little kid in the bedroom?
Hey, hey.
Glad you came back for another night.
It'll be a lot better.
What did I do?
That was light.
That was vent.
I pressed that button.
No, no, no.
Hey, man.
Hey, Bart.
Come on into the bus, man.
Totally, man.
I'll get you to school on time.
I like this one because the screen is bigger.
Is there a light I can put in here?
Oh, yeah.
This one sucks.
It's the bunny that...
Yeah, this one's not good.
I don't like this one.
This one sucks.
I played this on iPad and I was like, this game sucks.
Where's that?
New error.
Sonya?
I already lose?
Did I lose already?
Oh, shit, right.
He's gonna scream my face.
He's gonna scream in my face.
What's happening?
he's gonna scream in my face hey where is he there he is there he is that bastard hey nothing
happens on night one oh well let's i at least want to see him walk by the screen we got to see it at
least once all right hey happy halloween by the way don't eat too much candy is it hey is it dark
out yet it's not even dark out i have this like big bright orange light that i want to put on oh
look at that it's very graphics we went to halloween authentic vr experience including
using scanned photographs for reference and using original performance routines where applicable
all right all right let's at least see the monster in five nights at freddy's three
oh you're getting something that you've always wanted i'm playing every five nights at freddy's
game on stream i never thought i'd see the day where i actually do this really dark in the uk
oh hey happy halloween in the uk can i turn the light on here
there he is what's that for man what the hell happened why'd you do that it wasn't even funny
can occur why'd you think it's broken shot gonna truly i'll be back i'll be back i'll see you in a
minute i'm going to get another fuck truly i'm not playing this one again i'm playing i'm doing the
next one this one does that hurt my body hair this overexposed camera too hey who who ordered
the pizza who wanted the bird's nest you have tiktok hair uh this kind of is what it looks like
when you make a bowl of spaghetti this is just spaghetti this is a bowl you're looking down at
your delicious bowl of spaghetti right now don't you just want to go in there with a fork and like
twirl it around and just okay uh i'm i'll be right back that literally i almost died on camera i'll
be right back i'm back all right let me just wipe the lens that was just horrible everything about
that sucked the last one i'm gonna do all of them man don't worry genuine fear but that's the
thing look if anybody screams in your face right in your eyes you could tell me you were going to
do that and it would still fuck me up you understand you could seriously you could tell me hey jeremy i
just want to let you know i'm going to scream in your face right now and i go okay well that
sucks i don't really want you to do that but i'm ready for you and if you went like
yeah like i i'd go it doesn't matter if you know what's gonna happen it just sucks uh let me
my camera look hold on wait i'm gonna put on the scary light remember that picture that somebody
linked oh i just look red hold on let me fix this you look you made it a plastic i know it's my web
this webcam sucks guys oh it's all right it's a little scary in here and once the sun goes down
you know here this looks like every movie that jason statham is in this is just what
it looks the color scheme of every one of his movies i just now i just need to like have my
heart explode if i go underneath like 800 beats per minute or something whatever it is this is a
boomer actor what am i looking at oh i was like what the fuck okay once the sun comes down this
is gonna be really cool it's gonna be like a weird fucking scary room for you guys you don't have
candles if you want me to light candles and put them around me when i could knock them fucking
over and not know about it and burn this place down come on i gotta have a little bit of common
sense here i'm a shotgun it's really that was so loud that just hurt my ears did you pee your
pants now turn the light off in the room how's that better is this spooky good ten out of ten
good the light at a lower angle it is it's going like going up into here there's someone in your
room with the lights well can you still is this like is this where the face is detected i've seen
that meme it does make more sense i'm gonna just say so you get it now so you have so if you go
see a scary movie in the daytime with like a matinee at 11 o'clock in the morning it's it
sucks because when you leave the theater it's goes back to normal and i don't i hate it for 9k andy
pretty fuck that's pretty good voice crack stop saying andy i'm just react oh it's that thing i
just got scared stop all right i'm never gonna say the word andy ever again unless i have a person
that is in my life that i know that's name is andy wait no i'm ready this is scary i'm like i'm a
scary guy you're like over there watching me and i'm like hold on i'm ready play the game i'm taking
it's been down in two hours with my eyes in front of a mirror that blows in my eyes
give me a minute i'm taking a two minute break and i've been vr i'm gonna be here all night
did i bring my control we're gonna do five nights at freddy's for the ultimatum vr just get one more
taste i know about the screen don't worry i got it all right see you in a minute halloween you jokers
jokers or is the worst one i have to i have to play them all maybe some tape i need to i might
need to reapply some tape all right we got two three this is dark rooms oh wait i don't hear
anything on with plus traps stop plus trap on the x on with flush for flashlight stop him on the x
have a flashlight i don't get it up him on the x does he run at you what's that counter up there
time it when that hits zero let it move hey you little shit okay he's scooby-dooing over there
play uh what's my favorite pizza uh thin crust pepperoni pizza is my favorite pizza
and crust no other bullshit on it or garlic and onion garlic onion marinara mozzarella
give me some shredded chicken on it too and a drizzle of olive oil uh stuffed crust pizza is
incredible disgusting oh fuck deep dish i'm sorry it's too doughy too doughy and thick and
push it up in your mouth now don't like it thin crispy crust pepperoni marinara marinara holy
shit you little asshole he's got me he's got me he's got me he's got me what happened why am i
what what was that yeah oh i got him i got him got him you stay right there
give me that present right now berries and chocolate no marshmallows and blueberry what the
fuck what else is there dark rooms plus trap nightmare bb oh it's just different versions
of this they get harder i see i try balloon boy lost a headphone no no no no no jesus don't do that
move get in my fucking mouth already i can get it let's get it excuse me uh whatever whatever
yeah whatever you don't like it then whatever but you don't like my potty mouth now okay here it
comes come on now and d oh come on i'm doing this one more time that's it what if you just don't do
anything i just don't do anything will he scream in my face i just pressed every button okay here
it comes you shithead okay here we go here we go here we go here we go credit shelf lol why
are you saying that parts and services bonnie oh i'm getting close to the shelf okay grab and
release push buttons repair bonnie make repairs face screen welcome back to parts and service
oh no it looks like bonnie's guitar is out of tune and must be recalibrated
first we must access his harmonization module located inside his secondary throat pipe
to access the throat pipe both eyes must first be removed you must be as precise as possible
when removing the eyes from their respective sockets first firmly grip bonnie's left eye
and carefully remove it from its socket that's this one
great job deposit the left eye in the cleaning receptacle on your left well done now firmly
grip bonnie's right eye and carefully remove it from its deposit the right eye in the cleaning
receptacle on your right excuse me what happened there attention back to parts and service great
job deposit the left well done now firmly oh bonnie's right eye and carefully remove
deposit the right eye in the cleaning receptacle on your right good job to open bonnie's face plate
carefully press the two buttons located on either side of bonnie's jaw when done correctly you
should hear two small clicks at the same time well done you now have access to bonnie's harmonization
module press the blinking button inside bonnie's secondary throat pipe to enter calibration mode
i've played this game with the alligator and you take the teeth out and if you get it wrong
he smashes his mouth on your hand something is not right one of those notes is out of tune
you may push the button again to replay the audio check press the colored button that
corresponds to the incorrect note what okay hold on i don't know i don't play guitar
uh re green green green press the blinking button again to verify your work
yep great job bonnie is in tune and ready for his solo let's close him up simply replace both
eyes in the same order that you remove them then close up the face plate and we'll call it a day
well done that concludes your parts and services task oh see you next time got it yeah chat was
wrong you guys are wrong this is freddy for asbear dude scott carthorne probably has made
500 million dollars off this he i guarantee he has a gold toilet he's probably got like a gold house
hey chico probably good for him laughing my ass off see right now he's he probably gets a
notification when a five nights at freddy's stream happens right now he's probably on his toilet
with his gold plated toilet paper and he's probably just going yeah pretty good out here
that's god available two parts in service there have been customer complaints about
i just want a piece of the gold i don't need all i don't i only want a piece of
the gold not all of it place it in the refuse bin on your right what did it say remove the
food particles how many how do you have pizza stuck to your head food particles
it looks good job make sure chica is not hiding any other treats inside her beak
she knows to open her beak carefully press the two buttons located on the sides of chica's head
when they get when can vr have like taste mode it looks like chica has picked up some unwanted
friends to clear the infestation apply the fast bear entertainment restaurant grade chemis spray
to chica's exterior oh press the button under the hanging canister to activate the chemis spray
avoid inhaling the chemis spray exposure to cleaning disinfecting and maintenance
may result in respiratory problems skin or eye irritation good job now reattach chica's upper arm
hand and cupcake plate upper arm i dropped it don't scream at me upper arm hand and and
cupcake plate well done oh no it looks like chica needs another dose of the chemis spray
do not let the infestation spread be sure to give the canister button another push as needed
now what return the cupcakes to chica's plate what what do you mean get over here great job
chica is ready to serve pizza and hugs to the kids again take a complimentary slice of pizza
for a job well done is serious oh how they doing this to us go on take it oh why you this is like
my favorite pizza ever thin crust pepperoni pizza delicious see you next time oh i that's how much i
eat too i almost i eat a whole pizza eater roach hey speaking of cola i've got an adult cola over
here that i think i want to have a sip of it hurt that like sucked it was a suit my like my
vr nose is huge oh okay don't fall these i like these are kind of fun all right freddy parts and
services i'm gonna 100 this off the game but this part the forbidden adult cola welcome back to
parts and service it looks like one of our guests left a personal item on our star attraction let's
return it to the lost and found carefully grab and remove the child's hat from freddy's mouth
freddy's got a pretty good hold of good job now place the hat in the lost and found bin on your
right crunched up this kid while we're at it let's make sure there isn't anything else stuck inside
to access freddy's chest cavity grab freddy's bow tie and pull it outwards well done freddy's
chest cavity is now open remove the child's watch and place it in the lost and found bin
be careful not to touch any of freddy's sensitive wiring okay let's see it no i want to see pumpkins
i want to see germa pumpkins i want to see the pumpkins for one day only the sun is a pumpkin
i want to see germa pumpkin good job it appears there is a child's shoe wedged behind freddy's
music box the music box must be removed before you can access the child's shoe how do i get that
gently grasp the music box and extract it from freddy's chest cavity before the safety latch
descends what's this what's this music box i don't know what that is i don't know what a music box
is this it right is that is that the music box is this it carefully place the music box on the
work table to your left great job to reset the safety latch press the button located on freddy's
endoskeleton now remove the child's shoe and place it in the lost and found bin don't fuck with me
here don't fuck with me don't fuck with me i see some fucking germa pumpkins please well done
return the music box to freddy's chest cavity and we'll call it a day oh no you seem to have
mishandled freddy's music box this is not good a replacement may be found on the work table
a slow and even pace is recommended crisis averted to close freddy's chest cavity
press the large black button on the center of freddy's face
that concludes your time in parts and service your pain will be docked accordingly
oh what oh you know what i was hey why did you what was that for why did you do that
hey you know what's like a cool uh for halloween if you want to watch um you guys have you guys
have seen operator it's like like a claymation stop motion horror short it's awesome never seen
operator okay do yourself a favor halloween tonight go watch there's two of them go watch
operator and then operator 2 it's terrifying it's about this it just i don't i'm not gonna
give away just watch it's crazy it's fucking horrifying make sure it's the claymation one
there's a couple other things that are called operator you'll know it if it's like a claymation
yeah somebody blink it it's like it's like six minutes long it's not it's not long
you got hey if you got like four you've got like seven hours to watch this stream you've got like
seven minutes to watch operator watch it on stream no no i wouldn't i'm making a third one
and i want to watch it so give them the views act two parts in service foxy has been out of
commission for quite some time this series of simple repairs should return him to full working
condition first carefully pick up and place foxy's head on his endoskeleton okay oh no
it looks like foxy's proprietary servo motors are malfunctioning it is recommended that you keep an
eye on foxy at all times you will need to place new control fuses in the exposed receptacles to
continue uh-huh retrieve the fuse from drawer number one that matches foxy's leg receptacle
for number one bodily harm wait for foxy's legs to stop moving before inserting the control
it's red red don't fucking do that don't move the job okay foxy has regained control of his legs
a gentle reminder it is recommended that you keep an eye on foxy at all times i've got an eye on
him i can see him no it looks like a former employee attempted to repair foxy's chest motor
using an incorrect fuse carefully remove the incorrect fuse from foxy's chest and inserted
i can't get in there receptacle i can't get i can't get in there dude he's
ow i'm looking at it i'm looking at it well done all right the remaining chest fuses are located in
drawers number two and number four fix both fuses to continue two that's two two and four
um okay red red green red red red red green red red don't hit me let's draw two let's draw two
green green green blue blue blue blue let's draw two let's draw two oh green green green blue blue
green green green blue blue blue blue green green green blue blue blue blue don't bite me you
motherfucker i don't i'm sorry foxy but i gotta reach under there fuck him all right i gotta
retrieve foxy's eye from drawer number three when foxy's eyepatch is fully open place the eye back
into his eye socket colorize fuck you no don't run no you stupid video game you dumb video game
dumb video game dumb video game dumb video game dumb but he came out of the ground i grabbed it
welcome back to parts in service oh no it looks like foxy's proprietary
servo no i need that i need that that's
welcome back to parts in service foxy oh no it looks like foxy's proprietary servo motors
are malfunctioning it is recommended that you keep an eye on foxy at all times you will need
to place new control fuses in the exposed receptacles to continue retrieve the fuse
from drawer number one foxy's leg receptacle to avoid bodily harm wait for foxy's legs to
stop moving before inserting the control fuse what oh good job foxy has regained control of
his legs a gentle reminder it is recommended that you keep an eye on foxy at all times okay
sick oh no it looks like a former employee attempted to repair foxy's chest motor using
an incorrect fuse carefully remove the incorrect fuse from foxy's chest
and insert it into foxy's upper arm receptacle well done the remaining chest fuses are located
in drawers number two blue blue blue red both fuses to continue okay now we blue blue blue green
blue blue green blue good job all right go free foxy's eye from drawer number three
when foxy's eye patch is fully open place the eye back into his eye socket well done
this concludes all your parts and service tasks
okay that sounds like a scream fog fog raid raid actual raid
we raid we're gonna raid what happened who raided us i can't see we got a raid what is it we got a
raid from g mart thanks g mart welcome everybody oh raid i saw it yeah it's right there from
wait was that like two hours ago thanks for the serious things i didn't see it raid someone sir
i'm currently streaming oh dude raid raid someone i may uh maybe later maybe later tonight
well right oh shit it's dark out actually kind of scary you guys straight up bully this guy huh
remember who holds all the keys here i don't haven't in probably three or four years
it's me this light actually is hurting my head did you go see did you see operator yet
have tiny hands whatever you'll you'll get over it oh i won't well what i'm gonna get a hand
enlargement surgery that was fun it's not working aim one claim your prize
who's this who's this character green's tiny yeah there are like 10k people here
oh we dropped down to 9800 move 8.9k and
hey you know what i i do actually have something to say it didn't kind of seem like yesterday
that this stream was seeing like five six seven okay on every stream i took like three months off
and i came back and this like eight to twelve thousand people here a stream that's fucking that's
insane when did that happen when the fuck did that happen second germa need to break 20k no
i mean this this channel has seen a lot of support from other channels i mean obviously like vine
sauce like many joe those guys have been huge just huge supporters of the stream which is
unbelievable i can't even think but like ludwig too uh ludwig has been you know he sent you guys
here a bunch of times if you if you're from ludwig we've seen a lot of support from other
streamers i can't even fucking fathom oh hey you're here let's go kit boga too kit boga was
another one that i saw a lot of new people from kit boga oh it just seems like a lot of people
have just kind of been exposed to me over the last like 12 months so hope you like it and if you don't
you know you can never mind welcome to vet repair fazbear entertainment priders yeah that's another
one most comfortable facilities each facility is a ton a lot it's kind of hard to keep up with it's
been the four active indicator lights mean we have a well-functioning ventilation system
your headlamp should protect you from any critters who may have stumbled into the ducts
as a certified vent technician you should need no instruction however in case of an emergency
it is important to remember that as the vent technician you should never under any circumstances
attempt to pull the heater okay cool great i'm what do i do oh i already fucking hate it
i already hate it yeah okay get the fuck out of here oh shit okay come on let's what do oh
oh hello wait a minute where is it i hear it i don't know i hear it i don't i hear i don't know
what i hear it where is it i hear it i don't know i don't i hear it i hear it where is it i hear it
drink drink drink drink drink yeah bro fucking drink found it what what get away from me
what's the menu on the screen what there's nothing here get away from me get away from me you little
shit there's no there's no valve there button hate it off already the button do i press look down red
red orange blue green green orange red green blue orange orange blue blue fucking there's
something in the way green orange red orange blue orange blue red orange orange blue red orange blue
green red green red off please 22 degrees good job see you next time that does suck that does
suck uh i thought this was mr game and watch using proprietary technology developed by fazbear
entertainment our vr development teams were able to use vintage control boards inard like plug and
play digitally recreating performances and who's inard and hard stark it's empty it went okay went
how let's go this is i like this one actually i don't hate this or wasted white girl wasted
i'm in i'm in virtual i'm in virtual reality you don't know every beer you drink in vr is times
three don't you get it every time i consume one ounce of alcohol it's four ounces in here
welcome to circus babies entertainment and rental it has been zero days since last incident
emergency ventilation repairs may be necessary to reach the boiler room on sub basement g
we apologize for the claustrophobic accommodations of the secondary service elevator
but the comfort of the main elevator is well above your pay grade now let's get to work
yep wait why did i i don't know what to do motion trigger breaker room excuse me i'm pretty good at
these well done hold you well done can you get a little harder please meet again game over everyone
oh it's not opening it how did this move did this chat shifted going lower into hell i like
these more than the actual freddy games oh no oh no no no no no i oh no oh no motion trigger
secondary service elevator ventilation shaft give me that give me that give me that give me
give me give me give me give me go go go go go go point they stole that from super mario they're
in trouble hey you what dick where is he holy shit it's you um um um hold on stay right there
okay no you stay over there please hold on we gotta get this correct okay oh oh oh this is not
right oh um oh so yeah hey he is oh well you guys i need that i need okay fuck you
oh there you go very good he was right there please move please move move please move please
out of my way please move your face out of my way please move your face please please move please
move shit shit shit well done open tier three here we go happens on tier three okay i must cut my
head off what is this all right focus focus focus i gotta focus focus focus focus motion trigger
boiler room focus oh fucking saw god damn it it's saw well done
wait what i didn't get i didn't do it i lost what's going on
shit shit are you dummy what are you dumb what are you didn't go to school
school where is he what you're not going to middle school you can't even get middle school
shit right look at that 72 degrees see you next time i dropped out of the first grade
it's not even what oh germa he was that was rude but because i was dumb because i didn't i'm
talking what that that puzzle was like a fourth grade education you're talking about
yeah night terrors okay bullying us what are you talking about i didn't even see this
i what is it i don't know what it wants me to do christ oh yeah this one sucks
who's talking i don't fuck with me that here do i have a battery in my flashlight or no
fuck did you just run to holy shit you little weirdo where's the peewee herman guy
i scared him i win i don't understand this i hate that one that one sucks
oh i did it all how much how much money do i have uh does that do two dollars what's this
this is unlockable wait this is hard mode you have to complete it all i get it all right well
this is hard mode for welcome back to parts and service oh no it looks like bonnie's guitar is
out of tune and must be recalibrated first we must access his harmonization module located inside
his secondary throat pipe to access the throat pipe both eyes must first be removed you must
be as precise as possible when removing the eyes from their respective sockets first firmly grip
bonnie's left eye and carefully remove it from its socket great job deposit the left eye in the
cleaning receptacle on your left well done now deposit the right eye good job to open bonnie's
face plate carefully press well done you now have access something is not right one of those notes
is out of tune you may push the button again to replay the audio check press the colored button
that corresponds to the impress the blinking button again to verify your work great job
bonnie is in tune and ready for his solo let's close him up simply replace both eyes in the same
order that you remove them then close up the face plate and we'll call it a day well done
that concludes the parts and services task see you next time all right we're moving on this was fun
i enjoyed this one this was good it's just too much some of these are too much for me though
halloween one where is it what games next uh we have a couple of choices here hospitality vr which
is you sit in a room and think scream in your face or the walking dead vr halloween dlc oh i
don't i didn't buy that walking dead hospital hospitality hospital hospital hospital all right
well here hospitality is like 10 minutes i'm gonna play that first i'm gonna play hospitality vr uh
where is it hospitality this is a 10 minute game what about saw 2 don't control hospitality
oh whatever you're gonna load you might not even load oh no no loading you're not gonna do it
go for it i want to do it all right we're playing walking dead hospitality vr does not want to load
the headset has to be on i don't think so loading i guess you don't want to do it try this
reload it recent are you okay we're going back to home i can get it through home
i have boneworks i do have boneworks uh okay hospitality i mean i'm boneworks is not a
halloween game here we go enter just press enter i don't care all right this is an experience where
you get scared missed all the phasmophobia spam i recommend sitting during this experience look
forward and hold any button to calibrate while we're standing your heart quality setting hi
oh this is kind of like a ride yeah this is a ride at disney but i'm standing
it's kind of chase off hi i'm just walking by you that is that's it i'm in the chair
i have no hands so let's just drink i caught it it's caught in the microphone it's caught in
the microphone let's just let's just enjoy the movie what the fuck holy shit man excuse me sir
yeah what is it you can't bring alcohol onto the ride what are you talking about this is a great
this is a grape juice this is grape soda sir that's very clearly an alcoholic beverage it's a truly
i drink those all the time they're delicious don't you love these everybody loves them
yeah i'll be all right whoa hey hey look at this you want to go to the bar after this too and get
like fucked up yeah yeah yeah we waited like 25 30 minutes for this fucking ride shut up you shut up
lady hey what is she what do you want to calm down have it truly what the fuck what happens
this is a guy where's the where's the bad guy hey hey dude hey dude hey when the when the actor
comes down the hallway he wanted to fight him no i don't want you to fucking fight him yeah you
sure no just let's enjoy the fucking ride please you're embarrassing the fuck out of everybody here
all right man okay shut up man i'm kidding around with you what oh shit hey i heard something over
this way we all heard it hey have you guys been on a tower of terror yet that shit's crazy i threw
up in my mouth like four times you want you don't you said you don't want some can't wait to get
off this fucking ride with this guy i swear to god just technical difficulties are we on a ride
or are we in just a in a hospital hey someone's coming out of there oh you're big and scary you're
a big scary guy now you see that thing's moving on its own how do you guys do that anyways you
got a fog machine back there i got a string you pull it with strings right whatever i spilled
a little on me all right i'll get it fps two fps what do you mean two fps shh hold on right now
there's somebody that's just running around opening and closing these doors
no ghost do you want to press a button okay that was fun yeah that's a pretty good actor
hey don't really there's always something it's always somebody that in these rides
or in these experiences that does this and like fucking don't be this person you ready
okay god damn it man please pretty good effects hey don't worry they can't touch you they can't
touch you otherwise they get arrested all they can do is yell at you if they touch you they go
they go to jail i know i read that online on snopes it's in your room it's not in my room
yeah or right at the end of the harry potter ride every time you ride the fucking harry potter
rides at universal i'm gonna be behind you yeah man that was awesome i know i we all rode the
same ride we know it was good or you hear it's like well that's a good thing i don't want to
clean that up i think it's gonna get up oh shit all right well i don't feel like this is a watch
dogs character not anymore it's huge not anymore it's huge they can't touch you though watch dogs
because it's three fps
okay good nice very nice what's that i hear sounds i don't like it watch dogs
our most ambitious title yet just put as many collectibles on the mini map as possible so
we can say that our most ambitious title what's what's going on in like the last three or four
years where every fucking single video game has to be the most ambitious title ever no just make
it fucking good we played mario and like mario chased a monkey up a staircase and we loved it
i don't care about all your collectibles you don't need like a 5 000 kilometer map
with like 10 million collectibles and like 30 000 worth of in-game currency shit which by the way
what the fuck's up with that if it's a 60 dollar game and what's up with you i've got more to say
i've got more to say you got something to say to me try to silence me our most imp oh the most
ambitious game ever what am i having to make a good game why can't you say are a good game
that we made this person's doing this on the ride it's like dude we all right man we get it can we
enjoy the scary ride now and another thing ubisoft is just good it's going out of control
it's like dude we get it okay cool uh we're trying to enjoy the fucking tower of terror
hey meet me outside the exit if you want more shit from me oh that was cool though that was
pretty cool hey well that was all right that was cool that was cool that i liked it i liked it
because we're gonna ride a ride together no it wasn't it was good hold on i'm trying how do i
spell this hospitality guys guys guys this game is two dollars okay relax i think this came out
like four years ago play phasmophobia i don't have any god damn friends like it's soloed
fuck that no i got i got plenty of friends okay like god hand do you know what day it is it's
not like fucking thursday it's halloween fucking watch dogs man we're just shit loaded hold on
whoa we had 10 community subs from super foil 10 community subs from princess i've been holding
this for like an hour princess hotcakes super foil thanks to the 10 subs each and then alex
and nation thank you five subs uh elusive saint five subs as well thanks guys uh let's do walking
dead let's let's go you have only fans lighting uh what kind of terrifying only fans are you
subscribed to this is what only fans lighting is like this is scary i wouldn't i wouldn't pay for
this is terrifying all right walking dead it is let's go i'm in hold on he hates only fans
i don't have an i don't care like i i think you're seriously overestimate how much i give a shit
about any of this stuff what's my only fans uh here he doesn't care no all right walking dead
let's go i'm going in it's like pitch black in here by the way in my entire place i've been told
the walking dead is actually really good go feet what's all right let's get out of here
i have the walking dead vr where is it i'm not waltz of the wizard saints and sinners there it is
all right let's do it oh no oh somebody uh is there a mod here is hey leather jacket
specifically i gotta i gotta change the title of the damn stream it says we're playing five
nights at freddy's i'm not even in a fucking category why does he keep doing this how am i
not in a category what the fuck twitch i'm in games and demos what the fuck is this talking about
all right no more squares for the rest of the night all right does it say i'm playing the
walking dead i'm just getting 50 bucks oh my god a human uh 5 000 bits take off your shirt all
right well i mean you gave me 50 dollars thanks for the 50 bucks how do they look by the way
are we good how's the tape tape still on there holy shit laughing my ass off what
third nipple this is tape what no this is tape this is like kinetic tape what do you guys say
you're freaking me out what happened you you guys are freaking me the fuck out what happened
okay no we're good okay walking dead saints instead of pressing hold hmd
reset your current play stance for sitting or standing hold l menu plus r menu what is it saying
what are you talking about what is it telling me what do you want to do
and you button yeah i first sir yeah but i mean i don't understand this how do i get out of this
old l menu plus plus r menu for eight vr is not ready for humans
okay gameplay nausea reduction a hundred percent what does that mean what are you guys doing
why are you guys spamming me right handed stop stop voice immersion what was that what was this
number what was that number is a raid who's raiding who's raiding who is it what was it
primer raid what the fuck are you guys doing what degrees was it help me please reset two
distance all right fuck this let's go standard hurry standard voice selection i'm ready i'm ready
just another survivor let's do this let's do this people call me people call me the tourist i'm
ready just another survivor just another survivor let's do this hey i'm a spaghetti person
what do i look like ale this must be pretty good
press the hmd reset button to reset your current play style or enter the world of the walking dead
you need to learn the gameplay oh that's my get that off reach down to your left hip and grab
the small weapon in the holster turn it and let go good reach down to your right hip and grab
this small weapon in the holster go to the holster and let go this is this is good this feels pretty
good reach to your right shoulder and grab the big weapon okay i like this let it go reach over your
left shoulder grab pull up the backpack let go the backpack it will auto return to the same shoulder
take food from your backpack and hold it to your mouth to eat restore stamina nutrients stew
okay take bandages and wrap it around your arm
this audio is is freaking me well your journal that's not a journal reach over your right side
grab your journal ah ah do you hear i'm in the game ah this is fucked up do you hear me
oh hey everybody you hear that right there's an echo
hey hey everybody how are you my name is turbo see no you can hear me in the game
journal tracks your tasks it's a map and provides helpful info i can hear myself fucking talking
angle button it's a square button where okay let's go pick up the ship i'm ready
okay talk walk walk double tap is run steam grab fire interact pause look left look right steam grab
that and i'm sick i have durability okay lead to the next tutorial holy shit cool all right
one
they like combat and running running a stamina will make the combat difficult let's hit myself in the
mouth murder get away from me
fun i don't need to learn how to do that i already know how to do that
use the trigger to interrupt the offhand to eject the magazine
have a magazine from your ammo the person by the exit
oh
money in here but if the city is where you're headed i suspect your story
is just beginning how are you about it new orleans city limits today one lone soul
to enough the dead we think to be fearing in the big easy help us out the way the tower on one side
spouting their ideals and shunning any folks who don't be toeing the line hey don't kill that guy
don't shoot that guy you shot that guy and by the way look off those reclaimed renegades are on
the up making everyone's skin crawl with their horror show tactics and the powder cake that's
going to make the whole city blue the reserve i can tell by the spark that jumped up in your eyes
if you've heard the legend the reserve is real when the flood to end up military bunker
never distributed to the people because the government didn't know its ass from a hole in the
ground i can't before they could figure it out the dead started walking happened to my right arm
oh meds military oh diamond dallas page and am and guess who's close to unearthing the mother
that's right you're looking at him snipe but this broken body has seen better days
and i need to get after it real quick before the fools get wise sure so if you find yourself
itching to step out of the bayou and help out an old man well you can find me in the cemetery
where i'm holed up there would be a 50 50 split in the future
i ain't greedy and i ain't no fool i'm in give it a ponder tourist you just might be what this
sinking city needs to keep his head above water but then again maybe you're the type
to pull the whole godforsaken place under what's it what get out of here this is my boat
this is my boat sky dance interactive presents the walking dead the only walking dead game
since 2010 that was worth playing fucking i'm going for it i think notes and drawings are
stored in your journal okay journals here right pretty long intro okay let's go graveyard strut
old man named henry lives in this graveyard told me to meet him here if i help him find the reserve
he'll split the supplies with me find the old man's hideout go let's find him punch
under i don't press down on the right trackpad you crouch i press the trigger to flip the melee
oh yeah thank you i'm way better at like stabbing than thrusting that i am at late
or that is grab the top of the flat surface and push down
oh
it's dead i can't i can't see him it's just so bright you're seeing this
requires a broad range of motion dead guy
got him i sub expired somebody open oh the weapons right
oh my arm oh that's a real injury that's a real one that's a lasting one
oh that's gonna be a huge bruise fucker oh that's nasty that's nasty actually nasty
i mean it's not bleeding but it really hurts oh it is bleeding kind of oh it's like bleeding
under the skin i'm burning that shelf by the way he said oh it hurts because i had to stab a guy
oh i did it okay uh this is the old man's hideout a rusted out bus better look around try to piece
together what what happened find clues well art of darkness uh axe man loved as maybe a band
teacher he left ass here amongst custom footwear upgrade okay this is uh i guess an upgrade tree
oh yeah or i appreciate rival station amongst sterile bandage upgrade
i don't have a gun i'm gonna get an ammo for a gun
raid each crafting station to unlock the next recipe craft new items
oh nothing asteroid raid cool who is it i had an inkling and by god i was spoiled
all right it's out there it exists this job i found proves it still so much work to be done stones
they gotta be overturned riddles that need solving actually oh it's a harry potter one and frequency
61 has to be connected to the reserve somehow command and control i'm guessing that's the next
if i can get this blasted radio repaired and if someone is still inside as soon as my ankle
feels steady i'm gonna take the skiffle mansion in the garden district when niles and i recorded
the tip one and a two the blue palace it's my best yeah nice microphone for the radio powers
covered with the bus battery just got connected can't go out at night got encryption covered can't
afford any eavesdroppers that's what haven't slept in three days these creaky bones are rattling
with excitement so quietly imagine what might be in there grub art raids weapons ammo all of our
life sent me up for a decade all through the night but your years is not
hell i'd even be willing to split 40 60 to make all this easier
hope they show up before it's too late getting old it's that was the battery a gun that's how i had
a gun oh where's my gun there it is okay let's go escows that way wait all right resting place
run hear the bells run henry believed repairing the radio would get him close to the curb
we need to get the shallows track down those party yeah the shallows we're gonna find the skiff
let's go food edison let's go we go this is this is the shiv go to here shallows shallows at one
oh to the oh i do this wrong fix the strategy fix the radio i'm not running
up i don't run i can't run that is the right way go back am i crouching or something what's going
on hand up like this button here on the base pad select the location on the map the shallows
selected go to the shallows go here go here turn off nausea reduction it looks terrible
does it better oh my fucking god that was unbelievably awful i was gonna shoot someone
i just want to shoot somebody all right we're gonna go find prepare the radio i'm radio stuff
i missed and he was standing still how does that happen i have no idea please i need your help
easy there oh where is it my husband he's turned my husband i have no one my husband
he's turned he begged me not to let it happen but i just couldn't pull the trigger i can help you
my husband my husband my husband he's broken he's broken i can't what am i gonna do
it was it was glitched out it was broken what am i gonna do oh i can't run unhinged okay there's
only so many times i'm gonna sit there and go my husband my husband my husband my husband
my husband before it's like all right listen i gotta keep moving lady
keep triggering it what load up he's right there what's the problem a live stream video or clip
whisper private message what appropriate germany five's channel points towards what are you doing
this is the strongest fucking person ever
oh okay and from here where oh this is you want with your fingertips this is super human strength
like spider-man hello everybody in here oh free soda
been home and i'm bald headshots
oh shit oh shit
ah mo back from beauty and the beast here they're oh i got okay this microphone good
keyboard do i need a keyboard watch uh i'm hungry aimer headset oh cool i put it on all right so
what else we need follow the microphone install the antenna now have a battery battery to the
backpack take it what i mean i could probably use it right lighter oh shit this is awesome okay
put this keep this too i don't want that oh spoon i want that uh razor blades give me those
i want it band-aids yeah
the help hard skill this game's actually pretty good this is pretty fun oh anyone out there
all the image oh ow ow that hurt open uh yeah sure
just let go of me just let go i need any bandage yeah okay good i got it down pretty well i got it
down well
we're gone out andy out andy i i just read it i'm sorry hit him off
hit him off i'm gonna break damn it a bill back up wait he's a fool
do everything
we're good oh shit that hurt is that my health bar what's the yellow one i got it oh fun fun part
uh hold on where did i end up i'm all the way over here i gotta pee pee time pee time and water
uh even though i have the kinetic tape all over me starting to get starting a little painful
easy i'm right back i have returned oh we did get some subs though hold on oh it's vr josh what's
going on josh thanks to the subs 10 community subs from vr josh thank you josh and then austin
atlantis gave 10 and uh balls for brains gave five uh so i'm probably gonna i'm don't think
i'm gonna be able to do this so i took the kinetic tape off and like my body's going to shit right
now i've had some tightness over the last three or four days uh especially my chest
and i the tape was bothering me i had to take it off see you next week at least six he's falling
apart i really am it sucks uh i'll go for we'll go for a little longer i'm actually interested
in this game so i don't know how much longer i'm gonna be able to do it though if i'm honest i
took the tape off i had two going down the back and then two going around the chest
so what knows i got them all all right let's get back in i wanted i want to play for a little
longer i mean this game's fun the bionic boomer uh do i have the right all right i'm going back
in go already i'm good i'm good i'll be good for a while stop stop stop rest i'll be okay
look at maybe like another 30 minutes we'll see 40 minutes let me know stop streaming no i'm not
done i'm having fun in my vr video game and i'm not gonna stop playing till i'm done
uh which is the right side these are this game's these a lot of these have been fun
i actually really like five nights at freddy's i'm surprised i'm saying that i love
i'm back in oh yep it's sweaty am i dying why am i covered in blood what's wrong with me
i have to go back to the house what's wrong with me i gotta go back
but i concluded that there was little quality evidence to support the use of other
i'll be positive telling me that i shouldn't go to sleep i can't i can't believe i shot that
lady it was glitched out but like man that was bad alvage items so alvage somebody's head
yeah what about what about razors phone headphones i got a lot from that lighter
uh cool all right and now let's go to bed get him to understand this
uh
he concluded that experts both back then using the tape i didn't look all right what's wrong with my
character i'm eating bad food and what that was on to the shallows wait wait the radio
all the microphone i didn't salvage that did i
right there wait i picked it up click the next page oh here we go microphone okay battery antenna
antenna go on the roof what's wrong with my character left to the bus antenna all the antenna
henry left in the bus the colors turn it on turn the antenna to get a strong signal
water channels holy shit back take contact on station 61 hello hello hello is anybody out there
anybody there hello hello hello waterfall hello hello hello waterfall waterfall
anybody i said i said waterfall that's not possible who is this the joker just someone
who enjoys waterfalls who is this big fan of all varieties you your mic funny why does that matter
i'm asking the questions are you alone do not lie i will find out and then this conversation's
over hey i am uh no a tiny guy someone else is here weird little guy staring me down
doesn't blink at all and he's got this twisted grin plastered on his filthy face
tell me what he looks like he's really short i'd say 12 inches head to toe kind of chubby
got his hands on his juice all the time creeping me out honestly shut up smart ass you're fucking
and i don't appreciate it if you're straight with me our conversation continues and believe me i'm
someone you want on your side i i know things things you're not going to get from any other
source i i need to know though that you're above board with you both with the mic down
i come first okay come meet me at the graveyard alone and i'm pretty sure i know who you are
what i'm most curious about is how you found this station and why you said waterfall
uh i okay i believe you're alone and i'm pretty sure i know oh i didn't want to skip who am i
i came across a journal belonged to a soldier this frequency waterfall gnarly
does anyone else know about it yes an old timer named omri but he's dead no clue about anyone else
fuck okay shit sorry uh okay i got what i need for now i know you're telling the truth
just remember and you tell me who you are ears everywhere i hear it all i get it your turn keep
it brief i got shit to do okay i come to the reserve reserve what do you know about it
i've heard of it what else you know everyone's heard of it you know you'd have to live in a hole
in the ground not to i'm interested in more than that yeah well how would i know more than anyone
else you mentioned your ears were everywhere you heard of me before i even set foot in older
seems like someone so informed would know a bit more than the average schmuck when it comes to
the thing everyone is talking about right not necessarily not too friendly are we all right
i'll drop it for now um you know what to call me but i don't know what to call you
you got a name i'm not telling you my name okay we don't ask anymore no need for the attitude
where you from can you share that how many subs if he shoots himself tonight
fuck look enough about me already i would say that how many subs if he shoots himself
so i came to nola to meet up with an old timer named omri
housing speaking to you through his radio he wound up dead along with a bunch of owls
oh i don't know anything about a dead old man the old man had a name and it was omri and it seems
like omri was trying to track you down there must have been a reason right i'm telling you i don't
know anything about what's going on up there there's no reason to trap me down we're going
in a circle going in a complete circle omri was on to something that was clear and it must have
been clear to the fuckers they killed him too so i've been straight with you why not be straight
with me maybe we can help each other cut the bullshit and i'm telling you i don't know anything
about what's going on up there there's no reason to trap me yes you do up there what do you mean
up there what are you talking about up there here with the rest of us where are you those that's
classified you don't have clearance in fact i don't even know i'm talking to you right now
pet the dog pet the dog there's something going on over here hold on just a minute
fuck shit no i should never have no no fuck off wait do you need
they coming for you shit it's windy here i don't know probably nothing hold on
let's get the strange sound that was not is ammo it's a septic
what do you need ammo weapon or something i make ammo let's go say hi
what was that might have been the old man a picture of bridge it's a weapon i have to use
this for weapons foreign oh shit uh i don't think i can kill these things
oh shit aliens are gonna be right around the corner guaranteed yep
oh
i've stopped it's getting to be too much like right here and right in here oh the game's boring
anyways thanks for streaming i wanted to go for like at least another 40 minutes
he's gonna bring out bugleberry i'm not bugleberry's not gonna show up till probably
thanksgiving check the link journal chat kinetic tape well thanks for watching everybody
i'm sorry we're cutting it like half an hour short but i just can't even if i was sitting
down it's just the weight of the device on my head for those of you that don't know i have
costochondritis and sometimes it's a new thing it's annoying but oh no i look fucking terrifying
happy halloween though that five nights at freddys is good hospitality disney ride was fun it was
two bucks don't even worry about it uh what else we play we played with three other games
that first game killed me that mansion game was insanely terrifying the mansion affected the
mansion took that murdered me in the first 40 minutes of the stream thanks a lot that's shit
load of subs came into a ton of people have subbed on top of the people that are already subbed
have a rest have a safe rest of your halloween everybody happy halloween we'll see in a few days
i'll see you on let's see wait let's all right this like i don't like this let's take the scary cam
off even worse that's fine we'll see you guys on uh here the subs by the way what's today today
is i'll probably see you guys on the fourth wednesday the fourth or thursday the fifth
probably wednesday the fourth so check the sus tomorrow the next day if you want an actual
accurate answer uh we'll do a raid yeah we'll raid somebody who are we gonna raid i see i'm
seeing a lot of names here but let me see who's currently live who's live right now we have not
raided uh joel in a long time and he's doing halloween shit too so go enjoy the rest of your
halloween spooky night with uh with varg skeletor with joel i'll see you guys in a few days happy
halloween i had fun just my body uh hates itself it was a shit load of people here there's a shit
load of people here every time now and i don't i don't even know what to say i hope you think
it's interesting i hope you're having fun here go say here's what i want you to say when you go to
joel say happy halloween joel that's really easy no say boo b o o exclamation point happy halloween
joel wow really interesting thing to say in a raid just say boo with two o's and then exclamation
point and behave thanks for the subs though seriously there was a lot tonight i'll see you
guys on probably wednesday last night you said you wouldn't be doing this in five years are you
gonna quit oh i never take anything i say seriously unless i'm directly looking into
your eyes in the camera all right good night guys go raid joel happy halloween see you in
a few days can somebody link me the clip of when i like broke my arm on my shelf
i just kind of want to see it in my own time i'll see you later