Hello, Perk. You guys asked for holo. There we go, now you should be able to hear me.
How you doing? If you're wondering about the mic change, it's because I'm using the index micro-
is it quiet? Let me turn it up. What is that? I wasn't wondering. Ow? What do you mean ow?
I just punched- oh shit, that's gonna happen, isn't it? All the time. I needed- all right, listen.
I needed freedom in my space, okay? In that room is my office. It's too cramped in there. I had to
upgrade my space, and that means bringing my entire computer setup, monitors, tower, keyboard,
into my fucking living room. So I would have streamed like three days ago,
because it wasn't feeling well. I had diarrhea. Bad. But I brought my entire computer into my
living room, so I couldn't do anything. So I just let it run its course. I think I'm okay today,
I hope so. We'll find out. You and I are going to find out very shortly if I've got to run away,
which I hope doesn't happen. And by the way, this is- the mic's going to sound a little better.
I'm holding- look, I'm just gonna go live, whatever. Okay, listen. Got an index. Oh my god!
Hey, look what I got for Christmas! I got an index! And I tripped over the wire and fucking
ate it. I have an index now, and I can't- how's my hair? Probably do. What do you mean? What?
No, it's because the mic- the webcam's like up on a thing. Like I have like a- I embedded it into
the fucking wall. I'm gonna trip over this guy, I know it. We're gonna play Boneworks first. So,
yeah, you'll hear me better when the headset's on. It looks beautiful. I can see you guys in here.
I'm just delaying it, because I hate getting into this fucking thing, because once I get in here,
I know that I'm gonna lose 400 or 500 hairs off the front of my head. That's why I don't like
doing this. I'm just like- I'm just making sure you guys have an image of me with an extra 400
here. Right in the front. I'm probably cutting out what I want. Sure, that I have hairs on the top
of my head, right? Is that what it sounds like? That's probably what it sounds like. Bobby? Also,
what do I hope that this looks okay? Because what I've been told is the index has a higher
field of view than all the other ones. By the way, pog. But it can make capturing it kind of
a pain in the ass. So, I have three different capture modes on this thing. I feel like I'm
working on a fucking sink with somebody. And they're down there. Yeah, so move two or three
inches to the right. The screws are right there. God, that was a pretty good joke. Am I going in?
I'm going in. I can see you guys in here. Let me get this on right. And I got that thing. Where am
I? My hands aren't on there. Hold on. There you are. What are you saying? What is your room like?
What? I gotta get I got these I look at these things. Tiny hands. I don't have to what do I
have big fucking hands. My hands are actually embarrassingly large. I hate it. I don't I don't
why do I have to log in? All right. This. This just reminded me of I know this is a joke. But
for a second, I was fucking furious. Because I thought this was like, like origin or something
like you got to log into origin before you play the game. I was about to get really, really mad.
That room makes me look tiny. It's a gigantic fucking living room. Yeah, you know who else looks
small you when you take all the furniture out of your living room, all the couch, the chairs,
the TVs, everything, you move your entire desktop into the center of the room. You probably got
going to look six feet tall anymore. It's up. I swear your cameras blurry. Oh, shit, I actually
forgot. You're right. You're right. Good. Good. I'm going to stall as long as I want because
once I get in, you know, we're good for like, we want to change the camera. You guys can't even
hear me. I've been talking shit for like a minute straight and nobody can hear me. I've just been
over there just just like talking shit. Nobody could hear it. Oh, what did I just say? It was
such it was like a good I said it was a whatever. Oh, right. Auto focus. Why the fuck do people put
auto focuses on a webcam doesn't move it in the same exact place you don't move you physically
don't move. Ready? Pretty good. Oh, shut up. I need to wear it. Otherwise, my doctor is going
to be mad that I did this today. All right, here we go. What does this say? Where's my center? There
we are. Hold on. Boneworks attention bonework subroutine operates on highly experimental
simulated physics. My pants are going to come down at some point during the stream.
It's nice and tight. Look at that. Oh, he's got an index. Oh, dude, he's got an index. What?
You can't do that unless you have one. Okay, I think I'm ready. Expert VR users only.
Finally, the penis stream. Please identify your real world height. They think I'm five nine. See?
Oh, look at how small you look in your room. I think it thinks I'm five nine. This is a
this is a big living room. That's not how tall we really are. So let's make it accurate.
Expert mode. Average height. Am I on the camera from over here? Make sure I'm in the right spot.
Can you guys still see me? Yeah, that's fine. I'm gonna be that's a cute look. I can go like
I can fucking go like this today. You know what I mean? I couldn't do that in the other room.
I'm gonna be standing. Are you sure? I don't know why that just said attention. Try seated mode if
you have a soul. Like wait, what do you mean? Like a soul? I'm soulless? I'm I'm not concerned
about my real world surroundings. I'm gonna be fine. Wait, what? Is your floor okay? Yeah,
yeah, that's fine. Soulless Andy. I think that looks all right. Administrator privileges granted.
Confirm measurements to proceed. You want to know the best part about the index? I know you're gonna
hear that. Look, by the way, I need to make a really this is a real warning for the stream.
The real warning for the stream is I'm going to punch myself in the face probably twice.
I'm gonna say two or three times. I am using the the index mic. So I am really sorry if all
of a sudden you hear like an explosion because I punched myself directly in the eyes. I'm just
saying it's possible. All looks fine. Yeah, save settings. Stress level zero. Boneworks.
So that I need to be aware of that because I put that on the ground so I don't get like killed in
here. That's like where I'm safe. As long as I'm like in this area, as long as I'm in this zone here,
I am safe. Okay, should I do anything? I'm not even capturing this. So who cares? This is loud
too. I gotta drop this. All right, that's better. Okay, new game story. Is this zipper down? Why
are we watching a movie? By the way, I haven't done this yet. I want to do this.
I want to watch a movie in VR and pretend like I have like a 500 inch screen. Movie night. Oh,
I can skip this. No, don't skip. By the way, this is the middle of my room. I'm not even like on
camera. I might need to recalibrate that. Should I skip the movie? No, I'm not going to skip the
movie. I don't know. Look, it's quiet. Why can't I do a peace sign? It doesn't look right. What's
wrong with my hands? They calibrate themselves. Object. Coffee cup. Indestructible.
Skip the shit out of me. I thought I was too far away. Coffee cup. Oh, that felt good. These
are cool. These are cool. That's fun. I have barely played with this, by the way. All right,
wait. Put it in the archive. Like I've barely done like this. Oh, it's weird though. I'm not.
Actually, do I pick things up like this? I think I do. Shit, it's kind of hard to get used to.
What? No, pick it up. Stick my pinky out. This is freaking me out. Oh my God. This is so easy.
Oh my God. It's so easy. All right. Disposal. It's so weird to do this. Honest to God. I feel
like I'm stuck on this. I know it's like I just have to use my hands the way that they normally
are but still put it in the gammon. I got a better idea. All right. Let go. Oh, I was holding on to
it. Skip the shit out of me. I didn't let it go. How do you jump? All right. I'm listening.
Because I didn't let it go. All right. Where do I go? Do it. There we go. How's the audio? We good?
Before I get really started here, I want to make sure you guys can hear me and shit.
We good? All right. Let's fucking go. Snap turn, crouch, locomotion. Oh, I don't need that. Look at
this. You think I need a snap turn? You think I need a snap turn? Can't do this in the other
fucking room. It's fun. It's a brick. I'm keeping this and I'm going to smash this on somebody's
fucking head in like two minutes. Our minds are directly connected to the void. Bone works.
There's some kind of diamond. Why am I holding this like a jeweler? If you die in real life,
do you die in the void? Probably. We're gonna fucking imagine that that's your head. Okay.
We're good. Pizza? What? Nobody throw. I can't throw with my left hand. Okay. You want to see?
That's right hand. Perfect, right? Let's try left hand.
How come we don't teach that in school? You know what I mean? Why don't we like teach people to be
both left and right dominated? You know what I mean? We should teach that because everybody
just uses the same hand for everything. Give me that. I want the fucking coffee cup.
How would you get this in real life? Not bad. Let's go.
Just wait. I'm fucking ready. Why am I crouching? Stand up. What's wrong with me? What's wrong with
my character? Why am I stop crouching? There we go. What does it say? All right. What? Oh, I got a
gun? Okay. Uh, 10 PM. Willie Arthur Ford was seen eating lunch in the anomalous object disposal
break room. Well, I'll sit on a, he's on a break, check his time, whatever. Like I probably could,
should I take this? I probably need this. Can I use this computer? No, I want, I could have fly
paper all over me. Let's go. How do I walk? I can't walk. Fix your webcam. What's wrong with it?
What's wrong with it? Yeah, I'll move it up. I'll just give me a minute. Okay. Key card, right?
Where's the key card go? Security director. All right. Key card. Oh, don't do that. Got these,
these fucking hotel keys. We got bags here. Honey, go, um, go to the front desk and find out what the
fuck is going on. Stupid fucking hotel key. What was that? Out of frame. All right. Let me fix it
right now. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me get, let me do it. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
All right. I'm just going to turn it this way a little bit. Is that better? That's probably better,
right? How's that? That's probably good. Game audio is low. It doesn't, it looks like it's pretty
high. All right. Let's go. This looks good. I have a normal house. I almost just fucking pulled the
whole, the whole tower down. Did I? No. Holy shit. That was terrifying. All right. Let's go. If I
need to move it a little more, I will. I think it's in a good spot though. All right. You don't
have any idea. I'm so excited to play with these and I heard that this was the thing to play.
I'm going to milk it. You know what I mean? I'm going to milk the fuck out of this.
Oh, I didn't tell you my favorite part about the Vive. It's not the Vive. Fucking sorry about that.
It's an index. So my absolute favorite part about this whole thing is these headphones.
Holy shit. They're open ear headphones. I can have these on. I can hear everything around me. I can
see everything around me. It's unbelievable. It's the best feature of the entire Vive by far.
Holy shit. It's unbelievable. Mega milk. All right. I feel like I'm going to need this
and I'm going to need to go to Rick. Where am I? Okay. Look, here's another thing. I'm scared to
be in a big open space because I feel like it's more dangerous for me to be in a huge open space
because I'm not scared to go like this. But I lost the key card. But I feel like that's even
worse because I'm going to run through my wall like a Looney Tunes cartoon. You understand?
You're nude. What are you talking about? My pants down? I'm wearing an abdomen chest brace
thing. So it's probably what you see. I'm still out of frame. It's not perfect. I have a big room
here. Okay. Snap right turn. Yeah, I know. Oh my God. Yep. No, I want this. Oh, you got to be
fucking kidding me, bro. I want to keep this. I'm going to start a fight.
Game with us. Monogon. What happened? What? Oh, I think I was supposed to turn that off.
Oops. Don't do it. It's over the face. Oh my God. Is there a baseball mini game?
Is there a baseball mini game? I'm asking you a question. Is there a baseball mini game?
No. Oh well. These aren't buttons. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, don't open. Don't open. Don't
open. No, don't open. I have to do like a Bloodborne or Dark Souls thing. Oh, that was wicked funny.
This is so fun to throw stuff. Is it going in? Oh, what's with this fucking immersion?
Nice. I have a cool immersion. Is this supposed to be happening? Critic Andy.
I think we don't have full body tracking. Check my zipper. I don't have a zipper. These are
fucking like workout pants. I think my pants have been down. Holy shit. What? No, they're not.
Can you guys see me? No. Yeah, my pants are like coming down. Whatever. Fuck it. It feels like
I'm wearing a diaper. Yeah, there's like my underwear down. I think my underwear is like here.
How is that possible? Oh damn, my VR too much. My underwear came down, but my pants didn't.
That doesn't make no sense. Opening day. Stop that. Let that gut breathe. No, I can't.
Do you guys probably think I'm wearing this because I'm trying to hide
like my Attack on Titan, Titan stomach. I'm not. I'm wearing it to support my fucking chest bones.
Prepare for the future. Okay. Am I still in the tutorial? Menu, grab, snap, turn. I already did
this. Oh, there's a jump. Okay. There we go. Touch. Honey, can you see it yet? Can you see the porn
channel yet? God damn it. I'm trying. It's still all blurry. Okay. Yeah, that's a turn. I get it.
Hold on. How do I run? Oh, okay. Just hold it. This is Minecraft. So like in 500 years, are we
going to be, are the aliens going to think that we were Minecraft characters? People play too much.
It's Roblox. Like that's what, that's what the aliens are going to think humans are.
Because we're just, we're just going to be playing Minecraft forever. No, it's not.
Which is, I mean, the game's fucking phenomenal. So I could understand.
Like a museum. And there's a guy just like, why? I don't even need to see this shit.
It's double stick to run. Oh, that's helpful. Thank you. All right. Let's ruin the experience
for everybody here and just play both at the same time. Cool. What about this one? Whatever.
That was cool. Museum. That was fun. All right. Now what? Here comes the gift shop.
App for a quick hop. That guy's 800 rounds. Jump while crouching for a huge leap.
Okay. So it's Luigi from Mario 2. Got it. That's fine. Wait, crouch. Oh, did I make it? I did it.
All right. We're good. All right. That was fun. terrain can be crossed by running and jumping.
Why does everybody do that in every TV show and movie? Whenever there's a big jump, the
character always does that. They go like this. That doesn't do anything. Get into a fucking ball.
I told you it was going to happen. I'm sorry. But get in tight jump and then get tight like
a fucking goddamn cannonball. You'll move. Yeah. All right. Yeah. I just impressed the fuck out of
like half of you. Half of you. Climbing. Oh, wait, can I? Ow. That hurts so bad.
Let go. I'm not even holding it. All right. To save additional items, place them in the platform.
All right. Let's go like this. I thought that was my face. I was like, why does it have that?
Because look at the background. It looks like a webcam room. I was like, I don't have a goatee.
I was like, where's that from? All right. Yeah. Save manually if you want to. Let's go.
I have this sweat coming down my ass. I think I have to take off this brace. It's like making
me fucking sweat. They're making like, whoa. It's like going to the McDonald's play place
and thinking you're like the man for being able to do that. Sorry. I'm facing the right way now.
What the fuck? Get out of the way. Oh, this is brick. You know it. Come on. Oh, heavy. Oh,
this is heavy. Very cool. So much can break. So much it can break. Interactable handles
and grab points can be found in the environment. Sure. Okay. Don't be too aggressive. Oh,
holy shit. Ooh. It's like all the kids at the fucking playground. They all have like the ball
and they're like, pull it harder. Harder. And finally an adult looks over and is like, no,
no, no, no, no. And one of the kids gets it right in the fucking face and flies.
There's a wall. Didn't hit it. I don't care. Only hero objects can be grabbed from a distance. Okay.
God damn it. They need to be thinner. That's fun just to do that. Move heavy objects slowly.
All right. I don't know why. Did anybody just feel like what I was just doing right there was
one of those like zombie iPad game ads where it's like all of a sudden that person's like,
oh yeah, cooking a burger. And then it's like, ah, they start running wicked fast and fucking
zombies start attacking. That's how I just felt like it was happening. Dude, I get so many ads
on Twitter. These are, that's hard to do. Watch that form, bro. Okay. This is just like a little
playground in this game. Well, I'm not going to spoil anything. Where am I going? I'm over here.
This is double deer. This thing's like squeeze. This thing has a tongue and it squeezes out people.
Oh my God. I'm going to Indiana Jones myself. Should I jump up there? Where am I? Should I
jump up here? Oh, I got it. All right. I did it. Get on top of this. What the fuck?
Whatever. Crouch that this thing's gotta come off. Even if like my like chest muscles hurt and my
like back hurts. This thing I'm wearing like a sweat belt. It's coming off. Press it. Oh,
companion cube. I know. All right. Hold on. Where are you? Hold on a sec. I'm taking this thing off.
It sounds like I'm wearing a diaper. Hold on to guys. I just got to change my diaper really quick.
Okay. That's better. That thing is just too much. Oh, how are we doing? Okay. I need to do this.
That thing is the best. This is OVR advanced settings. It's that thing tells you how many
times you've spun around. Awesome. Okay. Exhibit under construction. Let's go. I feel like this is
a TF2 map, right? Don't you just feel like you're going to see like soldiers just like one, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight, and get to the top by breaking the glass. I can do that in
this room. I can do that in here. What? Why can't I break that? Oops. Back it up. I can't even. I
can't touch it. Whatever. Break the barrels. Turn it around like this. There we go. Try breaking
the planks. Oh, it's fun. I don't want to do puzzles. Oh, TV. What's on the TV? Let's find out.
Wait, is this cheating? What am I? What do I have to do? Do it right? Look at me. Look at me.
Okay. Now get me over here. Why can't I get up here? Okay. What? What? What's wrong with me?
Why did I do that? Why did I get sucked backwards? Somebody just grabbed me by the back of the head
and just pulled me up here. Get. Go. What's wrong? You're five foot three. What? Where'd I go?
Okay. Hold on. Trouble jumping? No, I'm not having trouble jumping. I'm fine. What happened?
Emergency elevator lock. What? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, don't go without me. Oh, what's wrong with me? Emergency elevator override. You failed the
tutorial. Did you say I need to pull this out? You know what? I could do without like the fucking
porn music in my ears. Can I just skip this shit? Okay. So I have to go. I, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's
go. There we go. All right. Move. All right. What's wrong with this shit? Why is it so difficult for
me to do this part? I'm not supposed to be doing it like this. I'm doing this part wrong. What?
What is this for? Okay. All right. Let's not fuck this part up now. Let's go. Now that's going to
stay, right? Get off it. What's the point of this? Emergency elevator override. Puzzle master. Go
back up. This is a puzzle game. Please don't tell me this is a puzzle game. How do I go back up?
I can't. It is. There are a lot of, not this way. Get the fuck off me. Can I delete the soundtrack?
Like how do I just remove the soundtrack from the game? Yep. Okay. Okay. Okay.
I gotta go back up there and then jump over that shit. I don't know. Shut off the TV. Okay.
Whoa. All right. Get me the fuck out of here. What's this portal bullshit? Welcome to floor two.
I keep thinking that's me. Hold on. We're good. All right. Let's see. That makes me dizzy though.
I gotta be careful. All right. Where's the fucking Macy's? Here. Skechers is here. You may find these
exhibits more complex and somewhat challenging. Please take all the time you need in order to
fully grasp these mechanics. We recommend taking a short break then return to these concepts.
Oh god. Is this gonna fling me? Oh. Can I weigh this down? Drinking of water. Where is it? And I
will have some coffee too. Let me get some coffee. Okay. All right. We're good. Out of breath?
I'm not having... All right. This music though has gotta go. Menu operation. Pressing menu
button again. Hold the menu button and point cursor. All right. What's the... Okay. References.
References. What the fuck? I'm not listening to that for like another few hours. I'm just not
going to. Does that change? Like I could tolerate it like here. The music changes. All right. Well,
how about like a six? What's this? Okay. That's a menu. Got it. Let's go. Body slots?
Large items can be stored in the back. You just grab it, let go.
So you can reach back and pick them up. They were very concerned that you weren't going to
know how to like jump and hold items in this game. It seems in the beginning here. Gun mags have a
pouch on your hip. Yeah. That's this thing here. Okay. Well, give it to me. Okay. Because you don't.
Oh yeah. I know how to do this. All right. How do I let the clip go? Not like that. Is it storing
it? All right. That's storing that. That's not how you do it. How do I do it? There we go. Okay.
Cool. I can sit with the gun. I have an inventory. Yep. I go like this. Inventory. And then I can
grab shit. Manage slots. I want this on this side here. What's the... What? Figure discipline.
How did I drop the... How am I dropping this? Lower? I have to go this way. All right. I'm ready.
I'm ready for bone works. Fuck. What the fuck, man? Okay. What's this? Throw these objects
into reclamation bins to unlock them in sandbox scenes. Oh, cool. What's this? I already have
one of these. Search these bone boxes. They contain reclaimables and throw the reclaimables
in the reclaim station. Oh, come on. Purchasing items? Exchange bullet tokens to purchase items.
Those ammo? What? Okay. Preserve acquired items for later use using a reclaim bin. All right. So
what do I want? Okay. So let's go here. Inventory. Where am I? Where was my bin? Okay. Give me that.
They're all the same thing, right? Cool. All right. Give me a refund. Cool. All right. Oh,
shit. I already have one of those though, don't I? Did I just waste money? Okay. Did I waste money?
Stop. Just get it in. Okay. Okay. Can I... Let's go. Are we ready? Items cannot travel between
instances but projectile math can. What? Projectile math? Keep weapon pointed in a safe direction.
Keep your finger off the trigger until you're ready to shoot. Keep weapon unloaded in an
equip slot until you're ready to use it. Okay. Are these made out of cement? That's like a 98%
accuracy. Oh, that would have been sick. What's this one? Why am I crouching? Stop crouching.
Get up. Fun. All right. What else is there? Oh, wow. What is this one? Where does it go?
Where does it go? Okay. What? Is it ready? Hey, how do I turn it on?
There we go. Cool. What is it doing? It's hard. The index controllers are like really hard to get
used to. That thing was automatically firing because I have to physically actually hold this
with like all my hands. All right. Inventory slots. Cool. What's this one? Let's see what I'm
talking about. Uh-huh. Fire. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's because I'm gripping like...
Where are you? Because I'm gripping like this, right? You're supposed to do this when you hold
a gun because this... Yeah. It's tricky. Don't turn around. Cool. You can't gun. Be careful.
You're wasting ammo. This is just like a how to shoot the gun tutorial. Impact physics. Oh, yes.
Okay. I've been waiting for this all fucking day. Damn it. Fuck. Oh, this is knives?
Holy shit. Come on. I got to do it like in the movies. No. Who's that guy? The League of Legends
character? A twist of fate, right? The guy that throws whatever he is. Oh, yeah. I'm ready. I
literally made a fucking mess. Let's go. Hold on. Wait. Break the... I got to break the barrels?
Oh, shit. Cool. How do I do this? I see. Okay. It's got to go in that one spot.
Should I take a gun? All right. Let's go. I took more than one gun.
Where the... Oh, I threw the handguns. Fuck. I don't even know where this come from.
I don't fucking even need it. Let's go. All right. This is not the place to be on the shooting range.
Hold on. It's like... Okay. You ever go to the driving range? Like the driving range, right?
With the club. You're hitting golf balls. And like you hit like a little dribbler and it goes
10 feet in front of you. Don't go get that ball. Do not go get that ball. Don't do it. You see
people do that shit. They're like, oh, whoops. And they walk out there like five feet. You're
going to get a ball sliced into your head. Just don't fucking do that. Handsless psycho. What?
Three handguns. What the fuck? Dude, this is kind of hard to do. Am I doing this like wrong?
It's like I can't reach that far into my body. It's because you're crouched?
Even still, this feels weird to do. Like you need pants. You are crouched. I'm not crouched.
Like you have... Look at how like weirdly I have to look down at that. I don't... I don't need 500
bullets I'm leaving. Like this is... Okay. Let's go. I don't care. You don't need to put... Oh,
wait. What did that person say? No, we're good. You don't need to put the bullets in your pouch?
Attention. The exhibits in the following chamber represent complex concepts.
You may exit through the gift shop if you desire to bypass these advanced chambers.
I'll be using that. I got the key. Where is the gift shop over there? I'm going out through the
gift shop if this is too hard. I don't even care if everyone... I don't care how embarrassing that is.
Time control? Whoa. Hey, what the hell? Where do I go? Trash handlers. Oh, I can move around
with this. This is so hard. Hold on. I need to... Am I going to knock that down? I'm going to knock
this down. Am I holding this backwards? What the fuck? What the box? Do I have to like get
them to come over here for something, right? Did it... Oh, the box and the... Wait, I did it?
Oh, I did it. How do I put this away? How do I put this away? Get rid of one of the pistols.
All right. I got it. Nice. That was fucking easy. I'm like a rat in a maze. It's a collectible. All
right. Gravity room. Negative gravity fields provide temporary inverse mass calculation for
improbable... I know what this music reminds me of. Okay. If you were to right now go to the
app store, the Apple app store, and you were to type in like marble adventure game. This is
every song that plays on like a marble get through the obstacle course iPad iPhone game.
That's what it is. Mass... Okay. Gravity. Anti-gravity. Anti-mass physics are extremely
experimental. Please enjoy this exhibit at your own risk. I got my gravity gun. So now what?
Balloons deliver capable upward force. What? Oh, I'm making balloons. Do I have to like...
What just happened? What happened to my... Hold on. What just happened? Oh my god. I'm so sweaty.
You farted? No, no, no. Hold on. Did you hear that? Give me one second. It sounded like my VR thing
fucked up. Let me see. You guys can still see, right? Okay. That was weird. Let me just drink
some water and coffee. I'm... Okay. I'm forever in balance. I'm drinking a shitload of coffee
and a shitload of water. So like the diuretic that the coffee is, is being outweighed by the water.
All right. I'm going back in. Can you guys even hear what I'm saying? Probably not.
Where are your eyebrows? They're being squished. Where are your eyebrows? Oh, my hair.
Back in the bone work. Oh my god. This is probably so loud. I'm sorry. I just lost audio in my left
ear. That was weird. What's going on there? Okay. Audio is like leaving my left side of my head.
Spin. All right. So I have a balloon gun. Where is it? Right here. Did I just do it to myself?
Dude, is it going to work? Come on. Why is this not working? Come on. It's in every cartoon. Yeah.
My headset's fucked up. Oh shit. This is like actually like broken. My... This cord is...
Where does this go? Because my... I keep losing audio in my left ear when this cord is like
moved at all. What? Cord loose? That's what I was hearing. Oh, it's fucked up. Yeah. I'm losing
audio in my left ear. Whatever. It doesn't happen all the time. It sucks though. Index.
Broken out of the box. I think that's better. Okay. Sounds like it's a... No. It's still happening.
Fuck. I don't have audio in my left ear. Because when I tighten this is when it goes away.
Oh, that's monumentally fucking disappointing. That's really disappointing. Oh well. All right.
Let's go. Check the connections at the tower. No. This is all plugged in good. Yeah. This is all
good to go. Because when I... If I put pressure on the cord up on my head, it cuts out in and out.
Went to... What are you saying? Hold on. Went to SteamVR beta instead. Updated to beta headset
firmware. Verify integrity. File of left speaker now works. Oh shit. Really? Huh. That's a lot of
messages. All right. Whatever. It doesn't happen that often. It's not a software fix if I can wiggle
the cord. That's really fucking annoying. This shit's like a thousand bucks. Like, come on.
I mean, I did like punch it a little. I like hit my face a little bit. Did I break it by like
hitting my head? Like kind of a little bit? That's disappointing. But whatever. It's playable.
Just disappointing. Sorry about that. All right. Let's go. It's playable. It's just annoying.
All right. So this is... Let me go like this. Oh, I gotta pull my pants up. No gravity. Do I have to
make this thing move? How do I get these off my body? Can I get these off my arm? How do I get
these off? Cut them off? Shoot them? I have to shoot them? Where's my stuff? Shoot more balloons
and they'll go away. Oh, pretty sick. Oh shit. Gotta go. No, but I don't want these on my arm.
God damn it. How do I get rid of these? All right. I got a plan. Wait. No, I don't. Fuck it. Let's
go. Oh shit. I'm fucking... Are the balloons keeping me up? Go die. Give me a... God damn it.
What do I do? I can't... They're attached. How do I get out of here?
Why is this happening? Let me go. Softlock. Did I softlock the game? No. All right. How do I reset?
How do I reset it? Burp Charlie. Eject? Punch them? Shoot them? I don't have a gun. Get off of me.
Put more balloons? I can't. The gun's down there. Throw ammo at them. No, come back here.
Oh, it works. It works. It works. That person's a genius. Okay. Get me up here. Go. Come here.
Break it. What's this one fucking made out of? Come here. Wait. Wait. This is less. Go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Why do I... Okay. I'm good. Why are the balloons still there?
Shouldn't they be deleted? All right. Here's the gift shop. That's creepy. What does this one do?
I don't like that. Get it off. Crystals? Can I steal this stuff? I'm just going to walk out with
it. What are they going to do? Wait. I want to drink. Never mind. Never mind. Pick up that can.
I don't want this. Never mind. Recycle. Garbage and recycling chamber. This is fun.
I'm done. Were I supposed to do that? Tutorial complete. Okay. I'm in the trash.
Better. All right. Let me get this situated. Better. Can't grab anything.
Feels like a person. Come here. Big city. Did I go that way? Okay. It was an audio again.
You know what I think it is? I think it's like the top of the cord is like something happened to it.
Like in here. Like wherever the cord sits. Oh my God. Oops. Sorry. Are you guys here in the
audio cutout or is it just me that hears it? Oh box. Okay. Wait. I break with this. There's
nothing in here. Tether ball. Cool. Now what? Tether balls are the best. Yeah. I remember just
sitting next to the tether ball. Everybody did this shit. You would go be going around slowly
and you would just be like queuing up a fucking haymaker and you were just going to like crowhop
like three times and punch it as hard as you could. You know those things need to come back.
They were fun. Jerma seems not very enthralled by this game. Not really. I think it has to do
too with the fact that I sometimes don't hear out of my left ear. Keep out. Oh, a brick. Two bricks.
Get it off. I can't pull this off. Why not? I can't get it off. Why is the guy alive?
Come on. Let me skyrim this guy. All right. Wait, wait, wait. Die. All right. Well, he's dead.
Ball. Give me this. Can I? Wait. Hold the other way. Get off there. This way. Can I go that way?
All right. We got it. That guy attacked us. District six. I can't break that with a hammer.
I have to put a brick. Now, of course, I've got to shoot the basketball. Not even close.
Oh, free stuff. All right. Where are we now? Broadwatchers skip. Um, you get VR streamers
skip might be actually what we do here. We've got 35 games. Skip it. I'm going to give it a little
bit more time. I feel like we just kind of got into it. I'm not into it though. It's not doing
it for me. It just isn't. All right. So they okay. Let me start attacking them. Let me try to like
just actually fight them. Never punched before. I don't I think I just have to keep going and jump
over this. Get the hammer. I thought that was a gun. What is this for? Why can I pick up this
fucking satellite? Okay. Who is howling? Smash him with the satellite. All right. Let me see if I
can hit him in the head with the satellite. All right. Come over here. Come here. Come here. Come
here. You come here. Can you not jump over here? Get the fuck. Why is this slow? Wait, what? Did I
die? I'm just going to keep going. All right. I need, I need a general consensus from the people
that are in chat right now. Should I continue to play Boneworks? Like am I like, should I just keep
going or what do you think? Hey, this is a four hour game. I feel like it's longer than that.
I knocked him over. We're good. That's not going to shoot me, right? I don't have an inventory full
of stuff. Uh, yeah. I took a bunch of guns. Oh, come on. What employee promotion raffle? Um,
it's like 10 hours. It's cool, but I kind of feel like I'm just moving from like portal room to
portal room. It's like, I didn't, I didn't think this was going to be like a puzzle game. This is
not what I thought it was going to be. The shooter part starts like now. That's what I kind of, I
want, I don't want to just leave immediately. I want to kind of see. Can I go in that door?
Oh, it's a fake door. All right. So I got to find the key, obviously. And the key's probably like
over here. What the? I thought I knocked it over. Guns in this game are fun. Yeah. Um, I'm moving on.
That was Boneworks. There's a button on the back of the gun. Yeah, we're gonna, I'm moving on.
It's, this, this game's like 10 hours and I, I kind of wish I didn't do the whole tutorial then.
I feel like I'm invested at this point, which is unfortunate. Um, you literally stopped before
it got interesting. I know, right? And that's like, I pressed this. What is he doing? Can I
press the button? Please get the fuck out of here. I learned this from wrestling empire,
motherfucker. Come back to it another time. All right. Yeah. We're moving on. It's like four
different games tied to the tutorial. All right. Boneworks. That was Boneworks. We're going to move
on to one. I think I'm going to have a lot of fun. That was a journalist. I, I was kind of boring.
I have to be completely honest with you. I think I thought, I thought it was kind of boring.
Tape the cable. It's better later on. Yeah. It's like two, it's a tutorial physics showcase. And
then the game, there's a lot of people don't get into Boneworks and a lot of people get very
mad when people don't get into Boneworks. I mean, I, have you bet? I mean, it's look with
the knuckle controllers, that was fucking cool. I had a lot of fun and like to just jump around
and throw things and shoot stuff. It was, I mean, look, if it's a 10 hour game, I only stream for
like five to six hours. I'm probably not going to do the whole thing. I hated this game at the start,
but pushing through it ended up being kind of worth it. It does suck at the start, but that can't
be, oh, oh, well that's all right. Maybe we'll come back to it. It was fun. I just, it was,
I guess I was expecting something else somehow. I don't know why I went in. I don't know why I
went in with an expectation. That was, all right, we're going to move on. I turned the gun on.
All right, we're going to move on to, uh, I want to play the baseball game. All right. Let's,
let's, let's put, let's get the energy up. Are you guys ready? Are you ready for more high energy?
Weekly meltdown? What? I do have to change this, but that's not what we're playing. Does this even
have a, I don't even, I'm not even sure this is on steam or on Twitch. Oh yeah, it is. All right.
Well, it's ready. Hey there, all you bat swingers out there in VR land. DJ Debbie here to keep
things cooking with some of your fave hits from around the globe. Relax and sit back. All right,
time for high energy. I don't know. You know what it was? I think that game just made me like low
energy. I don't know what it did. I don't know why it was just like, I got, I started to be,
I was like, let's go. This chord is really tangled though. I blame the music. No,
are we going to do some untangling? I just spit that all over myself.
All right, which way do I got to turn this way? Find out.
I can't wait for this. This is going to be awesome. All right. I really got to be careful. I
don't actually hurt myself here because I'm going to be super into this.
You ready? All right. Character. Whoa. Okay. Head. I like that one. I don't think it really matters
over that one. Face. All right. That one. Body. That one's fine. This one's fine. What about,
can I make it brown? Facial hair? No, none. No, I'm not doing that. All right. Confirm. All right. I
get it. I'm so excited. Here we go. Always hold both controllers when playing this game. Okay.
Are you, I'm right-handed. Choose your locomotion. Running. To move, hold down the buttons.
I freaked out. I thought this was like a local Vegas radio station.
Hold down the buttons lighting up on your controller and swing your, whoa. Okay.
I don't know if I really like that. That's too much. Walk by holding down the trackpad thumbsticks.
Okay. Yeah. That's hold down bolt. Yeah. Okay. That's much better. Some players have issues
with locomotion. So we've given you an option to create a projection of your character when
doing movement inputs to allow you to see your destination before teleporting there.
Let's just go. All right. Announcer. Practice. Pitching practice. I'm ready.
Oh, here we go. Oh, this is, all right. This is going to be sick. You got a Mega Man hand
ball. Do I, I don't have to actually throw it. Right. You actually have to catch the ball too.
All right. This is cool. Hey, do I have to actually catch the balls? Oh, wait a minute. Quick menu.
Cannon. What? Oh no. Wait. Left. I can't give it to me. Fuck. This is so hard. And you actually,
you actually have to grab too. I'm going to, maybe I shouldn't do manual. Maybe it's going to be too
hard. There we go. All right. Just takes a little bit of getting used to. I'm going to do that so
often. All right. I get it. I get it. I like it. Let's go. Okay. Now I want to do hitting. I want
to do hitting tutorial, batting practice. Dude, if this is okay, if this is as fun as I think it's
going to be no fucking way. Are you kidding me? This is like, we, this is everything I wanted from
Oh my God. It's like exact one to one. Shit. Where'd the bat go? Damn it. Okay. I'm swinging late.
Swing early. There we go. All right. I'm hitting the top of the ball. Stand back. Am I too close?
Keep dropping the bat. Baseball is back. You keep bunting. I'm trying not to bunt. It's,
you got to slow down. All right. All right. Yeah. I, I, I, I got to back it up like here.
What is it? What is it doing? Get off. Fucking index. What are you doing? All right. One more.
I got to get under the ball more. I'm too far over it. Kill the batter. I mean,
I have to get the ball in the air. This is such a good weakling. All right. Why does every VR game
have the same song that's looped on five seconds? I don't know. Cannon. All right. I got the hang of
it. I'm ready. Okay. Let's do it. Play ball. Easy against the sloths. I can't do anything else.
How many innings? We'll start with three. I don't want to do nine innings. Wait, why am I the
announcer? Why am I announcing the game? Oh shit. All right. I'm ready. Oh my God.
Yeah, whatever. I just, I'm warming up. Okay. I'm fine. Wait, can he run? Wait, he can run. Hey,
don't let him run yet. Oh my God. This is crazy. Come on. I got to release like earlier. Oh my God.
I can't. What happened? You actually field the balls. Can you hit the batter? Stop, turn off,
throwing assist. Is that going to help me? What the fuck? Why? I'm not. Turn it on. Oh, I thought
you said turn it off. Do I have to actually run as the runner? My back went fast. Fuck. Come on,
dude. God, I can't. That's a strike. That's a fucking strike. Good thing out of here. Wait,
who's? What? I'm so confused. I threw it that far. This guy is a psycho. There it is. All right. I
think I got it. All right. Up. Get it. I think I have to stand back a little more. Oh my God.
I'm just going to use the cannon. Fuck it. God damn it. Strike. Give me the fucking cannon.
Give me the cannon. I don't care. Give me the fucking cannon. I can't hurt them. Wow. That was
bad. Give me it. What? Get it. Get it. Get that ball and throw it over there. Oh, I wonder if
it's going to be a ball. Wait, can I, can he, can he hit it from here? Oh, damn it. What are you
doing? Boneworks lost to this. Yeah. I'm actually like, I'm like enjoying myself. Fuck. All right.
Time for my turn. Low blood sugar. Andy, what are you talking about? Low. Whoa. Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. What? Why am I still at the plate? That's way, way outside.
Way outside. Go, go, go, go, go. Why am I so slow? I got to get like in there. Like in there. Safe.
That's a hit. Oh. Somebody just called me a fuck boy. Why?
I got it. All right. This is actually really fun. Can you imagine playing this at two player
with multiplayer? This would be so good. All right. Down and in.
There it is. Out. He's gone. He's having fun. I am having fun.
Hold on. Hey, Sally. Good to see you. I want to get a strike so bad. I'm just ruining the
game for everybody. Oh, come on. Turn off the movement vignette. Can I? See if I can turn it
off. I don't think I can turn off the movement vignette. Don't break you back. I'm good.
Well prepared. Don't ever look when you're running to first base. It's a huge mistake.
Oh my God. Go. He sucks so much. It's difficult. All right. Come on. Strike.
Wasn't even in the batter's box. I got it. I don't know how I got it, but I did.
That's so cool. Got it. That ugly ass vignette. Yeah. I don't know. It is weird. That's not a home
run, right? Okay. I don't even. Where's that player? Oh, you're you. What the fuck? I have
to catch it too? What kind of Bugs Bunny shit is that? I have to throw the ball and then catch
the ball that I throw. Oh, fuck. I should have laid out for it. Get out of the way. Oh my God.
All right. This is my last chance. Fucking run. I did. Okay. I got it. All right. I'm good.
That's a ball. Go. One handed baseball. I mean, it's hard to do it. I'm doing better than it was
last time. Damn it. No, that's I'm good. Man on first and second. You're not going to catch it.
I know I'm good. I got it. I got it. I got one more. One more. One more. One more. All right.
We're good. All right. All right. All right. Right. I'm I got it this time. It's loss of
fucked. Let's go. Just back off the plate. No more vignette either. We're good. Oh, thank God.
Resident sleeper. Let me enjoy my baseball game. Don't worry. Do I have it? Who has it?
Where's the ball? What? What happened? I don't understand what happened. Double play. Let's go.
He's coming back. Give me the ball. You have to catch it on your own. There we go. All right.
I'm backing way off the plate. I wasn't even ready. That's bullshit. Oh my God. Just throw
me out. I don't care. Dead there. Oh, come on. Throw it. You want to go pickle. You want to do a
pickle. This is the technique. I got it. Ball. This is so stupid. Run back. Why are you running
that far? What the fuck are you doing? Why would you do that? I have to like move with it. The
fair ball. That's not a fair ball. Wait, what just happened? Are you fucking kidding me? Oh,
always run it out. Always run out the first base. You all, you know that. Oh my God. Why did you
stop? Cause I just thought I was gone. I can't do it. It's so fucking awkward. I know the arrow is
there, but it's like weird. I'm like facing a completely different direction. You high.
You think I would play VR high? Are you out of your mind? You were in the batter's box.
Give me a break. I've done VR high. No, I've drank and played VR and that was fucking hell,
but it was fun. There we go. All right. Come on. Safe. Nice. Do I keep going? What's the score?
Zero zero. Mike muted. What do you mean? Nice cam. Sorry. All right. I got men on first and second.
Base is loaded. All right. Let me give me a home run right now. Come on. I got to impress
everybody in chat. Finally see his balls. That's it. There we go. Finally my first run ever.
Okay. This is pog. Yeah. Fuck. Whatever. Run. It's all right. It's all right. What the hell
just happened? Attacking me. Stop facing the guy. Why are you swinging downwards? Cause every time
I try to swing upwards, I never get the ball in the air. How come computer hit far, but you know,
Oh shit. I won. All right. That was fun. Now what? Where are we going now? Let's see. Where are we
going? I got a lot of shit here. How about time hacker? Pull up your pants. I, I, oh boy. It's
time for time hacker settings. Ambient. 100%. How do I change that? Oh, voice. There's a voices
timer on hand. Right height autos. Fine. Reset progress. Okay. Take control, teleport and
rotation. Can we continuous motion dash grab? Shoot. I'll figure it out. Let's go. Hello time
hacker. Welcome to AI development. Now I will take you on a tour and you will show what you are
capable of as you increase the size of the sphere. Time slows down when you make the time
completely expand the sphere until it breaks. What the hell move to an indicated place using
continuous move. Try to move by dashing. Open the door. All right. Wait, that's me. I'm moving so
fast. Open the door. How do I do that? Okay. Try to turn using the controller. This person is very,
this is like a very close to their mic with a high compressor. I love it. Right. Do what with
the controller? All right. It's like snap movements, fucking fluid. I like it. Movement is very fluid.
It's very good. Teleport to the indicated place. Teleport. Oh, all right. Pretty fluid.
Uh, can one of the, if one of the mods is here, can they make, um, can they make a,
can they change the game name to a time, uh, classic, whatever it's called? Oh shit. That's
me. Time hacker. I will destroy everyone and you can't stop me. Notify something, say about
first. Activate the virus. Do I have to slow down time? This guy's moving like he's in VR.
Now kill him. Kill me. Time to die. Oh shit. This is 2501. Our first AI development that failed.
He managed to get our robots out of the control. Only you can control them and stop him.
Show what you can do. Expand the sphere until it breaks. Point your hand at, hold the button.
Point your hand at the enemy. Hold the button and pull towards you to leave the body. What?
It's the same button. Look at this guy. I just realized that I'm like a super jacked
Batman guy. Try to get back into the character. Excellent. Now you're ready for real resistance.
Really? Okay. Until the enemies spot us, make them destroy each other. What to stop time completely
expand, take control of the first enemy. Point the gun at the second enemy and shoot. Check out
the enemy. Quickly take control of the second enemy. Shoot the first enemy. What? Check out
the enemy to restore the time. How do I get out? Missed. Get back in his body. Get back in his
body. I'm a fucking time hacker. You can't kill me. Wait, how did I miss him? What the fuck? Until
the enemies spot us. All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Each other to stop. Take control of
the point. The gun at the sec check out quickly. Take control of the second enemy. Shoot the first
enemy. Check out to restore the time. Take control of the main character or wait.
Oh, that's cool. That's really cool. All right, let's go. Oh shit.
Destroy the enemies on the level. Why is it slowing? I love this game. I love this game.
Destroy the enemies on the level. All right, I gotta get into this guy.
Got it. Nice. Oh, this is, this is fun. Oh my God. If the enemy is in a headset,
you can't control of him. Oh, I can't control that guy. I can do this though.
All right, now get in that guy. All right, get me out of here. I gotta get out. Got him. Fuck.
That was from Minecraft. That was from Minecraft.
If the enemy is in a headset, you can't take control of him. Holy shit. Okay, you and then you.
Do I just hit the head? Yes.
What the fuck?
Ruminant enemies can be grabbed and moved. Push the enemy into the turbine.
What the fuck? How do I push him in?
All right, you spin around. Headshot this guy. You shoot. Headshot this guy. Wait, where is he?
Oh, he's dead. Oh, fuck. You point the gun at your own head. Oh, no, I can't. Let go of the gun.
Shoot. Oh, that guy. I can't kill that guy. Oh, I think I'm dead. Wait, this guy. Wait,
shoot. Oh, that guy. I can't kill that guy. Oh, I think I'm dead. Wait, this guy.
We're kind of like Tony Hawk, this guy. Okay. Oh, I was trying to like hit him like his, you know.
All right, let's go. I can't do that. Why can't I do that? I'm just like a shell now. All right,
I can't. All right, hold on. I can't do that. It's time to die. All right, let's go. Get me out.
What? I pushed him in. Oh, my God. Okay. This is awesome. So, now what? Start. I don't know
what I'm starting. Oh, okay. Tutorials easy. Base tutorials. All right. So, I think I have to beat
these. What the? It's just us. Are you fucking kidding me? I can move the bullet out of the way?
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. This is Quicksilver. No, give me that back. I'm going
to kill myself. Am I dead? No, I don't want to die. Is that going to do anything? Oh, shit. Okay. I
got to put it over here. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Oh, fuck. Put it down. Put it down. Holy shit. Put this down right here and then put it down.
Put it down. Try and shoot this guy. No. What the fuck just happened? Okay. This is all right.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. Get in his head. Are you kidding me? That's not a second.
What the fuck? That was so stupid. How do I kill this guy? I have to wait. Oh, fuck. I have to wait.
Wait. Can I? I can't pull him down. I can't manipulate him. But the barrel. The barrel can
float. All right. I should probably wait. I'm going to wait. No. Get over here. He's going to
miss me, right? Oh, shit. God damn it. All right. I got it. I got it. Is it going to hit them both?
Why is it doing that? Got it. This is so fucking fun. Oh, God. Oh, my God. Oh, God. I missed. I
missed. I missed. I missed. I missed. I think I missed. But who kills this guy? He's going to
get me. All right. Hold on. Wait. There's a barrel over there. All right. I get it. There's
another barrel here. I got to think about this. OK. Go. OK. Give me this. He's going to get blown
by that. He's going to shoot this. OK. You shoot that. You shoot this one here. Shoot that one.
Now you shoot the barrel. Got it. Oh, that feels good when you get it right. Hold on. I got to
spin. Two more. One more. Oh, all right. OK. This one is. I'm really into this. This game's
actually really cool. Dynamite can be attached directly to enemies. Oh, my God. They're going to
have timer on them. Oh, shit. Give me that. OK. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. What happened to his?
Wait. I didn't. I put it on his neck. Dynamite can be attached directly to enemies. One, two,
three. Good. That's good to know. They blow up. Holy shit. What? Can I drop a box on his head?
I don't know. I'm confused. Is there something here? What? Why is he? How do I turn it on?
OK. Banana peels can only be attached to the floor. Banana peels right under his foot. Like
right here. That was a really good like a pratfall. Give me that. Can I take the sword
out of his hand? Give me that. I can't. Let me have a gun. Oops. Wait. Can I get it now?
Oh, God damn it. What am I missing? Am I missing something? Oh, the. All right. There's a. OK.
Valve. What the fuck? All right. Just kill me. Wait. I think I can still do it. Shoot. Come on. Die.
Got it. What about be careful and dodge flying objects?
Wait. I don't think I dodged that. That happened so quickly.
Be careful and dodge flying objects. Oh, my God. No, no, no, no, no, no. Move.
What the fuck just happened? Where did I go?
Was that my body? I think that was my body. Where should I take this guy?
I think I've killed him already. Wait. Hold on. Is that going to? That's going to kill me.
Get back in my body. Quick. Oh, damn it. Whoa. We're good. No, no, I got to. What should I do?
Come here. OK. And then I didn't get him. Thank you, Freddy. What happened? What the fuck?
There's a helicopter. No, don't kill me. Holy shit. Who has a gun? Anybody have a gun?
Oh, boy. I need to go into my body quick. And then. Oh, shit. Is that going to hit him? Did I hit him?
I have to get all back over to my body. Oh, my God. I can't shoot that guy. I can't even
get out of this. I can't get out of this. That will click the button. I think I just lose.
Oh, well. OK. All right. I got to be ready for this. OK. Who has a gun? You shoot that guy.
Fuck. That's going to be the last thing I do then, right? I can't get back over there.
Teleport. Oh, my God. I forgot I had that. Oh, oh, my God. Nice. All right. What happened?
What happened with Freddy Dread? Say thank you to Freddy Dread right now. There's 50 subs from
Freddy. Thanks for the 50 good immunity subs, Freddy Dread. That's a lot of money. Thanks, dude.
The super contributor to the stream, Freddy Dread.
Rescue the hostages and don't forget to destroy your enemies.
Am I the only person? Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. No. What? Rescue the hostages
and don't forget to destroy your enemies. Move. Yeah. Fail. How did I fail? How did I fail?
Rescue the hostages and don't forget to destroy your enemies. Safe.
We're good. You're safe. Got it. My God. You have to shoot. OK, get in here.
Quickly, quickly, quickly. Come here, quickly. Come here. Got it. Yeah, we're safe. I thought
he's going to T-pose. He looks like somebody. Oh, God. You're fine over here. Oh, shit. OK,
now you have to go just hang out over here for a second. Stay right there. You.
How do I kill him? How do I kill this guy?
That should do it, right? Oh, my bullshit. That was horseshit. Oh, help, help me. Oh, shit.
I can't get back up. Can I catch him? All right. I think I can catch him from here. No, I'm good.
No. Fuck. Teleport. Right. Sit down. Good. Oh, come on. You. I can't believe it's fucking my crap.
Oh, no. Get the fuck out of here, man. Come here. Sit down. All right. No, you can't. Good. Safe.
Got it. I love this game. Oh, God. Get. Come here. Oh, he's got a Vera helmet on. I can't kill him.
Oh, wait. Shooting was shooting missiles.
Am I good? I think that's it. Holy shit. Oh, boy. Oh, God. Let's do this one.
This is a hard level. What the fuck? Oh, my. Oh, my God. OK. Oh, shit. Who has a gun?
Are we good? I think I got it. I got it. Oh, fuck. Oh, shit. Who kills that guy? Who kills that guy?
I don't know who kills this guy. I think I'm dead. Oh, come on. Wait. What about the guy in the
helicopter? Oh, that shit kind of worked. I think I got it. I got it. I got it. That's it. I win.
That's it. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down.
Get down. What? I saved him. I saved him. I saved him. They didn't get hurt. This guy sucks.
I'm getting tangled. Who kills this guy? Me. And then this guy has to shoot. No, no, no.
Come on. Come with me. Come with me. No. Safe. That's it. What the fuck? He shot the same guy
twice. Fuck. Whatever. All right. One or two more and we'll move on. Oh, shit. Get out of there.
It's going to fucking electrocute everybody. Get out. Get out of there. OK. We're good.
That's going to zap him, right? Who is that not zapping? It's wrong. What was wrong? What happened?
I don't understand. I thought I did it right. I get it. No. I threw her across the map.
I just I tossed her across the map. How is she getting electrocuted? Come here. Sit in this chair.
All right. You're safe. Let's go. Done. We're good. All right. Let's do. All right. One more.
These ones. Time hacker. This is like my favorite game. Redirect the car by turning the steering
wheel. What? Are you serious? This is so stupid. Well, then how do I get him to die?
Wait. He's dead. That seems like that. OK. Whatever. I'm not going to. I'm not going to fucking
ask any questions. I've turned around so many times. We're good. We're good. I think. Hold on.
Let me make sure I didn't like pull the cord out. I think we're good. Yeah, we're good. All right.
Water time. All right. One more revolution. Holy. How many times did I turn around this way? Holy
shit. Water. All right. Go back in. Oh, how's it look? All right. Let's do it. Pull my pants up.
What's going on here? You shoot this guy in the head and then car. Oh shit. There's another guy.
Wait, I have an idea. Just hit him both with the car. All right. Let's do it. That should be good.
OK. All right. Last one and we're going to do another game.
Right there. Go. That should get him both. You get him. Oh my God. Come on, dude. What the fuck?
It's so stupid. OK. Let's do a different game. Let's do a different game. All right. What else
we got? This Space Channel 5. I have so many games. Oh no. I lost chat. Why did I lose chat?
Space Channel 5, baby. Ready Space Channel? What happened to chat? Hey, you guys aren't there
anymore. The chat window closed? No, it's here. Um, hold on. I'm going to actually, you know,
I'm going to take a break. It's been three hours. Holy shit. I've been playing for three hours.
Yeah, I'm going to take a quick break. I'm going to pee. Get some more water and we'll come back
with a Space Channel. Either that or maybe I'll pick one. Can you hear me? How are you doing? Good.
Oh, so let's do. I think I need a Space Channel. Dino Extinction. Turn the compressor off.
Is it too slow? Well, it's because I don't have the headset on right now. The headset's like
resting over here. It's fine. Yeah, I think it looks all right. All right. Space Channel. And
then, you know, let's do Dino Extinction. I think I want to play that one. Going back here in a
second. Getting back in. You'll see me very, very, very momentarily. Um, should I do? Yeah,
I want to play the Dinosaur game. Yeah, I have sentenced. I have a lot of games and I'm playing
VR like this. All right. Dino Eruption is what we're going to play. Time Hacker was a solid
experience. It was very, very much pleasantly supplied. I can't even talk. I can't even say
words. VR just takes so much out of you. I have the L.A. Noire VR files. I got a lot of stuff.
This is what we're doing for the... I'm streaming like three times this week. You're not just getting
one stream, Andy, here. I'm streaming today, tomorrow, and then probably Saturday or Sunday.
Probably Sunday. Or we're doing today and then like Saturday, Sunday. I haven't figured that out yet.
But I'm going to stream three times. Did I lose the chat again? There it is. All right. Dino
Eruption is what we're going to start with. If I can figure out how to get it to work. There we go.
Dino Eruption. Here we go. I can come back to you guys so you can see. And this is very tricky with
this. It should be working. Okay, there you are. Press and... What the fuck is all this?
Dino Eruption. Why is all this stuff all over my arms? Press and hold the marked button
for laser interactor. Press and hold the marked button while holding scan button. Press the grip
button to open menu. Wait, what? Holding scan button press. Oh, all right. There we go. How
are we doing? Adjust height. What the fuck was that? Set height. Okay. Your current height. One.
Your eye should be this high. A little more. All right. That looks good. Comfort options.
No vignette. What's with the vignette? The game is really quiet. I can help you out there.
Let me give you a hand there. Come on. There you go. All right. I'm ready. This game looked
very interesting. I am very much excited for this one. Here we go. How do I get the fuck out of here?
Okay. 100%. What is this? Zero times. So short he's off the screen. Juggles.
Juggles. Stop talking about my fat stomach. Is there like a play the game button? Titan
stomach. Stop it. The game sound. You're not in frame. I am now. Whoa. Juggles. This is not the
game. I need to like leave. There's probably a door. How do I get the fuck out of here? Wait,
menu. Start game. Press grip button to open menu. Where the fuck is that? Click the button. Do I
have to restart the game? B button on Oculus. Yeah, that's what I'm... Oh my... What? I just
pressed B. Okay. Fucking God. Touch marked button to move. Snap. Press the snap turn.
What is this music? Press marked button to activate laser. Wait, press to mark for laser
interactor? What the fuck? I don't know why that scared the shit out of me. That scared the
absolute shit out of me. My whole body hurts. What the fuck? Anime intro? Sly dash. Swing,
swing, swing, swing. Block, block, block, block. Cast magic. And then it cuts to like somebody.
Show me Cameron. Really close on a mountain and the guy's fucking face and leans in and he's
fucking got wind in his hair. Reach behind your head and release. All right. I'm scared. Oh,
I just realized what was happening. We're in a... I can't look out there. I can't look out that
window. I can't look out that window. I can't look out that window. Oh my God. Thank you for
coming in. Time is unfortunate. This guy's proportions are strange. Press marked button
to activate laser interactor. I don't know. I don't know what is... Press marked button
to use laser interactor. I know you've not been on my security detail for long,
but word has reached me of an impending threat to my family. I feel like I look like this guy.
I kind of have like a small head and really long arms. Okay. My wife is the head of an exclusive
facility that observes these creatures, some of which you see here displayed. Okay.
A facility that you should be parachuting down to in approximately two minutes. That's a long time.
Can we make it like 30 seconds? I have recently lost communication with my contacts there.
An auspicious sign given what is coming. I can't pick up your chairs. Your mission is to find her.
Dr. Layla Kessler. Protect her and get her to safety. You got it. And what will you be doing,
sir? Are these dinosaurs? What's the threat? What's the threat?
To put it concisely, I've received advanced reports of solar flares hitting the earth.
Normally, I'm told these things are not cause for worry, just flashing lights colliding with
earth's atmosphere. However, they do interfere with communications.
You'd like dinosaurs. Two minutes and 36 seconds. Okay. I guess we're waiting the two minutes
before I can leave. The last report recently stated they are getting vastly larger with a CME,
a giant solar eruption predicted. By now, it may have already happened.
Okay. You got it. I didn't work when I was over here.
When it arrives, this may wipe out all advanced electronics on earth. The facility below has
advanced electrical security systems to contain the research. The research?
Oh. So find my wife and get her to safety before the eruption hits.
Oh, find your wife. Okay. Before the eruption hits.
Time to jump. Time to jump.
Look at your arms. They will display any injuries. 100% health.
Interact with various electronic devices such as machinery and doors.
Whoa. How do I use it? Okay. I have a bow? You can practice further when on the ground.
Keep my wife safe. Now look around and go to the marker by the-
All right. Let's go. All right. I'm ready.
Press the marked button to equip bow. While holding the bow button,
point the laser on ammunition icon and press the left trigger button to choose your ammunition.
Okay. Did I do it? Did I get it? I like hear it. How is he doing that?
Okay. Press. Where is it? This music is so epic, but I can't fucking even do the tutorial.
How do I? Oh, shit. The weak spot.
Where's the weak spot? Right in his mouth. I swear to God. Just shoot him.
The weak spot. And where is the weak spot? Mr. So-
He's fucking dead. I killed that perfect crap. Using explosive robot arrows.
Explosive robot arrows? I can steer the robot using your
right touch pad or joystick, depending on your headset.
What? Where am I? What am I doing? What? Do I got him?
How? What did I just did? Okay. Press the what button to jump?
Press the joystick. Oh, you press it in. Okay. That thing's going to fucking explode, dude.
Why would I? We just like kept this guy in captivity so I could kill him with a bomb.
That was fucked up. Okay. Connect with laser. Laser detected. I have to jump out of that?
This seems like stupid. Hold on. Do I even have a parachute?
I don't think I have a parachute on. I'm just going to jump out of the fucking plane?
Was I supposed to do that? Whoa. I did turn around. What? Oh, shit. I made it. Okay.
Press the grip button to grab a round surface. Move controller to climb.
What can I help you with? Shit. Oh, man. I'm inside of it. What's going on?
Whoa. There's a dinosaur over there. What's happening?
What? Press the marked button to equip bow. What the fuck? Why is there a T-Rex over here?
What the fuck? Behind your shoulder, press the trigger button to grab an arrow.
I think I just blew myself up with a grenade. Print? Shit. Oh, he ate it?
Hold on. Heal. What do I need to do? I don't have any arrows. I don't have any arrows.
Do you have any arrows? You're talking to me now? We're in a bit of a daze there.
Figured I'd take you up to see the dock.
Fucking dinosaur. So, you're the rescue party? Where's the rest?
And press right trigger button to respond. He's talking. It's the dinosaur talking.
Thanks for the tutorial, T-Rex. I appreciate it, sonny.
Dr. Kessler said we have it under control. But, oh, I don't know. A little something with
giant teeth here tells me that might not be the whole story. Yeah. Anything else?
I love this. Come on. Continue. Anyway, your bow there is good for putting the smaller ones to
sleep. But I doubt it's going to help against our big friend here. What do you mean? Can that
T-Rex get to us? Where are your guns? Where are your guns, dude? Guns? Not here. It's an observation
facility, not a hunting range. If we have to, we use state-of-the-art electrical shockers,
force weapons, and... Force weapons. ...tranquilizers like your little bow there fires.
But I think this guy will need a bigger dosage than you got there.
And why is he on... How did he get on this rock? All right. I'll get... Oh, shit. It's food.
Why does he have like a big steak? Come here. Come here. Come get a steak. It's so stupid.
I can't print any more steaks? Where's the doctor? She's just up ahead of the backup
generator facility. He's freaking me out. I was just admiring this guy. I heard you can distract
them with a bit of food. Sure. He looks distracted. He's like, yes, you can. I'm very distractible by
food. He's correct. What is he doing? Okay. I was going to make some with the generator there
and feed it to him so we can get by without any worry. Shall I give it a go?
Sure. Show me. All right. Let's give this a go. Are you walking like that? Why is he walking like
this? Why would you ever get this close? His shoes. His shoes came off. His shoes came off.
Press the marked button to equip. What? Reach behind your shoulder and press trigger button
to grab it. Eat this motherfucker. These dinosaurs think they can roam the fucking earth again.
Not on my watch. So what? That guy's just gone. Am I stuck here? I think the whole thing is
fucked up because that guy is like, oh my God. Everything about that was fucking amazing.
Um, can I get out of here? This is like the, this is like the Disney rides and the universal rides
from like back in the nineties and the eighties where you could literally be going that way.
And King Kong is right there and you turn and King Kong is right here too. It's like, oh,
there he is. King Kong fucking scary. And he, oh, okay. Reach behind your shoulder and grab.
I don't have any, I don't have any arrows. Where am I? Use laser to print. Okay.
Oh shit. Arrows. Do they get them? Arrows stored. Thank you. Okay. What about in here?
What the fuck is that? Why do I hear that? Bombs stored. Bombs stored. Can I get in?
Is that the T-Rex making that noise? Your health has been restored. Oh, okay. Is that
a bad guy? Jump, jump. What happened? What happened? Why did that happen? I'm so confused.
Hold on. Why were they, we keeping it in there? What is that? Okay. I want the bow. No, put this.
Give me, give me, give me, give me. Not this again. Oh no. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Dr. Kessler. Okay. She's just at the backup generator. I've gotten bigger somehow. Show
me how to feed him again. Don't do it. Don't do it. You're so much work. Your life is so much
worth living for. Help. Press the marked button to equip bow. Why can I throw this shit? All right.
Get me the fuck out of here. No, I'm getting out of here. I need, I want to go down.
Okay. So behind the backup generator is where I need to go. I'm ready to try that or attempt it.
Okay. Something exploded in here and I don't know what the hell it was.
I don't know. Something, it was like a bomb. That fucking dinosaur.
Uh, arrows stored. I'm not leaving this one yet. No fucking way. Not a chance.
Bombs stored. Bombs stored. Your health has been restored. Okay. Here we go.
I need to refill my health. Open. Oh God. Come on. All right. Well, whatever.
I need to equip the bow. First of all, I got to back up. I'm way too close.
Arrows stored. I also have to spin around. I'm so tangled. All right. What does this do?
Connect with laser. Let go. What did it do? Laser detected. I have no idea. Okay. There are
dinosaurs here. Do I have to do anything with them? Why am I going up here? That was so pointless.
For what? Okay. I'm getting down. That hurt me that much. This ain't baseball.
It's a petroterricitia. I feel like you can get out of here. What the fuck?
It was an eagle. That's not, I want that. I want those. They're not doing anything.
Arrows stored. Can I pet them? Hello. Yes. You're such a good boy. Stegosaurus. Come here.
Come here. What's this one? Oh, it's like, it's an armadillo one. Hello. Okay. Where am I going now?
I can't believe that guy got fucking eaten. What's happening over there? What is going on over
there? Hold on. Did one escape? I wish I could move faster than this. You walk like you've been
drinking. I'll take care of the dinosaur. Don't worry. That's true. I am just like,
should have lopped it around. Okay. Okay. Am I launching a missile? Oh no. He turned into
wood. He didn't even eat it. You're welcome. All right. I think I got to go that way.
He's freaking me out. He can't get over that fence, right? Okay. I kind of need to see what
else can happen in this game. Yeah. 19% health, 13 arrows. So is it kind of just like a Jurassic
park where you just walk around and look at the animals? What's with my hands? Why is she
fucking tiny? Hi. You must be my husband's newest security edition.
Hope you'll last longer than your predecessor.
Oh, no. What do I do?
Can I feed her to the fucking T-Rex? Please, please let me feed her. Let me feed her to the T-Rex.
No, no, no. Oh, God damn it. Fuck you. We already know what happens to you. Get him out of here.
Why am I getting taller? Oh my God. Get me out of here. I can't believe. Oh, God damn it.
I wanted to bring her over here and feed her to the T-Rex. All right. I don't care about what the
I don't care about this game at all. I care about feeding that lady to a dinosaur. I don't care
about anything else. Arrows stored. Okay. Let's go open it. Beach behind your shoulder and press
trigger. Different monster in here. Fuck it. I'm just going up there. I'm good. I'm back. She keeps
getting smaller. Yes. I am the new recruit. Every time I kill, I grow in size. So fucking bizarre.
Oh my God. Dude, that's just, this is just not cool. Oh my God. Let go. Let go. I just,
I gotta bring her over there and I gotta get her over the fence. Her neck.
I just gotta get her over the fence. If I can throw her far enough. If he eats her.
Okay. Place your bets. If he eats her, this is, I mean, this is gonna be the funniest thing ever.
Oh, hold on. My underwear is coming up. All right. Can I do this?
Shit. I need to. Damn it. No, I'm fine. I'm alive. I don't know if I'm gonna be able to do this.
Too heavy. Wait, what about one of these guys? Why do they keep getting smaller? I don't understand.
I don't think I can do it. I don't think I can. I think she's too heavy. Wait. Ah, shit. I gotta
kill this guy. Where is he? Where is he? I think. Break forward. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go. What the fuck? I'm kicking in. I can't bring her. I can't. Fuck. I just see what
she wants. Let me die. Hold on. Just die. Just die. Just die. I'm so disappointed. I can't take her.
Fuck. Why am I still alive? Press the marked button to equip bow. Now you were in a bit of
a daze there. I'm gonna be as big as you real soon. Press marked button. Laser interactor.
Oh my god. Every time. This is important. Hold on. Hold on a second. I need to die like 10 more
times because I want to be like so much bigger. I don't think I can even leave. All right,
we'll just feed him already. So you the rescue party? Dr. Kessler said we have it under control.
Anyway, you're little. Well, we had a power out and don't worry, the backup kicked in.
Though I heard one or two of the dinos did get out of. I assume that's why you were here.
Okay. Actually, she's just. I'm getting like winded. I was just admiring this guy. I'm getting
winded. I might have to stop. I'm starting to get like seasick. But I have to power through
because I have to see this one more time. Let's give this a go. Get in his way. Don't do it.
What's happening? I'm going to puke. I'm going to puke. I'm going to puke. I'm going to puke.
I'm going to puke. I'm going to puke. I'm going to puke. Give me a sec. Yeah, I gotta stop.
In my view, the world like just got disconnected and I almost just fucking instantly threw up.
Oh my god. That was fucking funny. The audio. I know.
All right. So here's what we're going to do. I'm going to call it here because like, yeah,
I'm actually starting to get like sick. I don't know what was about that game, but it did it.
So I'll be back here tomorrow. We're going to continue to go through the VR catalog.
Why can you shoot the people with the bow and arrow? Why is it like Dark Souls? Why can you
kill NPCs? Oh my god. So tomorrow, I think we're going to open with Space Channel 5.
Then maybe we're going to do some L.A. to more VR case files. And then we're going to do
Sentenced, which is an executioner game. I promise I have eyebrows.
And we'll go from there. But yeah, that's the end of that. Air check. I'll see you guys tomorrow.
How do I look? Sam and Max VR? Is that out? I didn't know that was even out.
I'll get it. Red from Scooby Doo. Well, some of these games were really fun. Boneworks was
cool. It just, I don't know, it was kind of, it wasn't grabbing me. It wasn't grabbing me.
The first like 15 to 20 minutes, I was having like kind of a good time, but it was just,
I don't know, maybe a little too slow for me. Or maybe like I really need to put like a few
hours into it. But I've had a blast. Baseball game was fucking awesome. Time Hacker was
hilarious. VR really is so much fun. But it just, it just annihilates me. I just get so tired.
So that's why we're going tomorrow. Let's take a shower, freshen up. I'll see you guys back here
same time. Four o'clock Pacific. You guys soon? Can't hear me. I'm trying to lean in.
I'll see you tomorrow. Can I get the subs to come up? I can. Look at that. Scammed bet. Well,
I couldn't do it. I didn't do it, obviously, right? I'm really disappointed that the,
I don't know what happened to it, but I'm going to like disconnect all the wires.
That left ear thing is really disappointing. I really hope it's not just a bad cable or something.
Because I have dinged it a few times. I have like punched it a little bit, just like the left side.
You saw me do it. But I don't think that should be enough to kill the left hearing in the headset.
Update. Yeah, I'll do the firmware thing and see if that's a problem.
I've smashed mine into a wall before. Yeah, these things are usually pretty hardy.
My Vive fell off my head flying down into the ground. I have smashed that thing so many times.
But I'll check the cables. I'll get the update. What's your opinion on VR Zorn?
I've never done VR Zorn. I'm terrified to do it. I talked about this in another VR stream,
and I'll make it really, really clear again. VR porn is one of those things where anybody that
you know that could possibly come to your house, or that you possibly are around, you need to make
sure that they're on vacation. Because being inside of this headset and being there,
and you have to be absolutely fucking certain that no one is going to show up.
And I mean, like, if you know that, like, everybody in your household, like, is on vacation,
FaceTime them to make sure that it's proven before you get in.
Like, oh, just checking on this thing. I'm going to FaceTime you like a mom and dad.
Yeah, so how like, show me around Italy. Okay, they're still in fucking Italy. There's no way
they're going to come home. There's no way they're going to see me jerking off in my fucking
VR headset. No possible way, right? It's so vulnerable in there. I wouldn't want to know.
I don't want to do that. Lock the door. No, but why is your door locked? Son, what's the what's
with it? Why was the door locked? Oh, by the way, how are you going to hear that? If somebody tries
to come in your locked door, you're immersed in VR Zorn. How are you going to hear that? They're
going to get like the fire department there because they're scared. They're going to break
your door down and the fire department's going to see you in there. Fucking fully nude in VR. No,
everybody had don't you have to make sure that no one will ever be around. Like he accidentally
locked himself in the door in the room. Are you in there? Hello? Knock, knock, knock. It's where are
you? You're immersed completely. Your headsets are open ear. Well, depends on how loud you're
listening. I'm fucking out of here. I'm sorry. Alright, I'll see you tomorrow. We'll open with
Space Channel 5 tomorrow. See you guys later. Take care of yourselves and goodbye.