Sorry guys, we were having a little tech talk.
T-E-C-H. Ster's trying to figure out some tech.
He's trying to figure out how to get his tech working.
Spoiler for everybody here, he didn't get to use his tech.
It's still not in a good functioning state, unfortunately.
Wait, wait, wait, it's not over. The stream is not over.
We just started. Hey, there we are.
Hi guys. This time I'm back here with Ster.
Who is in fact streaming today.
From what I understand. What I've been told.
We're going to jump right in to pick up what we left off yesterday.
Unless he's got anything to say.
Everything I'm going to say is a technical problem.
So I'm just going to let everyone know.
I don't care and I'm ignoring them all.
I've had my little headset handbag in my hands here.
I've been sitting here waiting for you.
I'm ready. How do we join up in game?
See you tomorrow. See you in 40 minutes.
I have no idea. Let's get in.
Are you ready to go in?
Shit. Sorry we're a little late.
You know what's great about not using a webcam is you just, I'm nude.
No one's going to know. Wait, how do you not do a VR stream
without a webcam? You've got to have the people watch you do the funny movements.
Do you want to wait another 20 minutes? No.
No. Alright, I'm going in.
This is called Clash of Chefs?
I don't know. It's a game where we have to compete and cook food together.
Just hold on. Against each other. Not together.
Wait, this is not a together game? This is an against game? This is not a together game.
Really? I think we're on opposite sides of the room
and we're trying to cook the things faster. Your shirt is too small.
You want to wait another 20 minutes while I go get another shirt?
No. The dryer.
That's the advantage right there.
Wait, is this the right hand?
Guys, something you've got to know about buying shirts. I learned this first hand with this one.
First of all, if you buy a medium it's going to turn into a small
and don't leave it in the dryer for too long.
I like this shirt, okay? It has to be form factor.
So my perspiration doesn't get stuck in there.
Whatever, I don't give a shit.
You can make fun of my baby shirt all you want.
Just wait until you see me cook up a couple of dogs here.
Alright, this music is going to drive me insane, I can already tell you that.
Are you in my game? No.
I'm going in. How do we do this?
I'm going in.
Is this frame rating? That's what I said. Do you have the window on your desktop?
Did you close it or did you minimize it?
I didn't minimize it, I dragged it to almost non-existent.
So I minimized it? Yeah. Open it up and shrink it.
And then my game stopped lagging. Really?
Shrink it to barely existence and then move it off the screen?
Yeah. I have it as a 10 by 10 window.
That's very oddly specific how that is.
Did you minimize it after that?
Actually it is really frame rating. Maybe it's just the game.
I think it's just the game. We'll get in and see what happens.
Because my CPU is at like 11%.
My CPU is better than your CPU. That helped a lot actually.
That fixed it for me. Yeah, dropping that.
Let's go.
Play online. Invite?
Or should I just invite you?
You are none of these people.
Do you want to invite me?
Play. Invite.
Are you online?
What is this?
Am I cooking a stack of bacon? How do I get one piece of bacon?
Sure enough.
Are you online on Steam?
I should be.
I don't see anybody named Tommy Pickles.
I don't know how to do any of this.
Why can I not open my Steam?
Why can I not open Steam?
I don't want to open a mobile hotspot.
You can spend weeks preparing.
I'm signed in now.
You're online?
Invite. There he is.
Waiting for a friend. Meet me at the bar.
Okay, I'm here.
Friend invited you. Please yes, go.
Please yes, let's go.
Why am I this small? I'm not this small.
You are. No, I'm not this small.
Who is that? Is that us?
We just determined who us was.
Is this a surveillance camera of what we were doing?
We're getting orders.
Are you sure we're getting orders?
How do you play?
He wants a cup of busted and he wants a burger with
these customers.
These are pre-sliced?
Who does that?
You don't use your bare hand.
Where's my spatula?
He's down here.
That doesn't take very long at all.
Where's the trash?
That's his group.
There's going to be a fire.
These take two seconds. We've got cheese, two buns.
Done. Bingo.
Cheese.
No, this is the wrong bun.
Where's the aioli?
How do burgers burn this bad?
This one's easy. Shake this off.
Just burn it off.
It's going to be done.
Tutorials up.
I've got to toast these buns.
Where's the trash?
I just need
fresh hamburgers.
I'm not agreeing with the physics.
How do I pick this up without it dropping?
I did that one.
I've got to season the grill.
What is in here?
How did it go through the grate?
I don't even know what that is.
Will you come get this burger?
Right here. I got one right here for you.
What?
Are we supposed to make all three on the screen?
The ones that are right out here.
How come it takes longer to fill a cup with a drink
than it does to cook a hamburger?
Because it's a fucking video game.
Take it.
How many red sixes do you have?
I need a plate.
What?
This just came in.
I've done the thing.
Are these green?
Oh my god.
Who needs plates?
You're being back VR. Does that mean that she's grabbing you from behind
and moving your shoulders?
The air is making this fall. I didn't make that fall.
What is doing this fall?
I found out how to play.
I'm serious. I don't know how to play the game.
What do you mean you win?
It's giving me the advanced super lag mode.
What did you do?
I got an order in.
Why?
I can't look at this.
Play next match.
My board is blank.
It's the paddy. What is that? Did I do it?
I think I might have fucked up the game.
I think the game is broken.
Why are these green?
This is getting weird.
I'm out of here.
You're gone.
We didn't get to do anything.
My game doesn't work.
I invited you.
I think I see you operating a table.
Now invite me.
I didn't do anything.
Did something pop up?
Did I invite shortboard?
I just got a message of what the fuck.
I'm pretty sure I clicked on you.
Can we play the next game?
Friend invite.
My game is still 10 frames a second.
Why are you persisting?
We can't do that.
That's going to cause real sickness.
I won.
I feel so much better to be in 60 fps.
What do you want to go next?
Climbing?
Let's do climbing.
I don't know.
Maybe.
We wait for him to return.
Video games are too hard.
He's not in discord anymore.
Maybe that's what was causing all the lag.
It's possible.
I wonder if he's going to come back.
Do dreadhalls while you wait?
I'll do tilt brush.
I need to open my library.
Chef VR
blue screens his game.
He was underwater in that game for too long.
Let's open up tilt brush.
I've never played it before.
My computer
had an oopsie.
That's probably what was killing us.
Really?
It wouldn't close.
My VR crashed.
Why? You just infected me.
You infected me.
My OVR drop just crashed.
Let's play that virus game again.
It keeps you there thinking you're making cheeseburgers.
Hold on.
Where's my hand?
I have to set this back up.
Where are you guys?
I've got to load my chat profile.
Why did the chef game have to do this to us?
It completely logged me out of steam.
It completely logged me out of steam. I don't know my password.
Hold on. What are you talking about?
Do you really get logged out of steam?
How did you get logged out of steam?
Tell me that I got my serial key and my card numbers.
For the love of god.
Technical difficulty stream welcome.
I had a profile saved.
Why is it not here?
I'm playing the claw game right now.
Hopefully I win the big teddy bear.
Why don't you have a stronger password?
Are you still here?
Is he gone?
He might be gone again.
Are we infected?
I think he's the only one that's infected.
I'm going to open up tilt brush and wait for him to tell me everything is okay.
This is actually kind of scary.
I don't think we are infected.
Let's relax while we wait.
The star is still technically in discord.
Maybe when we figure it out, we'll hear him.
That's not him.
Let's see what this game is.
Tilt brush. I heard it was very relaxing.
Trigger to paint.
You hold the trigger down to paint.
This is unbelievable.
Swipe thumb pad.
Straight edges.
Mirror.
Night sky.
I'm going to make my t-shirt.
How do I erase?
That's really cool.
Why does it keep changing?
It's there.
Color pick.
What color do I want to smoke?
There's a little bit of smokiness here.
No, that's not going to work.
I need to make the brush bigger.
How do I do that?
Hard press left side of left touchpad to undo.
That looks good.
I'm drawing my t-shirt now.
You're having a little bit of trouble there.
There's my shirt.
This is amazing.
Can you come into my game and do this with me?
This is the real star. Do you want to play a game?
Let's play Climbing.
Snow?
This is really cool. Unfortunately, star is back.
I'm sorry.
Tilt brush.
Medium are quite nice.
Are you ready for climbing?
I am in climbing.
I am sure about that.
There was a foreign man at my front door.
I gave him my social security and he said now I can play again.
Is this you talking?
This is me talking.
This is a weird scenario here.
Are you ready to play this game together?
I'm ready to play this game together.
This is called Climbing and it's not what my current game title is.
Floor, grid, clothes, robot, cam.
What does cam do?
Turn off camera.
How do we get into the same game?
Let's get started.
My camera is telling me I'm not live.
Now they're telling me I'm live.
I'm going to stream VR again.
He said grip and then what do we do?
Get the fuck out of my face.
Climb up using the trigger button.
This is really cool.
I sure wish one of my friends was around to play this with me.
Where's the tutorial?
Help me.
There's no start button.
Where are you?
I'm in the big world.
Hold on.
I can't move.
I'm going to have to do this again.
I'm going to star the technically illiterate guy.
He doesn't even know how to set up his virtual headset.
How do I move?
This game is going to be real fun.
It's like climbing.
I made it.
Jump climbing.
Remember when Valve made games?
Or when we made the portal?
Am I in a tutorial?
You have Wheatley talking to you.
Wheatley with the helmet on.
Do what Wheatley tells you and then we'll probably get into a game.
He's standing in front of me but he wants me to jump forward.
Get out of me.
I already made that joke.
What joke?
He's body blocking me.
How do I get out of here?
Up there.
You can't do that.
Did you make it?
Why are you like a baby?
I just wanted things to work.
It's a marvelous invention.
Go for it.
I have to complete the tutorial first.
Oh no.
What?
Listen to the baby.
Stop that. You want your bottle?
I'm not doing that anymore.
How do I get over there?
Is this really a tutorial?
It's teaching you how to climb and grab and move.
It's a little more challenging than the others.
Remember you can put that up to 3 checkpoints per level.
If you just push the menu button.
Checkpoints make it so you don't have to restart the entire level.
Use them wisely and you'll be much less frustrated by difficult levels.
Just stand on it.
I almost ripped the headset off.
This is actually fucking cool. You don't like this?
I just want to play with my friend.
I'm alone. I can't even see chat or anything.
I just feel like a dumbass.
If you press the button to rotate while you're on the moving platform you fall off.
What are you talking about?
If you try and turn your character I just fall off.
I'm almost done with the tutorial.
Good thing I can see my chat.
I don't have a checkpoint.
Am I okay?
Just make sure to not orientate yourself and punch my wall.
We have to work together and shit.
I don't even know where I am in my room.
Be careful.
How come every game you can't do a tutorial with a friend?
To give you confidence.
I'm almost done with it.
This is the hard part.
Only two more of this shit and I'm good.
Last one.
Let's try.
Let you be free and play the game as you wish.
In any sort of way.
Not tutorial.
Set checkpoints with your wrist.
How do I get this off?
Listen.
Main menu.
Servers.
Go to the main menu.
I'm doing my jumps.
I'm doing my solo exercise.
Start server browser.
There are three people looking for a server.
I'm coming in your room.
I'm joining you right now.
I feel like you lied to me.
Open a room.
You're going to have to explain.
Select a level.
Start from the beginning.
Hit the menu button.
Activate main menu.
Select the built in ones.
My hand buzzes when I click main menu and I can't leave.
I'm in the main menu.
Go to built in mode.
You have a selection of levels here.
Click on 001 climbing 101.
That's the first one.
Do 002 jumping 101.
Do 006 climb stuff.
Get in there.
Go.
New play.
Go to create private room.
To the left.
Create public, create private.
You're standing at the built in with all the buttons to press.
Go like this.
Go like what?
Movie, TV show.
Seinfeld.
Labyrinth.
I only had a heart.
Wizard of Oz.
Turn to your left.
Create public and create private room.
Sometimes with this guy, sometimes with him.
I'm in.
Turn around and see your new best friend.
You can hear me in the game too, like every VR game.
They don't expect you to be in a discord on a stream.
Where's the options? Input.
Mic, turn it off. To the top left.
It's me and you.
What do I have to flare?
The thing on your right shoulder strap.
You have a thing that says vibe.
Let's pick a level.
Family guy joke.
Family guy routine.
Pick one.
It's going to be so funny.
Can you pick a level?
I'll do it.
I don't understand.
After selecting the levels you want, press the menu button.
Don't read it.
Just the way to get it so we can play.
I see checkpoint on the top right.
There's no start.
It's levels that are available and they're calling you an idiot.
Top right.
Look who the fool is.
Look at this guy.
There's no level selected.
Don't touch anything.
Player scale 1.5. Look up.
We have a list here.
Wait. Refresh.
Can't we just start at 006?
Why did our games decide to undo everything that had been learned
from making menus and UI in games?
Gullible is written on the ceiling.
I'll handle this.
You ready?
I have a suggestion for the developers.
This whole wall should be a button that says play.
This one should be the mission you started.
Turn off 1.5 times player scale.
It's your lobby so you have to start the game.
You have to open up your wrist watch menu and hit start.
Nothing says start.
We're here. 006.
The trick is you press playlist.
It's like I'm right next to you.
Are you going to do it?
Are you going to do this or are we going to just
get the fuck away from him?
You just fucking threw me over.
What the hell are you standing on?
How come I can't see you on that?
That's my real wall.
Be careful. Watch out for the wall.
That's my wall.
That's my VR sensor.
He's breaking his shit. I'll get over there quick.
I almost fucked it up.
What?
Crawl you fool.
Why do I not have a checkpoint?
You thought you were going to beat me.
I grabbed it.
A store has a checkpoint there.
We both have our own checkpoints.
Make your checkpoint.
I didn't know how to do it.
Me getting to the end doesn't end the level.
I'll get there. I was just rushing because I was trying to beat you.
You didn't.
Here I am at the checkpoint.
Where is it?
Tommy Pickles.
I didn't know what it was.
What am I touching?
Wait over here for you.
I'm trying to rush so much.
It's next level.
Are you ready?
That's what Mario would do.
I'm sliding.
You're trying too hard.
I'm not doing anything.
I'm just being pushed around.
Are you lacking again?
There you are.
That's an interesting long way to go.
This is going to be really interesting here.
You're going to have to climb.
I don't think I like this.
I don't think you should be playing this one.
You can't do that.
I'm going to wrap all the way around.
How are you hitting the ceiling?
You're not nine feet tall, are you?
How are you touching your ceiling?
I'm going to freak out.
Your arms are longer than mine.
Can I put a checkpoint here?
You're going to make me let go.
From here?
No!
What?
Sometimes you just need to put the radio on and relax.
What do I do from here?
No!
He hit his head on the ceiling and I forgot you could do that.
I even mentioned it.
Can I make a checkpoint here?
It broke his ceiling light and distracted me.
I'm out of checkpoints.
This radio sucks.
Where even are you?
I went all the way to the beginning because it didn't make one checkpoint.
You started smashing stuff and I forgot it was a game.
I hit the wall and I don't know what hand is gripped.
Which one of these hands is gripping the ceiling?
I have no idea.
Why does the game move you when you're in a spot?
Give me a checkpoint.
I'm going to put a checkpoint right on top of that.
Minutes.
Next level.
I got to the end.
I did the whole thing.
You're a liar.
I came back because getting to the end doesn't end it.
I see what happened.
Movie.
Ow!
This is the number one punch your wall game.
How do we keep doing that?
I got cute with it.
Are we going through?
I'm coming.
How do we do this?
Are you putting a checkpoint here?
VR notifications.
Get away from me.
No, I didn't put a checkpoint.
Why do you keep doing that?
I don't know.
I pushed you off the mountain and I forgot.
I was going to put one down right there.
Why do I keep doing this?
I beat it.
I don't know where I am in my room.
Just go.
Unbelievable.
Why don't you near me?
That's weird.
What's the goal here?
Ow!
How many holes are we going to have on our walls?
Weird sex music playing.
Ow!
We're going to break something.
What are you jumping to?
Why am I jumping sideways?
How do I jump backwards?
I got a checkpoint.
How do you do this?
Oh my goodness.
I'm in the opposite direction of what I'm trying to do.
I can hold onto you.
How did you do that?
I had more attempts.
Don't do it yet.
It's so difficult.
Don't go.
Don't do anything.
I'm saving you a lot of embarrassment.
You're going under.
The level is over under.
How is he doing this to me?
I was planning and correcting.
Where is this going?
Are there no checkpoints here?
I tried to press it.
I'm going under.
Under this.
There was a movement platform here.
On the side?
That just booted me.
Did you stuff yourself under here?
I feel dizzy as hell now.
My face. Are you lying to me or did you actually do that?
I did.
Remember when we used to have an honest relationship?
Down.
Where am I?
I feel like I went back to the beginning.
Crawl?
Why is this working?
It was a good thing there wasn't a wall in front of me.
I beat it.
I couldn't figure out the crawl thing.
I'm dizzy.
I'm going to check in on my chat.
Lose in a children's game.
This is a workout.
Oops.
Lose in a children's game.
I see your final checkpoint.
Be easy with this shit.
How's your chat doing?
They're great.
I'm going to assume I should use it right here.
Hard jump.
How many more are there?
There it is.
Should I put on the dumb music too?
No.
How did you get to this?
Am I actually going to get Lose commercial?
Are you kidding me?
This is a real radio station?
What are you doing?
Did you get a Lose advertisement?
No.
What is this?
What's your plan?
Are you ready?
You sweaty?
I did it.
This is my chance to show everybody that I have what it takes.
You say one thing about it.
This shit's moving.
The moving platform is freaking me out.
I think I'm on top.
It's weird.
I think there is ice.
This is ice.
That's hard.
What the hell?
That was too fast.
This is awful.
I can't do it.
Did I win?
You're going to win.
Touching the flag doesn't do anything.
Can I hold onto the flag?
I didn't get to complete that.
I thought you said you were at the end.
You took it from me.
I've got to wait a long time.
Let's just stand and skip.
We need to skip.
This is the level where you wait in an elevator.
What am I supposed to do? Patience?
That's hard.
Can I stop?
This is Mario 64 shit.
You don't want to go that fast.
Look at this shit.
Look at this.
I'm throwing up.
Easy.
I feel like this is going to be worse than elevators.
I think you better set to go for it.
Wait a minute.
No.
Go for it.
That's so weird. I think you have to do it really slow.
Like a snail's crawl.
I can't do that turn slowly.
The force you need to do it right angle sends me flying.
Just walk.
I'm going to mean just walk.
Walk backwards.
Wait. Hold on. That was close.
Grip and just pull.
Grip and pull.
See how fucking you just start flying.
Hold grips and swing arms.
No.
Wait.
I'm practicing for a while.
It's grips.
Grip not triggers grips.
I don't want to mess up my strategy.
Cranking.
I'm just like the orangutan.
You're like the mom.
You're the mom orangutan and I'm like the baby.
Get off of me.
That thing makes you fall backwards.
Get us out.
Slow down.
I just hurt my back.
My back hurts.
Sit the next one up.
I think I was going to do the shake thing.
I hit the ceiling.
I have to go to a chiropractor and have him do the fucking
undertaker move where he breaks my back.
I want to go to a chiropractor that gives me a fucking tombstone.
Just bring me to a fucking cane.
Scoop me up and do the fucking tombstone piledriver to me.
Just end it.
Are we playing ping pong?
Bounce. Bounce you stupid game. Dumb.
This game is so dumb.
I'm actually really surprised that we're still playing this and I'm having fun.
I expected this game to be.
Somebody in chat last night said you should guys play climbing.
They said you'd probably get a couple of fun interesting orangutan on the mother jokes.
That sounds like a good idea.
I win. I win.
I win. Are you literally jumping?
Stop. Don't go yet.
Are you sure you want me to end this?
Dermot was just joking. He could beat that level any time he wants.
That was the one. High five.
I just actually put that in my fucking mouth.
Tongue in mouth.
You're not going to get me are you?
Get me up to the summit. I'm just like the parrot that you bring with you that Grant's wishes.
The parrot.
I love the parrot that Grant's wishes.
Excuse me. Not that fast.
Get on my back. Why did you push me sir?
I was putting a check point down and you pushed me. You can't push.
You pushed me. You did. I promise.
I bet you 500 cents.
Call my lawyer. You didn't have a lawyer. I know this because I've sued you before.
And won easily. You showed up there. You showed up in a fucking tank top
in pants suits.
In a fucking chicken costume.
Underneath?
Yeah. Underneath.
I was in a suit under that chicken costume.
Mom, I don't want to do this part.
I feel like that's you on every level.
What?
I don't want to get thrown off while I make a check point. That would be sweet.
Thank you.
You know what I'm really concerned about with VR?
I win.
When you have a VR helmet on
I hear that cheering.
And it's infuriating me.
When you have a VR headset on
You know how the glass is really really close to your eyes, right?
It's literally right here.
Not that it fogs up. I'm talking about
I kind of have this weird concern that you know how you accidentally
smash your face into a wall and you bump your controller into your face?
What's the testing? Have they done extensive safety testing where if
I punch my face accidentally and the glass shatters it's not going to shoot into my eyes?
No.
What if it just explodes the glass straight into your eyes?
Have they done tests of that yet?
Or are we the test subjects because VR is not really caught on yet?
You're so smart. Okay, next level.
We win.
This is like a safety glass.
Is there a level that we didn't do?
We did skyscraper?
We did it, we beat it.
There's like an open workshop button.
Let's take a little chat poll here.
What do you guys think?
Star does really well while I pretend to grab onto him as a baby monkey?
No matter what game we play that's going to happen.
Is my cam's frame rate wrong here?
Why is my camera's frame rate fucking off?
That's weird.
I think everyone wants us to move on.
Pavlov, we also have
The Lost Colony.
We should probably end on Pavlov because we'll probably be in that for a little while.
We had chef game that turned out to hack your computer.
You want to take a quick little piss break?
I'm a gamer, so I'm ready.
You can take a break.
I'm afraid it's going to break and shatter into my eyes.
Let's do Pulsar.
I have the lowest expectations for Pulsar.
But I'm coming in with an open mind.
I just get the vibe it's going to be NPC talking to people, reading boards.
I don't know why.
I can't read, you know that about me.
Did somebody just say you literally cannot play this game without five people?
It is driving a ship, so I also worried.
You physically can't play this without five people.
Pavlov does kind of need it. Can't we do all of it?
Just do three stream snipers.
Let's just do Pavy.
You don't even want to give that a try?
Not really.
Whatever you want to do.
Since we played VR last week, I've been waiting to do this again.
I'm really excited.
You've got a hot mic right now.
Don't talk about your credit card.
Hey, what's up? Hot mic.
Don't say credit card.
Don't say the word credit card.
Wait, was I on hot mic before?
Are you sure?
I know you were streaming.
I'm streaming, yes.
Probably shouldn't have done that.
I'll just cancel it.
You'd rather cancel your credit card than cancel payments?
You know how you said we were definitely not done playing EDF
and then you never played it again?
I still have the PlayStation subscription, but my PlayStation is completely unplugged.
The only way to cancel it is to plug it all back in.
Then I still wouldn't get to play EDF.
Pavlov!
Which one are we doing? Pavlov or Pulsar?
They both start with P and have Ls in them.
Honestly, I think it's going to take 30 minutes
to set up a VR game, tradition has shown, and then we're going to play Pavlov for 10.
I mean not Pavlov, Pulsar.
I'm opening Pavlov right now.
He just doesn't want to play Pulsar.
Can we get a handful of screenshots
of every time I have the helmet off in VR?
I want them compared in a collage.
Whoever has the technology to screenshot a screen,
just use it wisely.
Alright, I'm closing this. Calami was fun.
It was worth playing. 10 bucks. Pretty cheap.
It's still there.
People can hear you, right?
I feel like we'll be in Pavlov for a little while.
I'm launching it as we speak.
Not yet.
Ow, my knees!
I'm excited!
I just heard a gnome.
Did you guys hear that?
I'm not insane.
That's a bad place to put this.
Are you good?
My stream is showing the SteamVR menu,
but I'm in the game.
What do you want me to do?
I'm trying again. What do you want me to do?
Let me just get in my headset.
I'm trying to get air.
There's no oxygen in this mask.
I don't know if I can do this.
Pavlov is working for you?
I got it.
That's what I'm saying. My Oculus is showing inside Pavlov.
How did you launch it?
Launch it in SteamVR and launch it in OculusVR.
I launched it in SteamVR.
Let me try launching it from the Steam couch room.
Probably a good idea.
I'm getting one last sip.
It says you're playing it.
You don't understand the problem.
I don't think I can get this to work at all.
I have no idea what to do.
What if you open it in OculusVR?
The game launches yet.
My screen is showing something that is not happening.
Really?
It's like an infinite loading screen on my screen.
Do you want to try something else?
I'm going to try one thing and see if I can add it as an Oculus game and launch it from Oculus.
Hey everyone, buy an Oculus.
Keep hearing the note.
That's a joke where you're not supposed to buy an Oculus.
Press menu plus trigger to open the game menu.
That's me.
That's because it's this.
Grab right from using the grip.
Press the lower button to release the magazine.
Now it's a completely blank screen if I launch it from Oculus.
Grab your head and press rip.
Press menu to open the scoreboard.
I'm getting some resistance here.
That's better.
Don't jump out the window.
Press menu plus trigger to open the game menu.
Play offline, play online settings.
Every single game makes you do that, doesn't it?
It actually feels pretty good.
Where's the clip?
That's how you throw.
Grab, activate, and then let go.
The controls are actually really good.
Let me try this thing.
What's going on here?
Are you going to cock it?
My chat said your game is loud and also we might have to play in the beta branch.
We both have to be in the beta.
Do we have to download the game again?
If you just right click properties, switch to beta, it's a short download.
Can you confirm that that works first?
Then I can launch an Oculus VR mode so it should work.
Bunch of beta boys.
Did it work?
Is it confirmed?
The problem is solved.
How does this one work?
Are you good?
I'm in the game and it works.
That was a nightmare.
I think I'm going to throw my Oculus in the trash after the stream.
Why not on stream?
Let's close this.
Go get the beta client.
Do I have any betas?
I don't see any.
Beta dash.
I'm getting it.
Update queued.
Game will launch in approximately three hours.
No way.
Is there a reason why?
There it goes.
The beta client.
I totally am too tall because I can't reach the floor.
This shit is taking a long time.
Why is everything always about you?
You're almost at strike three.
We had technical problems when we started and now you have technical problems again?
That's strike two.
Strike three means you know what it means, right?
That's what it means.
Give a tour of your VR house.
This is what it looks like outside.
You hold your hand up.
A butterfly will land on you.
An Oculus.
Mark Zuckerberg.
I hit my mic.
Where are the butterflies?
What am I at?
25%.
I have gamer neck.
Just open my screen and take a screenshot.
It just puts extra weight down here.
Just go. I wanted to go but I have to download this beta client.
It was downloading so slow.
Blaine Star.
We were ready to go.
I was like alright fine.
What do we do?
I hurt my hand.
I just hurt myself.
For this you have to go on cam and do the Fortnite dance.
What's the one that goes like this?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm just burning conversation fire right now.
What if I can't open the beta?
It's almost done.
You can't climb a tree.
Hold on a second.
Is there any reason why OpenVR wouldn't be capturing this?
I feel like every time I talk to you you're not there.
Is there any reason OpenVR wouldn't be capturing this?
I can't think of a reason.
OpenVR pulls whatever is in your headset.
Strike 3.
Now you can open the game but you can't capture it.
It's because I'm on an Oculus
and OpenVR is for Steam games.
Which is why if you have an Oculus
it should go in the trash.
It's quite the expensive technology.
All I have is desktop capture.
Is there a way I can change the field of view of my desktop capture
so it's not 6?
I'm about to launch the game.
This has been a pretty good break.
Enjoy the chat.
Just hanging out.
Enjoying my beverage.
Why did that person tell me to fuck off?
I'm opening the beta somehow.
I'm going to chill
playing with grenades.
I'm going to try a few things.
Is it opening?
I guess I'm in.
This looks ready to go.
I think I did it.
Did you figure it out?
I'm heading back in.
That was so loud I almost thought it was going to drive into my house.
This person is brazen.
They're starting to get even more ridiculous with this.
One of these days that car is coming through the wall.
I can't wait for that guy to be in the next Jerma Rumble.
Fucking vroom vroom is what that guy's name is going to be.
Why does this do this to me?
Easy. God.
Thank you for your patience.
Your patience is appreciated.
Therefore, you know the rest.
What does this do?
Pistols.
This is cool.
It's a little magnum.
Where did this come from?
Did I buy a pistol? How do I send this back?
Ten hours later, I apologize. This is all my fault.
I'm an embarrassment to you and your family. Thanks for having me over for Thanksgiving.
I invite you to my wedding and all that. I know now why you didn't come.
I'm ready to play.
It's giving me a random question.
How do I get out of this? How do we play together?
There's a menu.
Play online?
I don't know.
North America, Europe.
Make a game or something.
If you hold down the menu button and then hold trigger,
you're going to get a menu. You're going to do play online.
I think these are just games that are going on right now.
This is just like a multiplayer shooter.
I'm going to make one.
Anybody watching right now that wants to play?
Don't stream tonight.
You have a headset on.
That's the future.
Why is that a bad idea?
We'll do it right now.
Check it out.
Input.
Hold on.
Sound.
What is that? Sound.
Is there no sound?
There is no sound option.
There is no audio setting.
We're going to get stream sniped.
There's friendly fire. You can turn bots on.
I see your lobby right there.
Whisper me the password.
This is friends only.
What's your phone number?
It was 741.
Can I mute me?
How do I mute you?
You can mute people.
That's not a problem.
It's this biz kid.
Quick.
There was a kick button here a second ago.
Get him out of here.
I don't care.
We're going to get five copy pastas for the people that come in here.
There's a mute mic button on the left.
When somebody comes in, just hit mute mic on them.
I swear I saw a kick thing.
How many people are watching your stream right now?
6,000.
5,000 here. How many do you have there?
There's like 6,000 people watching this together.
Only Tanner from high school has this game?
Collectively we have 6,000 people.
I'm Tanner.
I'm not. I'm shooting the bots.
Why am I dead?
They just walk over.
How do you reload a gun?
Do I have any more?
I need more bullets.
You have bullets in your sack on your left.
Look in your sack.
I can't bend that low.
Do you have infinite ammo?
I don't know.
Are we playing the gun game?
I'm just playing. Stop with the questions.
I'm here with bot Kurt.
They're letting me do this.
They shouldn't be letting us do this.
Why are you shooting people in the head?
Why?
You're that big. I knew it.
I knew you were the huge guy.
I should have known.
You're bigger than Earthquake.
He's out of ammo.
What?
The different trigger for grabbing the front of your gun is really screwing me up.
This is nauseating.
Wait a minute. What the fuck? Are you kidding me?
This actually is just VR counter strike, isn't it?
You just bend over and pick up guns because I totally can't.
I don't know.
We can play with the actual people.
Anyone joining?
Damn it.
What was this?
Now I didn't get him.
Why did I just hear you?
You're gonna die.
That's the bot Dave.
Is that what it is?
They're footsteps everywhere.
Why can't I hear him?
No.
The bot Dave spawns behind people?
As long as you don't break TOS, we're fine.
You're a reasonable person.
I feel like I've seen you one time.
I just thought you were reasonable. Let's not push in here.
This feels good.
Fucking bot Dave!
Throw it right over his head.
This is not what I thought it was.
What do you have?
This is cool.
I want to keep this.
No!
This is alright.
He's bottom bragging.
Let's do a gun game.
Experience all the guns on data center.
Turn off friends only they say.
I assume they can join even if we're playing.
Unless this is 2003.
Why is everybody doing Bunker S?
What's the nuclear option?
I actually have no idea.
Can you open the menu the way you did before?
No talking anyone.
Do you have any idea?
We're inviting a vampire into our house apparently.
Go to menu.
Save by spring.
Save our spring.
You already did that.
He's behind me.
Drop it.
I can't even see your game anymore.
Why are they always behind you Jerma?
I press the lead button.
I don't want to know what that is.
Is your game still named Star?
I see data center.
Can I see who's in this game?
It's probably full.
I accidentally did it.
I thought it was back.
Don't do that.
You do have to do that because now you have to make a new game.
I'm in the lobby right now because I did the thing that you almost did.
Kick somebody and invite.
Just kick somebody.
That doesn't feel good. It feels better when the streamer is an idiot and has to make the new game.
Play online. Creating lobby.
Friend only so you can join.
I'm setting a pin so it's only stream friend.
I'm in your game.
I don't see you.
Your name is not Star?
This is definitely the lobby.
That was a wrong game.
What's password?
Friend only.
Don't open the menu and click leave.
It's actually leave game.
How do you arrest somebody?
Final gun and gun game is handcuffs.
There we go.
I'm ready to win.
I'm fucking ready.
This is loaded?
You're like gun gaming.
It's like back and it's leave.
I didn't mute it.
Is this a countdown preparing us?
I don't see a countdown.
I muted Josh.
This is fucking awesome.
What is this like?
I'm muted every time.
Everybody is muted and I'm still hearing people talk.
That's the kill feed.
Oh fuck.
I should always be turning around.
I can still take this.
That guy's fucking hat off.
I got it too.
I hate the controls in this.
It's just different to grab than the other gun games we've played.
You don't keep trying to grab the full of your gun and pulling out your magazine.
You have to do it on some guns.
You don't understand.
Oh shit.
You don't like this? I think this is a blast.
This is awesome. It's hard to get used to
being the opposite of how it is.
Nice spawning behind me.
Nice. Nice job.
I got no scoped.
Really?
Nice. Good shot.
I hate these snipers. This is so awesome.
I just got turned on.
Oh my god. Are you kidding? That didn't kill him.
What the hell did you just do?
I'm trying to pull the little handle out.
There we go. It does it automatically.
No it doesn't.
On what?
Oh my god. I hate you.
Fuck you Tommy.
Fuck you Mike.
I hope you guys saw that. That was fucking cool.
I don't know how this gun works.
Shit where? Over here?
Reaction time.
Somebody put the handcuffs on?
Did you use bolt with two hands?
Let's do it again.
I'm bolting with the wrong hand.
I was doing it too.
Learn to use the iron sight.
Forget that.
What? What?
We're people in this game?
I don't believe you.
We're all around looking for people.
I did not.
Get your right in the head.
That was a waste.
I expected to not find anyone for 15 minutes again.
That's what I have to say to that.
He's holding it upside down.
Geez Louise this is a bad one.
Turn around.
I'm walking in circles.
Anyone knows if there's moving and accuracy?
That's a good question.
Come on.
I've been stuck on this saying two guns.
Wrong button.
Don't grab the mag with that gun.
I have to turn like that.
360.
What was that?
What?
I'm confused.
Why did I not see you?
That's my mic.
I'm trying so hard.
I didn't get that kill.
Damn.
I didn't grab it.
I'm so confused on that.
How do I have zero kills?
This is fucking hard.
Again.
I have to solve the mystery of taking your hand off the trigger.
After you take your hand off the trigger once
then you have to hold forever.
I'm going mad.
My headphone fell out.
Can I glue this into my brain?
My ears are getting too sweaty.
I wish I could see how much health they had left.
I got him.
Shoot me please.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
I'm having problems here.
You spawned right...
I got you.
Where did you know
that I was there from?
It's the free upgrade.
Oh fuck no.
Poor spy crap.
Understand how I didn't die.
Did a lot of
little bits of damage apparently.
Come here.
Yes.
Good job.
What happened there?
I'm trying to use the iron sight.
I wonder what that looks like to people watching.
Use the front?
I am using the front and rear sights.
The way that OpenVR works is it only captures
one eye. So depending on where I'm holding it probably doesn't look like
I'm doing it but I am.
Search and destroy?
What is this one?
My arms are covered in water.
Unless your other eye is on your chin.
It's hard.
It's a thing you never did before.
It's a really
not loaded map.
He's played this game before.
No.
I don't know about this one.
What is that?
Up top.
Excellent work.
Did I get him?
What happened?
I don't know how it works.
Please sitting down.
Good.
Make sure nobody hits me.
It's so hard to do that.
I'm going to sneak up and just shotgun blast.
How do I go faster?
I thought I was going to shoot anybody with this thing.
I have no idea how you're supposed to hold a sniper
straight when it has no weight.
Looking through the scope.
There's no way.
Don't people have VR gun things?
I think you can get one.
I got a sniper rifle again.
Now I can shoot it.
I didn't hit him in the head.
What?
Put it down.
It's an HTC Vive gun.
That's so cool.
He's just waving at me.
This is like a demon.
It looks very uncomfortable.
I'm sitting down.
I got him.
The intensity is here.
I got this sniper rifle again.
Hey, just want to show you where I am.
That was horrible.
I fucking murdered you.
Jesus Christ, you need to buy guns?
That was fun though.
No one's spotting behind me.
Buy a gun.
How do you buy a gun?
Get ready.
Left controller on the trackpad.
You can buy stuff.
Trackpad?
Are we bad guys or good guys?
We're the good guys no matter what.
I'm ready with my little baby gun.
Is that a bad guy? Who's on my team?
I took one second to see where I was.
Is there a bomb in here?
I'm dead.
Where is this bomb?
Have I played Counter-Strike before?
Maybe three or four times in my life.
We are defusing bombs.
Let's go.
Put your hands down and move faster.
I'm here.
Just say behind.
Like a chef.
Not behind you.
You have a roast duck behind you.
I don't lie.
We scared them.
Are we supposed to be planting the bomb?
No.
Can I sell this?
I just need to make sure it works.
Covering fire.
Did I?
I threw his gun out.
I like this gun.
What's this?
Devolitions.
Stop.
I don't know.
Put it here.
There's a spot on the wall.
I don't have one of those.
You got this. Easy.
They're the ones planting the bomb.
I had bombs.
Grenades.
How do you throw the grenade?
If I did that over here, I'm going through the wall.
When you throw in this game, you throw really fast.
Do you have to hold grip and let go?
Or trigger and let go?
Let go.
Who wants this gun?
It makes me hold it easier.
It's like monsters.
I think I got an extra.
It's my time.
Let the rookie in.
Look at that line.
I'm going to make sure they don't come down that way.
This is really awesome.
Do I have to pump it?
I can't see.
That's it.
Time for the big gun to come out.
Where's the other one?
Can I haunt him?
This guy is always behind me.
Let's see how things are going.
Where are you?
I'm stream sniping. He's planting a bomb.
Get a good view.
I don't believe it. It's impossible.
That was like the term VR is in your name.
Is this going to blow up?
Is everyone sneezing?
I'm going to stay with everybody.
I'm getting spam weapons.
This is the ultimate spam weapon.
I'm going to hold the buttons down.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Watch out.
I think I killed him.
This is really cool.
I'm trying to figure out how to jerk off the gun.
Did that button not do it?
I don't know what to do.
Two shotguns?
Knife only.
Let's tell them knife only and then let me shoot them with the shotgun.
Where are they?
On the right.
Covering fire there.
What is this? It was like a drone here.
I fucking hate this game.
Hold the gun and pull it out.
Is this like 60 rounds?
I don't need money.
I can't buy anything.
I can afford the pirate gun for rushing B.
Let's fucking go.
Teams.
I don't know what to pick.
I'm not sure.
I'm going to be Reaper.
I panicked.
I don't know what to do in these scenarios.
I'm going to server.
There's too much.
Headphones are gone.
That's not how a shotgun is held.
Jesus Christ.
Are we going to the climbing game?
What am I supposed to do with this?
This is too expensive.
I'm not supposed to own this.
This was like a $75 gun that my mother bought me.
Buy armor.
I aimed for the head.
It was a very heavy statue gun.
Where is this?
That's bad.
That was a 1 in 10 game.
You almost had it.
Are there other people that want to go in it?
Are there people that want to play?
What?
That's a good joke.
What are you doing?
You're waiting for me?
What did you just do for a game mode?
TDM?
Walking around corners is the hardest thing.
I'm trying to get the sidearm.
Give me the shotgun.
I'm ready for 5 guns.
I'm too slow.
What did I do?
What?
You bastard.
I'm so sorry.
I saw a person teleport in front of me.
There's a guy behind you.
I got him.
Get over there.
What's happening?
That's not good.
I'm so sorry everybody.
That had to be the worst offense ever.
I was reloading the gun.
It wasn't that bad?
What did you just give me?
I've run a full lap.
The inside of my ear is straight water.
There's no way these are staying in for more than 5 seconds at a time.
I don't want this little thing.
Oh god.
That's what I'm talking about.
Bread and butter.
That's what I'm talking about with my bread and butter.
My lighthouse.
I broke it.
I'm just running a marathon.
Where's the button to press to make this work?
What happened?
There was someone the whole time.
Wait.
I don't understand.
There's a guy on the ceiling.
It was a grenade.
I think I might have to go to the bathroom.
What?
I swear.
This is one of those games where my thumb is really hurting.
This game is wild.
Run!
Save us!
I'm losing my mind.
My tail is wrapping around me.
Oh my god.
The drink?
You scared the shit out of me.
I thought I dumped it on the ground.
That would be horrible.
This is ridiculous.
I'll do one more and then we can move on.
Gun game was fun.
I think I gave up trying to get this thing.
Now I've got to wipe my disgusting headset.
I'm almost back.
Don't shoot me.
I feel like I can hear footsteps on the other side of the map.
Shit! Nice shot.
What do they say?
They say game up.
Twitch energy drink mode?
What the hell does that mean?
Game on.
The gun doesn't even make a noise.
Don't say that.
You just spoiled the whole show.
Like your avatar.
Sometimes it pumps in my cheek.
How can I have somebody be in front of me?
Nobody around.
Wow!
Watch out there.
Did I do it?
Behind you guys.
This isn't fair.
I was supposed to win.
Why are we watching Jeremy be bad at games?
Do you understand how hard this is to do?
No.
It's harder when you're short.
Game on.
You just did it.
You're never going to see him again.
Wait for people to come from exactly right there.
Don't worry, I'm behind you guys.
He's behind me.
Stop! I'm concentrating.
He's behind you.
He's behind us.
No, I will not.
Was I behind you?
He was behind me.
We both can't hit each other.
What the hell are you doing?
My hand is breaking.
Did it change guns?
I was standing in my dead zone.
No tracking there.
Why is it quiet?
Jeremy's bad at games.
What?
This is fun as hell.
What a fun game.
Let's do it again.
I love this.
I think there's more maps on the workshop.
I think I can download them right through here.
You should be able to.
They all have 2 star ratings.
I'm not a kid, I'm 14.
You can't emancipate till 16.
That guy is in some kind of shape.
I think someone is behind me.
You have to believe.
I thought he was upstairs.
No one can be behind me.
Don't say that.
They told you they weren't.
It's so hard.
Let me take a look through my scope.
Why is that my kill?
Did you shoot the gun out of my hand?
What weapon?
Dime sized scope.
Too many people in every direction.
There's a monster on the ceiling.
That's game 2.
I'm getting better, but I'm not better than Guy with VR in his name.
I got sweat all over me.
I'm shaking.
Game 20.
Just one more.
Just one more game.
That's it.
After this one game where I don't get on the scoreboard.
This is the one.
I lit that pool up.
You stole that from me.
Where am I?
Somebody is behind me.
In both directions.
Did I get you?
I'm not listening to chat ever again.
I will never listen to you ever again.
Dump soda on the ground.
Unbelievable.
It's the first thing I see when I come out.
Who threw the gun?
My hitbox is bigger than everyone's.
Maybe you shouldn't have the giant setting.
There's one other tall guy in here.
Where is this coming from?
Excuse me.
I have no idea how to reload this.
I got like an achievement for killing him.
Why was there a dude that was massive?
He was like the size of a skyscraper.
I have no idea.
I don't even know who was tall.
Maybe he is just that tall.
He might be like 9 or 10 feet tall.
He's standing on a chair.
The last one.
Can you smell me?
Why would you ever want the fun thing?
I'm so close.
There's a wall here.
Where are you at?
The data.
I'm getting disoriented.
Thank god.
I just spawned there.
I'm going up.
I don't know where the hell you are.
What?
This is not a one shot kill?
This thing's not a one shot kill gun.
Right hand bolt.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why this gun spawns in my hand.
I should be used to it.
I'll take it.
Not bad.
I heard him.
I don't know how to reload.
That's what I want.
How come the guy with his hands won't run to me?
Thanks for playing guys.
That was a blast.
That was fun.
How long has it been?
I have no idea.
Sorry everybody.
3 hours and 45.
Unless there's something else you want to do.
I have a couple other things I could play.
There are a few things I could play.
It's up to you.
Let's see.
There's always Pulsar.
He's not going to budge.
You're going to remake it for me.
You need to remake it for me.
Beat Saber multiplayer.
That would be me getting my ass kicked.
I have a handful of things I could do.
That was Star by the way.
That's not true.
Twitch.tv.
That makes so much sense.
I should be able to walk.
That's great.
That was fun playing with you.
Enjoy Beat Saber.
We have D-Rail Valley.
Minecraft.
That's going to have to be another day.
Pavlov.
That was probably the best shooter for VR.
Let's try Disassembly.
You could make cars and tear them apart.
It looked interesting.
Did Gorn get an update yet?
I don't think it has.
Last time I tried to play Gorn with the same settings,
there was a performance update.
I don't think they updated it yet.
Are you sure?
I'm just going to open it and see what happens.
The beta build reportedly fixed it.
How does this look?
Before it was like 20 frames a second.
Are you okay?
That looks a lot better.
I should have dragged it that fast.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
The vroom guy has to go home.
This is what he does for work.
He gets paid $50 an hour to drive fast.
What do you do for work?
It's funny you say that.
I just drive around in a circle.
It's hard to explain.
Twitch streamers try to explain their income.
I'm like a guy that has a platform called car.
I drive around in a circle.
I step on the gas on this one specific strip
of 800 to 900 yards
for 12 times a day.
Who pays you?
I do. I've had a lot of money in bitcoin.
This is my dream.
That was fun.
More multiplayer.
Star couldn't figure out how to get his shit going.
What was that?
Looks like it's fixed.
I'm sure we'll find out real quickly here.
If there's a mod that has the capability
to change the name of the game to Gorn.
Grab world. Move hand here.
Move back.
Press and hold to grab world.
I have different controls set up.
What the fuck was that?
That was very odd.
It's fixed.
Yes! This is the game everybody wanted me to play so badly.
Now I get to actually play it.
This is the one.
Let's kick that guy's ass.
One of these emote faces. This game is absurdly violent.
If you're not over the age of 21, don't consume alcoholic beverages.
This is fixed. Let's fucking go.
Toggle hold. Hold. Gesture.
Is that the only gesture? Just middle finger.
Real mature. Right off the bat.
I don't know what this is today.
I've done it like five times today.
Let's go. Gesture. Hold. Toggle hold.
Let's go.
Streamer tells audience to fuck off.
When did I do that?
Toggle hold.
Okay.
So is there a quick turn?
Or do I actually have to turn?
Alright. Let's go.
Is there a block or a parry?
Is this what you want?
Is this what you want to see?
Come here.
Ooh. I broke his ankle.
How's the audio?
Label?
Good.
Okay.
How do I grab this?
There we go. This is like a rubber mace.
Alright. Bring it on. Next wave. Still alive?
You gotta go. You gotta break their arms.
Holy shit. I just blew up that guy's head. Watch out.
Oh my god. That's terrible.
You got shin pads? I see. I see. I get you.
Come on. On the ground. Right in the chest.
I fucking won!
This is actually really fun.
Do I just have to keep going?
Shield this time. Okay. I want this in my right hand.
Excuse me.
Okay. Easy.
This is a huge shield. It's like an umbrella.
Can I hit myself in the face?
Oops-a-daisy. Easy here. Right in the legs.
Come on! Oh, is this your friend?
How come these guys don't have armor? They're just free kills.
Rip off someone's head?
Oh, okay. So there's a champion at the end of this.
I gotta do this.
So, wait. Wait. Wait.
Free for all? I don't have a weapon.
Oh, fuck. Give me a weapon.
Give me that. Come here.
I think he's dead. I'm getting wrapped up in my cord. Uh-oh.
Careful there's a wall.
I'm actually getting stuck.
Stuck. Oh, god. I'm getting close to something.
I know it. I can feel it. How many more? Free for all?
Until what? Until everyone's dead? Oh, you can throw shit too.
Come here.
I just fucking Curly, Moe, and Larry.
Whatever their names are. It's free punks.
I did it! What's the final channel?
Okay.
Alright, let me get ready here. Let me get ready.
Bring it on. Alright, does it get like a gulp mask on?
I'll take that. You ain't gonna be fighting anymore.
Oh, it took his whole arm off.
That guy was easier than the default enemies.
I almost just hit the wall. It's okay.
Alright, Achilles. General? What's Achilles?
This is easy. Soda. The soda spilled. Oh, no.
You don't have a camera anymore. You opened the door and walked outside.
I can see the soda on the table, guys.
Should we go to tier two? How does this work?
I can only do tier one. I'm just gonna go to Achilles.
It is.
This is a proper sword. This isn't a real sword.
This is a fake sword. So we got slicing action.
I gotta cut a leg off. Oh, my God.
That was actually really cool.
Holy shit.
How do I rip somebody's head off?
Take a body of limbs and your head.
How do I rip his head off?
How do I do that?
Well, that was absolutely brutal.
Where's the new weapon? It's Battle Axe.
Yes. Jesus. Yeah, that was pretty insane.
Two hands? No. A little slower movement on this one, I think.
Yeah, a little bit.
Legs. Try to sweep underneath.
Are you still swinging at me?
How are you still doing this?
How are you still doing this? Oh, my God.
Whoa. I took his chin off.
Shit, he hit me.
Oh, there's bow and arrows in this game?
Come here.
Whatever. He's dead.
You fight that guy, eventually.
I'm going to get taught.
Okay.
Alright, so we got blunt.
We got our little hammer here.
Let's go for, I'm going to say shoulders.
Go club. This guy's got plate armor on.
That's new. What weapon? Something else I can use?
Oh, fuck. It's kind of hard for me to do two at the same time.
I'm dead. Yeah, do well with this control setup because
when you have two weapons, this no longer
is like walk. So, it's hard to do two.
This is like better for shield for me. Because then I have to use this to walk when I swing
with this hand. Come here.
Good night. What else you got? Grab the armor first.
Nope. Just kidding. Watch out, there's a wall somewhere here. I want that axe.
Hello? There we go.
Anymore?
This is a soda.
Okay, what do we got?
Okay. Hmm.
I wasn't a fan of this last time, but I'll try it again.
See what I mean? I can't walk forward. Because when I raise
my hand up, it's like, are you sure you're moving? It's not ideal.
See when I lift my hand up, even if I'm trying to
walk forward, I go backwards. So, I have to go backwards
when I lift my hand up here. It's weird.
Come here. I don't think so.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Good thing I had the hand scraps on.
That was a broken glass. Something would have shattered.
Arrows. Goodbye. Yes!
Is there a multiplayer in this game?
I don't think there is.
Okay, here comes Achilles.
Where am I? Ooh.
Alright, I'm going to go with just one hand here.
I'm way better with one hand.
Let me see his leg. That's why your name is Achilles!
That would make sense, wouldn't it? I guess that's throwing shit.
Oh, what a clever boy. Achilles.
Preserker. General. Well, we can go into tier two.
What is general? Is general just
like the general? Badgermancer.
Everybody seems to want to see this one.
This control is...
Okay. I like spears in these games.
I'm going to have to move around with the right stick here.
Really slippery though. I guess I can just swing.
Nope. I need to go the other direction.
Come here. I need to, yeah, I gotta go the
other way. Alright, you can pick people up, I think.
Come here.
What is happening? Alright, let go of this.
I don't want to use this thing anymore. That's what I'm talking
about. That's much better. This thing is so tangled.
Jeremy, you're a sicko. Oops-a-daisy.
That thing looks kind of fun. Oh, I thought you went under.
I thought he went down. Oh, shit. Is he dead? Yeah.
I'm ripping his head off. Oh, fuck it.
Oops. What? Did I bump into my thing?
Open it up.
Ugh.
One, two, three. Oops-a-daisy. That didn't work.
That did not work like I intended it to.
Oh, the goddamn controller.
I'm going to die.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
I really wish it, okay, so this is the worst part.
Ready? I'm moving forward. Now I'm moving backward.
It doesn't matter. I'm holding here. Now we're going this way.
I wish it was just forward because now I have to go. I have to switch to back.
It's literally, it's just whatever direction the track pad is in.
I'd rather just have this be forward.
Will you stop? Bring him on. Yeah, crash.
Look at that dude. Oh, trying to do a cool move. Trying to throw him in the air.
Does that guy have a t-shirt on?
That guy just almost did the look at me. He's close.
One, two, three. Is this it? Last guy.
Come here.
This is fucking so much fun.
Spikes? Oh, shit. Those are spikes.
What are those? What is on me?
Spiderman grips? Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me, give me, give me.
Give me that back. They're like boomerangs? Okay.
That's really cool. Holy shit.
This is too much.
No. Those things are really fun. I'm running out of gas so I'm not going to lie.
I'm running out of gas. I didn't have very much left in the tank when I opened this.
That's a good technique. Just thunderclap.
I've got to throw somebody in the spikes at least once before I leave.
Thank you. Come here. Jesus. That worked.
God damn it.
Alright. I'm killing the badger guy and I'm done.
I've used all my fuel. This game is fucking awesome though.
That guy don't matter. We'll take care of this guy first.
His eyes just popped out of his head.
I've got this guy's like juice on me.
The people are stuck. Get this off.
How am I going to release?
He's still on me.
Alright.
Too many movement games today.
The climbing game. The run around shoot game.
It's been just exercising for four hours.
I'm running on a treadmill for four hours.
I want the bow. Let me try the bow. How does this work?
Wow. That's fun. Give me the arrow battery.
I'm going to use this.
That didn't go very far.
Not good. Give me something else.
I hate that control scheme. It's going to make me scream.
Can I change that?
Funny.
Are we going to get a comedy level?
A little stabber?
I'm doing it like real life.
Come here. You can pick him up and you can
skewer him. That's amazing.
See you later. That did so good.
What happened to your arm?
Your arm is not doing so well.
Goodbye.
Alright. Boss time after this, right?
You're dead?
What?
What? What happened there?
I don't understand. What was hitting me?
There was nobody else behind me. You have to kill somebody to live.
He hit me once and I feel like I shouldn't have died there.
Is it like a fast
kill for these things? This thing is fun but
I'd rather just use my weapon.
I like this thing way better.
That feels good.
Alright. Watch out for the wall.
I was trying to get a wall.
Why does it just have its mind of its own? That's it?
Delay. Drink him.
Badger Mancer.
Here it comes. Let's go.
Do I get a weapon? Do they come after me?
What do I do?
What's going on? What's happening?
Why is it still giving me a chance?
I'm going to go kick the shit out of him.
I'm going to get fucking hurt.
I did it!
I ran out of fuel 40 minutes ago.
You get special weapons after you beat the bosses. That's actually really fun.
You had grappling hooks the whole time that you didn't use.
Oh well. But that was a ton of fun.
VR is just too much fun. I wish I had more stamina.
End of the Badger Mancer voice.
Imagine the smell. I don't smell. I smell fine. That was a lot of fun.
Let me take this off.
I will see you guys on the next stream.
You can change the control screen. Yeah. I'll have to do that.
I'm not streaming tomorrow. I think the next time
you guys are going to see me is Wednesday.
Two days. Not next Wednesday.
Going is a lot of fun. I might have to come back and play it.
We're going to do a VR night where I complete the
games that I didn't beat. And Mind Show 2, I know.
There's so many experiences. The thing with Mind Show though is Mind Show should be a pretty
I don't think I'll play that for like three to four hours. I feel like I could
do that for a while because it's not a whole lot of like fucking jumping around like running and
breathing and up, down, up, down, twist, twist, twist.
But thank you everybody. I'll see you in a couple days. Like always.
These streams are a fucking ton of fun. Playing with Star was a lot of fun.
The last two days of co-op have been fucking hilarious.
And stressful. And fun. So it's been great.
Thank you everybody. I will see you all real soon. Take care of yourselves.
Stick around for the bits if you want to. What am I going to do on Wednesday?
I don't know. There's a... I could dedicate
Wednesday to Mind Show. Or I might put the
VR away for like another three or four streams. Still going to play...
Channel 5. Seaman. We still have that. That's been kicking around
for a while. Ace Attorney Trilogy comes out on the 10th of April, yeah?
Oh man, oh man. There's a lot to do. Stupid Invaders
Disc 1. You know, it's true. Let's get the outro going here.
Yeah, a lot of people
have been watching these streams. I'm
very happy that people are liking them. There's been a lot of positive
feedback on the VR stream, so I'm really happy.
I'm glad it can be fun. It's a very enjoyable experience,
I think. At least for me. At least for you too. Do Onward?
Yeah, we'll have to do it. I have it now, so it's time to do a bunch of it.
Let me close out of this. Finish Dreadhalls?
Yeah, we'll do like a finish the game stream. Not
necessarily on Wednesday, but I'm not sure. I'll be around. I'll be around in the Discord.
I'll be around in the chat here
in like a day or so. We'll talk about what we're going to do.
But I am pooped, as they say.
Let's head back a little earlier, a few hours ago, about four and a half hours ago.
Where do we start here? Yeah, right there.
Thank you to Divus five hours ago for the 250.
Appreciate it. Also thank you to
Take Me Home for the 250. You can set SteamVR to show your
IRL surroundings if you get close to a wall. Yeah, it's already there.
I have the blue thing set up, but when you get heated, you get
in the moment. It's so hard, because you're focused on
what's happening in the game. And even with the blue bars,
it can be very, very hard to avoid them. Oh, there they are.
No, it straight shows your room, not just the blue bars.
Oh, really? It shows the room? That's
weird. It's just a learn thing. The longer you play VR, you sort of remember your
space better, but accents still happen. It's a lot of fun.
Frody and Weapon Thanks for the $5 JermaJex, JermaJex 2.
There were two or three Jex moments tonight.
There were at least seven or eight
John moments. And there was probably 30 Jeremy moments.
So, it balances out, I think. Is there a
top 10 JermaScreaming clips from this stream? I don't think there's very much screaming.
No, that was a few days ago. This wasn't a scream stream.
This was like a try-hard shooter stream.
Like Star was saying before, imagine PavlovVR
in a competitive LAN setup, and they're all up there
like game show contestants hooked up to different helmets instead of computers.
That'd be wild. And then if they die, there's like a trap door that opens
and they fall out of their VR headsets and go through the trap door.
But thank you to
the Nintendo PlayStation for the $5 here.
Been watching you for a long time since TF2 2014.
Thank you. Really appreciate it. And you're currently playing Homeworld 2.
Homeworld 2. With like a Star Wars mod?
They had Star Wars mods for Homeworld?
That's kind of insane. But thank you, Nintendo PlayStation, for the $5 here.
Or actually $7 here, $7.50.
And they say the heavy machine gun you use is an MK48.
The gun appears in so many games like Black Ops 2 and it's even
in GTA 4. The huge one? Yeah.
That gun is in like every game, isn't it? That fold-out
like futon gun. I call that thing, that's a futon.
It's just a huge fold-out machine gun. Bro luck!
Thank you for the $2.50. Don't know if you've seen this yet. I'm not sure.
I'll tell you about it. Hello Moto.
I have not seen this. I'm not sure why I would want to see this.
Hello Moto Ring.
Oh shit. I've been like talking this whole time.
I don't know why that muted.
He's stuck in the, what was the last thing you heard me say? Motorola?
Oh god. Well I said, I talked about
D. Reggie Deddy gave me $3 and wrote something about a
flamethrower. It's an RPG combined.
It's like a plasma in the gun. And it's a link to
I don't even know what it is. It's a weird looking little gun thing.
You were just playing the music and nothing else.
We just heard the music.
I'm tired. I don't know.
This is what it looks like apparently. I have no idea.
Thank you Core Monster for the $15. That was a load of fun.
I was bargain binned with the pink avatar. Hope you can do this another time.
I was looking forward to this shit and it did not disappoint.
Thank you. Glad to have people participate if they can.
Sometimes it's hard to do. It can be tricky sometimes
with the amount of people that show up to streams.
I like to do community stuff when I can. Involve people if they want to play.
Thank you for the $15. Appreciate it. Glad you had fun. Cause it was fun.
I might not be the best VR shooter, but I tried.
Thank you again Core Monster for the $15.
Thank you also to Nintendo Playstation for $12.
I have an idea. Get VR troopers.
It's a better headset. I disagree.
Thank you though.
I'm going sicko.
I didn't do very well for a lot of those.
There was a few rounds of the gun game.
I was really feeling it. I could just feel the weight.
I was pretending. You have to actually move your arms.
I came into fourth place one of those times.
Sick Jax.
Sicko mode is a great song, but the meme is getting very old at this point.
I don't even know what it is. Poor Boomer has to do physical exercise.
What was me? I had to get up and move for four and a half hours.
Also we had the
Jewish Bro came in with about $4 here.
Could you play Seaman and more shitty games on Wednesday?
VR is fun, but let's go back to the basics.
I'm of the opinion. If I'm having a good time, I'm going to keep having a good time.
I definitely don't want to do exclusively
only VR, but it is a brand new toy.
I was tired after just the Pavlov match. That's a lot of exertion.
Jerma did Climey and Gorn today.
Before Climey, Star's computer broke in the chef game.
Any plans to go to the furry convention in Chicago? Yeah, I'll be there.
I think they say, can you pull an all-nighter and see how long you last?
No, I don't stream all night.
I can't do that. Let's get the credits going up too.
All the new subs and resubs, thank you guys.
And his rat costume? No, his frog costume.
Just want to make sure everyone's really clear. Frog.
Oh, is he a rat? Is he a...
Maybe he's a fox? Nope. Frog. If I had to pick.
Frogs don't have fur. That doesn't matter.
Could be a froggy. Why do you enable them?
It's fun. And we had Bingo Sunshine for $5. Thank you, Bingo.
Whoops. You missed that one. Try another VR stream.
Okay, then. I'll be a penguin. See you there.
Someone's going to edit that clip and just cut out you saying
just kidding. Well, people have their...
The internet's a powerful place. I've said this before.
Think of how many sentences I've said being recorded on a microphone.
I have said every single word. If you were dedicated
enough, you could make an entire audiobook
of me saying anything you wanted over the course of like
four or five hundred pages. You could make anything.
And you could write a whole book and have me be the narrator
with different clips. You could just make an AI to view your videos and recreate
you in your entirety.
I haven't said every word.
Relax. I see my name. Time to watch every
Jerma stream and make sure he's said every single word.
Streamer lies. Jiggle it a little. It'll open.
Oh my god. I've never swore on stream.
Yes, I have. I think I swore every like eight minutes
today. You've never said... No, I'm not saying
words. But the next time I see you guys will be
on Wednesday. Have a nice relaxing start to your week.
Thank you for joining me on the VR stuff last couple of days. And we did VR
three days ago too, right? Four days ago? Thanks everybody again
for hanging out. Hope you have a good time. Take care everybody.
And Nintendo PlayStation with $2.50 right at the end. Hey Jerma, can you say
like... No. I'm not gonna say the thing from...
I almost said Breaking Bad. No. What's that show with
the nerds? It's like a nerd show. Earth. It's called like
at the... We're at the Earth. The Big Bang.
Yeah. I don't want to say the Sheldon catchphrase.
But I'll see you guys soon. Take care. Have a nice one.
And goodbye. Eat your vegetables. And drink your fucking water.
Like I'm gonna go down water right now. See you later guys.