No, I wasn't I wasn't going to the bathroom. I'm and I know sometimes that pops up hold on wait
Well, I just wait I gotta wait 30 seconds
Hold on baby. I gotta give at least a minute for people to get in here. I know i'm late. I'm sorry
I got snagged, you know, like you have something to do and like you're like, oh, it's fine
And then all of a sudden like it pops up
At 2 59 p.m. You're like no you just can't don't pop this up right now
snagged by the toilet
No, that can happen
What you're describing is very real, right?
That didn't happen to me
But at 2 59 if like you I don't know
Feeling a little woozy down there. You're gonna have to go that didn't happen to me
Uh john cena, thanks for the 10 subs
Did you do twice?
Wait john cena is killed. Did you do you did two different 10 community subs in a row?
Holy shit. Well, thank you john cena
You're late mister
I know it's but it's all right
All right. Now, let me let me just tweet this. I look I got snagged
I've ever I gotta tweet this. I didn't even tweet this. I'll be right back. We're gonna play black masses today
Uh, it's a game where there's like 5 000 enemies on screen a 10 omega lowl 80 should be cool
um
I don't know. It looks like it could be kind of fun. I have a backup game if this game sucks
And it's a good one and I am i'm looking really forward to playing the backup game eventually if I don't play tonight
Oh my god, this game sucks next I didn't even do anything
Is sim casino out?
I'm dead when that comes out. I'm gonna play it
I thought that wasn't coming up for a while
This game is not good. Well, it's all right. The backup game is gonna be so good
Because the backup game are you ready for this?
No, I can't do this. I can't tell you what the backup game is
Because everyone's gonna freak out and be like dude play the backup game right now. Fuck this game
Now hold on
It's a backup game for a reason
Because everyone's gonna want me to play the backup game first. Let me tweet this up here back everyone. Hold on
Just how you guys doing today? I didn't even ask you that
How you guys doing? You guys doing good?
sim casino came out in november
What?
All right. Let me tweet this beer back. I didn't know what to write. So I just wrote playing games on twitch
Oh, well, okay. So yeah, let's go. This should be fun at least for a little while. We can play roblox
Um, i'm i'm never gonna play roblox i've come to the terms and i'm waiting for their ipo
When their ipo comes out, maybe i'll give it a look roblox waiting room
When is the ipo? I don't know. Yeah, I don't think it's coming out soon
Let's move it over here
this game
The cam's not on right? Thank god. Thank god. Hey, here it is. This is called the black masses
Um, I you can just I have the settings already
I can play this online. I don't know if I want to do that though. Is that bad?
This is a game where like 5 000 people can be on the screen. It's a huge like medieval war game
I've had this in my steam library for months and months and months
in fact this game has been on the
poll
For the last like seven polls
And nobody ever picks it
So it's time for me to pick it. It's time for me to say we're playing it. Nobody wants to see this game
But you know what I do and that's what i'm because hold on
No, you don't even know what this is. Oh, yeah, what game is this? You heard me say it like four times
What game is it? What game are we playing?
All right, should I just play online?
Oh, I don't know. I don't know if I want to do that. Never mind
Please be patient click clicking at 90 percent causes windows to think application has stopped responding
Okay, i'm not touching four percent what
The best part of all this it says please be patient
Oh, dear
I have a fat wait. Did it go backwards? Oh, no, we're good. Look at that. Okay. Yeah, give me a break
Can you hear it? Is this audio good? This is like an rpg guys. It's not just like a game
We run around and hit stuff
There's like a quest giver and stuff this guy i've been trying to play this for like three months. I'm gonna do it
I'm not clicking. Don't tell me no
Oh Jesus a 25 community subs from nuclear waffle. This has been a lot of subs today
That's a gigantic sub
That that'll feed an entire super bowl party
All right. Here we go
Did not freeze
Maybe it did
Did it freeze?
No, this is skyrim intro
Hey you
You're finally awake
A fucking meteor just hit the side of the house
Hey you you're awake
What can I change the fov?
You have been chosen
me
Oh sure. Okay
Do I have powers?
Back to bed
This is a vr. Oh shit
All right
So this is me. I have 60 health 100 green and 100 blue
Where do I go?
I just woke up on the beach. All right
It's actually skyrim
I open up like chest press action button to open
15 fps. No, it's not
What am I supposed to do?
Wait options
All right. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait
Yeah, I put it on medium. All right. Is there you got a problem with that?
I put it on medium because I knew there's gonna be like 5 000 people on the screen
I'll put the terrain at high
All right terrain is at high
New quest something isn't right scavenge for supplies. All right sick blood on the ground
Open your journal
How do I open the journal?
Something isn't right scavenge find a health potion find a light source find a weapon make your way down the road
All right, let's go. Whoa
All right
Put it all on potato. Not yet
This is cain's house
I've all right. I promise i'll put it all on potato eventually
All right. I will tell you
This looks like i'm watching a stream at like 3 000 up
I feel like the bit rate. I feel like i'm playing this through a stadia
You're seeing right now the reason why not to buy one of those
Oh look, oh quest
I'll jump to initiate a climb
press w
What the fuck are you serious?
All right, this game just got way cooler. That was pretty cool. All right, that was pretty cool
All right, what's in here?
a sword
I'm not even in here
Oh health potion and a key
Find a health potion health potion found
Press l to turn the lantern on
Oh shit. Nice
Oh, this is a key to cain's house
You apologize
Uh, i'm sorry. All right. I got the key to cain's house. I'm good
Did you have to eat in this game?
Does it fall damage?
Nope. All right. Here's the key to cain's house
All right, is cain does cain live here?
She would be worried about cain being upset at us coming in his house
Does anybody live in this town?
I gotta what do I need? I need a weapon
Oh hold. Wait a minute
What though?
Uh, can you hit somebody with a feather?
Is that cain?
It's gonna be a screamer. Here it comes
Is there a punch?
cain
Hello
Oh, this guy's actually kind of this guy's actually kind of scary. I don't like this guy
trouble, oh no
Are you serious?
I thought it was gonna be a sword
Are you kidding me?
Find a weapon. Okay
Well, hold on. That means I have to kill the guy down there
He's alive down there. Yeah, I can hear
You picked up a weapon press attack to equip or open your inventory for more options. Well, hold on
Where is he now?
Oh footbridge
This is actually got okay i'm into this let's go. Oh shit there he is. Okay press the attack
Holy shit, I peeled his face off. Oh, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I ripped his entire mouth off
I'm just like skinning his head
Is he dead
Okay, I think he's dead
I hit him so hard. I ripped his face off. All right. How do you take a health potion?
Oh, that's why I gotta go there. Okay
frames
Yeah, we might have to make the graphics way worse
We're probably gonna have to have the graphics be terrible because that was one guy on screen and it's like
stuttering in 40 fps
the steam page
Of this game touts potentially hundreds of people on screen
Okay, let's go check your map for quest markers. Holy shit. It's like day z
What the fuck?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Everybody slow down for a second. Are you serious? This is huge
This is monstrous
This is the early access map
uh
Okay, we're going this way apparently
Find a safe space. That's very surprising
Find a safe space
All right, i'm just gonna go let's
Oh, that's my stamina in the middle. All right
Our most ambitious title to date
Oh shit a human
No, wait, that's a zombie
one two
Two people on screen
Die
All right. Let's do a running charge at this guy. Wait, this is level one. Is it wait I level up in this game
oh
Holy shit. I took the guy's leg off. All right, I need a safe place
I'm getting there. All right, we're gonna go to strathsphere
nice
dodge, okay
Oh shit that hurt the person has a t-shirt on do they have t-shirts in medieval times?
Oh, there's blood all over this shirt. I thought it was like a graphic t
All right level up. How do I how do I get points on it?
Open blessings menu
The hell is the blessings menu blessings
What the hell?
strength
Perform a 360 degree spin to clear enemies around you with a flaming sword
uh
Fire three normal projectiles and a horizontal spread. I need a bullet. There's a guns
There are guns in this game
dark arts
allows instantaneous travel to previously visited safe zones or
Stamina regenerates while in combat. I don't know what to do
It's skyrim with guns
Yeah
I think i'm just gonna do strength. That's the easiest right?
I'm gonna do strength
Oh, look at that
All right. How do I do that? How do I do that move? Oh, that was nice
I'm intrigued at this game. I'm not i'm not done
I wish it would run. Um, maybe five percent better, but i'm kind of into it. I'm into it right now
I want to know what's what it is in store for me here
I have to put it on potato
Okay reflections potato. I get you post-processing low
Trees to get that off
Shadows and rendering you can put that on high
Okay, let's see how that looks
No, who likes reflections in games anyways?
Yeah, this looks better now. I actually think this looks better
I hate reflections. It's too much
Okay, i'm almost there. I gotta bang a right bang a left
How do I do the 360 spin somebody behind me? Oh shit. Okay. Hold on 360 spin
How do I do it?
Okay, that was with an oar that's not intimidating that's pretty stupid
How much does it take?
I like this game
I you want me to lie to you? Sure. I hate this game. There's your lie. Here's the truth. I like this
All potato. No, I don't want to do all potato
I can't wait to get more items
Maybe it's just this area that is choppy. Maybe it'll even out. This is the town, right? Yeah. Okay
uh
Wait parkour
Yeah, don't fight. Why would I fight? I'm just gonna get killed
This is bread
Okay, I don't they probably can't climb right?
Can they climb?
Oh Jesus. Okay. Hold on
All right. I'm not gonna go that we're gonna go to the house
done brum
All right, what's better the bro?
Wait, wait, wait, can they come they can come in the house?
I want to use the broom. How do I put how do I equip rare it is?
This is light
This thing sucks. This guy has no arms
This is terrible. The broom is not good
You're hitting him with the hay end
Yeah, it's like a bug
It's like a spider on the wall
Okay, hold on. I need it. How much health do I heal with a health potion?
Oh, what's this repair kit?
Okay, no more fucking around. Give me the ore. I need where's is there any towns people?
I'm just running
Yeah, fuck it. I'm just gonna run
Wait church church church church
All right. I found a safe zone open
Are you human?
a human
Okay, what? Hello?
Thank god
Oh another human
What happened here?
Uh, they're all possessed. Where have you been?
Something happened to my ship and it sank in the night. I woke up on the shore
What do you mean possessed something happened to my ship and it sank in the night. I woke up on the shore. What do you mean possessed?
I don't fully understand it myself. It has something to do with the black liquid they found by servatia
After people started to drink it. They started to change
I see
They're all possessed. Where have you been?
Something happened to my ship and it sank in the night. I woke up on the shore
Well glad to see someone normal
Maybe we can help each other
Any chance you can help me get off this island?
You're you're asking for a miracle, but it's possible there might be others left who can help
Any idea where I can find any other survivors?
Many fled to fort wyver. It's a short walk down the road, but I fear the worst
It's too quiet now. I'll check that out
I can't kill him. What if I need him later? I don't want to do the ore flaming ore spin
No, I can't
How do I save the game?
You sleep in beds like skyrim
Wait, I can steal from them. Does he care?
Many have died we might need this guy later. I can't
Finish him. He's not even wouldn't even finish him. He's fine. He's like alive
Wait, let me back it. Wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait
Where are we going?
All right, we're gonna go this way
I need another weapon
Oh shit
All right, let's go. All right. I gotta go up and then right
Is there a boat?
Boat boat boat boat boat boat boat boat boat does it work?
No, it doesn't they can't swim right? Can I swim?
Oh shit, what the fuck is happening?
Oh
What the fuck?
Okay, I gotta get out of here. I gotta get out. This is too much for my brain. This is too much for my brain
Why is that person still alive?
And can I I have to loot the houses? Yeah. Well, hold on a second
What the fuck why?
What did that guy even say in the water? He just went like
That was way scarier than if he said any actual words
That's all I heard
That was terrifying this is more finished than cyberpunk
Okay, I need to find weapons
I don't i'm not an arrow guy though
Oh, wait a minute
tomato
blessing
Simple potion to refill your powers
Oh shit. Okay health potion blessing potion
cyberpunk joke
Now the funniest thing i've seen of cyberpunk is when the guy is on the roof and he spins in 360 degrees
And there's nothing around him and he like shoots somebody down like a thousand feet below him and like police spawn behind him on the roof
Okay, I gotta loot more houses
This is this game is so crunchy, but I I mean I kind of like it. I kind of like this
I just wish it ran. I just need to
Oh my
Okay, we're in trouble. I'm cutting off all their arms
How do I take a health potion
That lady is so bloody
I'm gonna level up. Is there a block?
I don't think so
My son is watching. Can you please limit the violence?
He's trying to hit this person in the head as much as I could
Level up
Is there a bomb? Holy shit this bombs
There are bombs
knife
Where's the knife?
inventory
table knife
Okay, get rid of the broom
table knife in
How do I use that?
It's a throne item
Holy shit. Oh shit. What? Hold on
Can I eat a tomato?
Can I throw an item?
uh v
v
g
mouse scroll
Grenade. Yeah, there's grenades in medieval times. There were
q
Wait q. Oh, that's how you drink a potion. Okay. Well, that's good to know
d
f
h
j
Go to fort wire a wyver. Okay
Um, wait, let me look at the can I look at controls inputs? Okay
I'll go sprint enable item and consumable scrolling
Match camera sensitivity. Wait, no, okay jump attack block is mouse two. Okay
Mouse two is my super move bash is f
Usability is mouser like from mario 2
Okay
scroll
Sprint sneak use conso- okay. It's g and b
g and b
Do I not have it equipped?
It'd be g and b, right?
g
b
Huh? I'll figure it out
corn repair kit
Be on the controller
I love the music. It's just like a violin. Oh, come here you
There's a sword on the ground
I didn't even see it
Where's our sword?
Oh shit. Oh my god. I have a sword
corn
Oh nice
So it's pretty good
Nice. Okay, cool
I don't even know what I picked up. I'm just touching everything
More rusty broken sword
No, what do I can I throw this?
Can I sell something to somebody eventually?
Dual weld can you
No, you can't
You can do well. No, you can't
Maybe you can get a shield eventually though
Stamina potion dual weld dual
dual wield
Sorry
What do you want to say? Sorry dual wield
dual wielding
You cleave if you can cleave this skill goes up a ladder grade
Uh, I don't think you can
Holy shit, you can do that though
What are you in here?
No second breath potion that decreases your stamina, but only for a little while and some arrows and was it brass knuckles?
musket ammo
Dude, I can't all right. I can't wait. I'm having fun
And there's tomatoes in the game
All right
Is it a kitchen knife?
How do I get rid of all this stuff?
Is it it's a there's a tomato so there's plus one letter grade
Yeah, i'll take that that's not a bad indicator
But hold on. Excuse me, sir
a
Equippable tomato something you a pick up pick up a bull tomato not just one for decoration. That's really important to distinction
All right. Let's go. What do I have to go?
This way. All right
I'm gonna run for it
Man up you can throw these I gotta figure that out. You can throw tomatoes at people
All right. I need to go
Okay, we're just gonna we're just gonna parkour
I'm not parkour. Okay. Hold on
He's way too high
I feel like this is water this looks like water
Going the right way. Yeah. All right. Let's keep it going
It's very crunchy water
It's all right. It's okay. That guy is so far away. His lod is like one fps
He's not a threat at all. His ai doesn't even know i'm over here. That's just an animation
Don't worry. We're fine
Is everybody in here? I kind of want a handgun
Or use the rusty sword for the tetanus bonus
Uh, thank you kai's kitchen for the five community subs appreciate it. Can I use can I throw corn at people? I hope so
What the hell is this?
Bone like a dog bone
Let me get a nice sip of my tea. Hey, by the way, if you don't have like a tea or
Water or you know coffee or something take the time this opportunity to go gamble
All right. What there's a door
What happened? Oh, there's a day night cycle in this game
I thought there was something wrong with my game
I thought the render distance went to zero
All right, i'm going up. Can I sleep here?
Is it worse at night? Is it scarier at night?
Need another point in strength three blessing points three
What do I have to wait till I get to level? Well, I gotta get level five. Okay, I see
It's going pure strength
Are you telling me you don't want me to get the huge two-hander and be able to chop up like a hundred people in one swing?
Guns are cool bows are cool, but huge two-hander is what I want
Holy shit, this is awful. Um
I'm just gonna stay on the path this way
How do I get out over this? I gotta go on the road
There's a road from here. All right. All right, it sucks, but you know what we're just gonna run
Okay. Um, we're going this way
Yep. Okay, then bang a left at the end of the road
Right. Oh my god, just jump
Right. Am I going the right way then bang a left
Oh right the chest
Oh fuck. Oh lord
Cool. Okay. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. We're going to the town
All right, just fuck everybody. I'm running
All right. Do you let this guy in?
The guy running towards the gate with the sword going
Help me
Help they're after me open the gate
Open the gate
You open the gate, right?
Or am I the guy that does that and then just gets absolutely slaughtered by like 50 people and they tear me apart
Oh my god
What?
What the fuck is happening over here?
Run away. Oh my jesus christ
Oh my god, they're like a pack of ants. I found an anthill. Holy shit. They're still running after me
Where am I supposed to go?
Where am I supposed to go? They're all after me
It's chat
Holy fucking shit, dude. Oh my god, that was actually terrifying
That was insane
So what that town got overrun by the ants
That was ridiculous. I can't believe that
I'm just gonna farm exp
How do you sleep? They're not still out here, right?
They're not just waiting for me like a disney ride
Can I not sleep?
uh journal
Go to fort wyvern and look for survivors. Um, how am I supposed to do that?
is
What oh I have to go back
I gotta go back and talk to the priest
Okay, i'm going for it
run
Not if they're on every single road
Oh, man
All right. Can the priest help me?
Oh Jesus go this way
All right in in in here in here get off that map
I gotta find a way in
I got it. Okay. I swear to god if this place is full of people i'm gonna be so mad
Hold on. Oh, yeah, I gotta get it. What the fuck just happened
Oh, okay
Ow
All right. Hey, dude, let me in you don't have any idea what happened out there. Listen
um
How much food do you have?
They're all possessed. There are thousands outside the fort walls
So everyone has turned
I was afraid of this
But while you were gone, I saw a few survivors enter the town, but it looked like they were in trouble
Well, they're dead
They were being chased by the possessed they appeared to be held up in the tower. I'm sure they could use some help
Right. Well, I just want to let you know
That was me you were looking out the window. You saw me running away. I fucked up in the tower
You were looking at me man
Okay, we have to go to the tower
What what is he saying?
Okay, so there are survivors up in there
Gotta go in the tower and help them
All right. Are they in here?
What the fuck man? Why?
Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up on the book. Okay
I need to throw a grenade over there. How do I throw grenades?
How do I throw a grenade inputs?
usability mouse one
q and x g and b e and a
v
z z z z z
z bread
Oh, wait tomato
I just drank it to my dick. Why I just drank a tomato
what
Bread, I just drank bread. Okay. I'm I just drank the bread. This is weird
z okay, what about
weapon
open stats journal player list
menu
Yeah, it's supposed to be g but it's not hold on
Okay, how about
Use consumable q and x use item g and b g
Okay g b
mouse scroll g
x oh where we go
Okay
So i'm gonna i'm gonna throw a grenade in that crowd. Where are they? Where are they? Where are they? Where are they?
I didn't hit a single person
eat it
Oh jesus christ, what do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? They can't get me. They can't get me. They can't
get him off get him off get him off get off me oh my god i have to leave now i have to leave
now wait wait i'm gonna farm so much experience you have no idea oh this is just what it feels
like in warcraft when everyone's on their flying mount and they're just going they're freaking the
fuck out all around you they're just waiting for the portal to be open this probably looks so stupid
from an outside perspective warcraft reference yeah don't care got it i'm gonna kill i'm gonna
get to level four wait it's daylight does that mean anything i don't think so
they're just extra hungry all right can i crouch i can't take it i have to leave i have to get up
just hit him in the fucking head just hit their head quick eat a tomato i got it i ate one did i
i got it i this guy's dead whoa don't crash don't crash come on don't crash it's too many
body parts too many body parts i leveled up all right let's go go go go go go i'm here
open what do you mean locked oh shit how do i get in climb this i can't climb that look i'm trying
to get into get away from me okay i climbed the side wait what oh my god i could climb it
5k andy what happened how do i open this oh was it like a bots got banned so who's in here
i'm supposed to rescue people oh no he forgot to pay his view bot service it said 10k
yeah it's probably bug all right there's supposed to be survivors in here i'm just i can't leave
okay i was gonna say oh survivors i found you how did you get here is he pissing off the edge
whoa how did you manage to get up here i climbed there are quite a few possessed by the entrance
or it was until i showed up oh we know they chased us down the road we're making our way through
sonin pass from the village of grimsby so are there more survivors out there
yes we were out scavenging when we ran into a horde in the pass and ended up on the side
when you head back i'll come with you that sounds like a good idea but we barricaded the way through
sonin pass to stop the horde is there any other way to grimsby yes but the only other way would
be through the mine and far too dangerous okay i'll deal with the possessed at the bottom of
the tower first thank you we'll make our way to the chapel when it's safe it's safe travels
it's great to see a fellow survivor they chased us down the road we barely made it stay safe
you look like a fighter okay it's safe though i didn't i don't fall off the edge
oh they're talking about these dickheads over here you twitch viewbot i do look like a fighter
don't ever do an accent people are gonna scream at you they're gonna be very mad that you just
did that didn't i kill everything that was down here if you see a possessed knight thanks good
if you see a possessed run remember you give good tips i don't think i do my tips are usually pretty
bad so wait i didn't kill everything already he's still left out here oh you okay fine really
okay are the nominations still up they are the nominations the ability to nominate for the end
of the year is going to be closing over the next couple of days voting will happen probably mid
week up until obviously the 30th if you have a nomination please get it in on the discord
there is a new year's eve discussion and nominations channel i uh i would implore you to do so where do
you vote you will find a place to vote later after the nominations have been compiled and the poll
has been made okay so did they are they are they back at the church already that'd be interesting
if they were hey i found some survivors it's great to see that there is others still out there
that's jigsaw i just want to put a filter on it that's jigsaw uh yes they told me there are more
survivors in grimsby but they did mention that the past is now barricaded and the only way to
grimsby now is through the mines i see the lord had locked the mines just off the process from
coming out what do you suggest i believe he fled with everyone else but i'm sure a key to the mine
would be at his home mesra castle southeast from town on the coastal rock isle i'm sure you'll find
many useful items he left behind okay i will go to the castle many many have died make your choice
yes okay where are we going from here so we have to go oh shit that's pretty that's all the way down
here all right we're gonna go down if i just go straight from i'm just gonna go straight over
we're gonna climb over some shit he said there's useful stuff in the castle so that'd be cool
this game is this game is ridiculous all right i can actually climb the mountain
look you can go anywhere you want it's a completely open playing field ow okay tod
anywhere you can go anywhere i can't wait to see mesra castle it just works it kind of does just
work i got blessing didn't i all right blessings level four almost one more one more point with
strength okay this looks that's a level eight i'm level four and do i fight this guy oh okay
oh no no no no no no no run run run run run away run over this guy's gonna kill me
i haven't saved the game is it okay there's a level one why is there a level eight please get
out of my way please get out of my way please get out of my way please get out of my way
oh my god get out of my way please get out of my way get out get out get out get out get out i'm
dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i have one health right what's a healing potion what's a q b how do
i wrong button wrong button what do i do what's the what's the button what is the button to switch
to healing potion i don't i i don't have no idea x z is it x god damn it never drink sticks
i feel like this guy's sleep talking that's how just odd the things he's saying are all right um
we're gonna go i'm gonna do it again you have to 100 this game
from the trailer there looks to be some very very insane things that i would like to see
so yeah we're still here i'm still interested okay no level eight that's good wait nice okay
bread anything else in here this bread i want to ten dollars off the debt if i play something else
no thanks you can keep that ten dollars you can keep it on the debt a life i thought that was a
mace i was like holy shit give me it can't open that no you're gonna have to add probably like
20 zeros oh god damn it don't run after me hold on let me just clear this that move is really good
take the heads off that's easy to do this i got level eight no okay all right whoops
it's z okay it's z all right this dude like this dude has some secret shit in here i can find
this dude he's stuck in the chair bring us the ratatouille and wipe away the debt i'm never
loading that game again okay this is a shitload of people in this room right i mean come on
ed okay there's only level ones and level eights i think that's kind of odd don't you think
but those are bugs all over the screen um okay no go up these are peaceful villagers
villager villager there we go that's better
show your feet all right okay here we go there they are they're right in front of the camera i'm
holding them up can you i'm rubbing them can you hear that did you see i'm i'm i'm gonna hold on
let me put them up i'm just gonna put them like on the desk like flat on the desk it's kind of
hard to do okay um i can do this is kind of hard to do but i can do this with my feet this is cool
do you guys think this is cool it's kind of hard to do that juggles lead pipe oh all right where
are these so-called secrets that this guy has juggles got unbanned now he's permanently banned
from twitch i the one i last i heard he was like doing a thing where he was shaking his stomach and
he kept on saying like kind of really really like strange shit to people he's talking he's
shaking his stuff again like talking about like just filling his body with gatorade and like i
wish that were me or something where's this secret item where is this thing what this is not even a
castle what the fuck is wrong with me i'm in the wrong house right song all right we got all we
got garbage links oh dude garbage links in chat right now i mean i hear this fucking garbage links
in chat i ain't clicking them all right there it is there's the i avoid this all right i'm
gonna go around i don't want to fight that guy i can i'm level four where's that boogeyman
watch out for the boogeyman this is bad this is not smart this is really this is not smart
right this is not smart oh i hear him get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up
holy shit this guy scared the shit out of me i don't know why this guy's terrifying
why does that scare me so much that actually puts me in like a panic what is that why is it
got here a dude looks like the flying dutchman i get up i don't think i can even climb up this
oh here we go so work what does that sound
oh my chest my whole body hurts my whole body hurts oh my god what the oh my god dude why why
that was i there was no reason why that would ever happen god damn act that hurt my entire body
i climb dude please oh it's the stairs don't come through the walls i hate this
oh grenade nice horn all right we're almost there you should have the cam mr streamer hey
i decide when the cam goes on i decide it's my stream i tell you when i put the camera on
man three is psvr only i still haven't gotten over it i'm still very mad and the last time
you heard me talk about this i have been seething for the last six weeks it's not it's in my brain
every day this is the manner right here all right let's go can i climb this guys level eight little
two no okay hold on i want a different weapon watch out watch out watch out no shit okay hold
on um what did i what's the point of this where am i i can't get up there i need to parkour all
right i'm on the roof now i need to i need to get in the house oh that house all right i'm gonna
go for it let's see if i can make it the game lagged and i fell off the game is all right
every every 15 feet you move the game has to load at 15 feet down the road one two three
we're fine we're fine we're fine we're fine we're fine where's my potions there we go all right i
said he had goodies in here i hear a lot of people but what kind of goodies does this guy have
the three crones the three all-seeing crones the mori who had been with him for a previous
eternity guarding the river of sticks in the underworld and passed through the worlds of the
living and the dead would often come to visit his spirit oh gwen had no soul so it could not
go anywhere and there was no one to ferry it but he had a sort of spirit they could talk to that
conveyed his disembodied state i feel like i'm reading i'm doing a play and the people in the
audience just fucking hate my guts i think it sucks tons of moaning just groaning booing it's
hard to read the more i took pity on him and visited him regularly it is important to know
that the more i are neither good nor evil they're impartial typical of all the clones they enjoy
stirring the cauldron yeah intermission ended 30 minutes ago i know that some of you are trickling
it in you some of you are shuffling in uh half of you though that's really annoying sorry the line
was so long but when the show starts get the fuck back in here can i take it melt down on oh there
we go tower room key the book of gwen part one all hail gwen the merciful and great keeper of
our souls gwen i'm not even gonna read it whatever somebody caught on the stage i've got i've got my
like wooden pretend sword to defend myself from the angry people in the theater okay so i got the
key to the tower which uh stop stop it leave me alone all right what's these two-handed mastery
or one-handed mastery i mean it's two-handed it's two-handed five points in two-handed just
fill it up wait should i've done that i don't even have a two-hander uh can i hold this with
two hands find the alchemist slab okay what just happened i pressed l oh all right i gotta i gotta
go to the tower i don't have a two-hander i'll find one and when i do i'll be ready l oh all right i
gotta go to the tower grab these potions why not headroom okay hold on you don't have a
two-handed sword in here like a broadsword or something why come on i don't have bullets
i'm just getting in press t doesn't t doesn't do anything all right tower time oh shit
once i find a two-hander this is game over for everybody she's fast yeah all right so i have
table knife two of them it sounds like there's so many people out here all right i just i'm gonna
run i'm running i'm gonna get out i'm gonna run i don't even know how to get out of here
two-hander fuck grenade oh two-hander is that a two-hander this is a two-hander it's a two-hander
it's a two-handed rake where is it two-handed rake yes miriam a horde is making their way down
the road we have to whatever this is a note wait grab my rifle as well i'm going to my
laboratory to get ammo keep the door locked take the other woman including that sick girl into
the study room where's the study room it's under me door is locked laboratory hatch
shit it's upstairs all right i'll go get it it's a rifle i want it study room this is a study wait
why is it pointing down rifles are two-handed he has the tower key yeah no that's the key to the
tower if it's did i go all the way up maybe i didn't go all the way up i have the key i have
the key to the tower i don't have the key to the study fair kid it's probably up here
another two-handed rake no thanks key constance mine key what's this i've been treating several
people here for some sort of lunacy or madness the last month has taken a very dark turn okay
will need to drink the medicine or they will succumb to this dire consequence of eating this
or being infected or something oh okay the guard turned into a brute force i wish i didn't have
travel here this constant outbreak of violence and fighting i heard word of another town that
they hung three people for theft of fortnight ago i've been making it at night i've been having a
lot i've been making potions all right so where's this rifle i want the rifle but is it no i don't
know would it be in is it in the lab i don't have a key to the lab though well hold on let me see
go to the castle yeah get to get the study room key from the laboratory
all right let's go out the door to the laboratory time to face the music oh yes bro i can farm here
all day can i throw a grenade i no grenade i don't need it drink get out of there get out of there
i'm all right i'm gonna be fine this is a good farm the person is so why are they doing so much
damage what level was that person they level two okay that's why this is tomato juice ours
okay i'm good all right i can all right out out out uh where's the i don't know i don't know i
don't know what to do i don't know where to go is it like underneath i have what's the lab key i
have a lab key i don't know what to do with the lab how do i get down there dude back up to 10k
oh shit the molotov cocktail yeah i gotta follow the marker but the marker is like
down there wait what where is this this doesn't feel correct this is the mine oh shit okay hold on
this is gonna hurt oh fuck the rake is gonna break it will soon but i'll be okay funny scream
thank you for that funny scream oh there it is okay cool lab door is locked laboratory
what the door switch is being repaired you in the top floor workshop use the floor hatch entrance
for now
shit but what no are you serious i look i have so much bullshit where are my keys use a repair kit
um okay i don't know how oh did it work oh i guess it worked okay uh where are my keys
okay so now what the hell am i supposed to do do i have the lab door key right oh come on
dude i'm in the water i'm in the water get out of the water please get out of the water please
get out get out get out i hate that guy i can't see is that water fuck why did i have to come all
the way down here no water get to the beach quick get to the beach quick guys go go go go go go go
i'm not i'm not looking away from me i'm not in the water anymore get away from me please
yeah
he speaks backwards okay now i gotta go where the hell it's too dark i can't see anything
all right bang left just running around with a rake i don't even know if i have pants on
i don't know if i have pants on all right straight okay oh no level eight level eight level eight
please get away from me get off the bridge i have to go up here please give me an oh fuck
get away from me okay all right open this dumb door
it's just morty but not high pitched
fucking morty this dude does a real morty when he's scared all right hold on
i leveled up what can i do can i put it into this one-handed or this is as far as it can go
endurance dark arts i don't think i can allows instantaneous travel the previous visited zones
i can't even click it i need a certain consumable agility enables the ability to vault over short
objects yeah i mean you got we kind of have to spread out a little i could do this one too
you know they'll do endurance let's do endurance i have one point let's see uh blessings can
regenerate in combat or decrease movement based stamina costs blessings can regenerate in combat
i think yeah all right cool we're looking all right all right now i gotta just go in this guy's
stupid secret lab bullshit thing what i thought that was a repair kit are you serious do i actually
have to go right now where the hell is this study isn't there like a door somewhere for the
marker yeah i don't see a marker you guys see a marker i don't see one thank god it's almost
light out is it down uh it might be done thank you for the funny stream it's absolutely my
pleasure i'm still getting sick let me i'll fix that that was better still getting over that uh
cold i had so where's this marker how do you how do you make that noise well it's from
uh lying in the bathtub for like an hour and just sitting there practicing it over and over again
and i already get this anything's one of his hobbies yes it is i love i love taking baths like
one of my favorite things in the world where's this goddamn marker that's a tower room up there
isn't it i would classify this as a tower get the fuck out of my camera there it is okay what's in
here holy shit all right what is it power room there's nothing in here power why'd you just say
that power unlimited power total corruption total power why are you saying that why'd you do that
tell me explain to me why you did that i want to know now why would you do something like that
now why would you do something like that there's nothing here
that was stupid can i track the quest somehow journal investigate the laboratory complete
get the study room key from the laboratory what investigate the laboratory get the study room key
from the laboratory i where's the laboratory go back to the room look up what do you mean look
up what is it look up you missed a legendary chest it's in here i gotta go back in this house
hold on bottom floor of the house there's a hatch okay yeah but i couldn't open it but it is that
look just let me in the damn house please um look all of you get away this is a level fucking seven
level seven don't like it level seven feet away from me so door is locked what do you mean door
is locked this is the study don't i have the key to the study what i have to go in the laboratory
first laboratory door is locked laboratory hatch is locked what what the fuck wait this
what wait a second hold on this is the door to the study that is locked but i i'm in it now
i can't do it i can't interact with this do i have to go back all the way down grab my rifle
horde is making their way down the road we haven't much time take the other woman including that
sick girl into the study room okay i'm going to my laboratory to get him i'll keep the door locked
so i have to switch now now i go down where the thing was well i don't have a marker anymore
oh my god what the fuck i have to switch again okay so i use it outside where the mine was right
i think this is bugged i have to switch for the i don't understand how come it's not tracking
anything you're actually pretending i i have no idea what's happening he's not pretending game
sucks oh i don't know what's going on i'm gonna go try to go to the mine i don't have a marker on
my map anymore oh my fucking god please holy shit i killed everybody all right so i have to go
back to the ledge and go where the mine was to open the door with i guess i have to switch now
yeah well how come it's not on the map he's like i remember where the fuck that is
select the quest active quests the study room and the mine key i mean but it's not showing
anything well i'm just gonna go down here am i going the right way though i don't remember
being down here the door is locked where's my marker where's my marker where's my there was
no marker there i don't want to hear it there was no marker here i don't want to hear it i don't
want to hear it there's no marker what what who is this guy level three knight
get away from me i'm gonna throw grenades at him
i can't knock him over
why is he not doing anything i take his weapon that's a huge two-headed sword can i take it
i can't take the weapon i was trying to blow him up and it's that explosion radius is so small
that's like a firecracker my god let me let me out of the room why is it too i'm at you
bastard okay don't lock the door behind me because it might be another one you're just
slapping a guy with a rake yeah well it's two-handed so okay study room key oh my god
do i have to actually go back to the fucking study oh shit how do i get up there's nothing
up there i like get the gun hold on hold on hold on a second i'm gonna get the gun just wait
i'm looking around for lore i'm just hold on looking for lore i want to build a read shit
you know i'm looking to read if there's anything around where's the gun my way everyone you guys
freaking me out is there a gun i everybody's freaking me out it's on the bed it's in the
study yeah you guys are wrong okay you guys are freaking me out why is everybody freaking me out
all right study room finally look see now i got a marker somebody come in and like extra kill this
guy oh no that's uh so wait they didn't die there they didn't die there to get they did not die
there okay whatever let's go i'll crash i'm having too much fun in this game for this to crash come
on man okay can i climb no just go the right way wait the the boogeyman's gonna get this guy right
where did you the body parts kind of fall off really easily i've noticed okay going to the study
we're gonna get the gun in the study and i'm gonna use the gun to shoot someone in the head here we
go tell us the backup game no no because i'm gonna play the backup game i'm into this i'm playing this
for a while you'll know the backup game is soon enough this week oh i'll tell you what the plan
is though if you want to know uh i have some stuff i got to take care of over the next couple of days
so there'll be no streams over the next couple of days but we'll be going
either thursday friday saturday or friday saturday sunday and the game we're gonna play when we come
back from our errands one of the things we need to do is fear 2 i'm gonna play fear 2 i've been
talking about it for a long time we're gonna play that okay into the study level eight oh that hurts
okay i forgot the rifle actually you're level seven stay back there don't move how do i can i
zoom in why did i not pick guns not too late that was level seven guys that was still good
okay now how is this automatic i don't know
okay so we got the gun we're good now what's next on the list of things to do go to mesmer castle
follow up with peter once you're equipped find the alchemist lab did i not find it
you're in it aren't i you already did it now go find peter oh shit let's go to peter all right
time to talk to peter i need health potions i need to sell too all right back to peter hey remember
to chime watch out watch out don't be an idiot okay straight up the throne and left i'm gonna
try my absolute hardest to do a peter griffin i'll try it hey hold on i'll get it hey i can
probably do it pretty well i mean it's like boston accent you know what i mean like they're in
rhode island what are you talking about lois yeah hey lois you remember the time that me and stewie
went to wait who are these people oh wait these are survivors i'm bringing it back to the church
this is just bloodborne okay peter i have the key good head to the mine's main entrance and make
your way through didn't i do that i've noticed lights coming from the mine storage on the ridge
can you check for survivors into the depths
can i sell thanks for clearing the way thank you for helping us we decided we're gonna stay here
yep you've already done so much for us and i hate to ask but we could use your help
we had dropped a fair amount of supplies we scavenged when we were chased food medicine
ammo stuff we could really use it's up the valley the bag should be the well by the well in the
center of the next group of buildings after the bridge be careful there's a mob 20 of them
if you see a possessed knight run um okay i want to i don't give a shit about your supplies i want
to do this now we go out of here okay talk in the peter voice for how long how long do i have to do
that for you want me just to do like a pretend like peter griffin let's play like is this like
2009 on youtube do we want me to do that am i gonna do it like a peter griffin plays sky room
all right i'm gonna try let's see what i can do i'm gonna try so hard i'm gonna try not to laugh
and fuck it up all right okay so we got some bad guys here oh i gotta go this way around the bad
guys hopefully there's something in the shed i can use no no no kind of reminds me when i
fought the chicken all right you look like lois i am peter my name is peter i'm killing zombies
my name is peter fucking game crashed whatever it's over
oh by the way i'm gonna make that i'm gonna make like 60 of those videos
okay where we going whoa you should bring that back uh i remember that was so that's so old
that's so long ago that's like 2010 or something 2009 2011 hold on hold on what's this
a rusty sword no thank you better do stewie griffin playing black ops 2
all right it exists already i don't have to do that if you just type into youtube like stewie
griffin plays x you're gonna get like a thousand videos i don't even have to do this they already
exist i say brian like i'm this fool thinks you can fire at me it's definitely there like i don't
have to even do it wait i didn't go up because i did okay i need to go to i think i'm going the
wrong way but stewie was awful i say brian any idea i look i've been sick you can't blame somebody
else i'm going the wrong way look everybody can do stewie griffin for the first word i say brian
it that's it nobody else that you could do that much right uh stewie is playing black ops he
all right i gotta go this way i climb this i don't why are you not allowed in the water
everybody's find that strange there has to be a reason why when the player character goes into
the water there's probably like a memory leak that happens in like a minute that they have to
try to avoid somehow to fight fight i can't swing in the water i can't fight the zombie
all right we're going the right way across the river i can't even swing my uh sword i'm sorry
rake persistent bodies it's kind of pog that's kind of a pog moment unfair okay cool let's keep
going over here the mine all right get over here i'm gonna fucking hit do i have any grenades
i have a molotov cocktail i'm gonna throw it into the water where is he what the fuck there he is
there he is there he is all right come here come here come here come here come here come here
i shoot him if i could shoot him in the head i'm gonna laugh so hard
go here dude i'm gonna kill this motherfucker all right all right come on come on over whoa
that's why that's relax i can't shoot him that was so overreact that was overreaction that was
the most extreme overreaction jesus christ don't move don't move don't move don't move don't move
this is so hard okay if i miss the shot i add 50 billion dollars to the debt
now thank god i don't have to do it thank god his armor on um i didn't miss at him right in the
head oh my god damn it man what the fuck is happening right now um you hit the door
i did not hit the fucking door
whoa okay he figured it out he figured it out he figured it out he figured it out he figured it
out it's okay just i'm just like a monkey i'm like a monkey that's like gotten out of like a cage
get away from me you little shit no don't eat those tomatoes
like in every single movie with a monkey as a main character he's eating the food
get that handbag around his mouth oh no it's me the hotel clerk he's always causing problems for me
this is actually starting to hurt me monkey please
my stream crash my stream just crashed am i live oh i am i can see okay that was weird
wait that that doesn't happen in those movies you can't add 50 billion i hit him in the head
it's just the bullets i made out of like fucking cardboard it did not hit the door i did not hit
the door i did not hit the door no i didn't i hit him right in the head it hit him directly in his
head i even shot twice and it hit him in the head he's wearing armor i can't pierce the armor with
the bullets no this doesn't count it doesn't count no it doesn't count how does it hit the
door this is so hard okay if i miss the shot i add 50 billion dollars to the debt explain how i hit
him how i miss him okay i now thank god it hit him in the head it hit him in the head
look at where the particle effects are guys look where the part look the particle effects are on
his head the part of like the art in his head look at where the crosshair is i hit him in the head
okay i need to relax this is gonna kill me um i it may i don't know they're gonna need further
examination no no no excuse me it's fine it's impossible i'm telling you right now it is
impossible for that to have happened it's not it is impossible that's impossible you understand
god damn it no experience gain yeah i have to kill something to get experience gain you don't
just get it for shooting things double or nothing what do you mean double or nothing you want me to
bet a hundred billion dollars to the debt that i can make the next shot with the rifle sure it's
this guy oh holy shit i almost just pulled the trigger when i got hit in the back all right it's
this guy right here i just have to hit him i just have to hit him it doesn't matter where
i have to damage this guy with the gun okay like i said i just have to i have to damage this guy
with the gun it's not my next shot not my next move i just have to hit him with the gun
so i'm gonna get rid of this person i'm gonna get rid of this lady
okay i just have to shoot him with the gun that's it i win okay my heart was just racing right there
oh my chat i gotta pop my chat out this is like broken no deal no deal whatever
that was a deal i made it how do you turn the night mode on on twitch where's night mode how do
you turn on dark one okay there it is okay i got it okay i just gotta go into the entrance here the
mine i'm with my two-hander shoot another night i mean maybe eventually i will but not right now
and why did i not just pick tonight with a one-hander this is so much better than using a
two-hander why would i have ever done that all right survivors in here is it cutscene is there
cutscene no way
i'm gonna be able to wait is that the that's the water guy
he's just reading like the back of a denny's menu and they reversed it
you must put me together so i may be whole again
there are towers each contain a piece of me
you must enter these towers and collect my pieces
so
stop what i didn't pay attention to the last part go forth and be wary of temptations was
the snake gonna show up and eat me an apple no i okay welcome to the mine that was pretty abrupt
yeah cut all right now the actors are going to eat lunch nice job bob you really gave it you gave
them when you talk about the two pieces and shit that was ad-libbed i can't even fucking believe
that man it's my fucking turn at the food truck bob and he's such a good actor the pieces of me
two pieces of me they didn't even write that un-fucking-believable god i wish it was as good
as he was just read my lines i can't come up with new shit on the spot i gotta read
him better than he can read his scripted lines though i don't know how much damage does this do
that was just one word i said a whole sentence but it was a single word how much is that
game runs so much better indoors okay into the mine again i hear a lot of noise
make me whole again look out yeah this is just how everybody plays dark souls when they play a
dagger build just it takes like forever to kill anything you just spam you just r1 r1 r1 r1 r1
r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 or try to dodge around and stab in the back and it always seems like a fun
thing to do at first oh no i'm gonna do a dagger build in dark souls and then you you see what i
just did on screen and you're like no no i'm going back to like just strength this is stupid
when you do eight damage to the first boss in dark souls per swing with the dagger you're like
nothing so i don't do this anymore this is fucking stupid pretty damn good in this game i actually
like the knife i wish i could do too why can i do uh dual welding knives just slash them side by
side like crazy just be a long road it's loud though it hurts okay this way we're gonna level
up i will then hey oh no next frame please all right we're almost out hold on level up
all right i got two points one handed mastery yeah probably and then rage charge oh shit
i gotta what's this what's coming up next two handed impact yeah i gotta get rage charge man
this is just one point okay well should i put should i just do uh man i'm gonna do one hand
as well whatever who cares dark arts i can't do dark arts i don't have enough the i don't have
any of that currency whatever it is dark farts i hope i hope you get in trouble in this chat i
hope you got like i hope you actually got in trouble you know one of the mods is just like
okay dude gone this is too good it's too good of a weapon you need to have it needs more cool
down on the swing what are you in here oh shit what am i gonna do what the fuck durability i have
a repair like repair what's next okay keep going i got banned from your channel for saying streamer
smells like dog shitty oh well uh okay dog shitty i kind of just feel like that i have like one of
those chunk destroyers in minecraft like i can just walk forward and just
door is locked open it minecraft gamer minus two hey what's you almost had a chance to do it you had
a really good chance to have that be a death very close sorry but then here's the best part tons of
you just the second you saw my pixel go over the railing we're like fall joke oh my god fucking
idiot and it didn't happen and now you it's you can't delete that comment it's there forever okay
i need to get in here okay that's fine i'll do it okay find the mine and make your way through
investigate the sounds is this you making that sound thank god you came along when you did
i've been trapped here for months how did you survive there was the storage house of the mine
it has food and supplies but there is almost none left now i haven't slept much because well you
know you can hear is it safe for them to all be down there i locked the door many of them were
my friends i'm sorry peter the chaplain in strathshire sent me to help you i wasn't sure
if anyone was left down there is it safe to get there mine isn't saved and the nearest exits are
caved in well i have explosives in a crate it's downstairs you get the key here it is before you
clear the north entrance could you open up the side for me first i'll make my way to peter when
it's safe i will when you hear the second explosion you'll know i've cleared both ways
it should be safe enough to get back be careful i would have been done for if you hadn't come along
thanks again i hope you find more people in grimsby just imagine you see someone coming
around the corner going like this oh shit i'm dead yeah hey i'm going to help you man where
were those where were those explosives again downstairs you said right that guy looks like
glue man give me in there what the fuck get me in there never mind hold on i have to have a uh hold
okay that's blood got the explosives microwaving popcorn that's explosives that's like a
a bag of like halloween candy what are you talking about there's a bomb in there
i'm going up to blow up the okay blow up the mine when you hear the second explosion okay
what is my way to put the bomb knife is almost broken oh shit it is well i'll repair it repair
kit uh kitchen knife we're good how much further do i have to go oh shit all right explosion one
how do i blow it up wow okay now i need explosion two is up this way get over here
explosion two coming up and then when he's gonna go back to that church
sick all right he i did it he gets to leave journey to grimsby going to oh going to grisby
this is pretty sick this is pretty sick human no is that a human no is it no it's not a human
is that a human that thing's level 10 well i'll be i'm completely safe don't worry i wasn't i mean
it was not that safe but it was still okay okay we're gonna go to grimsby there's like a major
town wait there's a whole other house over here remember you're under leveled you got to farm some
more souls um i'll be okay in a minute i forgot i even had that move why i even do that when i
can just do this we got any weapons any armor what do you got for me in here something good right
the chest shitty spawn shitty spawn right really there's nothing in here stupid it's funny even
having this why is this even here they added the 50 billion no they no they didn't take it off
take that off that's not real i had the crosser on his head and he was directly shooting him in the
head no you can take that off that's not real i hit him in the head just sparks you saw the
sparks come up uh i ain't going that way i want to pine to the mountain here i'm gonna get a
pretty good view oh this might be actually pretty cool a full hp yeah i'm good okay well this is a
hide knight shoot him i can't hurt him shoot him shoot shoot him it's doing damage yeah but
it was the other guy had a weird uh force field around him yeah i did i don't think any damage
went down when i just hit him in the head did no fucking way dude no way i shot him right in the
head should be right in the face all right just keep raking him all right fuck you dude stop
die that was that was a good andy toys are here thing or whatever toys andy's here that was
really really good that was good i like that like wait andy's the one that pretends to fall down
oh no andy quick the toys are here pretend to be asleep the family has to do that not the toys
level 12 this all right i actually probably shouldn't be here no arms you're good okay you're
dead nice metal gear survive well uh i'm not gonna go that way but how many wait do have grenades
how do i not have any grenades oh oh there it is turning to grimsby oh god
wait there's a knight grimsby survivors there's a knight here there's a knight friend
this is a knight friend no that's a possessed knight do i have any knight friends
i have to find i have to look for survivors in grimsby oh my fuck jeez give me the tomato
church go in church survivors it's you it's peter peter what are you doing here
oh this is alderman gibbons another survivor i was marooned here but i made my way up from strathsire
that's unfortunate i heard something plagued the waters before this all went down
i went and ran into ira and derek they're staying with chaplain peter after they were chased by a
horde glad to hear they're okay we got worried after not hearing from them but we're still in
need of supplies there are many supplies from miles except the storage house of course
okay i'll clear them out i can handle it i'll be back
am i gonna be able to do this i would really like a new weapon or something
i have so much dog shit two femur bones common peasant sword and a rake i kind of want to lure
somebody in here to kill this guy can anybody get in here let me vote yes no vote no oh vote no it
doesn't count don't vote yes well you guys are doing a democratic approach to this
don't vote i don't oh that probably hurts okay i gotta go this way no not gonna happen run
shit i can go this way come on no let me glitch up here you're not gonna let me do that
please thank you holy shit that's a lot of people oh man what am i gonna do
uh knife it's time for the knife
knife playthrough let's go okay wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
why do they fall down i need where's my healing potions i'm gonna be in deep shit
okay all right all right all right all right all right i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine
this there's probably a thousand people here that fucking hurts me well i like thought it
was going to hurt okay get up get up double double yeeted okay okay i thought it was like
wait a minute that's kind of moving really fast does that hurt i don't even know how i got hit
twice lost two gigantic pinwheels hold on a second so that means that'll work on all okay
that's gonna work on like the thousands of them that are down there can i just farm insane amount
of experience if i killed like 5 000 people with that windmill i'm gonna level up like eight times
okay let's go okay slow this down poll canceled poll is botted there's no poll all right let's see
if i can do this do i have to tag them first holy shit it actually does work okay hold on wait wait
wait run them around holy fuck okay watch out don't get hit by it jesus christ there's too
many people there's too many people all right i'm gonna hide up here where are they going
why are they going this way did i crowd i'm not getting any exp oh shit i have to tag them
um what was i doing what was i doing no don't kill this guy that guy's a good guy
throw a grenade i don't have any grenades i use the ball okay whatever i throw a tomato
ignore the poll i'm not voting on a poll there's no poll what poll are you referring to i'm not
clicking on a poll there's no official poll i have to make polls we don't we don't go by unofficial
polls here i didn't make one wait you won hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what do
you mean i won i won does 50 billion get added to the debt no all right yeah use this one use
this poll we're gonna use that poll that's a good poll thanks guys we're gonna use that one it's
okay we can use that no it's not official but it's okay i made i just made it official
just go the right way for the love of god dude
just go the right way just who cares go the correct way okay i'm almost
they're all covered in blood all right slow down hold on it was too bad when the pastor
wall collapsed get up there new poll no bots what are you on about okay i'm gonna try to do this
again i gotta go which way this straight ahead okay all right come on get me over that stupid
windmill oh actually we found out that you cannot attack um peter or peter of variance
that's good to know noob streamer can't even do a wall skip all right i'm gonna go this way
i'm not gonna go down the other side here we go okay now can i go in that building no just stand
just just everyone's gonna get hit by this just relax get in get in is there is a door all right
how do i get how i need to get their attention i throw something done i have a gun but there's no
bullets move out of the way move out of the way move out of the way out of the way come on are
they following me okay go now now now now's the time now's the time go go go go go go go go go go
go oh shit please don't do that get up there please get up what are you doing you fucking idiot
oh shit oh now now you decide to come over right so you don't want to come over over there now you
want to all right i'm gonna i wish i had a grenade right now so bad holy shit okay everything's fine
and just vibe it
give me the rake that's a lot of blood look at the xp bar
it's so loud i can't hear anything i love the sound it makes though it's speed con
i'm out of mana this is stupid i don't know what to do i guess i'm just gonna get to like
level eight or level nine what are the potato mode now just mash these people up through a
blood soup what if there's too much blood on the ground it's actually kind of starting to happen
it's getting in my eyes you see that look at the screen it's too much it's getting in my face
it's dripping in my eyes i can't even move open blessings man what was the music did you hear that
okay i can't just sit here and do this for 40 minutes you're almost there i can't tell who's
alive and who's dead they're the same you made this bed you have to lie in it you're here
yeah i know i'm this almost two full levels have changed from this they're all the actually the
objective this would have been so this is so ridiculous all right i think that's i think
it's good i don't feel good about this you know what i mean i feel like really bad about this
i don't i'm not like happy with what's happening okay so i killed a lot of people
i've killed a lot of people and i'm i guess i'm ready to move on and go into the tower
oh my god this is so horrible i did this prepare the weapon oh shit no i don't want to do it again
no i'm getting flashback from five seconds ago no not again no okay so what do i have to even do
in here i'm on the ground just clear it out how can this still be this many of you outside
holy shit i dug that through his pulse fine okay what's in the chest
i'm gonna drink some shit whatever just drink up psycho stream murders innocent zombies
no i'm doing i have to i don't want to i have to it's either that or i'm gonna be dead i'm
gonna be killed and i would really appreciate a weapon that's not a rake or a kitchen knife
can i just say i would love a bastard sword or a spear or a a long sword or i've been using the
rake the whole game and a kitchen knife i have a gun yeah but i don't want a gun i want a bastard
sword very specific thing that i want you have one there's a weapon outside in the barrel oh
okay is there what this person's bedroom back to the broom my inventory is huge i have so much
shit in my inventory i don't even want to kill this guy i like i want to leave him alone
all right give me the knife back to the kitchen knife where's my knife there it is all right nice
okay well i killed him anyways so what's next go back to um gorge house hoard i did it right go
back to grimby right i did it right settle down i did it they're all the possessed outside settle
down that was horrible just leave me alone i'm trying to look at my book they're all the possessed
tell the okay so i gotta tell i gotta go back in the barrel barrel outside check the barrel
okay um there's a lot of barrels in this game which one should i go for right one that's against the
house where you killed them oh hey where the fucking swords let's go let's go you see that one
let's go look at that let's go yeah i'm not going that way can you please play lego star wars this
game's too violent maybe one day i'll play it for your birthday when's your birthday hold on too
this is i gotta pay attention get the hell away from me fucking jumping stop jumping oh fucking
jumping am i gonna actually die right now you went swedish jumping oh a potato okay hello
i killed them all sticks we wouldn't dare try to kill that many they must have been hundreds
they took some creativity i'm starting to look up thank you can you help me i have to get to perth
why do you want to go to perth it's completely overrun peter told me if i i might find someone
there who can help me get off this island i've made it this far i don't think you understand
there are thousands of them and they have an overlord haven't you seen the tower here we go
some say there are demons from the underworld they have power beyond our comprehension
grouping up with more survivors is our best chance kirkwall is the nearest city and it had a
significant military presence how do i get there it's down the mountain from the north side of the
lake there are several rows that lead there just take any got it many have died okay let's go we're
going to kirkwall that's far away it was too bad skill points all right rage charge charge
forward while performing two horizontal swings all right rage charge and then hold on to more
points versus one handed attack dark arts oh shit hold on instantaneous travel to previous
zones you visited oh all right okay and then moving space some what okay increases damage
resistance right can i talk just damage assistance i just eat some like peanut butter what the fuck
is wrong with me this dude is baked that guy in there sounds like a public toilet that can talk
if a public toilet can talk drink how do i use the charge even abilities as well there it is
okay ready pretty cool all right it's time to start the journey to kirkwall let's go this way
so this apparently has a military presence this is about to get very interesting i think
i believe this is going to get interesting go to early access what is there um i think this is the
name of the zone and you're mispronouncing it it's like early access or something it's the
the country or something oh fuck don't jump off of this you fucking dope i need to get a good look
look in the wrong way we're gonna go this way we have to go over vienna lake into okay so we
gotta go that way ow ow ow ow oh oh let's go let's sort of pig anybody sort of pig
get out of here okay okay we're good just gotta get over there before the weird guy comes and gets
me he missed he even made he even made it oops oh no i missed oh man okay let's go we're going
the right way i'll just climb yeah fuck wait hold on there might be food in here
raid charge sucks how do i get in here what the fuck are you doing okay okay okay okay it's time
please don't okay did i get away i got away i think i got away oh okay i did oh this is actually
pretty beautiful wow look at this you can see this pretty cool that must be kirkwell kirk wall
okay oh it hurt it hurt i didn't even go that far i have to regen don't do anything stupid just
fly there i have to be there first before i can fly there all right there's a house right there
holy shit don't die okay i'm good level nine what am i level eight oh ow how do i regen i have to
move eel i can't i don't have any healing potions or anything i'm good this works okay now i have
to be really extra careful here i need to get on the road it's like an apple of food in this house
these guys are tough get just run run run away just run don't stop for anything i have to go
i said don't stop for anything up to here you say run
yes i know what that is i've watched television before all right i gotta go left here i saw season
one i was like all right okay all right cool got to season two and they just did the thing
where every character like is just in it just they turn them in arc i was like i don't like this
i'm just bored do the good stuff please we're in 45 episodes there's like one maybe 12 minute
segment where anything really progresses any of the story i mean i'm not a big fan of that
kind of style i know it's cool you know i get it to go uh through here this is too dangerous
i'm gonna take the road not doing that i'm not stupid chests nothing nothing is that kirkwall
it is that's kirkwall that's i i made it i made it to kirkwall it's right there
okay i'm gonna watch out for that lag missed stuff i did why do i think i can do that
did i okay i don't care oh my fucking god don't do this to me
i'll be okay just slide down gently slide easy carefully and we are safe okay
this is gonna be bastard swords at kirkwall i guarantee it they said there was in a huge
military presence here i'll be good all right kirkwall i'm ready i'm a soldier at kirkwall now
kirkwall east they have military grade rates yo when does he get to the ass eating part
um i don't know if this i don't there's none in this game all right i'm just running
okay kirkwall open the gate i'm here close that okay kirkwall open oh yes traveler we can use a
man like you oops never mind oops all berries all zombies again oops all zombies never mind
it's been overrun right oh come on what the fuck this is stupid no i didn't want to go that way
oh i am in so much trouble now climb this climb that am i safe what no not this again let me in
what wrong move wrong move wrong move wrong move wrong move excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse me wait it's empty okay can i get into kirkwall can i actually get in there
can i just run in there i think i was trying to go in this house no i'm gonna go in the house
like it's stuck it's stuck in here just sounds like a school cafeteria eel corn uh potato pain
reduction okay i got potatoes where are they there was a thousand of them are they in the house
aren't you kind of curious oh shit bad idea just stay on the roofs nobody can hurt me if i'm on the
roof in my gun i feel more comfortable with the gun i don't know i just i don't make any sense
roof to roof okay now from here i can nice all right i made it i think this is safe this dude's
a fucking squirrel it's kind of i gotta go in there that's a bomb you know what i'm gonna do
with this thing right you know what i'm gonna do with this i'm gonna kill like 200 of them why
is there so much corn i'm seeing far less weapons and items and way more corn than i should be seeing
okay let's get the let's get the grenade ready i got it i got some potatoes so i gotta go back up
here all right i'm throwing this thing in there i go uh can i go up and out yes i can okay
what do you mean door is locked give me a break never mind i don't care
get me out all right i'm going for it just be slow no hoard anywhere this is good
where the hell is everybody uh i mean i didn't kill any of these things there's blood everywhere
i didn't do this my god i don't want to roam why did everybody despawn oh they did not despawn
they're all just over here all right hold on i want to try to pull everybody over here and
just throw a grenade right in the middle and just watch the fucking fireworks where they come
come on over here i want the entire group shoot the night shoot the night all right
i show the guy behind him hold on he's moving around erratically whatever you found it all
right here we go it's just another priest in here good to see another face we can always use the
extra hands i just came from brinsbury there are a few survivors back that way perhaps we shall
send a search part to go help them out when we have the time sprouted from the ground it must
be a source of power i need to get into that tower either you're insane or you're up to
something questionable neither i believe there is something useful we could put an end to all of
this i hope you're right but between you and me but between you and the tower a ten thousand
possessed huh how many soldiers are here a couple thousand but you'll need to talk to the general
where can i find the general he's down at the garrison northeast outskirts i will go talk to
the general and maybe i could save some time for a great low rate you can save online go to the
general save some time generally even actually a good insurance company i mean are they they're
horrible okay really i shack uses them um no guys i'm not i'm not sure that shack actually uses the
general i could be corrected and that's fine if i need to be corrected i will it's like okay if
i was paid to tell you guys about like gamer goo or something it doesn't mean i eat gamer goo all
the time you know i don't like go try this new snack gamer snack i show it on camera i wave my
hands a little bit i go look at me add content and then i just never eat it ever again and i
jump down here this is gonna be a huge battle soon and i cannot wait it's all been leading up
to this moment i'm dead if i jump down there oh i'm fine calm down i love you do like the
cod run you know what i mean the gun moving back and forth all right there he is give me all of
your finest soldiers i'm ready to do battle with the demons i haven't seen you around these parts
i need help to get into that tower would you like a crown as well i'm serious first off i don't know
who you are or why um do you know there's something you look behind you first of all i don't know who
you are so why should i help you i believe there's something in that tower they could put an end to
all of this and what would that be a body part from a god oh really um you're gonna have to prove
your trust worth first what must i do well behind me there are maybe six to seven hundred of them
i'm sure you hear them there's a wagon that's turned over i need to see your prowess stand on
top of the wagon and spin around 400 times cutting off as many heads as possible oh my
fucking i'm good at that there's an ancient relic a weapon at arbor hollow what sort of weapon
let's just say it'll help i'll do whatever it takes oh and by the way there are hundreds of
those zombies in the hollow okay just avoid the front entrance and i'm sure you'll define
he he is this like a cute text from a girlfriend or is he telling me that be careful i could get
killed by hundreds of monsters i'm sure you define oh he he we're the ones fighting oh my god that's
so many people uh so we have to go down here arbor hollow be quick about it all right i thought
i just said i thought i just failed the mission we're gonna kill them all okay hold on again i
oh my god they're where are the soldiers by the way it's just you this is supposed to be like
3000 people no we're not it's me and you man it's just the two of us this is not going to work out
i gotta get a spot i have to get in a spot right there on top of that tiny little rock i think
it's gonna be good i think i can get on top of that little rock and i think it'll be fine right
oh my god oh my god
there's too many spawning oh my god they're aggroing
i did not kill anything
this is the cow level from diablo 2 that's perfect that's a perfect description
get on the rock quick oh okay i have to let me do the mission i gotta finish this
move move move move move i can't wait to do the battle you know it's gonna be such a
shit show it's gonna be so stupid it's gonna be worth the three to four hours to get there
it's gonna be the most unbearable stupid thing i've ever seen and i can't wait
okay how do i get at it okay anyone remember when they were really trying to show off days gone
this is what the fucking potato this was the cool feature in days gone remember god damn it i lost
my chat again the tower it's me and i don't have the weapon okay i need the weapon the relic arbor
hollow is where am i now okay i gotta go down down all right down here the tower the tower
okay just wrap around go to arbor hollow i can't wait to do this this is gonna be so much fun
this is the part of the stream where my computer crashes and then when it crashes
i'm just turning the stream off no human could that that doesn't nobody could do that that
doesn't make any sense but i'm glad i was able to do it teleport i can't i'm already like almost
there you can only go to safe places oh okay and arbor hollow is right here let's go straight
i need to heal though i have tomatoes and stuff i'm good remember was raising a bond
oh it closed the door what are you what are you raising the bond there it is that's not gonna
that's this weapon is terrible let's just be honest what a great selection or is locked
i'm flying the ladder why is this a fake ladder how what no it's not i just grabbed it what
what is what just happened oh shit i'm dead i'm not there's a door
oh well oh hi yeah i know go into arbor hollow yeah thanks for the rake thanks for the rake thanks
for no weapons i just have a broken dusty ass sword a one-handed sword a knife and a rake and
or i do what do i get where do you get a weapon let's go whatever it's not that far it's fine
sing the fucking rake song um swish swish swish swish break up those leaves and have a
fun when you break up the leaves swish swish swish swish break up the leaves and make a wish
go in the weapon store now break me up rake me up inside no that doesn't work
that's stupid you can't break up then save me from the dark in my blood to run
or come on now save me from the nothing life's big
i've been raking a lie there's no leaves outside that's a tuber joke it's fine though
how do i get up here i don't know oh turn around now it's dark this is not the way you're supposed
to do this mission but i have to do it as fast as possible because i can't help it i gotta get
i have to get to the 10 000 person fight am i running up a mountain i think i am i oh all right
i was uh i think i can get out it's quicksand it's quicksand it's quicksand i can't die
i think it's i might be possible to get out i can do fast travel but i'm right here oh come on
ow my legs did you hear that did i lose the legs when i teleported back it's me
uh-huh goodbye i'm just taking the goddamn road no more jumping over mountains so i have to go
out here and then on the road whatever i'm i'm going up the mountain i don't care just get the
fuck out weapon store right okay where's the weapon store king's arms it's a fake it's a fake
building i can't go in here that's not how that works but okay i'll take it
uh am i just standing on the ground what the fuck am i doing well hello hello anyone there hello
hello yeah yeah
climb it we're gonna take care of that eat eat can i eat the potato go i think i made it out of the
town i did i'm good too much okay what are you a little bit about he got through there never
mind okay almost there bang on right right there could be some supplies in here i'm gonna wait
i'm just gonna wait it out i'm gonna wait till it's daytime i ain't going anywhere i'm just gonna
hang out here for a little bit okay if you have a problem with that then you know there's millions
of other streamers right now that you could go watch you have a problem with me standing here
waiting for sunlight to go up i can aim at a thousand streamers right now they're streaming
right now that they're streaming right now you can go stream to them okay so people have a problem
with that apparently okay fine 9k andy raging on stream i need some supplies betty's i forgot
about that yeah that is that's a long time ago i should let me do some repairing drop all this
crap drop a femur bone drop the rusty broken sword there's no reason to have any of this stuff
rake is gonna be one kitchen's knife's gonna be two common peasant sword will be three
rifle will be four and just get rid of the bone okay blessing potion vial of pain reduction
okay second breath stamina pain reduction hair kit broom herb milk herb milk yeah that's kind
of gross it was herb milk all right is it almost light prepare the knife prepare the rake get the
gun how's the sword sword's fine what are you linking here all potato for a hundred thousand
off the debt that's not that's worthless anything else in here oh bullets okay bullets
i wonder when this is gonna come to ps5 okay daylight is about to be upon us
kind of wish i could pick up the two by four and use that instead all right so we're going this
way we're right here and find there's a ton of people here or did they spawn in yet can i get
him before they spawn now they're here all right so what's what's the strategy here i can't just
run on the front door i have to go up there and go in that way oh how do i get up there
around maybe around the mountain i keep going up from here that'd be pretty cool
anything so wait that's the that's the trap that i got in before this is the same place
do not go over there that's the quicksand get it fuck shit grab on to that why do you pick and
choose what ledges you're gonna jump on to it wants me to go up there all joke waiting room
somebody said that probably stop pretending to fall down the mountain i was about to just jump
off and die this left person got very angry with me uh there we go finally okay now i'm in a good
position what's that light are you exhausted from pretending no no yet i still got at least like
i got like another hour at least of pretending i know i can get up there but
that i gotta get right there how do i do that it looks like kind of good but i guess not
go in the front door i can't there's like 5000 people in the front door i have to go all the
way around don't i all the way around back uh don't kill me whopper watch that sounds
kind of good right now actually i would take a whopper right now i don't even like burger king
i would say burger king is my least favorite out of the three but you bring a whopper in here right
now you present one to me i would eat it on stream and after every bite i'd go oh my god oh my god
take a huge bite oh my god oh my god found it i can't wait for the 10 000 person fight
coming up soon eat it on stream for the debt reduced so if i take a bite of a whopper and i
do the oh my god oh my god so good try try it try it oh my god how much is that how much do i
have to reduce i would look like such a dickhead it would be so embarrassing but i might do it
because that's a kind of funny to me like i might i think that's kind of funny just being irl just
chatting without context you just have you're just eating a burger king burger and you just
can't stop talking about how much you love it and you're doing the oh my god thing putting your
hand up you know take a bite oh my god put your hand up yeah kind of i'm not covering your mouth
but covering in front of your mouth and do that after every bite until it's gone i think about
it i think about it okay i'm gonna get up there that's hilariously bad i don't know it kind of
it's making me laugh right now and like a lot of times that's all it takes so
you know we'll see we'll see uh can i go up from here do it we'll double the offer if you do it
tonight i can't no not tonight i'll do it this week i promise i promise are you ready i promise
you give me an offer and i'll say oh i might agree to it i want an offer i need to go up not down
okay finally a it's a crossbow it's still a new weapon finally it's taking two hours to get one
tonight do it tonight hey for burger king or this is for the burger king on stream no
you made that name right now to just give five community subs just do it do it i don't i have
yet i haven't seen an offer yet by the way i've not seen an offer so until i see that we're not
talking we're not we're not talking until i see a real offer two billion interesting two billion
huh hold on wait wait i don't want to die i'm so far into this hold on 1.5 billion nah what an
absolute low ball no um actually i'm i'm pissed about that not doing it tonight what a low ball
unbelievable 1.5 really i'm walking away the hell is this two billion
nah i don't get out of bed for one three i mean less than three less than three i don't get an
event for less than three oops you're not gonna do it anyways okay i haven't taken i'm gonna take a
break i haven't taken a break all night i gotta pee i'll be right back i'm gonna take a quick break
be right back okay hello i'm back here's the deal chat what do you think wait yeah we got a real
deal let's see we got a final offer hold on final offer number 95 whopper challenge do it tonight
three billion off the debt later this week is one billion what no deal no deal no deal wow getting
a lot of no deals right now no i'm just i'll do it later this week i i i don't want a whopper right
now i want something else yeah i said if you presented me with a whopper i'd eat it i didn't
say i would love to go order a fucking whopper they're gross shit they're no they're um they're
they're okay uh is that how many are they look at all these cat boys that's like cat boy number five
a revised deal i'm not doing it tonight i will i will get burger king and i will open with that
at some point this week i'm gonna do it because i think i think it's funny and i'm just i'm gonna
do it i can't wait to do that because it's gonna make a lot of people um they hate me all right
let's keep going i want to get a most at the end of this uh game some pretty sick art though what
you think i think so too hold on a second we got an animation you're gonna feel like shit for the
rest of the stream yeah i don't want to eat like burger king right now not right now i thought
about it i was really thinking about but like no i was just walked right off the edge okay that was
stupid all right i got the um i got the item let's just teleport 500 million per mick chicken
eaten tonight i don't think you want to do that deal man i can eat dozens of chicken nuggets
if i really was hungry and i really sat down i'm not kidding i could probably eat 50 in one sitting
over the course of about maybe like an hour i could probably eat 50 mick chickens no
i mean nuggets it's a lot that's too much all right so now it's time i have the the
relic of the item why are you still playing this i don't know because i want to see the huge battle
that happens in about 10 minutes no i could i could definitely without a problem 20 to 30 chicken
nuggets and i would be able to stand up and stretch my back and go oh i feel okay and i would lie down
for a little while i'd be able to do it after about 30 i'd have to clock out i would
it'd be like 35 40 hey i can listen i can definitely eat as many chicken nuggets as years
i've been alive guaranteed that's easy yeah for some of you for some of you 15 year old some of
you yeah what are you 16 20 18 30 i'm 35 that's a lot of nuggets some of you guys are like in
your early 20s i'm in my mid 30s that's a lot different i know a lot of you guys are like oh
yeah it was my 19th birthday yeah you can i can eat 19 nuggets try 35 35 is not impressive
yes it is i gauge how impressive eating food is by the burger boy uh index here like the burger
boy like tier list burger boy i think could i think burger boy one time ate like 44 or like 45
nuggets what would they come in pieces six pieces right 6 12 18 24 32 36
37 38 39 40 40 yeah like foot no 46 burger boy eight foot yeah i think burger boy's eaten
46 nuggets before in one sitting that's a lie somebody just wrote who the fuck is burger boy
right a lot of you guys are new i forgot i forget that sometime who the fuck is burger boy
all right here we go how would we get in the tower how do you feel about a full scale war
do we have enough men isn't there 10 000 possessed with my tactics and this weapon
we could do it with 500 men you're the general so you would know when does the battle start
prepare yourself and come back when you're ready then we will start okay i'm ready all you have
brums rakes and kitchen knives take 15 of my men and flank through the right side of the tunnels
the rest of the army will charge through the front gate ring the bell on this platform to start
what do you want now all right let's go it's time to do it here we go it's time for the final battle
start the battle by ringing the bell oh shit here they come i gotta get in there i gotta get in line
oh wait 15 this is like 100
what do you want to do guys why we're going through one single door this is not
the easiest way for us to fucking lose go through a single bathroom doorway get in
fight fight them
move get out of the way
i'm a traitor wait what is going on
wait wait wait wait shit
we gotta get in the front door man hold on where's my where's my break where's the break
how do i change weapons no i want come on baby charge forward get in there and fight them
they still can't get in they're all stuck in here why are they all going over here
they're trying to climb the wall
get out of the way move
it's so stupid they're so stuck i wish i had a grenade or something i don't have any grenades
i have nothing use the relic with what relic i'll get hit me i'm your captain you dummy
use the relic i don't know where the where's the relic room repair kit crossbow stamina
kitchen knife rake musket merchant crossbow for a second i thought that was one of ours
but he was naked like he had his arm he took his armor off before he died i have no idea why
but wait am i pissing him off i don't think these guys have help what i can see that guy's bones
current on potato mode this is gonna take a minute lowest resolution oh my god what just
happened they turned into just shields except for all right charges this is like lord of the
rings it is like lord of the rings i'm still only conscious one especially if you kill 15 of your
own men i can't i let's do the highest let's do ultra everything ultra it's gonna crash no it's
i got a 1080 1080 still good enough still good okay it's raining right now it's something it's
kind of hard to tell if this is red rain or not i think we're gonna get in use the new weapon i
i don't know where i don't have it where's my new weapon it's not even in my inventory on the right
why love pain blessing on the right look at the zombies on the right i don't i don't know what you
mean bro i have on the right the general has it yeah i he's nowhere to be found
oh shit here we go we're moving we're on the move we're on the move we're on the move go go go go go
break that guy the face and i'm i don't get a sword come on this way are you running back
why are they going backwards get over here into the castle let's go uh-oh just nice
just bring your kid to work day oh i don't know just give me a fucking break
dad dad daddy bastard i'm sorry i'm looking for dad
why are we all going through this way again we're all gonna get
stick with the point here excuse me excuse me i'm gonna get the bad guy yeah take it
holy shit jonathan what was that a pretty good thing the front damage i find that's my son up
there that's my son up there i don't want to die i don't think they're even attacking
they're just walking forward and and just overwhelming them and just like assimilating
them into the crowd they're not even attacking it's just overwhelming numbers walking forward
and stepping on them i've seen maybe one of the swing a sword two of them they're like an amoeba
they're like a white blood cell getting a virus okay it seems like we've taken the longest way
possible to get to this castle right why couldn't we just walk forward why are we down in this like
ravine are we down here for i kind of want to go forward and see what's up here okay we're making
our way all the way to the hand tower i kind of want to see what's up here no you're gonna break
the sequence am i no no fall damage on people's heads holy fuck i'm almost dead
everybody why are they going left why are we going left we need to go that way visual
representation of chat i kind of want to get to like the destination already
we have to go up in the tower how is it possible that i could be bored by this isn't that kind of
bizarre i was supposed to sneak in oh my god i couldn't talk i was supposed to sneak in with
15 people i understand that but why are they going away from the power i went the wrong way
i was spawning behind us i went the wrong way come on can i fix it i'm gonna fix it somebody
gave too many subs someone gave 100 community subs all right you guys zap x gave 100 community
subs holy shit dude what that what are you doing my god i can't even talk that's insane thank you
so much for the insane amount of subs that's too many subs where these guys come from all right
this way that's a sub for each soldier it's like the secret entrance i'm supposed to go through
i'm almost out of stamina okay well that's the tower oh jesus
hey who's up here those those are not mine those are not mine they're not my friends
yeah good luck they're just getting stomped i wish i had a grenade why don't i how am i so
unprepared all right there's a door up there i'm going for it now we may are we in they get in
get in here oh my fucking god there's so many i'm gonna hide i'm gonna hide them i can fight them
about to kill them right dude i have no idea what the fuck is going on here all right i gotta
go up the stairs i gotta go up i'm going upstairs what's up oh shit go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go um go i don't know where am i going hey great what was i doing
here freddy dredge escape 25 community subs welcome back freddy thanks for the subs freddy
thanks to zap for the hundred and thanks freddy for the 25 you guys you guys are trying to sub
everybody that's in the game that's a lot of money thank you oh hold on and go i thought that was the
boss holy shit let's go um up up i don't know i don't know this game may be like sick again
what broken sword oh actually kind of scared this is i think this is kind of the end
i don't have any pointy and friends where are my pointy end friends he left him all behind because
they've gone the wrong way okay you found it what did i find victory for the humans light the fire
let them see victory for the humans we did it uh what do we do hand tower ascent go to the top of
the tower oh i got a long way to go i'm not even close i missed a raid oh shit i did miss a raid
all sham no wow what's up thanks for the raid dude hope you had a good stream currently trying
to parkour up a tower sing the raid song thanks thanks bank you for the raid thank you for raid
thank you for aid thank for the raid thank you do i have to jump in uh do i have to jump and get
this yes you yes thank yes for yes why didn't i pick up that was weird holy shit oh my god i
thought i just freaked out i pressed the buttons i did it i made it i'm good why is this segment in
the game are you kidding me do i actually have to do i really have to jump from here to there
i don't right do i actually have to do that now what the fuck am i supposed to do
loot there's nothing here there's actually nothing here box i can't open it there's nothing in here
why oh and i really don't know how i'm supposed to get up there i guess i gotta climb this i must
just fell off the whole thing the wall the wall need an eagle why would i need an eagle i really
don't understand what's happening but i'm going uh how did i lose how did i lose like ascend you
gotta be kidding me dude no way no fucking way don't put that there why is that there why is
this part of the game in the game a blacksmith hammer oh dear this is so hard save what do
you mean save there's no saving save where what am i supposed to do here this is ridiculous
i'm supposed to go on the cage
i can't move i can't move i'm stuck i can't move just hold on i can't even let go
i can't let go my hands are stuck
now i just have to hang up here my arms have wedged into the steel look at all the blood
this is the way here until i starve to death come on it can't be the end here right that can't be
real just hang here till morning oh how am i supposed to get up there spam everything i'm
pressing every button p o i y t a f k quest log turn off the light teleport wait
where the hell am i i still have to climb the tower this is just a chest i can store stuff
don't give me that back i still have to get to the top of the tower how am i supposed to
rely on you do that why did they add this weird far cry segment where you just jump and parkour
up a tower seems like it shouldn't sorry i couldn't mute it didn't work it didn't work you can't grab
the cage it didn't work you can't grab the cage it didn't work it doesn't work you can't grab the
cage it doesn't work you can't grab the cage you cannot grab the cage confirmed i just confirmed
it you can't you can't you hello can i move look up the ending on youtube i don't think this game
hasn't end yet yeah i'm just a ghost i don't think i'm dead i think that's it i think this is when i
I die it's over you help me. I can't move. I'm stuck in spectator mode. Well there it goes that work
Finished the climb
I don't think even do it on when I laughed really hard at all the people stuffed into the hallway
I gave myself the cough again. I started laughing and it was just that's it. He's gonna take two weeks off
No, I'm not get some water. I have a drink right here. Nobody click. This has been fun, though
I'm glad I played it. It was just like it was just crunchy enough
I really want to get to the top of the tower though. What was the backup game?
Oh, I guess I could tell you know backup game was a the
Leaf blowing simulator idle game looks awesome. I can't wait to play it
All right, follow up with them. Hey one wait. I don't have to do this play it. I'm gonna play it
You'll see it. I will be in the house. Hey, I'm back. What's the status? I haven't made it up the tower yet
I found the body part. I've been what do you need it for?
I cannot use this weapon relics to its full power though the body part of a god
What are you gonna do with this weapon? It's none of your concern. I'm the bad guy. I'm a very I'm bad
You won't be leaving this place
Oh, it was really
What ow? Oh fuck you. You can't open doors. Yes again. He's a person
Let's go. Come on. Oh, I know what I know what to do
I'm gonna lead him into the fucking I'm gonna lead him into all the zombies
Where is he? Come on, dude. Let's go
Level 20. All right. Yeah, I got it. I'm gonna just just I'm gonna kite this guy
All the way from the badlands to stormwind and this motherfucker is gonna get destroyed
Like on the right way. Okay, we I think get out of this menu get out of the menu. You just run into something
Oh
No, he's stuck in the rocks come on get up he's pissed
Come here. I need some enemies. Where are the enemies? Where are the enemies on the map up here, right? Okay, come this way
This is not supposed to happen yet. I don't I think it wasn't
He's level 20
Look if I have to walk him into the ocean and get killed by the boogeyman guy, that's what I'm gonna do
Zombies are all dead
Are they? All right. Keep going. We'll get him
There's zombies near the tower. Yep. Okay. Oh
There's some up there too, but I think there's more over this way
Take him to the windmill
Remember where the windmill is the guys I don't remember where the windmill is
Where's the windmill get out before he gets me?
Where's the windmill? I forget where the windmill is
It's like all the way down here, isn't it? I forget I'll find it. Let's see if I can get him there
Let's have to go this direction
Come on
worst joke
That's this is not a joke. This is just a destiny. This has to happen. This is not a joke. This is this dude's destiny
Windmill it's coming up here somewhere, isn't it? It's down. It's down here
Hey, no deal. I'm not making a deal. I just want to do this to this guy
Hey a little bit more down this way lead him off a cliff
I guess I could I could just but I don't think he'll come up the mountain that the windmill is that it right there
This is actually the final boss. This is it up here, isn't it? No, holy shit. This is so far
What all right? Well, there's people here. Never mind. Well, they attack him. They do attack him. We get a cheap shot in the head
Where'd he go?
It's just oh I can't even anymore man, this is so stupid I'm just gonna lead him into the water fucking I don't care
No, I can't do it again stop. Oh my god
Is he still out here I think he might be still out here
What the fuck he's dead who killed him what
Which you guys don't understand as I hit this guy in the head like ten times with a hammer
Eventually the adrenaline is gonna wear off and you're gonna fall down. You're gonna go to one knee and you're gonna die man
I hit him right in the back of the head like six times. Oh
That was so dumb. Whatever
Hey, I hope all hey the general tried to kill me by the way
Yes after the invasion of the tower I obtained a body part of a god the general tried to kill me and attempt to take
It for himself. I'm sorry to hear this but somehow I'm not surprised
The general's behavior recently changed after he started studying the relic. I'm not sure what he's planning to do with it. I
See something I should tell you
I've been having visions. I wasn't sure if they were real until now
Visions of what ever since I was marooned here a mysterious voice figure has been appearing and talking to me
What do you think the white figure is? I think he might be some sort of God
He gave me the mark on my hand. Well that confirms the visions are true. Okay
Like I'm not I wasn't just smoking in the bathroom. You just believe me. What is the relevance of these body parts?
He said that he could only take physical form once all the body parts
It sounds like we may have yet a chance I strongly advise you continue on this journey
Do you know of any other towers? There are three possibly four. I don't know
Sorry, I'm not much of a navigator
Okay
Good luck. I will spread the word about what you are doing as well as the general's betrayal. Thank you
Hope you caught a cross past again
More and more towers. I can tell you right now. I hate doing the other four towers
the McRib tower
But I just want to look at it. I just want to see it
You didn't even do this tower
That's true. I know I just want to look at this tower gets in the snow area. It's right here
All right, I'm gonna see
Climb the bar. No, I'm not climbing anymore. I'm not climbing the tower anymore. All right, we need to go this way
Towers that way. That's the direction. I'm going. Let's go
is the windmill to
Game it. I don't even know what killed that guy either. Wait, is there a better way to go?
Mmm, I gotta get up here. Uh, yeah, just go around. I'm not gonna fuck around and die
It'd be stupid
My whole body hurts right now my the face hurts my like eyes are hurt. Oh
had a shitload of subs come in to
ash
686 868 gave 25 community sub
Thank you ash the insane sub
Rob
Thank you. It's a lot of money. Thank you. Okay, I'm gonna go this way
As I just hit myself in the face
With the hammer I hit it off the rock and a bounce back and the spike hit me in the forehead
All right. Here we are almost there. Oh
I can't believe he played this all night. Are we sure he isn't being paid? I
Don't know. I don't think you understand. I wasn't gonna give up after the first hour. Oh
Shit, look at this. Very cool
Let's go
Cool. All right, first stop a lot of fighting going on here a lot of fighting going on here
Why can I stand on this? Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. See you later. See you what?
Uh, I got some stuff going on over the next couple of days. I got to really hunker down and do some work. Uh
Derma rumble characters are about to go into full force. This is a lot of new characters really got to get some time into that
And the New Year's Eve stuff, too
By the way, you only have another couple of days to nominate something
So go take a look at the categories in the discord channel
I would do that if I were you if you want to participate and I will be back on
Thursday
Late afternoon and I'll be starting late on Thursday. So I'm we're probably around
We're gonna do we're gonna do a night stream on Thursday
I'll be like after like about 5 or 6 p.m. Pacific. We're gonna do a night stream
Sorry that the week is gonna be and next week to this like holidays. I've got a lot of stuff going on next week
I will not be around
So I'm gonna do what I can. I'm gonna try to do what I can got a lot of characters to make too
So this is actually a lot of fun. This was a really I had a great time
So hope you did too, of course as always
Let's run the credits. Well, this music is still just playing
Oh
Let's do a raid. Uh, yeah, we'll do a raid tonight. Let's see
The choice is here. Uh, we are going to raid kitboga
Always nice to catch kitboga streaming. So we're gonna raid kit go say hello funny guy really really awesome stream
You never watched I'm sure all of you have I mean, it's kitboga. Come on and I'll see you guys on Thursday
Thank you for the subs. There's a lot of subs. It was like
300 community subs tonight or something insane crazy. Thank you guys
Hope to see you again really soon. We're gonna start fear 2 on
Thursday evening you like that game. I've never played it. I going in I have no idea
No clue
More community subs. They just come in right now. They did
Haven is bad. Oh, sorry Haven is bald
Thank you. Haven is bald. I'm gonna be there too pretty soon
Not quite, but maybe a little bit later. When are you gonna play the leaf blowing game?
Probably at some point when fear is done. I'm sure fear what how long is fear 2?
12 hours something 8 to 12. I would take two streams to do it's 40 hours
No, it's like 10
This music works pretty well here here too is barely 8. Yeah, we'll do it at least one or two streams
That was a great outro there. Oh, it's a load a kitboga. Are you done with the Yakuza? Um, we'll see
We'll see that will be decided
Somehow I wonder how maybe we'll find out in a couple of weeks. Thanks for watching as always. Take care guys. See you Thursday
Wait, but are they in no, I don't know who knows you have no idea. Good night guys. Let's see you soon