That was a good game. Alright, so what do they update in Vampire Survivors? What's the update? What do they do? Let's see. Should I even look?
One stage, one relic access, two minor gameplay mechanics, two new arcana, there's one more rank.
Did they add anything? What else did they add? Oh my god, fuck, I hate that there's no noise gate.
I do want to turn this down because it's probably going to be pretty loud.
There's three new characters and two new evolutions. Really? I turned it down for you but not me.
I turned it down for you guys, thank god. Not for me. Okay, let's put that on the screen.
Looks good. So what do we got? Okay, anything new? I need to do survive 15 minutes with
Consetta. Unlocks shadow pinion. Okay, well that's, who's Consetta? I've done almost everything else.
I've played this game by shitload. Find the magic banger. Find and buy the glass
visard. Unlocks a merchant. Find and open the coffin in the gallo tower. Okay, we'll go to the tower.
There's so much shit to do. Unlock hyper mode for four normal stages. Alright, there's so much more.
Alright, let's do this at that one first. So go to the tower. Let's refund. Who do I want to play with?
Consetta. Where's Consetta? Consetta? I don't think I have Consetta unlocked. Alright, well we're
gonna go with Popia. Popia's got the cool shit. Movement speed, area, cooldown, duration, luck.
I have so much fucking money. It's insane. Oh, let's do growth. Revive. Can I? I don't need it.
Do I need to revive? Meh. I can almost do everything. Banish, skip, re-roll. I'll do another
banish. Another, yeah, another banish. I always use three banishes. Sound pretty good to me. Greed and
max health or whatever I can buy. I can't buy anything, so who cares? Alright, let's go.
We're gonna go to the tower with Popia. No, you dummy. Okay, the tower. Let's go. I've already
turned this up. Feels weird, man. What, what'd I do? That sounds good. Let's do it. Alright, I want
uh, garlic. So I'm looking for the question mark. Yeah, I'm going to the question mark,
so I gotta go up. I love lightning rod. It's like my favorite move. Feels weird, man. Put the music
up louder. Nice face, nerd. You're on Twitch. You're on Twitch, dork. Oh, Laurel. We're all dorks
here, okay? We're all geeks, nerds, and dorks. Alright, I'm gonna go up. Not me. Some of us are
dweebs. Yeah, well whatever, you know. When was the last time everybody said dork? I feel like,
I feel like that's kind of fallen off, right? Oh, shut up, you fucking dork. Yeah, whatever,
you fucking geek. I kind of feel like it's, it's got, there's a lot of, uh, I can't, yeah,
I feel like, like people don't say it anymore. I feel like if somebody called me a dork, I'd,
for a second, I would take a minute and go, hey, like shut up. When are you gonna, I like when you
play actual games and not meme shit. You think this is a meme game? This is like one of the best
games on Steam right now. Uh, should I get the tiramisu? Nah. Are we talking about the puppet
combo stuff? I never played him before. Yeah, Song of Mana again. The camera smudged? What?
Was it smudged the whole stream? It was? What the fuck? Uh, garlic again. I gotta remember
some of the combos here. I need duration. It's the shadow from the mic. Oh, well that's alright.
It's the mic shadow. That's fine. It doesn't make a difference in 160p. That's true.
Oh, the cats. Right. Should I get the cats? No, they're kind of terrible. They eat all the food
and they attack you. They're terrible. Um, hold on a minute. I need, I only have two more slots.
If I'm going to do eight the sparrow, then I need the tiramisu. I think I'm not sure what to do.
I think I'm just going to do garlic again. The cat evolution is great. I know, but
let's look for the other gun. I can't pick up anything else though. I need the other gun.
I'm going for it. I need the tiramisu and the other gun. Whoa, careful. Will this guy die?
Zoomer? Binding of Isaac? That's not right. All right. Eight of, eight the sparrow. Yeah,
I also upgraded this a lot. Looking for the other gun. This is not even remotely like Binding of
Isaac. These guys respawn. It's annoying. Song of Mana again. I think I need to buy, I gotta get
curse for that, right? All right. I'm almost there. Don't touch any of these. Ooh. All right.
So I want that because I want to evolve the garlic eventually. Turn over the question mark. I know.
I'm going, I'm heading up. That's my destination. I should get there soon.
Well, I'm going to do this first because I have the evolution for it. So I want to get that
quick. Are we there yet? Nope. Not yet. There we go. Duplicator. Lightning. All right. Just don't
mess this up. Laurel again. I need Laurel. It's a, I can't play the game without it.
Especially after about 10 to 15 minutes. I just bump into so much shit. Oh my God. Oh,
it's always Duplicator every time you see it. What's hitting me? Oh shit. Fuck you. All right.
Ah, I can't take any of these. Sorry. I need the other gun. We'll do lightning run. Sorry.
Someone says, I think I'm going to go to bed. I had a lot of fun interacting with the German 985
chat section on Twitch. German 985 was super cool in his exploration of the murder house. I wish I
could stay for a while longer, but at last the sleepy time calls to me. Once again, thank you
for the awesome live stream, German 985. Good night and sleep well. Well, that was really nice.
Hope you have a good sleep too. Ah, pentagram is sick. I'm going to leave that. In fact,
let's hang on here for just a second because I'm close to, not really. Just take it.
Nevermind. I'm not really that close. I'll get more. Damn it. I need cool down. Bad.
There we go. All right. We're good. I can't even walk over here. Let's make a line for the
question mark. There's a turkey right there. Looking for curse, the other gun, a tiramisu.
I'll take any of those. I might banish something as well to make sure I get something. Banish
the copy pastas. I mean, they're going to get banished if they're not careful.
I want what was in here. Give me a chest. Did you guys remember the last time I played this a month
or two ago and everyone was bat-chesting me because I was playing this? I'm not making that
up. I remember that, right? That was a thing, wasn't it? I was getting bat-chested. I think I
heard Otto. Was that Otto? Let me see. I'll be right back. One sec. Yeah, it was. Just give me
one second. I think he wants maybe some water. He's still kind of getting over the UTI, so
I just want to make sure that he's good to go. I'll be right back. Okay, I'm back. Hello. Sorry,
that was so long. That was a long time, but I wanted to make sure he was good to go. And you
can probably hear him crunching in the background. Yeah, he had to take his antibiotic, so that's
kind of a little ordeal. He has to take it every 12 hours and it's been almost exactly 12 hours.
Where's this train wreck of a streamer? What are you talking about? I'm taking care of my dog.
Give me a sec. Okay, it was a raid. Was there? I'm gonna say a thousand people from Menace.
Menace Alcamilla. What's going on? Welcome. Thanks for the raid. We're just kind of winding down
here. Thanks for the raid. Welcome, guys. Playing vampire survivors just for a little bit to wind
down the night. Yeah, he's good, though. But I wanted to take his antibiotic. He needed to go
outside. He needed to go pee. He needed to get a special treat for taking his antibiotic. He
gets a treat and we can go. Let's do it. Hello. Oh, it's been playing this music the whole time,
hasn't it? It's just been going. All right. Should I pick that up yet? Yeah, whatever. Yes.
Yes. Really actually not that happy about that. Two of the heart ones. Come on. I need both
headphones in so I can hear the stereo sound. All right. Song of Man is level eight. I need the
curse skull, right? I gotta go up. I'm almost there. I need the other one or tiramisu. Either
one. I don't want it. I don't think I want to take any of these. Maybe the spinach. All right. I need
the other gun. I need the curse. I could take the spinach or I could just reroll it. That sucks.
Garlic. I need a curse. Okay. Garlic. Okay. Garlic eight. All right. Good to go. I just need a chest.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday. Happy birthday to you. All right. No more farming. Just go up.
No more farming. It's not my birthday. Is it your birthday? Whose birthday is it? It's not mine. I
don't want to see this ever again. All right. This is where I'll get it. That's going to drop a chest,
right? There it is. All right. We got the garlic upgrade. There it is. Soul eater steals hearts.
Power increases when recovering HP. Let's go. All right. Now I'm going to go up. No more farming. Go.
Turma, you should be on Cameo. I did Cameo for free. I said a hundred people's names and did
birthdays or anniversaries or it's still available. I think the website's still up. You didn't say my
name though. Oh, shit. All right. Almost there. Just keep going. Come on. Give me the other one.
Well, I got max lightning now. That's good. Just need a chest. Add more names to it.
Oh, no. No. I don't feel like it. Okay. Here we go. I'm hungry. We're talking about Pizza Hut.
Five hours ago and now I want it. I just want. I want a large Pizza Hut pizza all for myself.
Here we go. This would be the lightning upgrade. Should be pretty sick. Should I get this? No,
I need the other gun. That thing's really cool. That's too bad. No, I probably shouldn't need
pizza. That's good. Evolve lightning ring. Projectile strike twice. And that's awesome.
And it's really, really good. Watch it. Here it comes. Boom. Really need the other gun. All right.
Go get the item. Ate the sparrow. Another one. Durnby, it's 1 a.m. Yeah, I'm not streaming.
I'm done after this. I'm like, I'll only be live till this is over. That doesn't drop anything.
I just needed a wind down from the puppet combo insanity. I needed a little wind down. Another
one. Shit. I guess I could just take the attract orb, but I don't know. Either that or skip.
The attract orb is just, or I could banish the armor or something. I'm going to banish armor.
I don't want it. Oh, it's right here. Okay. I'm a sir. What is that? What the hell is this? What
the hell is this? What did I just do? I don't even know what I just did. Oh, I found it. It's that.
Okay. So did I do it? Thank you. Pop up for arena. The vampire is at another coffin. There it is.
Concetta. Very cool. Got it. We'll check out what they do. Try to get the 30 minutes there.
I need to be doing way more than this. Nothing else up here. I don't want to get the bracers yet.
All right. Level eight, eighth sparrow. Maybe the other one will show up now.
Shit. Shit. I have to start taking something though. Area, it's going to be the candle.
I need spell binder and candle. They're both all right. I'll take the candle. To upgrade what I
have, I only realistically need curse and then the tiramisu duration is fine. I only need any
tiramisu and curse so I can take spell binder or cool down. I'm skipping. Those are the good shit.
I keep missing it. Spell binder is good. I know what it is. It really is. All right. That's good.
Come on. That's huge. Look at the area now. Look at the garlic area. That's just stupid. How big
that is. Where's the song of mana? How come the song of mana is not shooting anymore?
What's going on? Song of mana isn't firing. The mirror broke it. Wait. Why is it? Oh, there we go.
Finally. Okay. Why is it not shooting? What happened? The game looks fun. The game's amazing.
I think it's bugged. Hold on a second. What's, is something wrong? What's the matter? What's the
matter? Where are you? Hello, Agile. I think he wants something again. Do you need something
again? What can I do for you? Okay. Well, watch out. I don't. Move over there for a second.
Watch out. What do you want? Yeah. I, I, I guess there's something he wants. Do you want me to help
you? Yes. Okay. Let's go. Agile. You want me to show him? Um, I can't really. Let's see if I can
show. Agile. Can you see? All right. Agile. They want to see you. Come over here. Over there.
Auto cameo. Hold on. Let me see if I can. It's too dark in here. Hold on. I'll show him. Let me
turn the light on. Can you hear him? Can you hear his feet on my, uh, thing here? Okay. Can you see
him? I just turned the light on. Agile. What's that over there? Go, come over here. My hair looks
fucking crazy. Put this down. Hey, look. Agile. Agile, look. Agile. Agile. Look over there. Look
over there. What's that? You want to go? Okay. Let's go. Okay. Let's go. For real. No, he's not
wearing pants. All right. Give him a rest. All right. What are you looking for? What do you need?
All right. Give me one second. I'll be right back. Come on, you. Somebody said this song is driving
me insane. Why? It's not that good. Why? Okay. I'm going to have one earphone in because I don't
know if he's, uh, he might need, um, me to follow him again. I think he's just bored. I'm honest.
I think he's just bored. Okay. I'll finish this. This won't take that long. Another 12 minutes or
so. Yeah. What happened to the song of mana? Is it actually, is it happening? And I just don't see
it. I'm very confused. Is the animation bugged? Go back into the mirror. Hold on. I will in a
sec. Yeah. So what's the problem? I can hear it. I think it's happening. Um, I can't leave. Oh,
oh shit. That's not good. What if I just sit here? What if I just sit here? I can just win.
I don't have to do anything. Just sit here and win. This is a free win. Okay. All right.
Is it, oh, there we go. I don't know. I think, I think the animation is bugged. I think it's
actually still happening, but we just can't see it. That's my theory. Good. I can, uh, oh,
I need the tiramisu and I need the curse. There it is. Okay. So now we'll, if I evolve it,
maybe it'll fix it. All right. I need tiramisu. Hopefully it fixes it. Oh, I turned off the damage
numbers. Yeah. Oh my God. Die. How much health do you have? Holy shit. That was ridiculous.
Okay. Do I have enough? Yeah, I do. Let's do it. All right. Please fix it.
Might slow enemies. Does it fix? Um, I, yeah, I did. All right. It's good. It fixed. All right.
Thank God. That would have been bad. Yeah. It comes up from the middle. All right. Now
we're looking for a tiramisu and that's it. And that should get me pretty much what I want.
Just survive. We're at a Pizza Hut Bistro. What the hell is Pizza Hut Bistro? Let me go to six.
All right. Be careful. I don't want to die. The spammer is one. I don't know what happened.
Tiramisu. Oh, hell yeah. This is a guaranteed win. I'll open up another slot too. And there it is.
All right. I got leveled up. Yep. Let's open that chest up and let's see the double,
the double revolver upgrade. It's actually pretty ridiculous. I think it's just a huge circle. Union
of Ferrara de la Tefilo and Eight of the Sparrow. Check this out. I need duration. Oh well. Okay.
Now I can go down. I can collect all this shit down here and I can, can I, what should I get?
What's the, what's the candle upgrade for the clover? Which one? Cross is, uh, one of them,
right? I actually don't really want to upgrade the skull. Axe and cross. Which one's better for this
build? Probably the cross, right? Oh no. Axe is better because Axe is the spin. Yeah. I'll get the
Axe if it shows up and it's okay. You know, I got a craving for bugles too. I just want a big bag of
bugles. I'm going to eat the whole bag. Tons of area. Yeah. So much area effect. I could probably
just stand still to be honest. Yeah, I can. I'm going to stand still for one minute. I'm going to
collect and I'm going to get all the items. Try the spicy fried chicken bugles. I don't know why
those sound terrible, but I feel like I probably would like them. Those sound gross, but good at
the same time. I can't really, I gotta move. All right. Come on. Stop. I'll take it. Ooh,
that's a tiramisu. That means I get to revive if I die two times. There's so much food left over
from the tierless stream. Uh, I'm not going to eat Mike and Ike's snowcaps and butterbread for
dinner. That's not what I'm going to eat. Well, it's over. Uh, I'm probably going to have to just do
santa water or whip. Whip is probably better for here. How much is left? Uh, the two diet sodas
are still in the fridge. I refuse to drink them. Upgrade the whip. I can no longer upgrade anything.
I'll take the water. Why? It's just area. Um, what were we just saying? Yeah. Okay. I've opened up
the fridge and gone. Okay. Wait, there's a soda in here. I drank all the other ones besides the diet
Mountain Dew and the diet Coke. Every, all the other ones are gone, but man, I just think of
drinking the diet soda and I go, that's, that's grossing me out. I do not want it.
And I get kind of annoyed that it's in there. I get sad and irritated that it's in the fridge
because I can't drink it. I don't know what to do with it. Diet soda sucks. It really does.
It's just awful. I know some people have that specific palette that really loves diet soda.
I'm not, I am not one of the metal. Pour it in your engine. I'm not going to do that.
That's a very bad idea. Um, I'm going to have to upgrade the skull-o-matic.
This is going to be a disaster. Five minutes. Okay. I'm just not going to level up for five
minutes. Regular soda is too sugary. You know, this is, you can't really do this with soda,
but I will buy juice from the grocery store. And instead of drinking it just straight up,
I dilute most of the juices that I drink besides orange juice, which I feel like orange juice and
apple juice. You can't do this with, but all the junk, the cranberry juice cocktail that tastes
like you're drinking a syrup. Um, I dilute it by 50% lemonade store lemonade, lemonade you buy in
the store. I dilute by about 40 to 60%. So if I buy a, I don't know what two liter of lemonade,
that'll last for fucking two weeks at least. It lasts a very long time. I dilute a lot of my drinks.
I guess I could go pick up those items. Yeah. I'll just do it. What is that? Um, what is that?
What's going on? That's kind of weird. I don't know what that is. I'm afraid to go over there.
I'll even do that with Powerade or Gatorade too. If I get a large Powerade from something like
McDonald's or something, I always drink half of it and then put water in it, drink half of it,
put water in it, drink half of it, put water in it until it's, Oh, Oh, Oh my God. I'm dead.
I got to, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Just relax. It's supposed to be a
wind down. I'm fine. Yeah. It gets to a point where it turns into like homeopathy. I just
diluted so much. Don't die. Please. I don't have enough dip. I'm fucking dead. Oh my God. What
happened? No, I'm fine. I got revived. Just run. What is going on down here with this fucking weird
cold shit? Guys, I'm going to die. I'm going to lose right now. I've never seen this before.
I'm dead. I lost games over. I don't know what's happening. I can't even do anything. I couldn't
move. You picked garlic. What just happened right there? What is it? What's going on? I
have my screen. Like my CRTV fucking is broken. My CRT TV is broken. What is that? What the fuck
is going on down here? What is this? What is this? I was half the screen. I can't go over there.
What the fuck was that? What the, who gives a shit? What were we even just talking about? I'm pissed.
What were we just talking about? Cause I'm never bringing it up ever again. I dilute all my drinks
like a fucking weirdo. All right. Good to know. Okay. I go up to this. I go to the sink and I
fill it with water and I make the Powerade last an extra, an extra six hours. Dude,
you're a fucking weirdo. Stop. Why can I not do this? Can I buy it? Oh, all right. What the fuck?
I'm so pissed. Oh, I want to see what that does. Gains 1% area every level. I'm, I'm curious what
it does. So I want area. I can't believe I just died. I wasn't killing anything fast enough.
I'm fucking mad right now. All right. Let's check it out. Moon glow. What's moon glow? Should I try
it? All right. What's this new weapon? Whoa. That's kind of, does it go in the area that you aim in?
Oh, that's kind of weird. That's pretty weird. Wind down. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm up.
Said I was only going to do one round. You're right. What is, look at all this. Um, there's
items everywhere. He's cranky. I was, I was shocked that I lost. I was doing so well. And then I was
talking about diluting my Powerades. I feel like the next thing I was going to say was, oh, I also
reuse my band-aids too, because they're fine. I take them off the cut and I put them in a box.
And then when I have another cut, I put like, what am I talking about? What the hell am I talking
about? He's frugal, frugal. This character is pretty cool. No, no. Why would you don't do that
ever? Why would you ever do something like that? Talk to the guy in the middle. Oh, I thought that
was an enemy. Golden egg. Summons the merchant in all stages for 10,000 bucks. Um, that's okay. So
I can buy stuff. It's another money sink. Well, that makes sense considering if you have more
than a few hundred hours in this game, you can pretty much buy every single upgrade in the power
up list. So I'm imagining this is the way to make it so people have to drop 20 grand. That's fine.
All right. That's fine. Yeah. Yeah. I'll say what only I was only going to one more than a few
hundred was a few grand. It was like five, 10 grand. All right. What was today? Well, let's,
let's talk about what we're doing this week. Uh, I have access to the multi versus game,
so I want to play that. Uh, let's get a schedule here. All right. Here you go. Here's, here's,
here's a schedule for you. Wednesday. We're going to do multi versus and, um, probably the house
flipper at DLC. And then this weekend, probably Friday and Saturday or Saturday, Sunday, we'll do
something else, but we'll do Wednesday. We're going to do multi versus and, you know, fucking, uh,
fucking heads DLC. Sounds good. You should play Soma. When's the Elden Ring PVP thing? You know,
it's, I gotta talk to Ludwig because I, when we did that last time, it was just, it felt like so
difficult to actually get that to work. Um, and then it kind of fell out, fell out and fell out
and fell out. So I don't know if we're going to do it. I'll, I'll ping Ludwig and say, uh, maybe
we'll do something else. Go get a Snickers. You're not you when you're hungry. I'm, I'm fine. I'm
having a good time. I've been having a good time this whole time. You should try people's playground.
I'll check it out. When are you going to do the green screen stream? I will announce the date for
the green screen stream when, uh, we get closer to it, but over the next night or two, you will
see a green screen discussion for you to please go to that channel, talk about what you want me to do
actions you want to see. Cause this is the last time I'm ever going in front of the green screen
ever. This is it. This is the third and final four to six hour green screen
stream. And then after that, they will be a green screen movie night. I know the whole copyright
thing. I don't give a shit anymore, if I'm honest. Um, I feel like I've had that bottled for two and
a half years or so, two years, and I'm just going to do it. So we're going to have some rules in
place to make it so it's not, if you do it, if you're going to, this is all stuff for like a
couple of weeks from now, but there's going to be rules for copyright. There's going to be rules for
length of the videos and we'll, we'll get there, but let's just, let me get in front of the screen
first. Why is this going to be the last one? It just is. This is the last green screen stream.
I feel like it kind of has to be. Can I find the stream schedule anywhere? Um, I don't really have
one. Uh, if you, if you want to know my schedule, well, this is not even accurate either. Exclamation
point sus, nothing to do with Among Us. I, that was my thing before Among Us came out seven years
ago. Okay. Uh, exclamation point sus. It'll tell you the general idea of when the next stream will
be usually a date. Sometimes I do it another day, but sometimes I do it early. Whatever.
Whatever. It's okay. It's okay. I might do a stream earlier than sus or later than sus,
but that's a general idea. And I usually stream about two or three times a week, at least once.
He's never been earlier in his whole life. Bullshit, bullshit, bullshit, bullshit. I was early,
literally two days ago, three days ago. That stream was not supposed to happen on that day.
It was supposed to be a day later. It was literally three days ago. Dermot, when you retire,
can I have your life force? Um, why do you think it should just be you? No, I want you to fucking,
I want, I want you to fucking sprinkle my fucking ashes. I want you to fucking sprinkle my ashes
in a place where I want to grow into a big fucking tree with a lot of shade. And I want
people to be able to come in and enjoy the shade as a, I want to be a big oak tree.
Retirement doesn't, well, that is retirement does not mean you're going to die. Yeah. Retirement
means you're going to get cremated. I probably shouldn't retire then. Turn them into an urn tree.
All right. I'll see you later. I'll see you on Wednesday. Thanks for watching as always.
We'll do multiverses and the pets DLC on Wednesday. See you in a day or two and then we'll see you
this weekend as well. Can I keep some of your ashes for jewelry? No, you're, this is what's
going to happen to me. I'm going to, my urn is going to be filled with fertilizer and like fucking
vitamins for an oak tree. You're going to put an oak tree seed in the urn and you're going to bury
the urn. That's what happens to me. Yeah. I want vitamins. I want oak tree vitamins. I want you
to sprinkle in a little bit of stuff that I like, you know, maybe some green tea powder,
stuff that I like too. A tree will be dead in a week. I want some orange juice. If the
thing's going to sprout up and just be dead. Oh God, you should be an apple tree. No, I don't
want people to eat me. That's kind of weird to me. I just want to be a huge towering oak tree.
And the only thing you could ever do is if somebody ever came up with, oh, I can,
we can hear, we can hear the oak tree, some sound of phone or whatever. I just,
all I want is to be able to hear like, that's all I want you to be able to do. Nothing else.
I want you to be able to hear that. It's going to be a short tree. No, it's going to be the
biggest oak tree in the forest and the whole forest. Yeah. You're going to put your ear up
to the bark and you're just going to hear like Nutella. Yeah. You put your ear up and you just
hear Nutella. What do you mean ow? Stop that. I didn't do, I, I look at it, but that's not even
that loud. They're going to chop you down for a housing development. No, they will not. I will
stop them. They will get to my tree and the, it's going to darken and a storm is going to
start rolling in and then lightning strikes, strikes, strike all around the tree, all around
me. And they're going to go, we got to get out of here. Oh my God, this is crazy. A storm.
And then right when they leave, the sun is going to start shining and a sun shower is going to
happen. And every time they come over there, every time they try to take my tree down with
a bulldozer, the storm rolls in again. Lightning, lightning, lightning, lightning, lightning,
lightning, lightning, lightning, lightning. They'll never take me down. This sounds like a child made
this story up. Oh, let's just get rid of our imaginations. Okay. Bye. I'll see you Wednesday.
Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. Call your mother. You know, good night. Goodbye.
Take care of yourselves. Call your mother. See you Wednesday. Goodbye.