Oh, shit. There we go. Hi. What's happening? How are the cheese toasties? They were
absolutely delicious. Before we get started today, with uh, you know, Drew Crew.
That's not even a phrase I coined. I saw that in chat yesterday. I was like, that's pretty good.
Drew Crew. I like it. And to solve some mysteries. I've been told this one's actually good. Now,
I don't know where that stands on the Nancy Drew tier list. Oh, fuck. I just gave it away. Well,
you can see, you can see the title. What do you, what else would be Drew Crew? Oh yeah. We're
doing Drew Crew. What else could that be? We, are we playing uh, Price is Right? What else could it
be? Uh, this apparently is a good one. I'm going to hold all judgment until we play it, you know.
50% of the stream's income should go to that guy. 50%. That's, that's not gonna happen. Anyways,
one thing before we go. Not go. I mean, like, go as in like step on the gas, not hit the brakes.
I have just opened a channel in the Discord. Two channels, actually. One of them doesn't work yet.
They are at the New Year's Eve, worst streams, worst of the year awards. We're gonna do that
again this year. The categories are up. If you want to see what you can possibly nominate,
the list of what they are are there. That channel is open for discussion. There's a separate,
just submit a nomination, which the rules aren't there yet. Uh, I kind of want to give like a day
or so or like just for people to discuss and collect some of the data. There's a category
on there that's not really a category, but it's something that I want to do. Um, if it's possible,
I would like for whoever wants to embarrass me, go for it. Find all the times or specific times
where I have told a lie. Because I'd like to see, I'd like to, you have to look in the mirror
sometimes. I want a full compilation of every time I've ever lied on this stream.
Just play a 15 straight minute video of every clip every time I've said something that was,
wasn't true. The video is going to be too long. Well, we can condense it. I'd like to try. 15
minutes. Yeah, you can shrink that down. You can shrink 150 hours down to 15 minutes. You just need
like two words, three, one sentence. You know, like I will play ace attorney. That's not even
two seconds. You think I've lied more than 150 times on this string. I don't think so.
He's probably lying right now. I said Drew crew first. Don't let this man's greed fool you.
Speaking of Drew crew. Yeah. Yes. We're, we're playing Nancy Drew in the sea of darkness.
I, this is what people want. It's just, this is what they want me to do. I, I was all right
with maybe just doing one, but I did buy like seven. This probably isn't even a Nancy Drew
stream. Well, what do you think this is? A screenshot? Here we go. Get ready for Nancy
Drew, a sea of darkness. I'm going amateur. Uh, can this be changed on the fly? Because the last
time I got really stuck, I just, I, it doesn't matter. I'll just cheat more challenging. No
hints. Basic task list. Yeah. I'll just, it doesn't matter. I'll just look up the answer if I can't
get it. Uh, why are we all cheering? What, what is what happened? What just happened? Everyone was
like, yeah, here it comes. Oh, it's getting close. Uh, I got Ford. I got you contacting him through
a friend of mine. I think you did some good sleuthing work with her in Scotland. Not too
long ago. First some background. Yours truly. You could officially call me a locator of fine goods
per se. Can either condense this down. This is too much. This is too huge of a letter. Nobody can
write this small and this legible. You guys ever tried to write a letter and not on lined paper,
by the way? Yeah. Right. Yeah. You can write like that. I actually do though. You cannot
write that perfect on paper. That's not lined paper. No way. No one writes letters anymore.
Yeah. They just write emails, but still I literally can. No, you can't go back for the boots.
Yeah. Anyways, here's some background on yours. Truly. Yeah. Yeah. I'm currently I'm in Iceland
in a small town called skip brought when I first arrived the, the here. Well, okay. I don't know.
KO legacy just gave 10 community subs. Thank you. KO legacy. Appreciate that. Thanks for the 10 drop.
German just has bad handwriting. No, we haven't even started yet. I was about to go get paper
and show you. No, I can't. No, we have, I, what's the, okay. I helped to restore the ship. All right.
Who cares about any of this? Wait, long staying rumor about a treasure concealed somewhere.
You want to try? I'm going to try to do this. I'm going to try to do this letter.
All right. I'll be right back. All right. Hold on. I got the camera on the tripod now.
Do I even have a pen in here? I'm supposed to be playing Nancy Drew. That's not what I'm doing.
I think all my room is clean. I need a pen though. Maybe I got a pen and this is on
perfect computer paper, by the way. You got one? Open the Xbox. I just need this much room.
All right. I'm ready. Uh, computer paper right here. I just need to be able to see what I'm
looking at. Missed bits. Hold on. I'll get it. Okay. Okay. Now, um, I need a fucking pen. How
do I have an office with no pens in it? We're fucking running around. Okay. I got it. Wait.
You guys get it. I'm going to have to use the webcam mic. Is it plugged in? All right. Hold
on. I'm, I'm almost ready. Do it on an overhead projector. I don't, I don't have an overhead
projector. I have to get this right. You're a loser. What? Get my coffee out of the way.
All right. There's no bank statements here, right? I have to pick up the stack of computer
paper and here's my bank statement. All right. Are we ready? Can you see it? Can you guys not see
this? Uh, it's not, uh, what is that? I can't even see. What is that? An image up? What the
fuck is this? What is this aiming at? Why is this so blown up? That's not the, no, it's not the
chair leg. Oh, it's up there. Why is it up there? Why is my hand so big? Why do I have a monster
hand? Why do I have such a big hand? Hey. Oh, look at those bones. Oh, what is that? Okay. My hand,
you know, you know, when you go to the Halloween store and you see like the look at the spooky hand
with real animatronics inside. That's what this is. Um, okay. Hold on. This has to be over here.
Oh, I thought found the computer paper. Found it. What? Xbox is on. Okay. I can see it. Move this
over here. Shrink it a little and then we got to turn it like this. No, I have to do this the way
that I know it. I can't see what this says. Pale hands. There's no white balance on this camera.
Don't you understand? I don't have any fucking white balance on it. Can you see? Okay, good.
Let's go. Let me get myself a little reminder. Do laundry later. Okay. Good. I got your contact
with St. Nancy. I need fucking, I need writing music. Okay. Best music for writing.
He's jacked. By the way, can we just talk about this fucking walnut desk? Immaculate.
Except for the couple places where I hit my hand with the VR controllers. Best music for writing.
Two hours of amazing writing and study playlist. What does that sound like? That sounds good.
All right. Let me see if I can get this. I need to make this bigger. Thank dear. Okay. Nancy,
Nancy, I got your contact info. Get out of there. I'm going to try my hardest
and don't make fun of the way that I hold a pencil. I know I got shit for this since I was
like the sixth grade. Okay. This is how I hold a pencil. I don't go like this. Oh, look at me.
Hold a pencil like that. You got to put on the other microphone. Can you guys hear me? I don't
know why nobody can hear me. No, you can't. Hold on. You're not alone. What? Add audio device.
Audio output. What was that? What was that? No, audio input is what I need. What was that?
What? I don't even know what that was. Was that the music? I haven't even started writing. Hold on.
God damn it. Hold on. Audio input. Audio input capture. There we go. Hello? Choose your
input. Dude, this shit. I can't even capture the fucking microphone. Why?
I can't. I can't. Why can I not capture the microphone? All right. I'm writing. I'm going
for it. Who cares? Fuck it. Ready? Here we go. Nancy, right? I drank like a large coffee.
Wait. This is going to be... Nancy, you can't even see. Look at... You can't even see it. I
got to zoom in it. It's so out of focus. I can't even read it. Enhance. I'm going to try to enhance
it. Hold on. Hold on. I need to enhance it. This camera sucks. Who cares? This camera sucks.
It doesn't matter. Nancy, I got... Okay. Let me see if I can get this correct. I got your
contact info through a friend of mine. I got your contact info through a friend. Friend of mine,
Mara... Mara Chisholm. Is that right? So far? I got your contact info through a friend of mine,
Mara Chisholm. I think you did some good sleuthing work with her in Scotland not too long ago.
Okay. Am I actually going to write this? Why don't I just take a script? I'm not going to
write this whole letter. I'm not writing the whole letter. Who the fuck wants me to do this?
Nobody wants me to do this. Nobody wants me to write the entire letter. You want me to write the
entire letter? Where's some background on yours for a moment? Where's your background on yours truly?
You can officially call me a locator fucker. A locator of fine goods. All right, now here's
the real... What if I just drop this into somebody's mailbox? Be like, what the fuck is this person
talking about? Send this to a friend of mine with no return address? Send this to Burger Boy. He's
going to be like, what in the name of fucking God is happening? Per se. Nice things get lost.
You would think this person was insane. If I write this whole letter, I have to give it to somebody.
I have to finish the letter. All right, once I finish the letter, we can do something else.
I didn't even... I didn't even get one second into the game too. All right, I gotta hurry up.
I'm on two sentences. Get lost. Nice things get lost. Nice things stay buried for a while.
Nice things get... For a while. I find the nice things. I get a piece of the... What? The pea?
The pie? The piece of the pie? I get it. I get the nice things. I get a piece of the pie.
Okay, I get the nice things. I get a piece of the pie. In other words, I'm a treasure hunter.
Is that a new paragraph? In other words, that's so much space. God damn it. In other words,
I'm a treasure hunter. I have so much more to do. I have so much more to do.
let's just let's cut let's cut to the currently I'm in Iceland in a small town
we can skip the rest currently I'm in Iceland in a small town called skip
brought skip brought right when I first arrived of this is all this doesn't mean
I don't need any of this stuff keep going keep going keep going I don't know
I people are leaving people leaving let's get to the end let's get to the end I
helped to uh oh that's so funny imagine opening up a stream and the guys
writing a letter and you're like I'm fucking out of here uh-uh I helped to
restore the ship along with my business partner this guy Magnus under two
conditions though one I would be entitled to a portion of any treasure found okay
cool I I'm not doing that we bled out like 500 people and the stream and even
started yet I'm not doing that why does this look so framerating oh I get to
backstabbing business partner Magnus I'm sensing you're a little stressed out
about this oh I'm so mad I've been an inch away from setting this town on fire
like robot chicken are you okay what oh just the fire comment I thought metaphors
Nancy keep up with me here so listen right now I'm focused on this town
there's this ship in town that was being rebuilt real old 18th century I offered
to sponsor the rebuilding project to get the ship floating again mostly because
I'm super nice and cool like that but company spent also because there's a
room decades on the same engine on board worth millions Magnus man in charge of
the project and my business partner promised we'd find it and split the
earnings but he's gone missing now so am I Nancy are you always Nancy and left
me looking like a fool okay was there any proof when did he
when did he vanish he disappeared sometime before our ship crashed into
the harbor they say he must have wait so they crashed so they crashed all in in
the water but the guy sails for a living is everybody all right don't why do we
don't we care about that first okay I get it you think he ran off with the
gold then you think he ran off with a gold then there was a shitload of money
that came in oh audio I got home let me delete these my audio captures all
fucked up because I tried to all right somebody gave a lot of money
German sucks gave ten community subs drinking skills gave five community
subs thank you appreciate it also fifth 5,000 bits came in from numb legs thanks
to the 5,000 bits I really appreciate it they say Merry Christmas to all it looks
like we have gained back the viewers
I'll be right back wait wait
ready let's go let's do it right here right
You're shrewd.
How do you, how do you, how do people do this?
You can't, like,
You definitely, you had to put this shit down
on a table and like smoosh you.
This is how they had to do it.
There's no other way to do that.
Should I do more than one?
A bunch of kool-aid.
Okay.
It's like all over my head.
Oh, okay.
I really gotta carry it away.
It's blood.
It's blood now.
Christ.
I didn't even know what I looked like until right now.
That's from smooshing my mouth.
You're a joker.
Nancy fucking Drew.
I haven't even played a minute of it.
You don't know what you look like.
I just, I ran in and grabbed one of Kim's lipsticks.
Look, look, look, look.
That's a little kid.
That ate too much, look it,
comical how much chocolate is on that kid's mouth.
Except it's not, it's lipstick.
It's, how was I eating it?
No, that's, it was on kind of normally
and then I smooshed my face into the desk.
Is it still, yeah, it's still there.
What do you think, it disappeared?
You got it in mommy's lipstick drawer.
Uh, okay, I, um,
What do I wanna do? I can't leave again.
I've left like six times.
I've left so many times.
It's music.
Okay, I need to compose myself here.
Oh my God, why did you give that many subs?
Jerma sucks just gave 61 subs?
Holy shit, dude.
What are you doing?
That's a lot, thank you for the huge sub drop.
That's a lot of money, thank you.
Dude, go gaming.
Crackdota five community subs, ten actually.
Kazzy five community subs, thank you, all of you.
Thank you Jerma sucks, seriously, Jesus.
Raphrod, ten community subs from Raphrod, thank you Raphrod.
Am I gonna just stream like this?
When I take a break, I'll get it on.
I, I'll just wait, I'll take a, I just, let me in one minute.
What do people in town think of the dis, I don't even know what's going on.
We shall,
What's with the, why's the audio so low?
Leave it on, no, I can't.
Without a body, you're still convinced he faked his death?
Yep, which apparently doesn't take a lot of work in Iceland.
I do have it all over my hands.
Oh my god, what the hell, what's going on, what, oh my gosh, Coke, are you serious?
Okay.
I'll let you go.
Stay warm.
Okay, so, explore the town, search the ship.
How do you walk?
Alright, explore the town, I wanna go check out the ship.
Spamming it in channel points, oh yeah, I have to do channel points, I forgot.
What about the rope?
The gangway is missing, there's no way on board.
I need a new gangway?
What?
Oh my god, what is this, what is this, oh my god, are you serious?
Coke gaming.
So I, I need a, I need a, I need a new one.
Alright, I, I have to go.
I have to like, not like leave, I have to like, this is like, I feel like, I don't know why, I feel like this is like seeping, I feel like this is seeping into my bloodstream.
I really do.
I really feel like this is like seeping into my bloodstream.
Alright, I'll be back.
Give me the...
It's not, it's not working.
It's not working, I just like ate, like I just ate like a person.
What did I eat right here?
Get off!
I just went hunting.
Like in a pack.
Flaming hot Cheetos.
If anybody asks, I really like flaming hot Cheetos to the fact that I'm permanently stained.
I'm willing to do this because like, fuck it, who cares, ready?
I'm just gonna pretend like I'm shit-faced on like really, really heavy red wine.
What, what, what does this mean?
What does this mean?
Why, oh that's from, okay.
Uh, yeah, so if you guys, I'd stick on.
I drank three of them.
Is someone on my camera?
Hey, thanks.
Thanks a lot, Coke gaming.
Let's go.
So what do you guys want to do?
I can barely do anything.
I really don't want to lie to you guys, but I seriously fucking can't do shit right now.
I, we were gonna play Nancy Drew, but I don't even, I don't even remember what the first part of it was.
TF2, play TF2.
I'm not playing TF2.
Why would I play TF2 right now?
It's not fucking gonna happen.
Uh, I think we'll, um, I think we'll probably have to call it today here, I think.
I think we'll, uh, drink more.
Somebody's been that person.
You didn't go off camera.
Shut the fuck up.
You fucking idiot.
Go to sleep.
I don't, I don't have to go to sleep.
I don't have to go to sleep.
I'm an adult.
Okay, I'm getting off the camera.
But seriously though, um, I, I can't get this off.
I'm just making it worse.
I'm just getting, hold on, let me fix my like disgusting hair.
I'm just getting like red face.
You know, it's like spreading.
I need toothpaste.
I need a special tissue.
I, Kim has this stuff.
I've just, I'm just gonna be wine mouthed.
All right, let's go.
Let's play Nancy Drew.
Uh, this, what?
Dude, this, the stream has been going for an hour.
Holy shit.
Wow.
All right, Nancy Drew, let's go.
Seriously though, on my next pee break, I'm gonna have to put like vinegar all over my mouth.
I don't know what to do.
All right, let's explore the town.
Uh, meat?
Is this meat?
Chaos at Skip Brock commerce meeting.
What's the, what the fuck was that?
What's the lipstick brand?
I don't know.
Kim's.
Kim's lipstick.
The color, um, big red.
I don't know.
It's Kim's.
Okay.
Town hall meeting this week erupted into discord when a local fisherman caused a scene of what
he calls a threat to score Icelandic values.
Skip Brock citizen Gunnar Tonneson brought a written petition to the meeting, hoping to
interrupt the board's vote on fiscal allocation for the annual ancestors festival.
A lot of reading.
Ooh, it's a hook.
A meat hook.
A discord town hall meeting.
All right, I got a meat hook.
This is a measty skip.
The measty skip.
Measty skip.
Sleep near.
That's Star Wars.
Okay.
I was wondering what the hell that was.
All right.
Is this a menu?
This is a dining room.
Good day.
Hi there.
I'm investigating a recent disappearance.
My name's Nancy Drew.
Speak up, girl.
Louder.
I said my name's Nancy Drew.
Mind your ship flag and temper.
Looks like we have a real angry one here.
Uh.
Name's Gunnar.
What you can call me, Gunnar.
Gunnar.
The skip is my home.
Oh.
What?
Louder.
Are you a sailor?
Was.
Long ago.
I gave up the sea for good.
And I'll never sail again.
You still look like a sailor to me.
Whoa.
What does a sailor look like?
It's a certain quality.
I can't quite place it.
Worn?
Broken?
Bitter?
I don't know.
Broken?
Bitter?
The sea chewed me up and spat me back out, and I lost everything in her waves.
If you can do a convincing Scottish accent...
I bet you'd not last one minute against some of the gays I've sailed.
You will always have voice work.
I'm so surprisingly hard to kill.
Well, we'll see about that, detective, won't we?
Someone's always looking for the Scottish accent.
No matter what, it doesn't matter.
What are you talking about?
This is not Scottish.
What is this?
What is it?
It's not Icelandic?
Did you know, Magnus?
What?
Sure did.
Never liked him.
Did something happen between you two?
No, I don't like anyone.
I don't think I like you.
I'm still going it over.
Norwegian chat.
Icelandic is nothing like this.
Thank you!
So you were wrong, too.
I was wrong and you were wrong.
We both get to be equally wrong.
It's good.
What about your fingers?
So, about your fingers...
My lucky three?
Is that what you call them?
Sure is.
It's a long story.
Now, there I was.
Out in the peach black of night, with no sign of shore and only my fishing spear.
Then suddenly, I saw a shadow.
It was a mighty squid, the greatest hunter of them all.
That's a lie.
Few men have had to sit and tell the tale.
So I pulled out my spear just a little too fast, mind you.
And that's how you lost your fingers?
Of course not!
I drew the spear right overboard and I hauled that fellow into my net.
Took all my weight, used to keep him from wriggling free.
But his strength proved too much for me.
He gnashed his giant beak and, well, I was done for.
So the squid took your fingers?
No, no, no, no!
Right as I thought I was dead, a massive shark leapt out of the waves and ate the squid.
It was the sleeper shark.
It stalled six meters long with four rows of teeth.
He bit my arm and pulled me under as I gasped for my last breath.
So it was a shark then?
No!
I managed to punch him in the nose!
Did you ever fight a shark?
You know how to punch him in the nose?
He let me go, I swam like a merman and made it back to shore.
Three months later, I was in a wood shop accident.
Right, that's what it is then.
That's what I knew it would be.
At least it makes for a great story.
Yeah, I mean that's...
That's a...
Have you met Dagny?
Who?
This guy is based.
The Republic High's restoration.
Brown hair about Yehai?
Ah, a tough little mink of a woman.
Not bad in my book.
Did you see her the day of the ship crash?
Yeah, she was there, but I paid no attention to the mink.
Okay, um...
I heard you had problems with the festival the last couple of years.
I heard you've had problems with the festival the last couple of years.
Care to talk about that?
The festival is not what it once was.
I turn things to the old ways no matter how many buckets of hot tar I have to dump.
Why are you dumping hot tar?
Some of the harbor boats still have holes in their bottoms.
I see. Did you have a plan like that for this year too?
Elisabeth said no more trouble or she kicks me out of the skip.
I only pay with an angry sheep.
What does that mean?
Means I do it, but I don't like it.
Oh.
I'm sorry, I'm new around here.
Be gone with you.
Did you just...
Learn Icelandic and earn...
Kromer!
Yeah, let's do it.
People.
What?
Aunt.
Boy.
Brother.
Child.
Child is barn.
Daughter is dottir.
Doctor is lake-nir.
Father is fower.
Friend is viner.
Girl is stolka.
Magician is galdremor.
Mother is múdir.
Musician is tónlistamor.
Nurse.
Nurse is fóyaf.
Júkrún.
Júkrúnafrún.
Okay, I can't do that one.
Parents is a forreal drawer.
Photographer is jósmidari.
Let's try it.
Please place the Icelandic word next to its English match.
Child is barn.
Right?
Daughter is dottir.
Frendi is afi.
Uncle is frendi.
And grandfather is afi.
Got it.
Husband.
Magician.
Sailor is sielur.
Magician is galdremor.
Woman.
Husband.
Kona.
Eginwar?
I'm going to say it's that.
Got it.
Jósmidari is, I don't know, photographer?
I don't remember.
I think it's photographer.
Domari is judj.
Friend.
Mother.
Got it.
You guys don't think I know Icelandic.
Parents.
Sister is definitely sister.
Kinaari.
Teacher?
Or parents.
It's probably parents.
Sister.
Forrealdar is parents.
Got it.
I win.
Congratulations.
You earned 600 bucks.
I'll take it.
Why wouldn't you just sit here if you knew English and Icelandic?
Wouldn't you just sit here and just print free money forever?
This seems like a lot of money to learn just basic words.
And there's nobody here.
You could just sit there all day.
You could just sit there and just, I know what that word is, and then go order another drink.
Alright, this is employees only.
Fuck it, go in.
Gasoline.
I'll take it.
It's five or six bucks.
Damn.
That's a lot.
Well, maybe if you weren't given away $3,000 a night.
$3,000 a night to people that knew what father was in Icelandic.
We wouldn't be in this position.
I'm trying to get the lipstick off my mouth.
Hold on.
I wouldn't be sitting here discussing it with you.
Now would I?
What makes me a good dimwit?
Alright, is it gone?
I've been sitting here this whole time.
Is it actually gone?
It might be.
Let's see.
No.
Not even close.
It's better.
Alright, so I got gasoline.
Get olive oil.
Who's been sitting here watching me?
Well, I can't, my mouth feels, my mouth hurts.
Am I allergic to lipstick?
What's this?
Full, I can do this.
Skip rot, a history.
It's 450 bucks.
I can do that.
The people of Skip rot struggled to survive and his crew were rescued and taken in.
Okay.
Let's just make some money.
No, no, that's magician.
That's musician, sister, writer.
That's child.
That's veterinarian, Barnas child.
Fuck.
Friendy is uncle.
Hi nurse.
Got it.
Okay.
I didn't study this one.
That's mother.
That's father.
Switch them.
You aren't, do it again.
I'm just going to have, I'm just going to keep doing it.
For real door is just, can I just do this forever?
And just till I have like $5,000?
I don't, I don't remember these.
Which one was it?
Sailor, husband, grandfather, magician.
That's aunt.
That's musician.
This is doctor.
That's soldier.
I got it wrong.
It's okay.
Got 500 bucks.
Another one.
Pull my finger.
I don't know.
Thumb, mouth, cheek, tooth.
Got it.
I'm going to say foot.
Brain is probably, one more, one more, one more, one more.
I still want to, I just want to, I'm almost done.
Sailor.
I'm actually learning Icelandic.
This is pretty cool.
I'm learning Icelandic.
I know these words now.
These have a pop up ever again.
You're addicted to Icelandic.
No, I'm addicted to making $5,000.
So I never have to make money again.
So I just walk around with a huge purse full of money.
Okay.
It was mother, judge, doctor.
Yeah.
Go.
Oops.
It's all right.
I just want 2,000.
That's all I want.
$2,000.
I just got to get them all out there.
Okay.
A friend is, teacher is, I fucked it up.
Don't matter.
Father.
Grandmother is this one.
Nurse is this one.
I fucked it up.
All right.
I got exactly 2,000.
That's why I messed those ones up.
I'm done.
All right.
Let's, what do I need?
Can I look at the bar?
I can go through here.
What's this?
Gunner, I'm going to be spending all my time on the ship over the festival weekend.
As a reminder, here are the rules in my absence.
All mugs and dishes must be cleaned.
Customers must be served promptly.
Yes, even if they are tourists.
Don't call customers weak spined ninny faces.
No challenging customers to fights.
Yes, this includes arm wrestling.
I'm not going to write this.
Write and kiss another letter.
No, I'm not putting more lip, I can't get this off.
This is not even a letter.
This is notes for the write and kiss, write and kiss.
Nope.
No, I'm not putting lipstick on.
Again, I can't get it off.
Probably shouldn't be back there.
Can I put the hook in?
No.
All right.
So I got gas.
What do I need?
This is so neat.
I wish I could play these.
You can just do it.
I'd imagine text popping up at the bottom of the screen and they're talking to me.
Sure.
I'll help.
Cello.
Liar.
Langspiel.
Fiola.
Gigia?
Harp.
Know your instruments.
Ooh.
These are don't starve voices.
Don't starve.
It's at this point that somebody's just like, stop doing that.
Yes, they're instruments.
Yes, they're on the wall.
You're not the first person to walk up and go like this.
Please.
Endless night, endless tunes.
Elizabeth Grimer's daughter.
That means daughter.
The Landlubbers, a night of Icelandic classics.
Featuring Neo J. Mel, Corvallis J., Seeker Rose J., B. York.
That's a long fucking name.
Neo J. Mel, Corvallis J., Seeker Rose J., B. York.
That's you.
I know it's multiple things.
All right.
That was fun.
Can I touch the fire?
No.
All right.
Let me get out of here.
I got the gas.
Wait, what's this?
I can't interact with that.
Why the fuck not?
All right.
I'm out.
Should I do part two?
No.
Who gives a shit?
I'm saving my money.
Customize your gear.
Great.
Do I have to remember this?
Music book.
Current tide is low.
I should try to get some sleep while I'm here.
Write that down.
What am I going to bed?
Is this Christmas?
This is the perfect game to play right now.
I didn't know this takes place in Christmas.
That's kind of cool.
Where's my hotel?
Probably here.
Can I get on the?
No keys.
Guess I can't just take them.
Hmm.
I feel like this is my live stream.
When you know you haven't spoken, you haven't said anything in about like 30 seconds.
So you're like, fuck, I have to say something.
Hmm.
I got nothing.
I have nothing to say right now.
And like, there are people that are watching this stream.
Uh.
Okay.
That works.
Good.
He's inactive.
All right.
I need to go to the inn.
Can I, is it like a, can I go to sleep?
Culture center?
This person's scary.
I don't know what it is about.
It's the fact that they're the two different styles of, you're like lit improperly.
Like you're a hologram.
This just looks, just seems, this is freaking me out.
Oh, simulate your fear.
You got me.
All right.
Well, that's cool.
Learn to speak like a sailor aboard a tall ship.
Touch to begin.
You need to match each sail to its name.
What?
Is this Iceland?
Is this Icelandic?
Jib.
I don't know.
Okay.
This is, what do I?
Boat.
The main top mast stay sail.
The missing top galant sail.
Okay.
This is, what's a jib?
I have no idea what any of this stuff is.
There's this much shit on a boat.
I thought it was a big bed sheet, like two big bed sheets on two large poles.
I don't know.
There was this many segments.
I don't even know.
What's a jib?
The, uh, the four top sail, main top sail.
You need to find the treasures learning about the ship.
Where's the jib?
All right.
Um, I don't care.
Parts of a ship sail.
Oh, here we go.
Here's like a, this will help us.
All right.
I got it.
Cheating.
Um, how is learning cheating?
How would I, why would I ever know this information?
You want me to walk down the path and find what all these are named?
This is just learning.
This is learning what these are and then clicking on them.
Uh, where's the flying?
There's the flying.
This is learning what these are and then clicking on them.
Uh, where's the flying?
There's the flying jib.
It's not even on here.
What about the one underneath?
The four moon sail is this one.
Do they have different names for everything?
This is supposed to be the four moon sail.
Four stay sail.
This is the wrong sheet.
This thing's called the spanker.
Uh, incorrect apparently.
Parts of a ship.
What about this one?
The main mast is the one in the middle.
Okay.
So this is main mast, main top sail, uh, main top galant stay sail, main royal sail, main
sail.
Okay.
The four mast is the one, so this is the, there's too many parts here.
He doesn't know.
Even with a, I have a cheat sheet right next to me and it's still confusing me.
Because people call these different things.
Somebody said this is the beak.
This is the spanker on one list.
All right.
Here we go.
He looks, this looks like a good one.
Main mat crows now.
Okay.
Shrouds of the officers.
No, this is like the four top galant sail.
This is too many sails.
Why there's too many?
What is this thing?
This is, they're just floating.
Uh, I can't even cheat.
I can't cheat because these are all these images of like different from each other.
Every single one of these is different to the next one because some of them only have
one or two masts.
I can't cheat.
Holy fuck.
Wait a minute.
Is this actually, is this from the game?
I think this is from the game.
I just typed in like parts of a ship.
I'm going to type in force for sale for sale.
Um, I, do you think I'm going to sit there and look at all that shit?
They're all so different.
For Royal, the eggplant sale?
What?
I'm putting this on screen.
This thing, seafaring, captains and shit have different names for everything.
Let's go over this.
Help me.
What, what, what, what, what am I looking at here?
Okay.
So see that that's the four moon sail.
The mizzen is the back mizzen moon sail.
There's the stay sale.
He's don't even mizzen top sale.
There's only two.
No, I can't even read this mizzen.
Click my link.
What the fuck is that?
That's a lot of, but mizzen Royal's not even on here.
Mizzen sky sale.
All right.
The ones that mizzen are in the back.
Okay.
Mizzen top sale.
I don't know this one.
Mizzen stay sale.
This one.
Top glance sale.
Use this one.
I'm trying to click it.
It's going too fast.
That's not, that's not even what this is.
Game boomers.
What is game boomers?
All right.
Did you just give me the actual solution?
Is this the solution?
A, E, K, B, A, E, K, I had K, correct, K, B, H, O, F, N, D, J.
Uh, M, C, I, M, C, I, well, hold on.
I'm not spelling out something fucked up, right?
Okay.
I'm not.
I just, somebody just linked me like an, like an imgur link of, or I don't, I don't know
why I just figured maybe they would like making me spell something fucking crazy.
Okay.
And the last two are L, G. Learn to speak like a sailor.
Rear or towards the stern, front or towards the bow, port, parts of the average ship's
bow spirit to David, forecastle gaff.
Didn't like a boat crash into a wall and aren't we, is it, wasn't it like a murder
or something?
Why do we have to do this?
That's all this was for.
That's it.
Maybe later.
Complimentary gift wrap available.
Gift wrap on gasoline.
All right.
Let's talk.
Hi there.
My name is Soren.
You must be Nancy.
I'm Soren, the organizer of the Ancestors Festival.
I run the culture center here in Skiprock.
Nice to meet you.
Can you help me get onto the ship?
Ah, you're in the laundry room?
Is Elizabeth not manning the gangway?
The gangway is missing, unfortunately.
Oh dear.
Well, that's highly unusual.
I'll take care of it straight away for you.
No accent?
Rose, truly.
But she does have thorns.
Hey, what do you think happened to Magnus?
What do you think happened to Magnus?
I admit I haven't the faintest idea.
That man's mind is a hive of mysteries, an enigma, an impenetrable den.
So you two never really talked?
This dude's sweater.
An understatement.
I want a nice hot coffee right now.
The man hardly spoke 10 words to me the entire time I knew him.
I do hope he's all right.
I don't know why.
It's getting an automatic response from me.
I want like a nice hot latte.
I don't...
I just want it.
I'm already disliked.
And it would only show the others how easy it is to make someone disappear.
What is this place?
This is my battle station.
The place where I endeavor to fight my way through the thickest mysteries of Icelandic
history.
Here, confusing ancient shipwrecks and obscure writings from millennia past are converted
into knowledge and truths.
This is my battle station.
Also, I have swords.
Take a look at how many monitors I have over here.
So, you're a historian, archaeologist, a bit of both?
I dabble.
I spent some years at Harvard pursuing my doctorate in Viking history before returning
to Skipporad for research.
I'm one of the only few to ever travel in this town.
Everyone here should try it sometime.
Really shakes up the old bag of prejudices.
I guess that explains why you don't have much of an accent.
Check out my washing machine collection.
You know, there's people that collect everything.
If you don't think that somebody has a basement full of washing machines and dryers, there
definitely is.
In fact, if there's somebody that collects it, that means that there's probably a convention
for that too.
I guarantee it.
If you typed in vintage washing machine convention, you'll find something.
Alright, what are you researching?
Wash-con.
Did you do it?
Oh, you lost me.
You lost me real quick.
Cool.
Cool swords.
Bye.
What do you think about this sword?
I could use a little space, Nancy.
Alright.
Uh, nothing over here.
Wait, what's this?
Uh, the sextant.
Navigational instrument which allowed sailors to determine latitude, the astrolabe, the
sunstone, the fishing reel, the cargo lantern.
There's a lot about boats.
There's a lot of things about boats here.
Do I have a...
Oh, my cell phone!
Settings.
Why would you want this as your background?
Is it bear traps and meat hook and shit?
That's kind of creepy.
Oh, I like the crystals.
Ringtone.
What?
What's comedy?
That's a comedy.
I don't know.
That's pretty funny.
Alright, I'm going to do the Yoshi sound.
Ringtone.
Oh, that one's real.
Why is it called Oregon?
Should I do the burps?
Alright, that's pretty good.
Definitely the scratch one, okay.
What about my photos?
View galleries.
No photos?
Okay, what about, um, my diary?
I'm not writing it down.
Phone.
Oh, it's Ned!
I can call Ned with this.
One, because this number doesn't exist.
For everyone else, leave a message.
I just really pissed that person off.
Because they just got...
Yo, you have a new voicemail!
Oh, let me listen.
I wonder what it is.
Why is it only four and a half seconds long?
Oh, it's just this.
It's like swishing pants.
And the hang up noise.
Okay, cool.
Alright, get this down.
The game wanted me to go to sleep.
What was this?
One, two, three?
Could you finish setting up the knots display?
You just need to match the images to the knot they create.
I do it myself, but I don't have the time.
I don't...
I have no idea what you're asking me to do.
Put the knots next to the knots that they create?
Put the knots next to the knots they make?
Uh, this is...
Is that...
Is this correct, right?
Wait, there's five steps for each knot.
Oh my god.
I don't know how to do these.
I don't know any of this stuff.
I don't know how to do this.
It's not this one.
So we got, okay, one big loop.
And then...
I mean, that's like, this is done.
No, it's not.
What?
I gotta get...
I gotta spread them out a little.
Go get string and do it.
Am I dumb?
No, I...
Alright.
Chat.
Excuse me.
When was the last time any of you made this knot?
If you ever made that knot.
Ever.
And I'm talking for any reason.
Nobody has made these knots.
Maybe one of you have done this.
I can't believe you just know how to make a...
I can't even give you a fake name
because I don't even know what these could be called.
The pretzel knot.
I don't know.
This isn't even a knot.
This is just what happens to my fucking earpods.
That's your...
That's a headphone.
That's a headphone every day.
Is that done?
Did I do it?
No, this one goes up here.
I think this one goes down here.
I gotta get them all out so I can look at them.
Are there any baits?
Okay, there are no baits.
Alright, we need to get the two big ones.
There you go.
Okay.
Looking good.
Alright, looking good.
This one's done.
We're gonna need a game boomer here.
Now, this one, this is the fat loop.
So this requires a big loop.
This one has a small loop.
This one can come down here.
I think we're gonna be good here.
I need to have the finishing product.
This is the finished product of this one.
This looks like a pretty...
Um...
Literally no.
I kinda wanna make one of these.
Yo.
Fuck it.
I'll be right back.
Alright, let's give it a try.
See if I can do this.
So, we've got...
Let me see if I can do the middle one.
Yeah, I don't know if these are shoelaces
or if these are strings that go inside of hoodies or pants.
I found them.
Alright, let's get the cam on.
Is this drawstring?
Yeah, I think it is just drawstrings.
It's just pants.
Why does this keep happening?
I keep having it so shrunken.
No, it's gotta be this way.
There's the Xbox.
There we go.
Okay, right there.
See if I can do it.
So, we're looking...
So, we got...
Here's our string.
You need two strings, right?
So, you take the two ends like this.
How far up does this need to be?
Just needs to go wrap around like how many times?
Twice?
So, like...
Hold on a minute.
This is...
You go over and...
Hold on.
Am I supposed to be doing it like this?
Over?
Like that again?
Okay, like that.
Then, you...
These are too...
Look at how long these are!
These are so long!
I need like three people to do this.
Over, under, like that.
Okay, that part's done.
And then we go like this.
I need like a person to hold on to this shit.
Like this.
And then, from here, I go...
What the fuck do you want me to do here?
Again?
Over, under, again?
Like that?
Oh, dude!
Pogchamp!
I got it.
What the fuck, dude?
Are you serious?
How am I gonna do...
Oh, God.
I'm not gonna be able to do these next ones.
This next one is just...
Okay.
Now, I don't need the second one.
What does this say?
Do what?
Do...
Do laundry.
Okay, I gotta remember that.
All right, these...
I gotta fix these ones.
I didn't want to do it afterwards.
Okay.
All right, so...
I...
How does this one even work?
Is there something wrong?
I don't know.
Around, and then through that loop, so that's correct.
And then, once you get to up here, you go around, underneath, and then through, and
then that's it.
Is that right?
No.
This is...
This is for the one up there.
This is for the one up.
That starts there, and then it goes up, around, and then...
Let me do it.
Switch top, left, and bottom left.
No, that's not correct, because this has to go up through that hoop.
Uh...
From there, you go under, and then you wrap around, and then you...
Like that?
Yeah, like that.
But that's...
That's the...
That's this one.
Got it.
Okay.
Now, let's try...
Let's try that one.
This actually...
Kind of fun.
I like this.
All right, so then we start.
Uh, this is too long.
It's too long.
I can't do it.
And then this has to go...
Make like a circle around and under.
Like that.
Right?
Get...
Okay.
It's too long.
This is way too long.
And then this one goes...
Uh...
Through the hoop here, over.
Like that.
And then under, and then over.
This one needs to be much smaller, but this one's going to be a little bigger.
Uh...
Wait.
Hold on.
Fuck.
No, that's okay.
So then this one goes underneath this one.
And then it wraps back down through...
Over there, through here, under.
And then you pull it.
Did I get it?
I got it.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Doesn't feel very secure, though.
Nice.
I can't...
There we go.
All right.
What's the last one?
I've got to get it right.
Last one is...
Start there.
I want to just do this.
I want to just make nuts.
Is that fucking stupid?
I wanted to do this.
Okay, so then wrap it around there.
Then that...
Oh, shit.
No, no, no.
Don't leave the screen.
I want to see that.
Oh, god damn it.
I can't see.
Shit.
Uh...
It's all right.
I can kind of see it.
Click on it again?
I can't.
I can see it.
You just simply wrap it around like that.
Like that.
Okay.
And then this...
What does it do?
It goes under and then over, like, right there, immediately.
And then I can't see.
Let me make it bigger so I can see it.
This is insanely important to me, so I can't click on it anymore.
So let me do this again.
Reset.
It's just...
This one has to be longer.
So like that.
And then it wraps back around.
So under, under, and then over, immediately right here, like that.
And then you go back under and through the loop, like this, and then out across to here.
And then that shit goes all the way around and then under itself.
Like that.
And then tighten it.
Did I do it?
Did I get it?
Okay.
No, I got it.
That was correct.
Nice.
Somebody give me, give me, give me another knot to do.
I want to do another knot.
Anybody have one more I can do?
You're a serial killer.
What?
Fun knots to do.
Ooh, essential knots.
How to tie 20 knots.
Why is doing knots a serial killer?
Okay, cool.
We did the square knot.
Okay, what about the bow?
We did the bow line.
The figure 8, the street, the sheet bend, two half hitches, taut hitch line, fisherman's
knot.
Look at this one.
Let me try this one just by hand.
Check this one out.
This one's fucked up.
Look at how crazy this one is.
See if I can do it.
Let's not be in the gem watch.
Look at this thing.
Cool.
Let me try it.
Okay, let's get some music here.
Let's try it.
So it looks like it's a small circle here.
Cool.
Like that.
And then it goes underneath itself like this.
Actually underneath like three or four times.
Make it a little bit bigger though.
Ow, ow.
Um.
Okay.
This is breaking my finger.
It's breaking my finger.
Oh, I hate this.
I hate this.
Hold on.
I gotta.
How do you escape?
How to escape a knot.
How to escape from?
Please.
How do I get out of this?
Yeah.
Presentation.
Ow.
How?
Knuckles together and pull my hands out of most of my chest. Oh
No, no, no, that's wrong way wrong way wrong way
So that when he ties me up I've created
That when I breathe oh
Oh, I just had to let go with my right hand. I was holding it. That was weird. Okay, that'll heal
I think okay, that'll heal nicely in the next six months
Okay. Um, that's good. What's that sound? Oh, it's this
Sound
Not
Make this a not stream. No, I did my I did my I got trapped
Trying to do a fucking necktie segment. Okay, I went doing that again
What did I get for this? What did I get for this? Oh something in the seat? Oh
Everything in the gift shop is available for purchase and I got
$2,000 too. Oh shit. This stuff is still on screen. I'm sorry
Alright, let's get some slippers
2,700 bucks some money first. That's too much. This stuff is also expensive. I just fucking I just bought it
I just bought it. I don't have any money left. I bought one
Looks like you're out of cash. I'll need to earn some money first
You'll need more money for that. Damn it. I hope I need that item soon
Back to the learn Icelandic game
No, I have to go to bed. I hasn't even one evening in this game
All right, where do I where do I go to sleep you again
What do you think of Gunnar in terms of the treasure?
He tried to sabotage the festival last year and any though before that are you certain?
I wouldn't be surprised if this is a stunt of his
Bye. Bye
See you drew
Where's the bed?
Explore the town search the ship explore the misty skip. I can't explore the thing because I can't get up there. Wait a minute
This wasn't here before
Who let you on board if you're here for the festival? It's canceled. I didn't mean to intrude
I just like to have a look around if that's okay. My name is Nancy Drew. I'm a visitor. I
Know you're a tourist
Oh
Storm and boat a tourist. I'm here to investigate
Thanks for setting up that gangway for me, by the way, the gangway was meant for sorry
I didn't know he planned to let strangers on board. Are you with that snake of a woman?
Hey
Yes, Dagny, yes, I'm working with her if you're after just the gold I want nothing to do with you leave
Wait, I'm not after any treasure. I just want to help find Magnus
Magnus
Look, I think we might have gotten off on the wrong foot. Maybe I should start over. My name's Nancy
It's really nice different voice actress. I'm Elizabeth. I run the misty skip club in town. What do you want with Magnus?
Oh good. So you know him. Hmm. That's a question
Is it I thought I knew him maybe I was wrong. He's a pretty mysterious guy sounds like quite the mysterious guy
It doesn't matter I want nothing to do with him now or you
It's in the bag
Ma'am, can I take a look at that bag, please?
Hey, Elizabeth, may I borrow a snowmobile key?
Depends are you going to steal it?
Not this time. I think I'd have trouble fitting it into my carry-on luggage. It is a different person
Here's the key. We have tourists take them every year. I'm watching you
Always use the provided seat belt snow looks soft until you land headfirst
She stole it last time
What do you think happened to Magnus? The current rumor is that he fell overboard
Do you think happened to Magnus the current rumor is that he fell overboard? Do I think he is drowned?
Is that what you're asking?
He might have I didn't mean that I didn't mean it that way. I certainly hope so
Some people think he ran off with some old treasure. It may be a coincidence
It may not Danny doesn't think it was a coincidence at all
So I do like
Just a bit here and there even I've really really want to go shop at Old Navy now
Because everyone that we've seen so far was in an Old Navy
Too lofty to concern himself with human affairs
Do not go to Old Navy
Old Navy gaming what did Gunnar do anything unusual leading up to the festival?
Well, if you include the two festivals before this one, they look like mannequins he ruined them single-handedly
Aside from that only the usual threat. Oh, thank you. Oh, Navy game
And sent him out to sea
Bye bye
We really got it getting we got to get in that that twitch culture, you know, I mean we got to get in there
What are you doing using your key? Hey, what are you doing? Oh, that doesn't fit
Crows nest. Let's go up
Jesus
80 what does 86 mean? Is that I don't know. This is a currency thing
Is this some kind of currency thing? All right, let's get down. How do I get down?
I'd be careful up here though. At any moment I could like I
Think I'm I could I could slip. Oh, oh shit up. Oh, I
Lost the game capture
80s it was some kind of currency thing 86 is that a currency? Oh
Wow, the Aurora boiling house. Thank you right now, right? It's absolutely beautiful
Something like that. Why did you do that? Why do you sound like me? What?
Why do you sound like me? All right, let's take this
Pretty good song
Captain's log
Thank you. Hank cheesecake for the five community sets are really appreciate that
Here it is one more time for you
Masts from tallest to shortest. We already did this. We just cheated for this one. That's fine
My pretend to steer the boat. All right, Nancy put it down. Wow, I can
Can I honk the horn? I don't think I can honk the horn. I let me um, let me go to the snowmobile
What is this?
What we need a gas for Oh the book for the snowmobile
That makes sense. I kind of want to take a look back here though. Can I know just leave just leave leave
What looks like this day is in good shape?
All right to the snowmobile let's go hello. Hello. Oh, that's my ring tone
No, I'm already getting closer all the time. I thought that was my swishy
outdoor winter pants
It's hard to get people to talk though
Yes, I've managed to narrow down that the treasure is related to the ship somehow, but beyond that I haven't figured out the specifics
Of course, then will you take any other photos of yourself
Sunday it's our anniversary
We had reservations for dinner remember Ned dot dot dot
So am I under the impression that
She forgot about their anniversary when they had a reservation planned
But instead she got on a plane to Iceland or is he here too? And why does
What does he not know this?
Sorry, Ned. I forgot about our anniversary. It's not like I'm in traffic on the way home. Oh, that's right. Shit our anniversary
I'm coming right home. No, I mean Ned. I'm in Iceland and I'll see you in two weeks
I'm so so so sorry. I completely forgot
This case is really important
Do you like gasoline? All right gasoline. All right, let's go
Yeah, no shit
Let's go
I'm on the
Why is there a magic cave not a big fan of exploring caves in the dark. I'll need a light source
Use your phone
You kidding me. I'm not a big fan of it. I came all the way out here for no reason. I'll need a light source
Here do I think this is um, I don't know
somewhere post 2010
That this isn't supposed to be like the early 2000
Drive to Ned's house
This takes place in like 2014 or something
All right. I need a flashlight. I mean, what is this sketch piece?
The number 86 was carved into the mast
learning about the ship
He could have gone left there. I thought somebody was just making a joke because like the cave on the left thing
I actually do have a name, you know, it's Nancy
This is the 30-second Nancy Drew game
Get your little lady bones into the prep area and get some Torremotor orders ready
It's all hands-on back for the lunch rush. Wait, cooking segment?
I'm a sleuth not a chef. Are you sure you want me back there handling the sharp stuff?
You're eating a lot in here for free. Why does every Nancy Drew game have cooking food in it?
So it's only fair to get some good work out of you. Well might as well take a stab at it
Oh my god, this is not cooking
Fill the Torremotor tray according to the order where they eat penguins
they eat penguins and
All requests must be filled though. Some compartments may be empty orders can be filled in one of two ways across a row
And in a Z shape within a color tiny group
When checking whether an order is complete empty spaces don't count. I don't know what this is telling me
All requests must be filled though some can some compartments can be empty
They can do they can go in a Z shape
When checking whether an order is complete empty spaces don't count
Remember that each row and each color tray group counts as one order and must contain no extra items
The row below has an extra Lundy so it doesn't meet the order requirements when all orders are filled
You receive any remaining tips choose to make a new order
What I mean, that's not a penguin is it like molded up ice cream to look like a penguin I don't understand
What are you talking about?
fill them
Okay time to get to work
lax
Lundy and Hikaro
so the first order is a
one order of I
I I I I one order of that and then okay order done
Then hey, whoa, whoa. Whoa, I'm doing it. I'm going
Alright new water get it out ship it out of here. Did I do it faster? Oh
I know and I can't do it faster than that. It's just too confusing
Just doing Z's only Z's. I don't care
And then then
And then sheep and then sheep down here and then fish and then that no, no, no fucked it up. What's happening?
this one good got it and then wait, no, I have to desist
I
That one's done I got
No, this one
This is this is dumb
it just needs three three and
No, get in there. What are you? I have no idea what he's doing. Neither do I have no idea what's going on
I thought I was gonna be flipping pancakes
Why would you put me back here, I don't know what any
That one looked really easy wait, hold on wait, wait, wait, wait, wait shit. Wait, wait. Okay. This one. No, this one looks easy
shit
How do I fix this? I need two and then one I'm confused
it can be in a Z or
Cross or a cross has to be I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
This is
Then we need a
This one hair has to be done. Now this one top one. What's top one top one is? Oh, god. Damn it
Give me a break. This is the easiest thing ever. It's it's not the easiest thing ever. I
Need to get that there or yeah, I can't move cuz it has to I wish I could pick it up and didn't oh
You motherfucker. Why does it I'm trying to pick this one up?
Why is it giving me like a ton of them?
It's the same fucking thing. All right, if I flip these I would love to flip these so we got to do
Sheep on left. What do you mean on left put a bad review on Yelp?
Fix the bottom row. I can't I can't I can't I can't there's not enough spaces. There's not enough spaces
Switch the rows. No, that's not correct. I
Give me fuck out of here speak up now
Elizabeth said you threaten Magnus pretty directly. I did it was
How do you call it friendship?
Friendship that's friendship to you. What are you on about?
It still seems a little strange
spoken by a woman with no friends
Hey, I have friends and I have boyfriend who I am ditching to be here talking to you
My friends are back in the US
They don't like Islam don't like cold. What? I think they're in school right now
school
Okay gunner, okay
Does this dickhead not understand that it's thousands of dollars to travel across the world?
How can you expect?
How can you pick like a 19 year old to have like?
$4,700 in their bank account to like come to Iceland for fun right now. We talking about
You spend a lot of time in the pub, don't you why what kind of a question is that?
Sitting in the pub crying over a tiny
Ever lost in the writing it all down at the wind be little notebook. No would be
Magnus me. I am a mountain wolf. I know the wires and I keep my own company
I am a predator
Did you go to the festival this year? Is this your hook?
Embarrassing for you. Well, everyone else is scrambling around for hidden treasure embarrassing when I was so young
We fought over things like longest fish and shiny sport
Gold ever since that sword took over the festival running. It's been straight to the bottom with it
Did Magnus ever say anything about a treasure chest that you may have found
Did Magnus ever say anything about the treasure a lazy purple? Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody
Welcome to the fucking stream
Yeah, somebody look somebody rated me and like I'm just being I'm being fucking weird because now it's a year my head
Because every time somebody rated before I would be like, hey, what's up guys?
Not now see I'm like fucked up. So you don't want to watch this spring, right?
Link the slap look I hit myself in the face sometimes see
Welcome to the worst dream ever you paid Oh the worst dream ever you paid channel points to say that which means you've been
Sitting here for at least like 67 minutes. I'm sorry, but he could be in danger. I need your help
Don't care don't want trouble. I'll let you go. What happened to you?
Oh
Do you do this room along girl? Did you make these?
What did I get $750 from I find it on the ground?
All right, 86. I need to find out more. Look at this is definitely a puzzle
Can I get some puzzles and no?
needing to know what
Masts and sails on boats are is not a puzzle. That's information. I want a puzzle not info
I gotta learn more about the ship. I need a flashlight. Can I go in? Let's go over here. You got any new info for me?
You do you have anything like what about these sketches? I didn't think it was possible to be this cold
Can't you go inside the hell you're asking people to fix this broken heater so I can watch over my ship
You know what Gunnar told me freeze for all I care. He is the worst human being
Maybe I can help you out with that heater. Then do you know how to do?
Machine things I've picked up a few things. Okay. I don't care what they
You're okay, Nancy Drew. Thanks for showing me that I need to up the price on that to like 5,000
This is good data. I'm collecting here. Do you want this?
Sorry, can't talk need heat teeth freezing into tiny inside fix the heater
There's no Peter outside. What are you talking about the pubs around the corner?
You could always go inside or you could fix the heater gee, I wonder which of us will cave first
What's the what are you talking about?
So we're gonna do this middle management style. That is what I'm where am I and I?
Supervise each of those circuit pieces will attach anywhere on this mine sweeper special numbers
You've got to watch out for covered numbers add together to give that piece a total value
If you can use all five pieces to hit all five target values the heater will be fixed
You know, I made this like that's how electricity works. Oh, yeah. Okay. Where'd you get your PhD in electricity again?
Are you sure I don't have to?
tighten a valve or
find a
valve under a mat and then screwed on to here I
So we need to have
If you know this much why haven't you tried to fix it yet. Hey if I had to do all the hard thinking around here
You'd be out of a job. So where'd you come from the United States? Hey me too. Where in the u.s. South
South I just like to get to know you a little I went to school and then I had a job and then I was married
And then I wasn't and now I have another job involving definitely legal treasure hunting activities
That's me, dude, I just smoked this everyone anyone who isn't paying me dude
I just I fucking smoke you want to write me a check. I can tell you a sad backstory and we both can pretend
It's real. Sorry. I left my checkbook at the lodge
It's smoked. I mean are you an open book with every stranger who crosses your path place it
No, I guess I don't like to talk about myself much either. What's your jam?
Witness protection program arch nemesis. None of those I guess it's that I meet so many interesting people. I just feel
Ordinary by comparison. That was a strangest wiring panel. I've ever seen but I think the heat's on you're electrocuting her
Toasty feels just like
By the vibe you've been up to Magnus's cabin yet. He has a cabin
Up in the hill keeps a key in her bag talk about refusing to let go but there's no way she'd ever give it to you
We'd find another way to get in there
Check out the cabin
Find a look. Okay. I need to know who has it who is pre I need a I found a radio
But I need a key to turn it can I borrow your key radio on board?
But I need a key to turn it on can I borrow yours?
Here you go, I wonder what minigame it is to kick her off the deck
Hey, that was it's called now against the ropes jump thing two feet. No forward. I don't have radio experience
land on stomach experience
Figures well, thanks. Anyway
Okay, I
Got the key. Bye. Bye
Bye now nice the heater works check out the cabin outside of town
Find a light
All right, I got the radio key, let's go check out the radio
room crew
Who what's this?
Who knows? I don't know something else fucked up. I can't do anything with it
Hey, can I get a just let's see who's here
I just need to know probably one in the chat if you're part of the drew crew. I need to know it's important to me
Where am I going?
I'm like in the basement. Where am I going?
What somebody just said fuck the Drew crew
All right, dude. Okay, man
Wow, sure. Can you believe what somebody just said? I can't believe somebody said that just that's disgusting behavior
It's disgusting to me. That's somebody said that I could do the battery
Wait, turn around. Can I go in any of these rooms go on this one? Alright, this is the captain's room
Each row column contains exactly two of each toy
No, not one of these both puffins are to the right of both dogs. No adjacent toys of the same kind
No ponies in the left half of the cupboard
Both dogs are somewhere to the left of both puffins. The puffins are between the ponies. The dogs are adjacent
Who was that a locator?
Here's your puzzle. This is not a puzzle
Wow an antique desk and it's in pristine condition
Time to break it open. I need to figure out the rules being used in each row here
Fill in the three squares to complete the sequence using each of the rows
one two
Let's I don't know three
Three two one three two plus three is five. I don't know three and
one and then
Uh, two two is four
Yeah, they they add
What about this? Does the color mean anything?
One to the two to the two to the three
That's just one two three
No, it's two to the one to the one to the three
What is somebody going to what does that sound is somebody in the bathroom?
That was weird
What's the solution? I don't care
This is not even puzzles
These are all right. I'm gonna say it and I don't like even
I don't know. I don't like saying this
I don't like saying this. I don't i'm gonna say it though
I'm gonna say this is
This is like this is boomer puzzle because this is like the shit that they do in a newspaper
This is a newspaper puzzle
This is not find who the murderer is or unravel the mystery. This is open up
page 16 of a newspaper
There's a this is
Come on, you should be good at it. Then read the newspaper
I don't like the way that it feels it. I don't like how it feels my hands
It's like weird and like sandy and crusty and it may it dry. I don't like it. I hate it
When I okay, those of you that don't get it next time you have a newspaper
on your person
Just like open it and like take and grab and like slide your fingers up and down it and touch it
Grab it. It's dry and gross and fucking I hate the way it feels. I fucking hate it. I hate it so much
Thinking about holding and turning and sliding and grabbing a newspaper makes me want to do. Ah, it's the worst
It's like nails on a chalkboard. Um, uh, just give me the solution. What is it?
All rows add up for five six seven eight nine all rows add up to nine. Thanks for that. Appreciate it
Five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven
eight nine
Uh, what two four five six seven eight nine?
so it actually was two to the three to the
six seven eight nine
Yeah, it was two to the three to the one
Three four five six seven eight nine five six seven eight nine. Wait one
Five six seven eight nine
One two, three six seven eight nine six seven eight nine. What do you that's not working?
Does this row meet? Hold on. Wait six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty fourteen
three
colors at the top
And what the hell does that matter does it have to be three in each row?
So five six seven eight nine
Two four five six seven eight nine
It has to be four red and three yellow. Okay, so that's one that's six seven eight nine
I don't think that's correct
three not two
Two three four five six seven eight nine
Why is it five another key? How many keys do we have?
See this one has lines on it so that means you can tell i don't care
Screenshot it if you care about it
A code I have to hold this up
Looks like one of these words is scrambled with no no
Magnus just saved
Games from the newspaper. He was gonna do this later. This has nothing to do with anything
You think it does?
But it doesn't
Okay
uh clue
Do I have to get all of these?
I have to get every single one. No, I don't
See clue
What is a what is a clue?
Is that what the english spelling of clue?
a clue
Okay, uh
Yeah
Drew clue
Where is it? I need to find that first. I don't care about anything else
See just look for c's
see
No, what does it just want me to click them? That's not word search
Yeah
Uh, I thought it was a word search
Oh, no, this is bad. This is gonna be horrible
C l e w is it why is it not scratched off?
Same row. Oh god c l e
Fuck same row
I don't know same row
c l e w
There's none of these are in the same row. What do you mean? I'm still not doing it. What what are you talking about?
They have to be horizontal
This is stupid though
But who cares?
I
Bilge let's look for bilge
Bilge ain't up here
How about bosun?
I want puzzles. This is not a puzzle
No, I want this is i'm gonna give you some audio of what a puzzle is, okay
That's what a puzzle is
Not click on d
I spell bilge
It's a puzzle
Just just click on words in a row
All right, let's bow spirit
david
gaff
uh
Guy B
Guy B no
Hosser
Helm bosun what do you mean? Did I did I skip that one?
This is this this is some cereal box shit. All right, you can't this is cereal box shit
This is advanced cereal box
There's no no, there's no s t there's no e
bilge
And i'm gonna have to go down too, aren't I?
I have to go down
Do you see this? I have to go down
No, I don't c n d
None of this is gonna work. Oh god
All right. How about what's this one? Jack stay? This looks like jack stay
Okay
What a pain in the ass
Bottom right of the screen. What are you talking about? I'm not clicking the bottom right of the screen
Don't you dare try to get me out of here
read the notes
Left click to select a letter from a row right click to select or for a column. Hmm
So, uh, okay with r
y'all
Purser no stop
Oh, sir stern i'm just doing i'm i'm gonna go one at a time here
to
rake
Ra is our k. No
Spar it's probably at spar
Okay, that this is done. Nothing else goes here. Don't touch anything here
All right. The next one we've got uh, second row is done. Let's do second. Here we go
No, oh no t lull, right luff
Okay, okay, we have third third is done now, let's do
uh
keel haul keel haul no
rake
uh rake no
transom
transom rake
There's no a I can't click that because this is this is david. I need to change the a
No, fuck
Okay rake now we are in row four which is
um
keel hedge
Purser ha ha sir
ha sir
Resident sleeper write another letter
I'm halfway done with this
Don't worry. We're almost out of this. No, we're not not even close
This is the droid crew
All right. Now we get we gotta go this way
uh
Anything with f's anything with f's or b's
bilge no
jib
jib no gaff g
Okay, good. Now we gotta go down
uh
helm
kej
Yep
shit
Is there another g f um
wait
No, there's no other g is
There's two g's where
I got it
It's fine. Oh big brain big brain big brain big brain big brain
Stop. Okay. Let's go this way. We can go
um keel haul it looks like it's gonna be keel haul
keel haul and then
Stern s t e. Yep stern
uh
jib give no bilge
Got it. Okay. What about down here?
uh, we got
Pem
uh
Occam
helm
jib no
p e p
This one's purser
purr
Uh-oh purr
Oh, it's not purse sore. It's purse or
Oh shit. No, no, no, this is wrong
uh
Par what was this one spar?
Do this one up here maybe spar?
Spar
Okay
batman oakham asylum
I think it's something it's messed up somewhere. I don't know where
rib
See
It has to be clue, but when what happens to the top?
Clue but then what happens up here? What does this turn into?
mash
jib
Oh, all right, let's go
What down here?
Soon su no
uno
Bose spirit what?
This whole thing is messed up. Let's go to the next row. I'm going all the way again. Uh, let's go
Possibly be this
true
Purr, uh, it's per has to be purser has to be
or gib
gib is
Oh, no, here's jib
And then this is yeah, here's y'all
Are there two y'alls?
What happened to keel hole?
Where's gib?
This I think this row is completely wrong
Bose spirit. That's that one's not happening
He wait, I need an e
All right, we're good. We're good. We're good now we need
Wait, one, two, three, four five one, two, three, four. One of these is a bait word
transom
Oakham this is wrong
oakham
Does it know they?
shit
Fix keel hall
I don't know where
Wait, oh, there's no l a key hall
key hall, um
uh
Then what happens to this?
There's no more luff anymore
Lu is it two f's there wait there is
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good
Oh, let's go spar is wrong
Second to last row is bow spirit. No, wait, wait, wait, get back back back back back back
bow
spirit
Ja jab
It was good. What?
It's bow spirit. I just did it
bow spirit
Oh, it's
I don't know what a bow sprit is. I thought it was
Spirit
I got it. There's one more in here and it's def. It's definitely purser. It has to be or oakham
Oakham or purser or hauser. Wait, is it hauser?
Oakham purser hauser transom
Where's hauser?
keel hall
hauser
Okay. Wait, wait, wait. I can do it. I can do it
purser
pu
There's no r this is wrong
There's no other u in here though. There's no u. There's no u. There's no there's no u
First column is boston
No, stop stop stop stop stop stop. I'm gonna blow this whole thing
Boston is transom
What?
Hauser is the top row
Transom is instead of boston
Really?
Now, where's boston? What is bob? Wait, okay now we uh spar spar is right here. I need an a
s
p
Where's an a?
Which one can I take purser and oakham? I can't do that with this
Spar is on the far left
Isn't that where the other that's where that is?
bottom is oakham
But what happens to the
Okay, then that
Oakham, but now I need a k. Wait. How about I set this is a
rake
spar
purser purser what
purser
All right, um purser
spar s
p
A I can't take an a from anywhere
a
um
Something's wrong here. This is not david. This is something else. What is this fix david?
No, that's not right keel hall
Move the a on keel hall to the right
spar whoa
David was what happened to y'all was y'all
right
y'all david
Got it
Hey looks complete
What can I use this for?
I don't know
he
Draw figured this figured out the sounding depth the numbers
What the hell he?
I can't even interact with it
Write these down on a piece of paper
I'm gonna try the locator. Yeah, that's what I was thinking. It doesn't seem to do anything
Take a picture of it. Oh good idea
Got it
What the hell is this man didn't open I just I gotta keep searching I gotta keep searching
What about here hourglasses anything to do with anything?
I think I need to get all the wooden sections pressed down. What's going on? Oh down. They have to be pressed
God damn it. Did I what I won the secret egg?
Okay, I got I got the egg. What does that do? Yeah that that that deserves quite a few
of the
That thing that people say when something crazy happens and scary and I don't know what the fuck
Dude
I'm concerned about it
bed
Put egg in bed hatch egg on bed
What this what's this here for?
Pro bar
More clues haven't done that
What else is in here? Oh a suitcase
Can you pet dog in nancy drew?
Shadow on the ocean. Yes
They look who is this still to find clues for this shit. I better find some pins first. Wait
This is um
Isn't this it?
No
Hold up a piece of paper pins
What do I get pins?
Those cities are one-letter names
Yeah, I can't wait to go to gee
I wonder if that's why she called me instead of going to the police about magnus
Have you been running your mouth hope you realize it's going to take a lot of dough to make this disappear
Iceland government reports big treasure to be found
All right, where the pins?
I'm apparently still not done in this office. I guess not
Let's go talk shit. She's not here anymore. I got a lot of stuff
Jeremy, can you pass the cereal box? No
You guys remember when I was gonna do the stream?
where
I bought a shitload of cereal boxes and we did all the activities on just put the camera on
And then I had I realized
that you
That would be so
horrible
Because what I would what I actually would end up doing
I would have
20 30 plus cereal boxes in this room
and I would
Be drawn on them and shit and then i'm thinking what am I going to do with this much cereal?
Uh
And I could I could only donate it to like a food like a food pantry
Then that's makes sense. But then all the boxes would be wicked fucked up
And that's like maybe I could take the bags out
Right, like take the bags out and just keep the boxes and then recycle the boxes
And then donate the bags
Would that make sense?
Does it put labels on the bags?
Do you think they would care if you did the puzzles on the box?
Well, no, but I mean, I I don't know
It's am I I don't know. It might be like messy
what if I like
Mess up and I get angry and I like oh god, I like stabbed the box a bunch of times
He's fucking bad. I didn't think everyone laughs
You know what i'm saying?
I I need batteries for my flashlight
Wait, let's go check on a couple things here. Let's go talk to you. I got some shit to tell you
Uh, I need to know some things
Who was present at the time of the festival raging at a cereal box? Who else did you see only gunner elizabeth and soren were thoroughly mia
Although half of iceland is probably related to itself. So people kind of look alike could have missed something
How'd you meet magnus? I heard about the rumor of the treasure through my connections then I approached him
He's a hard guy to pin down that blind up all the cereal and glue it to your hair
I just happened to come in at an opportune moment
Magnus do with a treasure. Why would I do that desperately wants to buy his own ship true? Not true
That makes no sense. Ship guys are like that
So the ship he helped rebuild isn't his we funded it, but it's town property
Uh, how long were you working on that ship project?
About two years on and off of it magnus supervised the rebuilds. I provided the cash
That's a long time to hang around in iceland. Have you been in skip rot all that time?
No, I think the locals would have offed me by now if that were the case
I don't like to stay in one place for too long. She's not quite 30 fps
If you stay in one place people start to need you and feel things about you and all that icky weird stuff
I'm not really the having friends type. I'd like to think you and I are on friendly terms
What is this are we gonna hold hands and sing campfire songs now, I don't want to do it but find my gold
Later, I want to do it
I wonder like every
I can't say this because if people want me to do it and they're just gonna annoy the fuck out of like half the people here
They really will people will be as if it was just leave and shit
Like whatever
I want to just like play like we can loud party music and put an echo in my voice every five minutes and like be like
Where's the drew crew?
Just to make sure you guys are still watching but of course you are
Like where's the drew crew at the club like we're at the club. I don't know
Do you have any batteries in here? Hi
Do you have anything which might help with my investigation?
If i'm not in town, i'm always locked up in here. I do have some very nice pamphlets though
The pamphlet lovers journal rated them a nine star out of ten. I put them together myself
Here's one for your troubles
Give me it's hard to turn down an award-winning pamphlet. I'll see if I can make use of this
Oh, okay
Ding dingies. Hey sailors. Did you know every year in iceland roughly 0.8 out of every 100,000 citizens die of drowning?
How does 80% of you drown? What one per I don't get that
or approximately 2.6
Wait, what?
Because modern science has not made it possible to save six-tenths of a person from drowning
Caution while out on the seas can be the most important factor in saving a life. It's an average
Oh
Know your motor proper voltage must be flowing to jump start a broken motor
As a handy guy remember these standard recommended voltages 16.9
Ooh
Until utila hooks scraping barnacles easy pancake flipping
threatening political dissenters
Thanks, soren
You're kind of a psycho. All right
Uh, I sent some bad blood between you and gunner blood between you and gunner
It's more like gunner dumping bad blood onto me
Repeatedly while laughing. I try to be patient given his
History, but what a nanderthal that one. I can't reason with a man who only speaks fist
Between you and me he's never been the same since that terrible crash years ago
Didn't within the boat just crash
Don't know that it's my place to speak of it
But his boat sank to the bottom of the bay and he hasn't sailed since now. He stays locked up in that pub of his
So you attended the festival, right?
present and accounted for naturally
Interesting dagny says you weren't there. Why would she lie about that up in old stulka manning the controls for our audio
That's the tower right outside this center mind if I take a look very rarely look up I found which is a shame
Lots of nifty things in that direction
Mind if I take a look later?
Bye now
The bitcoin crash. Hey soren, can I use some of this gift wrap? Yes
Great now how about a magic egg? That would be fun to get
Oh
I guess it's gonna all right. It's the
That
Okay, I hope somebody wants this I need batteries
I'll need to earn some money first
Do I actually have to go do the language things the only way to make money?
batteries
I can afford that
Get him in the get him in
All right. I got a flashlight. Let's go to the cave
Buy the sword. I don't have any money to buy the sword. Not yet
Sort of riot you don't have to riot. That'd be fine. That's where it gets scary
It's a glove
Wonder who it belongs to it belongs to the icebreaker
The local town in iceland's favorite professional wrestler
somebody in the ice
What's in the ice?
Dean dingus. No, I don't know why okay
What's in there?
I'm gonna need to melt this eventually
There's nothing here. What about this looks suspicious
These rocks. No, what was the point of even coming in here? I have to go back to the captain's quarters. Apparently I missed something
I got this toy bullshit the locator
I did get the radio key. Let me go up there
This is this is oh, she's back
Hey, yo, what's up? Can I help?
Yep
What's behind the door? So what's behind the mystery door?
Just an old broom closet. Can I see?
No
Not even a hint go away
Hey nancy
I spent a lot of time out here. Don't you have somewhere else to be?
Can you tell me about the festival sound system?
It's been broken for a week soren told me he was manning the sound system on the morning
The hierlich hide crashed what but that's not possible
There was no sound that day sounds like we've got an alibi that doesn't quite match either you're lying or he is
And i'll find out
Is there anything more you haven't told me about magnus? No
Guess you'll have to leave now
No sound
You know i'm better than anyone. I don't believe that for an instant
You know him better than anyone. Wait, what? I don't know him an instant
Didn't she didn't respond to that
I need your help elizabeth. I need to know what you know better than anyone
He is quiet
Keep me obsessive
first over his dog
Then over his writing then over me
Then over the ship why would someone like him be hiding for gold in the first place he has certain
He just wants treasure which we go mega lull maniac
He desperately wants to leave town leave island. I thought he was a captain already. Oh, he is
but for wealthy people
Private clients never his own boat never his own destination. He dreams of living like the old captains
Sailing wherever the wind takes the treasure not real. I see so the treasure would allow him to fulfill that dream
It's gonna be an old wooden leg and mongus left some guys dentures after we broke up. He called me looking for it
Secret map it looks like it might be the key to open some kind of box
But i've never seen any box like that before. I don't know why I kept it for myself
Maybe I wanted to see whatever it was. He saw it. Yeah, dude
Lines continue across the gap interesting
Numbers appear to show the number of touching sections which have been filled
Must find all five pieces to reveal these two by five. Okay
Uh intricate moving. Thanks elizabeth. I'm going to get to the bottom of this mess
We're gonna get to the bottom of this mess
but first
Just want to just give a quick little check to see to make sure we have uh
Those of you that are here with us
That are part of a very specific crew
I want you I want you to put oh I give up on that one. I'm not doing that
That was like a yeah, nah not into it
Has anyone checked magnus's cabin? No
I
Wanted to but you didn't or can't
Soren wants to do it. I had to get really high energy there and I'd
Can you help me find a way in?
No, this town takes care of its own
Our problems are ours. No one else is
Goodbye. Bye now. I was dancing. Wow. He's low energy
I'm getting in this fucking door
All right, where's the radio?
up here, right
All right. Here's the key to the radio
That's a radio, right? Where's this radio high energy low iq?
Where's the radio?
Where's this radio?
There it is. All right radio key
Turn it
Hello. Hello. Hmm. No one's there
Guess again. Oh, who is this? Wait? I'm not sure. Why are you you're under investigation now for the murder of
His name ken. Why don't I say ken operator alex lintrong speaking. Hi alex. I'm nancy
Hi, i'm nancy. I'm a detective trying to find out more. No, no, no, no, no, you don't go you don't i'm
Like don't I legally have to say i'm a cop?
Well, you have to be like before I say anything have to be like, oh that's great. By the way, i'm a detective with
You know, I do have to say that
You you legally have to you know, you legally have to say i'm a police officer. By the way, here's the rest of my sentence
That's in that's just movie shit
Why why am I saying that like cops are like what like a vampire if they're like a lot like wait
I know that wait. Hold on a minute. If if the cop comes to your door
Do you and they say can we come in?
If you invite them in
Hold on. I mean, I don't know these laws
All I know about police is through television
Does a cop have to announce they are a cop to you?
Does it does that have to happen?
Do cops have to tell you that they are a cop?
No, this is perfectly legal in most jurisdictions
Your question repeats one that is often asked as people for some reason assume that dishonesty by a police officer should always lead
To a dismissal it is only police tactics that could deprive you of some constitutional right that would lead to suppression of evidence in a subsequent dismissal
It's not entrapment
Entrapment does not simply mean that you were tricked into getting caught
Entrapment means that the police persuaded you to commit a crime. You had no intention of committing at the outset
In your case you intended to buy drugs all along you didn't just intend to get caught. There's no way what?
You aren't a police officer
Why i'm a detective
I'm a vampire. You shouldn't have done that
Well, like you know, like okay
I am a person outside your door
Yes, who is it?
I'm a cop. I'm a vampire
Can we come in?
Um, no, thank you
how does it
vampire cop
I'm a detective trying to find out more about magnus
Come back with a warrant vampire
I don't know if I can tell you why not vampire is just like
Can I come in? I just want to take a look around but you gotta invite me in first
Come back with a warrant. Okay
I'll come back with a warrant
Slow down and stay calm. I need your help. If what you're saying is true magnus might be in serious danger
Why would you write that?
All right, i'm back i'm back with up with my with my warrant
I'm back. Can I come in fuck? I put more on
That's been notarized
Can you imagine that's how you had to notarize documents?
This is the way that you notarized documents
Yeah, I need to get I need to get this bank statement notarized. Oh just one moment, sir
Okay, there you are
That's just the official
Let's go, but you don't have to handle this alone
I heard a voice on board. I mean he went to go check it out left the radio on
I'm not using that much lipstick. This is expensive lipstick
That's not what it is. I think this investigation just went from missing persons to abduction
It's dark out there and the water's cold
What brand is it? I don't know
um
Okay, this
This lipstick is called the the countess
countess
This vampire lipstick
this 20 bucks
pretty good
Could you hear anything magnus said something about the ship? That's all I got. I I was too scared
Who are you by the way? Just a lowly undergrad
A cubicle a pair of headphones and a computer. I'm here on an internship for my maritime psychology degree
My parents said I'd never find a paying job
Shows them me and magnus we were kind of buddies. I mean, we never met or anything
You guys don't know what the what the color is
All right, are you?
You don't sound Icelandic though. Nope
Massachusetts, so what are you doing here?
No, no, no, no those of you that are saying, oh wow
Really? I'm gonna laugh pink red
No
No, you don't understand
There are like four or five thousand different
red shades
Of lipstick that have different names
It's it's like willy wonka guys
It's not just pink
No
Schnauzberry red, that's what i'm saying
Lipstick colors seriously may as well just have they may as well be create the crayola
There's a box of crayola. It's like 5 000 different shades
And they all call them different things
I need a way to distract someone on board this ship so you can snoop through their stuff can't
Very good
Yeah, I can help what do I do hold up klepto. I've got a favor to ask. Okay name your price
There's a lighthouse near skip rock
But the light's busted right now if you can get up there and fix that light
Where's the lighthouse I can stay here at hq with my cup of tea and giant snuggle blanket
I'll give it a whirl my cell number is nine seven eight five five five. Oh one three nine
Give me a call when you're standing in front of the light. I'll tell you what to do next
Wait, is this actually cat bondi? I don't know
She's probably had this lipstick for like three years
Calling who am I calling?
What on earth is a maritime psychology degree? I have a 30 page thesis answering exactly that question
It can all be boiled down to two words
Interesting
Is he eating it?
I'm not eating it. I'm not I don't you don't eat lipstick. You don't well people somebody said that you eat crayons
I'll tell you some lipstick
I don't know why I mean, maybe I do know why
There are some lipsticks and glosses that smell like candy and cakes and and pudding and stuff
And I have come very very close
To this one in particular that
All the all the girls in high school when I was in high school
They all used this it was this cake batter
um
Lip gloss stuff and it smelled like a vanilla baking vanilla frosting cake thing
And I know I just I just wanted somebody to put a little bit on my finger and let me just eat it
I probably did if I was like, hey, can I
Like could you put like a little bit like on this paper and I can like put my finger on and eat it
Thanks for sub. What are you talking about?
Show so show kuji. Thanks for the subs that no that had that did happen. Thanks for the five community subs
You're right. That did just happen. Well, why did you say that?
Do remember the lip that lipstick is made from beeswax and whale vomit
Get the fuck out of here. Wait
What is lipstick? It's made out of clay or something lips. What is lipstick made out of?
It's like it's clay
Wax clay, whatever. Here it is
uh, it's made from
Here. Okay
It's made from like fruit pigments
fruit pigment
Strawberries are first juiced and then dehydrated into a powder. That's pretty cool
the powder is then soaked in oil to extract pigments and blended into a mixture of shea and cocoa butter done and then
Rice starch provides opacity giving the lipstick long-wearing coverage
right, and then
Uh candle candelilla wax from the candelilla plant allows the lipstick to hold its shape and then there it is
Yeah, it's made of the clay
Then they add the whale vomit. Okay. Well, what does it say that?
Oh wait, sorry
That's it. That's one brand of lipstick like I told you this by the way
I said there's like a thousand shades of crayola for lipstick. There's also a thousand crayola brands of lipstick
There's a thousand different boxes of brands of this shit. Okay. Hold on. What does lipstick met is listed is lipstick made out of whale sperm
What?
The fuck is lipstick made out of okay. This is ridiculous
You want to know what the top search is for what is lipstick made out of what the suggestions are
What animal is lipstick made from is lipstick made out of bugs?
is
Makeup made out of poop. What why would you put poo in?
Is there bad?
Wait
Hold on a second
I didn't scream. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is the best reveal of the night. Are you ready?
Here comes the best reveal of the night
Oh, this is gonna be fantastic
I can't wait for you to see this. Give me one second so I can get it on the screen
We're gonna slowly go through this
I love this so much
Why are people searching this it makes no this is make any sense
Hold on I got it. I got i'm bringing it over
What are you talking about isn't I have no space to save an image
That's what
No, okay, wrong drive. All right. Here we go. I want to make sure that you guys don't get the reveal too quickly
Because it's fucking ridiculous
This is to what?
this is
You gotta be fucking kidding me. This is so stupid. Here we go. I need this reveal to be
legit
Okay, you ready?
This is what you get for searching. What is lipstick made out of?
Is lipstick made out of bugs
Is makeup made out of poop?
Is there sperm in lip gloss?
Is there whale poop in makeup?
Is maybelline vegan?
I don't know interesting is fenty beauty vegan
Is mica safe in lipstick?
Oh, I wonder what the next one might be. Yeah
Is there bad poop in Doritos?
Why I
Is there
It won't make a bad poop in it. Is there bad poop in lipstick?
Why wouldn't there be bad poop in Doritos?
Oh
Is there oh, is there bat poop in Doritos?
This boy there's bat shit in Doritos. That's real
There are common ingredients in many food products called guanine which sounds and looks a lot like guano
Another term is guanylate which comes from guanylic acid, which is an active ingredient in Doritos
This term also is also confused as being a root derivative of the term bat feces
But it's not it's not it's just is there bat poop in why would that be linked?
Is there bat poop in energy drinks
Everyone why does everybody think?
And then people get even more
People just get curious
Why
Would somebody search for I don't miss people. I I swear to god robots search for stuff
It's not possible
I guess maybe I maybe I when you're lying in bed at like four in the morning and just like yeah
Let's just fucking do I don't know
All right, we're gonna reveal this one, too
And I don't know what it is about this thing in particular
What is it up with this animal in particular? I don't get it
Is sperm made out of poop?
Okay, here we go, here's the new one
Starting us off nicely we have
Oh, I think I fucked it up. Oh shit. I fucked it up. No
No
Wait, okay. I got it. Okay. Here we go
No, no, no, no, it's wrong. It's wrong. It's wrong
God damn it. Stop. Why is it doing this? I'm trying to do the stupid reveal
All right, who cares? Here we go. Don't do that again. You're making me upset
Here we go
Okay. So is there bat poop in mascara?
What is bat poop used in?
Is there bat poop in energy energy drinks?
What is with bats?
Is the sodium guan like bat feces?
Gets better
Is bat poop a delicacy?
Where is guano found and by the way, is it toxic?
So I can eat it
How do you clean up bat poop?
How do you identify bat poop so I can eat it make sure it's not poisonous
And then clean it up
Look at these
I this is not me. This is other people that somebody else wrote this
Can I eat it?
Where do I find it? Will it make me sick? How do I clean it up? And how do I know where it is?
in a row
Is it bat poop in Doritos?
Oh
I can't I have to play nancy drew
Let's go. Have you met dagny? What's his image? What are you talking about? Is it bat poop in the stream?
I know i've seen that image of my mouth
jeez
christ guys
Why do I keep looking up bat shit?
I know i've seen i've seen i've seen it. I've seen it. I've seen it. Crayola taste test when
Sounds like her
I've always tried to get information about magnus's flight apart. I'm not showing that on stream. It's gonna scare people. I'm so disorganized
I can't match my thought colors, let alone keep records of magnus's charting
She always wanted to know when he'd be gone. I never told her obviously. What was she trying to do in his absence?
No clue, but I imagine how fucked up we've gotten as a society
Imagine how that explains why she's been hanging around. We have become
Were you as a person?
Are sitting somewhere and you need to look up if there is bat shit in your food
How did we get here?
I just was curious today
Am I eating animal shit?
I might be that's why i'm concerned to look what did you mean by daily logs earlier?
There are these logs i'm supposed to fill out whenever a vessel passes through us. So are they filled out kind of I turn
It's better than the old days when you ate bat shit
Versus guessing if it might be trace amounts in your food. I
That is kind of true. How cool are we talking?
What do you mean my thumbnail
What do you know about soren that guy who runs the festival yes
Always seems like there's something just under the surface with that one cheerful and yet angry
Like he was holding something back. They say show the link for the vod. Oh my god
Who even is this character?
I don't even know who this is
No, that's scary. I'm not showing that one. You'll have to find that one. It's somebody from monsters inc
No, that one's scary. I don't want i'm not showing that one. It's scary
Give me give me the monsters inc one
Who is this? What character is this?
What's this character's name?
It's called for
ferg
fergus
that
When I that's not
That when I type that's not who I get. That's not who I get
um
What's uh
What's this? What's this fucking thing's name monsters inc?
Fergie
This is not there's no people in monsters and called fergo
Ferg what's this thing's name fungus
Show the edit i'm not showing the edit fungus in the scream extractor. What does he do?
I'm muting this. I just want to know who he is
I've never seen this movie. I don't know what it says
How would you even
Uh, we have to play after this. It's so cute. Why is it so big?
It's it sucks his lips up
they do and by day
I actually just need
Have you been talking on the phone for like 30 minutes? What can you tell me about? I just don't even totally
My items my inventory
Oh interesting any other information for me
Updated it's called ship facts want to hear about it. I sure I guess sure educate me. Well, sure
Why is that try bringing it like an english sailor with no formal education?
Please look up more bat shit facts. Hey, that's pretty neat
I paid 450 channel points for this and there are no refunds
Can I hear another ship fact? How about this before?
1865 captains sometimes had difficulty finding people interested in joining their crew
So they just started kidnapping them
They pay a big guy to go around a popular harbor
Not young men unconscious and not wake them up until they were far out that shit facts another shit fact
One particularly evil press gang or even threw himself a fake birthday party specifically to attract kidnapping victims
Of course justice was served when he himself was press ganged a few years later. I have a crush on this intern
What are you talking about? I'm out of here
No, i'm not putting the image of the scary one up i'm not putting the scary image up
No, you'll have to find that one. Baud watcher is good luck. Find that one. It's scary
Not quite. No, no, where's the blogging?
I'm gonna go to the lighthouse
Lighthouse lighthouse. I got it. I got it. I got it
All right, where's how do I get to the lighthouse?
Where's the light
It looks like the original hell someone made off with some of the decorations though
Uh an egg
I don't know
All the elements and a gun
turn
Show image now show I wouldn't even have suckered puzzles. I haven't even done one in like 40 minutes
We've been too busy looking up bat facts
All right, I need to get to the lighthouse
How do I get to the lighthouse from here?
fuck
Prepare the lighthouse find and return the helms missing decorations
Figure out the sounding depth numbers search for clues. Check out the cabin outside of town find a light to use in the ice caves
Oh, I still have to do that
That's done. Can't check that off yet. Get in. Okay, can't check that off yet. Still have to do that. What?
What the how do I do anything?
If this section of the original ship was removed then maybe others were too
That was pointless
dude, I
I seriously I can't where am I supposed to go?
Go to the lighthouse
That image is fucked up. I know why do you think I don't want to show it because it's actually terrifying
Yeah
Elizabeth seems like she's withholding information
She still seems pretty intense about magnus as far as I can tell and she thinks the treasure belongs to her
I've seen some exes do some German
Looks like the other mother from core line. That's why when I end a relationship, I just move to a different continent and change
What?
Uh-oh
Fuck yeah. Yep
Yeah
My phone number so much easier than doing the whole breakup thing
That must be exhausting just quit the fucking game
I can't really do mailing addresses anymore quit the game. I'm
Make the game larger the game is it's from I can't
I can't okay. How do I?
I want solutions
I want solutions to problems
What do I do the egg?
The drew crew is just getting started. That's right
Don't don't let any
Drew crew naysayers tell you
That with the way that we're done playing nancy drew are streaming on upset
Two games done 30 to go. That's right
He's crying
No, i'm not
Oh, this looks like a door
lighthouse
No, how's it what what has happened? What the fuck just happened? Why I can't go up
Well, I need to go to sleep
I have to go to bed
Right, remember she was like, oh, yeah, you got I gotta go to sleep now
How do you sleep in this game
It was doom
Can I go to bed speak up now?
Soren told me about your boat crash
He will pay for a wagon
Seinfeld
Do we still have do we still have drew supporters in the chat right here
Is i'm gonna need to see a one miles away and he's a stranger forever
Well, that seems unfair to soren
Unfair means nothing you think because a culture is unfair. It will change for you. That is not the world
That is not skip bro. Later
Later would you like eggs?
Egg
Okay, um
Seinfeld theme you got it
I tried
Um, I need to sleep go to bed sleep somehow go to sleep go to fucking sleep
go to
sleep
Where's my cabin?
How do I go to bed?
This means something what does this mean?
How do I go to bed give me a walkthrough I love nancy drew
See ya. What is this called?
Just open up a walkthrough. Who cares?
What do I need to do?
Game boomers don't what is okay. There it is cheats
All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah explode the port the snowmobile
The misty skip that's what it is. That's where nancy is staying and it has a pub. So how do I sleep there?
All right, get on the ship
Uh, we did the knot. Yeah, I remember that part. We did the that part. Okay, we did this part
Uh, okay, uh take the lighthouse key got that
Okay, so we need to go wait we go go to the cupboard inside the captain's quarters
This is not captain's quarters game
Where's the captain's quarters?
They're like down here. I don't know
All right cupboard where's the cupboard let me see a cupboard cupboard you're out of the dru crew. How dare you?
How dare you?
Remove me from the dru crew. I am the original dru crew member
To the largest don't I get a piece of paper two three two. No
No, what is this? What is this 80? What was it? What was the number 84?
No cheating. I'm not cheating. I got the pins. I needed check it out
Check it out
Check it out. Okay. Check it out. Check it out. Check it out. Okay place some pins
Uh, what am I doing here? What is that? Where's that paper that has this stuff on it?
You guys know what i'm talking about. Where is it? To my phone s r d
a
s r d c u j l
s r d uh
Do I just have to put the pins just there? I guess I
e v f w m e that's not correct
e v s r d
S r this makes no sense. The order doesn't matter
e v f w m
All right, close it then e
v
f w
M
uh
e v f w m j l u c
j l u c
j
l u
c
D r s do that is not
Not cute
d r
This is one of the sounding numbers magnus was looking for
What the hell does this do for me 14?
86 14
Okay
Is that for the number wheel?
Didn't work
8614 was that your iceland was discovered
That didn't even happen yet. What are you talking about? What are you saying is nonsense?
All right, i'm going to sleep
I know how to sleep. I have to go to the to the misty, uh, the misty mountain whatever it's called
Sleep sleep sleep illegal horn
If you want to sleep climb the stairs to the lodging floor and automatically wake up later
This is me waking up. Why did I need to sleep for?
Uh day two, this is like day 30. I've done this like a bunch of times
Did this walkthrough is
This walkthrough is so behind
He's cheating
I'm only cheating when I have to I have to play all three parts of that stupid ass story
That's not a stupid story. Is it a is it a dumb story? Is this like a made-up story?
Go outside the time. I can't go outside of town
Oh the cave
These caverns can be accessed directly from skip bro and are open for tours
Skip, okay. What does this mean?
What do I do with this info? I don't know
You're addicted to enancy true
I just want to see the end. No, I don't I just want to see like halfway through
Yeah, it's mostly halfway through
Then you got this guy getting new info
What's your relationship like with elizabeth presently quite poor? She won't allow certain
Members of the restoration team to access their work you mean dagny. Yes, but
Overall, she's quite a peach that one the only one who's ever shown me kindness
And the other half is happening tomorrow
I don't I I don't think we're doing too
Rocked the local mountains to their very core. I wonder if he's checked his voicemail since
Play ai dungeon now. I was planning on it
Did you lock magnus's cabin yes
No one should be going in there until the authorities search everything. Why not call the police believe me?
I want to but I live life one step away from an angry mob on my doorstep
Why do you think I stay in the culture center don't do tomorrow?
Ai dungeon tomorrow. Yeah, I guess sure
Well, you guess you could lie about it. You said two drew streams after jump night
That's that's correct still
So you're afraid to contact the police and no one else will it's less that i'm terrified and more than
Actually, yes, i'm terrified in these parts vigilante efforts are very much the norm
Even if the nancy drew dungeon, no one would talk. I hate to admit it, but it's up to us to crack this case. That sounds fun
Bye-bye
All right. I gotta let me let me go back to the uh, let me go back to the instruments
I gotta get that seinfeld theme, correct?
Where i'm looking for a uh, hold on a minute here. I'm just trying to take a look around the musical instruments
Just want to check something out real quick
Just want to quickly
Uh, I need to how do I open this I think I can open this
It should open why is it not opening why would it because i'm cheating and it says I can open it
That's a lang spill, right?
Open the lang spill
I can't open it
Yeah, what about it
Open the round case on the lang spill and see different pattern on each side of the decoration
This is the boomer strategy. The boomer guy doesn't work
Nancy doesn't know you can open it
What?
What do you mean nancy doesn't know you can open it. She doesn't know I have to know that I have to go get the
I did everything out of order from the guide. I haven't triggered that yet
I need to find a note
Where's this guy's note?
Okay, get the hook
I'm not done. No, i'm not done. This is not end of the stream voice. Don't even think about it
Vibe and chat vibe and chat here. I got it. I got you. I got you. I got you
I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you
Here go ahead. You guys can like vibe
All right, um, let's ship
Let's see. I got tools and I need to find a note
Get the key
Okay. Yeah sketch pieces crow's nest already did it
Go inside the wheelhouse. What the hell is that?
What's the wheelhouse?
All right, read the letters inside the box
Examine the box nancy says all the wooden sections should be pressed down inside that box there and there's letters in there
Let's go. Let's go read them
You guys vibing here?
Better be where's that dumbass box? I'm not vibing
Are you kidding? Are you serious?
Hey nancy
What are you talking about? You're not vibing
I
You spend a lot of time. You're really fucking with my vibe here
If you're not vibing
In case of a ship emergency i'm responsible. You don't know what that means
No, you're right. I don't
What does it mean?
I actually don't know what the actual doesn't do
Two people are vibing is to say that they're enjoying each other's company and converse easily
I was saying it wrong. I thought like vibing means like you just like hanging out and chilling
Things break suddenly and it's hard to hear the alarm from the harbor
I see
interesting
Goodbye, I need to get in that bag too
I'm not vibing right now
I need to get I need to read the stupid letters in here
Get me the
Okay, where's this dumbass thing?
Where's the box? What was that stupid box?
Why does everybody hide all this shit?
You like hiding hiding a picture of you and your dog. What are you doing? Is this where is it?
Where is it?
No, I already did this
I already did this I have to do this again
They've all got to be they've all got to be depressed down. All right open give me these damn
I wrote this
Dear elizabeth. Hi, I miss you
Love santa. Okay
Fine, we can get a tree. No two decorations never decorations. The book is coming along. Well, okay cool
What's your sense of holiday cheer?
Assistant over this long open the lang spill
Love you
Well, dude, if you did you you put them in a box behind a weird puzzle
Like if I want kim to look at in the lang spill i'm gonna just set texture and say hey honey
Look in the lang spill
It's like when me and kim want to go to dominoes
I don't just it's not like oh, hey kim, uh, by the way
I'd like for you to figure out here to open up my sphere of puzzles to see what I want you to do today
Cursed cursed cursed. You're welcome
What is this a new image? This link gives me a virus
I mean, I won't be I won't be clicking that one again
What okay? Yeah, the lang spill lang spill
lang spill
close close
Here we go. We got progress now. Thank you boomer gamers
There it is. It's subtle, but I see some differences in the halves of this pattern
Find the differences between the two mirrored sides
Now there's a lot. Okay, let's start at the bottom
Uh, there's three fingers
There is this one says no, okay. That's that one
um
There's no more
Cool a carved star. What am I supposed to do with that now? Oh, hey. Hey, Clarissa
Um, so what's this what's this? What was this one? What would I do now?
I'm just experiencing a walkthrough. No, nobody said that but I said that it's not what's going on. It's not what's going on
Let's go fix the dinghy motor
Somebody said boomer humor
You know boomer humor would be if I gave you like a quote from I love Lucy
Not Clarissa explains at all
What?
Let's fix this thing, huh?
Open it up
Okay. All right translate these first
Let's see. Where's that cool note?
Where's that cool note?
It's okay. I have it over here in the walkthrough
All right, so we need the voltage to be
um
What are you talking about do I
There it is I got the thing to translate voltage total
so there's my
My dinghy 16 9 19 13
I don't have any spark plugs
Will I open that thing?
I know what I have to do
Hello
Not quite yet need your help
What not quite yet
What the fuck are you talking about?
Where do you get this where the spark plugs guys find on page spark plugs
I don't I don't care about this. I know that I got a guy in the dru crew saying like I don't care
I mean, what I what do you want me to tell you?
You think i'm gonna walk around in circles to try to find?
The one place where this is
That
Who the fuck wow, what are you talking about?
What are they just in there?
Vote him out of the dru crew
That's fine. That's fine. I I you can get you can you can fire me from president of the dru crew
Whatever. I still get to show up
Are they just in here?
I have it right here. What are you talking about? These are the spark plugs use them
Nancy
What do you want me to do
It's right in front of me
The language barrier solved the puzzle. I apparently can't speak icelandish
So I can't do it open the motor place the spark plugs and connectors in their location. I can't even touch it
I can't touch this. It won't let me
I have to play the translate game. I'm serious
I have to go play the translate game
No, I don't
You need the guide from the gift shop
What the fuck is this?
Maybe if I save a little more
Why
in seven hells
Would you put
a make money
mini game in the game
but the only place for you to make money is to do
a
Minigame on a translator screen you guys want me to get the sword for seven thousand dollars. I have to sit here for like two hours
Cook food
I ain't doing that shit
mobile
So it's pretty much a 20 chance to get it right 25
All right, how much money do I need 1500 you could just learn
I'm not gonna i'm not gonna learn an entire language
for nancy dru
Dru crew fucking dru crew, huh?
I didn't say fuck the dru crew. I said fucking dru we vibing together
How much money do I have? He's just jealous
No, I love the dru crew. You guys seriously this is like the this is the best crew
I knew so I actually know some of these
uh, it's
Sister
friendly
one more
Uh a tree grass grass geyser land land
is ice
bear snow elding lightning snow snow farm
steward sea
Northern lights northern lights eldfall island volcano
One more let's go again bear
farm straw and beach is ice northern lights eldefall
Is
Your fancy
Tree tree
Sand your plant bloom flower plant plant
All right, let's go
This is exciting dot dot dot
I mean we were taking applications from members of the dru crew and uh
I'm sorry. I'm sorry to tell you that
You didn't make it
Sorry, I just I gotta tell you I gotta just tell you the truth
Can't just
um
Say yeah, you're in yeah, you're in the dru crew
Welcome, that's not that's a lot to lie. I don't want to do that. All right open the damn thing
The dru crew is all I have left. Oh, you're in it. What are you're in it?
You're in it
What are you talking about?
All right, I got the guidebook. Let's go
Odors intact, but i'll need to replace the spark plugs and cables
All right. Okay. So
um
Hello, okay. So this is one two
I need numbers. I need numbers
So I need 16 the middle one. It's so where where is it?
16 9 19 13
Uh 16 is 16
Nine
Nine is uh new
16 9
And then it was 19
All right, then what about the what about these ones?
fin
Uh, what does fin mean?
There's five
Wait, wait
This is five sixteen
Shit
This is total voltage
uh
So this would be what eight and what?
Damn god, he's another language
Tolf and ata are what?
I need to equal 16
What's tolf?
What's ata?
12 and at 12 and 8
This one's correct
No, it's not. Yes, it is
That seems right
No, it's no. No, it's it's how much you mean total total. Okay. No, that's not
I need 12 and
Uh, I need was four
12 and four
Your rear it's this one 12 and four is 16. That one is working
Say just say something sexy. Why is it so hard for you? What the fuck are you talking about?
All right
Two in two and you
Ten and nine
Was one is there a one?
Because this one has to be nine
Is there a zero?
uh
i'm just
Eight
Just get them out of the way
So this is uh
What is it again? I just I don't know. I don't I didn't learn this shit
fin and fear fin is five and fear is two
Two i'm gonna put them in order. I'm gonna get them in order
Check this out
So this is two
Two three four five is how it's gonna go
What's okay? What's what's two?
Two is is ten
Ten put that down here eight
New is nine
Eight nine ten
And then what's zero?
Seven so this is seven eight nine ten and this is two
No, fuck you. It's this is seven eight nine ten. This is two five
Okay
This is seven eight nine ten
Two five
I need to make let's make nine
right here
Nine so we get seven and two
Seven and two is nine
Let's go
All right. Now we need to make uh
We've got ten and nine
What?
Seriously
Ten no, it's just what?
Ten. Yeah, ten and nine
You kidding me?
That's 19
And then I don't know what's this is five. What does it have to be 13?
I am so smart. It's we're not toxic. I don't know whose boat this is, but i'll just
Quit for a little while
There's literally 300 000 people in there and where
What look look look, oh what is it gonna be a fucked up picture of my face
Yes, it is
Okay
I figured out what the lock in the cupboard opens. What?
I still have to do can't check that off. Can't check that can't still have still have can't check that up haven't done that
What have I done?
Can't check haven't can't still check haven't done that still can't
Imagine how much of a lazy motherfucker you have to be to not check these off automatically
Still have to do that. Have I not explored the ton of into every single place?
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go drew crew you here
Drew crew you with me?
Are you with me?
Now the music changed don't like it don't like it. All right, we got in the lighthouse. Um
Good space invaders images
the star
the jellyfish
the shark
the prongs
the anchor
the boat the crab
the nuclear launch
What else we got? I have to turn this place back on right?
Probably shouldn't have ran by everything. Um
Well
Shit guys
I think i'm stumped
Call the intern from what phone?
Wait
Oh this phone
Okay, i'm in the lighthouse
Finally a real puzzle
Okay
I need to create white light to get the lighthouse running again
What the fuck are you doing?
I
Am I playing tetris?
Green and green is red
and then red and
Is this just 20 at 2048?
and then
Green and then red and red
Is the wheel and the wheel and the wheel is
I'm not soft-locked. I've played i've played that game before
Actually guys, I played the original one
How many there's more than one?
I played threes. Yeah threes is the one that they made and then 2048
Just made another one and 2048 was like five million times more popular
I think it's fine if I let's see
What happens if I go left?
Yeah, I think you actually can't soft lock yourself. So I gotta be careful
Yeah, it's very soft lockable. It's soft lockable
Can I combine the two white?
No, you can't almost there
Just a few more lights
Bring this one up bring this one over
Bring this one down bring this one down. Thank you
Two more I gotta get this shit over here two more. This is actually gonna get pretty tricky. I gotta be careful
Uh-oh i'm about to fuck it
I'm about to fuck it all up
No, no, no. Oh, I fucked it up
Oh god, I gotta do it all in one go. Shit. Okay. I know what to do. I know what they want me to do
I know what to do. I'm gonna be here for a while
Oh, it's idiot proof. How would you ever say this was idiot proof? What are you talking about?
Shit, this is an ipad game now
Koala brain stream, right? Yeah, you do it. Yeah, you do it you do it you get them all in one go you do it
You do it zebra, but zebras are zebra smart
I hope not that way. They're definitely not there's no way a zebra is smart easy. It's left right left right left right left
Why would I do that to make a little joke when i'm halfway there? Why would I do that?
I gotta get rid of these blue ones or i'm gonna be fucking screwed again
No, don't do it
No
wah
ooh, ah
Show fuck I screwed it up. I think I can still salvage it. Oh, i'm in deep shit now
I'm in deep shit. Now. I fucked the whole thing up. No, I didn't not yet. Not yet
Not yet. Give me
Give me one. Ah
Fuck it's over. This is fucking insane
This is to get I'm getting two more after that
It's easy just left right left right left right. No, you were wrong
Smart clicks are you out of your mind?
Have I ever played 2048?
I just told you I played the original. Here's the difference
In 2048 you don't have to leave shit on the goddamn game board. You can combine things forever
I just told you I played the original
Why would I lie about playing the original?
2048's not even the original
It's threes dammit threes
He's played every ipad game. That's right. I have i've played every ipad game
I would know
This sucks
You gotta get rid of the blue. You gotta keep getting rid of blue. Get out of here. Come on
You're no longer part of the dru crew
You can't leave the dru crew
Hey, hey fellas he thinks he can leave the dru crew
Boy
Once you're in the dru crew you rent it for life. Fuck. It's okay. Fuck fuck
No
I need to go
Wait, I think I can still wait. Wait, wait
How are you supposed to get all of them? How are you supposed to get all of them?
All of them you're gonna get all of these things that like what?
Give me a fucking break. You're gonna get a you're gonna fill the whole board solve it already. I can't
Oh
It's all right. Everything's gonna be fine. Just go up stick to one corner
I'm on this i'm on the computer
I got it. Why did you have to spawn there of all places? Why'd you spawn there?
Why did it spawn there you spawned? It's a bad place
I fucking hate this
Why does it have to be like this?
The game that they copied to do this is not even like this last game I don't even oh my god
I don't even
I don't even I don't I don't want to play the like the impossible version of 2048
Fucking nancy dru
Remember when this was a nancy dru stream remember when nancy dru made 35 games and
27 of them were terrible
Remember that I remember that
You take that back
And he lost his job as a streamer
For doing it because everyone put the dru crew left. You know how many actual dru crew fans there were zero
Streamer can't beat game for little girls
That's not even accurate
I I expect the dru crew to get behind me on this one
Okay, I have to beat this
This is gonna drive me crazy
All right, I gotta do a real attempt
I gotta do a real attempt a real attempt a real attempt to stay in one corner. I don't have any sense
spam a corner
Fuck the dru crew
I didn't say that you did. How could you say something like just so disgusting?
All right, that one's up there
You're playing this all wrong
This this is just
Stupid you know how many seven-year-old girls would give the fuck up
An hour and a half ago when they had to go find the note in the guy's shoe box
I'm gonna smash my computer
Can you imagine
That's what does it is the nancy dru 3 knockoff
The nancy dru 2048 copy paste game without numbers on it that leaves shit on the board. That's what's gonna do it
All right, nobody breathe just help me help me do it. I can't I just the cause I just do it
I just do it do it. I don't even want to do this anymore. Just do it. Just do it. Just smart click
I don't care. This is not even a real game. This is a copy paste bullshit game
This is a copy paste fucking bullshit version of this game and it's not even good
It's not even a good one. Yeah, everybody's still like we get some dru crew ones the chat, please
Like dru crew, let's go
They just took a fun game and made it shitty
They took a fun video game and they just added something they made it bad. Can I can I
Here go ahead
Let me turn on my smart clicks
Do jump king dlc instead. No, i'm currently getting mad about
plagiarism game
Restart the whole thing. No, no, that doesn't need to be restarted you go up from here you go up
In fact, i'll do that for you because I know I know that to be a fact
You made a massive mess. No, I did what?
This is fine
I can't I once we get once we get to fucking eight. I can't do it anymore
All right. Yeah
All right. Just do it. Just read it. I don't care. I don't care. I'm just nancy drew who cares just go
I'm using a walkthrough anyways, okay, let's go
It's all right corner lads. I was supposed to be me that did this
And I I know how to play too. I just there's no numbers
Is this a fucking leave of white ones on the whole board gets them turned into a mess
Why did you make it like that? Okay, let's go
Please tell me where the fuck where to go. Just go no good. I don't care. There's no there's no limit. Just click
It's not a kid's game. We're going up
I don't even know what you're trying to do. Why would somebody do that?
What just hold on somebody just gave a what?
Is this person anonymous anonymous gifter gave a hundred community subs?
What the fuck
Uh, thank you. Whoever that was. Holy shit. That's a lot
Thank you for the 100 subs
You absolute beast
Let me just do this part
Reset you fucked it up already
Oh, ah, what the fuck
I have to run the game in the window because it's gonna be possible. You guys better get this right
You gotta get you better get it right. You gotta get this right get us out of here, please
I ain't doing this shit anymore
Stupid ass thing. Oh, i'm so mad right now like i'm like
All right, let's go fuck it who cares
It's a goddamn children's game. What do I really care that much about this? Go click. I just do it
It's gonna be three seconds per move one
two
Three you want to go up. What are you what are you clicking on go up left down right left up right left down
You guys aren't even doing this right
Where do you click and click? No, you gotta click on the way you want me to move it
Not the space you want me to put it to
Click the arrows. Yeah, not like this spaces
Okay, right go right
Now what?
Three two one. I can't believe i'm fucking doing this
Go up and right. Can you see twitch chat?
Okay, you want me to go up?
up
Okay again
Up right up right up right reset gang no
Spam up and right and only ask chat to choose when you can't go in those directions
Okay, I can no longer go in that direction
Now what?
left
Up do the same thing
All right. I'm going left. All right. Now what?
Now what do you want me to do?
Up now what up and then right you guys are a little you guys are are divided here
People are saying left now spam up right again
Up right up right up right. So go right up right up right up
Okay, I can't move anymore. Now what left once?
Be sure left. Okay left now what? Yes, then up right up right up right
Is that correct?
Up right up right up right until I can't anymore
Jimmy you're causing me physical pain
Well, get your laptop out of your underwear. Like what are you talking about? Like what are you what are you talking about?
Stop lying on your laptop on your back. What are you talking about?
Are you like sitting on your laptop?
Are you watching the stream upside down?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. What was it? What was it? What was it? What was it?
It was upright upright up. Okay up time. Yeah, I got it. Got it. Got it. Got it
Up right up right up right up right up right up right up right up right up right up right
I can't do it anymore. Help me
Jeremy you're causing me physical pain
Well
Stop using the laptop. I don't know. What are you talking about?
Left once then upright upright upright
Okay, I got you
Left once
I want to make sure
Is this correct?
You want to go upright upright upright?
You want to go right up right up. Oh, yeah that red wine thing. Not even real. Okay
All right. So we could let me confirm with you guys. Uh, uh, uh
A drew crew in the chat with whatever
You know, all right. I'm just doing it right up
right
And then just up
Right up help me. Uh nat kitty just gave 20 community subs. Thank you
Another huge sub drop. The last one was from somebody an on an anonymous person
Thank you both of you
All right now now up or down
Down durama. I don't like this stream
Get that person out of the drew crew
The drew carry crew, please
We're all fans of his
I'm going up and we're doing right up
up again
Uh-oh guys, I need a consensus here
Jeremy
I didn't do anything. Fuck the writers
I
Be sure about this because I don't want this to be my fault
It has to be a super majority or we're dead
Now everyone wants to go left
Okay
Now what?
Wow, 100 saying up look at you guys working together like that
and then
any resetters
And now right you guys
Don't do this now. We're almost out of here. It's good. It's right
up right
We're close
Guys, don't i'm not resetting. I'm not clicking that
Up right up right up right repeat up right up right up then right up right
up right
up
again
Up again up right up right
Okay
Go left
Up right
Yeah, okay up right. We're so close up right up
right up right up right up right up
Right up right up right. I can't go upright anymore. Okay, you take over
That's what i've been told I need to do
Left right. Is that correct? No, right. Just just regular right just right right
Okay, now what right again you fucked it. I didn't I didn't I didn't do anything
You guys have fallen apart here you guys
I just clicked on the thing that you told me to click on you said right 60% of you
Then up
This feels like being water ported
What the fuck
You want me to go down why down
Why are there most people doing down?
Is that not correct? That's not correct. Why 40% of you trying to screw it all up someone's sabotaging
One guy, uh, no, it's more like 700 guys
i'm going up
Now we're germa. I have 4k channel points. What should I spend them on?
I'll spend right now on on on germa wink
Just just say that just do it use them all
Use them all
Annual and that's at the 4 000 channel points is a germa wink
Did you use them? All right
Guys, uh guys we had a 4 000 channel points you spent
You know what? That means time for a germa wink
Oh people are still there's a lot of there's a lot
We had a lot more channel points just come through. You know what that means
It's time for a germa wink
All right. Where are we going? Right?
Up, right?
I don't actually i'm not gonna have it be down to me. This is too close
This is way too close. I am fucking this up
German you look like you just drank it. You had a red freezy. Yeah, it was delicious. You look like
What do you give us 12k points? I'll thank you
Thanks
We made it. This is it upright
Oh, what upright you said upright you said upright you said upright you said upright you said upright
You said upright
You said upright everyone said upright. They said upright upright upright
That's what they said
No one said yes, they did everyone has been saying up right this whole time
I didn't fuck it up
You guys want to go up again?
What is going on?
down
down down and right
I need one more
Left, wait a minute. What do you guys you gotta never go down and don't ever go down
Why did you just tell me to go down then?
We need one more
Russian bots are making us fail
I think up twice up. No, I win
I'll finish it
up
And then down
Here we go. I'm gonna tell you the play
up
down
Uh, no up up down. Don't all right. Fine. Fuck it. You guys can do it. Where do I go? What do you want to do?
No, please
All right, I got everyone up again. I told you it was up. That's what I said. Everyone's like call me stupid
Now what I said up up and you all freaked out but 62 percent of you is saying let's go up
Bro, the lighthouse looks like a penis. Ha ha ha funny
Uh-oh, they're divided
left
left up
Left up left up left up there it is
We did it
No, we didn't no, it's okay. It's okay
All right, where do you want me to go now?
It's not over
Any resetters do I got any resetters in chat with the leg fuck walk?
No, there's a lot of you actually
Oh, okay
Don't mess this up. I need you here
Left not left. Please god. Oh my god. Just redo it again. All the resetters need to pick something
Okay
Don't little girls play this game
Sure
Uh-oh, uh up. Um
Left up left up up left up left up left up up
I did it
I was here. I was here
I was here. Okay. Let's talk about paper for the term snoopy
Whatever klepto you need a distraction. I got one
We did it better than you 30 percent of you with me
So you were doing wrong 30 percent of you were clicking the shiny button on the screen
So sure like like 38 percent of you guys knew what you were doing
And the rest of you could just be lumped in with me
so
I've been locked in here
Somebody trying to kill me 13
uh
24, um
To 17
Minus uh 29
No, 11 is
Six seven eight nine six seven eight eight nine was there seven seven
eight nine seven
Eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen, which is a six
Uh, okay thirteen seven eight nine four five scissors six
That's obviously not correct
uh two
Two and two is four
Three and five is seven
seven and
Six and three is nine
It's too small at the bottom
Yeah, all right
What are you?
Please what no I had it quick get out of my head
Get out of my head get out of my head get out of my head small numbers at the bottom
Six and I had it right. No, I was doing right you got get out of my head
Get out of you guys are stuffed in here
five two
uh
How would I rate this stream from a one out of ten?
ten
Uh four plus three, but I can't move 13. This has to act somebody said small numbers at the bottom
It's not true because I need to make 13
I had it correct
It's eight
it was
six and
and
Eight no six and eight and fuck
Nine and four, I don't I don't know nine and four two four five six six over here
Uh four because I have a four
There's a four here, but I can't
Start at the top
Why would I start at the top 36 and
63 36 and
27 is
Hey, they're gonna get one of the chapter nancy drew
Drew I
She said she said that's the the big number at the top the big number
All right 20 36 46 56
That's not correct
There's 36 46 56
57 58 59 60 61 62 63. I need 27
27 so 13
Plus what is 27 13 24?
13 13, so i'm gonna have line around here somewhere 13 plus 14 is right there. All right 14 plus 14
24 24 22
We have 13 plus 13 23 9
And then we have 9 10 11 12 13 14 is 5
Oh 9 10 11 12 13 14 is 5. There's no 5
14 is 11 and uh
11 and 3
Okay, so now we got um
two and one
I'm blind to the top one
five and
I'm blind
Am I what was it again four 14 five?
What what am I doing? Uh, it was 12. No 11
What was it six and no seven?
Seven seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty. No, that's not correct. So eight
Nine was nine nine
Nine ten eleven twelve. That's thirteen. All right
Thirteen eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty. We need four. I got a four right here
Now we got five that doesn't equal that that doesn't make any sense. That's not correct. This is incorrect
I need the two over here. No, this is wrong
nine
fourteen, um
five and four is
Is there a zero?
replace 22
13 and five don't make 22
No, that's correct. So not 13 9 10 1 2 13 14
uh 7 and
9 4 2 3 4 9 4
9 4 2 3 5 9
4 2
3 5
4 5 6 is 6
5 and then 3 5 6 7 8
Something's wrong here
4 5 6 6 6 5 is not
One person did that one person get the logs and fucking type that in
Um god
Six seven two three five
Does somebody screenshot it screenshot that and ronan just give me screenshot screenshot screenshot just screenshot it
I don't want to do that. I'm done screenshot
Just give me a clip of that
Just give me a clip. I see a clip
Yeah, good image
It's basic matte. I don't care
It was wrong. Don't use it. It was wrong
What?
You guys got it wrong too, then
All right, 63 26. Okay, let's go
22 14
Uh, nine five eight
Six seven two three five six
Seven two three five. There it is. It was correct. Don't tell me it was wrong. It was right
Show this to future germo. Okay, what is it?
All right, you got it. I think i'm gonna go
All right, you got it. I think i'm gonna go get that coin. Can I like fucking scoop slam him and take over his place?
I don't get it
Like I don't care. I if i'm the new germa that guy germa if you're listening to me in the future
Just come do it and be the germa. That's fine
What an accident show that to sober germa
Haven't still still can't check still haven't that's still have to can't check that off yet
Now what?
Can I hear another ship fact? I don't know. I don't know the ship fact
Most people think all pirates were men, but that's not true at all
In fact, there were dozens of famous lady pirates in the 16th and 17th centuries fix the game
After her mother died and her father was killed she became one of the most feared pirates in the caribbean at one point
She faked her own death during a battle
She went undercover and pretended to be a man for years when she finally revealed her true identity
Other pirates gave her the nickname back from the dead red because of her bright red hair bad feces facts
later
Talk to you later. Bye. What do I do now?
Okay, I had to turn this on so somebody could
I don't remember. I don't know you like I know what this what's going on right now
Back to the ship. All right, right, right, and then I got a call
Back to the back to the radio room
You got it. Goodbye. Do you remember more? I'm not gonna say that because I don't get it. All right, uh, now what?
Who wanted me to turn the lighthouse on in the first place? Didn't she want to do that?
Why would you have a chair alarm? Does it why does it what are you doing? Oh her back her bag. I can take her back
This must be the key to mangas's cabin. I'll just be borrowing this
Elizabeth never opened her gift
I don't remember one notes
All right. I got the key to the cabin. It's that door right there. Right the one that she was like don't go in there
Where's this in here? Open it. That's not the
That's not a cabin
This is not a cabin
How is that not a cabin the cabin is in
log cabin
Figure out what the lock in the cupboard opens. Why does it want me to still do this? Check that off yet. I don't understand
What the oh
Right. Wait one. There's only four numbers. I know there's probably more
All right, find it and return the helm's missing decorations. What the hell does that mean?
All right, let me I gotta find this cabin. Let's address the cheating see what it says
Okay
I know what to do. Are we underwater?
Can I get the fuck out of here?
All right
I have to go to the guy's cabin is you guys were right
There actually is a way to go a different way from the snowmobile you're right
I could go this way
I thought I could before the cave there was a place to go left. Where is it left on the road?
Oh, that's no sign
Just a little why oh no checking in something's wrong tell me
Izzy everything's fine. Everything's normal. I'm just not vibing with you. I'm just getting a strange vibe. No
He sent a hit man
Ned sorry
Is someone trying to hurt you? Oh, no, dude
Who's burnt?
Ned ned what on earth is going on?
Come on, leave me alone
New content new content
buttons
Ooh, I know what these do too. I had a ten buttons
Nancy, why am I on the cover of this?
Am I in my own universe? I don't understand
I got some edits. I want you to do
ooh buttons
What about bed? I need ten of these. I wonder what these images are for
Oh wait
nah
cares
Not worth it
Locked up tight locked up tight
Do I have like a hook?
Locator
Star
Okay, I can't open this it's making a weird noise
These must belong with that reference. I saw earlier four of each color down and across no three together in a line four
Are you what is going on?
four of each color
You know in range of crystals according to the note about crystals four colors of each crystal in a row and column
Ah
I did just yawn. I did. Yeah, you caught me you did
damn it
He's bored. No, I just i'm tired about that
so
Four I have to go of each color go. What does the dumb note say?
Chat just do it. There's no way a human could do it
No true dru crew member would yawn at a nancy dru game
Why do I hate nancy dru? I don't
Why I don't
Let me see if I can figure this out
Four have to go across
If I go to these two down here, wait, hold on you need four of each in
So that means like they give me you don't have to be in a row. I could do wait. Hold on
Yeah, they don't have to be in a row
Yep, four. Okay, make them all blue then work backwards. I'm kind of i'm feeling it
I'm feeling it
I'm gonna do with rows
Okay, here we go. Let's go ready
That one's done
Okay, what about down? How am I doing on these rows? Is it fine?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
I'm almost done
I see hold on
Let's go
Okay
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah
I'm sorry. I just like punched you
This is beautiful
Now you're actually gonna help me to sleep now you turn it up. What do I need to do?
What does it who cares? What who met what does why does this matter?
No get out of this what am I supposed to do with this is there any key
You need to arrange these pieces to see what the full image looks like what pieces oh
shit, okay
Dude, all right. Let's go dru crew
I have one of those. Where is it? Where's my sketch? Oh, no, that is the sketch
Are we going? Uh, I don't know right here
I need a top
What the fuck? It's pretty easy
Why can I move it?
I can only put shit on the bottom
This is a children six piece. I can't even place anything. I can only place it on the bottom
Oh, I can't do it. Yeah, I can't do that guys. It's not it's not completable
Missing pieces, man
How many more of these was this? Yeah, okay. Nice publishing agreement
We do have some questions about
Depends it'll do
We'll definitely call you back. Thank you
Probably should have raised this one
I don't know how to race
only accumulate
Crow's nest
This is this is it solution is to divide into groups of six
No group touching another attempt after the festival crowds die down
a dog bed
But no dog those dogs this thing probably stinks
You need to clean that
a spare luggage key, huh?
luggage key
Where's the reason work with the original?
Heltreguide for all to enjoy
Did you see this there's gonna be tourists crawling all over the thing
We need to move faster by the way your mutt like shiny things
Discover this a hard way when spare luggage came with missing yesterday briefly saw it in
Tumi's mouth, but he ran off of it. Can you keep an eye out for it?
I figured it's gonna go back one way or another I check wherever he spends a lot of time wear gloves p.s
luggage
Can't check that off yet
Can't check can't check did that still have to do can't check habit can't check still haven't can't check that off yet
What the hell is this dog toys?
This must be related to the note magnus left for himself
Oh, is it this thing?
Okay, it looks fine no dog next to dog
It's a little tricky, but you know, you gotta just punch your way at it
It's very tricky it is it's pretty tricky, how am I out of dogs? Oh, that's for amateur. Okay, I see
I have
Excuse me. I'm gonna say let me do this 45 minute long puzzle on my own
If anyone else has seen these
You can do it. I tried it's only 45 minutes if you suck
Need to know you're with me that you're going to see this through just like we talked about when we started this project
Okay
I got the document
You've always had my word
You still do no need for that. So, uh, so dagny is in trouble
Haven't done that you're in deep shit. I still need how many coins two more coins?
You see any I don't see any more coins
I see one one more coin. That's it
That looks like one up there. It's not how is that possible?
Where's the last coin?
German boots
coin
Is there a coin anywhere?
There's one more hanging out somewhere where
mod kim
Well last time kim was a mod. She banned like 200 people
Checking the boy. There's a bathroom. Oh shit. There is a bathroom. Can I get in there?
Ban kim no kim is it doesn't even ban
Where's this last coin before I lose my mind?
No, i'll do this instead
Well, there are sure it is a vip you're a fucking moron what
Whoa
Whoa, man. Whoa
What?
What why did you say that?
All right. All right, but all right, but why did you say that?
We're supposed to be part of the dru crew together and you're gonna come at me with that kind of shit
Come on
We're in this together forever. It's true crew. I thought I guys I thought you guys have my back
I'm just gonna look up where the coin is. Who cares
Where's the coin? What do you mean cheating? It's not cheating if you don't see it
I'm really i'm getting directions
I well, it's that up there, but it's not
Give me a hint then
You can't go in the bathroom
Do you guys know where it is? I don't think you do
the box
There's nothing in the box left pocket
You know
Nancy dru would not approve of cheating
It's not cheating if you don't if I don't get caught what
What's on the lid of the box?
Go stand by the front door and check the ceiling light
I thought I made what noise you thought I made what noise?
Do the chest puzzle?
There is no puzzle
I can't do anything
This is easy
There's nothing to do
I'm just leaving i'm going somewhere else to do another part of the game
Check the door frame
Already got that one
Quick, please kim the the dru crew needs our cheese toasties
Those are so good haven't done that
Keyhole at the bottom of the box. I don't have a key
It's a luggage key
That doesn't work
Kim, please. I need my toasties
All right in the pre-stream chat earlier
She asked if I wanted any cheese toasties
and tomato soup she was just she was being funny and
And people think that that
I want to eat my cheese toasties
the shelf
There's nothing on the shelf. I did this already. I'm just leaving. I don't give a fuck
on tv
Why would you even hide this shit?
It's not that's not even a puzzle
That's not a puzzle. It's padding
We need to as the dru crew. We need to know the difference. I'm sorry
i'm done
Get me the fuck out of this house. He's quitting nancy dru
I don't understand break through this ice with a sharp enough tool. Why didn't she say that before?
i've had this hook in my
Inventory, okay, that's
Why can't I quit you?
I don't know. I don't know but this this kind of looks like my colonoscopy images
without the ice
down here
Hello, now remember we did that colonoscopy and there was a little ladder in your colon
Somebody's in there. Somebody's living in there
Oh, I need those anything else down here. It's oil right here. Can I do anything with the oil? Uh,
Okay, i'm lost in my colon
Uh, okay
Well, I apparently I can die down here. All right. Well, I have is there anything else I need down here?
I can't break this one
Where am I? What the fuck is going on?
This is a maze
Okay, nancy, where do you suggest I go? Am I any service down here?
Nickerson unless you're a telemarketer or my older sister in which case you've reached no one because this number doesn't exist
For everyone else leave a message ned. Call me back. I'm worried
All right, so I take a selfie down here
To prove that I was down here
All right, I figure how do I get out of here?
Go up to the ladder
and then
Is it I can go this way?
Am I going the right way?
What is going on?
Uh a generator
How did I do that?
Okay, there's a ladder. There was the glove
That glove doesn't do anything. I looked at it already. Okay up the ladder. There's two ways to go
Where did I go last time? Did I go? Okay?
He's already down here. Is there anything else in here? I don't think there's anything in here. I'm just leaving
All right, pull me out. Get me out of this. Get me out of the colon. I have okay. I got those sketch pieces
New alien colon where what was the sketch thing right here, right? Where do I put them? Wait, wait
Uh, no memory. No, I there's
It's back in the other house
I look about i've put 25 things in my inventory
Right. Okay. It's this thing
Can I do this yet? Well that goes
here
Do I need more sketch pieces or what?
That's not where that goes. I can't even place anything
I can't even pick this up
Didn't say overlapping. So why can I not put it down?
And I get it. I know I know you didn't know I had to do that either
I know for a fact that like you got half you guys are going. Oh shit. That's what we have to do
Like I need more I can't do it yet
Yeah, this is not I can't do this. I'm missing like four more pieces
music box drew crew
I gotta go talk. Oh wait, forget this. I gotta go talk to that girl
That admitted to the crime
Okay, thanks threatening big man with a knife
You where are you?
Not here, of course
snake
Have a check can't have it. That's that's done. Can't can't can't check that off yet
All right, but I hate getting mad all the time but it's frustrating
No, you don't think it's so mad
Just chill out. Just relax
It's all good. Maybe figure out what
What's like making you so angry? You know what I mean?
Watching you. All right. I know that's fine. That's fair. I'll take it
Well, where was that luggage? There was a weird piece of luggage hanging out somewhere. Where was it?
coin in that closet
Are you fucking kidding me? You gotta be kidding me. What was it? What's this doing in here?
They put nine coins in one room
And then that is the one that's in another room somewhere in the in the world somewhere
Nancy
I'm gonna put these coins away. There you go
If these wind fire
Match the words, okay feet house match images to create a single compound word foot house
uh
fire house
castle
feet castle
feet bow
bow feet
Does bow feet work? No fish feet
foot horse horse foot foot stool
done
whale wave
board gun
four
castle four
Four bow bow four bed four four bed
Four fish fish for a horse four
four horse four horse
four ball
whale four whale four board four board board four
floor board
floor castle castle floor castle four castle floor
four ball
four horse
fish four fish v
We'll fuck a little bit later sun
uh
shine ball ball shine
whale sun
sunboard sunbathe bathe board board
board bathe
bathe board sun
sunflower
fire bow
bed fire
fire bed fish fire fire fish horse fire
fire horse
fire ball
Got it
dorm board
rain board
board rain
rain castle castle rain
rainbow
wave bed
bed wave fish wave
Water fish fish water water horse horse water
whale water
whale horse
Uh whale water water board water board what?
Is that okay?
sea bed, uh
That's definitely not correct
what wave
water bed
These things don't those exist
starboard
Starboard starboard right? It's you you are on starboard
It's like starbird, right?
star horse star fish
spring castle spring board
four gun whale whale gun
Horse gun gun horse gun bed bed gun gun castle castle gun
whale gun
horse gun horse fire fire horse
shoot horse horseshoot
whale shoot shoot whale
Castle shoot shoot castle castle bed shoot bed
gun bed shoot bed
wave horse
seahorse
wind castle
sand castle
So what is whale gun?
Four bed
This is wrong. What's wrong here rainbow?
wave horse seahorse
gun whale
No springboard
sand castle
sunflower starfish fireball footstool. What's wrong?
River bed river bed and then four sea horse
It's not way it's not that's not sit what oh that's a that's okay. I thought it was like sand like dunes
All right, so it's not sand. Yeah. All right
Uh, so we got we have
uh river bed
seahorse
whale four
gun castle
Four whale whale four. What is that?
This is wrong guys
gun whale
What the hell is a gun whale?
What is four castle?
What is that? What is four castle castle four?
Fortnite
two broken pieces can fix a locator now
What do I do with this
Still have to do that
Check that's done
Haven't done that that's done still have haven't done that
What is a gun whale?
So I have the locator now figure out the importance of the contents of the foot locker
Figure out what the lock in the cupboard it opens
Right. I still don't understand that one figure out the sounding depth numbers yet
No idea. What's the luggage?
There's luggage in somebody's room
Right. Remember who had the luggage?
Who ordered the luggage?
Click the map to the left
map branded luggage
Yeah, what does this mean?
Can I climb this?
um
I gotta start talking to people
I've got to figure like we've got new dialogue to have with people and why do I have this weird egg still?
Hey you you got anything new to tell me? Oh, hello there
Hey, soren just saw someone take a sweater from the gift shop. Those are free, right? Hey, soren
I just saw someone take a sweater from the gift shop. Those are free, right?
No, all right. What am I eating tonight? You might want to look into that then
stop
thief
Oh, it's your luggage. I'll be taking that
Can I get over there?
He'll be back soon. Take as long as you want. There's no way he'll be back soon. Hey, it's right. I saw the other glove new
There he was
Create volcanic winter
All right, buddy slow down
relax
Uh, what else over here?
Soren's desk note mentioned volcanic winter. Do these elements link up to that somehow earth?
And water equals glacier. I played this this is doodle god fire and air makes energy
energy and steam makes a geyser a glacier
a geyser
and steam
Okay, so now we need water
We need glacier and and um
Get this shit out of here
glacier and
energy
Is an erosion
A maelstrom
So I need to do uh, let's do fire water
earth glacier and energy
How about air and glacier?
Glacier and energy is erosion
steam and glacier is flood
Flood and geyser is a maelstrom flood and erosion is a maelstrom
flood and fire is is
Okay, cool
Let's get i'm gonna get these off
Let's do
Water and earth is glacier water and air is cyclone
water and fire
Steam water earth is glacier earth and air is desert
Earth and fire is lava and we've got them all in that category
lava
And energy is eruption
lava and steam is a geyser
Lava and desert is a rock
Lava and cyclone is rock
energy and lava
Energy and cyclone is flood
Desert and energy is dust cloud
Dust cloud and flood is a maelstrom
Eruption and dust cloud is volcanic winter. I will take it winter guest records
Why elizabeth haven't done that?
All right, somebody should probably read that
Hmm. Here's the luggage
Get that shit open. What do you got in here drew through take a quick look. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah
Here is a landed sea
I'll probably need that at some point. Somebody will remember us. I'm gonna read that shit
All right, i'm ready
He's been gone for a really long time. What happened here?
Looks like there's been a struggle
It's dagny's phone, but where's dagny blood?
His password protected
Maybe note about this
The password is not true crew. Okay
I would know i'm in it
Does that work? I don't know what the phone is. I got bigger fish to fry here
Yes, guys, don't don't worry. I passed the fourth grade. I know it's not resident sleep or
Nancy. Hi, it's good to hear your voice
Why are you panicking? What?
Yeah, you gotta fuck off
It's kind of a sort of an intangible concept really when a guy like me begins ruminating
Let me tell you it can get pretty crazy up in the old noggin
Looking back on all the times we spent together
All those times you almost got seriously hurt
Like that one time you almost burned to death or that time when you almost got killed by that giant falling blade
Or on that raft in new zealand
Or that one thing with that mansion on fire. Jeez, what happened then? That's so non-sense
Well, oh maybe that one time that you almost burned to death, you know, I get lucky a lot and I kind of
Fall into things. Oh shit. Those are spoilers for other games that we're gonna play in the true crew
Future streams
Remember that time that you froze to death over fourth grade math twice. Yeah
Yeah, that's kind of funny that is funny that person said that's funny
Oh, i'm not sure how I feel ned i miss you okay i'll see you
Oh, I need to go to the cabin fucking yikes
Does net ever make an appearance in any of the games does he just die on the telephone
Why are they why are there two pieces of this? Why are there two pieces of this?
What is this two pieces of this for?
Oh, okay. I'm just gonna say why is this two pieces of this?
All right, this goes over here somewhere right there
Flower goes
It's over here somewhere it's over
Over here
Still missing pieces
stupid haven't done that
Haven't done that. All right, we're gonna find dagny
I still don't get what this thing is for. What is this for? We know
What do we do with the music box? I can't move metal pieces
They can't be touched
It's a puzzle dumbass
Well, some of you guys could do with some nice training some of you guys could do with a little bit of of nice training
You know what I mean? I know it's a puzzle
Don't you mean decency training?
Stupid fucking dumb fucking idiot
Idiot dumb fucking idiot
Okay
Let's go
What else is here?
Hello fiskeri. Do you have anything? How do you know elizabeth? How do you know elizabeth?
I've known her since she was a negative pre glimmer in her puppy's eye
Always had the local boys terrified. That was a new voice after again. She knows what she wants and heads put straight as an arrow
young men
Not so good with a woman like that
She's scary
I'm hungry. Oh, yeah, right. What what what what you guys think?
Still she lets me sleep on the official that's worth something
Did you know about her and magnus? No
We all did my fiskeri
She's toasties now. Not really unfortunately
No, this is good with waves. Not a bad idea
No skills to speak of he is. Um, how do you say it there? A runner he runs
Ouch. I'm glad he's not here. Let's vote on whether we should disband the drew crew
Now I can only speak the truth. This is the second time we've ever met. That was a side effect of shark bites
It is a curse. I bet that's not i'm not what?
I saw you taking a dinghy out fishing trip. You told me you gave up being on the water for good
It wasn't me. That sounded pretty good. My brother. Yeah, the other gunnar he um
gunner
Oh first that shark bite. I was
Looking for the treasure, but so far only empty hands
I think there's more to this story. Don't check me now girl the bull
Go
Not now
And fuck you. I have the treasure finder idiot
You're the dumb one
Uh, what do we do now?
Pete
What about you? Let's talk to you
Hey nancy
Uh, so you and soren work together you and soren work together
Yes, we both run the festival remove channel points I can't now i've already given to them
They dislike him. I'm definitely sensing some of that
Why not one of us?
He doesn't know our stories no shared memories
He mentioned that you've been kind to him
Being his friend has yeah, i'm gonna up the prices. Don't worry. You're either outside or inside in skip road
You cannot stand in the doorway. You will be driven out
We are not like great pick like a big city sounds like people are trying to get rid of him
Ruining the festival would be a great way to do that. Wouldn't it your words not mine?
Regardless, he is welcome in my home and that's my pub. I spent 5 000 points on a reverse tube
But I can offer a warm meal and a listening ear
Heard about the debt about the town's debt issues, I don't know what you're talking about
I have found some information in the culture center. So you
You want to gloat?
To chastise you can't you know these channel points to highlight an imger link of my mouth
Is that what you did?
Of course, it's joker
Yes, that's my fault
I won't sit here and defend myself. Why does every channel have points now twitch just put it through
And I was going to fix it
It is a new twitch feature that they have unlocked for I think a lot of people now
It just by default turns on and we gotta figure out what the hell to do with it
I'm really sorry to hear about year and magnus's breakup
It hardly matters anymore. I don't want to pry but if you want to talk about it, i'm here
Here's one for your case file. I've known magnus all my life
We dated four years
The winters are long and dark
We found each other in that darkness, but then he went through hard times
He became obsessed over the ship for a long time his world narrowed
Yeah
There was no room left for me. That's the end of it. Goodbye
Bye now
Bye
All right, get me
Where am I going? I don't know. What am I doing? I don't know
I don't know figure out the numbers figure out the numbers and go let me go back up
Am I gonna buy amd calls?
No, I don't fuck with the stock market anymore
Nothing's beyond me
Not since I was like it's there's no fucking way. It's gonna be that expensive
No way. It's so overvalued. It's not worth shit
And I was wrong
I want to get up to the crow's nest
Where's the crow's nest?
How do I get up to the crow's nest? Anybody know?
How do I get up there?
I want to get up on the crow's nest
Go back to the captain's cabin
I
Seriously
Just go down here. That's not where i'm trying to go, man
Fucking christ. Okay. What am I doing in here?
What is this thing? Do I still have fucked up lips? I don't know. Let's find out
probably
It looks okay
I've absorbed most of it. Not as bad. No, not as bad
Why do I have lopsided ears
I don't know because i'm a human and my genetic dna has made me look different than everybody else
And yeah, some of us have like a longer finger a bigger earlobe
A slightly elongated nose a big toe that is as big as three big toes put together some of it
That's i'm a human being i'm just a person here
Have I been streaming for almost seven hours?
Seven hours in antsy drew. Oh, I wouldn't have it any other way. I hate the skin
So I would not have it any other way. That's the doggy kennel in magnus's note
What are you talking about
What?
Why does there a doggy key? What's the doggy key for?
Why do I have a doggy key for a fake member of the dru crew?
I bet you half the dru crew does not like this game. That doesn't mean we have to make fun of it
Is that for the music box? The dog key is for the music box
You shouldn't be
Are you projecting?
I'm not projecting this is projecting
Use fidget spinner in the radio room
What do you use a fidget spinner in the radio room?
That makes sense
These must be the sounding charts from magnus's note. Oh shit to find those numbers and the locator compass he mentioned
Oh shit, let's go
These must be the sounding charts from magnus's notebook. I need to find those numbers and the locator compass he mentioned
the numbers first
I don't know how the fuck to get the numbers
How the hell am I supposed to know?
I have 14
I cheated this is like so dumb. I cheated
I never would have figured this out. I just I cheated
We're cheaters
What's the tide at?
Tides high tide has to be low
low tide
We're low tide
There are markings behind
You just you understand why the hell would i've ever done this?
Cheating in the game for six-year-olds. I would love to meet the six-year-old that knew how to do that
I would shake their hand and be like you are such a great six-year-old excellent work
Eating toasties into the mic
All right, 26
Go back up
14 and 26 done. You need to find two more numbers to add up to 86. Put the locator on there
Where's the locator?
Don't I have it?
Share toasties. No, they're mine
It's our oh it's
Find the location that reveals the correct set of sounding numbers and all four of the location holes
Okay
Looking for 14
and 26
14 26
14 and 26
That it no
14 26. That's not it
82 where's 86?
Can't go that far
14 20 14 26
There's another 14 20 where the fuck is 26
Fort drew crew. I know the numbers
It's 14 26 35 and 11. I can't even find those on this map
These are the four numbers for that lock
What 35 26 11 14 is the lock?
It was it was 26. Yeah, I know I had it. All right, now you just love hitting the turn around button
Hello
2020 year of the rat. Oh speaking of 2020 and end of the year stuff
If you go to the discord right now
The categories for the end of the year stream
on new year's eve
Uh, the categories are there
the new year's eve award show worst of the year and some best of the year
Of the channel are there?
Uh, go over them look over them. The discussion channel is live for you to talk about what you think deserves to be nominated
Very soon here probably at end of night tonight into morning to end of night tomorrow
The nominations channel is going to open
You are to nominate let's actually go over the categories right now so I can I can say them to you because I want to be able to explain
Uh exactly what I mean by some of these because some of these you can be like the hell is he talking about?
Let's go over them right now
Head over to the discord if you will
It's already been a year since the last one. That's true
Uh, the pinned message in this discussion channel is what you want
Please discuss
This is not the submissions channel the nominations channel. You need to make sure
I'll go over it. Let's just let's go over it right now. Whatever. So our categories for this year
Someone tell him to slow the fuck down. What are you talking about? I'm going just i'm going at a good speed
our categories this year are
Worst hair of the year, that means anytime that i've been on camera and my hair has just looked like absolute dog shit
We're talking worst hair of the year
You know, it was in a category last year
Uh worse new character
Some of the new characters that have made appearances. I'm not sure how many they've been so far, but we'll do it
If you know not bugleberry because bugleberry was introduced
Last year so you cannot nominate bugleberry again
He's not a new character bugleberry bugleberry was in the stream last year, uh worst face
Video and screenshot we I would like I want a clip of the face. You're describing a screenshot of the worst image from that
Face worst face of the entire year
We also have worst peter
Had to make an appearance had to come back worst peter is on this list
Worst chat experience of the year is on this list
What that means?
Some people got confused by this
That that's not like my stream. Oh, I didn't like the stream. No, no, no
This is like the worst experience you had in the chat
Like you're in the chat room and you're just going holy shit
This is horrible worst chat experience of the year
Worst noise of the year
And of course best noise of the year
I feel like we're gonna get quite a few nominations making an appearance again from last year also, uh in this same kind of realm
Worst impression and best impression
What you thought the worst?
Impression I did the whole year was and of course the best one
Worst meltdown on stream
I don't know if there's been that many this year. I'm sure there has
A meltdown. I don't even need to explain that. Here's a new one for 2019
best one guy moment
A moment where one person potentially changed the course of an entire stream
Best moment best one guy moment if you got a lot of them, then i'm sure there'll be plenty of nominees
worst gamer moment
Something that was just unbelievable that I I did it. It was so bad that you can't even
describe to anybody
Just how shitty that was whether I fell off a cliff in it or I did something like worst. It's terrible gaming video gaming
Jump king. I beat jump king. What how dare you? I what do you mean jump king?
I beat
I beat jump king
All right, whatever you could be free to nominate whatever you want
But I it is gonna ask it goes through the academy after the nomination process
Uh, and also best gaming moment something that I did something you never thought I was ever gonna do
something that was
You kind of cock your head to the side and go how did he just do that?
So worst gamer moment and best gamer moment also making a new appearance. Oh, not a new prince but coming back
Worst joke taking more than five minutes to set up
And best joke taking more than five minutes to set up. I think I don't have to explain what those what that means
guys every single one of these is you can't just say today there's been like
250 streams or something this year is you it's just fresh in your memory
Also worst stream of the year and best stream of the year. Good luck with that one
What do you think? What's the worst stream of the whole year?
Of this one get out of here
Making a new appearance this year because it's very important. I'm
This one. I don't know how this is gonna play out
Because there's been a lot. I don't know what the nominees for
worst joke of the decade
Will be that also includes youtube
Because we are at 2020 and I have been doing this for almost 10 years
I've been on youtube and on twitch for
just
Barely under 10 full years
Worst joke of the whole decade
Best joke of the whole decade. What do you think is the best thing i've ever done like joke was
Best joke of the decade. Good luck with your nominations. And then one final thing
This is a this is just fun
I could do it on my own
I maybe I was going to think of maybe surprising people about this
But even I and a few other people that I would bring on to try to do this wouldn't know all these
We're going to do a compilation
For all the times i've lied on this stream
or on youtube
so if you if you have
uh
if you have
Something that you would like to nominate for a time that I have lied
And you can give proof
You can show it
I'm going to make a large compilation video of every single time i've lied
Ever or just this year ever?
All lies of the decade
That would give us 20
Well 19 categories
does anybody
have
a category
They would like it for a viewer's choice
19 categories
I'd like to make it a clean 20
Best category worst category. I removed the me me shitty ones like best ice cream worst category best category
They would just fill her dog shit. They're not in it this year
Best and worst face worst face is on there. I'm not sure you can have a best face and worst face
What would a best face be?
What would what would a best face be?
Loudest vroom. I mean that's not even
I know that's not even nominations
That's just what was the loudest car go? Okay. All right
We have to have we have to find it somebody's we got to find the loudest rooms of the year
Let me add this let me add this that's so stupid
loudest fucking rooms
Oh shit, hold on
Why is this I don't want to do that
Jump king is not gonna win
I would be shocked
Best ignore stream moment. How's anyone gonna find that? That's a good question
That's a really good question
Hey, any nancy droop
Now, where's my writing music?
writing
Music, where is it? I like that stuff. It was good. Here it is
Okay, so uh anything else besides uh, the loudest of rooms of the year
loudest of rumors
Anything else
Best beatbox moment. I don't know if that works
loudest rumors of the year
best chat image
best
Best comment germa has read that's kind of a one guy. That's that could be filled in the one guy moment
best clip
Best clip of the year
I feel like it's tough to do best clip of the year because the best clips of the year might actually be in a bunch
of these categories
Isn't that just one of the most yeah, that would be like the most viewed ones wouldn't it? Yeah
Worst excuse of the year
Best qrs
Well, it would just be the original one that happened that happened this year, right? I feel like that's gonna get nominated for something
best singing moment
That was this. Yeah, that was like in January February. I think
How about best singing?
I feel like they can only be five or six nominations for best singing only because i've probably only done singing like that
Four or five times this whole year
Do I do that a lot? I sing a lot
It could that be a worst singing and best singing of the year
I don't think that it could happen
It's gonna be hard to find
All right. I'm gonna put it on here
But remember keep in mind some of these categories might get removed
If they have two nominations, you know
I'm not gonna do a full thing for that. All right, let's do that. What best and worst singing of the year
Let's put it right here
worst singing
and best singing
I already know what's gonna be nominated here like thousand times
Also, I don't want to go too far and have 30 categories. Why not something about the community like best community created content
Oh, I don't I don't want I don't really want to do that
Because I don't want to make community content a contest that will show up at the end of the year
Kim and auto best kim or best auto moment
I can name you four or five times or he just kind of kim opened the
All right. That's a joke
that's a joke category because
It's going to be the same clip five times in a row
it's going to be kim opening the door behind me and
auto in her arms
Four or five times in a row. It's not even
Just auto moment. All right, best auto moment. I'll allow it. That's just that's stupid enough for me to think it's funny
All right, best auto moment
Okay, I think that's good
Worst hair new character face beater chat experience
Best auto moment best and worst singing best and worst noise best and worst impression worst meltdown
Best one guy moment best and worst gaming moment
Best and worst joke taking more than five minutes to set up best and worst stream of the year best and worst joke of the decade
Times i've lied and loudest rumors of the year. Peter is a year-old meme. I know it goes. I'm good
I want it there. I want it there because I know i've said it a few times this whole year
Who the fuck's even going to find it though?
It's time to retire Peter
No, it's not
No, it's not not in nest. I okay i'll retire it after this
But the people that aren't here right now that are going to watch that stream
I want them to see that category and roll their eyes
All the way to the back of their head. That's the only reason why it's on here worst
cat puke
If you think that that's a bad noise or a best noise go ahead and nominate it. We'll see
Best scared moment. It's gonna get bloated. It's gonna get bloated
It's it's gonna start with I gotta put the can on it
Biggest all right. How about just instead of just biggest scare or best scare best scared moment. Okay, that that works. That's good
All right, and that's it. That's i'm capping it here. I'm capping it here. Best scared best scare moment. There you go
So, let's see. We got
One two, three, four, five six, seven, eight nine ten
Twenty twenty one two twenty three that's twenty three categories. I don't like that. That's like a scary like fucking horror movie number
Uh, so we need one more
Or i'm deleting one best jubate moment
No, not best not quietest of room
That's not even gonna make any sense
Best star wars shirt
That's funny
best star wars shirt
Best outfit I don't I wear the same like four pieces of clothing guys
Best hair. No, there is no best hair. There's only worst hair
biggest chin
Best new character
Has it been enough new characters this whole year that have been I don't think it has been
All right. I'm gonna put it on here. I'll put on worst and best new character
I mean it might I don't know if we have enough but we'll see
That that's 24 categories and 26 different videos
That's it
Check the pinned message in the new year's new year
New year's eve awards discussion channel
Talk about it go over them
The new year's eve nominations channel is only
It is not a discussion channel. I'm gonna put rules there and i'm gonna pin a message there
So you can see and you can read the rules there
basically we want
category
What the category is and then a short sentence or so why you think it should be there?
best feet
I I've showed my feet on camera once and it was because I was in a dunk tank
That one why did I read that I because like 50 people have been saying it
All right. That's it
There are your categories
so as of
As of some point early next week
I'd say
I want to give
I want to be able to have plenty of time
to put together the videos for the nominations
so
I'm gonna say
Let's see. How many days do you guys need like six seven?
One two, three, four five. I'd say by like early late by late next week
Because then that would mean
That would give one two, three four about five days to make the videos. Yeah, so as of thursday
As of thursday night at midnight
There is no you're we're not taking nominations anymore because I want to give at least one two three full days
Of being able to put these videos together
Thursday was two days ago. Well now it's six days from now
Oh, you know, I think no we can handle it. We can handle it. We can handle it
I'm gonna i'm gonna like hire a few people to do this. So all right 27th 27th
As of friday the 27th
At midnight, you can no longer send in any nominations
That'll give three full days. I'm gonna bring on at least four or five people to edit this stuff
So we can make sure we can get it up so just about so almost almost seven days from right now
And you know what? That's the end of the stream. Yeah, that's like it's that's it
I'm not going back to nancy drew right now. That's not happening. It's like seven and a half hours
Maybe i'll pick up pick up. Uh, how do I save the game?
All right
After we do ai dungeon tomorrow, maybe i'll just finish this
Because that's the plan tomorrow. We're gonna do ai dungeon
best nancy drew betrayal
I'll be i'll be left tomorrow
Yeah, that's the first time I save the game in seven hours. It's insane
All right, that's it
I did save it. All right
Let me turn this shit off
best drew crew breakdown
It should be a lot of fun though
I might try to get a few other surprises done
For that stream. I can't it there's been a lot of stuff going on. So
Last year that was a ton of fun
It was I loved everything about the kind of worst of the year stuff. So
It will absolutely be fun
What day is that stream going to be that stream will be on new year's eve
december 31st
We will probably start because I want to drop the ball
Uh like I did last year on um
What did I do last year? Did I do eastern the ball drop eastern or did I do ball drop pacific?
I think I did eastern didn't I?
So it wouldn't be insanely late
So the stream will probably start
around 7 pm
Eastern right or like eight. No, no, no eight. No, no, no, no
Nine nine pm eastern give us a few hours
Yeah
So that stream will start at 9 pm eastern
6 pm pacific
on december 31st and we're gonna go through like we did last year and have the ball drop and
Go over the worst and best stuff of the year
but for tomorrow
See you in ai dungeon
And maybe finishing uh drew crew
Green screen doctor camping hype
Yeah, if i'll try to get some stuff made
But let's do let's do the bits and the subs and everything and then we'll be back tomorrow
Let's rewind
Back back back somebody some anonymous gave a hundred community subs
my god
There was a shitload of community subs. It was like a bunch of there was a couple 20s. There was a 60
There were three plus hundred community subs tonight
A lot
But we covered I think most of them. Hopefully I got them all
And uh, we're gonna start with cruel cruel gave 300 bits
They just say hi. Well, hi cruel
Uh ko legacy. I think I got caught up, but you gave 10 community subs right at the beginning of the stream
I want to make sure I got it
Dark soul. Thanks for the 250
Hey guys back at you again with another bit donation. Can this donation get five poggers in chat if we can
I'll make another whole two dollar donation remember to like favorite and ring that donation bell
for more bit donations
Thanks a lot dark soul. Appreciate it
Thank you
Tara alacran for the 251 bits
Imagine having a gaming office but not chilling out for a quality overhead projector
classic low effort low production value germa stream
Overhead projector. Oh, I know
Okay
Well, whatever that's all good
jerma sucks is one of the people that gave
They gave 61 community subs in the beginning of the stream and then the more after that
My god raf rod 10 community subs
gme gone. Thanks for the thousand bits
Jerma, please put that letter up for bidding and donate the money my god. It's a masterpiece
I got them both right here
I'm just gonna bring it to like e3 and hand it to somebody
Thank you so much for the thousand bits
Appreciate it
Uh, thank you
Thank you minority matilda for the 500 bits
It's my birthday tomorrow, but no one's available. So I tried today. No one came. So i'm just eating at red robin alone
Gonna make this gonna make them sing the birthday song to me
I've been around since your judged red video and i'm glad you took my nancy drew suggestion
Because we all now have drew fever you and your community bring so much to my life the time where I
Acclimate to adulthood. I mean drew crew. We've got to represent the drew crew
Uh happy birthday
uh
But red robin's the uh, the hamburger place, right?
It goes red robin yum, right?
I actually don't think i've ever eaten a red robin
Being an adult sucks. Sometimes it's true. Happy birthday
Yeah, it's
You just learn
You learn to kind of grow
i'm still doing it
But is kim singing kim is like scream singing downstairs
I just hear like
I can hear it
Best singing moment nominate for best singing you guys couldn't even hear it probably
uh, but
Acclimate to adulthood slow
Take your time
There's no rush
Thank you so much for your 500 bits
German you stink. Ha ha ha xd
That's fine. Thanks for the 600 points. What you guys know is that translates into fucking streamer money
It does not
Hey the jewish bro. Thanks for the 700 bits. I was scared during your drunk bit because I didn't see it
Start so I thought you had lost your damn mind
Yes
I wonder how many people actually came in
I looked like
Absolutely, I looked haggard
You know, I looked like I looked like haggard
Wait, is haggard drink? I don't think so. I think maybe he does
Butterbeer. Yeah
That looked real bad
I wonder how many people actually are really concerned they came and they left because they're like, oh yikes
This is a stream. I don't want to be on tonight
Turned me drunk at it. Hold on. This is it. Let me see
Somebody's been at drink more
Somebody's been that person
This does look real bad
person
It's I just I have this stained mouth. It looks so bad
All right, let's keep going
drunk
I do okay. I gotta like get it together
Thank you for the 700 bits though. Thank you beans for the 500 bits. Do your best scottish accent
Okay
I'll give you the best scottish accent I could possibly do
Thank you
Uh, thank you lizard amiibo for the 300 bits. I was gonna write something more sincere
But fuck it. I just want to say that this is the hardest that was the hardest i've ever laughed in a long time
Thanks for always keeping it wacky and then did wacky and a bunch of cool text
Germa sucks. Thanks for the 250. This guy eats lipstick. Lol. W
Thanks for 250 again. Germa sucks. God. I hate this gamers
God, I hate gamers
Why?
Why do you hate gamers?
Thank you germa sucks and thanks for a huge amount of subs
Thank you michael smells for the 300 bits. I'm giving you bits for this dumb fucking not joke
But holy shit jerry, please stop please for the good of mankind. Please stop. Please. We love you, but please
What?
I did them all. Thank you hank cheesecake for the five community subs
Sad vega. Thanks for the 250 drew crew. You can't fool me. I say what's going on here. This isn't a crew
It's a cult and I'll have nothing to do with it
It's not a cult
it's a group of people that come together that are not part of any type of religion or any we just get together and we
Play the same game together
What is the definition of a cult?
What's the actual debt a system of religious? Yeah. We're not a religion. Sorry
Nancy the drew crew is not a religion
so
Dark soul, thanks for the 250 millionaire streamer steals nancy drew drew crew tagline from local chatter
See you in court. Hope you put on your best lipstick and uh,
Kill your money. Goodbye. You sicko
Hey bro. Luck. Thanks for the 500 bits. You didn't have to go to fucking law school to answer the three-part video game prompt
What what do you mean?
fail cakes, thanks for the 700 bits
Uh, there's no message. They just say pride 100 seven times
Thank you fail cakes. Thank you so much for the 700 bits
You wrote kiss
Oh, you wrote kill put on your best lipstick and kill your money. Goodbye. It's kill
Thanks for the 700 bits fail cakes though
damn
Hey squim pst. Thanks for the thousand bits. Hey germ wanted to say thanks for making the drew crew thing in your streams
Uh me and my sisters have a tradition of playing the nancy drew game drew games every year at the holidays
For as long as I can remember so thanks for bringing back my childhood. Welcome to the crew
I flew off the handle during the that like red light green light
Light up the white light segment. I didn't I say that there was like the 27 of these games were worthless or something
I was really mean
I'm supposed to be the leader of the of the drew crew and I said like every one of their games is terrible or something
This is why nobody talks to me
Because I can't like oh dude. I wonder if like germa talks to any game companies. No, no, they don't they don't nobody
They don't they won't talk to me
I that'll never happen. Dude. Does germa have like any sponsorship opportunities with a couple of companies though?
They probably watched the xbox 360 red dead rant and they probably are like, holy fuck don't close that window
old navy gaming
But yeah now welcome to the crew
Thank you squim psd and nancy drew is a classic
All of them you're not you when you haven't had your cheesy toasties
Oh, that's so sad
It's true though proof. He hates games. Let's see
Now I know this one. This is when I say that
I thought that was edited for a second not edited
somehow
Listen to that part right there
Is that is that impossible for human to do that? Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Maybe it is
Video games suck video games suck video games suck video games suck all video games none of them were fun
That's not even a meltdown. That's just me speaking facts
Hey
Sick kilos
Uh sec kilos thanks for the 500 bits germa
I recently bought red dead on xbox with backwards compatibility, but it says I don't have a card on file
Do you have any experience with this issue? I know you played it on stream and like 20
Did I didn't even read this one?
until right now
This is from two hours ago, by the way
I didn't this is I just saw this right now a card on file. Why would you have to have a card on file?
I don't I still don't get that
I want to buy something from your store
Okay, please, uh keep put a card in so we can store it and then buy it
Just let me buy it
You sure you don't want to store the card and then buy it
Here we go again
Uh, we had 120 community subs come in in
30 seconds of each other
Anonymous gave 100
Whoever you are. Thank you for your insane contribution and then nat kitty gave 20 right after it
Thanks guys
And why don't we take a look at how fast is it going to fly by?
Because they were a shitload of community subs
Let's just bump you here quick. Sorry about that
Uh, let's run them
Good luck reading those
It's hundreds of people
Thank you guys
And thanks to the people that
For some reason drop huge huge amounts of money on this stream
Much love to you. Thank you
Thanks for continuing to allow me to do the things that I do the things that I want to do
So
Am I ever gonna watch joel's movie and maybe a few years?
Uh, it's not done yet. I heard
But seriously
It's a lot of people. Thank you guys
We still have a few more bits to do. We have future gamer for 250
Uh insane cannibal caught on stream
It's actually kind of scary look at this scary image
Not that one
Not that one. It's a different one. I mean, that's also pretty scary
There you see him
You see
Where is it?
I see him
Enhance it. I will I just i'm gonna cover up this up
Wow before we do that
That was this future gamer's image. We also have 250 from butt squire who has a couple of images
There's me as the joker
I do I feel like you did. Did you enhance this?
Here find me find me. Okay. So where is he? I think I see him
Here's another one to look at
Yep
Okay, that was from butt squire. Thank you butt squire. Uh, very nice
Thanks for the thousand bits. I dreamed that I was sitting on a public toilet
And I heard you talking in the adjacent stall about how global warming is killing elephants
I was surprised to say the least also any thoughts on doing twitch sings
I will do twitch sings after new years
because I just put a category for best and worst singing on stream
And I feel like if I do that stream before the new years that'll take up every single slot
Maybe but thank you for the thousand bits ten bucks from very nice. Thank you
Appreciate that
Uh snooze and copter. Thanks for the 250. I was curious if you can imagine the taste this would have
Because for the weirdest reason I do
Everyone that had one of those old tvs probably can try it. Can I taste this?
Let's see. Can I taste this?
all right, uh
Taste this. Mm. So I can smell this
It smells like electricity. Do you guys know that kind of heavy
Electricity almost metallic smell that electricity smell
I know that there's people that can't
I think some people can't sense that right
You're like ozone. It's like that ozone smell that ozone in your nostrils and in the back of your throat
Yeah, I can taste this image
Yep
Any chance you're also going to revisit the sims with new mods
Maybe one of the older sims games too because they have other wacky mods
um
I feel like I did the sequel and I did the sims 4 and then I did the sims the sims 4 sequel
I feel like if I want to do that again, I would probably go back to one of the older ones and do something ridiculous
Because I've never really played the sims 2 or the sims 3 on stream
But yeah, I thought about it. That's what I was asking
Oh, yeah. Yes
Yes
Hey 25 dr. Pepper over 25 flavors in dr. Pepper. Thanks to the 250 worst impression goes to ed stark
You're not going to do it. I don't think that was this year
I think that may have been two years ago
Two more bits to do and then we're going to take off and see tomorrow for ai dungeon and maybe some more nancy drew crew
Esparta escalada thanks for the 250. Hey germa. I had an awful christmas celebration with my family today
And his dreams always cheer me up when I feel bad. Just want to say thanks
I'm really sorry to hear that
Nobody deserves to have a shitty christmas
I'm sorry to hear that
Regardless of however you celebrate it. I know people some people do a few days early
Some people do a few days after family travels. I understand. I get it
I'm sorry to hear that but
If this stream can cheer you up
I'm happy it can
very happy
Can we get one more germa wink before you leave? No, i've i've removed my shirt. It's off. I had to take it off
It's like I got lipstick all over it
But thank you esparta escalada
Anything else show official thanks for the 500 of bits not encouraging your nancy drew here's some stuff that is not encouraging your nancy drew stream
Also, just posted some images and projects in the discord for you
What on earth is going on here?
All right. This is uh
I like this one
This one is also a scary image
We got fucking scary images
This one is this is the scary one. We'll just do that one now
It's very large this is in blunder so you probably can guess what this is going to be
Jesus christ, what's wrong with my eyes?
Confirmed bald the more I look at it the more I feel like it's staring into me. I have to get it off the screen
Here's the other one
God damn it. Oh
And we also had from tingy
Thank you tingy
for the 250
And they say listen tingy say i'm still hoping you can get that rollercoaster tycoon 2 mod working where we're the guests in the park
I don't think you can
because
From what I understand
It's just not it just doesn't work anymore. Just not on anymore
The server is turned off and I would have to make my own server to host it or something
I think that was what we came to the conclusion of I can host it. I can host it. I can host it
There was a lot more to it and it took it was going to take probably another few days to figure that out
But i'm looking forward to tomorrow. We're going to do ai dungeon
This was this stream was very strange
Uh, I feel like this was like six streams
Because i'm thinking about the activities that were done and the things that happened on this stream
And I feel like that was over the course of the last like four days
That was a lot of different streams together
I was like changing channels in my brain
All right
Good night guys. I'll see you tomorrow ai dungeon may be finishing up nancy drew
for the drew crew
Good night. See you tomorrow