Hello, good afternoon, morning, or whatever, good, how, wherever you are, hi.
Welcome back to the stream, hope you're having a good day. Today we're gonna be playing Lisa.
Nope, just kidding, that's never happening. Today we're gonna be playing Doki Doki Literature Club.
Nope, just kidding, that's never happening either. Today we're gonna be playing Garfield
Cart 2. Just kidding, that's never happening either, that game doesn't even exist. How could it happen?
Mystery game today. Fuck you, Lisa's amazing, asshole. I didn't say the game was bad,
I just said I'm not gonna stream it. I didn't say, hey, by the way, Lisa the Faithful,
sucks. See, not clipped that one. Now I fucked up your clip. I'm gonna clip him saying Lisa the Faithful
sucks, you know what I mean? Not gonna happen today. Thanks, Zoidberg. Hey, you're very welcome.
Come on in. Everyone's saying Ratatouille. Well, here's the thing about Ratatouille.
I promised I would play Ratatouille on the 28th. The problem is, I didn't buy it yet. I said I
bought it, I said I owned it, but that was just, it was sitting in my cart, so technically I did
own it, temporarily speaking. Liar. He's a liar. That's not how it works. Anyways, so what we're
gonna do today is, because it's a mystery game, we just changed the title to something.
I'm gonna cue, let's put the title to, please spell that. Please spell that word. All right.
Yeah, today we're gonna be playing, I don't know, I can't spell this fucking word.
How do you spell this word? Is it one? A? Two A's? No, I keep my fucking promises.
Ratatouille! Is that loud? How loud was that? I told you guys I was gonna play this on the 28th.
I keep my promises. I keep my promises. I do. This is the original. There's like a bandaid over here.
This is Disney Pixar Presents Ratatouille, the video game from THQ. I actually looked this up a
little bit. This game apparently is fucking terrible. Every review place gave this game like a four.
The game sucks apparently. I don't even know, I don't understand what the joke here is.
I think two people said play Ratatouille and I was like, okay, fine. Well, congratulations. You and
your friends made me play a game on stream. Hey, Slalom, thanks for the five community subs and
for Litty, thanks for five subs too. I appreciate it. I unironically love this game. I don't know
why I'm so excited. I'm like, I'm like a lightning rod right now. I'm like ready to go. I don't know
why this game's gonna be fucking terrible. You know what's funny? I've never seen this movie.
Let's go. Sign in and continue. Yeah, I don't, whatever. Who cares? No storage device has
been selected, you know? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's fine. On the hard drive. You've never seen,
I've done, I've never seen this movie. I swear to God. You go, oh, I could go right to the
cheats if I want to. Let's play the story. Yes, for those of you that don't know, I just hit,
I just hit accept on the first generated name that Xbox gave me. I didn't even care. What the
fuck would I even care? Am I, what do I need to be German 985 on here? My Xbox 360? We're about
to start a new game. Would you like to continue? Yes. Select the charms for access to other areas.
Oh, collect the charms. Okay. Og, this is David's Xbox. Well, it's my Xbox now.
Got us some third party sellers. Thanks, Dave. Okay, cool. So, so far so good.
Kind of looks like, um, even pinata a little. Does this follow the movie? Do I have to watch
the movie if I beat this game? Yeah, you're clean, pal. Move it along. Yes. It's just the movie.
Just about dad. Can't a rat work in peace around here? Is that Pat? Wait, is Pat an
Oswald the rat in the movie? Cause we got to get those charms collected before her nap time's over.
He is? Oh shit. Charms to be collected boys, so get moving. If we're crying out loud,
Emil, stop eating all our supplies. What supplies? Keep an eye on your brother. This sucks,
turn it off. You know how much of a pain in the ass I was to get this game?
Just a pain in the ass, a real pain in the ass. Oh, I thought he was like smelling his butt.
I'm not gonna fuck this on and skip it in the beginning cut scene. That's not happening today.
You know how much shit people gave me to make sure I played this game on today's date?
All right, here we go. Welcome to Remy's home, Mabel's farm. Here you'll learn what your job
is in the colony. Ollo, Emilie. Okay. This is a charm. Collect as many as you can to unlock
rewards. Press A to jump. Double jump. This is a double jump in the game? All right, that's kind
of cool. It's an edge grab. God, remember when Xbox used to just give you fucking achievements
for no reason. You know, you can whip your tail to break stuff. Pretty cool, huh? Give it a try.
You can even use it on enemies. They just didn't even care. If you can hit them.
Jumping on the first stump. Come on, try it out.
He's doing it. Tail swipe. Okay, so it's just an attack. Okay, is this game like an hour and a half
long? Please say it is. You unlock bonus pack one. It's desync? Me or the game? What do you mean?
It should be, it's a game? Game sound is all fucked up. Hey, Jerma, slugpog, thanks for the
five community subs. Thanks for being an emote that'll be deleted in about three months.
Sound is early. All right. All right. Sounds good, right? All right, let's keep going.
Slugpog. I don't even know why it's activated. It's chili peppers.
You cook in this game where you just walk around and collect coins.
Oh shit, this guy's dead. Go pull us to help him.
Pick up an uppers beat. Okay, and then drop it here. Chili peppers can be used to destroy
certain objects in the world to defeat enemies. Tail swipe and get away. Okay, cool. It's a little
platforming game. Like every single video game that comes out that has a license.
Something must be wrong with that wood. Some objects in the world will have a glow
outline. That means this means the ready looks like you're gonna need to make your own bridge.
What do I do? Try hitting that other plank. I'm convinced that every single movie and TV game
that came out from like 1998 to 2010 was all the same engine, same video game that has put
different assets sort of in the game world. It's all the same exact game. Oh, I can smell.
These things are easy to use. Wrong. It's not wrong. Just jump on and go to town.
They just shared the source code with every single movie that was within six months of release.
You got to hold down your jump before you release. They changed the coin in this game to like the
cheese in another game. The cheese turns into like a star in the other one. Boy Story. Yeah,
Toy Story had like fucking action figures instead of coins. Use the same springboard to join me.
You can find out where to go next by using your sense of smell. Nice. I'm so glad that
there is like a fable to just walk this way. Idiot button. I almost fucked that up. Hold A
to compress it. Oh, I see. Speaking of which, German should play Dead Space one and two for
October. I actually might do that. Whenever you come to a wall or a pipe, just jump towards it
and grab on like this. Why am I playing this game right now? There's like no reason to be playing
this. There's so many things I can play right now. Grab, jump, and press B.
Okay, how long is the game? Somebody said it was... Oh, that's health. I don't have full health.
This game is 40 hours. It's 20 plus hours. No, it is not. The only way this game is 20 plus hours
is if level one through 10 was copy and pasted 30 times. A rappel object will work on all swarms.
Do I get to use the food? Please tell me I get to cook. You can't make a rat tattoo game
and not have cooking. I don't want to just like walk around and spray bugs.
Did I die? Oh, okay. I was just waiting for like Dark Souls text to pop up and go like
No. The underbuck. All right, now what? Give me more instructions. Chili peppers can be used. Yeah.
Oh, God. He's playing this. Yeah, I am. Because when I tell you I'm going to do something,
I'm going to do it regardless of how detrimental it is. Let me get the strawberries.
I don't hate it yet. I don't hate it yet. I kind of like it. Need another chili pepper. I know what
to do. Get up here. Is this it? Okay. Can I ask a question? Is the reason why everybody wants me
to play this game regardless of how bad it is? Because this is everybody's favorite movie here.
That's why, right? And you overlook how shitty this game is because you love the movie so much.
All you care about is like the characters talking. Right? If you want to jump on top,
just do this. You're watching like a reunion show, you know, that's a kind of tired and old.
But it's still your favorite character. So you like it. Get rid of enemies.
Not to mention, it's a whole lot of fun. That has really bad taste.
Now let's see if you have as much grace as I do.
Use the ball. All right. Jump on the ball and press B and you can squash the bugs.
There are surfaces in the world that will hurt you. I can get on. Okay. I can use the ball to
jump on surfaces that will hurt me like poison. That's one letter grid coming up. Does this count?
No, it doesn't count. The car actually has to turn. Oh, that's too bad. When do I get to grab
onto the guy's hair and like fuck with his brain? Like pull his hairs and then give him a headache.
When does that happen? So you see the pretty sparkles? Well, jump where they are and you'll
end up exactly where you want to be. Cool. Huh? Graphics are actually pretty good.
Yeah, they're pretty. They are. They're not bad. Let's see what you got.
Jump towards any highlighted point and press B. Use the left stick to balance. Oh, okay.
The Tony Hawk manual. Easy. Just play Tony Hawk instead. No, I'm playing Ratatouille.
Everybody thought that I was not playing this today too.
Everyone was convinced that I didn't buy it. Balance. What the fuck are you doing? No, no,
guys. Of course I did. Whoa. Sorry. I don't think you can fail this. This is not failable.
All right. Cool. We're good. Climb a pipe. Climb it. All right. I'm interested so far. I'm
interested. Check this out, Remy. Grab it, pull back and release the launcher. It's a flinger?
Now, watch the master. A fucking eagle just scoops him out of the air with his claws.
Use the ratapult. Stand underneath it and hold B. Sorry, Remy, but you need 20 charms to proceed.
What? Did I get soft-locked in the tutorial? What do you mean I need 20 charms?
I got paywalled? How did that even happen? How did that happen? What? What did I do wrong? I just
followed his instructions. I missed the coins. I did? I thought I picked them all up. The water
pump handle is stuck. Try jumping on it for a reward. Oh, there's going to be coins in here,
right? That'd be... I thought they would just collect... Yeah, I didn't know I needed them.
I guess I need them. What do I get? Oh, that's a coin. One? Wait a minute. I need 10 more coins.
10. Did I just run past them? What do you mean 5? Oh, there's a charm hidden in the stump. Blow
up the box. All right, I get it. No, no, no. I'm supposed to lose here. This is just a tutorial
to explore and learn and figure out what happened. I need to use the rat on a ball to reach this charm.
Right. Okay. Where's the rat on a ball? There's a ball. Is there a sprint button?
You know, Remy, if you just use all four of your hands, you could probably go so much faster than
this. All right, there's this one. You can dash? Oh, shit, you can. What did I just do? Failed it?
No, I didn't. Oh, that's fast. This is literally a plot point. Collecting coins? I've never seen
the movie. I know I'm going to piss off a lot of people when I say this, but I always saw Ratatouille
as a filler Pixar movie. Like, it was... Oh, yeah, they came up with like three or four every year
or two, and it was like, oh, this is one of the filler ones. I don't need to watch it. I'm just...
I'm not saying it's a bad movie. I'm just saying that's how I saw it when it first came out.
Oh, shit. Cool. What was this? Take that back. Look, I'm not saying that that's accurate. I'm
just saying that's how I felt. What do I do with this? You know how Pixar and Disney came out with
a shitload of 3D animated movies? There was like 30 of them over the course of 10 years.
Some of them, I was like, I don't know. I guess it's all right. I didn't hate the movies or
anything. Apologize for that. I'm sorry. No. Apologize for what? I didn't say anything.
Oh, shit. Find the valve and fix the sprinkler. What is this bullshit? I don't want to do this.
Wait, chili pepper. There's one down here, right? You're a Disney hater.
Look, once they announce the live action remake of Ratatouille, then I'll care. How's that sound?
You actually can do that. Oh, well. What? What just happened? Did I die? That was a trap.
What a rat's got to do. All right. I need more coins. I got that one. I got that one.
All right. I get that one right there. Daddy will trap. Yeah. What the hell was that?
All right. What's your, what do you, what do you want to see for a live action remake for Disney?
Nothing. That's true. Who cares? That's true. That's right. Yeah. Who fucking cares?
Okay. Once they made the third one in a row, it was like, all right, I don't care anymore.
This is fucking stupid. You want cars? Okay. That, that would be actually pretty cool.
I need to find a valve. You would have my attention with a, oh, valve. All right. Wait,
what happens if a rat fights a squirrel? Imagine looking at what you went to and seeing this in
the backyard. What do you do? I would freak out. I'd be like, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I would just go out and start clapping my hands. Really? Sucker punch. You fucking piece of shit.
Nice sucker punch. I kicked your ass for like five straight minutes and then you're going to
go, my back is turned. Typical fucking squirrel move. Stop. Leave me the fuck alone.
Give me this thing. All right. Come on. Come here. Get over here. Stop it. Hey.
That's so stupid. All right. Get me out of this. Blow up the squirrel.
That's evil. I'm going to blow up the squirrel. All right. So what the hell is that dude? Yeah.
Well, let me get up there then. Oh, I think, oh, I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
Um, why is it not spraying me? It feels like jump on these. All right. This is fucking dumb.
I do. I really need to get more coins. What a tutorial this is. All right. I didn't mean that.
I think there's a friendly. Are you friendly? Yeah. I just hit the no. Oh yeah. Of course not.
I'll get the chili bomb. Is this what it's like when we're not looking like every like
toy story and shit. When Andy's not home, the toys have a bunch of fun and they play games with each
other in the animal world. When the humans aren't looking, they kill each other. They eat each other.
They rip each other's heads off. Everyone thinks, Oh yeah. When the animals are together, they talk
and have like fun adventures. None of the rat literally gouges out this little chick's eyes
with his hands and then eats his brain. They can't make a movie about that though.
All right. What the fuck am I supposed to do here? Something I can, I can bounce on.
I need to, Oh, we need to roll in here with the rollie. Wait, I see that guy, this thing up there.
Oh my a psycho. That's real. That's real life. That's what happens. Like in real life,
these two would not have a conversation about their taxes. The dove would come down.
He'd get tail whipped. He'd get bitten in the face. The rat would lose its tail. This other
rat would come over and start eating the other rat, even though they're both rats.
I need to get on top of the tractor. No, it isn't Jeremy. You have to go outside.
What? There's a hole over here. Hold on. Oh, there's a flinger.
Play chess? Holy shit. Wait, I need to play chess.
Oh my God. There's like a thousand coins up here. You collect it. Wait, to glide. I can glide.
How do I glide? Just told me I can glide. Wait a minute. I can do a Mary Poppins.
Oh, cool. I got 20 charms. I gotta go find Eddie. Rats. You looked in, by the way,
you looked in your backyard to see this many rats. Eh, probably time to actually put the trash out
rather than skip it three weeks in a row because you, oh, fuck, I forgot. And it's like already,
it's like already 8 a.m. I can't get the fucking trash out now. I can already hear the truck
coming down the street. What am I going to go out there in my underwear? Like hold on a second.
I've thought about it before, but then you can't. You just can't do it.
How do I get back up here? Yeah. And then you go over in your head. Is it embarrassing for me to
go out there with messy hair and underwear and like a pair of socks or not have my trash out?
Oh, fuck, I don't know. I don't know. What if I get caught on somebody's ring cam?
I'll wait till next week.
Well, need your help. With what? This. It's a cookbook by Auguste Gusteau, my favorite chef with
all sorts of mouthwatering delicacies. Wow. I didn't know you could read.
Just come on. We'll get it now and I'll tell you more later.
I'm getting huge bugleberry vibes from that guy right now. Huge.
Oh, I thought the old lady was shooting a shotgun. She has a shotgun. It is a shotgun.
Does this happen in the movie? Does this happen in the movie? Oh shit. FPS mode. Run, Remy, run.
Why does the lady have a gas mask on and a shotgun? This actually does happen in the movie.
Holy shit. Oh, OK. I have to actually run.
Make your step and stuff. Get it next time. Go faster. Step in this. OK, it doesn't matter.
Go. Trying to get her to step in the mousetrap. That doesn't do anything. OK, cool. Those mousetraps
are from me. Touch that one. That was horseshit. God, no. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my
God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh no, you lose speed. I'm dead. Being a great chef sure isn't easy.
Imagine seeing grandma. Yeah, this game so far has been look out your window and be surprised.
The old lady outside my window shooting at a moving truck with a gun and a gas mask.
Uh, www.sillo.com and a new apartment in your area that are available now.
At least I'm a good cook. I got shot by the gun.
So you're telling me that there's a point in the movie where an old lady with a gas
mask on is shooting at the rat with a shotgun. You don't want to see this as a live action movie?
Sure. I didn't think of this one first. What did they do first?
What was the first live action remake? I'm almost so excited about it.
Shit. Cinderella. Oh, come the fuck on. Really? What? That thing is just in the way.
Wasn't Cinderella. Cinderella was like a daytime movie.
Talk about like a real remake movie. That was like a TV movie.
Fuck. I'm looking at chat. Somebody said Tarzan. Oh, that was also like a TV movie. Made for TV.
Cinderella was a made for TV movie. It wasn't in theaters. Stop looking at chat. Oh, well.
Okay. Honest to God, I'm going to beat this. I can't be one of those people that plays like a
three hour long licensed movie video game. It takes like three hours to beat, but I spend like
40. And I walked into that like on purpose somehow. And that one too. I don't even know how. I have
muscle memory to do a fall joke. I swear to God. I don't even know why. I didn't do anything. I
was trying to win. Okay. I just tried to jump, but it didn't do shit. Jump. There's enough
batteries in this fucking thing. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Go. How big is grandma's front yard?
Oh, I had an ammo. Sorry, grandma. Sand Raider. Boom, baby. Collected a health container. Oh,
so I got extra health. No reloading in the middle of combat. After the sewer, it's time to cook.
Oh, this looks open and annoying. All right. So does he read the cookbook now or does he already
know how to cook? And why does the rat already know how to cook? Where's his skillet? Where's
his fucking burner? Where's his microwave? You're not real. Why am I talking to an
illustration from a book? Excusez-moi, I am chef Auguste Gusteau. Don't you feel like if you
grabbed the tip of his head and pulled him up strongly, you'd make him look like a normal
person. Oh, gross. Feeding chum to dogs on the street. This isn't in the movie.
My restaurant from five stars to four. Rebuild Gusteau's. I think I can handle that.
Turn on captions. Is it available? To find a mission. The compass can tell you where to
find a mission market. Oh, no. You wish to begin a mission. You must start with the mission market.
I thought a mini mission beacon. What fun. Why don't you try a mini mission?
Timed challenge. You want? Sure. Great. Two minutes to do something. I guess to follow
him around. All right, let's go. Timed chaos build. It's kind of slow. It's actually the name
of a small like three part series I did. I thought it was going to be a huge hit. I thought that was
going to be a huge hit for the stream. Minecraft was just getting traction. Everybody loved it.
Didn't really work out so well in my in my head. It was a little different.
Collect enough of these items and you'll be able to open a tall mission. Wait, I need to collect
these to get a mission gate. This time gate shit currency gate. Fuck. Wait, why am I so heavy on
the right? Oh, no, you've lost the race. Let's start over. Oh, it's a race. I thought I was just
following him, but I kind of need to see where he goes. I don't know where to go.
Okay, you know what a really, really super pro player jumps off the edge, hangs on the edge,
jumps up and hang on the edge just because they're bored and they know every inch of every second
of the game. Pretend I was doing that. It's going to be a long stream. It is not. It's not going to
be a long stream. I have a finite amount of time I'm willing to give to Ratatouille, the official
licensed video game stream. I don't know what that is. I'm not sure if it's 20 minutes or well,
it's been 40. So that's wrong. All right, I'll get it right here. It's been longer than that.
All right, come on. I can do it. Going to the right. All right, don't fuck this up and I win.
What the fuck is going on? Collect enough of these. Wait, I'm going to open a tall mission.
Get it! I win. It does sound like Yoda.
Not really, though. He did for a second. Supey assistance. All right, cool. I'm looking. Yes,
I'm ready. I'm ready to have fun now. Here comes an actual cooking mission.
Oh, Supey mission. I mean, he kind of does. He did one word was like, oh, everything else was not
Yoda at all, but I get it. The soup is terrible. Use the spices to fix the soup. Knock the cheese
that is on the top shelf into the bucket below. Complete your tasks and don't let the chefs catch
you. This is a hidey hole. If you're spotted by a human, you need to run inside of a hole.
All right, so let's. I know you are hungry, Remy, but can you help that chef make a soup?
Spice is OK. Sounds like a plan. He said that rat's going to kill me. Oh, fuck, I broke it.
Oh, they have to go over here. OK. Imagine that. Imagine jumpscare on the guy on purpose.
You know you can fix that soup. What are you waiting for? It is kind of like Yoda. You're right.
The same noise I just made. I can't even boil water. Fucking useless. I can do that and I'm stupid.
All right, where's the next over here? All right, come on, ding. I did. He just saw me. He just
looked right at me. All right, was this this two more? There's two. All right, there's one across.
OK, I gotta climb up and then go down. There's one over there. Blind him. You know you can fix
that soup. What are you waiting for? You've been detected. What are the hidey hole? Tell you where
the nearest safe area can be found. Hurry, hurry, hurry. What? He's that much of a psycho? Yeah,
that's it. OK, so can I go from here? Can I jump from here? OK, I know where to go. How long do
you stay over there for? Oh, up. Hold on. There's one over here. It's an invisible wall, of course.
Oh, and this is bad. It's really bad. It's really bad. OK, I'm all right. I'm OK. I'm OK.
You know you can fix that soup. What are you waiting for? Am I stuck down here? A rat's got to do what a
rat's got to do. Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go in the hole. How do I get that
one? What the fuck are you doing? All right, there it is. Cream. Find a way to tip the ingredients
into the pot from. Got it. All right, there's only one more. Quickly find a place to hide.
All right, now backstab him.
What's his name? This guy's name is Linguini? Like Paul Linguini?
Fuck. No, turn around, turn around, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, camera, camera, camera, camera,
camera. I've never seen that. I've never seen the movie. I have not seen this movie.
Sheesh. The great chef sure isn't easy. I guess I could go that way.
Which one should I get? The one up top or the one down here? I'm going to get the one down here.
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry. You know you can fix that soup. Stop shitting up, Yoda. I don't need this force ghost to
tell me what to do every time. All right, there it is. Got it. Four to four. Now what?
Now what? You need the last one regardless? You do? I need the cheese. Oh, bullshit. Is that the
cheese over there? Is this the cheese up here? All right, hold on. I got to distract him. I'm
going to go, what's that timer? All right, we're good. You know, what can I tell you? I love good
food. Soupy assistance mission completed. You know, rip out the chef's tongue. Psycho. You,
that's you. That guy's gonna unlock hidden bonus material. Oh, well done, Remy. Well done. Perhaps
you can also use your nose to find all the rats. It's a perfect place for a colony of rats.
I thought I had a condo or something. Is that the end of the movie? He gets like a condo with the
guy. Thank goodness you're alive. Dad, it's great to see you too. It's dad. But what are you doing
here? We're here because of your harebrained scheme back at the cottage. It's hard to move.
I got a condo. I'm sorry, dad, but I'm here now and I want to help. How do you know that but not his
name? Follow me and we'll get to work. Guys, the main character that's an animal or some mutant or
alien or something that lives at the end of the movie with the other main character in a weird
kind of like odd couple scenario, that's half of every fucking movie that's ever existed.
Aha, there it is. Every Disney Pixar or animated movie that ends like that, always.
It happens in B-movie. Remember B-movie? He moves in with her in the end of the movie.
It would be so nice if you could speak to your father.
Okay, okay. Does that happen in B-movie? Yeah, it does. All right, let's sniff. What's that?
Trash. Is that auto? Okay, when there's food, any food. If I order like take out or something
or if I bring back something from cooking, you look over the side of where Otto's bed is and he
goes, he goes up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. It's the cutest thing in the world. I kind of
miss the force ghost guy. Where should I go now? I'm just going to go this way.
You could speak to your father. Find him. There he is. Okay. Hey, okay. Thank you.
He's still around. He's going to be a presence the whole game, isn't he?
All right. Why can I smell my dad? Did I walk by him? Jumping is fun. That's about it.
Okay, I just put my hand up to my face and like did like a like I'm going to talk to the microphone
and I like touch my work on like my fucking hands and all and I got it on my face. I didn't like
that at all. I hated that. I'm not doing that anymore. I don't like to lean in and make like
a hair. I'm leaning in doing a thing. Doesn't mean I'm going to get water on my face. No,
I burnt this thing off. It's fine. This is like 8,000 people that just happen to say that. Like
2,000 of you know what I'm talking about. That's a funny joke. Okay, okay. He's right here.
How do I talk to my dad? The colony is counting on you to distract that human and get us some
food. They feed dogs a bucket of scraps in the courtyard every day. We need to get a hold of
that bucket. Scare the dogs away from the courtyard. An idle rat is a worthless rat.
Find a coin in the bird's nest and bring it down to the courtyard. Be careful, son.
They're the gutter of the clutter. Maybe you can help that. I did that one.
Find all the light bulbs. We need the light bulbs. Live in this place up.
Oh, God. I got to do all these tasks. There's one cooking mission. Next game, please. I can't. I
can't. Dude, the next game is... Oh, look. This one already right here. Where's this one?
No, no, no. I don't want to go back to this stink home. I already did that one. Oh, shit. A cat.
Don't be afraid. Just go in. I've got a bunch of Xbox 360 and Xbox games back here. Whatever it
is, it's going to be on Xbox. I'll pull something out. No, I'm playing Ratatouille right now.
Talk about that later. Get me. Grab something. What's the point of this?
What's the light bulb one? Oh, the dog. Scared the dog's way. I got it.
There's my restaurant. Yes, and I'm here to see it. Why am I doing this? Stream the movie.
I can't stream the movie Ratatouille. How do I get up there? From here? Fuck, there's something
else here. Stream rationing. No. Hey, that cat just threw a fucking rock.
This floating thing is called a mission market. All right, that's all I wanted.
Hair balls you. X-Men Origins waiting room. No, you can't. Listen, I bet you you're the same guy
that said Ratatouille waiting room with a resident sleeper on it like six weeks ago.
I bet you you're the same guy. I was playing a game. I was doing something and I saw like
resident sleeper, resident sleeper, Ratatouille for Xbox 360 waiting room, resident sleeper,
and now I'm doing it and here you are again. You can't keep moving the goalposts.
I'm here. Find a way to scare the dog. Yeah, guess what? When I play X-Men Origins, Wolverine,
whatever it is, the same person is going to come in. They're going to say, oh, man,
fucking feeding frenzy for popcap.com waiting room. That's not a bad idea.
I'll take that idea soon. All right, hold on. I gotta wait. This looks kind of hard.
Wasn't there acid? Saw waiting room. Stop it. Find your way to the other side of the alleyway.
Yeah. Boom Beach waiting room. Isn't that like an iPhone game? All right, we're good.
What do I do about this? Oh shit. I know it's a steam valve. Fuck it. God waiting room. Jack
and Dexter waiting room. I'm okay. I'm going to have to stop you on that one. I'm playing
Jack and Dexter right now. I may as well. It's just playing the same game.
I'm going now. It's not timed. Oh shit. Wait, I'm going to fuck this up. No, I'm good.
I scared the dog. Knock off a tomato can. Peggle waiting room. I played Peggle on stream.
I've already done that, man. And why did you turn around? What was that for? More Peggle.
You don't want more Peggle. I know you don't. Because I extreme fevered almost every single
level the last time I played it. What more can I do to impress you? You can't get like 20 extreme
fevers in a row and then be like, yeah, I mean, like you could do better than that. No, I can't.
I cleared five levels in a row with one ball. I can't ever replicate that again.
Oh shit. That was cool. It's down here. Oh, this is just a way to get back up here.
A permanent environmental upgrade. I'm a one ball omega low. I'm trying. I'm trying to stand
with like that. Where you come from with this one. I don't get it. Club Penguin. No, nobody. You
don't want. OK, the special request video games. I think a lot of you have to understand. OK,
the special request games. It's really OK right now. There are 82, almost 8300 people here right
now. Four of you really want me to continue to play this and you're like you got your popcorn
ready. You were like, holy fuck, I can't believe you playing this. My favorite game ever when I
was a kid. And that and I'm doing it for you. You'll get yours eventually. You will. You will.
You're going to say like, oh, dude, remember that game Mischief Makers for the N64? Wow,
you should play that, dude. I loved that game when I was a kid and I'm going to play it for you.
One day. I didn't see that. Being a great chef sure isn't easy. It's right on my neck.
Why even balance? Just fucking go. Onimusha waiting room. Onimusha.
How do I know what that is? Nice. All right, I'm good.
Almost there. I don't fuck it up. Being a great chef. I hit B on it and it didn't do anything.
I didn't miss the coin. Play League of... Okay, that's one thing I will never play.
I promise. Okay, you know how I said that like four of you are really excited that I'm here
right now playing this game? There's probably like 3,000 of you here that would be excited
if I played League. I don't care. I only impress like three people, not like 5,000. I'm sorry.
Got it. All right. I scared the dog. This is such an elaborate way for me to scare this dog.
I'm guessing I'm going to keep going. Oh, God. Minigame unlocked. What minigame?
Play Neverhood. Maybe one day. I kind of like this game though. I'm not kidding.
Typically by now I would be like, oh yeah, let's do something else.
No, not today. I kind of like this. It's kind of fun. I don't hate this. What am I doing?
Find a way to scare the dog. Wait, right here. This is it. I'm not going to kill the dog, right?
The dog almost just exploded. Oh, now. Wow. Wow. Mission complete.
Should we do Jinx at the Sphinx? Right. Yeah, that's another one. That's another one. You'll
see, maybe. Somebody said worst stream contender? Get out of here. I'll give this a request stream
and get out of here. Ban that guy for real. I'm just like having fun playing Ratatouille.
Get out of here. He's still playing this? Yeah, I want to play it. It took me. It took me. It took
me. Hold on. Let me detuber that a little bit. It took me like three months to get this game and
find it and be like, yeah, I guess I'll pay for $75 for it. No, I'm playing this for like another
at least 20 minutes. The dog is gone. Yeah, we got dog shortcut unlocked. Those four guys don't
even exist. Yeah. Oh, they don't? Really? Really? Okay. Let's find out. Let's see. I'm curious. Hey,
excuse me. Sit down for a second. Let's do a straw poll. Straw poll. Let's see how many. Okay,
it's more than four. If this gets more than four votes for yes, I like this game, keep playing it,
then we're good. If this gets less than four votes, I will change to whatever game you want.
You ready? This poll is called. Here we go. You like this? Yes. No. Here we go. If this gets more
than four votes. Oh, fuck. All right, we're good. All I'm looking for is four yeses.
Oh, would you look at that? Two, 300, 500, 600. It's 40% of you guys.
42%. It's more than four guys, isn't it? Those are bots. Shit, a lot of people are voting on this,
by the way, and we never get this much participation. It's like 3000 votes right now.
Find the chili peppers. All right, avoid the thief.
Ooh, if I have to, but only because the other rats are counting for me.
Seven boxes left. All right, let's go. People happy. Yeah. Do a new poll. That's 45%. That's
more than one. Dude, those four guys aren't even here. You're right. No, they were replaced by
apparently like 1300 people. People have spoken. The majority wants me to stop, but the large
minority wants me to stay, and that's what we're doing. I never said this was a democracy
right now. I said this was a one guy moment, and there's 1500 one guys. I'm going to clear the
gutters. There was gerrymandering. No. Okay, I got to clear the trash. You're distracting me on purpose
now. You're doing this to me. What is this? Robots? You're distracting me on purpose because
you know that I'm going to be like, okay, I don't understand what to do or where to go, so we're
going to play saw. I don't even say that. Guys, even if I put saw in, I don't even know where to start.
There's like an hour left of saw. All right. Okay. Are you listening? Are you listening? Are you
listening? I will finish saw tonight. Okay. Are you all right? Are you good? Are you good? All right.
No way. Yeah. I will finish saw one tonight so that we can prepare for saw two during
the Halloween October month. Get that back. 24-hour stream. It's only been one hour, so
no. It's not going to be even close. This game is fucking sick. Actually, it's not even that bad.
You guys need to give it a real chance. How much was left in saw? Like one to two hours,
right? There was like less than an hour or two, wasn't there? Four hours? No way.
Irma's chat fucking sucks, dude. Where did it go? At first, I just gave it. It was like, oh,
fuck this. All right. I'm going to go a different way. Can I not jump? I'm going to knock them out,
pick it up, and then run. Here we go. Was it diminishing returns on the stun?
Fuck out of here. Leave me alone. World of Warcraft. Oh, shit. I can do a double here.
Please don't tell me I just screwed this up. Did I mess it up? I think I screwed it up.
Oh, shit. Does it still work? Like Ghostbusters Remastered. I hope this still works.
Doesn't have to be like in the indicator. Oh, thank you. Oh, I got something. Is there any
good Ghostbusters game? Yeah. Okay. That Ghostbusters game from like 2008. It was pretty good. It was.
It was all right. I wouldn't necessarily say it was the greatest game I've ever played. It was
pretty good. I liked it. It did a good job. Can I drag the box? I don't think I can drag anything.
I'm really getting another double.
One clean gutter. Coming up. Luigi's Mansion? Nah. Nah. No, Luigi's Mansion. Not right now.
Okay, there's only two more boxes and we're good. Oh, how funny is it that I played Mario Sunshine
on the GameCube and they just decided to HD re-release it. When I saw that, I was like,
come on, man. It's been like fucking 15 years. Like what are you doing that after I play it?
Hey, watch the stream. Nintendo watches the streams. Shit, I gotta go the other way.
It's trash. Is it? Yeah, I guess it's been confirmed that the head of Nintendo of
Antarctica watches the streams. I've gotten DMs about it. How do I get this over there?
The hell? Can I not go that way? Can I drop this down? I can't throw it.
Ow. Fuck. Easy. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Leave me alone, squirrel. Leave me alone.
Ignite it and then talk. No, I got it right here. All right. Is this the last two, right? Yeah.
There's one more. Shit. Bro. Bunker ass. Last one's down there. I got it. I know, dude. I have one
box left. Are you watching the same person? Who are you talking to? It's obviously not me.
Last one. Oh, I can walk it, right? Turn off the tutorials. Oh, all right. Am I going to die if
I fall from here? How much fall damage is too much fall damage? Wait, it's exploding. Oh,
that's annoying. Fucking ruined. It's fine. Yoda is stupid.
Yoda's not stupid. Yoda's one of the smartest Jedi ever. All right. You cannot let it go at all.
You cannot let it go at all. It has to be very gentle. I probably shouldn't even get this one
then. You're stalling for viewers. You think that's going to help me? Stalling in Ratatouille is
going to help me with viewers? It's the other way around. I can't get this one. This one doesn't
work. If I drop it, what happens? Of course. Fuck. Whatever. Let's go the other way. Oh, dude. He's
definitely stalling to lose viewers. That's what you mean. No, you guys aren't going anywhere.
I just saw baited all of you. Now you're going to stay to the end of the stream.
You're going to watch all the ads. You're going to watch. You're going to stay the whole time.
You're going to keep my engagements up because you know saw is coming at some point.
I've been saw baited. It's going to happen. I'm going to play saw. You know what I am.
It's not yet. This is like, okay, I'm going to go like activate a bounty for saw
and the whole time I'm going to be streaming naked. Trying to get like 50,000 viewers here.
Okay, now let's play saw for the bounty. I have to have as many people there as possible. The
sponsors think it's cool. I just stream naked for an hour and then I turn the webcam off,
turn on saw. It's a sponsored stream. There's 50,000 people here. I call this guy that's
sponsoring the stream. Hey, come look at the stream, man. There's a lot of people here right now.
Holy shit, man. That was a good idea to like have to sponsor that stream. There's 50,000 people here,
dude. And then 20 minutes, like 30 minutes later, I get banned. Hey, we're just like checking in.
We saw that your channel has been like permanently removed. Huge numbers though, by the way.
Yeah. So what's that payout look like? Um, it's like, it's like $700,000. Okay. Time to retire.
Goodbye. Oh, what's that? Carrying cash. Oh, nice to have to negotiate that like in your
contract with a sponsorship or like if you do to claim this. Yeah. Is it okay if I stream like,
you know, naked for an hour? And then if I hit like 100,000 concurrent viewers,
because I'm like the naked guy on Twitch, because that's still counts, right?
If I immediately switch to your game, it has to. What's that for? What's that for?
Hear me? You play. Oh, I want to play mafia. That's another thing I'm doing. Oh shit. Let's
do that tomorrow. Let's play mafia tomorrow. The mafia remake. I'm playing that tomorrow.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Playing mafia remake tomorrow. Good call. Good call. Oh, there's nothing there.
I'm going to play it anyways, but good call. All right. What are the missions? I have like two or
three more, right? Yeah. I want to play mafia. I've heard it's good. I've heard it's very,
very passable, which these days passable means good in the video game industry. Now
six and a half out of 10 is now a nine in this new world. We're in a video game.
Olives. Oh, spit them out. Gross. Crush them up into oil. And you got my attention.
Not whole though. Disgusting. Cutting board calamity. Oh shit. This is a cooking mission.
Would you date Remy if you were a rat? No. I may. Does somebody say olive eating challenge?
Or am I making that up? Smash 30 veggies before the time runs out. Oh shit. This is cool.
Just a trash compactor. Scream dark souls. What is this spam? You should scream dark souls while
naked and you start the camera resolution at like one by one pixel. And every time you die,
the resolution doubles. I think it's a great idea. It's like a sword art online,
but instead of dying in real life, you slowly get exposed to tens of thousands of people all
over the world. That's quite the challenge. Imagine you would be trying as hard as you could. That
would be a silent stream. Oh, wait, wait, wait. This is important to think about one by one pixel
that doubles in resolution quality or that increases in how much percentage
every time I die. How long would it take before your penile area is visible? How long?
One times one. How many pixels would it be for you to determine like the actual area?
Two, two, four, four, eight, eight. It would take like five deaths before I got banned from the
fucking site. 20 deaths, 32 by 32. But it would have to be like wicked blurry too. And like every
time you died after it got to like 32 by 32, how many times did I die in dark souls? That's what
I'm asking. I think I died like a hundred and like 12 times. So not only would it be visible,
but it would be in 4k by the time that I got to there. So that's not going to work. What a great
idea. Your penis takes up one pixel. It's so like fucking rude and like weird and gross and unnecessary.
Have you explored? Oh, okay. Let's keep going. Pixel dick. That's fucking funny. That's funny.
All right. I don't, whatever. It's a, you clicked on the mature audience thing when you got here.
You're fine. You are aware. We're all mature audience here. You clicked it. If you collect
another one, one by one of one pixel webcam that increases in quality, but you're naked. So you
better not die more than 50 times in whatever game you're playing. That's such an unbelievable.
That's like such a fucked up. I'm going to throw up. Where am I? I hate this. I hate this so much.
You have no idea. Where am I? What? All I heard was get it. Oh, this sucks. I don't want to do
this one again. Come on. This shit. All right. Do it again. Get it next time. Are you going to play
Hades? They put a huge Easter egg about you in the game. What are you talking about?
They did. All right. I got to beat this. That's debated. I would, I, why the hell would they,
what would it, what is it? That's just a monster debate. Is that what you're telling me?
Come on. I need two more of these damn things. Come on. Oh yeah. Come on. One more. What sloppy
piece of shit. There's 8,000 people here watching you play ratatouille.
I mean, yeah, I guess there is that speaks to the quality of the video game.
Right. That's people you're interested. I'm interested. No, it's not time for saw.
All right. I'm doing it. Let's go. One, two, three, silence. You have bots. If you, okay.
If you think that I've been doing this shit for 10 years and at year number 10 is the year that
I decide to turn on bots. I don't know, man. What? I don't know. Tell you. Come on. All right. Left
side. Three more. Hey, let's never do that again. I collected cream. Nice job. Twitch
username here. All right. What was, what was I doing over here? Oh, I cleared the gutters.
Now what? I didn't get to the next mission. Springboard race. Get to the end. Sure. That's
right. Oh, this is awesome. Okay. I'm going to do good. Is it okay? Odd watchers skip ahead.
15 minutes for saw and gamer wort pixel. What? Wait, is that implying that I'm going to show
my hand in 15 minutes? I'm not going to do that. I need a, where's the, I need a,
where's the, where's the other missions? I need more missions. I'm going to go back to the rat cave.
Wait, no, over here. Have I gone over this way? Shit. I can't go that way. Um, should I go?
No, I'm not doing a wort reveal. That's disgusting. And I don't want you to see that.
It makes me sick. Thanks for signing up for this trial run of Twitch bot services. And we hope you
are enjoying your personalized ego boost. I'm going to read the rest of that just because I
feel like it. You have 30, you have 30 days until your trail is over. If you were enjoying your
service, sign up for a one year activation plan. It actually, it said trail. I didn't say trial
wrong. It was trail activate. I should probably like alt tabbed. And you guys saw that I had a
view bot running and it was like 10 view bots. Like apparently I'm so, I need those extra 10
people. What am I going to do? Tell me. I want to know the missions, dude. That was a repeated
joke. Same joke. No, it's not. That's not true. That's not the same joke as last week. The joke
last week was if I just revealed that I have view bots, not that they were 10. I added to the joke
from last week. That's not the same joke. It's not a repeat. No, it's not. No, it isn't. That was a
different, that was a different piece of humor attached to the same idea. And look at the rules,
guys. Disagreeing with the streamer is a banable offense. Don't do it. I can go up there. There's
one here. There's a, okay. There's one up there. I'm going to go up there. There's a menu up there.
I can get it. Okay. Yes. Good stream. Thank you. You think so? Nice. Good. Because if you didn't,
you know what? I put my finger up and across. You know what I mean? You're banned. You're up.
Oh, right there. Okay. I see. That way. He's a murderer. No, I'm not. You're missing what I'm
saying. And I'm dead. I just did an Olympic dive. Okay. I did just say. Worst link. I'm not clicking
on any links right now. I'm busy. Wait, I got to go. What's the fastest way? Okay. I see. We're
going this way. The link sucks. Don't worry. I'm not going to soulless Marvel video. So all this
Marvel 2020 video game waiting room, soulless. Wait, is that the moment where it's the porn actor
versions of all the people get up there? Yes. What? What do you mean? What? That thing was
clearly turned off. All right. Do not. We're going to go this way. Wait, coin. Shit. I'm
actually, I like, I'm starting to actually unironically enjoy this game. You know what
I mean? I'm unironically enjoying Ratatouille. Is that bad? That's kind of not a bad thing though,
is it? I don't think so. I got a mini game. It seems like a solid seven and a 10. It's pretty
solid seven and a 10. This is where I want to be up here. Right there. Mini game.
Have you explored all of his dreams? Daring dash stage one. Was I lying earlier? I lie every day.
Sometimes I lie about a lie I already told. So there's a double lie going on and I don't know
which one I actually tried to put off as real. And I, oh, what do you mean? This one again?
Didn't I already do this one? I walked too far and went over the edge. That's how well I was doing.
This one's way harder than the other one. Under, underneath both of those, by the way. Good.
Hit detection. You know what I'm saying? Hit, hit, hit, hit. All right. This is fine.
Yes. What'd I get? Chocolat. Great. You don't ever do that to your ear.
Otto will be up in the bed sometimes and I'll just kind of roll over and I'll feel inside
of my ear. Just and I'm like, have you explored all of his dream worlds?
Oh, have I? Nice. Okay. There's another one. The ant army has invaded the courtyard. Clear the
the courtyard of 10 ants before time runs out the courtyard of the 10 view
bots they got already lost shit they have the same spider movement pattern and
binding of Isaac and that's why I hate those enemies huh I could beat the hush
with my eyes closed but I will get hit in the first room five times by the same
spider kill this I am anymore three more reminds me of Madagascar I mean they're
both just licensed video games look that person just came in and what did they
say you guys told me I wasn't I was wrong you said I was like I you're a
guy do you mind they're all the same game that person just came in said oh
well this looks just like Madagascar remember we talked about that rooftop
rolling yes let's do it Erty gee nice that I'm unlocking these for David and
not me everyone you cared about this shit remember when you really truly gave
a shit about achievements and you do the most asinine shit in the game to make
sure you got like a hundred points I hope you're not afraid of hands I think
I've got this height thing under control I remember I played Viking for the
Xbox 360 and I remember wanting there was like an achievement to kill like
500 enemies and I was like I'm gonna do that I want to do that I don't think
this game sucks I don't even care I need to kill these 500 enemies to get the
achievement because I want it find a way get the coin from the bird's nest in the
coin to the rain gutter and drop it down actually Viking was kind of good wasn't
Viking a good game it's kind of fun Viking was like God of War for the ps4
kind of way worse but still good throwing books out the window at me okay
honey poo waiting room sure hey make sure you watch every single stream start to
finish might happen and watch every ad what happened you new viewer here well
look at we look at the poo stream could happen I'd have to stay here don't leave
there was a 0.0001% chance that there was a poo stream okay there's also a
0.001% chance and you're gonna get that like burning team captain but you still
opened 5,000 boxes now didn't you stay here
what's a rooftop oh I got just I got double force ghost think I've got this
height thing under control no problem where is it it's on the rooftop
hey I apologize sorry sorry sorry for saying those two letters back to back
if you tired I'm sorry food is most definitely good oh up get on the ball
and go up to sludge was that Lincoln shot right now I have no idea um I'm
not gonna click it for at least a little while
Remy your father said a coin is in the nest on the rooftop I hope you're not
afraid of me afraid of height aren't I on the roof of course not and I climb
this I have to run into this with the ball shit being a great chef sure isn't
easy all right we're fine Remy your father I hope you're not afraid of
unlocked a bonus pack afraid of heights of course not like it okay let's see
what you guys got here not bad but I mean is it is it really is it that good
oh shit it's a one by one dick pixel wrong okay well what's the right one
lover German clicks as he has to play Glover you guys know that I this is one
of the first games I ever had for this n64 if German clicks as he has to play
Glover I did I clicked it is the reason why you say Glover because you're
watching me do the the ball here don't you turn into different hands in this
game there's like five different hands one of them is like a strong hand one's
like a quick hand I remember this game we're gonna play
Glover now not right now the n64 is one of the only consoles I have not really
done on this frame and there's a reason for that I just saved the best for last
we've done 3do Sega CD PlayStation 1 PlayStation 2 GameCube Xbox no we've
not done any and 64 why is that conquerors bad for a day that's illegal
can't play the illegal ones in the nest on the rooftop I hope you're not afraid
of heights I think I've got this height thing under control no problem I mean
your father is afraid of high from the skylight above the air vents lead to the
nest sounds easy smell the create through the glass yeah isn't like
conquerors bad for isn't like a sex scene in it or something something in
that that's not okay it's like this is like a sex scene in it or
something this level is pretty good this is a good level this is not a game
that's worth skipping I'm sorry wait I check over here oops okay we're good I
need the ball probably then there's a respawn of a ball here conquer Wow so you
guys don't know where the original conquer unbelievable people like minus
doing that because you think I'm just doing that like all that he made like a
conqueror voice you've never played Diddy Kong racing them unbelievable
that's unbelievable to me and that it makes me upset unbelievable you want to
play conquerors bad for that but Thursday but you don't know what the
origin of conquerors and you don't know what that voice was really you want to
play conquerors bad Thursday but that's it you don't know anything else
oh I win this one well there it is simple no minus four keep it up buddy
monkey yes bring the coin to the rain gutter minus four yeah you don't even
know how the minus system even works I think there's like a problem with the
minus system can we do the plus two's just to see if it works I'm testing it
out just to like see minus two somebody they did minus four and I like fucked up
the algorithm a little bit so we have to do plus two to even it out a little you
can see my face right now I just had the grossest face bonus pack what's that
even mean I'm getting trolled stop trolling me now I'm getting trolled stop
trolling me into the gutter sick I beat it yes good job rooftop rolling mission
complete construction complete it'll do I think I only have one more mission to
do don't fit you have my I'm intrigued oh this is for right now I see the joke
stock for today all right so it's been an hour 50 so all right I know that it's
being gamed I know you guys are fucking around what happened on me something was
really really funny like 20 minutes and then at 21 or 22 minutes that was
something happened nobody was happy even at 21 minutes what happened what I do
was a joke in the game up doing that you're crashing being a great chef sure
isn't easy yeah we were on a complete uptick here and now everyone's
manipulating the market I still want to do the market thing a lot more involved
than I thought it was gonna be all right dad now what now what I'm gonna
help the gang distract the human so you can get the bucket contents to the sewer
great this is the first major encounter of the game you're buying 29 28 calls
well I'm sorry if you just did that you're you just got manipulated dude you
just got you just got absolutely destroyed you bought those calls let's
say you that we was a big $500 worth of calls the second that you hit the accept
button they were worth $40 damn damn oh that's not good
Celine needs the handle to work the gramophone find the handle and bring it
to her coin you found earlier will help us distract that human
what it find you and knock it is a large coin from the gutter find the faucet on
so we can hear the gutter all right this is fucking time must wearing by the way
perhaps if you find the handle to the gramophone
shit this is gonna be bad I'm gonna mess this up like three times I love this
game it lets me cook all right got it now let's go bring the handle to Celine
who is standing near the gramophone I get out of the way with a gramophone if
you find the handle to the gramophone Celine can get it to work oh shit good
turn it on yes just do minus two yet poor guy is gonna owe money you're gonna
margin call the guy that bought 20 calls don't do that what you need to flood the
gutter tie a rope to the faucet so it can be turned on a rope turn off the
music why what do you mean turn off the music and that's done
that's complete last one is over here somewhere what is it
yep it dislodged the thing some music sucks whatever you'll be fine you don't
like like French Bistro music why not where is this thing that I have to get
where is it I don't see anything
stop it to lean turn on the gramophone stop saying minus two you guys are
ruining everything so if you find they're ruining everything they're
ruining everything that hurts my head remember you must find a way over what
let me see it's Scott it got it's got so bad if German clicks he has to spend
five nights at Freddy's 2 no I will not do that I'm sorry that's never gonna
happen guys I played five nights at phrase three on the iPad for no reason
what maybe was four I installed it I downloaded I bought it and I played it
maybe five minutes and then I deleted the app off the iPhone or the iPad I
didn't want played ever again I was like this stupid why did I buy this
ah what what happened did I hit my jaw on the edge why I just stone-cold stunned myself on the
edge of the concrete crashing we're crashing the bucket we're gonna crash
the bucket and what you guys don't know is I sold at the top already I don't
care crash away for I can't get it to work I made $14 well the German stock is
only worth like a tenth of a penny you guys got just being a great chef sure
apps if you find the handle to the gramophone
can get it to work you're a crash yeah German hey hello ladies and gentlemen
welcome to German crash the series where I crash stop dying on these the series
where I lose all my money at the stock market you blew my you've ruined my whole
joke the whole the stupid ping-pong thing apps if you find the handle to the
gramophone Salim can get it to work stop I have to pay attention to the
video game for the love of God pay attention where did it go sir I got the
run-in stimpy sound effect that came back in the life of what if you find
there have been a full to almost two minutes he's delirious no I just I had a
good germa crap joke and it got ruined that was a good one it would have been I
got interrupted in the middle of it turn the music off camera why is there why
is it extra loud what hello ladies and gentlemen welcome let me see if I can
get it correct I'll try it a few times hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to
episode one of German craft the series where I play minecraft it's pretty good
I need to have shitty your mic though that doesn't make sense all right so how
do I get that coin I get out okay I gotta go I get a Mary Poppins into the
thing all right actually robot playing my dad if I go in here with the ball
nope my dad if I get that showers off my head probably if you find the handle to
the gramophone perhaps if you find the handle to say grab a phone I can do
accents yeah I can do you know French or you can yeah can you give me a little
bit of a sample sure I have to go to this store today to get some of the
Tylenol very very good very good mods do something what happened everything okay
what's going on somebody add it to his portfolio now be careful in the stock
market seriously if you like it we make like jokes about stocks and be careful
because what happens is when you if you buy like a stock let's say you have like
an app or something you have like a like you just like Schwab or whatever the
fuck you use you think you're a genius you buy like five shares of fucking
Toyota or whatever and it goes up like 4% you make like eight bucks you're like
oh I'm the smartest man alive I can't fucking lose then you make one bad call
and use 500 bucks just be fucking careful don't be in it don't do it be
careful all right how do I get this lodged up in the sludge I can't get it
come back later that music does that music is hell well I gonna wait people
aren't gonna want fake meat oh stop reminding me of my past fucking mistakes
I was so certain so certain I was not more certain than anything else in my
entire life beyond meat was worth like fucking like 40 billion dollars and I'm
like there's no way there's no fucking way that that's gonna stay like beyond
meat was worth more than like every American manufacturing car company it
was more it's more expensive than any like all the airlines combined I'm like
this stuff there's no way it's gonna stay like $300 a share it did stay there
for a while don't die the hell do I need to do up up there I'm gonna go up there
now where the raid coming in with raid raid raid raid raid raid coming in from
RT it has not happened yet you guys are spoiling the raid it didn't happen I
don't see it yet oh it hurts I know what you mean now it fucking hurts listen to
this welcome guys playing a rat tattoo we were the Xbox 360 this was this is what
we call a special request Sunday somebody requested this and there's the
coin oh shit all right I gotta get up there how do I get up there how do I
can't get up it's not possible wait climb the I don't know it's Monday by
the way yeah but this is moved over from Sunday it must be yesterday but I I
don't know if I had diarrhea or something whatever how do I get up there
oh I see it I see it don't die it's not even that far of a drop it wasn't that
far of a draw but thanks for the rain welcome everybody's a gramophone all
joke for the new viewers hey guys welcome to the fall joke stream I fall
and I go and I fall and I go up and I fall and I go up and I fall and I go up
hope you had a good stream though dude so Megalel bad so Megalel bad shit this is
what you have to do what do I do from here shit why can I go up all the way
here okay I saw somebody using an emote it was a laughing face and a finger
point and it was like a cracking up face and a finger pointing and they wrote so
bad so bad so bad I don't know why I was making me laugh I can't turn it off
there tried it's even worse no no no no no it was like a human finger it was
like a human finger pointing right at the screen finish the level dude what
do you I'm trying what do you think I'm trying to do this game is one of the
hardest games ever this is one of those games that has a bunch of bugs and
glitches and it's got tons of difficult platforming it's one of the hardest
games on the 360 it's one of the hardest things is it a limit emote oh yeah yeah
it's it's just like a pointing and laughing it's just so like rude so bad
like pointing and laughing alright guys I I might I need to be like 11 to figure
this out apparently how do I get up just go up unless I'm trying to do so bad so
bad oh mega holy shit dude this dude is oh mega bad okay this way I gotta go over
there but I don't think I can make it from here dead again I'm dead I'm dead
I'm dead I'm dead I'm gonna go pee clockwork no I'm not not yet hold on do
this one first mark echoes I played that already you think you're pulling out
some really really obscure video game I've done I played that already on
stream I played the mark echo game already how many link that person to
where it is can I climb that I can climb this all right let's go I'm very back
okay I needed a drink too take a little sip no I'm I don't know why I'm laughing
there's no reason to be laughing I don't know I just somewhere in my head I
thought something was funny somewhere and I just started laughing it I don't
know why there well at least I'm a good cook I am just one of the weasels from
who frame Roger rapid I know that already I'm aware of it completely you
climb this please Remy fucking idiot yes the guy you guys think I say like fuck
well are you fucking idiot yeah I think I do I almost got air shot oh yep don't
know what there's so many roads that lead to nowhere I thought I died I'm
okay break through the window are you serious are you kidding me was I really
supposed to go through the window I'll try it I miss the music don't you I
really missed the hold on hold on okay I missed the music I don't shoot it
through the window that was wrong nice try though I appreciate it where do I go
this one's dislodged up there but then I have no idea how to go you must find a
way to the water faucet I lay force ghost I've done that I don't know what
the guy's name is no idea what this guy's name is there's the force ghost
chef his name is Alice Alice oh fucking wait I gotta do it in an order it's an
order you do the turn the phone on turn okay you turn the faucet on then you got
there's like three rats just die there's like this for rats you do the turn on
the phone the phone let you turn the faucet on the faucet then lets you
dislodge the coin somehow with some of your friends I got it here we go one two
three perhaps if you find the handle to the gramophone perhaps read chat more
sad boy why am I sad sad I don't think I'm sad right now I think I'm fairly
happy right now I'm very happy who said I was sad I want that person timed up if
you find the handle to the gramophone I want that person timed out to work or
long fucking time an hour oh fuck that's a long-ass time man shit one hour that's
a fucking eternity here no like this like dog years well in German stream
chat years that's like 30 years here we go this is now on now I have to find the
at the coin out okay the water is flowing now get your shit thing wish up
zip zip zip something all the water oh shit okay right right I gotta blow this
up I could blow this up okay I needed a bomb it hurts I know I'm sorry where's
the cherry bomb isn't it up here somewhere and a big view cherry bomb you
guys seen one I don't see a cherry bomb anywhere out here no it's at the very
top is it absolutely necessary right there oh zip zip zip zip zip zip zip zip
can somebody edit that for me like somebody I know this is gonna be a race
for you guys to do this but could somebody just take out all the times he
says zip in like a to like a 30-second video and just let me watch it on stream
no fucking convoked but where is this bomb I don't I can't get up there yeah
that's it I swear to God if you kill me I'm gonna be so mad there isn't one
there has to be that's how you get that I hate this fucking game so much as
triggering my fight or flight response all right fast forward to ten seconds
from now when there's a hole three monitor I'm sorry where is this bomb I
need to blow that thing up down there I'd like don't make me quit this game I
like this game I was having fun please get a good guide open the dumpster
dumpster all right where's the dumpster in this mission you have ten minutes to
do a couple of tasks which are no biggie so it starts turn your left and jump
out of the box to collect the gramophone handle and take the gramophone after
cutscene drop down to go to the opposite of the courtyard near the middle next to
the ball near a cat you will see a pallet of the gutter box in a box climb
onto this and hear that the blue had a little pipe all right let me actually
process what I just said next to the wall near a cat you will see a pallet
over the gutter and a box climb on top of this and up to the blue highlighted
pipe you got it I know what that is you should watch the movie it's good people
happy no I probably won't I just I'm serious I probably just want what when
we're gonna so much like TV and movies and shit that I want to watch that I
just have time for how am I gonna fit ratatouille I'm gonna fit ratatouille in
there I don't think I'm gonna it's the box it's the box in the gutter there's a
pipe other side see cat there's a box next to the cat box next to cat oh shit
I found it I believe you must clear a path to the sewer grade okay good and I
do this before I fell down oh I made it up here all right now fake fan no I was
doing that just to make you upset going stuck in the gutter get the ball to
Emily so he can dislodge it let's go where is he shit I need to go up there
are you killing rats in the game I'm not killing anybody and that guy for an hour
accusing me of killing something what he's trying to get me like in fucking
trouble or something like banned the person for an hour I was gonna die right
there yes I know and I just tried to do it what are you doing video game we got
final task is get coin okay oh my god don't do it please I know you want to do
like a TF2 Scout thing will you jump off a really high thing and then double jump
right at the very fucking bottom if you find their handle to the gramophone
Celine can get it to work I really I swear to God why would I want to do
this again why would I want to do this again why I just was trying to skip time
I'd like one minute left I don't want to tell my god that hurt my head when I did
that by the way not just yours literally why I don't know I thought it was really
gonna work I really did I thought I could do like a scout TF2 thing you jump
off the handle and dust bowl when you jump off the fucking roof where the
second turn is and you fall jump right before you hit the ground do the double
jump this is not the same game though oh my god I'm so annoyed what have I
done so unnecessary but like I just fucking had to I'd sorry I know what to
do I thought I could double jumps like boom right with the ground I really did
it I tried it's gonna be fast don't worry I promise I just spider-man to off
the Empire State Building oh shit okay come on
torture stream why do I always end up at the worst stream what hey man that
person right now Scott damn it what if I okay I don't know I don't know what
you're talking about having fun
I need to settle down that actually hurt
perhaps if you find the handle to the gramophone
get it to work why did I Empire State Building off what I was either that was
so unnecessary I wouldn't even try to be funny or anything I really wasn't like I
wasn't trying to make them sorry I'll get it right now don't just okay don't
let him don't let them see you upset next it's been two hours in this game
perhaps if you find the handle to actually been having fun though you can
get it to work I'm trying to maybe popular belief I've
been having actually pretty good time today this is fun words don't hurt when
you wear Gucci you said something like that I have no idea what you were
saying I'm gonna play saw I am gonna play so I need to beat this though saw
is coming up I promise this is my first stream and this is great hey welcome to
the stream thanks for joining thanks for hanging out I typically stream Monday
Tuesday and Thursday or to 5 p.m. Eastern maybe 3 p.m. Eastern sometimes
no one said yes they did oh look at the logs yes they did look at the logs I
believe you must clear a path to the sewer great the paid actor seriously
this is really finicky it just is but CBD streamer sing the song the new
follower song there is I don't know there is none I don't remember what it
even was hey you're new welcome to the stream it's such a dream or something
like that right now it's so fucking tiring okay this time do not Empire
stippling off the top some streamers do that yes and when you do that five to
six thousand times feel like that would get a little bit on your nerves do it
don't know I'm not gonna do it I'm gonna jump off into the double jump don't say
that stop it I'm gonna go down normally no I'm not gonna do it I'm not doing it
I'm not gonna do it no no I'm not gonna do it I'm not gonna do it I'm not gonna
do it I'm not gonna do it I'm not gonna do it I'm not gonna do it I'm not gonna
do it it's been too long I'm gonna go how do I get down normally though or
this way how do you actually get down from here normally it's an umbrella
where did I miss an umbrella up here hey I don't see an umbrella up here was
there there is he's blind fuck I'm so nervous I actually don't want to fall
off if I fall off again I have to turn oh shit there's an umbrella right there
you're right like if I fall off again I have to pivot to saw I do another death
here is on it's the inexcusable okay okay okay this game is fucking with me
now don't let go don't let go of a don't let go of a don't let go of a don't let
go get sweaty I know but don't go don't let go I thought I died I thought it was
dead I don't know why I thought I'm so used to hitting the ground and seeing a
black screen all right where's that coin there's the coin ah there's the
coin bring coin to what do I do I don't understand what well how do I get up
there oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I have to go back up there and go all the way across up there and get over
there somehow oh no no no no no no no no no no no I refuse to I'm not gonna
lose I believe you must clear a path to the sewer grid we'll stream buddy thanks
upset chili pepper bomb would help out up stop being chat for God's sake okay
why am I sliding stop sliding stop to slide good I win all right finally find
a high spot okay we still timed it's still timed oh fuck I forgot about the
slipperiness okay now I got to go here what
it's just an anime character that told anything slightly surprising have a new
viewer they're joining the stream gonna have a big super dream every day we get
some new bands to our club
if you find the handle to the gramophone
some cost fallacy some cost fallacy put another $500 it to be on meat put
another thousand dollars on to be on me it's not cost fallacy let's go you must
find a way to the water fast so I'm gonna play so I will in just a minute I
play saw in a minute just give me one minute get him away from the PC that is
good okay fine I'm away from the PC now I got a
wireless controller motherfucker I've got a wireless controller you can't take
it away from me I could be in the other room I could be anywhere I could be on an
airplane and still be playing right now the wireless technology that's in every
Xbox the whole concept of like the PS Vita couldn't you like turn on your
PlayStation 4 problem like your Vita and like to play a game on your Vita or
something I'm gonna go to the cat thing that's a scary concept by the way if
you do that what if you Vita runs out of battery and you're on vacation if you
Vita runs out of battery and you're like you like you're not gonna be home for
like three weeks that should just stay on your ps4 to stay powered on
what do you say smite time why would I play smite right now I need to complete this I
have to I will have nightmares about me not being able to beat like level one's
mode thing GTA 4 no look at how much faster I'm doing this right now look
we're almost done
I can't believe I fucking fell I can't believe I died and what did I okay is
the other rat traps instant death but did I just have one cube left I don't
even know they are instant death oh my god okay Grover I know I know I can
super Grover come leave me the fuck alone should have used those Dave
states fly it okay coin is done now he's gonna go to the other side I'm done I've
got it I'm gonna go for the skip and I'm gonna fuck it whatever I'm going for the
skip I'm gonna go for the skip right now I'm going for the skip right I'm
gonna get it I'm gonna go though don't get it there's an umbrella up there
shit just get the umbrella and float over there well I do that no Wow you can
actually do that okay I'm okay I'm all right okay now I have to get back up
I would love a piece of cheese right about now stop it I have to get back up
to that I'm gonna play saw we're gonna play saw I'm sorry guys I'm sorry I
betrayed your trust I'm sorry I betrayed your trust I'm gonna play saw now I'm
sorry I betrayed your trust okay I think the wireless controller is lagging even
kidding it's no it is it is it is it is it is I just pressed B I'm fucking out
of here turn turn it off turn it off turn it off oh I have to beat it though I
want to beat it so bad I want to beat it so bad oh come on man jump yep yep yep
I'm naked but I'm gonna turn it on I'm naked but I'm gonna turn the webcam on
this fucked up look look I need to everybody see this I'll just duck I'll
duck I don't even care look ready look look look look look look look I need to
wash up before I handle the food I told you fucking control is broken it's not
jumping look what oh wait a minute
stomach reveal no it's what are you talking about I was ducking in the
reflection of what okay that was me that was me knowing that there was gonna be a
frame so I blocked it with my hand I knew there's gonna be one frame cuz I've
fucked up before shit by all right I'm gonna give me a minute I'll be one more
break and I'm gonna move the saw a really important question do we gain
viewers I gained like 300 viewers when I said I was gonna play saw what I have an
important question this is really important do I even have like a save
file it's because naked what are you trying to show me here I can't even look
at this image because hold on let me change let me see he's freaking out
laughing okay that that's that's my hand okay guys I'm gonna break this image
down we're gonna break this image down that's my arm this is my arm new emote
that's my arm by the way if what you think what am I wearing a diaper am I
wearing a bee's nest is my bees net what are you talking about that's like I
don't know what that is that's like my hair that's like the top of my head you
think I would turn the camera on if I had this like bees nest ball sack on
stream all right let's go diaper okay let me put saw in I want to get I try
can I hear me out can I play ratatouille one more time please guys play rats to
one more time let me play ratatouille one more time we try to be that part one
more time okay and we're gonna play saw all right yeah let me just do that level
best to one more time okay I thought about it well I got a little bit of
water I'm gonna try one more time then I yelled I'll never play it again
does anyone remember if the saw save file is on David or if it's on my account I
don't remember I'm mine it's on tendon D ragoon okay which one can do is wait
is the webcam on is it fucking ducking I don't know no it's not okay good I was
looking just one more time all right what last try is it look I'm already
going I'm already there I'm already like all right here we go let's go final try
I promise bees nest okay dirty like rotten pair of underwear is what that's
in that image yeah it's my hair it's the light shining off the top of my head
myth busted sorry guys I get to keep my twitch account for now oh wait should I
have to play all right let's go forget how to play all right let's go let's go
this way perhaps if you find the handle to the gramophone
Salim can get it to work and by the way what's with this like dark souls 2
bullshit that the help bar if I died this many times that I can only go to half
health I need to take a humanity why am I only have four bars here this is
bullshit I don't why if you find the handle to the gramophone Salim can get
it to work I honestly thought it was your pubes you do understand I'd I'd be
gone and I wouldn't be coming back that would be the end everybody here yeah I
would be gone that would be my final image would be my bees nest ball sack
that would be it and I would I would make a tweet I'd be like guys yeah it's
been fun no these last like 10 years have been really really interesting and
really I've been a big fan of it and everything it's been a lot of cool fun
take care of yourselves and yeah do good school and shouldn't get good grades
and take care of yourselves and eat well and are and and by the way here's a link
to my patreon don't forget about me okay now I'm gonna do the cat thing there's
a cat thing over here just pivot to only fan no dude oh my god what are you
doing stop moving okay all right all right all right all right all right I
believe you must clear a path to the sewer great I believe what the fuck is
happening I'll get it next time I can't beat a kid's game I can't beat again I
can't I'll beat a kid's game I can't beat a kid's game it's over I top discus
out