Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Shuei with the new and improved Diamondback, which we're going to talk about in this video, and the... one of the knives and the dead ringer.
So, Smith's Miss 2013 came out a couple days ago, didn't really give us anything substantially new to the game, which leads me to my initial question of this video, and you guys can chime in the comment section if you'd like to.
Why did we get the Two Cities update back in November, which added a bunch of stuff to the game? They added like glowing weapons, a bunch of new MVM stuff, the kill streaks, like a lot of stuff was added in that November patch.
And I guess I'm just curious as to why they didn't wait the extra couple weeks or a few weeks to put all this stuff in a big major Smith's Miss update, but it's not really that big of a deal.
We've gotten a lot of content to this game recently, I'm not complaining really at all, but I guess maybe you could probably say that because of the big CSGO update that just happened,
the big Dota 2 update that just happened, they probably didn't want to kill their servers with like three major content updates to all their games at like the same time, so that makes some sense.
But regardless of any of this, they did more of these item changes. We didn't get any new items, but they made a bunch of the other items that are already in the game worth using.
First and foremost, we're going to talk about this main one right here, the one that I'm using right now, the diamond back. The diamond back was a piece of shit.
It doesn't matter which way you swing it, doesn't matter how you step up to the plate and you look at the picture, you're going to strike the fuck out if you have the diamond back equipped.
That's just the way it was. I mean, some people could do well with it, but it was a very situational item.
The only way you could really use the old diamond back is if there was like three engineers on the other team that were building a ton of buildings and you could really store up crits with it.
Other than that, it was just a minus damage penalty that didn't really do anything for you.
But now, now you can not only store crits with this by destroying buildings, whether it's a teleporter or dispenser or a sentry, if you backstab anybody,
if you backstab and kill anyone, you're going to get a crit stored in this gun, which means you can go on a good two or three chain stab, whip around and do 102 guaranteed damage as long as your aim is good.
We're going to talk about that because like the frontier justice, whenever I store this thing with crits, I kind of go into a mini freak out mode where I don't want to lose the crits.
I don't want to miss my shots. So I end up hovering over people and not taking the shots, not trusting my muscle memory.
And do I shoot? No, no, wait. Oh, fuck. I missed. Oh, I missed again.
Like I miss a lot of shots with the frontier justice and this. But the difference is the frontier justice has more pellets.
So it's more it's more reliable that you'll at least do some damage to somebody.
Whereas with this, if you miss that little pellet from the revolver, it's a complete wasted crit.
So this is definitely a patient man's revolver because you can't spam it as much as you want to.
Like the default revolver, you come out of disguise and you're bang, bang, bang, bang, land a few shots.
You can't really do that with the diamond back because the risk versus the reward is so high.
You want to be able to land these shots. And it's not like you can just aim over somebody's head and guaranteed get a crit every time.
It's not like that. But I do like what Valve has done with it.
I do like the direction they're taking it trying to make some spy players a little more aggressive.
So you don't just kind of kill two people, stab the heavy and then run away.
You can stab the heavy, turn around and shoot the medic in the chest.
Whether you shoot him in the chest, the ass, the foot, the head, you're going to get one hundred and two damage on him.
So you can play a little bit more aggressive and less reserved.
And probably the best scenario that I would see using this and where I think it's the most it shines the most is the sap and stab.
Because when you sap and stab an engineer, you're going to get that first guaranteed crit.
And on top of that, once the buildings get destroyed, you're going to get two or three more crits on top of that.
So killing the engineer and anybody around you, whenever you do a sap and stab, it is very dangerous.
There's always going to be at least probably a couple of people potentially around the dispenser if there's a dispenser nearby.
So you at least have a chance to protect yourself instantly rather than, hold on, I got to wait, where's my watch?
I'm going to see if those buildings are destroyed yet so I get my fucking crits.
Like, no, that's that's it happens instantly now when you get that one backstab.
I think it's a good change. I like the philosophy that Valve is taking recently with these items changes where they update the items.
They make the ones that are already here good before they put on a bunch of bullshit.
You know, like I've talked about this previously, that I think they're going to go through most if not all of the items that are underused.
And I'm sure Valve has statistics.
I'm sure there's some guy at Valve that can look at a screen and see, hmm, it looks like the only people equipping the neon annihilator are people pretending to be a pyro shock.
Something's probably wrong with that. We should probably change that.
Like, I'm sure this is a screen, a big screen.
What I picture is like a Minority Report screen where like Gabe Newell is sitting there like swinging his fingers around and like, yeah, that needs a little bit of change.
That was worth the wait. That was not worth the wait.
That needs to be removed and show me all the mutants, please.
And then the mutants all show up on the screen like an X-Men because he's got the X-Men cranial thing on his head.
He's got like the X-Men fucking Professor X.
I'm in the thing with the world and the reality, virtual reality.
That's what this is all about.
That's what the VR headsets all about is eventually to have Gabe Newell control us all through the fucking Professor X X-Men machine.
And if you believe that, then there's something really wrong here.
But anyways, that's going to wrap up this video.
See you guys all next time.
Thank you so much for watching.
And of course, take care.