Hey stealth, we're not going yet. Hey, hey, wait, wait, wait. Oh, let's get on the same. Let's get on the same field here. Oh, yeah
Jimmy you pick the same color bike as me. I told you I was going bumblebee yellow. You didn't listen. Look at this
man, man
Hey, I love how it says we've been sitting here for 30 seconds, which uh, yeah, we have we're just getting ready here
All right, are we ready to do this? Why stealth? Why are you like falling down off the oh?
Yeah, let's have like a biker hangout
The point of the race though, I guess
Oh
How do you how do you use the nitrous how do you use the nitrous
Sounds like way in the lead somewhere
Nitrous is terrifying. It's not working. Yeah, it is terrifying
As long as I beat boom, oh, I don't care this ah the lamp post landed on me
I'm in a really lonely race right now, dude, me, too
I'm using my nitrous boosters, baby
Really need a better bike
What's it? Why am I on this thing?
Wait, wait, wait, did I miss the turn one? Oh damn
I know it's a wrong way
How do you get c4 again down on the deep end?
I'm screwing up my bike. Dude. I'm getting I'm getting like a sedan
It was totally worth it
Give me one of these cars
Give me this thing lady. Is there even a lady in here? I don't even know. Hey, how do you change your weapons on your?
I think you just get one at a time. It seems like
We started with motorcycles and I'm legit in like an SUV right now. I'm trying to like come back
An SUV. Yeah, I'm in an SUV. I'm breaking the rules
Still be like way so far ahead. I'm not even trying to catch up now
Huh?
I'm in fourth. That's all right. I'll be in first place in like two seconds
Don't work that sucks that has like a sheet of you in on that seat nice
Oh
Devil going so fast right now. What do why do we have moped? Oh my god
I
Don't get in with me we can win together wait we can I don't know let's try I don't want a dumb moped
lap one of two
Yeah
Oh
You stole his cup dude, he did he picked me up to be nice and I pushed him out of the driver's seat
Wait a second stealth. Did you say you're already on lap two? Yeah
Man, I'm not I'm this is here. How are you? You are like winnings by
Guess I don't know. Yeah, I don't think me German boo. We're actually racing. We're just like screwing with each other
All right, well I I concede this race I
Will I will be the first to concede I
concede
GTA races, make sure you play on the map. That's like as big as the entire city
Are you ready? Yeah. Oops. Yeah. Well, how do you change the camera angle? Why is it raining?
Why does it have to be raining? Okay, there's already. Oh my gosh. My camera is like
Oh
Man, oh you're in the moped now. No man. Oh you did
Oh, no, come here you
Know later that was such a mistake. Why did I do that? I got a crick and catch up to
I can't catch up and like my both my left. I as a gun
Like
Get these get out of my way cars. Oh my car is gonna explode any second
Done it
Come on. Get out of them. We go over here, please
What? I refuse to believe this
Yeah, all right, can we do this again but not in the rain
So, you know what we're gonna play a little game called kamikaze bike
Whoever the first son of a bee to turn this guy take that
Oh
Somebody is gonna get this and they're gonna get it hard
Who's in first place blowing me up last game boo
Get you back
I'm gonna pass out. Oh
Man oh man, I'm just going black. Oh
Oh
Give me this sir. I'm gonna have to take your car because I need it cuz I'm in last place
That guy screamed pretty blood-curdling Lee
No, get in who was just waiting around this corner for me. Who is this right here? Oh, it's stealth
Well, I didn't work all my c4 didn't blow up they're supposed to kill you whoa
Whoa
No
That's okay. Just get out. It's easy. Just get out and walk away. It's fine. So Jim
I don't want to like rush you or anything. Yeah, but you're the owner hasn't finished. Oh, well
No, by the way, I still have another lap to do after this
So let's just say that I lost this match. Hey, it's gonna give you 30 seconds to try and finish
Oh 30 seconds at the finish line with like 18 c4s, but none of them went off and killed you
Good thing we got that that like 30 seconds for me to like do this. I have a max to see
Really? Oh, that's boring. I
Lost the game. I
Won and you did and I really sure how
What's like waiting at the finish line with c4 and you didn't blow me up
No, I love how it's 153 143 125 409
What was I doing that all time? Where the hell was I?