Oh, look, it's another player. Maybe we can be best friends.
Hi
We oh that was my face. I just hurt my face for you. That means we're best friends, right?
Trying this again
Look at who would swan if I was a threat to you. I would not swanton bomb off the top rope
Oh my fucking god, dude, seriously be my friend
Can you please be my friend?
Don't appreciate people that I'm trying to be their friend need a friend and they just do this to me every single time
You need a clip? I swear to god this guy need a friend. Yeah. Yes, you don't need a friend
You know why cuz you're a dick and you know what we do to dicks. We might get shot by this guy
We know got him got him. He's dead. Yeah, he's dead. No, he's dead now. He's a friend. No, you don't
No, no, you're gonna of course
Of course, why would you do anything else? I almost forgot. I gotta put on my safety helmet
Yeah, it doesn't do much. I think the reason this guy has not attacked me on sight is because he's afk. I
Fucking knew it. I told you what I tell you what I tell you
You know in all my years on the force team. I've never seen so many RDM dipshits in all my life. Yeah, fuck them
Yes, it's ridiculous, I'm the bad cop. All right, that's the last of that. Let's go and uh lunch is on me today, Tim
Yeah, right. I'm gonna get some dick fingers. Yeah, but yeah, yeah, absolutely
Yeah, I need them right now. Yeah, maybe make sure you drive us straight into the fucking wall, too
Like that damn right. I'm the bad cop
Excellent job, Tim. Great landing. What wait, by the way, what?
Where are we? Where are we? Where are we?
Where are we? I don't know where we are. I need to use my flashlight and see where we are. What happened? I forget everything. I think I have amnesia. You have amnesia too? Oh shit.
No, no, no, no, no now is not the time now is not the time to be doing this
You don't need the extra like thirty six dollars
You're gonna get out of that goddamn register get on the bike now. We gotta go three stars two cruisers outside great fantastic
I'm glad that you needed that like ten bucks. You just took and now we're both dead
Hi everybody, my name is mr. Sneak man
Hi, everybody. It's sneak man part two is equal
Mr. Sneak man part three this time. He's on a motorcycle. Yeah
Can we drive something else besides like your sardine creamed corn can crushed car?
This thing is a piece of shit
Look at this clown car. Oh
We got we gonna chop him gonna chop him. I'll take care of this
Covering fire. Oh
Oh
Damn, I didn't seriously shoot the pilot in the face. Did I this guy's driving around like a fucking maniac
How it is? How did I just do that? I'll never do that again. Put me in that same situation a thousand times
Holy shit, you're gonna kill us
This is the part of town Rodney that I was talking about with the invisible poles
You can hit your fucking head on pay attention to me. I know where they all are
I've mapped them all out of my GPF device except for that one