I'm so excited for this. Yeah, let's do it. Hopefully it's not too loud. We'll find out.
Why unpacking? I don't know, because I feel like it. I have played this game, haven't I?
I think me and Holly played it for a little bit. I feel like I've watched Holly. Like, I fell asleep
to Holly playing this. Calm down? What? I know, I, I, I just realized you can't see it. Come on.
I know, I'm working on it. Yeah, there already was a save file. I think I, I fell, I fell
asleep to Holly playing this. It was so relaxing. All right, you ready? So I think, yeah, I can open
up boxes. It's pre-recorded. No, it's not. All right, so I got to decorate the room.
Work faster. That's not the point of this, is to do it as slow as you can. You do this as slow as
possible. I don't like it. I don't like this. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I gotta,
stop, stop. I'm freaking out. All right, stop. Put it away. Okay, I would put a soccer ball.
I'm gonna do this the way I would do it. Of course, I'm gonna put the trophy right here.
There's no time limit. Wouldn't be going too slow. I'm gonna, I want the money in the bed.
This is like art stuff. I'm gonna put it up here with the other art stuff.
This is a diary or something. Put it away. Uh, trash. Uh, put the game away too. Only take that
out when friends come over. Yeah, put this stuff away. It goes here. Cool. Speed. I like this. This
is fun. There's a game change. You're going too slow. I'm gonna start. I'm gonna start.
I'm gonna start timing you up. I'm gonna tie you up for real. You're getting timed out. Okay.
This is a nice place for that. I don't want this in my room. How do I put this away? I don't want
this in here. Put them in the bed. I don't want this in the room. Now, this is a book. Put the
toy. Okay. Toys are going on this side. All right. That's no, no, no. This is going in here.
Check this out. This is going to be where the, my journal is going to go in here.
Now that's safe. And the scissors can fit in there too. Everything can, right?
That's perfect. That's good. I don't want this in the room. That's like school supplies that's going
there. What's that? What the hell is this? All right. That's kind of cool. You can sit out there.
Flashlight. Just put it, put it away. I don't need it. Put the books over here.
Dear me, this is a choking hazard. Wait, how old am I? You're supposed to be three? What? I'm
supposed to be three, 23. Don't even. All right. That's fine. Just put all the stuffed animals in
the bed. How would I even lie in this bed? I have too much stuff. What is this? I'll put this, oh,
on the sill. That's fine. All right. That's good. My bed has more than that. I got it. What's wrong
with this? These are wrong. Just put them away. This is the most stressful game I've ever played.
Why? Finally, my own room. Quick playback. I try to throw the dinosaur away like five times.
Tool assistant speed run. That looks fine. Okay. 2004. This is like a college room.
All right. This computer, computer's gonna go right here. I don't have like 40 stuffed animals,
right? This is a flute. I didn't mean to do that. I'm an idiot. All right. This is a book.
All right. Books are gonna go over here. Stand them up. All right. These are art supplies.
Um, oh, there's a kitchen and there's a bathtub. All right. All right. All right. All right. Right.
Right. Right. I gotta put this. I think I remember watching like I was, my eye was like this and I
remember going like this and seeing like flashes of this while Holly was like organizing stuff.
I was just like, I was definitely not dreaming. All right. I'm gonna put these up here for now.
These markers. I don't know if I'm up here. Book or books. I don't give, I don't give a
shit about books. All right. This can go here. I don't know what that is. It's going up with books.
What's that? I don't know what that is. Oh, it's a poster. Okay. Well, put it right here.
Book. Book. We got a lot of books. Uh, toothbrush. Oh, no, no, no. Take this to the bathroom.
Put that up here. Pants. Sneaker. What's the other one? Okay. Okay. A boot.
Remember, that's a mouse pad. This is a mouse pad. I don't want this ruler anyway. Get us out of here.
Okay. Whatever. This doesn't go under. Okay. These are, these are bras. Perfect. Gameboy. Uh,
put it on the shelf. Scratchy scratch. What is that? Files? Put it over here.
Why a toaster? Why do you have a toaster? Oh, because of the kitchen. Right. Hold on.
To make toast. Yeah, but still. I can hang those up. I don't think I want to do that, though.
I hate hangers. They just give you two spikes on your shoulders. I hate it.
But I'll do it for now. You don't know what I'm talking about? When you, okay,
when you put something on a hanger and it sits in there for a long enough time,
you end up getting this shit. It looks like this and there's nothing you can do to get rid of it.
It just looks like this. You have to wash the shirt to get rid of it. It's like an iPod.
Get a smaller hanger. I'm not, no, I'm not using a meat hook. I get, I get this shit out of the way.
I can't see. Okay. Jeans are going to go there. Fuck. Okay. Hold on. Hang up the ones that you
should hang up. Fold the t-shirts. T-shirts are going to go here. Hang this up right here.
All right. Sweaters, sweatshirts. This looks like an alarm clock. It is. Yeah. Fold up the shirts.
Hang up the big ones. What is that? What is all this stuff? I think this is pants. Should I do
this by color? I don't care. I genuinely don't care. I just reach in and grab clothes. I don't
care. Oh, right. I got it. Is there any more? What is all this shit? Too much stuff. I just want,
I told you like my, I should do this the way that I would actually do my room. And I'm telling you
right now, it is not like this. Just look at all that. You can't, you, you can't even move in here.
There's no room. There's just no room to move in here. I can't breathe in this room. Why are
all your socks on the bed? I kind of just seen what I needed to get them all out first before
I put them away. I don't like this up here. This needs to be here. Okay. Now what? Why is there
only one shoe? Towel? What is that? This is bag. A health kit. Don't act like you don't do that.
Don't act like you don't do that either. Don't act like you don't do that either. Quiet. Okay. I just
gotta get stuff out of box first. This is toothpaste. This is a brush. I'm gonna put this here.
This is soap. We're gonna put it here. Although gross, gross, gross. I, no, I don't use that shit.
I don't do that. Gross. Yeah. I don't, I don't smear around then lather up a big ball of
fucking bar soap, smear it all over my body and then place that shit on there for it to get like
stuck on. And even if you use a tray, it gets just stuck on the tray.
Bar soap is fucking dog shit. I'm sorry. It's dog shit. You just use a little bit of gel soap,
a little bit of body wash, lather it up, scrub it up. I, you know, I actually like Irish spring
for one reason, because the guy in the commercial used to be like, this is the Irish spring and he
would be cutting it. He had a knife and he would be cutting the soap and he had a, it was an Irish
guy. So I was like, Oh wow. Irish spring. I thought it was actually from a, I thought it was like
from a really, really rare resource in Ireland. I don't believe, I don't think that now obviously,
but when I was younger, I really thought it was a rare thing. Oh, only from the finest of the Irish
springs. You fell for the ads. Yeah. When I was 12, 13, maybe 11, not like I was 20, 30 years old.
I thought it was some rare ingredients from some incredibly exotic place, like deep underground
and some spring and I don't know. This is like an espresso cup. How's the bathroom look? I don't
like this. In fact, I don't, I don't think I even want this in here. What do I want this?
Is this deodorant? And I guess that would sit here.
I'm okay with that. Towel. What are you doing? Washing the utensils first because they've been
in a box for probably a month. Is this, yeah, you put the bug stuff down here. This is George
Warman. Does it go down here too? No, it would be like here. There's a scale. Uh,
put that here because it looks all right there. Pot. Put it up here. It's a cutting board. I know.
You think I didn't know? All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is,
I thought, okay, this is not a poster. That's garbage bags, sponges, spatula. All right. Let's
get some stuff situated here. Toaster is going to go here. Is this a dishwashing soap? And then
what is this? Okay. This is hand soap, obviously. What is, pine saw? What is that? What is this?
What's the difference? This is cooking oil. Oh, okay. Well, then it goes here. Cups. Cups
that go up here. Sugar. Put the spices and shit up here. Put the money away. I don't want to
advertise like my money. Why would I do that? Glassware will go, um, shit. I don't want all
this. What, like, what is all this stuff? Bingo. All right. Hold on. When am I going to put all
this? How am I going to reach this shit ever? I'm never going to be able to grab this stuff.
All right. Let's be honest. I'm only going to use this thing once a year. So let's put this stuff
down here that I don't need down here. What's wrong with this? I don't get it. What's the problem?
What's the problem? I can't have towels out. What? I put my shoes at the door. I don't,
what's the issue? All right, let's go. Let's take a look at speedrun. I was so zoomed in. Nice.
Very nice. 2007. Oh God. Okay. Oh goodness. I already have this bunch of shit over here.
There's already stuff here. There's some shit here already. Can I throw some stuff away?
I can't move anything else. I would just throw everything away. Well, I mean, I wouldn't,
but like in the game, I mean, I wouldn't just throw everything away. I'm just saying in the
context of this video game, I would just get rid of the stuff so I could put new stuff out.
You have a roommate? That makes it even worse. Can you imagine coming in and your roommate has
five or six contractor trash bags full of stuff? Hey, what's it? What's in the bags?
Oh, nothing. I'm just making a couple trips to the dumpster. Not a big deal.
You throw every single thing they own away. Wow. That would be awful. That's a power move. What
even is this? I don't know. Put it over here for now. Close. No, I gotta, we gotta, where's the
bedroom? Oh man. This is going to be so much of a pain in the ass. All right. I'm going to go fast.
I'm, I'm, I don't know. I can't pay attention to this. I can't do it. There's too much stuff.
I can't do it. I can't this. I, I don't care what to do with this thing. I don't want to
put some effort into this guys. Every time I've moved, I really sit there and look at all my stuff
and go, I just want to smash all this up with a hammer and the throne in the trash. I swear.
Sometimes you just look around and you just like, fuck it. Fuck this. You don't do it,
but you sit there and you have this, this thought of just, I really would love to put this all in
a trash compactor and just watch it get crushed. Okay. Where we need a box of the pans. Look at
all this. It's like, there's each, there's markers for each different like day of the week. This is
why I try not to own anything. I just, I, I want, I want just a, such a small amount of stuff.
I want the stuff that makes me, do I need it to survive? Yes. Okay. Toilet paper. You need that.
You need a rag, right? You need a good rag. You need stuff in the bathroom, a toothbrush. I don't
need all these books. I don't need all these things. I don't, I don't, I don't need all this other
shit. I just, honestly, I just need a pan to cook food in. I just, you need to only need a few pans.
Sometimes you go to kitchens and the person's like a master fucking chef. They have
15 different pans. It's like, do you even know the last time you even used that like extra large
wok? What, what, what do you mean? What? What's wrong with all this? You guys understand that this
is almost everything I own is in here and in that closet. This is almost every object that I own.
This is my whole life is this shelf here. All of my possessions are there and right there. I don't,
I don't like have anything else. I keep some consoles and some games and stuff. I have
three or four pans. Couch. I got a VR headset. I don't know. I don't like stuff. I don't like
a bunch of stuff. Yeah. I don't know. I don't like stuff. Like for instance, to me, this is stuff.
This is stuff. This is, I would get rid of it. Let me tell you what would go in this room. You're
ready. No, it's a book. Get rid of it. What am I going to write down? Alarm clock. Nope. I have a
phone. I don't need that. What is this? Some random magazine postcard. Put it on the fridge for six
months. After six months, have it lapsed. Take it off. Oh, you sent me a picture of, of, of like
your kids or something or like, Oh, something that like a cool thing. It's going on the fridge for
six to 12 months and it's coming off. What's this? Another one. Nope. I wouldn't have any of this.
I have a phone and I don't even listen to music. So I don't need this. A hanger. You're going to
bring a hanger with you. Okay. No. What did you, what did somebody just said? Something about how
I did. I lived out of a shoe. Like a lady from that nursery rhyme who lived in the shoe. What is this?
I want to show you guys something. Cause it's very important. This is my mouse pad. You want to see
how I don't own anything. I don't care. This is my mouse pad. I've had, I've been using the same
mouse pad for fucking almost 10 straight. This is a magic of wizard wars mouse pad. This is what I
use. I don't play this game. I don't give a shit about this game or this entire franchise. I don't
care. Magic of fucking wizard wars guys. I don't need anything else. I don't need another one.
Why would I get another one? What do I care? I've owned this since 2011. I think buy a new one. I
don't need a new one. This one works. This works just fine. It's just this floppy. Oh look, I'm
going to make thunder. I, I, you don't need, I don't need another one. If it were up to me,
I would just do it on my shin. I mean my thigh. If it worked, I used an Amazon basics keyboard
for five years. That thing was $9 on Amazon. I don't need stuff. I don't care about stuff.
This thing probably smells. I'll be, I'll give you a real review. I promise. Um, it's just,
I don't know. It smells like the inside of a closet. It doesn't, it doesn't smell bad. It smells
like whatever. Now I got to put this back over here. It stinks. No, it doesn't stink. It just
smells like fucking rubber. You should taste it. No, stop being childish. God's sake. Stop being
so, all right. Now underneath here, for instance. Now that's gross. Now that's just not nice. I
clean this from a lot, but that's just, that's just, that's just not okay. That just looks bad.
You're used to the smell. What, you want me to breeze my mouse pad?
Guys, I have one other mouse pad. Give me a second. I need to see if I still have it.
You're going to fucking shit your pants laughing if I can get it. I'm right back.
I got it. I got it. Okay. Are you ready? Are you ready for me to reveal the other mouse pad that I
own? Okay. Here we go. It's a Superman holographic mouse pad. It's pretty cool. Should I use this
instead of the Magica Wizard Wars one? What do you think? Is this worth any money? Does it make a
sound when you scratch it? What the fuck? It's been a rough day today. Everybody shut up. You're
ruining the surface. That's the only other mouse pad I own. I just don't care. I don't care. I don't
own stuff. I, I get, look, I would, I will spend money on, on things that are very essential that
I find essential. For instance, a nice fucking meal. Nice fucking delicious meal. I have McDonald's.
Not at McDonald's. Superman mouse pad is essential. You're acting like I bought this recently.
Yeah. I, I, I don't, I don't even know where I got it. You eat McDonald's and shit.
Just because I eat McDonald's doesn't mean that's the only food I eat. Oh, I like McDonald's. You
eat it three meals a day, every single fucking day. It's not what I said. I just said I enjoy
that restaurant. All right. What, I gotta get this, I gotta, hold on. This is some kind of
tablet or something. Why do I not have the thing to put this on? Why is it? Wait, I'll make it,
you know, here's the idea. You put it that far away. So then when it actually beeps, you have
to get up and climb up the shit to turn it off. So you, you make sure you're going to get up for it.
This is all wrong. All wrong. Maybe you didn't have so much bullshit. Where the fuck am I
supposed to put all this shit? Why do I have business cards out on my own desk? I know who I am.
Put these away. So many books. Oh, just get the digital one. Too many books. Too many books.
How come there's no end table or anything? Am I going to put all my stuff on the ground?
Take the other side. Okay, whatever. Bottoms are going here. Tops go in there. And then underwear
is going in here. A lot of pain in the ass. Oh, this hurts me. Oh, I just hate it.
Okay, thank God. I hate it. I hate it. Oh, get this out. Throw them away. This is going
to somewhere else. Look at all the stuff we have. You understand that we probably had
20 more encyclopedias, but they're being taken up by like Crunchy the Cockroach.
Like a bunch of action figures. This can go back here. Come on, get back there. Can I go under the
bed? That's not a bad place for it. Good, good, good. Feels good. The worst possible place to
put a tower because you can't ever touch the back of it. I hate this. I have my tower right here
and it's not enclosed by a bunch of this shit and I still hate it.
What's that? Frisbee? Hey, leave that under there for like 10 years. Is that a shoe? What is this?
That's a squished up shoe. Is that a paint can? What is this? Honest to God, what is this? This
looks like a Ghostbuster trap. What is this thing? What is that? It's climbing chalk? Chalk bag for
climbing. Okay. No, get back here. There's not enough room in this closet. There's no fucking room
in this goddamn closet. That's the, that's a pants hanger. What is this? A yoga mat or something?
This was so small when I took it out, I thought it was a Pez container. This is a trash can.
Yeah, good luck throwing one item in here and then needing to take the whole bag out.
This is all fucked up. This is, look at all fucked up. This is, this is fucked up. Look at all the
stuff on the desk. Alright, looking good so far. Not bad. Okay. Dining room. More books.
Let's be, let's be realistic with ourselves here. Everybody that has all these books,
they buy them. They like open them in bed and they read three pages and they close it and they just
pretend like they're reading it. I knew for a fact that was going to get somebody. People are just
like, I fucking read. What is he saying? Oh, back to the living room. Alright. I would never do this.
This is stupid. There's already a visual here for the television for you to look at. So putting
another visual right behind it is, that's dog shit feng shui. That's bad. This is no, because
there's another visual right behind it. This is going somewhere else. Too many visuals. Is that
GameCube? I hear the games. Let's get the games over here. A little blanket. Cool. All the vents
are blocked. Oh my god, look at this shit. Um, too much stuff. There's another thing I don't know
what to do with. Okay, I'm gonna take this down. Put these, can these fit up here? That can. Too
many things. That works. Alright, that works. I can sit under there. Alright, kitchen. More mugs.
Towel. Mug. I've been drinking out of the same coffee cups for five to ten years too.
Guys have a problem with that? Yeah, as long as you wash it. Oh yeah, of course I do. What is this?
Oh, it's a magnet. Have you been shitting out of the same ass? Yes. What a weird, what a weirdo.
Organized. This can't fit in there. Whatever. Medic kit. Sponges. Spatula. Spoon. Cutting board.
Alright, I think this is like a towel. This is going in the other, this is gonna bathroom.
Towel. Alright, toothbrush. I'm not putting my toothbrush up here. This is coming with me in the
bedroom. This is coming with me in the bedroom. No, I'm sorry. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
like to, I don't want to leave my shit up. When I'm done brushing my teeth, this is getting put in a
little plastic bag and I'm bringing it into my bedroom. Putting it in a drawer. Holy shit, look
at these. Those are Costco. Those are bulk. Damn. Spray. That's horse shampoo. How much shit does
this person have? That, thank you for saying that. Thank you. Alright, so what's the problem?
All of this apparently shouldn't be here. Where else are they supposed to go? Put it, you gotta
put your clothes away. You gotta put your shoes away. Put your shoes away. No. Actually, my shoes
are at just the front door of wherever you live. They're just at the front. I'm not putting these
all in here. They're just at the front door and these can't even fit. Yeah, that's good.
This looks good. What's up? Is there a problem? Kitchen's a problem. For what?
Oh, sorry. My mistake. There were two towels on the counter. I'm so sorry. I will fix this
immediately. God, what a bonehead. What a dumb, what an idiot. Forget about all the dirty fucking
dishes in the sink or all the other bullshit that's up here. Let's see the speed run.
Okay, so am I just really doing this? Am I doing the same speed? Am I just weirdly
consistent with how fast I did this? Or is it just going to put it out no matter what?
Hey, you don't watch a spider make its web. You just see the end result. So please
spare me the criticisms. Those just jumped around on their own. How do I get a better view?
There's two zoomed in. Hey, remember this rant? God, it's like it was yesterday. 2010. Okay,
what is that? Oh, what is it? Pet bug? I can move everything. Is this mine? Why can I move
the guitars and TV and the dumbbells? Whatever. Okay, what we got? I have to make sure everybody
knows that I play D&D. It's the first thing that I want them to see so I can have an hour long
conversation with them about D&D. They go, Hey, man, what's this thing? Oh, well, let me tell you
something about Dungeons and Dragons. How much time do you have? It's like a mini ukulele. Oh,
wow. Look at this. We've got a super closet now. Perfect place for my shirts. Who's this messy
person? Look at this messy bullshit. It's not a bowling alley. Okay. Symmetrical and flush.
It's messy. Just rip these doors off. Just take these doors off. All they do is just cause a
huge problem. They're a massive pain in the ass. Those of you that have ever had to use these doors
before. Fuck these things. They come off the first day I move in. I don't care. Without a doubt.
First day. Of course, gonna bring my Game Boy everywhere I go. Those are cigarettes.
What is it? Why do you have these? Oh, how much underwear? Is this underwear? How much
underwear do we have? This is kind of a lot of underwear. Are we planning on shitting our pants
a lot? Are these socks? Are these socks or is it underwear? It's both. What are these?
Get these fucking fruit roll-ups out of here. These ties, I think, right?
Game's gonna get mad at me for putting the shoes in the wrong place.
Just grab them and like the Hulk rip them off. I hate these things so much.
What am I supposed to do with this? I don't do what this is like. Degree? What am I supposed
to do with this? I don't, there's nowhere for me to hang this. I'm just gonna put my degree in
the bathroom. I don't care. That's where it belongs. These shoes are all mismatched. I don't care.
It doesn't belong. All right, let me take these markers. I think
put these back here. Look at this mess of a living room. Come on. I brought these everywhere.
Too many books. That just really is. I'm sorry. I know that like a lot of people like books and
stuff so that I don't like books. I just they take up a lot of space. It's just too much shit.
This is important though. I would say this is very important. That's the most important thing
that I've packed is the chicken thing. And this, I don't, let's put this in the bedroom.
If I could move it, I would. Look at all these. What the fuck are these all for?
Why has that many of those? This is bullshit. Everybody that owns more than one of these,
you go, you fan, you see five to 10 pages with shit on it. The rest is empty. And it's like that
across every single one of them. You don't need all these. The first five pages have stuff on this
and the rest is blank. There's sketchbooks. There's a lot. You don't know how to read.
You don't know how art works. It's an artist. But I mean, it's a lot of books. Look at all these
large cheese pizzas that I have to put across my whole house. Think about that. I have to find room
for like 25 pizza hut boxes. And by the way, how dare you be this talented? How dare you be
this talented to have that much material? There's another pizza. I don't know where
to put this other pizza. Here comes a backpedal. Do you guys hear that? What the fuck was that?
That sound was coming from my speaker. It was weird. Yeah. What time is it? Six 23. Nine.
What? I'm so confused. I'm sorry, but this is a GameCube house. We're gonna put this one,
we're gonna put this one in the closet. I don't fucking want this thing. I just get rid, I don't
care. Okay. Cookies important. Measuring tablespoons. What was that? Molasses. Oil. Oil.
Garlic powder. Thyme. Has this one been here for more than six months? I gotta, is there a place I
can put this? What even is this? Is this leftovers? Why do I have like takeout still? Throw this away.
All right. Salt and pepper gonna be on the table. Is this coffee? I think. Whatever. What is this?
It was a marijuana scale. What are you doing? What is this? Why is this here? What is this for?
Is this a juicer? It's a cooking scale? By a show of hands, one being yes, two being no.
Do you have a cooking scale in your house? And do you have you used it? One is yes. Two is no.
Fucking liars. No way. Liars. Lie. Lie. Lie. I see a liars. I don't see anything but liars.
You've used, you use one of these on a regular cooking scale?
I have, I have never like sprinkled shit on a cooking scale and weighed it out to exact. No,
you just eyeball that shit. It's not for cooking. It's for baking. But just follow the recipe.
I need one tablespoon of baking soda. Here it is. I don't, do I need to put that on the scale?
Do you cook often? I do cook, but I don't, I don't like weigh my fucking cheeseburger patties on a
marijuana weed scale. I've never heard of people doing this. Yeah, guys, I make like turkey
sandwiches. I don't weigh the deli meat and go, I had to make sure I have at least 0.2 grams of
turkey meat. I make eggs. I don't, I just crack the eggs in the pan and fucking eat them.
If I'm going to be baking, I just bake cookies. I don't need to, what am I weighing? What am
I weighing it for? What's it for? That's not cooking. If I bake salmon in the oven,
I don't need to weigh, what am I, what am I using it for? Dude, it's sad what you're saying.
Volumetric baking. Okay, but, but if you don't bake, you don't need one of these.
I just like making pasta is pasta. Making a salad, I just make the salad. I just cut up some tomatoes
and fucking onions, red onions, swirl it around, put it in the thing, press the button so it spins,
spins, spins, spins, spins like a merry-go-round. I would put, I'm going to put a whole turkey in
the oven. You just put a turkey in the oven. It's for baking recipes. I don't, I don't bake.
A lot of, I don't bake. What I do is I shave onions into the pan, mushrooms, chop up the
mushrooms, chop the onions up, get it in there, swirl it around, swivel it around,
put a little bit of oil in there, cook up the mushrooms and onions, get those cooked out to
perfection, make them nice and caramelized, put them over on the other side, put the steak in there,
two minutes, two minutes, put that on top, a little bit of A1, chop salad, chop it up.
I'm not weighing that. All right, you're distracting me.
Yeah, Derma A1, get it. Bang, I've been wanting to talk about this for like a week,
two, maybe three weeks. Guys, Five Guys is 100 times better than Shake Shack,
a hundred fucking times better. I don't know what happened, and I'm going to be really honest with
you, Five Guys fell off for me five years ago or so. Shake Shack was number one, best ever.
Number one, best ever. I'm telling you right now, Five Guys has improved in quality,
while Shake Shack has gone way fucking down in quality. Five Guys is now all the way up at
the top. They are number one for me. Seriously, I'm not kidding. I don't know what happened over the
last four or five years. Shake Shack, I have to be honest, this is just a review of that restaurant.
It sucks. It sucks now. What happened? Why? What happened? I don't know what happened.
I've had Shake Shack from more than one location, more than a few locations. It was kind of bad.
It really wasn't that... Okay, I got lettuce on a Shake Shack burger, and I'm not... I wish I took
a picture of it because it was fucking ridiculous. It was one tiny, wilted, small, thin piece of
wilted, wet, gross lettuce. I have to be honest with you. I went to Five Guys and I got lettuce,
and it was this crunchy, crispy, like... It was packed full of flavor and juices and stuff.
Oh my God, it was so good. And I used to think Shake Shack was the best. And I thought that Five
Guys was okay, but something happened in the last few years. It's probably the best takeout burger.
The tomato, if I were to have it, which I don't have it on my burgers, but if I did,
so crunchy and so just full of just juicy, delicious, fresh flavor.
They flipped. I just put it under the fucking bed. I don't care.
What do we do with these controllers? We have too many systems. What do these even go... Okay,
four is actually not a bad amount. Oh, we have two systems. Okay.
What is this? What are these things? What do I do with this record player?
Just keep... Everyone puts in my hair anyways. It's fine. But seriously, Five Guys, I don't know
what you did. The burgers are fucking on point. Better than anywhere else. Oh, not very much
storage. You know what I mean? Like, I don't... Where am I supposed to put this? There's way too
much stuff on the counter. Are you supposed to prepare food on this counter? You better be
throwing pizzas in the air because there's nothing... You're not going to have any room for anything.
I don't know what to do with that toothbrush. Let's go. Nail clipper. Let's go.
Shave and razor. Let's go. Mug. Hair gel. Febreze. Medicine. My god, what is all this? What the...
Rich streamer has never unpacked in his life. He gets his man servants to do it for him.
No, that's not accurate. That's not accurate. I just don't care about other people's stuff.
This is not my stuff. This is not my stuff, so I don't care. I don't care about your dumb green
toaster, all right? If this was my toaster, I would want to know where... I would want to
put it somewhere special. What's a razor doing in here? There's no room for anything. Where is
the Febreze supposed to go? Why is this so... Why is everything so wrong? There's no... There's no
where to put... I can't put anything anywhere. A Febreze goes in any room, okay? I don't understand.
This is stupid to me because considering... Like, how many times have you fought it in a room
and, holy shit, you hear somebody walking down the hallway, like, I don't know, your girlfriend,
like, you know, a few days ago, and you hear the footsteps and you just laid out a fucking gross
one. And if there was one in the bedroom right there... Done. It's for any room. It's literally
for any room. There's no room it has to be in. Oh, he fought it. Yeah, that's funny. Where does it
want me to put this? Does anybody have any idea where this... Where does it want this to go?
Where does it want this to go? I can't even put this anywhere. Why can't I leave it where it was?
I can't put it anywhere. What do I do with this? This is a laptop. How is this place worse than
the last one? There's less room than the last one. Where's it supposed to go? What am I supposed...
What the fuck am I supposed to do with this? Are you missing another room? I don't think so. The
side table? Well, that makes sense, okay. But what about the Etch A Sketch? I would think, like,
right here, right? No. I don't even have a desk. I don't have a desk. I've got plenty of fucking
underwear. Where's the desk? Throw it into the river. Piece of shit. This one's good. We're good.
What am I supposed... I don't understand what it wants me to do with these. They can't go anywhere.
I can't put them up anywhere. How is this not on the right spot? Why? On the coffee table in the
living room? That's kind of in the way. That takes up a... That's in the way, right? Am I crazy?
Fuck. I don't care. What's wrong with these? Okay, that looks all right. All the weird...
I would put them over here in a place to store them. I think that's good. All right, now we just
need to fix the bedroom. Right. My degree, which I don't know where it wants me to put it. Under the
bed. Under the bed? Is it supposed to be sad? I was just picking it up and putting it down for,
like, a fucking full five minutes. Jesus. I'm just angry. I feel so serious moving into his
place. All right, so now what? 2012. What's this? What am I doing here? One pound weights.
Oh, we got a DS? No, we don't have just a Game Boy Advance DS. I can stay here, I think. On the bed,
maybe. There it is. I'm putting the degree back up. What is this? These cartridges? That's better.
What is that? Why do you look so scary? I don't know, man. The light is on me.
Medkit. All right. Okay. He looks a bit scary. What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about? I'm just sitting here. Yo, he does look a bit scary. All right,
that was a quick one. What's wrong with my eyes? What's wrong with this? Why do I have to take this
off? Throw it away. That's a way, right? Oh, I got it. Don't piss him off, guys. He'll yell again.
I'm not going to yell. This room used to feel bigger. Game's not even hard. Give me a fucking
challenge. 2013. That's a big one. All right, how fast do you think I can do it? You know,
I was just told if you really want to make moving around and opening boxes and putting stuff on
shelves and stuff, do it to a song. Isn't it fun? Okay, so I got everything out of the boxes. You
can do the rest. I'll be back. Why is there a cane? Am I old? All right, let me rethink this,
because obviously that was just, wow, laughing out fucking loud. I've always put these things
at the highest possible level. All the video games going on the bottom shelf. It's just easier
to keep track of. Any more stray video games? Yep. Perfect. Oh, I want the chickens in the bedroom.
Was it a DVD player? Yep. Sort them by console. No, you sort them by time played. Not by console,
but there's a bug in here. Where is it? That was weird. No, it wasn't. It was a floating piece
of dust. That was fucking terrifying. It just swooped into my... That was weird. It's by time
played. On what game? I'm sorry. That's the way it is. I don't know what that is. Okay. Frog.
You can sit over here. I want the chickens in the bedroom. What's the fastest way to get them over
there? This is gonna look really stupid when we see the fast motion one. The ukulele has a stand?
Where? That's a ukulele stand? I thought that was just like a piece of woodworking. I didn't
think it actually had a purpose. I thought that was just a piece of art. I didn't know that it
actually had a purpose. Okay, it does. Not bad. Oh, no. No, thanks. I'll do the computer room.
There's gonna be so many books. There's gonna be so many books. I'm not just talking about these.
I'm talking about these two. I'm talking about just all the books. What's that? Blanket. Laptop.
Tablet. Book. Book. Book. Book. Whale. Two whales. What the fuck? You have so many of these.
I'm a fax machine? Cods. Wi-Fi router. Clock. All right, let's organize this, please.
I don't know. I don't even know what these are. What is this? What is this thing? That's a scanner
and printer. What is this? Printer and scanner? So I have a scanner-printer combo and then a printer-
scanner combo. Why are they detached? What year is this supposed to be? They were connected always
for like the last 10 years. Printer-scanner combos existed since like 2005.
One is the scanner, one is the printer. Well, printer-scanner combos were- yeah,
they existed in 2013. Yes, they did. Yes, they did. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Yes, they did.
La, la, la, la. Those individual cookies? Oh, they're coasters. All right. Oh, a curveball.
One of the reasons why I just- I know that, oh, you have a bunch of spices in your spice rack.
I kind of just want to consolidate them all into one bottle. Does that make sense? Just combine
half the spices I have into one fucking bottle because it's all going on anyways.
Come on, I can fit the strainer in here. How does it not fit in there? You can't be serious, right?
Oh, shut up. Stop. No, stop it. What are you doing? What are you doing in my wellington? Stop it.
Stop. What are you doing? I'll figure it out later, whatever. That's good. Do you drink oil? No,
I put olive oil in a lot of foods though. That's really good. Don't say that. You can only microwave
ramen noodles? That's not even true, man. So there it is finally. It only took like two hours to get
to the scale. What the hell is that? It's a linen ball. What is this? Oh, okay. What is this? This
looks all right. All right. This is going to be fun to wear. Little books. I'm just putting the
books right here. I'm going to put every book over there and I'll figure it out later. All shirts,
all pants are going over here. Whatever the hell this thing is. Okay. I love how seriously he's
taking this. Yeah, I am. I mean, I'm taking it dead seriously. All right. Get the other box open.
I got to make sure I get this right. I don't want to screw this up. Candle. Put the hangers up.
I'm concentrating. There's just no order here. That doesn't have to be. I operate in chaos.
What happened? Nothing. Is there another bedroom? No. Okay. Some of this shit's wrong. I wanted to
get the Wi-Fi router out of the way. How's that wrong? The microwave can't be over here.
So where else is it supposed to go? Where would you want me to put the microwave here?
There's no room for it. How is this supposed to go anywhere? Now where's the toaster go?
Where's the toaster supposed to go now? How is it wrong? It's a fucking towel. This is right.
What's wrong here? This bedroom has something wrong. Oh, book. Got it. I thought this was
the Sims for one second. That looks good. This hurt my neck. This game's really fun.
There's something about it. I don't know. I'm not really talking that much, but I'm just kind of
having a good time. I'm just enjoying it. You manipulated too much. Not really. Maybe a little.
2015. Now what? What? Is this the same place? Oh, these are cute. Those are cute.
Those are coasters. I want those. Those are cute. They actually really are. They don't
don't act like you don't think it is. I love these. I really do. Get them some fruit coasters.
I would love them. I'm probably going to get them. I'm probably going to go get the fruit coasters
wherever I can get them. These are comfy. This is comfy. I like this. What are these little games?
I got no room for these. Whoa. Book. Book. Book. I don't care. I don't read. I really don't.
Does the living room door just go to the outside? Yeah, I think it's an apartment.
This is done. All my shit is here. Oh, wait. I'm adding more. I understand now. I was like,
wait, what the hell am I doing? I get it. I'm just mixing up all the clothes.
I'm mixing up all of the clothes. I'm just putting them in random places. I'm not even...
Whatever. What is that? Are these walkie talkies? What do I do with this? What is that? All right,
close all this up. I can't see. Where do I put this? There's not enough room in the closet to
put this. These have to go into the bed or something. Have you filed as a furry for tax
purposes? I think you... Okay, this looks all right. Kitchen needs a little bit more stuff.
Put this up on the sill. All right, this is where it gets... It's going to get hard here.
It actually is. Cups out. A gigantic cheese grater? I don't... What is this? What is this?
What is that? A juicer? We don't need a juicer. We don't need one of these.
Ice cream scoop. That's a great addition, actually. Okay, these go this top. I mean,
that has to... I don't... Put this. What do I do with this? There's no counter space.
There's no space to put anything. All right, it's gonna have to do for now. I'll figure it out later.
There's not enough room. We don't have enough room. There's not enough room for all this.
I don't have enough room for all these salves. These gels. I don't have enough room for them.
This is too... I don't have enough space. Okay, towels can go over here. Bath mat. Look at this
countertop. This countertop is a mess. Oh, man. Wait, do we have... Are we gonna be on the walkie
talkies next to each other? What are the walkie talkies for? It's cute. It's fun. What is this
thing? I don't know what it wants me to do with that. What? What? Plants. What do I put this?
You know what's gonna... I'm gonna knock this over. If this is on my bedside, I'm gonna have a bottle
of water or something here and I'm gonna go reach to get the bottle of water and it's gonna annoy me
and I'm gonna knock the plant over. All right, what do I do with this thing? Can this fit in here
anywhere? There we go. I can't just go on the bed. There's a book in here. Get this book out of here.
Oh my god. What the fuck? There's so much shit in this room. If I abuse this desk, I'm gonna have a
fucking heart attack. Look at this. I can't even move. I can't exist in this room. Okay, got it.
Kitchen. Where do I put this? I am like throwing this across. I'm throwing this in the trash from
across the room right now. What do you don't like about this? I got it. The wooden thing? Is it a
relaxing game? Ah, it is. This is kind of... This is a little shitty. This was not a good one, I will
say. This wasn't a great one. If my nine-year-old sister was playing this yesterday, she was doing
better than you. How long did it take her to place one object? 2018. This place is huge. Nice. Nice.
Nice. First try. I'm getting this absolutely first try. Look at that placement already. We're good.
Let's take this up to the bathroom. Bingo. Check it out. Hand sanitizer. A bowl of fruit. Another
towel. Easy. Done deal. All right, this is a books. I'm gonna decorate up here. Okay, looks good.
I mean, put the baby toys in the baby bed, right? Some cream. Looks good. The ba- what? It might be
a little excessive, I agree. But I'm just barely... I'm barely... I'm barely functioning. I'm just
figuring it out. I'm getting it all in the same spot so I know where to put it. And this is not
going to be the end result. Okay, where should I put this? Look at all this baby stuff. I'm realizing
what happened. And I'm a little embarrassed, but whatever. I'm putting the clothes on the bookshelf
and the books on the clothes rack. This is what... I don't care. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
It's fine. Too many plants. I- no, too many- there are too many plants. There are way too many
plants. I'm just gonna be honest with you. Do you have too many plants? What? I fucking hate this
box. This box has been a pain in the ass at every single level. I hate this thing. I- I- I- I- I
can't- I don't know where to put it ever. I hate this box. I don't want- yeah, I don't want this
fishing tackle box. I- I don't- it's annoying to use. Somehow we're getting more chickens.
How do they keep increasing? They keep increasing. Man, I- this makes me anxiety. I hate this.
I don't do- I can't do clothes thing. Big closet or something. No, no, no. I just have five Star
War shirts, four pairs of jeans, a suit, and a bunch of fucking cartoon shirts. I can't do this.
I have- I mean, well, let me look at it. This is- this is like a nice shirt. This is fine.
It's a nice bean. I have got five of these, six of these. I got like seven or eight pairs of jeans.
Different colors. Some slacks. You're speaking gibberish? What do you mean? What? Man, I gotta
get some of these boxes out of the fucking way. Get up there. Huh? Why can I hang these? I was
gonna put the pants on the bottom and the shirts on top. I don't care anymore. It's such a mess.
It just- all their clothes are all over the place. They don't even color
coordinate or anything. It's such a mess. I'm not a designer. I'm not a designer, all right?
You're just lazy? I'm not- I'm not lazy. I don't know- I don't know where things are supposed to
go in a big walk-in closet. I just- underwear goes in the underwear slot, shirts go in the shirt
slot, pants go wherever you want. Anywhere. At the end of the day, as long as you just kind of know
where your clothes are, does it really matter that much? As long as you know where your stuff is.
And it's not a mess if it was clean in here. Of course there's a fucking book in here.
Of course there's- of course there's a goddamn book in there. They have so many books that- that's
in the bathroom boxes. It's in the clothes boxes. You have too many books. All right, where was I?
Oh shit, that was bad. Was that cookie tin? I don't think- I think it's a sewing kit.
I think this is a sewing kit. Yeah, this is definitely for sewing. Oh shit. Hiding something
here. This all can't fit over there. All right, bathroom time. I thought that was a wishbone.
One of those sinks. One of the sinks that has the- the laminor flow. This is definitely one
of those sinks. I love it. How do you say it? Yeah, laminar. Laminar flow, yeah. I learned.
I paid attention last time you talked. I heard what you said. I don't want this thing, but I'll
put it over here. Oh, that's cute. Yeah, these are cool. Oh, look. Oh, look. Oh, look. Oh, look. Oh,
look. More of the same- how many copies of this book do you need? How many copies of this book
do you have? That's a lot. That's a lot of copies of the same book. It's a published book.
Let's go. Let's go. There's so much shit on this desk. Hey. Hey, look. All right, living room time.
Observation, humor, Andy. I feel like I haven't talked in like an hour.
Wii motes always go on top in front of the TV. They never go inside of any storage. They're always
in front of the TV, so you're ready to game. Anyone that comes in your house always knows
you're ready for the Wii. The Wii motes on top of a certain visible area is a prop. It's a set for
your house. It's a way to start a conversation. It's a way to get gaming immediately. These are
not out of the way. They're there by very much by design. What is that? This goes in the kitchen,
right? I need the- anything that holds that. Oh, my favorite part. I'm fixing it. I know people
are freaking out right now. They're in the wrong spot. They're in the wrong spot. I got it under
control. And next person that says wrong spot, Andy, would hate to be you. It's called the timeout.
So many games. We have a shitload of games. Oh, my goodness. I don't have enough room for any of
this stuff. Um, the cane. Where do I put the cane? Figure it out later. You look a little pale.
Probably the white balance. I got a big bright ass light in my face. I can't see. I got to get
these two boxes out of here. Glassware up here. Bulbware up here. Just- I need to get the boxes
out of the way. Like, I can't see without moving it. Okay, now I can see. Let's get some stuff
situated. Okay, shit. All right, move this out of the way. We'll put these here. These all go
together. All right, I'm gonna put these up here. This gets the toy truck out of the way. Uh, this
is like a serving tray, whatever. All right, I need to- spices and sweets need to go up here.
Spices and sweets go up there. Coffee's gonna go up top. Freaking out. Why? Why? What do you- what
do you mean? Why are you freaking out? Go- go- go to the- I'm- I'm fine. I don't have to go to the
bathroom. I'm fine. What are you talking about? Ooh, that's helpful. You mean in the game. Oh,
okay. Towel. Cheese grater. Poster. Trash bags. Idiot. This looks like- looks like a
fucking kitty litter thing. I'm sorry. Freaking. Freaking. What are the utensils? Oven mitts.
Another tray. Nice. Go piss. I don't need to pee. Stop. That can't fit up here. The rolling pin
needs to be able to fit in here somewhere, right? Okay, there we go. Ah, utensils. Fuck. I can move
with that. I can move with that so I can talk. Just slow down and say what you want to say.
I can move all that stuff up here in a minute. Okay, let's do it. Salt. Uh, paprika. Keep the,
where's our shower? Why is the microwave next to- you just hurt my chest. There's nowhere else
for it to go. Books. What is this? Oh, just getting it out. Don't worry. It's gonna be fine.
Why is there a toaster in here? Um, guys, where am I supposed to put this? Move. What is this
even doing in here? I'm setting the table. You catch the game last night? What's your favorite
subject in school? Do you like hot fudge sundaes? Somebody just said did I catch the game last night
and it freaked me out. That looks nice. I don't want, I don't want to put this in here. Okay.
What's, what remains? Oh, there's an upstairs. Oh shit. Okay, so we do have a bathroom up here.
I forgot. Why did I not finish this? Tissues. Eh. Okay. Am I almost done with the game?
When does the game end? Oh, this is the last level. Oh shit. All right. Laundry. Okay. Okay.
Okay. What do we do with this towel? Whoa, there's a whole nother place to put stuff.
Okay. Oops. Fuck. It's a bath mat. So what? Oh, right. What is this bag of dog food?
What is this? I don't know what it is. Actually, I really don't know. This is soil. Why would there
be a bag of soil in the laundry room? It's a bag of dirt. Okay. This has got to come with me.
I just got to cut the other bathroom. It's got to come with me. Now what's the problem?
Okay. It's very unhappy with this. Why? The coffee can be there. What's wrong with the coffee being
up there? Bro, where else am I supposed to put this stuff? Bro, I think that's good. Apparently,
the scanner can't go here. So the scanner is going to the office. Problem solved. Problem solved.
I have to fix this, don't I? I can't believe I did that. I need to, I need some protein or something.
I need to eat like a bag of peanuts. I don't know what the fuck I was doing.
I actually don't know what the heck I was doing. Okay. There's all kinds of problems.
Look at all these problems. Plant. All right. What am I missing here? This is in the wrong spot.
Not anymore. Nope. Okay. That's in the wrong spot too. What am I going to do about this?
This bag doesn't fit. Yes. Towel and that's it. Let's go. Just put an extra towel somewhere.
Just a fresh towel somewhere. What do I do with this? I don't. What do I do with this towel?
I can't go in the baby room. Where is this supposed to go? Thanks. I appreciate the help
when you say up my butt. Thank you. Thanks. But like I'm looking for a practical answer.
Where is this supposed to go? Under the sink? How am I supposed to put this under the sink?
Oh, I don't know, dude. Maybe like up your butt. Try up your ass. Oh, okay.
This is an extra towel. I don't need this. This is an extra towel.
I don't need this extra towel. Dude, this can't go anywhere.
Now where does this piece of shit go? I just go. This dude is cracked. Oh no, sorry. I'm going to
go and they all do it for me. There's a lot. Take another bong rip. No, I'm good. I'm good.
I think I'm good. I like this a lot. This is really fun. There's one thing I would change in
this game and that's to be able to be allowed to have stuff in the wrong place. It's the only
complaint I have. It's this very solid fun game though. I thought it was good. That was great.
There's a setting where you could do that. Oh, cool. That was a good time.
Let's get a song.
Knock on the door. Now all your stuff is here in boxes on the floor.
You open up. There is so much to do. I open up my heart. Did you understand the plot?
I think a little. Yeah.
Three games finished in one day.
You can't count Freddy fish. That doesn't work.
I do look kind of pale, don't I? It's because of the lighting here.
Auto balance. I kind of look a little blurry.
I just moved it over to look at it. That was a lot of fun.
That's a good place to end it. Six and a half hours about.
Freddy fish was fun. This game was fun. Good hanging out with you.
Yeah, have a good time. I had a great time. Yes, have a good time. Yes, I have a good time.
I had a great time. Next time you're going to see me will be Wednesday.
See you guys on Wednesday around the same time, between 2 and 2.30 ish.
I say 2, I know, but it really means 2.20. Great, I'll see you Thursday or Friday. Nope,
it's going to be Wednesday. I got a lot of stuff to do this weekend.
There are many, many things that my brain is going to be spread out into five or six places.
So I'm going to have to take the time this weekend to situate them all.
Yeah, see you Wednesday, two o'clock. I don't know. I have no idea what we're going to play.
It'll be something cool, though. I hope. All right, guys, let's run the credits going.
This music is going to stay on. That's fine. What is the oh, never mind.
I enjoyed the music. They would know the game is great. That's really chill.
It was a good chill time. What should I do on Wednesday, though? That's a real good question.
Cruelty Squad? I don't know. I feel like playing Ultra Kill drained me of two straight weeks of
video game playing. I can do Dread X. Don't you feel like you want to have Dread X be for a weekend,
though? And which one should I play? Because there's four or five different compilations.
Which one's a good one? Just start at the beginning. Vampire Survivor. We'll figure it out.
They're all good. Each could be its own stream. Really? OK, I'll look into that. Maybe we'll do
that on Wednesday. Maybe we'll play the first one. Unless we can get some ideas. I can go look at
the recommended two. All right, guys. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. Thanks for
watching. Call your mother. Have a great night. We'll see you again soon. Take care.