Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with the Team Fortress 2 Scream Fortress 2 Halloween Update for 2012.
Got a bunch of stuff to talk about, but first and foremost I wanted to say this first off the bat.
There is a new seasonal key, the Eerie Key, and this will open up the Halloween themed crates.
Just in case you want to know that, in case you want to start collecting those, they are now in the game.
As well as a bunch of other miscellaneous hats, and miscellaneous hats, hats and miscellaneous items that are crazy.
My favorite one so far is probably the Executioner. This one right here in the middle. It is just ridiculous.
I want to get that so bad, I was going to buy it, but I was like, no, I'll hold off for now.
But let's talk about what is in this update.
So the first thing that was added was, oh my, look at the top of the screen.
This is the new man versus machine level called Wave 666.
So as you can see by the top of the screen, it is an insanely massive one wave mission that you cannot do in man up mode.
This is only for the boot camp mode.
And look what happens here, it gives you a ton of money to spend on whatever you want.
Get out there and try to complete the entire wave.
I see 9 tanks, 40 huge demo man, 10 huge soldiers.
Look at all the stuff that comes out in this one wave.
It is probably incredibly intense, incredibly fun.
I had a little bit of trouble getting into a server, so I just wanted to show you guys what that looked like.
So now let's move on to what happened on King of the Hill Lakeside.
So King of the Hill Lakeside is the fourth map that Valve has turned into a Halloween wonderland.
And if you notice on the screen here, this is seven minutes against seven minutes.
It's not three, it is way, way longer.
And if you notice right there, somebody just capped the point.
Every single time somebody caps the point, it's going to do something crazy like this.
This is actually my favorite one right here.
Making everybody dance and then all of a sudden, oh, time to fight now, time everybody shoot at each other.
It's just total pure chaos.
And by the way, it is completely random.
There is no set rotation on any of these things.
It just spins the wheel of fate and whatever it lands on, that's what happens.
Like this one, for instance.
This one reminds me, if anybody ever played GoldenEye, they had something called DK mode.
Where everybody's heads were just proportionately way too huge for their bodies.
And Valve takes it a little step further.
Valve actually drops the voice lines of everybody to sound like this.
They drop it really low.
That was a bad impression, but you get the idea.
And there's actually a whole wide range of these crazy weird things that can happen.
And I don't want to spoil them in the video because when I saw them for the first time, I was laughing my absolute butt off.
So I would like to keep that hush hush for now and for you guys to experience that on your own.
Now let's talk about the boss, Merasmus.
As he is the title character in this update.
Him and the soldier going back and forth.
And he is the cause of this whole problem going on here.
So what does he do and is he killable?
The answer is, I'm not actually sure.
Because all the times that all the servers have been into, even on my server, trying to kill this guy is really, really hard at the moment.
I'm not sure if we're doing something wrong.
I don't think we are.
But how the mechanic pretty much works is like this.
He's going to come out here, take regular damage and if he gets stunned.
And the only way he can get stunned is if you run into him as a bomb.
Which is something he periodically casts on random people.
I don't think there's a real set in stone way to get the bomb cast on you.
And once it's on you, you run around like a chicken with your head cut off and you run right into him.
That's going to stun him.
Once he's stunned, everybody will do crits to him.
And the person that stunned him actually gets an Uber charge to kind of negate some of the damage because they're right next to him.
The problem here is not so much that he has too much health.
He just disappears too quickly.
He's only really around for maybe a minute or two until he's gone.
And trying to coordinate this whole fight with a team, two teams fighting against each other is pretty impossible.
People are just killing each other.
People are running around shooting bombs and grenades and it's very hard to coordinate a whole team to do this.
Maybe if there was nobody else on the map and it was just the red team or just the blue team, I'd say this would be a little bit more easy.
And also on top of that, when you bring him down to about 50% health, he starts to play prop hunt with you.
He actually disappears and turns into a random prop that you have to find and kill the prop and he pops out of it.
So it gets even more crazy once you get to 50% health.
Oh, I also forgot to mention he can take crit damage when he's in the air too.
He does this crazy thing where he flies in the air and throws massive bombs at people and he takes 100% crits.
But still, it's pretty difficult in its current state.
But regardless of all of this, it's a great new update.
Scream Fortress 2012, I believe, is a success.
A lot of new collectibles, a lot of new cool things to pick up, a lot of crazy things going on in the world of Team Fortress 2.
But that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
So I'll see you guys all soon.
And happy Halloween, by the way.
If I don't say it again, which I probably will, happy Halloween.
And I'll see you guys all soon.
And of course, take care, everybody.