Okay, I'm back. So, Vampire Survivors. This is not the first time I've played this game.
Holly and I used to, when it first came out, really just grind this. I've played a lot of this so far,
but it was really when it first came out, so I have not played it in like six or seven updates.
I did play a lot of it though, so I'm very seasoned. If you don't know what this game
is, then you're in for a treat, because the game is actually incredible. Okay, let's get it open.
I might be a little rusty. It has been a while. We'll find out. No wobble dogs? No, I won't play
this. So, I don't know how to get like the new... There's a bunch of new characters, I think. I do
need to turn it up though. That is far too low. How's that? Better? Okay, can you see? I don't
think you can see yet. Hold on. You can't even see me. No. This is creepy. Okay, let's get it up here.
Fucking glover. Can you see it? No? I've never captured this game before. Do I have to capture
the... I probably have to capture the window. That would make sense, wouldn't it? Oh, let me get it.
Hold on. Okay, there it is. I should be able to see it now. Okay, that's not correct. That is also
not correct. That is not correct either. Hey, look at that. Okay, I got a lot of money, as you see.
I got a lot of cash. I play with a controller. Does that make me a shitty person? Does that make
me bad? How come it's not... There we go. Okay. Yeah? Does it make me bad at the game? I know,
you just move around. You literally just walk around. All right, so let's get started. So, start.
You want to see what I've done. I've gotten to level 20 in the forest. This, all this shit. Yeah,
I don't even know what this is. A hundred? I've survived 10 minutes. All right, let's just go.
Want to see my collection? So, they added a lot of stuff, huh? There's like a whole row of new
items. I'm interested. So, who should I play with? I like this guy with the bones. You get more... Oh,
wait, wait, wait. I need to do my unlocks. Oh, power-ups, yeah. So, did they add any new power-ups?
Revive once with 50% health? That seems kind of insane. Curse. Increases enemy speed, health,
quantity, and frequency by 10% per rank. Why would you want to do this? That feels kind of like...
Just make the game harder? It's a challenge run. Oh, okay. I'm going to try this. I'll take this one.
And then I usually take the damage one. I love the damage one. And by the way, the money I got,
because as you play the game, you just get money and you can spend it however you want. You can
refund it whenever you want as well. I know I'm making a lot of motions and gestures towards you.
You can refund it whenever you want. All right, so this is damage. 5% damage per rank. I'm just
going to do this max. What else did I like used to do? Pull down. Oh, more projectiles. Hell yeah.
Move speed. Hell yeah. Luck. Hell yeah. More coins? Yeah. What else is good? I forget. I haven't
played in like three or four months. Probably area. All right. Attack speed. Oh, that's right.
I don't really care about the magnet thing, although it's very helpful. Read. Max health.
Duration. Yeah, whatever. I mean, it's been a while, but I'm just going to fucking put points
away. It doesn't matter. All right, let's go. I'm going to play with the bone guy. So I get
extra projectiles. What do I want to play though? Not yet discovered. Stage two. Oh, the library.
Wait, so hold on. What should I do? This one? Can I do this? I can't do this one yet. Should I do
this one? The library? All right, let's go. See if I remember how to play this game. So all you do
for those who have no idea if those have never played, you literally walk around and the game
auto attacks enemies around you. And the game's harder and harder and harder. You get more and
more and more powerful and there's more and more and more enemies. It's so good. It's like one of
the best games ever made. Okay. So what do I want to do here? I probably, I like lightning
strikes at random enemies. You level up every so often. Check this out. Boom. See that? That's
lightning level one. There's like eight ranks. I think of 10 ranks of every eye of every weapon.
The little gems I'm picking up on the ground. That is experience points. When it fills up at the top,
you probably can guess what happens. I go, all right, what do I want?
I got to, you guys got to help me out here. Cause this is once you get two weapons to maximum,
once you level up and you get two weapons that can combine into a super weapon, I kind of don't
fucking remember. I know lightning didn't have one. Does lightning have a, an upgrade now?
Does lightning have an upgrade? It does. All right. How do I do it? It tells you what you
need to evolve now. Really? It's wings. The duplicator. Okay. So I'm going to, I'll go whip.
I like whip. Duplicator evolves lightning. Hell yeah. Lightning is my favorite move.
I'm not pressing any buttons. Just doing it automatically. By the way, this game is like
fucking $3. $3. That's, this is an ad. I mean, honestly, this is, this game is amazing. It's
through the three bucks. What do you want me to say? All right. 8% more experience. I like that.
Yeah. I want more EXP. This is making me want to play it. I'm excited. You know what I did?
The thing about early access, cause this game is in early access. I was sitting here going,
Oh wow, this game's so good. But it was so early. And I did the thing where I said, you know what?
I want to play it so bad. And this is like the last three or four months, but I just did not.
Cause I knew eventually, like right now I was going to get to a point where like, if there's
enough added, where there's way more for me to see. All right. So I already got bone. I'm
going to do bone level two last 0.2 seconds longer base area bite. Yeah. Let's go on level two.
Santa water is OP. It is, but I was that. Oh shit. Oh, okay. Don't be an idiot.
You do not die in one hit. You have health, but it's bad to get hit. Santa water has upgrade now.
I feel like I, did I play the one, the update that had the upgrade? I don't know.
The library is hard because it's not a whole lot of room to move around. There's a new enemy.
Do water and orb level two. Yeah. Yeah. I want more whip. Let's go. Whip is what? Whip is to
get the super whip. Whip and heart. Yeah. Okay. Hollow heart. Okay. Lightning again.
Do you say, do wings do anything? XP is early is good too. Yeah, but I want lightning. Let's go.
No, XP. Let's do it. So as time goes on, the game just gets harder. So you can really kind of blow
up a whole run. If you build without like enough damage or without enough health or speed,
you can blow up an entire run. All right. Does bone have an upgrade? I don't think this bone
doesn't have an upgrade, does it? No, it didn't have them before either. I want lightning.
Oh shit. What is that? Oh, one of the mod just linked an evolution chart. You're the best.
Bone is bad. Is it? I kind of, I like this guy. Is this guy at the bottom tier?
I thought this guy was good. Oh, chat gave it to me. Oh, chat is absolutely pog. Yeah,
bone bounces. I like, it can bounce off people. Can we go bone level three or do I get some
spinach? What do you think? I would say damage up and one more bone. Yeah, let's do that. That's
fucking pretty sick. Get the mouse off the screen by the way. Mortacio used to be the best character
in the game. Did they nerf this character? That one again. This thing's awesome. Did they give
an upgrade to this? Cause this thing's, this is incredible. This is the thing that bounces around
and goes through people. This thing's incredible, right? They did. All right. I want it. How do I do
it? I have no, I don't even know what this thing, how do I do it? Armor? I don't want to get screwed
up here though, because the thing is these are permanent. You can't take these off and you can
have six of each thing. There's six, there's a, see the top and the top left? The top is the weapon
slots and the bottom is the item slots. So you got to be careful. You don't screw it all up
because you, I can't pick anything else up. I'll do Rune Tracer. Yeah. Cause I want to see the
shit that I haven't seen. If I see armor, I'm getting it. God damn it. I'm, am I actually
going to stream like all fucking night? Yeah, probably. Yeah, let's go. I'm going to have to
take a break to eat something though. I would tell you right now, the stream is good. We're going to,
we're going to just kind of chill and just play this the fuck out of this for like the next,
at least three or four hours. So we're going to chill, just play, right? It's going to be fun.
I love this item. I just completed all my exams. Hell yeah. Hope you did good. This, you need this.
I, I need this because I'm terrible. Laurel sucks. I thought I, I'm, I'm awful at this game.
Let's, let's talk about what a chest does. Okay. So when you open a chest, it randomly,
depending on if you could get an Epic, a legendary, I don't know what it is yet.
It randomly upgrades one or two or three items that you have.
All right, cool. Yeah, that's good. I'll take it. That's good for me. You can get a legendary
chest. That's five random upgrades. And oh my God, does it feel good? Whip. I'm telling you right
now, I, me and Holly, we just, we just sit on the couch and I would just be high with my mouth open
just like watching her play. I would literally be sitting there like this for like two straight
hours. I'm doing whip again as it should be like, Hey, do you want to play? No, I just want to watch
you. Oh, dinner. Does that mean help? All right. I got it. So I, so now here's what happens.
So this is random, right? So if I max out the armor and I max out the rune tracer,
I can combine them. This is going to be awesome. I can't wait. All right. Don't tell me what it
does because I don't want to know. All right. Now this is a run, so I can't fuck it up. Don't be an
idiot. Once you confirm that you have the two items that you need to at least do one or two major
upgrades, don't fuck it up. This is an auto battler, resident sleeper. No, you don't resident sleeper
vampire spires. I'm sorry. You just don't, you can't, you can't do that. This is like actually
like, I think illegal. Nice whip upgrade. Okay. Do I just rush this or do I just let it go? What
I meant 10 minutes is where it gets crazy. Go with Santa water. If I get Santa water, that's it.
I don't have any other room for upgrades for, for weapons. So I need, if I do Santa water, so I have
the rune tracer. I need the heart container for the whip. So that's two. Okay. I'll have enough
room, right? Well, I have enough. I can't make the decision yet. I don't know. Only the weapon
needs to be max. Really? I thought it was both. Really? Fire wand. This is it. All right. We got
the hollow heart. So now I I'll be able to get the max whip soon, which is huge. The max, max whip
has life steal too, which is crazy. Okay. So we're going to do lightning orb, rune tracer,
and whip mega upgrades. And okay. Yeah, let's do it. Because that, if this is Santa orb, right?
Santa. Um, let me see. Let me make sure. Yeah, it is. All right. Let's do it. Around the 10 minute
mark is where this gets wild. What's the lore for the game? I actually don't know. We're gonna do
bone. It's like Castlevania. Kind of reminds me of Castlevania. Bone again. Another projectile for
bone. So am I on level two for the library? Oh, it's getting wild. Resident sleeper. No, I mean,
we're, we're just chilling out now, right? Like, okay, if I'm going to, that's like the, I need to
pretend like this is crazy. So you don't leave, right? Like, oh, it's getting real. It's getting
wild. It's getting crazy guys. Oh, whoa. It's getting wild out here. So, you know, like we're
going to click the X. Oh, you don't want to miss this. No, I don't get. That thing explodes and I
might get hit. I need to wait. I haven't seen ruin tracer at all. Oh dude. It's getting wild.
Those things explode and they can kill you in like one hit. They really can. It's awful.
It's truly terrible. Oh, this is going to be awesome. Oh, it's getting wild. You see that?
Okay. Yep. I want the Santa water. Santa water drops a little like a little splashes.
There we go. Finally. What's the lightning upgrade? The ring, the duplicator. Okay. So
I don't want to take, I'll take the, uh, you kind of like the friend that's really interested in
the niche game. I mean that I don't know. Would you call this game niche right now? I feel like
this is like one of the most popular games on steam. I feel like this game is like wildly,
wildly popular. So in that first screen, I know like most of you guys have already played this,
I've seen this a million times, but in that first screen where you can do the power-ups,
see the little blue area of effect that's kind of like twinkling. That's kind of on the ground.
That does damage when people walk on it. When you first do the, you look, you do the power-up
screen, you do area of effect, you do cooldown reduction, right? You kind of build the character
the way I'm sorry. I bumped it. What do I want to do first? Probably this one from what I remember
the Santa water at high levels is fucking crazy. And I'm not going to square anymore. Cause like,
what was the point of saying the F word? Good. I'll take it.
The F word. Oh fuck. This is a pro tip for you. If you see a health on the ground and you have full
health, don't touch it. You might need it later and things do not despawn. It's a little,
that's a little pro tip for you. All right. We're almost at 10 minutes is where it gets hard.
This is where it determines if you have the right build to continue going. And oh my God,
it's about to get really wild here. I actually stopped fucking around because I don't want to
lose at 10 minutes. The game says, okay, you've been playing for a little while. Let's see if you
can actually beat it. Let's see if you have like a build that's worth playing. I'm going to do whip
cause it's closest. Okay. This is going to be huge. Oh, should I just do spell binder for the
Santa water? So wild, crazy, hyper insane. Oh, I think I'm just doing Santa water. Spell binder
also helps the bone. Yeah, I'm doing it. Spell binder again. You love to see that. That's awesome.
You love to see that happen. Okay. I'm going to do bone again, base damage, almost at the max bone.
Whoa. XP batches. All right. Bone is maximum. I cannot upgrade bone anymore. That's good. It's
going to be bouncing around and helping out. Oh, okay. Imagine, imagine, imagine bad chesting,
vampire survivors. What do you imagine? Bad chesting, vampire survivors. Who are you? Okay.
I want ruined tracer fires. Another projectile. I forget what this does.
Kills everything on the screen. Hell yeah. All right. Spell binder. Yeah. The red ones are worth
way more. All right. Am I missing any secondary item that I need? Wings is, um, no, cause I need
the duplicator. So I can't do that. I just do what Santa water again. Come on. You should smoke weed
on stream. I'm not going to do that. Why? For what? Chest. Actually I probably shouldn't touch that
because when you get to a max, you need to open it in a chest. Has that changed or is that the same?
It's the same. Okay. All right. So I don't want to touch that yet until I have something that's max.
So I can open the, um, yeah, I'm not going to touch it. Look at that area. Look at that area.
It's gotten so much bigger. Oh, wait. Are you guys bad chesting? Cause I'm saying like, oh, wow,
this is so cool. Look at how cool this is. That's why you, that's why you're doing that. Right.
You said chest. Oh, please attract or begin. Cause I don't want to use the sec. I don't,
I only have one more slot, so I'm not using it. I need a duplicator. I love this game. Yeah,
I do too. It's great. Don't listen to all the bat chest haters out there. Okay.
They're all just making it up. You can't not like this game. I don't think it's possible.
Oh, that bat means chest usually. That means whatever. Fuck off.
Fuck it. I, it actually does though. If you, if you kill one of those highlighted bats,
there is a very high chance that it's going to drop a chest.
It's been a while since I've seen a lightning. Stop. I know. Stop. You're making me swear. All
right. No one's wearing. I can't. Whatever. Dude, this isn't paper Mario. Wait, are you defending
the bat chesters or are you saying they shouldn't be doing it? Oh, all right. We're good. I got the
duplicator. Whip is going to be first, I think. So how long do I have to survive in the library now?
40 minutes at least 30 at least. Okay. I think I've done that or have I? Maybe I did 20.
All right. There's, there's two chests here. I think I'm just going to get this one. No.
Yeah. Okay. Let's get it. Whatever. All right. Don't open the other one. I'm surprised as many
people don't like know what this is. Well, hopefully some of you guys that didn't know
what this was, look at this and go, this is fucking hog champ. And I love it. There's a bat chest
right there. It'd take a while to kill. See, I told you. All right. There it is. I got whip level
eight. Check this out. Bloody tear. Evolve whip can deal critical damage and absorbs HP. Take a
look at it now. Now this thing is insane. Play more of this? Oh yeah. I'm going to play in this
rest of the night. I mean, I will, I will accept you. I will accept you bat chesting Glover,
but I am not going to stand here and let you bat chest vampire survivors. You have any,
you don't even know what you're saying. It's like, it's crazy to me. Bat chesting Glover. Okay. Oh,
Glover and 64. Whoa. Oh, excuse me. All right. Lightning level six. Yep. I want to try to get
the lightning one. I wonder what it does. All right. Lightning level eight. Here we go. Let's
do it. What does it do? Thunder loop, evolved lightning ring, projectile strike twice. Oh shit.
That's probably crazy. Whoa. Holy shit. All right. That was actually insane. All right. That's
actually insane. Don't pass over the duplicator. Um, I, I'm messing. This is a good run actually.
All right. Duplicator again. All right. What do we got here? Rune Tracer level six.
There's a good chance of winning this. Yeah. Oh yeah. Absolutely. Sometimes you just get
this dog shit and you just can't get something going. One more projectile base area by 20%.
Yep. Yeah. I win this one. This is going to be a win here. As long as I don't do anything like
boneheaded. What is that? Oh, okay. Level seven Santa water. Rune Tracer. Another projectile.
This one. Jesus. Okay. Rune Tracer is level eight. I'm ready to upgrade it. Oh my God. They're all
level eight. Um, where's the chest? What does this one do now? No future evolved Rune Tracer
explodes when bouncing and in retaliation explodes. Oh my God. I don't, I think it's
impossible that I possible to lose. I got another one, right? Hell yeah. LeBora evolved Santa water
damaging zones, follow you and grow when they move. Okay. Time for the bit rate to shit the bed.
Don't have a funny title. Don't go. Somebody said, don't commentate the game. I don't care.
Okay. Wait, what? What do you want? It won't just be quiet.
All right. The title of the stream is not vampire survivors. And then in brackets,
long play, no commentary. Although maybe I should change it to that.
Should I just change it to that? I have a joke. I'll do it. I'll do it for that person.
Okay. Here you go. Here's your joke.
Fuck. For one second. Shut the fuck up.
Like people saying like mute your mic, mute mic, idiot. Like stop talking. Like I've built a
reputation of being the guy that just doesn't talk on stream. And everyone's like pissed when I do.
And that would be a big controversy. That would be a huge controversy. If finally I just, I said
something and I'd be like, shut whatever. Like I sneezed once, like relax. And I lose like
fucking a thousand, like a thousand viewers or something. Lose like 10,000 viewers. That's not
what I'm here for. Voice revealed. Like stop talking. Stopped up. Like I did. I talked for
not even a second guys. Like relax. This game is so loud. Hold on. Is it really? Hold on. Let me fix
it. Is that better? I'm unstoppable right now. Your face cam quality is dog shit. What do you
want me to do? I don't, it's so hot in this room. I don't, I always take the money. Always.
I'm, I'm just, I, this is amazing. I can't fall asleep to this. Here we go. More money. More.
Give me more. More money. Can we get a bit rate Pog face? Yeah. It's too quiet now. Holy shit.
I forgot about this thing. This was actually a great start. This is a great start. I got to turn
on hyper mode next time. I'm going to do like hard mode. I'll try it. Face cam is too big.
It's still too big. No guys. I'm not muting my mic. No, I, I want to do some new content.
I'm not muting my mic. I want to do some new content. And I, you've, yeah, you know me over
the last five to 10 years as being the long play, no commentary and everything. But today I wanted
to, I just wanted to have you, I wanted to talk. Why is that such a big deal? I don't know. I don't
understand why. I want to change. I kind of have what I'm doing and not just do like no commentary.
If there's a lot of people there, I figured I could see if anyone's still like, can I hear
me talk and everything? If you don't like it, then just fucking leave. Okay. How's that sound?
I'm doing it. I want to, I'm taking my channel in a new direction. It's commentary. I know the title
says that, but I'll change the title. Rip 200 people. Why is it 200 people? I don't get it.
We made you. We made you. Do you know what I would want to do so bad? I would want to do a like long
play, no commentary video. And it's like six hours long and it's a game, but somewhere in the middle,
just do this huge shitty mic quality burp. It's just like, what the? Holy shit. What was that?
It's just like a,
and that's it. And like, or like have it be like a plate of food, like metal onto ceramic.
He's eating a chicken parm or something, but he's not talking just once for like 10 minutes
in the middle. That'd be so weird. Yeah. You hear a lawnmower open up in the background. Yep.
Oh my God. Wonder what it's going to be. Holy shit. Imagine getting this like 10 to 20 minutes ago.
I'll take the money. How can we look like a simulation? You can't do that in a simulation.
Stop. Graphics have not gotten that far. Damn. All right. I'm almost at 30 minutes. I'm making
so much money. This is what space invaders look like to a three-year-old me. I could see that.
I'm going to puke if I keep watching. Why? Just turn your bit rate down. Turn off the damage
numbers so you can see better. I kind of like the damage numbers though. Like, well, not this late,
but it helps to know like how much you're doing. I'm watching this at 160. All right. We'll go in
hard mode next time. I'm going to turn on hyper and I'm going to do first mode. See how crazy we can
make it. All right. And I got one minute, one minute to get as much money as I can. I got to
get out of this area here. There's so much experience down there. I'm going for it.
I did it. I did it. All right. Oh, I get to revive right because of the thing I bought. Let's go.
Ooh, I unlocked Cavallo. Reach level 100 with unlocks reroll. Reach level 40. Unlock Dairy Plant.
Unlocks Banish. All right. I got a new character. Evolve the Ruin Tracer. You can see how much
damage things were doing. Looks like the bloody, bloody tear was doing a lot. All right. I got to
try Cavallo. This is pretty fun, man. This is a pretty fun game. All right. What's Cus Cavallo?
Gets more projectiles every 20 levels. And he starts with, what is that? He's functionally
identical. What is this? What is this weapon? This is a new weapon. It's a cherry bomb. I'll try it.
That sounds cool. All right. So this guy, let me see. This is more projectiles every 20 levels.
So we want to do projectiles. So let's refund this here. So we're obviously going to do this
because one more projectile is just great off the bat. So if we're going to be based on projectiles,
I want to do projectile speed damage. I'll do move speed too. A little bit of Curse. Yeah,
cool down as well. Banish. Oh, these are new. These are new. Once per rank allows to remove
an item from level up choices for the rest of the run. So what? I can say I don't ever want
to see this again. Once per rank allows to get different choices when leveling up so I can
reroll. That's a lot of money though. 11,000. This is kind of cheap, right? Reroll is stupid.
It's almost all the half the money I have though. Should I do Curse? Or should I wait to do Curse
and do it later? I'll do 20%. I like that. I want luck too. Magnet maybe. Area. Yeah. Max Health.
Breed. All right. That's fine. Okay. So I'll try Cavallo. All right. This is a new weapon. Dairy
plant. The magic map hidden in here might finally lead us to a vampire or at least to more roast
chicken. Dairy. This is new. Am I standing up? Let's do it. So what is this move? So it is it.
Okay. It is. Whoa, it exploded. Why did it explode? They blow up. All right. That's cool.
Okay. I made the game 20% harder. Oh, garlic. Definitely garlic. No, no, I don't. I want
projectiles. This is not a projectile though. Santa water again probably. I like garlic. Let's do
garlic. I love garlic. So how garlic functions is see it just does this big zone around you.
I know this is not the build to do garlic but whatever. I like it. It's my favorite.
Is there a chest already? All right. Here we go. Projectiles. Do I want to do axe or knife?
Probably knife. I would say knife or Rune Tracer again. Yeah. Rune Tracer is just too good. Just
too good. Any wings? Is this technically a projectile? Because this is the bird fly around
you. You need to do two different birds. Is that a projectile or is that kind of something else?
Yes. Bird is a projectile. Okay. Bird is kind of hard to use early but late game it's stupid.
Oh, shit. All right. Is there a map hidden here instead? Should I go looking for it?
Holy shit. Thank God for garlic. Otherwise, I probably would have gotten killed.
Oh, sorry. Killed. I probably would have gotten killed. More cherry bomb. Does cherry bomb have
an evolution? What's the cherry bomb evolution? No? Oh, shit. Okay. Well,
I'm going to do it. It's a great weapon though. It seems like it. It seems really good.
Chest. All right. Give me a legendary right now. Garlic. Legendary. Garlic again. That's actually
awesome. He's ignoring us? No, I'm looking over here every like 15 seconds. For a great
germa, you should relaunch the stream at like 3000 up and see how crusty it is.
Didn't I do that one time? I remember back in like 2016 when I was first starting streaming.
Oh, definitely Bible. I remember playing like Overwatch at like 100k up. All right. I have to
get the other bird. I can't do anything else. No more new weapons. It has to be the other bird.
Garlic. Bible. Tome. Speed. Equal. Yeah. All right. What do I need here? I need garlic in what?
Garlic in something else. Danish the garlic. I like garlic. Here we go. All right. So this is
Pumarola is the evolution for garlic. I'm going to get that. This is my first stream that I'm
watching. Really? What's up? How you doing? Welcome to the stream. First stream too? Really? There's
a lot of new viewers today. Where'd you come from? Where'd all you guys come from? Garlic again.
Garlic saves your life. It really does. I would have gotten hit probably three or four more times
already. I came from what? Gotta stay hydrated. It's a gaming sesh man. Gotta stay hydrated.
Blood looked like doom so I started watching and then this kept me here. Oh, cool. All right.
There's the other bird. All right. Now we got to get the birds up. Watch out for this Minotaur.
Oh, he didn't drop anything? I just popped into the stream. I'm already considered buying it.
Yeah. I want to say I'm curious how many hours I have in this game.
I should just get the duplicator just because garlic and okay. It's just, it's like one of the
best items in the whole game. Of course I am. Nice. Here we go. Very good. I'll take it. Yeah. No
reason to pass it up ever. How high is garlic level six or something? All right. The Bible is,
let me look at my cheat sheet. Bible and spell binder and then it's garlic and heart. I already
have it and then it's rune tracer and armor. Okay. So I need armor and I need, um, spell binder
and then we're good to go for a while. I wonder if I should just get this too.
Will I have enough? I need one, two, three. I'll have enough. Yeah. I'm just going to get it.
Just damage, straight up damage is insane. I'm done doing it. That's going to be like 50% more
damage. What I was going to say is I've already played this game a lot. The really slow burn of
progression in this game is really, really, really fun. Unlocking each new thing and kind of getting
better and better and better and better. It's awesome. Okay. I can't do that. We'll do this.
Yeah. Also crew ran X and chat made a lot of the pixel art for the game. Are they still here?
Really? That's pretty awesome. Oh my God. I'm going to die. Okay. Definitely cherry bomb. No.
Yeah. Spinach. I'm not entirely confident. I think I screwed this up a little bit. It's all right.
All right. Here we go. Spell binder. Hell yeah. I can get the Bible now. Did I need wings for
anything? No, right? I don't think so. How come you're a sloth? Do you think I look like a sloth?
I don't know. Oh, I thought you were talking about me and then like the camera in the top right. I
was like, I don't know. Do you think I look like a sloth? I kind of could see it for a second. That's
why I didn't say anything. I kind of like, I was like, yeah, I guess like I kind of, maybe I do a
little. I don't know. You're talking about that as a panda. I'll take it. Who can complain about
damage? Oh fuck. Okay. I need health. Is there health down here? I did make the game 20% harder.
So I gotta be careful. Jesus. How far down is this? Where the hell is this thing? Did I even go all
the way down here? When did I come down here? This is so far away. I'm not touching that yet.
How far? What the hell? Oh, the title needs to change. Oh shit. I'm probably like dumping
viewers. I'm dumping fucking viewers right now. The title is still there. I forgot about the title.
People probably are coming and they're like, ah, am I dumping? Am I? Are people? No, I haven't lost
that many. Hold on. I gotta change this. How about 160p is fine. Relax. That's better, right? I'm
leaving because you talked. All right. We got the upgrade. Let's go. Let's go. I need to minimize
this window, but I can't. I love the garlic and the Bible. It's just awesome. It's like the double
rings. Hell yeah. You can play Kirby's Air Ride maybe. Hey, it was free. I'll take upgrades.
Can you make the webcam 160p? I could try. I don't think I can. Let's find out. Yeah, I can.
There's no difference. This is at 160p. It's not that bad. It'll be worse. Why am I cross-eyed?
Oh, it's because my eye is like drifting this way. Make your voice robotic? No. It doesn't
like movement, right? Doom guy? Can I change this back? Can I even change this back? What was it
before? 720? Yeah, it was like, no, it was 1080, wasn't it? Yeah, it was 1080. Can I bring it back?
Where is it? What the fuck? What happened? What happened? That was weird. This is very weird.
Why is it like this? I tried to make it. Okay, there we go. All right, we're back. That's fine.
All right, I gotta get back into this. Eye only. No, no, eye only. That's fucking stupid. That's
cringe. Are you cringe? Okay, you sure? No, you sure? Okay, there's no enemies here. Why did I
pick this up? That was stupid. You save that when there's too many things on the screen. You just
get a ton of exp really quick. I still don't know what's down here, but I don't remember being down
here. The webcam looks worse. No, it doesn't. Okay, people said, you should get a better webcam. I
don't want a better camera. You can see every inch of my ugly face if I had a very
expensive DSLR or something. No, no, thank you. No, thanks. You'd be able to see the nose hairs I
have. I don't know. I don't like that. I don't know. I don't want you to see that. I'm actually
confused. Where is this thing? I want this thing to die. Oh shit. Die already, please.
Oh my god, die. Uh-oh. That's a good, I'll take it. All right, I need to break like a box or something
because I'm dead. Are there boxes? I know that this box is in the world, but where are they?
What do they look like on this map? What the fuck? I can't go that way.
Oh, there's like a, oh, it's a magic map. That's what it is. Permanently enables the map in the
pause menu. What? What does this mean? What's that mean? I'm dead. Well, I got the unlockable.
I gotta beat it with a bear. Do it again. Do it again. Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go. All right, no fucking around. Let's go. I'm ready. Axe. Projectiles.
This is Rick and Morty theme song. All right, no garlic. It didn't help us. Knife.
I'm not making a stupid joke. That's what it just sounded like. How many seasons do you think Rick
and Morty is going to go before they cancel it? Or do you think they will cancel it? Do you think
it'll go as long as like the Simpsons? Maybe one or two more? What is it out now? Season five?
I bet you it goes to season seven. The merch alone makes adults swim millions. Yeah.
Hell yeah. I got the bracers. Let's go. All right. I'm kind of getting shit on here.
Ooh, that actually worked really well. Fuck. Knife. I need damage now.
Surprise this is a dead run. I need damage now. This is a dead run. You picked up the worst item
in the game? Uh, ba ba ba. That's all I hear. You just picked up the worst item in the game.
What item? The knife? It's a challenge run, dude. Do the barrels open? Oh, Jesus. No! Fuck. I'm dead.
This place is hard. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it.
I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it right now. Let's go. That's it. No more bullshit. No more
bullshit. Fire. The lamp post of the drop items. Thank you so much. I've never would have guessed
it. It's okay. I don't like this level. Everything looks like it's on the same plane, but like I
can't move over this. It's hard to tell. It's like that in a lot of places. Pentagram erases
everything in sight. It's Ruin Tracer. Every time. Especially now that they can be upgraded.
Put a webcam on the character. How am I going to be able to do that? Yeah, Santa water is amazing.
check the map I'm so confused so what I could try the items that I can go get or
something so I need this for the Santa water pop left you can go over the item
cap if you get the items in the map really so should I not pick this up
they're far away oh fire want to move your webcam away from the level display
yeah that's a good idea there we go all right this is not a bad start
could be better yeah my ass hurts fuck oh god all right I need more damage you
know man the curse really does make the game so much harder because they're
faster than me 20% damn it fuck come on something good that's our it's not bad
because that's 20% more damage oh shit this is bad really bad dude fuck you
fuck okay okay okay I gotta go dude how am I supposed to get through that what
the fuck I'm dead no way no fucking way no way all right I gotta take the curse
off this level is fucking hard yeah I know no way not here speed area oh wait
do the expensive upgrades first right so what's the most expensive probably this
one and then this one and then I want the damage it's just so good
cool down is amazing speed is amazing I need movement speed all right now what
do I want growth recovery is good too yeah because that's that's a pretty
decent amount max health and growth growth and area and okay all right can I
do anything else agreed okay all right this is fine maybe I should have tried a
different character I like the starting with the lightning it's great permanent
plus 30% area starts with temporary cooldown bonus 30% area 10% more
experience every five levels that's huge permanent plus 40% duration and speed
this guy's so low as shit though maybe I could probably still do it on the bear I
have to do I have to beat it on the bear don't I yeah let's try it again all right
this time I don't have the curse so now they're not like 20% more 20% faster 20%
more damage then I'll be fine Domino's pizza I'm gonna eat I'll get the green
one yeah keep forgetting all right cross or garlic no cross mmm I like garlic
though I'm doing it okay now we'll do peach on I didn't mean to touch that
but I did race spinach team garlic garlic is really good it just helps it
just I can't like oh I was to throw up patriotic what's up I didn't spew it I'm
fine how you doing thanks for the Raven appreciate it playing vampire
survivors it's a good game I don't know if a truck has a shit a truck you played
this you played vampire survivors no no let's I want to see it let's see it I
want to see a truck play vampire survivors don't you all right garlic
this game is awesome by the way if you never played it but hey thanks for the
raid welcome everybody I know we're getting late here if you just want to
drop by and say hello what's up if you're gonna leave we have a good rest
because it's pretty late all right this club can discover actually upgrade
anything or what you're ignoring your chat I am not I'm yeah I'm looking at
you right now that's literally me looking at you it's the cross okay as
stands right now I need what I need for garlic I forget every time I think the
axe is it going way smoother red heart right it'll tell you it tells you there
it is ten percent more area we're gonna get the axe up hopefully garlic again
it's a huge area yeah what is axe turning to oh shit there it is
fire wand yep all right the seeds have been planted this is the one is a major
seizure warning late game here really I turned off the I checked the box that's
to make the photosensitive sensitivity mode active I'm getting Laurel ignores
my question he likes radiohead yeah I told the story how me my friends used to
jump around on a trampoline while that song was blasting on a stereo next to
the trampoline right everything is that story I did okay yeah just making sure
you know we would be just jumping it was like three or four of us just jumping in
a circle they're like do do do do do do do do do do it was the stereo was kind
of far away it was next to the trampoline but far enough away yeah
paranoid Android dude nothing will I think ever compare to doing the
trampoline jump in a circle thing well a CD is just blasting next to the
trampoline gimme it oh my god legendary if you're like 12 that's cool I that's
what I said when you were a kid huge huge oh that's huge this is looking like
a pretty good one so far Connor is permanently in your head rent free but
the huge thing I love numbers how much does this game cost looks really fun
well I have got a really really good news for you this game is not $20 it's
not $15 not even $10 this game can be yours for one easy payment $2.99 that's
right that's right that's not I did that wasn't a typo $3 but the amount that it
costs for you to buy three hash browns from McDonald's will get you this game
oh fuck I can't you're right I can't evolve the bird oh it's alright I get I
still got it shit it's okay it's alright I got enough mmm I wasn't paying
attention the run is ruined I think I'll be fine all right it's gonna be it's
gonna be a garlic carry anyways really go all right give me another legendary
garlic legendary why would you buy less than three hash browns when the
McDonald's breakfast is it's just one of those things where you completely
forget it exists until for some reason you just up at like six o'clock in the
morning you're like y'all that's what we're doing right now McDonald's is so
ridiculous I mean other places do this too but McDonald's just has two
completely different operating menus it's crazy the McDonald's breakfast menu
it's just like it's a completely different restaurant and some could
argue it's okay this is not on quiet it's not you me all right we're good
it's so expensive is the breakfast stuff more expensive than okay it's like a
double cheeseburger from McDonald's more expensive than and a sausage egg
McMuffin are they the same McMuffin is more is it really it's about the same I
wonder why maybe see ingredients cuz don't doesn't McDonald's use real
cracked eggs like a real egg that they like they have to actually crack it in
the morning right no they don't they do yeah they do it's only for some of the
stuff yeah but for like a sausage egg McMuffin has like a they crack it into
a little thing and cook it in there I'm almost certain they do god damn I'm
sorry I keep punching you they do yeah they have real and they have fake yeah
that's what I mean like it's some of the items have like actually somebody
actually crack the egg and cook it you guys ever just get in the mood
where you just want to crack like three eggs in a pan and just like flip them up
over easy and just eat each egg in one bite does anybody else do that I take
each egg and I go scoop it up I fold it in my mouth mmm and I eat the whole egg
in one bite and just kind of let it just kind of mush it around and eat it it's
so good I love doing that I love it cuz I'm I don't like when the yoke breaks
and gets all over everything else I'm not I don't like that if I have eggs on
a plate let's say if I go to a breakfast place or if I'm gonna have eggs in the
morning or something those eggs are being eaten in one bite why are you a
snake no but I get that energy I mean it you don't you know I'm not talking
about like you like no you pick it up and you like fold it up and you let you
eat it I don't like when the yoke breaks and gets all over everything else I like
enjoying an over easy egg completely on its own with the yoke and the white at
the same time now there is an exception right if you eat sort of around the yoke
you don't break it I do that too so you'll get the egg white kind of around
the middle can't go that way I'll eat I'll eat that and then you just take the
whole yoke that has a little bit of the whites surrounding it you eat the whole
thing in one bite how do you guys eat your eggs you let me guess you guys like
cut cut cut cut spread spread spread and then it touches all your other food and
then after about five minutes you have this cold yoke this cold gooey liquid
all over all your other shit yuck omelets are better omelets are amazing
those are incredible the yoke is like extra sauce yeah I would feel that way
if it didn't turn it okay yoke when it's broken after a few minutes changes
it turns into this half kind of solid congealed liquid but not liquid sometimes
it like heart I don't know mmm hard-boiled eggs are amazing but you
have to eat them right when you make them I would still eat hard but we
already went over the hard-boiled egg stuff right hold on I don't want to die
how have I not gotten anything to upgrade these yet that's kind of insane
deviled eggs are amazing deviled eggs can be incredible but they gotta be
fresh I'll be the first person in line when the deviled eggs come out I'll be
the last person in line when they've been out for more than five to ten
minutes like after a deviled egg has been out for like 20 minutes nope we've
been over this already yeah but there's new people here so much experience here
yeah eat food however you want right I'm just telling you how I do it and how you
do it is wrong right that's the point how come you're the panda I'm the panda the pandas
move actually when it's leveled up is really good the explosion is crazy get
away from me Jesus oh fuck oh my god I'm gonna die I forgot I got that thank God
shit's not dying fast enough oh boy this is it oh that's it say goodbye I need
survivability right now no way I'm not getting out of this no fucking way it's
over shit I wish there was one of those items on the ground one of those like
breathing fire items look at how much shit would be oh this would be crazy if
I could just have something to show up right now how have I haven't gotten
anything to upgrade these that seems impossible really hmm this thing's the
highest I mean it I gotta get it up oh god oh all right here we go I need a
chest right now please give me a chest that's a garlic evolution right there
I'm in so much trouble this is bad this is so much I'm in so much trouble I need
a chest right now dude um axe god damn it axe again try to get this I feel like
I should just get it I'm kind of afraid that I'm gonna die holy shit okay I don't
want I don't want to take up slots I have to get the thing in the middle
because I need for the axe candle improves garlic yeah but I need the axe
upgrade well what's the um I already have it I'm missing something what am I
missing bracer is probably pretty good here doesn't pair with anything though
candle and axe if I die that tiramisu goes away right I think I'm just gonna
take this I can't make a decision the other bird I can't take the other bird
because I messed up and took too many weapons I'm just gonna go with this I
can't make a decision right now I survived that I should be alright
duplicator dude come on I need to do but I need to do axe I have to evolve
something in that I'm at almost 15 minutes and I don't have anything
evolved okay axe Jesus get away from me all right finally axe level 8 I need a
chest somebody can I spawn a chest for God's sake I need something evolved
holy shit I forgot they were on screen I'm an idiot I think I'm gonna get this
let's go all right finally run saved there it is the side death spiral
evolved axe passes through enemies and it's huge if I remember it's gigantic if
I remember oh yeah I really kind of wish I had cool down I don't have anything at
max level do I that can be evolved I've got oh no garlic yeah I do garlic get
me up there please oh yeah steals hearts power increases when recovering HP so
it's like a lifesteal right let's get this up all right run and save I need I
need a lot okay I need a lot more in fire I'm just gonna get this chest
because I feel like yeah okay that was perfect because I got a long way to go
on the fire one really that's kind of absolute dogshit oh well okay yeah I
haven't seen any fire one yeah just get the cherry bomb up max take that please
not even one level really another duplicator I have to I have to wake up
what go to the question mark on the map I'll try to get there well I sort of say
wake up wait why did my voice just do that that was weird all right I'm gonna
make my way to the question mark I didn't want to upset but I did wake up
hurry up it's not it's almost time for bed okay base area 25 base damage all
right that's max that's actually incredible I talked a lot of shit about
that up weapon but that's really good the area of it that explosion area is
massive after this go to bed I'll do like no I'm not yet I'll do a few more
maybe like one or two more I want to see what I unlock from this because I'm
definitely gonna unlock something if I beat this so not quite my still I still
need to do the fire one all right I'm gonna try to get to the question mark
that's really far away but let's see if I can get there why are you trying to
send 36 year old man to bed I don't want to go to bed you go to bed right this
instant mister right now I will in a little bit maybe one or two more is that
I was gonna make a line to that all right I'm getting there just stay I'm
gonna go this way 10 more minutes it's gonna be close feel like I'm not
clearing that fast like I was on the first run give me that it's your stream
you should go as long as you want yeah oh yeah no I'm good I'll be good for a
little while I told you this is this is we're just winding down here this is the
chill part of the screen see we had three different streams today we had
like the kind of wild first two or three hours with that scary game then we had
the middle gamer moments where I was playing the FPS gaming and now we're in
the chill mode we don't talk about Glover that didn't happen
ooh I definitely want that that's gonna kill everything in one hit pick up all
the stuff hurry that first run was seriously so good that's exactly what
you want to have happen every time this one's not bad though luck I don't
understand what's happening uh I'm walking around and things are dying
that's pretty much all you really need to know all right eight minutes can I do
it how far how close am I my still that far away I think I'm gonna be here for a
while fire wand again just walk in a circle
fire wand again base damage up what is the fire it turns into like a meteor or
something right one more and I need a chest there's no Glover footage to
upload what do you mean all right there it is and what do you know just right
here it's like a meteor hellfire passes through enemies evolved fire one right
this thing's really deadly if I remember y'all yeah this thing's insane all right
I'm good to go I should get to 30 minutes because I don't think there's a
world where I don't almost maxed out here and then it's just get money hey
what's a bluffer I don't go too far there's no reason to go far because I
won't I'll miss out on money you just want to at this stage if you got a
really insane building you can't even do anything else just stand in the middle
and just collect money this is pretty much a locked in when I think I could
try to go get the question mark but I think I feel like I'm too far could I
you think I could I get there in time you think I'll make it it might be too
far I'll try kind of just southeast maybe I can't make it five minutes yeah
I'll get it turn on map guides guide guides show guides what oh that's
interesting okay I gotta be careful this is I could die really quickly if I'm not
okay hold on stop moving is it a key I wonder what that is good even though I'm
really powerful you still if I lose the Laurel you die in one second to these
enemies if they touch you you'd lose 30 40 percent per second you can die very
easily right now I have the two yeah right I have to revive to you right I
shouldn't be all that concerned Jesus how close am I now all right I'm almost
there there's a chest after nothing can be in there anyways so what is it it is
coffin what is it what is this thing thank you
at a cavallo but the vampire is in another coffin Poppaea Pecorino joins
the survivors oh it's a new character oh we're gonna check that out after this
all right now just live just survive I mean I could get this one this is pretty
close I think just live you're gonna eat a glove on stream it's yeah it's it's
currently midnight it's like three o'clock in the morning almost Eastern on
April 24th free stooges are not in fortnight although I wonder what what
legal battle was going on behind the scenes it was I don't know so I'm gonna
have to eat a I'm gonna need a glove on screen whatever it's gonna be so funny
if the three stooges are announced in fortnight in like five days you have to
eat a glove tomorrow I'm not gonna eat a glove tomorrow on screen that's not I'm
not even gonna scream tomorrow that's just free money you gotta give me a
little bit of time to be able to find out what kind of glove I want to eat so
we talking baseball glove we talking surgical glove are we talking what kind
of glove are you talking about here like a mittens like a mitten we're going
outside in the snow it has to be a glover glove a Mickey Mouse glove white
just a baseball glove love to do a poll all right mods let's see a poll yeah
yeah mods even here it's really late when I I would be surprised if there are
a lot of mods here give it up for the mods by the way it's very late all right
baseball glove Mickey Mouse slash Glover glove big okay no baseball glove cartoon
white glove surgical glove or winter mitten they go oh my goodness that's a
wall in front of me that's a wall in front of me that's a wall I can't go
down I think I'm fine I have to revive twice just give me the
points yeah master hand glove is cartoon white glove okay hyper dairy plant
popiah and gallo tower very cool make a glove pizza hamburger helper glove is
white cartoon glove it's Glover Mickey Mouse hamburger helper they're all the
same yeah Glover counts as a cartoon glove what is it at right now okay so it
looks like cartoon white glove survive ten minutes with okay all right what is
a popiah gains 1% duration every level what does that mean what does this move
the duration of her weapon effect ah there's no maximum that seems kind of
insane holy water Bibles bones really so I should do even more duration then okay
duration 30% more duration more area projectile I definitely want luck pull
down speed all right it looks like it's gonna be a cartoon white glove now
that's way too much on this again I want try even get the duplicate yeah I guess
so what else do I even want growth is so important moving speed good 4,000
advantage is cheap I was just take it I think that's good all right so we're
looking for duration stuff duration so yeah what is this I'm interested what
this move is gallo tower I'll try gallo tower yeah so I eat eat a cartoon white
glove you got it whoa okay this thing is awesome does this have a level up it
evolves with the in-game curse item what gloves should German eat no channel
points this time wait what none of these have a duration axe maybe or whip mmm
cross is good this weapon is awesome though all right duration is the ebony
wings is that duration I think it is right all right this time don't screw
this up and get the other bird this is a really this is really small area as it
just vertical it's a great character to take here gets the vertical cross again
song of mana base area up a hundred percent this thing is like s-tier this
is insane can anybody else get this or is this just just her this item is
basically garlic but good she's really busted late game Chris is always with
duration we got duration how do we get with this oh this is awesome okay what's
the red skeleton why okay white cartoon glove one again there's the Bible yep
hi this looks like a win already just don't be an idiot there it is all right
I got both the birds this character is awesome this is probably the best
character in the game cool down I think I want cool down what is cool down scale
with magic wand all right so I should probably get magic one the last one
right where's it no sorry is it rune tracer I thought it was magic one magic
wand is bad but it's okay the wand sucks don't even get it I definitely want this
do not get magic one magic wand eventually turns into a machine gun
it doesn't stop right there's rune tracer do I want that as my last lot
though because I can't I guess I could yeah duration it lasts a lot longer yeah
this is the character to play here cool down effect lastly I was just level this
up I want to get this thing up fast hell yeah all right there's the I can do the
cross now he's gonna be invincible yeah area is great yeah do I have enough
spaces to do that all right is the cross worth evolving really good hold on I'm
not gonna upgrade the tomb I'm not gonna upgrade the I feel like I'm
spreading myself out and I'm not gonna be let evolve anything you have the Bible
upgrade yeah I have a Bible I'll take the candle might as well I'm just died
I need a chest here he seems tired I'm just chilling man I'm just chilling
late it's like almost midnight just chillin where are the breakable what are
the breakable things here for food oh my god I'm dead I don't know what's going
on what's hitting me which is what was hitting me they teleporting against the
candles have a good race interest her ace damage ace area too all right now
we're talking they respawn out of this watch out for that evil position
cool down and last longer I keep running into them yeah I am why though they just
are kind of respawning on top of me again ace damage up more area what do I
need for this for the this thing this upgrade thing the TV static move I don't
have it oh shit okay oh my god I just walked into it they do respawn all
right I gotta stick around and be careful shit that sucks that's kind of
hard deal with because I don't know but when is it safe to go over there just
gonna keep moving cuz they respond but it takes him like a second or two so
all right level eight this is the max I can get for this so it's pretty much on
it's on permanently it's cool but it actually is kind of impeding my vision
it's giving me a bad bitrate on my own computer screen um anything on this map
that's like a question mark or anything oh this chest although wait let me go
get this first this is just free goodness there's a gate here I'm locked
in did not know I was gonna be locked in cross again sensory overload yeah it's
gonna get worse just go get the free item and then go back up and get the
chest please get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way
duplicator but ah I don't want to mess anything up here get the duplicator now
I feel like that's gonna mess it up always get duplicator it's okay hold on
it's cross and a Bible and cool down right this is gonna mess up if I want I
think hopefully this group anything Ross birds Bible and root tracer yeah this
thing is far away there's a potion it's like a magic potion down here all right
this is great I could just literally walk down this is perfect I just take it
right so if it's free level two yeah sure oh am I right oh my god what the
fuck just happened dude what happened what the fuck happened what I went to
go oh shit that was a good one too fuck oh that sucks oh my god I'm so pissed
that sucks see see I told you right it you die in one fucking second they got
aggroed after you took the item shit shit this sucks this is I don't want to
ever see this again what happened do what happened what the fuck happened
that was so quick I couldn't react yeah all right yeah let's just get these out
of the way right we're good we're good everything's good he's gonna melt down
no meltdowns today this level is kind of hard too all right so I take the item
and it spawns a shitload of things I gotta be aware that there's the magic
potion down here too kill please you have all six passives you can pick up
an extra one have seven or eight you shouldn't me this is gonna be the one I
this is the one don't be messing around you settling into bed you said that
thing sucks doesn't really suck that bad doesn't it go through people now that's
the fire Tracer again yep all right keep going down they keep showing it to me I
don't want it I keep dude they keep showing to me mouse cursor I got it okay
prices averted let's go give me a legendary oh my fucking god I forgot
these guys do that you gotta just keep moving those guys oh you got it those
guys awful you just keep moving you gotta just keep moving let me hang out
here for a second and get rid of this guy yeah come on that's all right he's
starting to slur his speech come on give me one why I'm not slurring my
speech this dude's slurring his speech he's sleepy I'm okay
definitely a song of ice and fire yes I'm gonna do this so that's a grenade I
gotta be why I'd be careful of that all right this is where I got cocky last
time I'm just gonna walk straight down easy don't do that
careful this kind of sucks all right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yep yep yep that
I'm not gonna happen that time not happening this time you pieces of shit
have a ton of health to pick it up pick it pick it up all right we're good this
stupid-ass magic wand I swear to God guys what the hell maybe he's not good
at this game that's probably Santa water it has to be all right let me chill here
for a minute where's the potion all right potions a little bit further down
don't get whacked did they respond more than once or is it just okay there you
go it's just one time is he playing with a mouse no I got a controller man I'm
not confident at all though zero look at my items I have seven items right now
seven minutes change insides so where's all the good shit these guys on dropping
any experience I got a chill for a minute because nobody I got a level up
no one's dropping enough experience come on something really important going on
behind me he's snoring he's doing that like he's like dreaming and snoring at
the same time yeah he yes he has two beds it's like Snoopy he doesn't like
that one that bed was like a hundred and fifty dollars that bed was like thirty
bucks I might even been more than that spoiled always I put a mic over there
um that's not gonna work okay we'll get it to max all right so what's this
potion what's there is it a quest item all right be careful careful careful
careful careful don't be an idiot we're interested level three oh shit
sorceress's tears permanently allows to speed up time in stage selection speed
up time I don't get it they keep seeing a stupid magic wand I woke up from a
dream about German fighting climate change why am I just infiltrating you
guys dreams so much I need the other bird Santa water again all right okay I
got armor for the rune tracer he's showing again I don't know what to do
here it's a lot of experience okay this is gonna be close okay this King Bible I
don't want to mess myself up here I need King Bible which will get me cuz that's
duration yeah oh the other bird hold on I need the other bird if I do Bible and
the other bird should be okay or should I just forget about the Bible I think
it's too good I still have a few slots I have options all right well there's the
axe do I even do I get the axe though I don't know what to do mm-hmm I have to
get something up because we're getting a ten minutes here yeah this would be the
last run to whatever happens here this is it I've got a win there we go I'll
take that this projectile is floating around I have to be careful don't be a
stupid idiot I know it's a duplicator is always an instant grab but not right
now I think I'm all right without it is there another item up top that's a quest
item tracer there is I mean it's so far away there's no way I'm getting at this
run that's a new enemy I don't know hang out here damn it if you 10 minutes to
get down you have 18 minutes left that's true that's true and there's a ton of
stuff that I yeah let's go back up there's a lot of items and stuff that I
didn't get don't be walking into stuff I'll go for it let's go back up Bible or
wait for um I kind of feel like the Santa water is not great here because
it's just a vertical map I'm kind of just going into the bright and left
sides there we go hell yeah all right perfect closer and closer that's huge
okay I'm gonna wing three okay back to back oh hell yeah this is it I might
even actually get the upgrade right now for one of them whatever it is it's
close I think that's it for rune tracer right or is that it for a tracer level
six all right no I'm almost there all that that's five items I don't have to
level up I don't know where the I with the things are but I am I'm getting them
I know I'm duration with this is crazy this is still going oh my what again
again all right ruin tracers maxed out see your chest more XP more XP this is
raining remember up holy shit yeah we're still going where this is it though
we're done after this oh my god well seven all right I might I'm almost there
I just need chests all right there might be a chest right here where'd he go god
there's so much on the screen all right I'm doing eight I just need just I'm
just power washing these enemies right now this is ridiculous holy shit what
the fuck does that mean I freaked out was ran Bible I don't I can't I can't
see I don't know what that is what is that thing what's all over me oh okay
no I'm fine I'm good good give me a chest please dude I gotta go up okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay all right everything's maxed out I just need
chests there's the Bible evolve King Bible it never ends I can't even tell
what's happening I don't even have everything maxed out yet either just
would be great just torrential downpour here we go why did I not evolve that's
the chest from the start of the game all it has to spawn after right okay I walked
by it's right here where is this there it is okay so now I got Santa
LeBora is now maxed out back up now I need the birds and that's it no rune
tracer isn't either is it like I have another ten minutes it's a vacuum
cleaner on in the room well I'm in an airplane I'm your chest right now this
one yeah this rune tracer this now explodes right explodes when bouncing
and in retaliation this is gonna be ridiculous this might be the most
ridiculous display I've ever seen out of all the time I played this game I'm not
sure I've seen something like this it's kind of kind of can't see what's
happening ten ten more minutes of this something's hitting me oh my god all
right they respond be careful circular motion circular motions circular motion
circular motions we'll get up there eventually okay let's go is there a
chest yet I can't even see I don't think so the colors are blending together hold
on am I there is a chest right here this is an AI generated image all right I got
the super bird this is where it gets crazy it shoots like the yeah I got ten
minutes to go walking a story line up everything's maxed out completely maxed
out what's all that all those cards one more weapon oh my goodness you're right
what should I try to get I forgot when they combine it you get another one back
what should I try to do pentagram oh that's right you can keep leveling this
thing up we'll do that for now pentagram should I do pentagram I feel
like this is the kind of ramps up didn't I banish the pentagram at the very
beginning I could do the axe because I have the evolve right all pentagrams do
I have the thing that requires the pentagram to evolve what do you need for
it I do all right now if it shows up I'll get it I never done that before no
no pentagram oh my god I can't see any help guys hey what's happening I'm
fucking dead huh what was going on I couldn't see what was happening I have
to dodge the mortis yeah I what I could I could see the exclamation point but I
didn't I don't know where the circle is do my screen is like I can't fucking see
anything what the fuck wings are necessary on this map because what the
hell was that oh my god I was trying to talk I could see the exclamation points
I'm assuming that there's like a circle around it and I'm trying to move around
and get the fuck out of the way god damn it that was such a great run too oh
that sucks oh come on really I didn't expect them to be that many it just they
just kept happening I didn't know where to go all right that's it oh that's
suck what a shitty one to go out on I even have that I had the movement speed
shit all right one more one more now I know that happens maybe I should do here
this is actually the last one for real there's no way I'm doing another one is
that the for real the last one who do I play with should I do the same character
I feel like I said I don't know stupid reporter what does hurry mode mean all
right we're going up it's all about the area it's all about lightning ring yeah
see it's like I it's hard to tell Santa water we're doing all area area area
area I'm going up I'm so salty with that one well now I know what they do it's
like they go whoop and they land so the exclamation point happens and then it's
like two it's like a full two seconds later it's like one two there and it
shows up see that I couldn't tell yeah you couldn't see anything and I'm taking
Laurel and I know that's like a you know wow this dreamer is actually gonna take
Laurel I want it and I need it I feel like it's a huge thing to have here I
feel like it's very important especially when you don't know what you're getting
hit by I'm taking it duration or it's just let's just rush these up as fast as
I can look we're already at one minute Laurel has helped a ton yeah it really
does especially when it gets leveled up because then you can take three four
five hits in a row it's really really helpful I'm not concerned about damage
here I have lots of concentrated damage so I think I'll be fine that one was so
cool though hey stop walking in circles it can't be I where do I get the thing
that upgrades it more more again more Kylo Ren more more I can't I don't know
why I just thought of the Voldemort Homer Simpson thing again that's been
killing me I don't know why I've been thinking of it recently legendary chest
writer stick around I'm not going anywhere until I get it up just in this
guy Bible this is area right but the Bible's are huge aren't they yeah hey
you good yeah you you good legendary get the axe for area passive that's
probably a good play Oh spellbinder yep do I use a voice changer
uh when I press the button yeah a little bit of sweet a little bit that might be
the greatest thing to come out of that stream those guys was so funny they
really were that was such a great group but that was such a great group of guys
yeah yeah let's go can I get a look at me okay if I don't do it this time then
when the hell am I ever gonna do I just save so much time very nice everything I
have it that's actually good to get early because it just makes half your
shit just go up higher yep all right all right no let me the heel I've been a
little excited look the borough cell Laurel cell fate whatever it is build
up all right lightning is maxed and then I just need to get the thing and I'll be
good to go get out of here yeah give me that thank you
yep all right we're good yep I feel a little more confident in this one
mainly because of the law of the Laurel I have trouble just stubborn this on the
switch would be crazy no kind of be hard on the switch anything that small screen
the hardest it was going on be cool I gotta get down here and get this all
these crunchies all right hold on I need I have the orb I think I take the I
think I take the terms too I'm not confident now let's do the candle again
how close am I to all right I'm oh look at all these cards and stuff what's that
whatever that is I'm almost there well oh my god this this is not the run then I
don't know what the hell is gonna happen is they're just giving it to me at this
point they're just giving it to me perfect beautiful oh am I in trouble
here if I don't banish one of these I need three slots don't I or should I
just take the crown I think I need three slots I think I need the slots otherwise
I won't be left I think that's where I call all right so I don't want to touch
this do I because this is gonna give it to me shouldn't I not touch this the
bracer that's up here yeah don't touch it yet all right
Bible's up all the way area be careful cuz it's gonna spawn a bunch of shit at
me isn't it Laurel be careful yep okay third of the way there
I haven't seen that in a while what do I want for my lap should I get my last
item axe right yeah axe okay here we go first evolve Bible I need more
projectiles maybe I don't damage is not a problem right now it really isn't
they would just bond over there just walk in a circle and collect all right
here we go we're almost at the I don't want to pick this up should I get this
now cuz everyone's saying this is insane get the pentagram pentagram pentagram
but not yet late game I'm not touching that shit it's okay Laurel for the win
damage is falling off I gotta get some more stuff all right that's fine
it was halfway there all right good opportunity for a chest I'm just
collecting that's it don't worry I'm going back up awesome okay so I need to
level up like one more time right I'm gonna stick around here for a second
one of the scientists let you out of the lab oh yeah let's go um well it was a
hospital and it was when I was an infant I was born and then my mother and father
took me home oh that was about when I was another day old how long are you in
the hospital for when you're a baby uh I don't want any of these so I'm gonna
have to just do this that's not that's not axe oh this is a disaster if I do
armor I can get the ruin tracer yeah yeah and then I have that okay well
ruin tracer it is or clover but I can't evolve anything with clover can I or is
clover axe evolved garlic heals clover and cross okay what would be better
probably garlic then they I don't guard garlic I feel like would be great because
it will heal and it's like a huge area oh I banished the item for garlic I can't
do it yeah I'm doing ruin tracer I banished it yeah I'll do interest or
anything I have to do armor this axe fuck do I want ruin tracer or axe what's
better for right now I feel like it's axe because it's up and down yeah let's
do axe keep going let me just chill here for a second
there's a chest right there do I have anything maxed out okay I can do I can
get the chest there's the lightning one so this this would be really good here
it's gonna just strike all over the place in this tiny little area the orb
again I gotta keep leveling up axe again I got it I gotta rush at home I will
maybe if you're good great I think I'm alright though I think I'm alright I got
a lot of damage I'll be fine there's a chest down here I think is there I can't
even tell is there a chest down here yeah there is so I can pick this up
because I think the ones ready to go seven just yeah yeah there's that max
labora now let's go up and get the other one bingo all right let's go now just
don't get hit by this shit and get the bracer too oh my I need it where's the
bracer stop bracer I can get it actually probably should start stacking armor
here's the axe okay let's go yeah let's I saw I need armor if I get hit by a few
those I'm done I went by the bracer I I mean I can't see anything what's it
right there all right I got it the other ones way too far down let's go back up
use this all right this is the one I'm not gonna fuck it up there's another
item right here okay go don't fuck it up smart smart plays this chicken right
there if I need it these shrimps just get in I need my laurel that's charged
back up these shrimps keep getting in the shrimps just keep getting in oh am I
gonna last another 10 plus minutes my god dude don't do that these guys are
freezing me dude this guy's a freezing me what is that thing random Mazzo
enables the unlocking and activation of our can't Akana's what happened healing
is doubled recovering HP damages nearby enemies for the same amount healing is
doubled recovering HP damages nearby I don't have any of that I guess I'm I get
it yet I don't think I'm healing that's kind of cool though I'm moving so slow
I'm gonna get blown up I gotta kill those things are they gonna this is bad
I'm moving I gotta kill them otherwise I'm gonna get blown up okay I think
they're gone this is that this is it this is when a huge problem happened
right at like 20 minutes is there anything else on the map no happens soon
all right get ready just walking in a straight line should fix it these fucking
things just respawn I gotta stand still for a minute what hit me I'm gonna hang
out here just move back and forth I think I'm gonna be fine I don't feel so
slow I feel so slow I gotta act like duck hunt move in a pattern don't stop
moving this is where I died before don't stop moving it's not here yet I walked
into that before remember that where is it who cares about the chests it's it
pauses me and gets me out I did it I'm slow as shit right now those magicians
gotta go this health up there though that's good I'll take it you get a
chicken every time you level up potentially that's true but I have to
level up to get it so if I'm almost dead I know where one is right down here
right five minutes I got it what the fuck is that what is going on with that
thing why is it growing in size okay that was terrifying I think the more you
hit them they grow what's going on what was what's that all about why was it the
bottom of the screen just blinking red drives just have to run get kill the
crab I think I did it's a little past your bedtime I'll be all right why move
if I don't need to just money all right this shit coming from all of this okay
be careful three minutes let's go this fucking lion is in the way I'm still
100 that's it 30 nice hyper gallo tower the arcana's
sarabande of healing and I didn't have that I had vanished before didn't I do
look at that thunder loop 2.9 million damage so much that's why lightning is
just so much it's so amazing this game so what am I missing survive 15 minutes
with Giovanna it's you a little pig are those guns survive 10 minutes with
pugnala 20 minutes with at least a 10% curse I haven't done that I tried
pentagram level 7 unlocks Christine interesting there's a ton of characters
all I can do banish more than once I get it level 99 it's you heart of fire what
that is evolve and unite ferrier dear two fellow and ate the sparrow cool all
right really cool yeah this game is amazing you probably see it again maybe
we'll do again on these kind of chill zones where we just kind of hang out and
play just kind of hang out the end of the night maybe okay so here's a plan
let's give you the plan I'm not gonna stream on Sunday which is technically
right now so I'll see you guys on not Monday maybe but hmm I got something
going on on Monday forget what it is keep an eye on the sus because I might
stream on Monday but I think something's going on I have something to do on
Monday I don't know what it is Monday or Tuesdays with an extreme will be I'll
see you then my voice man I really wish I knew it was wrong I have to go back to
the doctor and be like dude what's going on with me I'm gonna have been talking
for eight and a half hours right but I feel like it's kind of been bad the last
week or two it's been really weird that was a fun one that was like four games
that's kind of crazy fix the mic too has it been has it been eight and a half
hours of a terrible microphone yeah yeah I'll see you Monday or Tuesday keep an
eye on the sus and let's go ahead and say goodbye
hmm thanks to a tree off again for the raid last year if any you guys still
here if you are then cool thanks for staying up everybody thanks for the subs
all the bits and everything appreciate it have a great rest of your night have
a great rest of your weekend what is left of it right because today's Sunday
sorry I said you're bad at this game that's all good or I mean I did die to
a very easy thing didn't I risk of rain too I played risk of rain too when it
was in the first week of early access and then didn't touch it for two years
is it better it was fun when I played it it has so much more now I'm not sure
what we're gonna do on Monday or Tuesday I don't know I have a lot of stuff to
play I really I like streams like this though well we kind of just do some
variety just play like a few games just jump around every few hours they're fun
to do let me see what do I got here I got hmm I could play inscription I've
had everyone told me it was amazing and I didn't even play it yeah it's very
very good okay can I handle that game or is it am I too stupid for that game no
you'll be fine it's your vibe it's simple okay it'll be fine all right cool
maybe we'll do that on our money or Tuesday yeah let's walk it in let's do
inscription I'll play it I'll see you guys later thanks for watching good
night goodbye take care of yourselves see you later