Hi guys. How are you? Where's my stuff? What happened to my stuff?
Hold on, why is this over here? I haven't been here in like
like 38 hours, not like six weeks. Why is all my shit moved around?
Hold on. Yeah, that's a little better. Why the fuck is everyone moved around?
I didn't do that. Somebody like snuck in my room and did it.
All right, so hello there. Tonight we're gonna play
Mount and Blade Warband. I have an incredibly highly requested game
that... it took me like a year to get it on the screen.
It was a very, very tough battle between Mount and Blade and
I Spy Children's... Haunted Mansion kids children's game
thing and Desert Buzz. Let me get a sip of that coffee
and I'll be live at about two... I am live. I'll be here in about 15 seconds.
Hold on. Okay, sorry. I have two pieces of music playing in my ear at the same
time and it's jamming me. I have the Mount and Blade Star Wars
music going on and then also this. This is what I'm
playing. Ready? All right, let me get that over here. All
right, let's go. Mount and Blade Warband. I have no idea how
this game plays. I was told it was kind of like Kenshi. You wander the
wasteland or something like that and now you
should be able to see it. It's kind of like Kenshi but with a
thousand people. Oh god. Okay, well this is gonna be interesting.
All right, should I... I gotta play the tutorial, right? I have no idea what's
going on. You approach a field where the locals are
training with weapons you can practice here to improve your combat skills.
Continue... that's... Okay, we're just here. Walk around the training field and speak
with the fighters to practice various actors of Mount and Blade combat.
You can use Asdy... Come on, that's Wasdy, not Asdy.
Move around to talk to a character, approach him until his name appears on
your screen, then press the F key. You can also use the F key to pick up
items. Open doors interact with objects. Press
tab to exit the tutorial at any time. Okay, so
walk and then... Is there a sprint? There's a practice on this guy's head.
A novice fighter. Hello there, we're polishing off our combat skills with a bit
of sparring practice. You look like you could use a bit of training.
Why don't you join us and we can show you a few tricks.
And if you need an explanation of any combat concepts, just ask and I will do
my best to fill you in. Let's attack. Okay, I'm not going to read
any of the stuff up there. No, no, no. I... Why would I do that?
I need to, like, know what to do. Why would I not read it?
All right, there are four principal directions for attacking.
These are overhead swing, right swing, left swing,
chew chew chew, hey hey hey. Now I'll tell you which direction to attack from and
you must try to do the correct attack. Move your mouse while you press the left
mouse button to specify attack direction. Okay, so it's mouse movement and click.
Now for example, to execute an overhead attack, move the mouse up
at the instant you press the left mouse button. The icons on your screen will
help you do the correct action. Okay, so he wants me to do what? Swing to
left. Okay, how many more? Down? Can you move around and do that?
I guess you can. Very good. You've learned how to attack from
any direction you want. If you like, we can try this again and move to a
different exercise. I would like to practice blocking.
Unlike a shield, blocking with a weapon can only stop attacks from coming from
one direction. For example, if you block up, you'll
deflect overhead attacks, but you can still be hit by side swings or thrust
attacks. Bullshit. All right, you must press and
hold down the right mouse button to block.
Okay, I'll now attack you with different types of strokes
and I will wait until you do the correct block before attacking. Try to do the
correct block as soon as you can. This practice is easy to do with the
automatic block direction setting, which is the default.
All right, well I'm not turning that off. If you go to the options menu and change
defend direction, control the mouse movement or keyboard, you'll need to
manually choose block direction. This is much more challenging, but makes
the game much more interesting. This practice can be useful if you use
manual blocking. I don't care. No, I ain't gonna, I ain't
ready for that. So I just gotta parry until you hold?
Hold. Yeah, I'm not doing the direct, I can do the direction shoot with the other
thing. Swinging. Not with blocking.
Does this game suck? I'm curious. No, okay. Good, you're able to block my attack
successfully. You may repeat this practice and try to get faster each time
until you're confident in your defense skills. Do you want to have another go?
No, I think I got it. Detective stream part two.
Well, I guess I'm like, okay, let's take a look at this here. I was just
fucking blue and you know what? I gotta do it.
I have to do it. I have to tell you guys something. I have to tell you a stream
that's coming up. I have to because I need help with that stream and there's
only one way I'm going to be able to do that
and that's with throwing a line out to the community.
I have to do it. So I need, you know what? I'm gonna do, we'll do this in the
discord. Later on in the discord either today or
tomorrow, I'm gonna throw a line out about something to do with robotics.
Okay? If you know about robotics, specifically twitch-controlled robotics,
I may need to ask you a few questions. So, uh,
I'm gonna throw the line out to the community because I've been trying to do
research. I've been trying to figure it out for months
and that's the way we're gonna go with it. Bionic boomer stream.
What? I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna give you the punch line because that's very
important, but it's not the bionic boomer stream.
That's completely different. This is something else, but like I need,
I need some community help on it, I think. I'll throw the line out in the
discord later. All right, let's go. Do I get to create
my character? Uh, what do you want to practice? I want
to practice attacking. Blocking. Let's do some spar. No.
Regular fighter. Okay, I, do I know everything?
Do I need to spar? Non-lethal weapons. All right, let's go.
I'm ready. Okay, killed that guy. We were supposed to do non-lethal attacks.
Okay, uh, next time be more careful. Well, I, okay, but did I hit him right in
the face? That was good, but next time be more
careful. Okay, I'll be more careful.
Why can't I block this? Okay, this guy obviously
is not gonna spar with me. Uh, I'd like to do something else. All right,
what's this? You get to block every time they change
the direction. Okay, riding trainer. Good day, I've come here for some riding
practice, but my old bones are aching badly, so I
decided to give myself a rest today. If you would like to practice your
horsemanship, you can take my horse here. The exercise
would be good for her. Yes, I'd love to practice riding.
Pre-recorded stream talking voice. Uh, good, now I'll give you a few exercises
that will teach you riding and horseback weapon use.
Just take your horse for a ride on the course. Go as slow or as fast as you like.
Come back when you feel confident as a rider, and I'll give you some tougher
exercises. Okay, mount a horse by f. That's practice
horse. Ride, how do you ride? Just w-a-s-d?
I'm sorry, a-s-w-e-d? Whatever, whatever they said. It's very loud.
Uh, I may need to turn this down a little. That's better. Right, so
don't attack anything, just just ride. Is there a faster way to go?
Do what, what kind of weapons do I get in this game? Stick?
Long stick? Short stick? This is like 1,645, right?
All they had is brums back then. They didn't have any real weapons.
They had molotovs? No, they didn't. You finished the exercise, now go back to the
trainer and talk to him. Okay, how do I get off? Oh, thanks.
How do I get off the horse? F, okay. Uh, move on to something more difficult.
Grab the lance you see over there and ride around the course hitting each
target at least once. Okay, grab the lance. Grab the long stick.
See? It's just huge brums. Strike the dummy. How? Just got it. Not really that
good of mounted combat apparently. Is there a certain like hitbox or
something or is it? Okay, there we go. It's a little weird.
It's kind of, I'm gonna run into people like this accidentally.
All right, that's not bad. This game's fucking sick.
I'm just kidding. No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding guys, don't worry.
I'm in the damn tutorial. It is though. I know, I know, I'm just fucking around.
Delivered 29, so this really is like third person Kenshi, just the way that it
looks. It's by the same people, the same one
guy make this game. Your next challenge would be to using a
bone arrow to shoot at the archery targets by the road.
Put in each target to consider yourself successful. Okay.
Go near the practice bone, press F to pick it up. How do I get off the horse?
You didn't give me that information. How do I get off? How do I get off?
Oh, come on, in fucking Red Dead Redemption, you just have to press
triangle. Now do I need to, on horseback, so I gotta ride over there and do it?
So shoot it, how do I shoot it? Just hold it down? Okay.
Is there a way to stabilize? What's like the drop on this?
Press R, first person. Um, where's the, got it.
Uh, I don't want that view. I'd rather be on this view. It's gonna aim way higher
than that. Okay, this is weird. Can I?
Press, you hold shift to zoom in. So you gotta aim higher than that.
Control plus space? Why do you have dummies
in the same place there? I'd rather not go first person.
That hit. What? That didn't hit? How did that not hit?
Okay, can I please, the first time. Horse archery is OP, chat is dumb, level
it up. Well, let me learn how to do it first.
One guy said that, but guess what? Cash in your one guy tokens!
I also made myself a lot louder. Am I like really fucking loud? I should be
really loud. I didn't, I didn't increase the volume in my voice.
All right, able-to-shoot-a-torque-to-the-horseback-I-keep-riding-practice-do-today-and-you-breed-expert-horse-man.
All right, now what the hell do I do? That guy's like dropped into take push-ups.
Uh, you're standing in a really awkward, weird place. No.
Um, did I do it all? Am I tutorial done? I don't see anything else to do. What about
this guy? Archery, okay, hold on. Well, I didn't even know how to do this.
I went to the horseback archery before I did the regular archery.
The bow is a difficult weapon to master, but once you are sufficiently good at it,
you can shoot quickly and with great power.
Shoot the targets. The size of the targeting recticule
indicates your accuracy. Press and hold down the left mouse button until the
recticule shrinks down to its minimum size. Release the left mouse button when
its recticule is at its smallest. If you want it to wait too long,
if you wait too long, the recticule will expand again. All right, okay, I get you.
Hey, whoa, easy. Put the fucking safety on.
Well, so let's take a look at how the drop is then.
That's not hitting it. Am I fucking missing something here?
No, this is going in. So that, okay, I am hitting it.
Do I have to hit this 72 times? Okay, what? Oh!
Well, all right. I'm sorry, but the guy standing here,
there are targets over here, people practicing.
I hit it. Do I have to hit the tip? Oh, that's not going where I want it to.
Not bad, not bad at all. You seem to have grasped the basics of archery. Now try to
do the same thing with a crossbow. Take the crossbow of the bolts over there
and shoot those three targets. The crossbow is much easier to shoot with
compared with the bow, but you need to reload it after each shot.
I think I'm gonna be a crossbow guy. Okay, let's zoom it in.
Ooh, how do you reload? Just like that. This thing's great. I mean, it does take
too long to reload, but... All right, good. You didn't have too much
difficulty using the crossbow either. Next, you'll learn to use throwing weapons.
Pick up the javelins you see over there and try to hit those three targets.
Let's pick up the fucking sausage. Let's get the big cigar.
Let's get the big cartoon bachelor party cigar.
Well, that's weird. Yeah, it takes a little adjusting. Yeah, it's all right.
Well, with that you have received the basic skills to use all three types of
ranged weapons. The rest will come with practice.
Train each and every day and in time you will be as good as the best
marksman in Calradia. Now go talk with the melee
fighters of the hoistmanship trainer. They can teach you important stuff. So I
did it all. It's done good, right? It's a direction
block, direction, archery. All right, so just hit tab.
Start a new game. Oh god, now I gotta do the fucking voice.
I gotta put on a fucking voice now. Welcome adventurer to Mountain Blade
Warband. Before beginning the game you must create
your character. No, this is not that important. Remember then in the
traditional medieval society depicted in the game,
war and politics are usually dominated by male members of the nobility.
That does not, however, mean that you should not choose to play a female
character or one who is not of noble birth.
Male nobles may have a somewhat easier start but women and commoners can
attain all the same goals and in fact may have much more interesting
if more challenging early game. Okay, uh sometimes I just, I want the game
just to be, it said it was gonna be like harder to be like,
you were born years ago in a land far away.
Easy, no, I'll just, everybody quiet down.
Everybody quiet down or I'm gonna put on the YouTuber voice.
Do you want that this whole stream? I'll do it.
You were born years ago in a land far away. Your father
was a noble because that's the easy one. A thief, a hunter, a veteran, warrior.
This is not me though, this is my father. I don't have to be like my father.
A hunter. Um, I don't know. You came into this world a son of a declining nobility
owning only the house in which they lived. However, despite your family's
hardships they afforded you a good education and trained you from childhood
for the
life in court. You started to learn about the world almost as soon as you could
walk and talk. You spent your early life as a page at
the nobleman's court. A street urchin? I'm a, I'm a, I'm a
politician. I get to play the part. As a boy growing out of childhood you
were sent to live in the court of one of the nobles of the land.
There your first lessons were in humility as you waited upon the lords
and ladies of the household. But from their chess games, their
gossip, even the poetry of great deeds and courtly love,
you quickly began to learn about the adult world of conflict and competition.
You also learned from the rough games of the other children
who battered at each other with sticks in imitation of their elder's swords.
Then as a young adult life changed, as it always does,
you became a game poacher, a
university student. I got a real fucking non-like video game life here, don't I?
But you're oh a thief, oh a peasant working my way as a warrior.
I read books. No, that's not a video game start.
No, the distinction felt certain to you. Somewhere along the way you'd become a
man and the whole world seemed to change
around you. You found yourself as a student in the
university of one of the great cities where you studied theology, philosophy
and medicine. But not all your lessons were learned
in the lecture halls. You may or may not have joined in with
your fellows as they roamed the alleys in search of wine, women
and a good fight. However, you certainly were able to observe how a broken jaw
is set. How an angry townsman can be persuaded to
set down his club and accept cash as compensation for the
destruction of his shop. But soon everything changed and you
decided to strike out on your own as an adventurer.
What made you take this decision was personal revenge.
Only you know exactly what caused you to give up your old life and become an
adventurer. Still it was not a difficult choice to
leave with the rage burning brightly in your heart.
You want vengeance. You want justice. What was done to you cannot be undone and
these debts only to be paid in blood. Become an adventurer and ride to your
destiny. All right we got we got the noble houses
of Game of Thrones. House Lannister. House Tyrell. House
Stark. House uh what is it called? The Bears. What
are the Bears called? The Bears. The Bear. The Bears.
Mormons. House Mormons. House Pig. House um Tully. America. House America.
Um House B. House Checkers. House uh Legendary. House
Competition. House Bird. No House uh Targaryen. House
Woodsmans. Oops. How did I just click? I don't know which one I clicked.
Which one? Who did I pick? The three horsemen?
Okay I picked the three horsemen of the apocalypse. We don't need famine. Who
fucking cares? Uh no quitting without saving. Allow me
to quit without saving. Uh realistic. No allow me to fucking
I don't wait aren't these what are these both saying?
No quitting without saving. Allow me to quit
without saving. What is it how is what I mean realistic? So like if I exit the
game because I didn't like how that's just like allow me to save scum right?
Yeah allow me to save scum. I'm not gonna pick the first one are you
kidding me? What the hell would I do that for?
Now enter your name and distribute your attribute. You can scale and weapon
points. You can click on various elements on the
screen to learn how each one will affect your character.
All right I'm not doing I won't do that anymore. All right iron flesh power
strike power throw draw health 44 to 44 experience ball 43 next
level at 600. Oh god I don't know what the fuck I want
to do. I have no idea what any of this means.
Uh cart carton uh cor
cor carton carton like uh carton carton cart
uh strength agility I need to read these.
Every point adds plus one to hit points so this is health
and the following skills cannot be developed beyond one third of strength.
Agility each point gives you five gives five weapon points
and increased movement speed so this is weapon points and movement speed.
This next one is int every point intelligence immediately gives one extra
skill point so this is a skill point so this is for
this and then cha. Cha each point increases your party
limit size by plus one the following skills cannot be developed okay so this
is party limit. Those of you that are just
joining us in for the first time or that have never seen me play a game
like this I have no idea what to do. This is the first time I've ever opened
a mountain blade game ever. That's a lie. I opened this one like a
year and a half ago and like looked at the menu a little
bit. I don't know what to do and this is going to be terrible
because people are going to get so angry with me
because I'm going to put like two points into spotting and everyone's going to be
like why would you put points into spotting that's not
that's the worst thing you could have put it in. All right I'm going to go with
just basic dog shit I think I need some speed I get weapon points I'm putting a
point into agility it's already done okay wait wait right
wait wait wait reset reset reset okay okay I gotta make a choice here
one-handed two-handed polearm archery crossbow
or you throw is a javelin's dart stones I could throw rocks
don't uh why did you tell me I could throw rocks at people don't do that
I don't want to be like the shitty rock guy what have I done did I do that did I
do that wrong I'm throwing rocks at people I'm gonna
throw shit at people okay first aid power throw
each point to this skill increases throwing damage by 10 percent
oh I hate this I need more strength hold on a minute here
the following skills cannot be developed beyond one third of strength
all right right right right right I need like I need like three more points in
here sugary is good what's sugary sugary
like my coffee what are you talking about show
surgery uh all right let's get them uh I don't know is this too overwhelming
to me how about iron flesh well I need to read them just everybody
hold on read these somebody's why can't nobody see this
somebody's give 50 bucks wait wait wait wait wait wait wait why can't this not
it's not showing up oh what the fuck it wasn't for some
reason it wasn't pulling from the uh okay uh that was great canadian uh fuck
club uh great canadian says the war crimes
against swadian peasants don't count as war crimes is that a reference
to this game I don't know what that means uh thank you
for the 50 dollars I don't know I I'm not gonna go I'm not
war crimes who's talking about I'm I'm a fucking politician I'm gonna I'm gonna
have a fight I'm gonna fight for the everybody for
people I'm gonna bring everybody together here
my father was a noble I was a noble and I'm gonna bring the fucking world
together I'm not gonna draw a fucking pint of
blood I might throw a few rocks though but it's all right all right so we got
uh thank you so much though seriously 50
bucks I need to read these all right hold on hit points by plus two
that's all this does it's stupid it's dumb and you should never put a point
into it right guys each point to this skill increases melee damage by eight
percent that's pretty great let's character use
more powerful bows each point this oh it's one of those days I don't know
why I'm in one of these moods so this is like super bow makes it easier
to learn weapon proficiencies increase the proficiency limits limits go to 60
100 140 180 120 260 300 so weapons weapon proficiencies go up
easier I don't know what that means shield produces damage to shields
I don't I'm not going to use a shield I'm just um am I
you're running speed not bad higher difficulty riding skill
oh my god noob just gave 10 community subs thank you so much oh my god noob
I saw that before it even popped up looting the skill increased the amount
of loot obtained by 10% I'm sorry but like I'm that's that looks
good to me every day each hero with the skill adds
some experience to every other member of the party
that's kind of cool tracking tracks become more informative
starting battle advantage for every two points what is battle advantage path
binding party map speed is increased by three
percent what does that mean spotting party seeing
ranges increased by 10 percent what does that even mean
inventory increases inventory capacity by plus six per skill level
how big is my inventory standard party healing speed is increased by 20 percent
per level of the skill surgery each point to the skill gives
a four percent chance that a mortally struck party member will be wounded
rather than killed uh-huh first aid heroes regain five
percent per skill level of hit points lost during mission
I like that one too engineer construct siege equipment and who
no no no I'm not I'm not go with fucking numbers and machines
make other people accept my point of view I don't have enough chah
prisoner management every level of the skill increases maximum number of
prisoners by five nine I'm not I'm a fucking I'm gonna unite everybody
number of troops you can command by five and trade
this is trade penalty I'm gonna go with first aid
you didn't do it right that's too too late adjust your character space using
the buttons and sliders okay beard no beard all right I'm gonna
make David spade uh true Michi thanks for five community subs
thank you so much this is David's bed right here right that's what he does
holy shit oh my god new up another 10 subs community subs
and true Michi five community subs both of you I don't know what that's moving
why is it starting to look like Thanos and I didn't even do anything do I just
love that movie so much that everybody is Thanos
like did I enjoy that character so much that I
every everybody's Thanos another 10 community subs by
visual warlock thank you for the 10 community subs
appreciate it does this really matter no that doesn't look like Thanos
why would I do it if it doesn't look like Thanos great Canadian another 10
community subs from great Canadian fuck club thank you so much guys
10 more no I can't make every character Thanos that's not funny
now it's Bruce Willis no fuck that fuck that I'm changing this not
everybody can be Thanos I'm sorry uh adventure MF Dan thanks for
the five community subs shitload of community subs going on
right now here okay I like this so far I like it actually
completely all right that's good done all right
you hear about Kalradia a land torn between rival kingdoms battling each
other for supremacy a haven for knights and mercenaries
cutthroats and adventurers all willing to risk their lives in pursuit of
fortune power or glory in this land which holds great dangers
and even greater opportunities you believe you may leave your past
behind and start a new life you feel that finally you hold the
key of your destiny in your hands free to choose as you will and that
whatever course you take great adventures will await you
drawn by the stories you hear about Kalradia and its kingdoms you
join a caravan to Praven in the kingdom of Swadia
join a caravan to the Rayvadian in the kingdom of the Veir gears
join a caravan to Toga in the Gurtkhanate take a ship to Sargoth
in the kingdom of the Nords take a ship to Jelkala
in the kingdom of the roads join a caravan to none of this man I don't
know what any of this is I could throw dice in the air in
this one I don't I don't know what any of these people are I don't know what
any of these people are I don't know who what when why how or
when about any of these so I'm just gonna go like this
kingdom but somebody just like I did my like
bias my like hand bias picked this I had hand bias here I think
do a poll I can't even write all this down I'm gonna turn on clicks
because I can't I'm not gonna write all this shit down
just you just click let's say I gotta zoom this way to fucking this
hold on stop stop stop nobody click nobody click stop clicking don't click
anything nobody click all right that's probably good enough
no it's not good enough it's gotta be closer doesn't it no I think we're good
kingdom of the nords it looks like yeah looks like we're going to the nords
that's like that's 10 000 clicks how the fuck could there be 10 000 clicks when
there's only 3.5 billion people on earth you know
I'm saying there's only three there's only like 3.6 billion people here
I gotta be 10 billion clicks all right it's nords let's go
that's an old meme jerma kingdom of the nords whatever that means I just look
over the chat and I see oh my god he's gonna get wrecked he's gonna get wrecked
you took passage with a trading longship carrying
grifalcons from the furthest reaches of the north to be bartered for
linen and wool the best part about making an RPG is you can just make up
words you can make it but it doesn't matter
what the fucking word is it can mean anything
okay and it sailed early in the season but the master reckoned
at the risk of drifting ice and later winter storms could be justified by
arriving ahead of the sea raiders who by april would be sailing forth from
their island layers to ravage calradia's coasts
it was some relief when your ship came inside of the delta
of the vill and bollock rivers and a short while later road past tidal flats
and coastal marshes to the city of sargoth
home to the sea raiders distant kinsmen the nordic lords
who a few generations ago had carved themselves a kingdom in this rich but
troubled land okay you were exhausted by the time you
find the inn in sargoth and fall asleep quickly however you
awake before dawn and are eager to explore your surroundings
you venture out onto the streets which are still
deserted all of a sudden you hear a sound that stands the hairs of your neck
on end the rasp of a blade sliding from its scabbard
what is this guy oh the sound of a blade oh god
reload it reload it how do i what how do i change weapon do i have
another weapon it's this one person i can't reload
i got to punch him what what where am i how do i get out of here
give me the fucking bow he can kick okay seriously though like i need to
i need to why do i not have a weapon scroll up what the tutorial didn't
tell me scroll up oh god who's this who's this i did the
whole tutorial not once did they say by the way make sure you scroll up
is to get your melee weapon and scroll down is for your shield
who the fuck are you are you all right well i guess you're alive at any rate
i'm not sure that we can say the same for the other fellow that's one less
thief to trouble our streets at night although heaven knows he won't be the
last anyway maybe you can help me with
something let's talk more inside out here we
don't know who's listening uh the merchant takes you to his house
once inside he stands by the door for a while checking the street and then
finally convinced you've not been followed comes near you to speed
it's a lie he's coming to kill me so can i reload this
oops i can't take my bolts back sorry i was just testing that
all right what do we need uh now let me explain my proposition
we've always had brigands in the hills driven to banditry by war debt or love
of violence recently however they've been getting
bolder leaving their camps in the wild and
venturing into town looking for unwary prey the
the watch commander tells us it's because of all the fighting on the
frontiers fewer men to keep an eye on the streets
but i'm not sure what to make of that it seems to me that the most logical
explanation is that these bandits have an ally inside the walls
who helps them enter unnoticed and helps them identify particularly tempting
targets last week you see they took my brother i
don't know what my brother was thinking a lad from a prominent house this is
just a bad uh this is a bad audiobook this is like
they outsourced the audiobook to like fiber is what i'm doing right
now seriously i don't know what my brother was
thinking a lad from a prominent house out alone
after dark in times like these well i suppose you were too but you're
a stranger here and didn't know how bad things have
become he had no such excuse but he's family
so what can you do if you don't protect your kin then people will start
thinking that you can't protect your investments either
and i can't have that no doubt the gang will soon send word about a ransom
but i don't care to pay it do a nord voice i don't know what that means
what do you mean a nord voice so here's my proposition now that i can only do
irish so here's my proposition you look like
you've had a bit of experience with the blade
and more importantly you must have a bit of fire in your belly
or you wouldn't be coming to calradia to seek your fortune
so here's what i'm asking you to do gather a small party
track down these bandits to their lair teach them a lesson they won't forget
and get my brother back safe in return you'll earn my lasting gratitude
in a bit of silver what do you say you fucking nailed it you won't be able to
do this by yourself though if you try and take on the whole gang of
single-handedly the hunter will become the hunted and i'll warrant
you'll first want to round up a group of volunteers there's always a few lads in
the villages around here looking for a bit of work that's
more interesting than tilling the soil or hauling water they'll follow you if you
pay so take this purse of a hundred denars
consider it an advance on your reward go around to the villages and use the
money to hire some help i'll reckon that you need at least five
men to take on these bandits five men very good sir i'll go collect some
men from the other villages good you can find me in the tavern here
in sargoth after you've got your group together then we'll
speak about what we do next you have taken your first quest you may
view your quest log by pressing q at any time during the game that was me
what the hell is this how do i get out of here camp get out why am i like a
piece on a board why am i like in the legend of zelda overworld map
oh fuck no no no wait wait go back over here go back in here
playing might and magic go hold on from the prosperous town of sargoth is
bustling with activity the people look well fed and relatively content
craftsmen do a thriving business and some migrants appear to be coming here
from other regions to seek their luck you see the banner of king ragnar
of kingdom of nords over the town gates the populace
isn't different to you i go to the tavern right
i gotta find some friends right that was the quest
collect five men merchant of sargoth wants you to collect at least five men
from nearby villages after you collect these men fine and
speak with him he is in the tavern of sargoth so nearby villages
that doesn't mean here so i do have to go to the map but first let me just swing
my sword into this guy's neck wait what well i didn't well i'm not
sure some kind of um excuse me what uh what i didn't do anything
what did i do i didn't do anything
i'm gonna put my fucking sword in this guy's neck i'm sorry what happened
i'm sorry i'll leave okay i need to get out of here do i have any health packs
okay character fish plus four to morale the the deray military i'm gonna
fucking die i need to find a village around the town
okay so here's sargoth here's kieran castle and here's
quinn should we go to quinn finada let's go to let's go to quinn i gotta
recruit people who's that why is the guy naked this is a robbery
eh no no no no no it's a robbery i've given you one chance to hand over
everything you got or me and my mates will kill you understand
i'm afraid you've you've lost fight me if you dare
you've encountered looters you have one troop fit for battle against their 12
12 where uh do they exist where are they 12 oh fuck i have to have to
there he is get that son of a bitch that was so inaccurate give me my sword
give me my sword i'm taking about one by one
let's get back here telly ho this is fucking ridiculous i need to get like a
hell of a people okay hold on i can't do this how do i get out of here
you've retreated from the fight oh it's that easy
you've encountered looters you i thought i just ran away
get off the horse fuck they didn't go anywhere got him
all right can i just fucking ram him like a bowling ball
oh no i didn't get a strike um i supposed to leave the town to get
people i hit that guy right in the fucking head
i killed him holy shit that guy's dead let's do that 11 more times
the guy's throwing rocks i gotta learn how to be one of those guys
oh fuck you use my shield done just gotta do that
10 more times my health i'll be all right this guy in the corner here
got him i just got hit in the head got you they're not so tough it's a bunch
of shitties got him this is so stupid
one by one they charge at me and one by one they fall
okay well the guy made out of fucking cement i hit him right in the knee
the guy has like fucking cement feet all right i need a better
one mistake and you're dead i'm not gonna make one
imagine looking out the window of the castle and seeing this shit
wow this is fucking dumb what do we do just leave them
use your crossbow from the horse re it was so inaccurate i can't even aim this
thing like see i'm just gonna waste arrows
the arrows regenerate that guy thinks he's gonna get away
and what i said in the beginning no fucking mercy
okay we're fine in the shoulder everyone thought i was gonna lose
watch out gotta make this one count where's my
i win now what now what do i do you won okay wait i gotta hunt no no no no no
no i don't want to i bolts pick those up i what i mean i
can't take that why can't i take the bolts i can't take
bolts i have zero bolts now oh oh god all right okay i thought i had to go
around and pick up stuff like el diablo de diablo de odio de las muertos
you know what i mean that's what i thought i had to do
stone is nice i'll take them is it right click i thought this was
gonna be like el dio de diablo de los muertos too
but apparently not is there like a take everything button
it's an old joke shift click not shift click control click
how much do these weigh try not pick these all up
this is too much weight oh fuck i have no more room
so this shit down here sucks 25 sell price
okay so we're gonna sell price 17 these things suck
sell price 105 okay so then what do i what do i have that's a piece of shit
sell price 11 so so price 11 i need the rock because
i'm gonna i'm telling you i'm rocking these ones are fucking terrible
okay looks pretty good put on the outfit wait just wait wait wait wait wait do i
have any boots woollen hose weight plus three to leg
armor plus four to leg armor these things suck
plus seven to body armor plus two to leg armor plus 21 to body armor
24 22 21 21 21 24 24 okay put on the rocks
i will do time this is uh swing rating 20
b weapon reach 70 no this thing's better
directly can i put the rocks on no i can't all right good
fuck the shield i can't read the book that's not how you read
four thousand no gloves this game's fucking fun
now how do i get routed enemies traveling to sargoth this
so they're leaving read the book requires nine intelligence to read
i can't read this i don't have nine intelligence do i
save the game okay let's go here what the fuck was that
i will drink from your skull i'm not afraid of you i will fight
you've encountered a sea raiders you have zero troops who are battling against
their five why do i have to why can't fight your
enemies take you prisoner what i couldn't fight where are we
going what wait hold on why am i not allowed to
fight after painful days of being dragged about as a prisoner you find a
chance to escape from your captors this is so far away i know i knew that you
didn't know i knew you could go over the bridge and now
i got over the bridge the village of quinn seems to be flourishing the fields
and orchids are humming with activity with
filled sacks of grain and dying meat testifying to the productivity of the
villages cropland and pasture land you remember that this village and the
surrounding lands belong to harold harold of kingdom of nords
in different recruit volunteers go to the village center buy supplies and
take a hostile action why would i do that recruit volunteers four nord
recruits volunteer to follow you for 40 dinars
that's fine well it's not that expensive so i got four
okay go go to the village center i need to buy shit
where are my friends can i fucking run people over accidentally
good day sir what can you tell me about the village how is life here what is your
trade what is the latest room what's your trade
i tend cattle we dry and soak to preserve it
and send the hides to towns to be made into leather we also make cheese from the
milk what can you tell me about this village
this is the village of quinn sir our village and the surrounding lands
belong to jar of harold of kingdom of nords
we mostly produce pork chicken beef grain grapes dried meat smoked fish
hides and flax bundle here if you'd like to learn more you can
speak with our village elder he's nearby right over there
by the way sir why the fuck are you looking at a wall i'm sorry i'm sorry
excuse me this is the trade screen hold down control key while clicking on item
to quickly purchase or sell it i got like mushrooms and shit over here
meat i know it's meat and i know that's broccoli give me a fucking break all
right uh these suck uh do they have money
they don't have any money they don't have single cent why would i do this
trade with the peasants you mean give to the peasants is what you meant to say
buy food dried meat plus five but i need i gotta get rid of some of these t-shirts
you know speaking of t-shirts if i were to wear a shirt
it wouldn't be one of these it would be an officially licensed germany 85
outerwear the night sky and glue man has returned
check it out at the teespring store only on the teespring store
giving them shirts decreases meat price what
buying price is 85 85 that's a lie lie lie lie lie
buying dried meat i'm gonna buy the dried meat
and this is beef tuna and flax get the fucking beef 50 out of 50
i'm gonna need it right smoked fish i'm gonna have a lot of food
okay like how much i paid 228 tenders hope somebody tell how do i phonetically
pronounce this game food can spoil well then take it back
take one of the fish back take the beef back too smoked fish and
dried meat spell it out phonetically denar fish
well i'll take the fish smoked fish doesn't spoil you idiot
listen i i just bought a bunch of food and everybody tell me
nobody said it they just said you guys just said food spoils
not everything but fish just i don't know what this game
classifies as being spoiled yes i know you can have smoked fish in your fucking
closet for like 30 years and you can still eat it
but it's a video game and you guys just said it all spoils what am i supposed to
say what am i supposed to think i'm gonna keep the rocks i have meat
now all right leave so i gotta prove how many
people can i give my characters stuff
where do these guys get stuff oh i've got fucking points to put in
why haven't you played this game before you idiot i haven't read the book yet
i haven't seen the movie yet don't tell me how the movie ends i need
strength for intelligence now we can read the book
50 dollars 50 dollars just came in no seriously 50 dollars did just come in
atrox atrox thanks for the 50 bucks jerma missed my last 50 oh my fucking
god how did i do that oh it's because the fucking goddamn
machinery on that twitch tv connecting to stream labs
uh atrox gave a hundred dollars thank you for the hundred dollars atrox
uh and they said i drew this before you enabled
monka s i don't have i don't think i have monkey s enabled
and that is a broken link that link doesn't work i'm sorry the link doesn't
work but thank you uh and you said you're
coming in here to drop funding for jerma rumble live 2
thanks for keeping me entertained throughout the week so here's some
artwork is this link that way oh that link works
look at that look at that fucking artwork that's good shit everybody loves
shito shito emote is incoming by the way but
thanks for the artwork wonderful and thanks for the hundred
fucking bucks it's a lot of money thank you so much
funding for jerma rumble live 2 which will be live on twitch at some point
in the course of my online career i promise you it'll happen at some
point it will happen guaranteed anybody know
anything about robotics what were we doing throwing okay
power throw i can't okay right i need to get this at least higher
than crossbows and now i'm gonna do
somebody said do leadership idiot stupid dumb idiot and i was like whoa
geez man slow down and then surgery four percent chance that a
mortally wounded struck member will be a wood rather than killed party skill
yeah we'll do that okay so i got five people
now let's read the book how the fuck do i read the book
camp camp you set up camp what do you want to do take an action
there we go select a book to retire from i'm done
i you know i killed a few bandits i made four friends that's enough
select a book to read the deray military you start reading deray military after a
few pages you feel you could learn a lot from this book you decide to keep it
close by and read whenever you have time
bullshit now that i mean that's pretty realistic though
instead of reading the book what everybody does that you know i'm gonna
start a song of ice and fire book one a game of thrones yeah i've heard so much
about this series you open up like you read four pages
okay that was cool i'll do it i'll you know i'll read that probably tomorrow
night before i go to bed and the book goes on yourself for like six
months and then anybody that ever asks you oh hey dude i heard you were reading
game of thrones yeah dude it's fucking crazy it's really really good you know
i'm smart i read it's a great book so far i'm like it's
really long so i'm taking me a while to get through but
gosh man is it cool i like that you know i really like how it started
i was a big fan of how it started you start reading after a few pages you feel
like you learn a lot keep it close by all right wait here
for some time for what i'm never listening to somebody
in chat ever again literally never again like for the rest of my life
we've encountered a series of five troops battle against their
five i think i can handle this i got rocks
hey you guys go didn't i just get them though what are your troops to attack
without you pull back leaving some soldiers to
cover the retreat so this is just like sacrifice two
people to leave that's such bullshit
as the party member with the highest tactics skill and you devise a plan that
will allow you and your men to escape with your lives
but you'll have to leave one soldier behind
to stop the enemy from giving chase one guy i want to be drawing straws
oh i got the long one thank god oh that's the short one
sorry dan fuck you tell one of your troops to hold the enemy while you
retreat with the rest all right now where the hell are we
going i need five people so we're gonna go
like can i get somebody in the castle or should i go to gel bg party first aid
surgery wound treatment looting nord recruit okay how do i
weekly wage is two dollars that's horrible
classic how do i equip these people do i not
party skills you do not you don't equip them okay
okay let's have a discussion your orders sir
tell me about yourself all right sir let me tell you all there is to know about
me okay 50 50 50 50 50 this is kind of cool
okay what if you have like 5000 people he's stronger than me
don't ever say that in my ranks all right we're gonna go to
i'm gonna save the game and then we're gonna go to
gel veggie let's go watch it watch it watch it looters
you just have to avoid people sea raider 11
okay the village of gel beggy seems to be flourishing the fields and orchids
are humming with activity we already read this
okay recruit volunteers five nord recruits
are volunteer to follow you sure take them all now i got nine
what we got for supplies here oh grapes cabbage
and wool do you have money none of you motherfuckers have any money
dried meat fish oh yeah i only eat one smoked fish
go i have to go to towns to sell i wish i sold the horse here have this
rusty sword that doesn't matter i'm a fucking rock thrower anyways
all right i got the troops i needed right collect five men
collect at least five men from nearby villages and you collect these men find
and speak with him he is in the tavern at sargoth
i got nine let's fucking go well i went right through the middle there
hostile action no not yet once i have like 200 people on my team
i will burn a town to the ground looters looters looters
they don't seem to give a shit all right here we go
uh enter the arena go to the marketplace let me sell some shit marketplace
you have run into a trap you're attacked by a group of kids
what the fuck are you talking about who is shooting
fucking the rocks suck is this somebody in the window
he's right there all right all right all right hit him right in the fucking head
with a rock fuck you're gonna jesus i have a sword
i'm trying to level up my rocks any proficiency in rock throwing
did i lose how much did i lose what did they take
they didn't take anything they didn't everything
ah this bloke doesn't have anything on him this guy sucks
they took 60 cents at least i leveled up rock throwing
okay can i um go to the marketplace thank you
trade with the arms trader the armor trades with the good trade with the
armor merchant all right i got some shit for you here
those better oh fuck these are better than what i have on
they took the arrows back so is it worth me going to the arms guy and
what do you got here thick gauntlets do you have any way do you have cool
like better rocks because this is just stones
can i throw like quartz at people eventually can i get better rocks
just do it is there only one rock in the game 900 bucks i don't have enough of
that okay i need a hat though how much is
this eight that's it 20 plus four plus nine this is
fucking so cheap for nine armor 12 armor this is 20
okay wait one yeah this one i'll take that five to leg armor plus 14
uh what we got here plus 24 to body armor
yeah should i get uh plus 45 to body armor and plus 10 to leg armor this is
it's too expensive though holy shit 18 000 dollars
20 grand i'm never gonna have that much money
all right that's fine uh what else can i give you
take this battered old shield how's my reading progress zero percent i
didn't even i opened it up and i really didn't do anything okay so
that's uh you've received 18 bucks what about the arms merchant look at
throwing war spear throwing axe perfect okay it's for them
i have power throw three ranged 42 cents swing it's 32 cents to swing this
three thousand four hundred dollars sell the book
sell the book everyone was screaming at me to put get enough intelligence to
read it in the first place i don't have enough money for any of
this i have my rocks and my rusty sword one guy said that no
okay assess the local prices trying to work out the best deals okay
let's go to the uh tavern right as the party member with the highest trade
skill you try to figure out the best goods to trade in
unable to find any trade because it would bring a profit all right head back
we go to tavern there he is right where is he
said meet me at the tavern right he's in the tavern at sargoth
i don't remember what the fuck this guy looks like there he is
splendid you've hired enough men to take on the bandits now travelers
entering sargothel told us there's a small group of robbers working on the
outside of town i suspect that they are from the same
band the one that took my brother hunt them down and defeat them then
make them disclose the location of their lair
i could have done that voice for fucking red dead too
i do consulting work if you fucking wander in rockstar
okay very well i will hunt the bandits why don't you come with us
i mean should i bring them with us so just go hunt the bandits
let's go new quest take and learn where the hostages are held
you got it i need like ale i need something
i'd like to buy every man who comes in here tonight a jar of your best
wine of course my lord i reckon a thousand
dinners would be enough what should i tell the lads
actually uh oops let me just pull them up put my hands in my pockets and
open them up inside out like this and go whoopsie daisy
uh i should leave what about this fine cheese
so outskirts of town throw a few rocks you got it
i do i need local goods merchant right i need like first aid my guys
why is it christmas music playing pig tools tools
no you heal automatically over time all right i'm ready
leave looking for the outskirts the band of robbers
that's them right find if you defeat a group of bandits lurking near sargolf
i think that's them what do you want i've been looking for you
tell me where you keep your prisoners and i'll let you go
ha i spread it only got three better than you man yourself up
no but i brought steel you've encountered a band of robbers you have
nine troops against their four charge the enemy charge
this is cool all right i got rocks i want to run in with my friends
i will use conflicting fire that's not going to work is it
how do i run press f keys for commands follow me no no no no no no no no no no
charge charge charge i think i just get him excellent work man
the battle has been won no casualties uh three looters three killed robber one
wounded total four killed three killed one wounded
oh that's about that swimmer look have you got over four way
no one's trying now you have hit me i'll spare you life but in exchange i want
information either you or your mates kidnap the
brother of a prominent merchant in town tell me where you're hiding him and give
me your word that you'll stop troubling the people of these parts and you can go
free oh did you like that mate now it's a little uh i played it on me flute bless
you sir we've done the lad no harm we've been
keeping him in our eye down there i'm being
i'll describe the area nearby in detail so there's no mistake
and now give me your clothes like in terminator
oh just 24 coat you got any money all right attack the bandit lair
find the bandit lair near ambien and free the brother of the merchant of
sargoth merchant what find the bandit lair near ambien and
free the brother of the merchant of sargoth merchant
okay it's a lair near ambien ambien the village of ambien near sargoth
belongs to jarald to regor of kingdom of nords its property is
rich other pages that think here attack the bandit lair okay so we're
gonna go to the lair around ambien now where the
fuck is that ambien there's ambien kidnappers hideout
oh it's gonna be fun so we're gonna go there let's go
oh six i didn't save it as the party member with the highest
tactic skill one you decide you devise a plan that will
allow you and your men to escape with your lives
this is but this kind of plan okay this is like we're all
idiots and i'm the one guy okay this is like going to recess
and it's like the fourth fifth and sixth graders are outside
and everybody listens to the sixth grader that wants to play like the
nerf football game and he makes up the rules
just because they just happen to be in the sixth grade that's what this is
if you're in the fourth grade sorry you don't get to make the rules you have to
listen to the rules made up by the sixth grader
um i'm the sixth grader in this case so one person has to stay back and die
go on you tell one of your troops to hold the enemy while you
i can't pick who it is morale we're fine all right we're gonna go
to ambient what's this six plus five plus one
one of them pregnant i don't understand five and one's expecting
but how the fuck do i get over here looters i could probably take them
hold on a minute wait i didn't level up click on the party tab
seven plus one ready to be upgraded upgrade to huntsman or footman uh
what's better 20 days nord footman oh all right what about me
can i can i kick myself out of my own gang
all right we got a footman around here i don't want to fucking fight this guy
is there a quick save all right kidnappers hideout
i'm a footman no you're not kidnappers hideout
you approach the hideout the looters don't appear to have
spotted you yet and you could still sneak away unnoticed
the difficult approach to the site down a narrow defile
means that only a handful of troops in your party will be able to join the
attack and they will be unable to bring their horses
if your initial attack fails the looters will easily be able to make their escape
and disperse do you wish to attack the hideout or wait
for another occasion uh they're not what other occasion is
leave no let's get the fuck in there get out of my way all right let's uh
follow me everybody follow me is that oh that's my footman
you can tell because he's wearing like the blue shirt now
can they fall off and like die here i hope not
what are these boats all right where do we go
where's the hideout okay the hideout's over there but wait
there is there supplies over here everybody follow me
and that's just a set piece watch out for the fire
don't go in the fire who's that who's that who's that
who's that get him get him okay good work
follow me follow me follow me follow me follow me follow me fall back no no
don't go in the water what are you fucking lemmings get over here
no no follow me and this is gonna be here comes the fight
yeah use your like fucking dinner plate you made that at a cardboard that shit's
not gonna stop anything just looks cool all right i'm thinking
wrap around here good work all right now everybody spread out
no i mean uh advance spread out oh i got him i got him i got him
but that guy's throwing rocks too get him get him he's gonna cut me
somebody help me hell okay we're good okay uh hold your uh follow me
found the hideout right uh no we didn't we can't go in there
charge where are we charging to where are they going
backspace shows a mini map oh my god that's very helpful
we did it who the fuck are you oh thank you thank you sir for rescuing me from
those fiends did my brother and sargoth put you
onto their track yes i told them that i would find you i
advise you to return to your family as quickly as you can and be careful on
that road with their retreat out cut off the looters fall one by one to
your determined attack their hideout and their ill-gotten gains
is now yours oh rock a lot of nice hats too hold on
fuck was that granite or is that uh cement whatever i gotta sell these uh
falchions all right this is eight to body armor how much space do i have
look at all this shit i have so many like fishing knives
this is just like the showtime knife set by fucking ron papeal these things are
terrible that but hold on but hold on a minute
here that's not to say that the showtime
knife set is not a high quality knife set because it is showtime rotisserie i
mean ron papeal makes some great products
i didn't want to make anyone think that i thought that he didn't diamond rocks
just pick up the most expensive shit yeah
it's pretty much all i can get what did i pick up to like what dumb shit did i
pick up here self right you get fucking rid of this
sell price 12 sell price 12 57 57 57 16 16 16
definitely 75 57 so he did it attack the bandit lair
the quest has been successfully completed talk to the merchant of sargoth
to claim your reward did i level up at all i didn't even
level up from that i don't even like this game i'm
pretending to like it all right let's go with uh 20 days
footman and uh huntsman i'm just kidding i'm kidding this is this game is very
fun i'm kidding my god well i'm not allowed
to have a little fun all right let's go gotta go to sargoth
save this fucking game i thought this game was like a strategy game
i didn't know it was like this i think every screenshot and every
piece of video clip i've ever seen of this game was like this
let's take a click here eight versus your five i win
i didn't know it was this fun jeremy you were just using strategy commands
in game yeah but it's different though in game real time strategy right
rts is what they it's called real time in game strategy why are you going so
slow what's wrong with you hurry up why are
you going so slow hurry the fuck up it's night time
that means you ride slower whoa look at that that guy 51 people in his party i
can't wait to fucking slaughter that guy all right so we're gonna go to the um
market place see if we can get the armor guy to take some of the stuff off of our
hands this is 14 12 12 12 none of this scared of all of it
uh what else we got this is dumb shitty stupid all right that's good
let's go to the arms merchant i got some stuff for you here
why i thought this these said they were selling for like 75
wait maybe i could put one of these on rusty sword
versus rusty chipped is just a regular foul shit okay
98 weapon reads 73 price strength 8 how can you tell what how much damage it
does 24 versus 19 i guess 30 anything has to be better than rusty
sword all right it's like 18 18 18 18 got plenty of food all right let's go
to the tower complete the quest did your brother come in yet
well my brother is home safe i'm not sure what to do with him maybe
pack him off to a university outside calradia
that way if he gets knocked on the head in a street brawl no one can say it's my
fault but that's not your problem here's the
rest of your reward it was well earned thanks man oh the money is most welcome
and i'm glad to have been of service thanks good now are you interested in
making some more yeah what do you got remember how i told
you that the bandits had an ally inside the walls i think i know who that
is the captain of the watch no less some
months ago the captain seeking the amount of profit we merchants were
making from trade across the frontiers decided to borrow some money to sponsor
a caravan unfortunately like many who are new to
commerce he failed to realize that great profit only comes with great risk
so he sank all of his money into the most expensive commodities and of course
his caravan was captured and looted and he lost everything
as a consequence it seems our captain turned to villainy
to recoup his fortune i supposed i'd do the same if the heavens forbid
i ever faced indebtedness and ruination now any watch captain worth his salary
will have a few thieves and robbers on his payroll
to inform on the rest but our captain decides to employ these bandits
wholesale he brings them into the town lets them
do as they will and takes a share of their take
you've heard of poachers turning gamekeepers well
in the most unfortunate land of calradia sometimes gamekeepers will turn poacher
luckily there's are there's still a few brave honest souls in the watch who've
told me how he works now here's my plan i could bring this to
the attention of king rasner lord of the city but that would mean an
inquiry my world against the captains and when
this can be brought to evidence destroyed oh maybe the whole thing will
be forgotten if the enemy comes across the border
again and all i'll get for my trouble is a knife
in the ribs in time of war you see a king's eye
wanders far from his domain and the subjects suffer so i've got
another idea i've got a small group of townsfolk
together some men in my employ and some others who've lost relatives to these
bandits and will storm the captain's home and
bring him in chains before king ragnar hopefully with a few captured bandits to
explain how he fucked it up so much all i need now
is someone to lead my little army into battle and i can't think of anyone
better than you so what do you say yeah how do i know that you're telling
me the truth oh well i suppose it's possible that i
found a dozen bandits who were willing to give their lives to give a passing
stranger a false impression of life and old star star god
oh well i guess you can't really know if my word is good but i reckon you've
learned by now that my money is good and there's another hundred dinners
or maybe a bit more that's waiting for you if you'll do me this little last
favor so what do you say so this could be false too much
no fuck it let's go splendid it's been a long time since i stake so much on a
single throw of the dice and frankly i find it exhilarating
my men are ready to move on your word are you ready i don't want to be treated
like a fucking goddamn craps table where's the option to
fucking spin around i can get him on the neck yes give
them the sign good now strike hard strike fast and the
captain and his henchmen won't know what hit them
may the heavens be with you this guy's crazy
me crazy streamer this is this i'm role playing you leave the tavern
and go out to the streets nervous looking young men are waiting in
every street corner you can say they have daggers and clubs
concealed under their clothes and catch a mixture of fear anticipation
and pride in the quick looks that they throw at you
as you pass by praying that your enemies have not been alarmed by this all to
obvious bunch of plotters you check your weapons for one last time
and prepare yourself for the action ahead okay there it
it's time lads up and at them these are my face what the fuck
this guy's got a bat that guy's a fucking baseball bat
okay it's like a flaming fucking plus two magic sword
now the dogs are barking there's one more guy
looter killed by nord lord lord nord the remaining few men to scatter off to the
town's narrow alleys only to be hunted down one by one by
the angry townsfolk making sure that your victory is complete
and all the wounded have been taken care of you and the merchant head to his
house to review the day's events i don't think germa could be any worse
at this game well here's the thing i i've i put all
my points into throwing rocks at people so if i was using the sword this would
probably go a lot differently but i'm doing the
throwing stuff why because more like 201 guys in chat told me to do it
well done i hear you counted for one or two of the bastards and you're still on
your feet you can't ask for a better outcome of a battle
than that unfortunately about eight of my lads got themselves wounded i should
go look on them i'm not bad at the game i just made
bad decisions yeah it was the first time i've ever played it i'm just like
what you you want me to do like the meta play pick like the best things possible
in the first playthrough first time to play the game
no i want to throw rocks at people i want to throw rocks at people's heads
and that's eventually going to turn the throwing axes and that's eventually
going to turn into javelins and i will be unkillable in about 15
minutes all right i got yeah i killed a couple
of them ah well i'm proud to have done my bit along with the rest
yes yes now a couple of my boys have the watch captain pinned down in a back room
with a knife at his throat i'll need to go drag him before king
ragnar explained what this breach of the peace is all about
you don't need to be part of that though i'll tell you
what if all goes well i'll meet you in the tavern again shortly and i'll let you
know how it all came out if you don't save before this
encounter you're going to be very upset instead see my head on a spike over the
city gate i will assume you know enough to stay out
of town for a while and forget this whole episode ever happened
hopefully we'll meet again so this guy's dead i mean these this guy's gonna die
so he said make sure you save again all right uh let's go to
the marketplace arms merchant all right let me see what i got 728 throwing axes
don't have enough for it yet i should get rid of this war darts
oh i don't have enough for the war darts there are some war darts that hit dart
damage 22 what is the damage damage 11 7 out of 7
3 or 10 are there even shittier darts that's double the damage large bag of
darts no the bargain bin is even lower down
which what's it called throwing knife butchering knife
rusty rusty club scythe war spear bent bolts
it's like the club just put two rocks together
times two damage well i'm gonna get these i can just pick them up right there are
only seven of them yeah but i can get them right
i can pick them up and get them seven per battle okay that's not bad
that's double the damage i told you it's gonna take 15 minutes
everyone was mad that i didn't get like arming sword plus 10 strength
now i've got lawn darts get rid of the rocks
but it's sentimental okay that's fine i do want i want the throwing look at that
damage on that shit it's gonna be good i will never read this book all right
that's all right i got a better throwing weapon now and i have power throw
enter the arena no i'm not ready for the arena
so now uh i i got nothing right just kind of go
the arena is just it's easy oh well let's just do the arena
hold on enter the arena good day friend if you come to watch the tournaments you
came in vain there won't be a tournament here anytime soon
tournaments so they hold the tournaments here yes that's what i just told you
uh you should see this place during one of the tournament fights everyone from
this town and nearby villages comes here the crowd becomes mad with excitement
anyway as i said there won't be an event here soon so there isn't much to see
except as an official duel every now and then and of course
we have melee fights every day totally welcome
the fighters and knights get bored waiting for the next tournament so they
have invented the training melee it's a simple idea fighters jump into
the arena with a weapon there are no rules no teams everyone
beats at each other until there is only one fighter left standing
okay there is actually some of the wealthy townsmen
offer prizes for those fighters who show great skill in the fights
if you can beat three opponents before going down you'll earn
five dollars that doesn't seem worth it you'll get ten dollars for striking
down at least six people 25 if you can defeat 10 and 60 if you
can survive long enough to beat 20 opponents
if you're the last man standing you can get 250 dollars can i join
uh haha you would have been you would have to be out of your mind not to
the melee fights are open to all actually there is one going to be this
can be one right now hop in if you'd like okay i don't i guess
i can't i don't have any reason why all three you're fucking
ow i don't have any help anyways i have like no hp
oh he broke my oh boy no i made some money though didn't i you earned
five dollars for knocking down five people okay
well can i do it again uh there'll be a fight here soon cool i'll do it again
how many does it take i got a different weapon this time come on man what the
hell how many times do i have to fucking
use this i had to hit that guy like four times
this guy's good i'm not gonna do this watch out for the guy with the fucking
sword he's like bounced off that wall guy
what ah i was focusing on that guy now i'll do one more time
i'm learning how to like play he's doing easy mode
auto block well all right you want me to go i'm not going to turn that off
i am i i do understand how it works though you have to aim in the right
direction like i get it learning manuals fun yeah
maybe maybe and eventually here not right now that was easy
proficiency and pull yeah i'm getting proficiency too overhead swing all right
that's five i'm gonna beat 20
nice devil team same guy like i just came back from the future to like
fucking prevent him from winning this competition
again there's so many people left i don't want to get hit by this guy
oh god me and the fucking mountain whatever his name is no this is uh the
other one the dog the hound
fuck by the hound of obviously is gonna beat me
all right i get my ten dollars i need to leave
that's cool you have to sit there and do that to 30 people though
that's cool auto block noob yeah i i just
fucking downloaded the game an hour and a half ago
i was told by the tutorial maybe you shouldn't do this right now lad you
pretty sure you maybe you should do this on a later date
of course i'm new to the game that's what that means that that's that's
supposed to be an insult to me auto block makes it harder
look i'll turn off auto block in like an hour
so now what the hell am i supposed to do now need to go find stuff to do
i want to buy a new weapon i was already here i already got a new weapon
all right um let's go to the tavern because they was like oh what's there to
do around here right you heard of anyone in the realm who
might have a job for me king ragnar is always looking for
mercenaries to fight in the wars let me think jarl sirdin has been asking
around for someone who might want work i'd watch yourself with him though you
may want to speak with him let me think other work lords and guild
masters often have other tasks which we don't hear about
the villages around here frequently need help all right i'll keep my ears open
all right so we got there's what was that guy's name
just look at all these people's names that there's like a hundred jarls what
was that guy's name you got like a fucking bunch of them
it's a title i thought it was like john iria john herald john heda john gundor
yarl all right what was this guy's name again king
jarl sirdin thank you i've heard enough where are you
jarl let's let's go find this guy jarl sirdin is a
vassal of king ragnar of kingdom of nords he is the lord of bullen boilin
builin so we're gonna go to builin where's builin view the village of builin
near chalbeck castle belongs to jarl and he's
rich okay chalbeck castle belongs to okay so
we got a village it's good builin we're going to find builin it's
near chalbeck castle that's far fucking away so i can go here
all right that's that's this one option is to go kind of from the
what like cape cod in massachusetts what are the other
scenarios there this is a virgin again ah carton things didn't go quite so well
as i'd hope king ragnar couldn't quite find it and
overlooked my little breach of the peace oh he's grateful enough that i got rid
of his crooked captain a guard who led in bandits will
let an enemy army if the price is right but he can't
exactly have me running around here as a lasting reminder of his failure to take
care of things that's not fair uh feral this is calradia my
boy kings do what they will and the rest of us do as they must
he didn't string me up and instead gave me time to sell my properties
even put in a word with the other merchants that they best pay me a fair
price too
she knows that's gracious enough as kings go but he's a weak
king as they all are here are weak kings and weak kings must always look to their
authority first and just a second i suppose i'll do the same in his
shoes anyway i wouldn't go rubbing your part in
this affair that's a weird way to say that i wouldn't
go rubbing your part in king ragnar's face i didn't plan on it
but he's taken note of you and decided that you're not worth hanging
and that's something to which i'll raise a glass any day he might even have
work for you further down the road or you can sell
your sword to one of his competitors anyway i hope you've learned a bit
about what it will take to stay alive in this troubled land and i suspect that
the money you've earned won't go to waste good luck
so we can go talk to the king so let me see here we've got characters
what's his name king jarl i don't remember what his fucking name is
there it is the ruler of the kingdom of nords
he is the lord of sargoth the last time you saw him king ragnar was at sargoth
the report is current so the king is here so i can either look for the king
here find the king do king's bidding or
go find jarl see what jarl has to say i mean he's here
so let's just find him castle uh your castle looks like a shitty
tavern we are not supposed to talk while on
guard sir okay found you found you
do i know you my name is carton at your service sir
i am king ragnar the ruler of kingdom of nords
and the lord of sargoth i see that you carry a nobleman's banner
although i do not recognize the device know that i am always looking for good
men to fight for me once they prove themselves to be
worthy of my trust my lord i've come to offer you my sword in
vassalage you've yet to show yourself a competent commander
carton take your sword to my enemies and prove to me that you are worthy of
becoming my vessel then we may speak more of this now do
you have any tasks for me i need to send a letter to jarl
a din who should be currently at tier if you will be heading toward there would
you deliver it to him a letter needs to be in his hands in
30 days certainly i intend to pass by tier and it
would be in no trouble tier absolutely i appreciate it carton
here's the letter and a small sum to cover your travel expenses
give my regards to jarl aiden when you see you
okay so let's take a look at the map see what that is let's uh
you're just an errand boy no i'm not all right we're gonna go to tier
tier got a letter i gotta deliver to jarl of tier
and i'm here that's pretty easy errand boy you're an errand boy i'm not an
errand boy what you can't be the king of the castle
i have to deliver letters first so let's head out i need to go here just
make sure yet yeah it was believed to be at tier when
you were given this quest you have 30 days to finish it
let's go if anyone wants to fuck with me and you got me and my fucking boys
and i mean i don't think anyone's gonna fuck with me
you and your male crew oh look at that by order of king gravid count lara queen
of the kingdom of rodas has been indicted for treason
the lord has been stripped of all his properties and he's not driven like
he's rumored i didn't what did it say count lora queen of the kingdom of
rodox has been indicted for treason the lord has been stripped of all his
properties and has fled for his life he's rumored to have gone into exile
with the kingdom of swadia okay oh but i've got to deliver this
message village farmers take all of they have and put it in
my bag no no no no deliver deliver deliver deliver
okay uh go to the castle visit the tavern let's go let's deliver the note
all right i'm looking for jarle of tear lady jarle
uh i say you don't look familiar i am carton
carton i do not believe i've heard of you before
can i help you with anything i need to know the location of something
very well i may or may not have an answer for you about whom do you wish to
hear uh jarle one of the jarles one of the
many jarles that you you know a lot of people
you have too many friends it was eric no it wasn't jarle eric you know one of
my good friends is uh jarle eric you know eric jarle
he's such a fucking nice guy he's such a nice dude
oh that one john aiden is traveling to tear and he should be close to tear at
the moment i must beg of you i have to leave
uh so you're on the way here stop saying jarle wrong
phonetically pronounce it in the chat and we'll see there he is
yarrow yarrow yarrow it's ear all yearl yearl all right i'm gonna
i'm seeing a lot of different pronunciations okay so i'm gonna you tell
me with button presses which one's correct one
yarrow two yearl three yearl so it's one okay i got it
there he is no it's not him where the fuck is yarrow
he's supposed to be here did i cut did i was i way too ambitious with
trying to impress the king that i got here way too early wait here
there he is that was him right oh that's gotta be him right here is that him
which one of these is him now he had 68 people he left
uh is there can i like stop this i thought i thought i said wait
uh i thought i i didn't know i thought it was gonna pop up after like a day or
something i didn't know it kept going i thought it was like a scenario where
like oh wait oh you've waited for like a day and now let's go
i didn't know i could click there he is he's right there everybody
relaxed i got a letter for you i don't recognize the device on your
banner no doubt another foreigner come to our lands if we if we didn't have so
many here already now there's something which i would like
to discuss with you in private you'll have to speak to me at some other
time then i have a letter for you no i don't there's a guy look there's a
guy that has the same name as you but he has a d in his
name instead it's the wrong guy it's this guy jarl
aiden how many jarls do you how many yarls do you have in this town
he's in the field and he should be close to is mirala castle at the moment
where the fuck is that where did he go is mirala castle oh my god he's all
that's not that far all right if i go there and he leaves i'm gonna be fucking
mad all right let's go is mirala castle head
out i'm so fucking far away no just stay a
tear he's gonna come back who the fuck are these people can i
like joe how do i join that should i what do i do i'm gonna stay with these
guys they're going the same place are they
fighting who's fighting oh you come across battle
between jarl eric's party and looters move in and help
this party you're helping the jarl party against the looters you have 64 troops
holy shit all right hey where's my men my men my men my men
just don't get yourself hurt we're just here for mortal support
how did you let this guy get by everybody did that guy seriously get
through there's 60 fucking five of us battle one
do i get stuff for this good to see you here carton
ha we showed those bastards a thing to tear that didn't we
rock nice they're like going in a completely opposite direction i'm going
back to tear i just i'm going back to tear i'm not
doing this shit he's gonna walk by me it's gonna take me like
fucking three years to get over there where is he go and find him
i'm not gonna go find the guy hello i need to where is
aiden he's traveling to tear and should be close to
ferrichin at the moment where's ferrichin
he's coming here i'm standing i'm standing in the fucking doorway
you got food i was i'm not gonna just go
trek into the snow with like six people that guy's falling asleep
all right let's go find some more uh recruits uh visit the tavern
let's visit the tavern i want recruits recruit
hello if i look at you i'd say you're expecting to get into some fights in the
near future are you by any chance looking for some help
mm-hmm uh well sir as long as i can remember i've had a weakness for pretty
things and it's gotten me into trouble you see
i grew up in mallier castle as a bonded servant working alongside my mother in
the kitchens i would just amuse myself by hunting mice
through the pantries and sculleries i was so gutted that i put the castle cats
out of a job and eventually the lord realized that i might also be employed to
track down figure game on certain errands of a type perhaps better
left unsaid uh needless to say i found a number of opportunities to avail myself
of trinkets that formerly belonged to my lord's
enemies buy myself out of bondage and find a
hire as a free agent my job was here unfortunately my last employer's wife had
a lovely amulet of a kind i simply could not resist
she doesn't know it's missing yet but she might sue and so tell me are you
looking for helpers this person is gonna steal shit from me
what can you do i may not know how to read and write but i know the quickest
way to a man's heart is between his fourth and fifth
rib if you understand me i'm looking i'm like
looking down here one two three four five what's in my ribs
stomach stomach i can throw you and me are gonna be real close friends
i can throw i can stab and i'm slippery you'll find me useful in a fight that's
good so how about paying me a little something
to seal off our agreement a mere 200 would be enough
please don't take this the wrong way but i've had some bad luck with employers
you go fuck yourself you're not getting 200 dollars
me and five of my mates are looking for a master will join you for 15.96
two two four six eight ten fuck that she's there you guys are more expensive
what about you you do well to know me i travel a lot across colorado
and keep an open ear i can provide you information that you might find useful
um what can you tell me about this land divide into rival kingdoms which can
neither manage to live in peace with their neighbors nor completely eliminate
them as a result there's seldom a break to
the bitter wars which plague this land and drain its life blood
this must be a good place to be for an adventure such as yourself
with some luck and skill you can make slow the fuck down
you're going way too fast why does everyone want to go so fast
those kind of speeds scare me that's a that's scary speed
you go over like 45 and i start to get nervous
um what were we doing opportunities are endless and so are the rewards if you're
willing to risk your life for them tell me about these opportunities the
kingdoms will pay good money for missionaries if they are engaged in a
war if you've done a bit of fighting speaking
with one of their lords will probably result in being offered a mercenary
contract the real rewards however come if you can
manage to become a vessel to a king a vessel can own villages castles
and towns and get rich with the taxes and revenues of these estates
okay a king will not hesitate in time of war to accept someone who's
distinguished himself on the battlefield as a vessel
and grant him the right to own land not unheard of for adventures to renounce
allegiance to a calradian king altogether declare themselves kings and
claim land in their own name just like the video game
board game risk this is a difficult path however as the great nobles of the land
with their long long arms are not likely to accept such upstarts
as their monarch okay uh it might be easier for an
adventurer like yourself to pledge support to an existing king's rival
there may there are many such pretenders in calradia
those who are born to the right family who go around and stir up trouble
those claim holders could find supporters they could easily start civil
wars and perhaps even replace the king give me a name a claim holder's life
would be in danger in his own country of course therefore they usually start
they had rival courts i usually hear news about some of them
and may be able to tell you their location with some precision but of
course i would ask for a little something um i want to know the location
of a claimant i want to know uh lady is sola of suno
don't read everything just play the game now how am i supposed to play the game
if i can't i don't read everything let's be lost don't i need to know how
this works isn't isn't like reading like 50 percent
of how you figure out what to do in the game
all right nah never mind farewell that's super late game all right
where's the guy that i'm waiting for i have to fucking deliver the mailman
doesn't wait you put it in the mailbox where the hell is this guy he's close
to fair etchen what is that no no no okay
he's very he's coming did he get in was that him that little bug that went
across the screen no nothing happened okay nothing happened
oh god okay wait why he's in the field he's close to
his marilla castle you told me he was coming here
i gotta go find him his marilla castle uh he's over here okay he's going from
like here to here oh my god i'm fucking fine this guy
just go find him that i'm that's what i'm gonna have to do wait watch out
who's this who's that garrick garth's party
okay jarl garth is not who i'm looking for
carry on bunch of bandits who the hell are these people
no not the right person not the right person
that's eric wait there's true rigor no wait no do
control space well don't i want to i'm like looking for the guy right isn't
fast travel gonna dump me over there i'm like i'm looking for him all right
he's he's apparently in here no there he is again recruit more people
there he is found you found you you fucking asshole
come here i have i have found you my name is carton at your service
i'm jarl aiden a vessel of kingdom of nords and the lord of tier
i see that you carry a nobleman's banner but i do not recognize the device no
matter a brave man's home is all the world
or so they say what is it i bring a message from king ragnar
oh let me see that well well well it was good of you to bring this to me carton
take my seal as proof that i've received it and give my regards to king ragnar
when you see him again what a waste of fucking time do you
have anything for me to do no carton i do not need your help i
hate to deliver you my demands okay well then in that case fuck you and
empty your pockets no i'm a loser right now i'm a loser i
can't do that i gotta ask you a question what are you
and your men doing what is the realm doing how goes the world
what would it take to cement a lasting alliance with your house
all right where's the king traveling to sargoth he should be close to telrog
castle okay see you later now i'm going to control
space right control space click how do i fast travel
control space hold it hold it hold it control space hold it hold it
okay guys click first click first control space
holy shit that's too fast i'm never doing that ever again
all right i did your fucking dirty work now give me a place your council
you got this like dusty what about me we meet again my lord i've come to offer
you my sword i wish to ask you something you've yet to show yourself as a
competent commander i just i already did it i have something
we could i have something you could help with an
issue with the lawless villain known as al barred hothead
he murdered one of my men and has been on the run from his judgment ever since
i can't let him get away with avoiding justice so i put a bounty of three
hundred dollars on his head friends of the murdered man reckon that this
assassin may have taken refuge with his kinsmen at the age age
you might be able to hunt him down and give him what he deserves
and claim the bounty for yourself then i will hunt him down and execute the law
excellent carton i will be grateful to you and so will the family of the man he
murdered and of course the bounty oh fuck i forgot
i would be grateful to you and so will the family of the man that he murdered
and of course the bounty on his head would be yours if you can get him
well good hunting to you whatever no this is backhanded the king in the face
uh he's currently believed to be at the age egg
the village of the age egg near telrod castle belongs to yarl farn
it's very poor okay so near telrod castle let's recruit some people here
i'm gonna get at least like 15 to 20 people did you model your character
after yourself yeah it's pretty fucking cool huh good day
how's life what's your trade what's the latest rumor around here
uh trigor almost came to blows another lord lately
because the man made a joke about his nose have a nice life
all right let's go so uh where is that castle
what was it called again faye egg a faye egg how do i say this
faye egg faye egg it's why right telrod castle
click show on map no that is faye egg show on map show on map show on map
all right well i found it everybody fucking relax i need more recruits
though it's burning well it's all right they'll
it's been burnt well it's fine the guy's hiding there
i need more recruits now you know what fuck it i'm going in
need recruits the village has been looted a handful of souls scatter as
you pass through the burnt house uh okay um let's go here
let's get some recruits recruit volunteers
no one here seems to be willing to join your party and fuck off
okay what about what about these places does this mean i can't go over there
yeah is it like oh no you're at a rival place
am i am i getting in trouble for like talking to people here
okay recruit six swadian recruits to volunteer to follow you
hell yeah what do you guys got spices pottery
pork woolcloth and you got no money what about just go just like just snipe
people from all these villages recruit volunteers four of them yeah
okay hold on go up here let's go let's get like 50 people three
okay over here recruit volunteers two okay all right let me see what i got
still level two party 15 recruits okay so i got a lot of people now
let's head there is this thing still on fire things still on fire
let's head to ambient well weekly what wages for carton's party next 300 and
hold on earlier wealth new wealth 38 bucks i have 38 people in my party
okay no that makes that makes sense let's check ambient when does this get
rebuilt i'm gonna have to have like another
mission here then they don't fight for free so i need to do
something else what was that the guy that guy was up here right
billion i'm gonna go up here in the meantime all right where am i
let's go fight some bandits i could do that couldn't i
need bandits around the castle imagine serving under the sky
have a run into sea raiders i have bandits looking for bandits bandits
bandits anywhere well anybody have anything here nobody willing to join
okay go to village center you guys have any
problems what do i have a health bar anybody
need anything good day what can you tell me about the
village this is the village of coulomb sir our village and the surrounding
lands belong to jarrel i'm sorry we produce butter pork chicken
bread grain grapes fruit dried meat cabbages cheese smoked fish
so you get a guild master guild master great canadian fuck lovers get 50
dollars thank you so much for 50 bucks great
canadian fuck love uh they say here germa use this to recruit
more people just not suedeans all they do is eat butter
what do you have any tasks you don't need anything well
and the enemies we've neither heard nor seen anything
jesus but thank you so much great canadian uh guild master
look at the guild master you can't really go that way
wait that was him so they don't need anything done here
this place is just boring okay try to no i can't just like destroy villages
let's go where we're supposed to go if i see bandits i'll take them out
all right get in there crew volunteers i'll take them let me see what else i
had here there was what was his name again i don't
remember his name i know he was here though i have enough food uh i did buy a
lot in the beginning just declare war no i can't do that
i'm i'm enjoying just enjoying the game who are you village elder
welcome to boolean i'm the elder of this village i need you to set a large fire
on the outskirts of uh what is this you know i need you to
make a fire i have my reasons and you'll have yours a
purse of silver will you do it given the risk you are taking you're
entitled to know my plan i wish to rescue a prisoner from chalbeck
castle when you light the fire the guards in chalbeck castle will see the
smoke and some of them will rush outside to
see what's going on who am i rescuing as you say sir but in doing this we are
taking a very great risk what's in it for us
uh never mind do you have anything i can have bandits have driven away our
cattle our pastors are empty if we had just a
few heads of cattle we could start to raise a herd again
how many animals do you need i think eight heads will suffice for a small
herd i will bring you the cattle okay thank
you we'll be praying for you night and day
just go get cattle deliver eight heads of cattle
30 days do it where the fuck am i supposed to find cattle
wait will you take cabbages in uh instead
cattle i need to like wait here don't i you get a lot of experience but no money
terrible quest terrible terrible terrible all right all right all right
all right is this guy available yet i have to go into this castle don't i
it's this one right here right you are outside chalbeck castle you see the
banner of yal gondor of kingdom of nords over the castle gates
takes one in-game week to repair okay approach the gates
you approach the gate the men on the walls watch you closely request
entry to the castle or request a meeting with someone uh
request a meeting who do you want to wait forget it
uh let me get let me in after a brief wait the guards open the gates for you
and allow your party inside you are at chalbeck castle you see the
banner of yarrow gondir of kingdom of nords over the castle gate
take a walk around go to the lord's hall okay there's lady
karyasa i am carton i want to know the location of man at the honor of knowing
more about you i want to remove where's um well where
is he in the field and he should be close to
feinada at the moment can i know more i am wife to yarrow
gondor mother to yarrow garth mother to ladies sweepal may have the
honor of knowing is there anything i can do to win you a favor
no carton i have no need for a champion right now i don't i don't know you well
enough to act on your behalf vessel of king ragnar he's lord of
chalbeck castle he's got a big family last time you heard
about him was in the field and he was close to feinada
report is current cancel the cattle quest how do you cancel
like the cattle quest cancel cancel just it's gonna fail
whatever i'll take that place so he's near
uh go back out here we're walking on the courtyard
just leave i'm trying to remember what was the guy's name that was in
bullion there was a guy that i could talk to right
maybe it was nighttime that was me bandits
it is bulba i gotta get in some fights he's not coming after me what are you
doing i need to like level up fight him i'm not
gonna fight that guy uh count monte war of kingdom has been
taken prisoner by canate was defeated in battle all right
before there were just bandits running after me left and right of sea raiders
blocking all my paths where the hell are they now
right there sea raiders where the my party's too big and everyone's afraid of
me should i get rid of them will somebody
attack me please who the fuck are you farmers no i can't
just kill farmers i can't farm farmers for experience
sea raiders 18 i 33 18 versus 33 i will drink from your skull i'm not
afraid of you i'll fight here comes a fight look at this i got
fucking so many people i'm getting off the horse i'm going in
the battle charge get in there throwing this
all right i got i got one i got one i got one my guy
oh it's dead but so are they everybody thought i was dead there oh he's dead
he's gonna die okay your casualties uh five swedian recruits
were killed or four were killed six nord recruits three were killed three
were wounded so seven died four wounded 17 raiders dead we got some recruits
that need to level up uh footman footman again wow everybody
okay so let's go and then the rest let's get some
bow and arrow you can't i don't have enough money
oh shit i need money it's money oh god damn it oh look at these axes too
490 dollars all right it's time to get rid of some shit
i don't give a shit about rocks or crossbows i don't care anymore
i got plenty of food look at this stuff throwing axes
nordic helmet oh wow nordic sword battle axe long bow
just take all the all everything and sell it all
okay look at all this good put it on yeah i will
throwing axes i'm gonna put these on instead of
rock i got meat this is 22 plus eight pretty good nordic crude nordic helmet
39 39 nordic sword 29 21 i'll take it
battle axe 41 bonus against shields it's two-handed though bent javelins
uh nordic shield battered or okay this one cool
fighting axe this is better okay well i got
let's go sell some shit all right i just had to get in the fight level three
i need agility or intelligence again okay power throws i'll already at three
do prisoner management i mean i don't have any prisoners
let's do this first pole arms archery crossbows
i did like i'm going for it right i can't 64 is the max i can do you
can't have them without the skill okay i see
uh i guess i'll just do that you can sell people oh god
inventory management i like this everyone's gonna call me an idiot but
i want it and i'm gonna put a point into this
cool okay so now let's go sell some stuff right here
might as well those are sea raiders too i took them all without a problem
arms merchant five oh that's why all right i need money so i got 33
plus five this thing's better to sell everything this guy has 829 keep that in
mind 39 36 turn off the easy difficulty
what are you what are you talking about how the fuck do i do that
normal mode where do i what i don't even know what i didn't
make i didn't do any i didn't change any options
uh i probably should get rid of this but yeah i'm not gonna do two-handed
i'm gonna keep the javelins one resistance one
it's zero 13 no more rocks i'm gonna keep the javelins though
just because i could try them so this is gonna be 642 dollars that's
good i'll take it okay so what what are you guys talking
about i just loaded up the game and like started the new game i
didn't like let me put it on easy this is just whatever the default setting
is uh okay hold on uh can't pour pour
average average i don't good i don't know why that didn't change this
uh amco the terrible just gave 50 dollars
thank you amco the temple for 50 bucks big money
and they say ignore chat keep playing the way that you like and have fun with
the normal mode of warband is super hard and frustrating
just starting out just have fun i don't want you to abandon this game
he's what what it's right it's good advice
increase difficulty abandon probably bullshit but
what uh well i can change this at any time so this is if i don't like this i'm
going to put it back down to where it was
on the default i mean turn up the battle size
okay damage to the player wait damage to friends damage to player
so wait why the hell would they have this all on easy
as the default setting then is the game just that difficult
so am i am i gonna now just like lose every fight no
fuck that i don't know what this is on lance control what was it
it's unforgiving lance was manual okay it's unreasonably difficult yeah i
think i don't know if a lot of you guys might not know
that like this is does okay i don't know i have no idea
but i'm getting two sides of a coin here half of you guys are saying that
holy shit do not do what you're doing right now this is a really bad stupid
idea and the other half are going like get
good dark souls put it on heart you know what i mean i'm just gonna do
you know what i'm gonna i'm gonna keep it the way it was here
i'm gonna put these up that's it i'm gonna keep it the way it was
the fun mode is still on i mean look i understand like we have this
conversation sometimes if you have like 4 000 hours in warband
that's great and i'm sure you know everything i'm sure you're very good at
it but i just i just walked in three hours
ago and this is the default like i'm not going to walk into the
okay i just walked into the to the to like the taekwondo or like
or karate seminar and the guys sitting there like okay welcome to the karate
seminar we're going to put you into groups here of like of skill and
time how long you've been here and i like i raised my hand i'm like can i be
in the black belt class no no you can't yes i can get good
sit down you're not ready for that yet you need to go through the citrus belt
first no i don't get good idiot he's gonna kick
the shit out of me that guy's gonna punch me in the face once i'm gonna go
down is that what you want yes like what no i've got to get my like
fucking tapioca belt and go through fucking like well i
can't just go right to black belt anyways let's continue playing the game
after i take a piss because it's been three hours and i haven't gone to the
bathroom one time then that's a lot that's like an eternity
in this stream that just steal the black belt no but
but that is actually like okay to add on to what i just said
i go into the karate the first day of trial okay okay welcome to the karate
seminar i get put into citrus belt i do oh this is
jeremy you definitely don't have what it takes
to be part of the the brown belt or the black belts no no no no you've got to
work your way up i go okay sure so i do two classes in
citrus belt and then when he lost he went okay the
classes are over i break into the fucking karate place
and i scratch my name off citrus and i like write it into black belt and come
in the next day that's what this is like i i i just i
just like put myself on the black belt list under his nose
see you in a minute i'm back that was a nice long piss
hold on i'll beat this all right let's go what's the audio
that was weird marketplace okay i got 11 fish it's not that much money i'll buy
some more smoked fish sure can i just buy a certain amount
uh it's best party morale i have already too much food i think
we have a huge party though little pigs now
now don't buy the butter so i'm gonna eat it all right i'm good that's enough
for food i don't need any more than that riding one
what is my riding now okay so what the hell was i doing
right i had some money 75 bucks a week uh footman footman uh footman
footman okay it's militia this is 10 that's all i can do okay looking good
and i did what was this song easy was it on easy or easiest i think it was on
easy right yeah i put it on easiest for some
reason but it's not okay so are we good are we ready am i
ready to play or is somebody gonna hold a megaphone
up to my ear and scream in it am i gonna get screamed at it would be
very loud who is this internet funny man i'll tell you
i go by jeremy but that germa 985 my real name is jeremy elbertson
i was born and raised in i'm not gonna tell you all that info all right quests
i have to okay vege egg the place is currently burnt to the ground
where is it there it is there it is it's no it's good right
that's not burning anymore it's not it's not currently on fire
let's go who's this wait who are you man hunters
man hunters okay hey you there you seen any outlaws around here
i would get man hunter in your name yes they went this way about an hour ago
i knew it come on lads let's get out of here thank you
you're welcome looted it's not on fire though no no before dark before dark
looted fuck well let's go fight some more people then
what about this place just wait in a nearby castle that's not a bad idea
approach the hell the guard request entry continue
seven dollars a night make camp and read a book oh fuck read the book
so recruit some of your prisoners to your party what prisoners
i have prisoners read this book you decide to keep it close by and read
whenever you have the chance recruit some of your prisoners oh okay
so i've read the book still looted finally he's read one percent of the
book all right well let's go this way i can
come back here later uh village of is mural this is what the
guy kept on going back and forth here four recruits volunteer to follow you
no i don't want any more people take a hostile action
caravan caravan harish i feel like i have to start taking action here
what about rebatch let's buy supplies we're gonna do a date
join a kingdom as a mercenary i mean i'm trying to do
i'm trying to do just this shit for king ragnar but
this place is currently like destroyed and i have to wait like a week
so i kind of need to and then there's a guy up here that i was gonna do
but he's just not there you know i'm just gonna go in here
and just talk to the lord and be like hey i need to talk to you
uh lord's hall who are you and can i do something for you
i am carton uh they're not here why is everybody always at war and fighting why
you never at your house nobody's ever at that house it's called
warband if you got to leave some defense you got to
leave the lord this place is fucking ready yet who's that
deserters they're running from carton who the fuck are you
what do you mean running from me you're running from me
what where'd they go go go go go where'd they go
they're gone it's because i turned nighttime and my horse put like fucking
heavy shoes on wait there they are deserters
get over here come here how could a deserter have a better horse than a
noble lord i don't know he's too fast i'll catch him come on i just
bumped into him really where are they going all right
there's my weekly budget who cares about these guys this places
should no longer be on fire there it is just go hurry up where the
hell am i uh the village of veyagic looks
wretchedly poor and miserable only a handful of people are strong enough to
work in the fields many of which are becoming overgrown with
weeds the rest are weak and malnourished or have already fled elsewhere
okay the bones uh you remember that this village and the surrounding lands
belong to yarl farn the village is infested by 15 forest bandits
let's go oh my god i got a shitload of people here
look at united from all nations i told you i was gonna be uniting people
i got one no did i kill a farmer i think i actually killed the
fuck wait why am i killing farmers wait what hold on a second i'm
killing we're killing farmers why i gotta get my that's it only one more
that's it now is there more everybody charge
i think that's all of it all right we did it
all right 13 killed total allies seven four farmers dead only one wounded on my
team in a battle worthy of a song union men
drive the bandits out of the village making it safe once more
the villagers have little left in the way of wealth after their ordeal
but they offer you all they can find uh i'm going to refuse you need those
items more than i do so go to the village center and we are
looking for albert hothead hunting down albert
hothead i couldn't do it in time all right
villager villager looking okay you know the whereabouts look for a man by the
name of albert hothead strangers come and go to our village sir if
he's hiding here you surely find him if you look around
that looks like hothead right there bounties are difficult
heal first i don't think i have any ways to heal don't have to just
wait albert hothead excuse me where's hothead
okay no you guys are all protecting him drop the act where the fuck is he
okay drop the act over here maybe there he is drop the act
there's the elder you're gonna tell me what i'm fucking looking for
where are you off to he's not over there where the hell is this guy
i need you to do a mission for me you go find albus dumbledore
there he is definitely look he's got a sword nervous man who i wonder who you
are what do you want i'm looking for a
murderer by the name of al bard hothead you fit the description i don't understand
sir i never killed anyone i think you've got the wrong man
then drop your sword if you're innocent you have nothing to fear we'll go now
and talk to your neighbors if they verify your story i'll go on my way
i'm not going anywhere friend you're gonna have to fight for your silver
today you just dialed that up to 100 for no
reason i come not for money but to execute the law
die dog uh so maybe i should just wait and sleep for a little bit uh let's go
ahead and make some camp and uh wait here stay on your horse and
just fuck them up okay can i see my health from any menu
here health 29 and a little bit more of the
circus tent you make peace agreement okay all right let's go
all right so he killed me in one hit last time see if i can find him again
hey nervous man i'm just gonna stay on the horse hey is that you
that's me uh no problem just really i need your head
you're mine where's my where's my fucking
crosshair i'm gonna turn around he has different hair color
just i got an anticlimactic fight all right i'll give you a real fight
yeah no no no no no no no don't equip things you find on the ground
stupid what did i just pick up i'm good right
all right that's it uh talk to the king to claim your reward i'll be in the king's
favor now let's get the hell out of here but first
let's throw a bucket torch over there and see what happens no don't do that go
leave now who's this farmers so king was here
or that last scene here right let's go into the castle where is the king can
you tell me where he is king ragnar close to sargoth at the moment
he's in the field okay not over here hey you are hey hey you
this is an uprising we meet again carton uh about that task you
gave me yes have you made any progress on it
i found albert hart had had an vae gang and gave him his punishment
and we'll be a lot better off without him thank you cartman for removing this
long festering thorn from my side which is good to know you can be trusted
to handle things with an appropriate level of tactfulness
a bounty i promised and i bounty you shall have 300 dreams
and not a copper less let me take the money thank you
due my thanks for ridding me of that base varlet
blessed with king ragnar has increased from two to three
level two you have any tasks i have come to offer you my sword
you've yet to all right what more tasks you probably know that i am the lord of
the town of sargoth however it has been months since sargoth has delivered the
taxes and rents do me as its rightful lord apparently the populace there has
grown unruly lately and i need someone to go there and
remind them of their obligations and to persuade them if they won't listen
if you go there and raise the taxes they owe me i will grant you one fifth of
everything you collect uh okay welcome news card i will entrust
this matter to you remember those townsmen are foxy beasts
they will make every excuse not to pay me my rightful income
do not let them fool you cool collect taxes
collect taxes from sargoth collect taxes how does one collect taxes just walk up
to people and say give me money let's give it a go uh take a walk
around the streets oh they're getting a little unruly
collect uh come on this they just popped up for the okay
you can't give me shit for this because this menu just like popped up it just
bink it's added one it's like three days start the collection
113 113 184 203 203 144 85 39 77
three this is free money the people of sargoth are outraged at your demands and
decried as nothing more than extortion they're getting very restless and they
may react badly if you keep pressing them
oh give me more of that money 21 130 11 169 this i'm gonna be fucking rich
fuck the king fuck sargoth i'm gonna go over to the next
town and be cool with them and then we can go from there
why would i return this money this is free money look at this shit
let's hit the jackpot you've finished reading
wait wait you have finished reading dera military your tactics has increased by
one okay uh guys this is this is outrageous
how much money this is i gotta i have a choice now you've collected
8 000 dinars in taxes from sargoth king ragnar will be expected you to take the
money to him okay uh so um i mean the general consensus
is i'm never coming here ever again like we're gone
but i'm just gonna leave who hates uh king ragnar what's like the direct
rival time to find a different kingdom all right
hold on i need to think about this so the nords
the kingdom of nords is at war with the kingdom of vaguers
the kingdom of vaguers declared war to regain lost territory the fighting has
gone on for some time and the war may end soon with the
truce so we gotta go to the kingdom of vaguers
that's ten thousand dollars come on all right what about um
kante kana kana te we're at war with swadia
no outstanding issues with vaguers what happened to loyalty this is war
where the uh that title of the game is war band
didn't somebody talk shit to me about that earlier it's not
mountain blade do uh be a good boy band i'm gonna go check
this out kingdom of vaguers let's just do it
double cross so that's down here right no where's that
where are what where are they what like part of the world are they in
down here it's snowy down here this is cool
so we're they're at war here let's check it out that was a lot of fun
thanks for the money save in a different slot
is this that big of a deal i want to join
these guys do they have like a capital city can i just bust in the door and be
like i'm ready to be a traitor what's their
capital city hail the guards request entry continue
go to the lord's hall all right lady palecha
don't punch anyone that you want to swindle
okay where's the location of i want to approve my relation with the lord can
you help me all right king king yarrow glick is
traveling to ray vaden and he should be close to sum
buja at the moment so they're going he's going to ray vaden
ray vaden is um but where's the where's he actually gonna end up
over here so he's here and he's going here
let's go party has nothing to eat oh fuck all right
hurry up all right go to the marketplace goods market let's get some food in here
chicken dried meat and some bread and some more uh bread
and cabbages no this is cheap okay and back so let's uh let's go to the
castle see if they're here then nobody seems
to be here is it a free book wow you this this thing
sucks where's your lord no let's go to the town
center where is everybody town's woman uh what can you tell me
about this town a town surrounding lands belong to king yarrow glick of kingdom
of vaguers we mostly produce bread and a bunch of
other stupid shit if you'd like to learn more you can
speak with our guild master he's nearby right over there okay
guild master what you do do you ever have a job i have some questions of
political nature politics good heaven the guild has nothing
to do with politics we're loyal servants of king yarrow glick
we merely govern our own affairs and pass on the townspeople's concern to our
lord what did you want to ask uh what do you
think about politics okay internal bickering in other realms
the lords of a realm often have very different ideas about honor strategy and
the way a nobleman should behave they compete with each other for the
ruler's favor constantly weighing up their position how
they stand how their friends and family stand right
yeah it's about like oh you can sneak in and pull the rug from under somebody
and now you're a lord he believes that this is going to
change sides or rebel he may indict the vessel for treason and seize his
properties all right i got i'm i got nobody
i'm not i don't i'm good all right you got any work
uh one of the merchants here is looking for a herdsman to take his cattle
we already know that's a failure i wish to buy
land in this town for a productive enterprise
uh what do i want to do a couple of things to keep in mind skilled laborers
are always at a premium so i doubt that you will be able to open up more than
one enterprise here in order to make a profit for yourself
you should choose a commodity which is in relatively short supply
but for which the raw materials are cheap uh they do lots of bread
they do a lot of bread hold on never mind
how's the trade we have shortages of wool
smoked fish grapes grain pork and some other commodities
wool so i'm gonna make a i'm gonna make a wool factory
uh i'm just getting i'm getting like a virus update what the fuck are you doing
no i don't why is it taken off my computer give me a break
we have received many traders in town who travel is coming from where chagat
traded here two days ago okay there's little news about the
caravan routes to towns yeah yeah yeah okay so we need
how does the wealth of this region compare the rest of calradia
we are poorer than three towns and richer than 18
okay we produce less than seven towns and produce more than 14
production is of course this is one of those brain teasers
jane has six jelly beans if mark comes over
and takes two jelly beans and then gives them back three weeks later and she
produces 12 jelly beans a day i don't want to do that
looting and pillage and shifts in territory can make a major impact
okay the village is produced less than the hinderlin around eight towns produce
more than 13 the wealth of a town's hinder than of
course is heavily dependent on the tides of war
the town of suno is believed to have received the most visits from caravans
we have visited we are less visited than four towns and more visited than 17
in terms of attacks on travelers the town of dirum is believed to be the most
dangerous here we are less afflicted by bandits
and raiders than 12 towns and more afflicted than nine
i thought that was a middle finger all right i'm gonna buy a productive
enterprise and it's gonna be wool a weavery to make wool
cloth from wool they get a shortage of it a weavery and
dye works to make velvet from silk and dye check how much you make each week on
every option very good so the land of the materials
on which you may build your mill will cost you 1500
300 dollars a week 264 and labeled with 30
would probably be 18 dollars a week now a brewery okay so i guess that would be
probably 122 dollars a week no that's not good for me at the
moment tannery 220 dollars a week okay i think
it's going to be the tannery wine press uh batch will be
40 i guess that your profit will be negative 148 dollars a week well then
uh guild master gary that's not profit that's loss
so um no thanks your profit will be you owe me 150 dollars that there's no
profit an oil press 208 that's not bad
and iron works 42 dollars a week don't think so weavery and dye works
holy shit your profit will be 520 dollars a week
hold on so what about just what just a weavery
minus 50 dollars a week a weavery to make linen from flax
70 dollars no so that was crazy how much is that one okay so a weavery
and a dye works the land of the materials you right so
ten thousand dollars to start it and five hundred dollars a week after that
swindle the new king and then take the money somewhere else
just keep swindling people out of taxes and then
do tax evasion so much well it's not tax evasion that's just stealing money
okay oh right what if i just never come back what was i doing who was i looking
for oh right all right the king so where was
he he was like on the way he's on the way right he was going this way
he was gonna hang out somewhere over here where are you come on
all right only 100 okay that's the week is over are you in here or what
you've run into a trap you're attacked by a group of just me
oh fuck jesus christ man you gotta be kidding me
like what the fuck i don't know when i last saved it either
i have no idea what was the last save point oh let's put let's put
50 points into throwing weapons what a great idea jeremy
and let's put the difficulty up away from the default
with 50 points in throwing weapons where the hell was i here
you lost 300 time to save scum well i i have to save scum now yeah i was
that don't matter i literally just sat there and read the
the book with the sword in the first slot i have to now
and the time it takes me to throw a weapon they get so close and then i take
my sword out and i'm already dead all right looking for this guy food should
be good right now i have to do the find they're
gonna just just find the guy he's not here
uh i asked around it's like oh he's fucking walking around in circles
somewhere over here all right good to know
i'm gonna get ambushed no no imagine eating brain
dog food i'm not gonna buy dog food for my soldiers
where's the king excuse me everybody anybody here i heard the king was walking
around the circle over here somewhere elder can i talk to you please
all right they don't need anything he's set a fire
are there any lads from this village you might want to seek their fortune in the
war no all right can i run into him now where
are you wait where was he what was that him
now that's me i'm just gonna wait here for him
join the feast let's join the feast there's a feast in progress in the
lord's hall but you are not of sufficient status to be invited inside
perhaps increasing your renown when you admittance or you might also try
disguising distinct disguising yourself as a tournament
while the feast is in progress all right let's go to the tournament the door is
locked why is it locked you are at the tier one of
the tournament with 64 participants remaining in the next round there will be
four teams of three fighters each holy shit all right
hundred dollars on me wait the king is in this
you ask one of the criers for the names of the tournament participants what if i
kill the king accidentally all right there he is there's the king
oh i won 1300 dollars didn't i i did you've won this melee but now you
must prepare yourself for the next round you are tier two
like i'm not gonna win this why do they get swords come here
these two dickheads over here in the corner all right let me help you let's
double team this guy we did it that's another thousand
dollars tier three of the tournament was 16
participants next round there'll be two teams of four fighters
let's put another fucking thousand dollars man oh that guy just ate shit
get him back up back up back up back up back up i'm gonna get off the horse
no no just get off oh man i'm gonna make a lot of
money this is the last round of the tournament
you are tier four of the tournament eight people remaining
there will be three teams with one fighter each
kill this guy right off the bat fuck they're gonna fucking double t me of
course they are all right all right all right
no oh it's just uh oh god that like he's he swung once
and then twice and then they fight like they're fucking
possessed like they're trying to fight a demon
being exercised from their bodies how far the fuck away was i
i saved it somewhere i don't even fucking remember i don't where he was he
was he's always was a feast or something
wait day okay too dark out when did you guys
fucking get your asses kicked when did everybody lost everybody died
that was real quick okay what the hell was that
i'm doing this one more time and i'm just gonna light the place on fire
i'm going back to the other king he at least let me be part of the fucking
feast look we get like the horses this time
how is this tournament any how is this fair at all how is this a fair
tournament these guys with the one-handers man like
do you do you have a fucking stamina bar how am i supposed to get a swing in
how is it possible this shit is not possible to hit a guy
that swings every second fucking god i'm gonna go back and just give the
taxes fuck this it's because i had a lance i don't want
a goddamn lance i want my fucking sword no god damn it on horseback
again he can't fucking move you've pinned me
in here get me out of the corner get away from me
no get away from me i don't come here come here
i jumped over the lance good into his head come on
killer i don't do i have enough just fucking dismount the damn horse
get off i'm not fucking around so let's go
hold x but look add it to the list of other tutorial items that were never in
a tutorial you walked in here now i gotta get off
oh god i'm so fucked here wait no i just skilled myself into reality
my whole team is dead oh this is great what are we gonna do about this
off the horse get off the horse off off off off the horse
get off the horse please get off to dismount
why give me my sword do i not have this
i need a fucking weapon give it to me do i not have a
sword kill the horse i don't have a sword
all right all my fucking points into throwing weapons
now i'm understanding i mean we're talking about
every single point every single point has gone into throwing weapons
every single one fucking hell i can't win a tournament
after increasing the difficulty using a fucking lance or a sword
what i can't can i throw the lance through somebody's fucking brain matter
fuck the horse oh god damn it really you all fucking lost
all of you does this does the game just roll dice on
what what what's going on here don't let him out
no what oh i'm getting angry at this fuck you game unbelievable
i die i gotta pay i'm so tilted by this
fucking game and tilted by my fucking character choices
this character is terrible why did i make this
what was the point in picking this character this game is
so hard and i put the difficulty why did i listen to everybody to put the
difficulty up too why would i do that the game is on default
just play the game i pressed g instead of x
fucking god damn it i fucking threw on the ground
oh save it here i'm gonna actually do this one more time
and then i'm gonna fucking throw up on the monitor i fucking ran that guy's
head over who cares you just stole taxes you don't need
this money no i need a goddamn useful character
instead of this dickhead driver turn up the difficulty
hey you know that character that you made that sucks absolute asshole
yeah make it harder too
fuck off oh my body kill kill kill why don't you get a horse
what thankfully you're stupider than i am okay
there'll be four teams with one fighter each don't you dare fuck this up
dickhead oh that was the king no what i'm so under leveled that's the way
that's it you can't save in between the scum doesn't work
no wait wait wait wait wait hold on that's not true is that true
so then i can't join so i can't do it between rounds go back to default
difficulty well you understand i can't do that now
because like a shitload of people were screaming in my ear
to turn it up to hard turn up harder if i go back
i already made the deal with the devil i already signed the fucking contract
so like the 601 guys that are going to be mad
if i go back to the default difficulty we're not going to hear the end of it
the whole night i want i want to burn this fucking city
down how do i do that how do i walk in and just
like fucking slash at the king i was i don't care i'm going back to
the other guy and give him the taxes i'm gonna go throw a fucking rock to
this king's window fuck his feast fuck your
bullshit fuck your tournament and fuck your like what level you are
where's my money fuck this place now you like this place
here here take that i'm so salty right now i'm so fucking here it's avid
all right what what the fuck do i even have to do
i just wanted to meet the guy okay do you understand
this dude just has a fucking like what he just goes back and forth i'm just i
just wanted to talk to him you know he's over by some butcher oh no
he's not oh yes he is no he's walking over this way towards the castle
is he yes now he's here but he just left i'm sitting here reading chat what do
you mean he just left didn't he just have a feast where are you going hey hey
listen to me it's not even the same guy any tasks
no i've come to offer you my sword so do somebody do i really have to go kill
bandits for an hour go for the fucking king kill the king
and then leave where is he which one is he i think he's
right there charge no no no no charge oh fuck i was
attention they're gonna eat me i'm gonna get
fucking eaten fucking god damn it i'm looking for bandits
farmers no i can't just prey on farmers find more taxes to steal
it was going so well too caravan uh peace agreement okay
somebody said there's a lot of bandits this way
oh there goes doug and we got none of you just befriend the bandits
i'm not gonna do that what is what are you doing yeah bandits right here
is my am i on horseback slower than people on fucking foot
yeah you gotta be kidding me where do i put which
where do i buy the thing that makes it so i can go faster
my men would like a word i can smell your farts
from a mile away i think you could do with some lightning let's go
where are they are they okay well they're right there
now get up there men oh shit get off the horse
just an easy target
throw is not the way to do it i can't do it anymore
i don't care what it is i'll have to fucking get the points back some other
way
what do you have what do you got on your masterwork sword
okay fucking god damn it
i gotta throw rocks at people is that gonna be funny for
30 seconds let me just fuck up my game and then
oh this is actually good shit here you chose this life
yeah and then i got bullied into making the game harder so i chose the life of
being an idiot and putting points into fucking throwing weapons
and putting my skills into throwing weapons and then i got like bullied into
making the game harder you understand how this is like those
two heads of that sword that we both grabbed on at the same time
level four i ain't running this character into the ground anymore
what we got 14 can sell that now 16 no no you're better off with the rocks
no i would no way not a trillion years i'd slit your throat
ratchet well you're all dead too remember when this is a throwing stream
no i'm i'm i need to like i need to go kill that king
here's the last of the throwing that you're gonna get this whole stream
that's it got it yeah um one one person died that's okay
we have some level ups here okay skirmisher
let's go skirmisher who the fuck are you guys
higher okay uh you had just shit i guess maybe this is worth taking
not really though what is this just make an army of farmers
all right did i level up at all experienced i mean like i
i should have just walked around and just killed bandits for like 20 minutes
tundra bandits okay hold on there's a lot of them here
save the game everything has a price you bet your life
all right this the jokes stop here the gameplay begins
kill your party they'll be fine they got me on their team
oh fuck i'm gonna die shit help me help me
i am we retreat retreat all right we're fine enemies they are they all died
wait hold on the game is called mount and blade i don't but i don't like being
on the horse i don't like the controls on the horse
how is that not decisive all right good okay so i got i got
people i need they're wounded people here we're gonna get we have to leave
he's a fucking worth a lot of money how many jarrods do i have
pick those up balanced javelins those are worth a lot too
for the bent ones uh flanked mace i don't think i'm gonna take anything else
should i take the mace i gotta sell all this crap
these boots are fucking worth let's just take the things that are worth money
i guess that is 57 300 all right fucking let's go
all right uh how about this castle now for a stroll
are we what the fuck are you you've encountered looters you ate
uh i have to pull back i can't have to say i have to sacrifice let's go
what the fuck man where were you guys 30 minutes ago and i was looking for you
how much money 841 um no i i'm wounded i can't fight i have seven
troops god damn it approach the gates let me in
wait here jesus all right carrot party let's take a look
wait what are you doing i can't do this here all right let's go that way
so there's a lot of bandits down here okay what do we got let me see lord's
hall looks like i'm healed how's everybody
else i think everyone's good to go yeah we're good i have five prisoners too
okay let's go sell up here farmers no bandits
it's like 23 plus five let's get in here 22
i wish this was get off the fucking screen all right give me some shit
throne i should probably hold on to one of these what's this 39
still using the darts well i shouldn't be jarrod's get rid of these fucking
things darts versus jarrod's balanced light lance sell it
sell the book you don't you know what i know you don't have enough
give me that book back there's like fallout shit you don't have enough money
i'm gonna get a thousand bucks where can i get a horse right here
who sells horses horse probably the guy that that says horse merchant
eight armor 18 speed 41 speed 50 12 maneuver 42
charge 12 hit points riding two do i have riding two all right got a new
horse and let's go to the goods market how
do i got food i got plenty of food maybe some ale
uh why don't i have a pair of gloves is that what this is
hey you can take this all right so i'm gonna sneeze you okay i'm good
go to the market wait here level four let's go fight some more bandits
bandits don't i have the better horse there's 20 bandits there that's not good
okay well how many are there there's 29 i'll take 20 if i can even catch up with
you your money or your life all right you're
dead charge the attack the more horses i have
in my inventory the faster i go why does that sound like bullshit
the more horses in your inventory that can't be real
it's true it's a lot all right here we go
all right good good work it's pretty clean
last guy he's gonna run he ain't gonna get away don't worry
he's i thought he's dead we die i got him right in the right in the
teeth all right nobody dead more stuff to sell
that's it i'm not gonna pick it maybe a couple of these
level five intelligence maybe we got pathfinding okay more
four hours and only level five well that's because i didn't know that i had
to just kill bandits i felt like i was doing
missions in question no just kill bandits i didn't know we
can do this the easy way or the hard way right everyone's been so
silent speed and let's turn it in hello there
how's your mother hey how's your father who leveled up what
are you guys good crossbow can i talk to these guys i don't
want to spend too much money
all right keep going over there i need i gotta get at least like level six
before i go sell anything or do anything get recruit some people
and i can recruit people here hey two recruits i'll take them why not
deserters i'll take them we are the free brothers we will fight only for
ourselves from now on now give us all your gold or taste our steel
that what was the we fight for we fight for ourselves we fight for goodness wait
did i miss that there or something
take out the archers locked it good for you
uh nobody dead now let's go sell what do you say
not level up oh let me go sell and the bandits are up here but i don't
know if i can can fight the bandits not the bandits the uh the sea raiders
because didn't they make the game harder so
wasn't that the whole reason everyone everyone got really mad that i beat the
sea raiders they were like you're not supposed to
be able to do that and i had to change the difficulty let's go
over here this is the coast i think i need to where the hell am i
what's going on what all right hold on can i
here are these prisoners talk don't run away or doing something stupid i'll be
watching you no i won't okay can i sell them here can't gotta
go to like a bigger castle like this one can i not know bigger
bigger town like this one uh what about rivacheg
it's a huge place i haven't been to yet let's explore
visit the tavern okay i got five people here for you
uh geramus uh how can i okay can i help you
gross iniquity i want you in advance lest you are of a
choleric temperament and so become incensed of the injustice done to me
i'm gonna get a life story here i am by training a natural philosopher but
condemned by the jealousy of the thick-headed doctors of my university to
make my living as an interant surgeon hired by a merchant to cure his son
some fell into a coma after they fell from their balcony
i successfully trippanned the patient's skull to reduce the cranial swelling
they didn't listen to me i said take the willow bark they didn't listen
and the guy died the father rather than reward me for my efforts charged me with
sorcery such as the ignorance and and gratitude
of mankind i'm anxious to move on i'm a surgeon not
some silk-robed university physician i can get my hands dirty i treated every
variety of wound yeah get the fuck over here okay we got
a he uh we got a healer pretty cool uh tavern keeper i like to
buy every man who comes in here have you heard of anyone in this realm who might
need have a job no uh you have any from
mercenaries i mean three of my mates no ransom broker i broke a ransom for
the poor wretches who are captured in these endless wars okay
you look like the type who might have a prisoner to sell what can i get for a
prisoner it varies i fancy that i have a fine
eye for assessing a ransom now what if their families can't pay
surprised what sorts of treasures a peasant can dig out of his cow shed or
wheedle out of his cousins so he's got the proper motivation
would you ransom me if i were taking of course
okay uh i'd like to ransom one of my companions
oh i got prisoners to sell the guy i just talked to
hey come join my troop of merry men okay thanks you can have this guy okay
price 104 yeah take them all it's 500 bucks so there goes the
prisoners what is that you do it's a bard i don't want to hear you sing
i don't want to know i mean i don't want to hear you fucking sing a goddamn
sentence all right let's get out of here let's do
some selling 1300 500 bucks give armor to germa
uh looking like a beetle hat does he need a weapon too
a lot of fucking rock how am i doing on food i'm doing pretty good
maybe one more uh roasted pork he uses pole arms well
i'm sure we'll find one because now i have to buy it back at a premium
now he can take this i'm not using those anymore
all right so what level am i get i got ten thousand dollars
i could go do that thing where is is there a way i can go into uh let me see
your equipment you got better shit than i have yeah i
was gonna give him well you can have this hat what is this range 45 swing 16 c
20 p i think his is better here we'll just take
another one okay good more bandits save the game take his
shoes why would i take his shoes village farmer they're better than mine
no they're not are they it's a peace agreement between uh sultanate
and rodox let me talk to my companion for a second
you better shoes than me no that's not cool nomad boots
nomad boots no we got the same thing isn't that better stuff
why are you debating me why would you do that
there's no reason for that sea raiders uh i'm not going to be able to beat them
today the gods will decide your fate let's go
where's where's germimus is he in here which one's germimus
is that him we can't let him die sea raiders
you got it one more i think i ran over one of my guy's heads
i'm sorry people died is it good take it all you have lots of expensive
shit still not leveled up uh if someone soup you're asking what
the difficulty was on i just have it on the
the default here and then i turned combat ai and campaign a out of average
i think you're ready for hard all right so
where am i going now to sell all the shit that i just got
right here to uh booger castle let me in i can't do anything what's going on get
in there all right i got lots of stuff uh what's this
20 38 5 it's the same thing okay give that to like
turdamus whatever his name is 39 to head i'm just gonna get rid of
these 16 that's better heavy fighting axe one-handed
huh hold on to this 31 33
do you have a pair of gloves see a lot of boots
tattered leather gloves that's all you got for gloves
damn i might buy one of these i have 11 000 all right let's give this to
germimus he's like dead you all right you already
have something uh i need to he needs to rest that's
my what do you mean that's my stuff wait what
what are you talking about
whatever all right can have my horse too all right can he use this i'm a
fucking loser all right how do i move him is he this
means he's like in the back right if i put him back here yeah he was
already all the way down here okay so what level am i now i don't even
know what i was actually doing wasn't i waiting for that kid okay i
was waiting for the king to go from here to there where was it
i was gonna go meet with this guy but then i said fuck that i hate this guy
so now we're gonna go i have no idea i uh i don't know what to do i
guess maybe i could go back here i want to go back here
i've done my diligence here where's the fucking king
find the goddamn king we're in go to the castle
are you in here no you're never in here you have like fucking fruit by the foot
chicken apples nerds rope whatever the hell that is
you're never here he's always at war always all right i'm
just gonna walk around do you know anybody is how's your life
do the tournament jerry you realize the president doesn't spend all day in his
bathtub you but at least you'll take you'll take a bath once talk to anyone
in that faction i mean that that's great where are they
does it run into one of the like generals this place is destroyed
and everyone's faster than me i'm in the wrong country
no i abandoned this country i just bought a better horse
i just did that do i have to go put like four horses in my inventory
the king was there oh there's a goddamn peace agreement that i had nothing to do
with who is this he was in the town what i was just here
i was just here in his fucking bedroom wrong town what's the right town wasn't
i trying to i was trying to talk to the king
vagus is this correct oh look there he is
hey oh you've come in here fucking 40 times good to meet you i'm the king
enjoy my feast sorry i was walking around in circles as a
fucking monopoly piece sorry about that what do you need
i don't recognize you you ever think for me to do
no i don't i've come to offer you my sword you're not known as a
you are now oh you are known as a brave man okay
i am ready my lord good then repeat the words of the oath for me
i swear homage to you as lawful ruler of the kingdom of vargas
i pledge homage to you as lawful ruler of the kingdom of vagras
i remain as your loyal and devoted man as long as my breath remains
i will remain as loyal and devoted to you for as long as
i shall live and i'll be at your side to fight your enemies should you need to
turn into a monopoly piece and fucking be the thimble and go get park place
and i'll be at your side to fight your enemies and find park place finally i
will uphold your lawful claims and those of your legitimate heirs yeah yeah
yeah very well you've given me your carton
may you upload it at all it's proper courage devotion
let it be known that from this day forward you are my sworn man and vessel
i give you my protection and grant you the right to bear arms in my name
and i pledge that i shall not deprive you of any life liberty of properties
except that by lawful judgment of your peers
by the law and custom of the land furthermore i give you the
thief of ismirallah with its rents and revenues
what the fuck i just walked in here i don't understand this
you're giving me all this land and all this money i just had to
fucking run behind you and find you i have thief of
is ismirallah with all the rents and revenue
you've done a wise thing carton serving well and i promise you'll rise high
thank you i have great hopes for you carton i know you shall prove yourself
worthy of the trust i've placed in you and the reason why i did this is because
you landed a blow on me during the tournament i've got my eye on you
thank you what do you got for me to do there are some minor errands which i need
completed but it would be more appropriate to
give to one of my own men not a sworn vessel
if a worthy task prevents itself i may offer you
a favor my apologies i don't know you well enough to take your advice
so let's go collect some taxes thank you
fuck out of my way you know who i am oh are you
i heard that you have pledged allegiance to our lord king yaruglek
look forward to fighting alongside you against our foes bad guy bad guy bad guy
i want to talk to you in private hey this king over here
fuck them right let's usurp them i get 50% of the usurp you get 50% of the
usurp we're both happy perhaps we can discuss
this matter in a more private setting i get to slurp 50% you get to slurp look
it'll be easy i'll just throw a rock where's my fucking new town fief
let's see the kind of property i got right here right
thanks thanks king i hereby give you a broken down piece of shit that has been
looted and ruined welcome to the family can i do anything about it the village
has been looted a handful so scatter as you pass through the burnt houses
i i think it's time to fucking you slurp this guy
you know what i'm saying i think it's time we fucking you slurp him
see i'm this this is my house now now i'm gonna like launch siege weapons over
to sargoth right now it'll be just like my favorite ipad
game i build up my troops i spend gems and then i've launched a
fucking siege attack on this guy permanently he's not even logged in
right now not even logged in yeah what am i gonna do um let's just go
hang out over here i'm just gonna sit here for a week
who's that who's that get away from my fucking town it's fine now i'm not gonna
listen to that he's the owner of the i'm the owner of
this castle i'm the thief that means i own it right if
you're the thief of a castle it means you own the castle
all right is this thing good so let's go to let me go to the lord's hall can i
let's let's speak candidly here here's mr cable do i am carton i am boyer a
vassal of kingdom of iron the lord of ismaril castle well i'm the lord of
ismirala you pledge allegiance to our lord fight
bravely indeed you will be rewarded okay do you have anything for me minor
erin's i wouldn't give to you okay i think we can work together to advance
our standings this guy wants to work together i can't
think of anything right now but we will have some items of mutual interest in
the future let us discuss another topic very well
may i suggest a course of action i'm out of here i am wife to cable mother to
harish mother to harris i have no need for a
champion okay fucking uppercut
mother of why do they used to do that who's in the prison
who is in prison here currently no one i want to speak with them
oh shit no i'm the prisoner now hey okay you're gonna let me out
i don't think so that's a funny joke all right you can let me out
i just want to go check out my city you almost spit out your chocolate milk
i'm gonna refill ismirala come on i just i don't care over how long this takes
go find some tournaments not yet i gotta fight some more bandits
i gotta go collect mad taxes you know what i mean i'm gonna have to collect
mad taxes from this place you know in a roller coaster tycoon how you
get the thing where you can scroll left or right
how much you want it to cost to go to the park
oh i'm gonna be fucking mad taxes from this place
there it is let's go this is my castle here we go the poverty of this village
is unbearable only a handful of people are strong enough to work in the fields
many of which are becoming overgrown with weeds
the rest are weak and malnourished or have already fled elsewhere
the draft animals have long since starved or eaten although a few carcasses
still lie in the outskirts their bones gnawed by wild this is a slight isn't it
back in the day if you got this guy yeah i'm gonna give you this one
this village it's a great one and you come here and
it's all run down like this and all fucked up he and he's laughing
i'm getting hazed right now i don't like this
fuck this guy i'm gonna let's i'm gonna fucking slurp up that king real soon
uh the populace is indifferent to you let's see uh
manage this village the village has no improvements
i got money build this okay this is how you you
build a school first always build a school
i don't need like a big manor for myself build a school
they're gonna get educated school increases the loyalty the villagers do
by plus one every month as the party member with the highest engineer skill
you reckon that building the school will cost you nine thousand dollars and will
take 93 days ah how much
man is a little cheaper you know man it's a little cheaper for that one
what about a mill that's cheaper for that one
build a mess i need an engineer should i level up engineering
let me go walk around just see how they treat me this is mine
just go get an engineer party member who's this
hey i want to buy have you seen any enemies around here
it's got a target on my good sir our village has been going through such
hardships lately the harvest has been bad
they took away the merciless bands has took away our seed grain
if we cannot find some grain we will not be able to plant our fields and then
we'll have nothing to eat for the coming year
how much grain do you need four packs of grain
i'll get it i can't do that all right i'll be back
and you need grain fucking be back in 10 minutes
to show you just how good of a fucking guy i am your previous owner
let me put that on like a i'll look into it list not this guy
wait no never mind you pre what what's owner
no you're not even a real city i need a i need a castle this one
bring it back all right goods we need grain
you fucking idiots don't even have grain really
the town of dirham seems to be flourishing there's a tournament going
on right now hold on don't fuck this up no no i want
i need to save it i did just save it right let's go
okay we got team one let's go charge big ass helmet
he's left charge charge come on charge nice nice charge charge
charge charge thank you thank you thank you
okay tier two there'll be two teams with three fighters each
no no no no on the horse i hate the horse just like fucking random over
i'd rather just get off the fucking horse seriously
i know it's x to do the lance thing i know it's just
slippery and awkward to do this walk that shit
he let go of it do it in first person mode
that doesn't really help though yes it does
uh there'll be two teams of seven people each
and give me the bow i'm the i'm the yellow this time
they keep changing my colors okay you're gonna make me a fucking archer
really like honest to god you're gonna make me a fucking archer
why don't why why i have no other weapons
why would they do that you can pick up yeah but i nobody died
i bone arrow i have 15 points in bone arrow
four damage and i just five people run up on me and i die
tournaments are rng bullshit are they it's because it's a vanilla mountain
blade warband fucking just buy grain i ain't doing that
anymore that's the only thing that like irritated me about this game
is throwing dice in the air and picking a random character in the
tournaments give me some fucking grain i got the
grain i wish i could just fucking just leave a wake of fire no
relax and go back and give the grain to the people
that's all i needed right four packs of grain i've got five
i got the grain for you what do you think of me
it's i your noble ruler it's me how come you're not going fuck what the
fuck he's here tell me about the village they belong to
you of course my lord we mostly produce grain and smoked fish
thank you carry on where's the elder can you can we get the fucking wizard out
of the way i'm i own this place i could punch that
guy if i want uh about the task you asked me for yes
many progress i need i brought you four packs of grain
my good lord you've saved us from hunger and desperation we cannot thank you
enough but you'll always be in our prayers
village of ismirallah will not forget what you've done okay
anything else what a hero any enemies no anybody in this village i think of
one whom i suspect would jump with the chance you could pay ten dollars for
their equipment yeah okay
mclord that plays watch out for the axe you ever hear of that one i bring grain
but i also have my fucking fucked up amusings as long as
you just deal with my fucked up bullshit he will always be fed he will always have
places to sleep okay uh i need to do engine i need some
engineers one point in engineering
make cha did i put one in cha
where's uh trainer every day each year with the skill add some experience to
every other member yeah why i get fail fished what the fuck did
i do what's going on fail fishes what's happening
here i wanted to put points into surgery
because i don't i that's a good one i'm not i'm look i'm not gonna get fail
fished in my own city here okay 22 of you that have a problem
who's this eat them all right let's go uh what do i need
so i need to do stuff with the king i already have a guy with surgery
somebody just said it stacks isn't that a good thing
shouldn't we be happy about that all right i
i need what the hell do i need how's everybody doing
everybody's good right where can i find an engineer that is the real question
in taverns in taverns in taverns in taverns and what it where what is in
taverns of town i n t a v e i r n in taverns i
don't know that's not on the map i said tell rog
for yaheg fanada in taverns i don't know what that is
that was so loud i'm sorry i forgot i turned up the volume
i'm sorry i forgot that i turned myself up
oh like and i freaked out halfway through that
actually fucking scary it's a fucking demon
all right all right all right all right all right relax uh visit the tavern
show them the clip all right looking for an engineer
i'm an engineer no you're not traveler mercenary engineer i'm an
engineer i travel a lot and keep it open here
let me see it i don't know what that is
jesus christ i don't know what that is
that's so that is a cartoon donkey somebody animate that with me with
like a big donkey face how did i make that noise i don't know
i let me try to make that noise again
no i can't i was going to ask you look a bit down on your luck
my luck you could say that it was bad luck to be born a weak father who was
married me off to a drunken layabout or beat me it was bad luck
uh i'm taking my group of bandits it was my bad luck the only one among them was
kind of me who taught me to hunt and fight inspired the jealousy of others who
knifed him and forced me to run away again
uh are you by any chance looking for work i might be i could certainly use the
money but let your followers know that i do
not suffer louts and brutes anyone who misbehaves around me will quickly
find an arrow in their gut don't shoot anybody on the first day
thank you thank you engineer okay are you an engineer
that's what i'm looking for an engineer who's up here nobody will see it i'll
throw a knife in somebody's head i have to get my bloodlust out i told you
i'm a merciless ruler but i'm fair i can't do it all right but
this mercenary hi no you know i want i want the free
mercenaries not the people like that i'm going to charge them no
no tavern keeper can we look for a job okay yeah i know i'm already on that i
heard that voldrad has been worried about bandits
establishing a hideout in his area okay i don't want to hear all this
that's too many names so i wish to buy a town let me see
six grand what is the most expensive i could do one of these right now
i don't need an engineer for this 500 a week this is ten thousand dollar
investment for 500 bucks a week what do you mean that's not economical
for me i have 10 grand what are you talking about uh what
how did i lose that what did i get what go to a different town
that's because i just bought somebody right i want to go back to the king's
quarters i wanted the king king said come back
sometime and i'll talk to you that's what we're fucking going okay
do you have anything for me to do no lord should have to admit this carton
but i was inspecting my soldiers the other day and there are men here who
don't know which end of a sword to hold i need someone like you to knock them
into shape you're a warrior of renown carton will
you train some troops for me i would be grateful
how many if you can raise six vaguer horsemen and bring them to me
that will probably be enough give me six fresh recruits and i'll train
them to be horsemen taking a weight off my shoulders carton
i shall tell my sergeants to send you the recruits and attach them to your
command i'll advance you some money to help with
expenses here this purse should do it thank you
okay uh raise horsemen you have 120 days to finish this i need to
raise six horsemen oh okay i have to level them up
with the training field right here let's go to the training field training field
speak with the trainer range weapon horseback practice
speak with the trainer hold on all out here by yourself okay
good day you look like another adventurer who's coming a chance to the
yeah training field uh i do a few questions
i can't do anything i can't bring them here um it's fucking bandit layer let's
go you don't announce yourself so what are
you doing it's okay wait everybody get follow me
we're going in two different directions here i don't want that follow me
this is two guys who's dead wait how did you die what the fuck
you got you're getting shoot at uh that wasn't even a recruit that's fine
that's just not gonna fucking happen i wish i could get up here faster
okay a couple more didn't hit him in the head
oh that's wrong weapons i why even use them
fuck honey light lance there's a lot of shit here
take it all they didn't even do anything they don't put these anything
they've never even fought none of these guys even fought can i
spar with them go get more recruits go get a bunch more
recruits one oh man okay
should i fight them all am i gonna kill this guy
did he learn anything the training went perfectly
what versus three three recruits i just like get up on you like fucking bugs
they're just like attaching themselves to me they're like magnets
these are the recruits and i'm the nobleman teaching them
fucking embarrassing me that's the other way around
every like medieval fucking uh it's always that i'm just fucking
staring asshole with spine coach and yeah i'll kick you and push you and hit
you in the mouth these guys just got driven in here and
i'm instant i'm losing to them jesus
holy shit man this character this character
sucks i'm the one getting trained
this is a lucky swing broken clock is right twice a day
so let this guy embarrass me
i taught you well coming in fucking bruises oh these are the recruits these
are like fucking like just turned 18 you know what i mean like oh
father don't send me into the fucking i don't want to
you're gonna do it son you're gonna be a blacksmith just like your father
you're gonna get trained by the best punching bag in the whole
city oh i've got oh my points are in like power throw i have no points in
any like the melee shit upgraded now not yet not yet not yet not
yet i'm gonna teach these guys a fucking lesson then now
we're playing pool i'm gonna pool shark you never get overconfident
fellas all right when your lord turns and runs during training
all right let's go let's upgrade them what we got recruits
okay so now they can be footmen right so i need how many did it did i need to
bring back to him i need six so how do they what's the tree
to veteran than to horseman or to skirmisher than to horseman
what about me do i have any points to put in no i don't
just abysmal remember we were laughing at the guy that had 50 50 50 50 50 50
the beginning of the game who's laughing now your stats are
horrible i know they are i know they are all right we need
recruits come on fuck out of here okay overhead attack seems very good really
bring them all out now that's too many too overwhelming too many people too
many humans too many bodies too many people too many things in the way
okay we're gonna do it but go back to three it's like what the fuck
can i upgrade them now like jesus man okay where are my
veterans i got footman i have veterans here i need
six okay they can kick the shit out of me for like
40 minutes i could care less oh my god they're too powerful
they're too powerful for me they broke my fucking shield
it's the only one i have okay one by one you'll learn
what the jeremy's is what eating fucking popcorn and watching this
i was holding right click let's take a veteran on
okay seven footman it doesn't even matter
does it matter if i beat up like the weakest person in the party like here
what if i just kick the shit out of jeremy's
do i get points for this yes we're seeing the uh this from the other
perspective by the way that's me if i lose to jeremy's i will delete my
stream you understand all right we need some uh veterans so
then horseman i need six of these put music on what
music would you like to hear i'm not deleting my fucking stream
why is he better why did you get better you shouldn't have learned anything
on any soundtrack i'm only going to do this a few more time
nice blocking jeremy's put on white noise
save before i alt tab i'm not gonna no i'm not doing that
okay how do we look anybody else can level up footman veteran
recruit footman warrior just might as well do it all right how much
do you have how long does it take to go from here to
there jeremy's hates my stream this is determined to ruin my
career do i get more okay if i do jeremy's and
jeremy's who's like a piece of crap no they're
they're good archer didn't get the last hit
that doesn't count this character is so i can't even tell you
jeremy's didn't i didn't lose to jeremy this is this is jeremy's here
if i lose this one then yeah you could have you got some point here
i had he he got he didn't get the last hit sorry let's try them let's try them
both at the same time do they get more exp i don't know i
can't tell more more more don't you dare no that
doesn't count it doesn't count i it's just two v one he's not even doing
any of the work she is he's just accidentally in the way
sometimes he may as well be swinging around a
fucking vacuum cleaner like he's not doing anything
oh that hurt how are we doing he died to jeremy's it doesn't even matter
you're going through with your wrist get out of here all right
let's see who can level up what do you say
footman veteran veteran i need horseman so here's what we're gonna do we're gonna
we're gonna get two more veteran and i'm gonna take the
veteran into battle they're gonna be all the way up two more
almost done what if they die they won't die i won't let that happen
they're not all gonna die they're all gonna be highly trained and highly
skilled assassins what the hell are they talking about
we're gonna die look you don't even know what you're
talking about okay did these two gain experience they gained
five they they gain a dogshit amount of experience
where's the music there you go there's a little fucking beat
more more more more i was gonna do like a clown song
we're gonna baby gamer chop chop chop chop chop
oh what a baby gamer shut up last one why am i obsessed with clowns
i'm not i've almost ever heard of a clown is you guys are the ones that are
obsessed with clowns i just react to the clowns that you guys bring up
it'll be dangerous here oh you mother fucker get out of my way
how can you be this good how is it possible to be this good at the game
you've got a block on block how could you be this good at something he's got
auto block on don't let him say that he has auto block on
i think i'm starting to get this this is like a kind of a fun game i'm starting
to get the hang of like the symptoms in place he's playing on easy
don't let him do he's not allowed to say that
i'm i'm having a fun time i think the game is interesting it
takes a lot it does a lot of information he's playing on easy stupid
i'm having a fun time you're not on hard i okay
i'm having a good time playing here we go
i gotta do one more oh wait i'm i can't i can't lose to this guy
there's a specific criteria involved i'm not gonna fucking have that happen
all right this this is it one two go i need gamer assistance
now and even if i did even if i did who cares
even if i did who cares even if i need gamer assistance
doesn't matter i need one more of these guys
all right last time i think that's probably gonna be it and if not then
whatever we're just gonna bring them into a battle anyways
there it is all right we have six veterans get them to the top
move them up with me so i got the six veterans i need to turn them into
horsemen and then i go back and i've got even more favor with the king
what do we got here save that before anything fucking horrible happens
28 look for some bandits or something your relationship with
boy your knee lag has increased from minus two to minus one
oh right this stupid cattle thing uh it's 97 people
i need more men looters right here no no no no no those are mine that's mine
those are mine those are mine those are mine those are mine those are mine
do we really need this many people for like six bandits
there they are they stole bread send the entire king's army after those
motherfuckers these guys are not very good see you later
all right yeah that's very that's a great sound it sounds like somebody's
pressing on the ducks that meme video they push on the ducks
and they all go no casualties all right thanks for your help stranger we have
met property heavy what's your name carton well met carton i am kramak
thanks for your help and i hope we meet again i don't want that shit
uh three recruits i'll take them uh didn't take the prisoner
oopsie throw the rotten pork who's that tundra bandits free rotten
pork you know you boil it for long enough it's all right
holy shit 23 bandits we'll level up from this one
you go faster i don't know i gotta buy an inventory worth of horses
surrender or die as you wish prepare to die
31 versus 23 there's gonna be a lot of experience points in this one
i've got my champions i've got my nord warriors
bring it on i didn't hit anybody this fucking spam
watch out you improve your proficiency in one hand
your casualties one recruit one footman who cares
jeremus he's he'll be all right one veteran wounded it's okay
continue oh do we have that's when we do a scenario like
this one two unconscious just fucking dump
them in a river okay keep these guys in the back too
it's only 10 p.m for me it's uh 10 30 currently 10 30
all right now i can relax although i gotta sell stuff
yeah let's get some sales here where's the nearest town
hurry up hurry up where's the nearest town hurry all right may sell
hmm bata no i know what i'm gonna do i'm gonna buy a couple of horses
saddle horse and heavy horse right just put them in here don't
foot don't need them it increases your speed up to six horses
if you guys lie to me i swear to god 480
so i'm being lied to where if i buy horses in the in the inventory my
my little like fucking pony collection is not going to make me faster
that is a lie no it actually does make you fast it works
it's not worth it it's not a lie it's a lie
okay well i'm not gonna buy one i already sold everything how we doing on
food we got plenty of food we know we actually don't
get this like old fucking bread out of here i don't want it sell everything and
become a beggar no why would i do that
all right character no points yeah i know pathfinding does that i already
have points in it i already put points in it
i think there are rocks people i don't even care i don't even care
all right so i still i need six of them so i need to fight more bandits let's
wait so people can heal let me see what can you tell me about
your skills all right let me tell you okay what's this guy
gonna do how about weapon master engineer oh
reset i thought that was intelligence like wound management right
first aid wound management wound treatment wounding wound treatment
yeah surgery he's got four already first aid
woundage is already there how about first aid
yeah it's the healer and he needs some abilities
how about uh one in each what the hell should i give this guy
i mean he's terrible in everything now he's a formidable force
let me see your equipment and see if they have what kind of formidable forces i
can give you your gear sucks you should be fucking ashamed of
yourself 18 19 16 27 it's better you should be ashamed
of yourself you can't even hold that you should be
ashamed of yourself all right let's rest up the lance is
better on you it'll be fine assign him to a group in the
party screen uh and assigned to archers he'll just hang
back with the archers okay uh we need
we need to go and explore and find some more bandits
as a farmers you didn't have a bow we didn't need a bow even he's supposed to
sit back and do nothing like read what about uh you slum
oh i paid seven dollars this week four hundred dollars from rent okay that's
awesome this game sucks i'm kidding you think
i'd be playing this game for six and a half hours if i didn't think it was fun
oh let's see yeah give me that lance back give me a
turn of us light lance it's mine now take your staff
back it's useless you should be ashamed of yourself all
right bandits where are they you played getting over for seven hours
and said it was the worst experience of your life
yeah no i this game's fun i don't hate this game
i think it's worth playing i'm having a great time i really am
mod it with insane mods not yet jerma what is that jerma's bitten by what
they're bitten by a rapid master engineer master when the hell did that
just happen any volunteers yeah so let's um
i need to fight a bandit or something where did i go
declaration of war swadia has declared war against
rodox i got nothing to do with that farmers
oh no bandits when am i just gonna kick the
shit out of one of these generals that's what i want to know
nobody there bandits where are they i just saw one right here
no can we leave me alone get the hell away from me
bandits bandits bandits sea raiders 12 come here
they will drink from you yeah you will use lance use lance use lance i got it
um what the fuck are they okay well uh i didn't exactly do what i was
planning on doing you guys suck
whoa whoa whoa whoa all right get in there fight
did it hit the tree die can you guys like get the fuck in there
what are you waiting for like what are you waiting for
stupid like why are you all just walking why can't you run
stop using the lance i was screamed at to use the lance explicitly it was like
people were shaking me and telling me to put the lance on
oh my fucking god are the horsemen dead thank god they're not
well let's go hang on the castle for a year let's try it again
there's so many people coming now 19 sea raiders go this way
okay we declared war on swadia 13 no i don't want to fight all these guys
get in the castle quick hide shit okay now i'm gonna go with
i'm gonna stay with the group i'm gonna go with the fucking ant party
fucking fire at will somebody just get hit
how did you what press two movement orders
char i mean i where the fuck was that tutorial
get the guy on the horse who died fuck you just keep the horsemen
in the back they already are aren't they
just stay the fuck down here there's too many people
pick it up where you going i leveled up too all right iron flesh
plus two health strength i think i need more strength
i just need to get two more i need to get a few more horses
six horsemen i really am about to just go to the training field and just do this
today the guardsmen decide your fate what's happening
uh this 32 of them you devise a plan that allow you to your men to escape
with the flies but you have to leave two soldiers behind
okay i can win this you can win that okay uh three movement orders
stand ground don't fucking move those are the horses right
no no those aren't the horses those are not the horses what the hell those are
the you said it was three you said it was three you said it was three
no don't go in there horses don't back back back back back back back back back
retreat retreat retreat retreat you said it was three
they're all dead what the fuck he told me it was three three four
three four three just get off the horse fuck the horse
get off who is this who are you it's not i pressed three i did i pressed
three three three your casualties three
horsemen i can't have that leave where was the save i did not press
two i pressed three what the fuck am i two horsemen where where just get me the
training run i don't give a shit get in the training
run see six severs kill them okay three movement
orders hold this position i pressed three last time i didn't
press two i did not do that game's broken
my control was broken no fucking way i might kind of get up there
can the horse not climb this but everybody else can
kill them give me the goddamn thing don't let this guy die
do everything with everything that takes i don't we just won
horsemen horsemen okay i only need two more of these stupid things
two more horsemen we got 13 here 14 i could take 13
no no no you're not gonna get to the training field right now
where i wanted a veteran where are they three experience okay
there we go what the hell was that what's happening right now 31 of them
i who did i lose i don't care let's go back
you have your horseman in the infantry class it don't matter i just need two
more horsemen i can get out of here christ dude oh i fucked myself forever
they're not gonna come up on me like that again are they still training the
same six people technically yes in the most painful way
i think possible all right they're not they're not good
enough how much more well we'll do jerems and a veteran
training this way is useless once these motherfuckers get close enough it's game
over do this one more time all right we get it
veteran shit do i have a level up i do oh it's okay this is before iron flesh
put the veterans into calvary okay so i'm at war
this 18 deserters running from the all areas party
track them down i saved it right no i did we are the free brothers we fight for
only ourselves when i'm done with you you're gonna regret that
all right let's go horses movement orders
hold this position don't go anywhere everybody else i don't give a shit whether
you live or die none of you protect the horsemen at all
costs i'm talking about me too my life is
worthless here just die just beat them even if i die
as long as the horses are okay instead okay
can i turn off the kill feed speaking of horses that are about to die
mine's dead i'm dead who fucking cares just leave
oh man my everyone's dead so the horses have to fight because the
veteran team was with the horses get over here fuck off no no no no no
i put the veteran team with the horses and i made the horses stay
they're all dead the horses are dead they're all dead
speaking of dead horses my horse is dead so this is a fight
it's not fighting
recruit okay i'm gonna get 150 fucking people i could care less anymore
what the what do you mean the bandits what do you mean bandits what are you
talking about this is my town 20 mountain bandits
oh my fucking god you having trouble going across the bridge you
fucking dumb ants just get off the fucking horse
good work uh okay this is my town why would i want to do that
one more horseman and i can be done with this can i like leave people here
give me everybody take i'll take everyone please
what are you doing your village is under attack what the fuck are you
what are you what are you talking about i was just there
the count regus of kingdom swatty is laying waste to my town
get why are you such a mess go what is the give up or i'll ride you down
like a dog we will fight you to the end stay your
hand there's something i must tell you in private
bye i'm not in mood for whispering in the corner god
88 troops versus this 76 well i need to i need my horses no this
everyone's gonna get stuck on the fucking bridge again
no wait wait wait wait wait this is gonna be too
messy oh god damn it i'm going down to this fucking lake
with me cavalry with me with me this many people's not get off the
fucking horse off the horse i don't get off course
just everybody charge i don't care anymore i don't even know what the fuck
is happening right now did somebody help me you can't fight
more than one person in this game do something dude you fucking
idiot all the horsemen's all the horses are dead
i'm done that was fun game that was a fun game
i will never be playing it again what a great game let's just get two armies
and like flush them down a toilet together the game
why did i stop doing quests i was in the middle of doing a quest
i was trying to level up my horses and then i
i was doing one the beginning is tough but it gets
neat later on i'm sure it does the beginning of this game is shit
is it okay it is if you're bad i was about to turn the camera on and
fucking rant into the camera but i don't have any clothes on so i can't do
that well it's been seven hours anyways i'm
gonna i'm gonna that's it i'll see you guys tomorrow you had 120
days to do that quest but why would he give me something like
why would you put the first mission that you're gonna give me
yeah i got this one in like a few months no give me like
lining to find like the assassin go going like to the bandit cave
the whole all of its rng you became a lord too quick you were like level
seven that's not he offered it to me it's not what i'm gonna refuse it he
he offered me lordship well whatever it's a good game i just
no i ain't playing it anymore starting as a lord is a grind skip you
weren't very well how am i supposed to know that though
it's like the hold x to put the lance down
nothing how was i supposed to know to do that
if i didn't have a chat of like 3000 4000 people here
how would i ever know to press x to use the lance why the fuck would i ever do
that all right well i'm done i'll see you
tomorrow we're gonna play i spy tomorrow that's a
game more my speed i think i was having a lot of fun in the
beginning anyways i'll see you guys tomorrow uh we
have some bits to go through the first part of gameplay for
mountain blade is just grinding for money to do anything fun
i don't i didn't i thought you'd i all right
i should have had the wiki page open over here on the left the whole time
just played it wrong well that's just what happened
all right if you enjoy mountain blade i'm glad you do
it's a very immersive interesting game i just i guess i guess i didn't know i
didn't i didn't know what i was getting into
i thought it was a different game and that's on me
so i'll see you guys tomorrow have a great night
and let's go back to the bits so at uh seven hours ago exactly we had
ten dollars from miss melon tea thank you miss melon tea
hey germans my first first bit donation ever recently i moved back
to my home country away uh from my fiance
uh who i won't be seeing for months i just want to say that both you and chad
have been keeping me great company through this tough time
and i cannot thank you all enough love you lots uh thank you so much miss melon
and hopefully you uh can see them soon it's a long time to wait but
glad to keep you company thank you uh let me i had let me see here hold on
i had to move this one second uh thank you some guy for the 20 bucks
no meme video or phantom of the opera tonight couldn't find anything so in
stages a picture of my dog really that's a that's a cute dog let's
take a look at that dog thank you so much for the 20 bucks what
kind of dog is that are you still here it's a pug
i don't think that's a pug don't let dickheads get you down
you know there's nothing to do with that but if you want if you want a real talk
here for a second sometimes like for instance trying to
play a game that is a huge learning curve that requires
potentially hundreds of hours to understand everything
and for every action from the first 10 seconds
of in the game to be called like stupid and that i'm doing something wrong can
get fairly aggravating it just it can from i don't know we
were joking around in the beginning but if i click on the map wrong if i if
i don't go to the right place in the first 10 seconds
like the the hyper like overdrive backseating
and i don't know which way is which i don't know which way is correct
um i got a blindfold on and people shouting orders
and sometimes people backseat to get me to go in the wrong direction it's like
fuck well if i went that way and it was wrong but everyone
you know what i'm saying backseating for eye spy won't be as bad
i don't i disagree but anyways just disable chat no absolutely not
imagine having a chatless stream it'd just be like
hey it's me just sitting here in my room not saying that that was like a huge
issue tonight but trying to learn a game like this
is already frustrating on its own it's been an issue lately though
especially this year yeah i i don't i mean maybe a little bit
to secretly learn the whole street game off stream and pretend you're just
a god gamer or don't put all your points into throwing weapons
yeah but but i'm talking about jokes aside right
and that is actually a viable thing am i wrong to say that
that eventually like if you get lances and stuff and you level that up that
that's not like that's actually viable later on
it is viable right it's very viable okay viable but not for you i but i think i
think sometimes there's like a big disconnect
between like you guys got to remember i have never played this game before
ever some of you might have hundreds of thousands of hours in this game i
literally have don't even know what it is
i was it was requested that i play it i have no fucking idea what the hell this
game is i'm glad you guys are enjoying yourselves
but you gotta remember i i'm so blind that i
don't know that doing something like that is i have to learn it right he
doesn't know the game is pretty complicated just play
every game for a few hundred hours before streaming it
and then i think like if i'm getting my ass kicked and all of a sudden it's
like holy shit this guy sucks it's like do i suck
fuck i suck i'm not good at this game am i what did i do wrong i'm doing
something wrong you're doing something wrong i am
fuck am i it's like a it's like a circle of me
realizing something's wrong maybe start cracking down on it a little bit
chat can be real toxic sometimes it's pretty sad to watch
and it's like and then i i get like backed into like a corner and i'm like
a fucking cat and i'm like i got like two claws i
only have like two fingers just like toxic when one guy was actually the
whole guy all along but i'm not gonna harp on this anymore
it sucks i got i got really frustrated in the last like hour and the first like
six hours the first like five or six hours was
like so much fun i was having a great time and then it
like went self because of like dying to random shit
and not having the right things and doing the wrong things and
oh well no i had a great time i did play the simpsons hit and run that's a
stress-free game you were level six i know like that like
that's i wish i fucking just knew anything
about that it's all right whatever i'll get over it
i'll get over it let's go i'll get over it uh but thank you some guy gave 20
dollars thank you so much jeremy what's your target audience uh
chefs and small animals probably thank you sad vega for the one
dollar i had a dream last night about you which is weird i never dreamed about
this kind of stuff but i was over your house and you're
drinking coffee with your stream live and spilled it everywhere
you had to go clean it up and we're fretting because he didn't want the
stream to stop so i had to cover for you and talked about
talked to chad about banal topics like the weather for 15 minutes or so
i could have used you a few weeks ago oh i could have used you a few weeks ago
and oh no i dumped a whole entire coffee on my desk like like a month ago
where was your dream like a month ago but thank you thank you alec for the one
dollar hello sir hello marvesh mcgally thanks for a dollar i
found this video on reddit i think you'll like it it's
is it is it a gnome better not be it's germa animated
oh i did hear about this let's see it let's take a look
that's a big buck he hung up i think this is a ruse
you're saying it's a trap boss yeah i think it's a trap
yeah there's a one time when i was in a trap in one of my movies
one of you three is working with him and then i took him over there and then
where did i straddle that happened in my one of my movies remember that one
hey be the best you can and put your pedal to the metal
oh yeah i remember that yeah i didn't nobody even knew who the fuck i was i
just kind of walked in and did that that's the fucking goal that was a
goldberg's but thank you marvesh mcgally for the one dollar
am i gonna play apex apex legends probably not
probably not heard it's very good though i've heard it's good
uh thank you nate lane for the two dollars these graphics look like gta san
andres and do i know what a novice fighter is
god damn it why did i get so salty like i'm
why what the hell it was uncalled for i was having so much fun i like
rage quit the game was like chat's fucking mean
uh chat like i don't like it when they do that oh
god damn it you're allowed to have feelings i know
i know i know i wasn't here on a scale of joking about anger streamer to mario
tennis how furious was i no not even i wasn't even close to mario
tennis it's not being salty chat was mean no
but i also was like playing fucking dumb and uh all right i'm sorry guys i'm
sorry that like i got salty and annoyed
you're allowed to be human i know but still like it's i don't like to have
those moments where i'm like actually fucking
salty and mad it doesn't happen often very very infrequently does that happen
you were playing too joking must mean you nearly rage quit oblivion because
you picked skills with green day i know am i ever gonna do something
normal thank you divas for the two dollars
thank you uh noctil for the one dollar i'm so glad you finally got around
playing warband i had to leave the stream early but i
hope you liked the game warband has a lot of mods and maybe go
oh when you come back you're gonna be fucking probably pretty
disappointed i hope you listened the whole time because i did say the game
was fun and i liked it but i wasn't gonna play it again
it is i i made sure even in my like most frustrated i did say
it's a good game it's good i never said it was bad
you said i said it sucks as a joke though that was a joke i was just
making a joke anyways noctil it's a very fun game
i'm just probably not gonna play it again it's very like hard and
take complicated and maybe i'll install the star wars mod and like put it in
would you recommend it yeah i would i would it
there's okay there's a shitload of content obviously
there's a lot of content it's very cool it's just
hard hard to learn let's put it that way hard to understand
what's going on uh but thank you too mostly lost for the one dollar
chat gets mad at you for choosing easy mode but then also gets mad at you for
putting points into useless categories i don't get it
i don't see the contradiction well the contradiction is the game needs to be
potentially on easy for those builds to work early i guess
were people actually mad at easy mode no i just got i just got made fun of for
like 40 minutes until i changed it i shouldn't even open up the fucking
menu it was when we got to the c raiders and i
beat the c raiders with only losing like two people and it was like wait a minute
hold on a second what difficulty you play it on you
fucking monster make chat the weakest wrestler in the next germa rumble
uh i already did that i've done that before
and it came back to bite me because they did very well they eliminated like seven
people so i'm not sure i want to do that again
local streamer is peer pressured into having a bad time
i didn't have a bad time though i had a bad time
you know where it really started to unravel when i thought that when the king
killed me and i then when i turned into an archer
and shot my own guy in the back because they changed my colors that's
where it unraveled at about the five and a half hour mark
uh but thank you mostly lost so much thank you to uh a pepperoni for the
three dollars hey jeremy what's up love you and what you do buddy do you have a
chance by chance uh plan on adding sub badges
for consecutive years beyond two yes when i'm gonna do a little overhaul
here with the graphics i'm gonna get some more stuff some more
animations and some more uh sub emote stuff should be good
superintendent chalmers thanks for dollar germ you're gonna let grandpa
stream apex legends like that new fortnight game uh no
i've heard it's fun but no we've got eye spy to play like
why don't like i'm like i'm like pushing the narrative
so hard like streamer plays warband can't handle warband rage quits
warband next day plays a video game designed
for fourth graders like can i make it even more clear
you know what i'm saying god damn it just i'm leaning into that one
people are gonna come because no but most people don't stick around for the
end of the stream hang out a lot of people just
kind of leave and they left with me being like fuck god
god damn suck fuck this game and they're gonna come they're gonna show
up tomorrow and i'm gonna be playing eye spy hidden object game
they didn't know i was doing that they weren't here for that imagine though
no i don't think i'll play apex i i've never even played it off stream or
anything i don't really get i'm not really into
those kind of games battle royale there it's cool but
it's not something i'm into i'd rather play eye spy
hey creation the cyborg thanks to the dollar i forgot to cheer whoops
uh hey germa i was wrong about the sun exploding it's gonna expand
and in 2050 a meteor will crash into earth
and yellowstone is gonna explode at any moment uh that's pretty that's pretty
dark dire things here i don't know if that's
all gonna happen uh how does oh then the magma germa you
know nothing about magma on earth tell me how
does that work when magma when volcano and lava come from magma
and ice uh thank you tingy for the one dollar metro exodus comes out in a week
are you still gonna go through last light no
i don't think i have enough time for that i don't have enough time
i'll end up doing that like weeks or months later
and all the people asking about ace attorney yeah i'm probably just gonna
wait for the pc port because it's probably gonna be much
better i have the ipad one and i was told explicitly
well don't that one sucks it's buggy it's broken it doesn't look
good and i'm like oh okay and hey it's coming to pc this
dude doing it like a pc hd port right but is it the same one
as the ipad one or is that they're doing it from the ground up
the ipad one is not the one to play first okay
change all the models to fiaz for mod i don't know uh thank you go go man for
the two bucks they say not like this thank you dr clay for the one dollar
your character is literally shrek from shrek 2
uh i think outfit wise probably not hair wise though captain worgen
thanks for the five dollars germa's playing mountain blade this is a dream
come true now you need to lead a regiment in the napoleonic wars i don't
know i've never played it but thank you captain worgen for the five dollars
demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar hey germa why are you wearing a
shrek outfit now everybody's on the shrek outfit huh
thank you timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar i missed the first hour and
a half of the stream to watch a shitty anime movie and i gotta say it was not
worth it love your streams thank you timmy tim
tan sorry about the bad movie hey creation
cyborg thanks for the one dollar uh i have two ideas for germa rumble
battles floygan brothers versus ed ed and netty
uh and shito sega or triko who's triko the dog cat alien bird from
last guardian that's old that's old triko
oh it is uh i got no plans for who's there yet maybe eventually i'll try to
think about it that was two years ago that was a long
time ago combine thanks for the one dollar hey germy how
many times did you die the ludwig and do you have any tips
uh i think a lot i think i'd probably like
at least 10 to 15 times till it would don't really have any tips for you
because i haven't played the game in a long time
it's been a couple years i think since i would really last played it
thank you flank tank for the three bucks didn't you say you were gonna do it
uh eye tracker stream or am i insane anyway might be fun for a more chill
hangout stream it's gonna be part of the bionic boomer
the bionic boomer stream will have eye tracker so
the what the bionic boomer stream i'm gonna have like keyboard pants
fucking like a virtual boy it's gonna be nuts
that's still happening yeah it is just not immediately
uh thank you dead move with the three bucks swadian knights are op level up
your swadians to them thank you the tip thank you creation
cyborg again for a dollar hey germ i found a movie scene that is it that has
where the sun explodes and vaporizes anything
um you can show chat if you want i don't think i want to see that
i don't want to see the end of the future how we could we're gonna be
vaporized no i don't want to see that that's scary
that's a scary thing and it might be a spoiler
hey wizard ribbit thanks for the one dollar plays game on easy mode boast
about victory with two times the amount of units
you gotta take you gotta get you gotta take your victories where you can
uh meep people thanks for the one dollar germa germa only reads big bits
because he hates poor people what no i read the big bits
because that's a huge monetary commitment and
it's the same reason why i try to catch the big community subs too
you know that's a that's like a massive drop of money
that i want to address it immediately that's a lot
can't explain if i just explained it he's nervous
what are you talking about i can hear him sweating oh yeah kenya
i just i put my armpit up to the mic you didn't hear
shit but thank you uh meep people thank you plutonium for the one dollar who is
this internet funny man me thank you plutonium again for three more
dollars eat his kids did you make your character so
disastrous that enemies run from you the characters sucked it's my own fault
dead moo thanks for three bucks always pick die works
seem good seem good uh wizard ribbit thank you for the three four five dollars
here wizard ribbit to be fair you have to have a very high
scale level to understand mountain blade the game is extremely hard
and without a solid grasp of siege theory most of the enemies will trample a
typical player's army there's also king harlow's buttery outlook
which is definitely woven into his characterization his personal philosophy
draws heavily from bounty or if you go literature for
instance now the real gamers understand this
stuff they have the intellectual capacity to truly appreciate the depth of
this game what to realize is not just hard it says
something deep about gaming as a consequence to people who dislike
mountain blade truly are not gamers of course they wouldn't appreciate for
instance the humor in the sea raiders existential catchphrase
i will drink from your skull which itself is a cryptic reference to robert
e howard i don't know this is the fucking rick and morty thing
i'm smirking right now just imagining one of those fake
gamers scratching their heads in confusion as king ragnar's genius
tactics unfold on the battlefield what fools how i pity them like a crying
laughing emoji face and yes by the way i do have my
mountain blade tattoo and no you can't see it it's for the
ladies eyes only and even they have to show their gamer license
they have to have beaten dark souls before another personal kid thank you
thank you moderately depressed for the one dollar what the fuck did you just
fucking say about me you ill you bastard i'll have you know
i was promoted top my legion and king yargulix party i've been involved in
numerous battles against the swadians i performed over 300 confirmed scalpatians
i'm trained in horse archery and in the top archery in the entire kingdom
you're nothing to me but just another looter
i would like to view the fuck out with precision led likes of which is never
seen before how many of these are back to back thank
you sacca sacca so zero for the three bucks if you
didn't know in battle holding minus on the numpad zooms out view and
looks better i had no idea the only thing the game told
me in the beginning was how to block and attack i didn't know
anything else thank you three bucks and good to know
uh burty boot tree boot tree nipples thank you for the
ten dollars it's all right if you turn it to default if you aren't having fun
then what's the point that was three hours ago and now i'm like
angry that i did it in the first place god damn it it's not fun why bother
yeah and i was even defending myself going like who cares if it's if it's on
like easy mode it's okay i didn't figure out how the hell a
lance worked until i was 200 hours in see like like do you see
you didn't know how a lance worked until you played the game for
200 hours you understand what i didn't know how it worked
just rub it in no i'm you and i are buddies
literally aim your horse at enemies and hold w well it's actually x
so that's not correct so the thing you just said
was it's it's holding x right you don't need to press x if it was on
auto you don't need to hold x you don't need to do that
wait everyone everyone's lying to me one of these days this is going back like
to what i was saying before one of these days my fucking house is
going to be on fire on camera and the cam's going to be on and
it's behind me is going to be burning you understand and you i'm going to look
over a chat it could be like house is on fire
your house is on fire dude not kidding you're so stupid what are you fucking
idiot your house is on fire i'm not going to do anything
i'm going to go i'm not supposed to be listening to you guys
and i'm going to turn and i'm going to play my ninja turtles turtles in time
jim if that happens a 50 dollar donation would warn you
your house is on fire people are calling you a fucking idiot
i could they might be real i could arm wrestle hulk hogan right now on my
stream and beat him and he could be like
where no i lost and i like he i beat him i destroyed him
and i still would be like weak i still wouldn't be strong enough
i i could i could go on tv i could go on live tv
right now like on like cnn and be awarded
the fucking nobel prize for science because i like i figured out like i i
figured out aliens are real and i found out i figured out the way
to stop them and they're interviewing me i'm on cnn
the lot the alien guy and i did it he's only got like 70 iq
i figured out a potion that you can drink that reverses aging by 40 years
you drink it and like jim carrey you go back 40 years
you're not even smart idiot oh now he's getting
resentful i bet he vaccinates too oh god
when i you would beat up a retired wrestler
i almost have turned my webcam on again i can't do that wealthy streamer talks
for hours about how much of a victim he is
what what are you talking about germ's gonna flash us one day
i already did yeah accidentally why i didn't i said arm wrestling like he
him and i like you ready and he's like yeah i'm ready i'm ready let's go
okay it's that that's what i'm saying like i'm not like
what all right let's go wealthy streamer were you a goofball as a kid yeah
germa only a few of us are being dicks god damn
uh thank you to where are we oh uh thank you creation the cyborg for the one
dollar germa did you hear about the super bowl didn't play sweet victory
yeah it was i thought it was gonna happen it's kind of bullshit all right but
okay like it's only three people being
assholes it's only three people being like mean
okay so if there's a hundred people in a room and there was a pot of beef stew
in front of you and one guy pees in it he's gonna eat
it or is everybody gonna go oh come on dude
what the you're gonna eat that i'm not gonna eat it
so am i doing it or is it your turn i'm gonna pee in all my food for the next
week wait what no um why would i do that all
right no very much left to go future gamer thanks to the one
dollar future gamer i think it'd be fun to have a multiplayer stream of this
where we get like 200 people into a game why didn't we do that why did i even
play the single player what the fuck is the point of that why
didn't we just do that why didn't we just start with that
because it would crash oh they would have wrecked you
it's okay uh thank you it's time for slime for the five dollars
uh 100 other 100 other messages but they're all true still one of the best
channels on twitch you deserve it echoing 100 other messages
thank you so much time for slam thank you for sticking around thinking of
being a contributor both monetarily and
creatively we've seen a lot of your work it's great
thank you so much thank you uh trust no one thanks for the one dollar hello
jeremy one day you didn't do the thing that everyone in chat wanted but some
time later you made something better instead
what did i do what is this
instead i played blitz the league
we have to watch this right now
nfl cheap shots well i don't want to watch that right now no break us back
in half
yes oh yes i'm so involved i love being scariest things caught by
drones no that was fucking great thank you for
that watch it i'm not gonna watch that i'm not
gonna watch scariest things caught by drones aka i went into like premiere or
photoshop and added it later i like breathed hot breath on the
lens and then put the thing in the air damn it all right hey great canadian
fuck club thank you for the insanely large amount of subs and
donations and also for 15 dollars let's get down to
business to defeat the nords did germa did they send us germa when we asked for
jex they did they did thank you melted clowns
for the one dollar appreciate it uh thank you also to one dollar to
trust no one oh i almost forgot remember that
life is pain oh you want to fight you don't fuck come at me
don't it was at this moment that he knew he fucked up
i did i did that it was that exact moment it was
i am monk thanks to the one dollar you thought the first gift was bad
uh this is gonna actually hurt somebody's brain so i just want to be
aware i like me looking at this hurts my head
so only click this link if you are aware that this could cause like an instant
headache like it's gonna cause an instant i'm
being i'm being very very real this link that is gonna happen just if
you if you're sensitive like photo sensitive
be fucking careful because that like actually hurts my head looking at it and
actually i think i think i like that's changed me forever
looking at it for five seconds that changed my it that mutated my
dna uh jay paul thanks for the one dollar do the
500 000 games hidden object game that had
chad now we're gonna do one tomorrow mostly lost thanks to the one dollar this
might be the first time i've seen you legitimately
rage quit a game i had to i had to i had to do that it was
it was like seven hours in i was like i'm done
i had to thank you the one dollar though jay paul and mostly lost
because you're the one that said that something rather thanks to the one
dollar i got the fluid in my delirious fever i thought the stream went on for
like 13 hours hopes you hope your tax fraud went well
have a good night what is the streams title
what is shirts twice why don't you guys ever tell me about my
fucking messed up stream titles shirts twice shirts twice
a lot of people did did they buy mountain blade will stare the course i
don't know warband tonight shirts shirts i thought you're really excited about
your shirts i'm fucking pulling your leg i'm just
pulling your leg but if you haven't gotten a shirt yet
they are available don't buy them thank you jared for the one dollar you're the
best thank you appreciate that uh lobotomized
teddy bear thanks for the one dollar i can't believe i missed my favorite
streamer play one of my favorite games trial napoleonic wars multiplayer as
well i know there's ever a lot of people
literally love this game and i like just it was a perfect storm of i there's a
perfect storm of me being frustrated i but the game is good i'd never told you
that it wasn't good i want to make that very clear i do
believe that this game is fun i do believe that the game is good
it was a perfect storm of frustration and i had to get out i scrolled down
couldn't figure out how to not buy one of your shitty shirts
the shirts are actually fantastic some of the best shirts i've ever seen
sold on twitch or youtube or any anywhere any store
anything in the world what that's awesome what is this
oh i paid seven dollars this week four hundred dollars from rent okay
that's awesome this game sucks but that was not
that was that was me joking uh why did i do that it doesn't
don't i don't want to like rain on somebody's parade because the
game actually is fun i'm just being i was just like zinging
i was not that was a joke i really was kidding there i promise
at the end when i clicked exit as fast as i could that was not a joke
probably the worst game i've played in a decade at least
honest to fucking god how do people think this is fun
seriously like i'm sitting here right now unfuck i can't believe that anyone
would play this game i think it's even remotely interesting
see every time i hit the bomb i click the bomb every time
like i'm not i'm sorry i'm just playing minesweeper right now the game is
fucking dumb like why is it on every computer i was
just kind of passing the time and doing bits and
playing minesweeper i don't know why i need to update that fucking game man
seriously hey thank you big fry for the 10 bucks
first donation but the game has little to no tutorial
so early game is really rough for new players
yeah i kind of figured that out firsthand i got very upset
i got very mad and it was not nice that's what i've heard
i've heard it's very rough to new players and it's very difficult and the
learning curve is huge but people were being very mean to me
perfect storm of fucking potions that i drank people were being very mean to me
weren't they okay like that's like such confirmation like just
bias right guys people being mean to me right everybody
say right say yes but thank you for the 10 bucks it is a good game
it's very difficult when you first get in there though uh sam watching stuff
thanks for the dollar hey jeremy love you streams if you can play dragons dogma
to the aisle done the bitter black aisle dungeon it's really fun
best part of the game the game is kind of tough but the leveling is a bit odd
but it's good that game is fun oh he's there he is play
he's he's yeah germa the victim there he is
no i'm just kidding dragon's dogma was very fun
dragon's dogma is mountain blade for what hey mostly lost thanks to the one
dollar no germa you have the wrong opinion fortnight is a trash game
and anyone who plays it is in the utter scum of the whoa
jesus stop reading my comments why uh mr squishy thanks for the three
dollars germa been subbed since your stardew valley streams holy shit
36 month resub any new sub badges for old boomers like me first of all holy
fuck thank you for being subscribed to 36
months in a row you've deemed this channel worthy of 36 months of
monetary support in a row thank you so much
i can't believe it some of you guys have been subscribed for so long
uh yeah i'm gonna do a little overhaul not an overhaul but like an addition
i'm gonna do an addition to the germa house here and we get some new
animations some new bit stuff some new backgrounds we'll get a handful of new
things here some new songs maybe uh but thank you mr squishy for being
here for that one hey ben thanks for the one dollar much love
thank you ben uh thank you creation the cyborg for the one dollar but germa
there's no one screaming or anything and the movie came out in 2009 please it's
amazing no i don't want to see the sun vaporize
everybody there's no one screaming that makes it
worse that doesn't make it better that makes it worse
thank you jules for the one dollar here's a vid from the from a mountain
blade mod you don't have to watch the whole thing
it's pretty funny and it might interest you get a mustache
team building exercises with
i feel like i played this game already this looks like um what was that game
the the copyright thing what was that game called
well we had like 100 people in the same server hold fast right it's pretty funny
i'll watch it when the when we get offline here
mount and musket thank you lobotomized teddy bear for the one dollar
here's a vid from a mod of mountain blade wait what
oh this popped up twice uh lobotomized teddy bear thanks for the one dollar
that's a nice head you have on your shoulder hey thanks
mostly lost thanks for the one dollar you think you'll ever finish up metro
last light so you can play the new one uh no i'm not gonna play the new one when
it first comes out i'm gonna be pretty late on it because i
do want to do last light and i'm not gonna do that for probably a
while so i'm gonna be playing exodus like with 50 trillion ping because
everyone's gonna play it on day one or day two and day three and i'm
gonna play it like two months later no one's gonna play it on day one
because it's on the epic store you know it's funny i have the epic
store on my computer not because i wanted to go get it but
because i was gonna do a fortnight joke and i installed that and fortnight
and i haven't taken it off it's too late now
but i'm not i will not be playing exodus on the launch
not until i complete last light and that's something i have to do on stream
you know what i'm saying hey superman thanks for the one dollar hey germ i was
wondering what you'll what you would have pursued if
youtube or twitch didn't exist something with animals something with
computers something with customer service not
necessarily in that order i did a stint at an animal shelter
and i loved it i would have done it for work if i could have
something in that field i like to talk i just like speaking i'm sure you've
noticed so something with uh something to do with
talking for a job somehow so a comedian no
probably not uh but thank you superman thank you gold
ruby production oops a daisy thank you uh thank you creation the cyborg the
the scene is only one minute if you skip to the movies basically a thriller
movie with nicolas cage trying to save as much people as you can when aliens
try and this is the sun thing again and when he
refuses it's hold on i don't want to read like
spoilers for a nicolas cage movie nicolas cage and the sun explodes
what movie is that the movie sucks apocalypse
just watch it i don't i'm not watching the nicolas cage son
i'm gonna get i'm not going to jail thank you future gamer for the one
dollar you missed the second part of my bits earlier
uh kraken played a cool war warband mod called total invasion
it's like 10 100 to 150 players versus giant ogres
skeletons and why did i play the regular game
i played like the hard learning curve campaign why didn't anybody tell me my
ass was so big one person got it that's all i care about
hey james thank you james the five dollars hey germ i've been a fan since
your early youtube days just want to say you've been such an inspiration
and you give me such joy and i thought it's about time to show my gratitude
thank you james for the five dollars thank you so much
i'm happy you have fun here and i'm humbled and shocked
and that i'm an inspiration to you thank you i hope it's a good inspiration
thank you so much hey novi 333 with 333 bits
i missed almost the whole stream but it sounds like the vod is going to be
pretty entertaining it's it i had a lot of fun it was a
very fun game what an experience thank you for the
three dollars and 33 cents hey james thanks for the one dollar
again hey here's some goofy fan art inspired by
the condemn stream way back uh unfortunately
this link uh is private account is private
i can't see what it is i cannot click that link i'm sorry
james thank you so much for any fan art maybe uh maybe you can throw it up on
some like a twitter or something or a different link
sorry about that james mostly lost thanks for the one dollar mostly lost also
if this isn't the new sub sound i'm gonna have an extremely mild
disappointment averns i don't know what that is
that was so loud i'm sorry it's like things i can't ever live down christian
cyborg thanks for the one dollar please jerma this is all i ask please
okay all right fine i'm gonna watch the sun explode
everything burns scene all right hey everything burns scene if you don't want
okay well i can't even tell you it's a spoiler
here's a spoiler for the movie knowing with nicolas cage
that the name of the scene is everything burns
okay so this is probably the end of the movie the whole
i everything burns so you're planning for retirement
this is not all right what was this oh it's fucking patent manic
retirement after planning for retirement
nobody buys that insurance nobody wants that insurance
why do you want me to see this why do you want me to see this
okay i don't understand hold on so what you won't skip to
this is spoiler if anybody's never seen this movie
i'm just trying to figure out why why that's something we
had to see wait what go to the actual part what are you talking about okay
what is it what do you want 330 336 it's almost the end of the whole
i don't get it is that the earth watch from here to the end
i all right okay that's enough of this that's enough of that that's enough
sorry nobody can watch that movie no i my eyes
are fucking hurt from laughing at that i'm i don't but
why do we need to know that was the oddest joke to take more than five
minutes i didn't set that up i was told i had to play
that like seven times but anyways uh
where the fuck are we um okay thank you creation the cyborg
for the sun video gondra lane thanks for the one dollar been a while since you
played a point and click adventure game
there's a certain game involving a police rabbit and dog with humor that's
pretty much written for you it's split into three seasons with
episodes and it's on steam love you though i wait the day did you play that
one maybe maybe it's in it's in the bag
it's in the back pocket writer but thank you gondra lane looks great
uh creation the cyborg thanks for the one dollar the movie is copyright free
uh i i would put any amount of uh vegas odds that that movie is not
copyright free i would probably put any amount of money
on that that's probably very copywritten it's
probably incredibly copywritten i don't think there's a nicolas cage movie
that's in the public domain but we showed it we showed it hey james
thanks for the one dollar hey the link should work now hopefully and this
seemed like the easiest way to link it but obviously not whoops well anyway much
love to you oh that's uh i know what that is that's
the hyper cam thing that's awesome that's the compressed
hyper cam stream look at that piece of art look at
that art right there hang that up somewhere in a museum
oh that's awesome thank you so much james that's amazing thank you
ego maniac you guys have a lot of fucking talent you really do
i don't know what it is with just this community in particular
a lot of people that know what the fuck they're doing a lot of people know what
they're doing a lot of talented people am i cool yet
mummy yes yes and finally creation cyborg thanks germa
thanks for adult now you know how the earth will die if it survives mercury
wish you watched the whole thing no don't worry some scientist is going to
figure out fucking a flute they're going to play and it's going to play a certain
tone of music that puts the cylinder around the earth and we're
going to be fine but let's put the credits up thank you
so much everybody god damn this is a lot of people how many
people sub tonight thank you everybody i had a lot of fun
in mountain blade it is a fun fucking game
please excuse the last the last the last like
42 minutes of the stream was kind of salty and annoyed
i don't like getting there but sometimes it happens sometimes it just happens
so tomorrow i will see you guys i'm gonna play i spy
i spy the uh the children's game i might not put the cap on
warband it was just i had to get out of there
i was reaching fucking i was reaching the levels that were unquenchable you
know what i mean i couldn't squelch them they would just they were coming up
oh the haunted mansion one yeah i've deleted three comments because they
were too mean with mods yeah let's i'm not going to
put the close the book on it that game has a lot of potential to be
fun i had to just drain the fucking water
levels you know i mean i had to just had to put the spigot in my stomach and
turn it on just hot water was coming out knowing was a video game at one point
but was cancelled i wonder why that was very politically
worded that game had a lot of potential to be fun
and i'm the son of a nobleman i've gotta say
in game i was the son of a no the in game i was a pr guy
let us pee uh what should be more shocking to anybody is i think i only
peed one time in eight and a half hours that's a new record for me right i
only did one i did one break holy shit i didn't even
realize that wow all right i will see you guys tomorrow
for uh i spy the children's game thank you all so much and then we was
gonna get a sequel how do you get a sequel to a game when
the sun explodes and destroys everything but take care guys see you soon
much love to you and good night