Hey, sorry, I forgot to unmute. I've been talking. I was talking for about five minutes.
Typing, hold on. Just doing a little bit of typing. All right, so hello. How are you?
Hope everybody's doing good. Welcome to another stream. I saw you yesterday, but you know.
Today, Dark Tide is launched. It's on Steam right now. Sponsored to play it. I will be sponsored for
the stream today. Game's really fun. I'm looking forward to playing again with another group.
We got, who we got in this room? There's a lot of people that want to play today.
We might be jumping around. We've got Ster. We've got Vinny. We've got, I'm being told right now,
we might have another one. Hold on. Yeah, drops are enabled too. Drops are enabled.
We need one more apparently. Okay, that's gonna be easy enough. Yeah, should be fun. I'm playing as
an Ogren. If you don't know, Ogren's the big guy. The great reveal of who the fourth player is
gonna be is coming up here very shortly. Yeah, there was like a pool of people that were
potentially available today and there's just whoever's around. Did you say what?
I'm no, I'm not. This is sponsored stream. I'm not gonna read that. How does it feel to be
the resident Twitch theater kid? Well, it's resident Twitch theater adult.
Um, I, I'm not, I'm an older, I'm older. I'm older. That's such a little kid thing to say.
No, I'm, I'm older. Oh, okay. I'm not kid. Okay. All right, let's get a call with the three we know
are gonna be around. I got my tweet out. Thank you again to Warhammer for sponsoring the stream
and the last one that I did. Launch day games out four player co-op. It's on steam right now.
I will make a phone call. We need to make a new group then. Actually, do we? Oh, all right. We got
people coming. We got people coming from all over the place here. Hold on. Hold on. The final,
hold on. It's down to we, and we can look, we can jump around. We don't have four players. If
there's like six or seven people that are around, we can just, we can, we can smush up the lobbies.
It's fine. Let me see it. Cause we were seeing if Kraken, Kraken was around. I think Kraken was
around, but if Kraken is not around immediately, then we will go with another person that has just
DM'd me and they will not be revealed until it is time. Let's see how this plays out in the next
60 seconds. Connor, do I have you on steam? Oh, I just ruined it. Why am I assuming that Connor
is watching the stream right now? He's not, is he watching? Oh, why am I just like, oh, hey,
yeah, man. Uh, you watch it. Hey, what, what, what am I, do I have him on steam? He's probably
not even here. He, he's probably, he probably DM'd me from the bathroom or something, right?
He probably like DM'd me from his, his kitchen. Why am I assuming he's just here? All right,
but we can get, let's get in a call first and foremost because, you know, let's see how this
plays out. I'm just going to, we're just going to call Kraken. I'm just going to call everybody.
I'm calling literally this whole group. So whoever, honestly, I'm calling this whole group,
whoever answers answers. Let me add the people here, but yeah, should be fun. Okay. And right.
Is he playing a game right now? I'm just calling whoever answers answers. Let's see what happens.
Okay. Oh, all right. Stir has answered. Stir answered the call. You are in, you are the first
contestant. I, I apologize. Uh, stripping said he was going to play with you, but after yesterday
and he figured out you can only do like two voices. He really wasn't interested anymore.
Oh, well that's okay. All right. Yeah. Boy. Hello lads. Hey, there's Vinny. Oh my God. You,
I turned you up way too loud. Okay. Hello lad. Hey stir. How are you doing? Shut up. You're too
loud. Wait, was he too loud? No, you're good now. You guys, did you guys do this? Is this your first
introduction to stir and Vinny? Yeah. I don't know who you are. Um, no, it's okay. This is good.
No, I think as content creators, the best thing you can do is not know who anyone is true. Yeah.
Then when you meet them, it's like, oh, good. I can like forge my whole persona now. Hello. Oh,
tragic past. Hey, Connor answered. So Connor's the fourth. Oh, hey Connor. Hello. Nice to meet you.
Hi. Hello. Oh, look, everyone's here. We did it. We got a group. Oh shit. Kraken just said,
I'm coming. Wait, if they're coming, I can go. I can go. If you guys know, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, you know, no. Hey, I did say, I did say I was calling first. It's true. You did call. I mean,
it's too late. All right. Well, let's just tell, let's talk right. I'm just going to be like this,
this guy, this guy, this guy, Connor got in the, in our DM group. This guy. All right. So Connor,
do I have you on steam? Uh, I think so for, for, for, uh, what's it called? The battleship. Oh,
that's right. That's right. Okay. So we did a war or risk. That's what it's called. So I should have
you. Also, Connor, I think we're following each other, but do we know each other? We know what
Vinny, I messaged you one time asking about your microphone. There's somebody who said nightmare
blood rotation. What microphone do you use? And you couldn't find like the cable. I couldn't find
the cable that connects to your microphone. Oh my God. How long ago was this, Connor? It's like
over a year ago and I still could, and I ordered a cable and it took two months to get here and it
was the wrong cable. Oh God. Yeah. Yeah. I understand this pain. I still have it to this day. Yep. I'll
hopefully I get the cable eventually. All right. So yeah, we'll, we'll cycle people in and out.
Uh, but just to get the, to get the ball rolling here, let's, um, so let me, I think it should,
I make the lobby or do you know how do you do it? Is there, is there a quick way? Oh, my character
sick. All right. Hold on. Let me see if I think I remember, but let me get in the game. I'll let
you know. I'm going to be just recording this. I didn't, I, I streamed earlier, but, uh,
German, thank you for the invite again, buddy. I appreciate it. Yeah. All right. So who, uh,
stir, I have you. So if I invite you to my strike team, you should get that. I have accepted your
strike team. I'm ready to strike. Okay. Now the, uh, other of you honor and Vinny, if you could
appear online on steam, so I could, uh, you know what I mean? Yeah, I, I would love to, but my
dark tide for some reason, isn't the most bizarre resolution I've ever seen. It's like one and a
half times my monitor. It doesn't make any sense. So I'll be in in a minute. Okay. Yeah. I'm currently
trying to get troubleshooting. Okay. If you want, you want just do one. You knew it was random.
They take a while. Do they take like 15 minutes? By the way, if you guys know that this is a
sponsored stream, I'm supposed to play. So wouldn't that be kind of messed up if we did it without
them while Kraken sat there? That's true. That would be kind of crazy.
Kraken, for Kraken's probably sitting there watching, going like, are you going to do one?
Just you and stir, huh? What the fuck is going on over there? I'll be like 60 seconds and then
I'll be ready to jump in. Yeah. Let's start one then. All right. Wait, what? Don't swear.
I'll be right there. It's okay. Look, does he take 10 minutes to get ready? Look, I'm going to,
let's put it up on the screen so people can see. Here we are. Hi.
Well, let's go over the characters, the character creator. Let's go over the characters.
All the lore. Oh, we're not doing that again. Top to bottom. And then we could start.
Actually, you know, stirred. How much do you know about 40k?
Well, I like every, literally everything. Do you, are you actually a fan of 40k?
No, I was going to start making shit up and people would just believe it if they didn't know.
Well, no, you shouldn't do that because I'm sponsored to play this.
Yeah. You can't do that for sure. I did that last time and I, yeah.
Okay. I was being a jerk. What level? You're 17. So you've been playing a lot. You must like it then.
Uh, yeah. I've been getting into it. It took me a bit. It grew on me.
Jeremy, you should let Criken in for now because I still got to figure out my stuff.
Okay. No, we'll cycle people in. So we'll get you in, Connor.
I'll let you know when I'm ready if I get it figured out.
Thanks for being available right here. No problem. You guys are fun.
Yeah. We'll see you in like maybe like an hour or so. We'll grab you in.
Sounds good. Good guy, Connor.
See you soon, Connor. Good guy, Connor. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Good guy, Connor.
All right. Hey, now somebody tell Criken to join. Why can't I do it?
He made like other plans probably. Yeah. What if he just jumped in the game?
Sorry. Yeah. My, all my, um, with the release, all my video settings got
changed. So I just had to go in and like mess with some options, but they're good now.
Can somebody read what Criken just wrote in the DM group?
He said, what is going on? And I said, we need you.
Can we just pretend this was like an elaborate joke?
Yeah. I'm on the toilet stall.
Okay. I can stall.
On the toilet stall for time.
Here is the Lord.
Oh, he's not standing on the toilet.
Right. You need commas.
That I do know is my character is prisoner.
My family lineage, we've all been prisoners. It's a last name.
There's no comma. Ladies and gentlemen.
Three generations back, my great grandfather said the emperor doesn't wipe.
And our family line's been in prison ever since.
That many generations? God damn.
Yeah. Actually, let me look. I want to look at my weapons.
So for those that don't know, Darktide is a four-player co-op survival game where you
have to fight waves and waves of incredibly dangerous enemies.
Those enemies can range from machine gunners to zombie-type enemies to monsters,
to other big, big, big things, right? And it's all about working together
and trying to stop. If you ever played Vermintide, obviously same company, same group.
And it's very fun. And I think that we should take a look at the items.
Well done.
I only have two.
Sir, do you have a purple? Like, do you have any purples?
I'll be right back once I guess.
Yeah.
What's your what's your weapon loadout look like?
I'm not using it. I've got this charge gun that blows people up.
I'm trying and an axe.
Ooh, that sounds pretty good.
You know, you can upgrade your anything to purple if you want it.
And I do apologize to everybody watching that the only content in the last
12 minutes of the stream so far has been me walking back and forth
down this hallway while I talk filler words.
I think it's been great content to tell Kraken to go away
and then ask him to come back.
Then need him. Yeah.
I mean, I've been doing laps around the hub.
Have you?
It feels like 20 minutes now. So I'm ready.
We'll be good.
Yeah.
How long has he been on the toilet?
So wait, was he truly ready at all then?
What if he what if he was on the toilet just typing like,
oh, what the fuck guys, I'm ready. I'm here.
And he's just like leaning down like this, like on the toilet.
He doesn't want to put on the.
Oh, wait, they they was a they did come out with a beta headgear, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it just said it's a helmet that has like a beta logo on it.
So you can prove to everyone that you're a beta.
Do I have it?
That's why I'm wearing it.
Yeah, I don't even know where it is.
I don't know how to access it.
Is this do I get it?
Should have it.
You press I and go to cosmetic.
Well, I don't have it.
Is it an accessory?
It's a head.
Yeah, I don't have it either.
That's weird.
I think this is the organs.
Maybe you had to reach a certain level in the beta.
I mean, I very clearly did not have this stuff last time.
Yeah.
When I loaded in today, I got a bunch of unlocks, like a ton of cosmetics and stuff appearance.
Speaking of beta, the game is launched today.
It's official.
No longer.
It's it is it is here.
It's on Steam.
They did a bunch of updates to like for the launch.
So did they excited to check out all the new stuff because I've been on level eight now.
I really enjoyed playing this.
Yeah.
No, they added like eight new levels that you can play through.
New missions.
And there's a cosmetic store that's different than the armory.
That's awesome.
Because the more missions, the better.
It's just that's a lot.
That's good.
All right.
So it's still on the toilet.
Sorry, everybody.
Oh, let me let me get you into the lobby.
Yeah.
OK.
Is you are you parent online?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Hang on.
Sorry.
It is it is Steam.
You have to tell it.
You have to tell everybody you're online.
What is your name?
What's your name on Steam right now?
Gas can.
No, it's just Vinesauce.
Oh, it's like, wait, I was like, that's me.
Says you're offline.
A lot of a lot of an animosity towards Steam every time I play games with you.
Like, are you ready to go to the Epic Games Store?
We're all ready.
I don't know about that, Star.
Bro.
OK.
So you should.
I got the invite.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right.
Now we're just waiting for Kraikin to finish his movement, his bathroom routine, whatever it is,
and we can get started, which should be pretty soon.
Well, I don't know.
I wonder.
There's been plenty of times where I've spent quite a while.
Yeah.
What?
Should we ask how long?
How long should we stall?
I'm going to laugh my ass off if he says, like, 40 minutes.
If he just tells us what he ate, we'll know.
Like, if he says White Castle or Taco Bell, we'll know.
How long should we stall?
You know, it'd be really funny if he joined the call and flushed,
like there was a toilet flush sound.
I mean, that would be pretty good.
I should tell him to do that.
I mean, it would be funnier if he actually never came.
He's just not ever going to be here.
Yeah.
Sponsor to run around the hub world for 20 minutes.
Where?
I don't want to be playing this.
Don't worry.
He says he's hopping on now.
All right.
Yeah.
OK.
Well, hey, the last time we did this, too, we're getting ready.
Hey, sometimes you get a group of four people together.
It's actually takes some time.
Yeah.
And it took longer last time.
So this is relatively quick.
This is pretty quick.
We got this down to like a well-oiled machine like Kraikin's bowels.
Dan, if Warhammer, if you're watching this right now,
this guy's walking around in circles in the hub.
What is he doing?
We're just getting ready and we're going to be good to go.
It's actually part of the lore that you praised the emperor by walking around the ship.
Yeah, we did do this exact thing last time.
So what's what's what new mission should we do?
This new stuff, right?
What should we do?
And by the way, I know I'm a I'm a two bar Andy.
I know that a lot of you guys might be three or four bar Andes.
No, the level that you guys are at, like three bars is pretty rough.
Is it? Okay.
Because you do you do get a lot of power through levels and.
Oh, you mean the the difficulty?
Yeah, two is two is good.
I'm fine with two.
And then if you want, like maybe at the end,
we can attempt to three like when we're all like really like awesome at the game.
Well, there's also twos that have like nearly infinite hordes.
Right.
And those are also pretty tough.
Okay.
Before you get all your your levels up and whatnot.
We'll start with two and then we'll move on to three after a few matches or something.
Yeah, we can give I think maybe we'll be good.
Like we'll be like well practiced.
Yeah.
But if not, it'll be fun for the audience to watch us fail.
So what about map?
Is there any of these new?
I think the one on the bottom have Draco might be new.
I don't think that was there.
But wait, I don't know.
Is this a two star?
Wait, because they had a new mission type.
So that's investigation, which I don't think was there before.
Some of them are the maps that were already in.
But you do them.
You go to like different areas of that map and do a different mission.
Oh, okay.
Not I haven't done enough yet today.
So I don't like fully know, but that's how it's going.
Hey, hey, hey, how are you?
I'm great.
Am I allowed to be here now?
Yeah, sorry.
Yes, we invited.
I invited you.
Then we booted you.
Then I invited you again and then you were taking a bathroom break.
I'm sorry.
That's my fault.
That's all.
It's actually all my fault.
It was I thought I, you know, I invited too many people to the party
and then like too many people said yes.
You all sort of said maybe on Facebook.
Like that's you know what I mean?
Yeah, you guys should have all clicked.
Maybe on Facebook instead of.
Still organizes all of his streams on Facebook
and we're asking begging him, please, please any other platform, man.
But he just he's addicted to that.
Maybe you know that will they show up?
I don't know.
All right, let's let's get you in here.
It's exciting.
This is actually that get the fuck in here.
This is actually pretty great because this is this is a team of players
that know what they're doing besides me.
So this is going to be great.
I mean, you're level seven, you know.
I got carried by literally by criken and yeah, that that criken and stripping
literally carried as I was even when we almost beat a five a couple days ago.
Are you online?
Yeah, I'm logging in now.
There you are.
But we'll be doing that later tonight.
I think we're going to try to go for broke.
I was.
Yeah, I was going to play this with a couple of my my mods today.
So this ended up working out.
I was going to check out the new stuff.
Criken, do you know which map for sure is new?
Because we're looking at the missions have Draco seems new to us.
That one wasn't new.
There was one up top that wasn't it just rotated out.
Oh, darn.
OK, there you are.
And if I do, I can't invite you.
All right.
I'm just going to cold open my stream.
One sec, man.
Dave, I promise we'll play this eventually.
This is the war.
This is OK.
You know, before a big theater production, all you guys are theater kids.
Like I was like, you know, we are like I am.
So, so before a show, we all sit around and we go like.
La la la la la la la la la la la la.
Right.
So and everybody just gets warmed up vocally.
So then we're ready to go.
OK, that sounded kind of like the Peewee Herman's big adventure theme.
Jerma, that was a cult.
No, it wasn't.
It literally was.
It was not it.
No, it's what are you talking about?
All right, let's see if I can get criken in here.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time for us to.
Hey, look, a lot of streamers have like 15 to 20 minute countdowns on their stream.
We haven't even started yet.
The stream hasn't even started.
We haven't begun yet.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was a public access guy.
I wasn't a theater guy, so we didn't really like warm up or anything.
We just made terrible television with no warm up.
What in German, German, whatever, whatever.
Yeah.
So, sir, how was your day since yesterday?
My day since yesterday, I've really just, you know, been having an amazing time living
like the most crazy life ever.
I'm gaming on a yacht right now.
I'm right off the back.
I can see the amazing Seattle Vista Skyline.
Oh, what the fuck is going on in my game?
Yeah, I think we're once this mission starts,
I'm going to hop in the helicopter and game from there.
All right.
So I'm getting a million items added to my thing.
Me too.
And video settings got reset, too.
I don't know if that happened to you, but just double check that you're all good.
OK.
Yeah, I hit level 30.
So it was like, oh, yeah, here's the rest of the game.
And they just updated it all at once.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Warhammer Darktide launch event.
It's here.
It's on Steam.
And I'm ready to queue us up.
So that was that was sick.
I'd ask to do that again, but I think you nailed it first.
Yo, what is up, guys?
This is episode number two of Darktide.
Stop, stop.
OK, so we'll be here.
You just inspired me to sub to Jerma with that voice.
Thanks.
All right.
So what are we cracking?
We ask you because you're level 30.
Damn.
Yeah.
Where should we go right now?
Where should we what should we do to experience the launch of the video game, you would say?
Let's see.
Is there some new stuff?
There's a few new areas.
Yes.
Refinery Delta 17 is new.
Vigil station oblivion is new.
Let's do the Vigil station and the five.
Let's do the three Vigil station oblivion three.
We'll start here, you know.
Oh, let's go to fives at the end of the day.
Oh, OK.
I'm I'm I'm actually really pumped.
Heck up.
I did a five a few nights ago.
It was like me, GMart stripping and I was the last one I forgot.
But we we got all the way to the final objective and like like four out of five.
And it was an absolute like it was so difficult, but so fun.
I really, really like it.
So what was the whole thing?
Five is like impossible right now, right?
Five is like insanely hard.
It's it's super hard.
It's because there's no limit to how many specials can spawn at a time.
And there's just constant hordes like literally endless, constant,
like just absolute room filled with enemies.
So you're dealing with all the enemies and also the specials.
And so you just have to be like super coordinated as a team
and bring like the right weapons for, you know, whatever the mission is.
You have to be you have to be perfect your gear.
Yeah, pretty much.
And it felt but like it's also doable.
Like if you just, you know, dodge and parry perfectly and don't get hit,
then you can, you know, just avoid all damage and like it's easy.
Yeah.
Jim Martin thing was level 19, actually, when we did a five.
He'd still like could contribute.
So it's like it's doable in lower levels.
You probably need a couple of thirties to carry.
Right.
This is probably loud.
Did I turn it way too high up?
Oh, look how pretty it is.
This looks like Vermintide.
This does.
Oh, oh, wow.
Oh, swamp level is a swamp level.
This is actually pretty sick blight town.
This is this is blight town.
Also, I just got to say, sir, I don't know if you know this,
but I literally remade the character from your campaign.
Or, yeah, yeah, of course.
I know.
Yeah, I had to.
I love the character too much.
This is literally what he looked like.
So I was like, I might as well make him again.
I mean, the tattoo, but yeah, yeah, you got to praise the emperor.
And yeah, looks great.
You wouldn't be able to read the emperor tattoo and survive.
So all right.
You guys ready?
This is a three bar.
This is my first time doing a three mission.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I figured let me hit like level 10 and then I'll do threes.
But yeah, you can handle it.
I'm ready.
We've never done this mission.
So what's worse?
They can have good luck.
Yes, they sharp.
Keep your head down.
Let's use those.
Stay frosty.
Stay.
Yeah.
We got a big guy over here.
Hey, guy.
He's nicely handled.
That guy's still alive.
What?
I thought he's dead.
Yeah.
Okay.
Kraken, what's your feeling on auto guns?
Because I'm using one right now and I'm trying to figure out if I like it.
Good for hoard clearing.
That's mostly it.
I mean, it depends if you can like aim down the sights and like hit specials.
I didn't really use them that much.
Okay.
Yeah, because I'm not sure I'm going to stick with it, but I'm just trying it out.
Also, yeah, the game just launched and I'm sure they added a bunch of stuff and I literally
just booted it up and joined this.
So I've not had a chance to look at any of the new things.
You know, I don't know all the answers now.
Why does he look like a bodybuilder at this angle?
Holy shit.
I'm keeping this angle forever.
Try like widen my shoulders up.
You need to slowly over time start like integrating like Instagram filters on your webcam.
But very slowly.
Like, yeah, like a five percent at a time.
Yeah.
So people don't notice right away.
And then like a month from now, you're just jacked.
Wait, so Joe built that in with channel points.
And if you do a channel point redeem, you can lower the opacity of his camera by 5%.
So you can slowly fade away.
Wow.
What was that?
Yes, snipers do like all of your health and death.
Yeah.
I think like 90% of my deaths are, oh, there was a sniper.
Somebody sniped.
Explosive guy.
Oh, we got a shield guy over here.
Oh, God.
Guys, we've got to learn these names eventually, man.
It's called a scab bomber.
Shield guy.
Why can I not think?
Fire guy got me.
I got you.
I got you over here.
You can also pick people up.
You can hold right click to block while picking them up.
Oh, OK.
He's got the chainsaw.
Oh, my God.
Got you.
Bad day.
Yeah, that I need to dodge more and I need to block more because I was
mainly used to shooting a lot.
But I'll get it.
I'll get it.
You're good.
I mean, when in melee, if you're not swinging, basically just I'm holding
right click for block.
You know?
Yeah, sure.
So just in between the animations, you can just throw it up in case there's
an attack coming out.
You don't see the block is actually amazing in this game.
Yeah, it's it can take a lot.
I think I also have a counter attack with my blade because like the other
button like brings it up for a second.
Yeah, you can kind of mash that and throw that in between swings too
because it doesn't really take time to do.
It's just use the stamina when it triggers.
Gotcha.
What was that?
Horde.
Grenades here, lads.
Oh, what does that sound?
We got a mutant over here.
Oh, smash.
Help.
Oh, that was you.
What the heck is another one?
All right, I got to I got to get back into the game here.
Grenade.
Hey, what the heck?
I don't know why I'm doing that right now.
Somebody said it and it got in my head and I won't get it.
I can't.
It won't leave.
What?
What the heck?
Oh, yeah, I've been saying what the heck on ironically for like two years now.
Why is it infiltrating my head?
Well, that's how bro got into my vocabulary because I turned against bro
because my high school was all just like, yo, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro.
And then the past couple of years, like people say it ironically online
and I'm like, what's up, bro?
Yeah, I'm same.
I've been doing that, too.
That's weird.
Sir, sir.
We're coming.
Yeah.
Gunners down.
Machine gunners down here.
Let's try to.
Holy shit.
Oh, I'm just dead now.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
You're good.
I thought I had way more help than that.
Oh, that's bad.
That's bad.
Oh, I'm done.
Oh, that got that got hairy.
I think we're I think we're OK, though.
I believe in you.
All right.
Thank God, there's two of you that had that are very good.
I was the first to go down.
Am I on that list?
Yeah.
I was the problem.
Oh, you were the issue.
It's all right.
They might have made the threes more difficult
because this is how do I get up there?
What the hell is that?
How do I get up to Vinny?
I recognize this this music.
Oh, you did it.
Thank you.
Oh, it's this friend again.
Oh, the beast.
OK, let me get behind him.
No, he ain't that guy.
He did eat that guy.
It was like a frog.
That was great.
Wow.
Is there ammo anywhere?
Oh, geez.
Or a little bit more.
Stop saying that.
Well, Smush, you just got like a bomb exploded.
Do we walk past the Medicaid?
I feel like I feel like we did.
Right.
Because there's no way there's hasn't been yet.
Yeah.
Maybe like some random corner we missed.
That was intense.
Dog dog.
Gotcha.
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
Sometimes, Jerma, you'll know what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Sometimes they run at you and they make like noise,
but it sounds exactly like the imps from Hearthstone.
And I think like someone's playing an imp.
I hear it all the time and it weirds me out.
Do you know what I hear all the time?
And some of you guys might know this.
The Warcraft wolf sound that goes.
Do you know what I mean by that?
Definitely in the Hound Warcraft 3.
Yep.
No, just like World of Warcraft, the wolves, they go.
It's a very distinct sound.
Okay.
All right.
We have a lot of medication here.
I think someone should get it and either me or.
Yeah, I can hold off on getting it because I, you know,
I just need some regular meds first.
Yeah, I got some regular meds too.
However, I could use ammo.
If anyone finds any ammo, please let me know.
Yeah, I do too.
Bad.
It's nice to bang.
Yo, sorry, bro.
Oh my goodness.
Wow.
Oh, no, no, no.
Like I threw a grenade at his own team.
What are they doing?
Those are mine.
Oh, oh.
I'm chucking.
I generate a lot of grenades.
So I just throw them around.
Okay.
I got a grim war.
I grim.
I can't stick my head out here.
There's a gunner out there.
That's bad.
You can dodge these guys.
Check it out.
Wow.
That was sick.
Did I do that?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
You did it.
It's fine.
I'm all right.
I'm sorry.
I just Steve Urkeled, by the way.
Did I do that?
Oh my God.
All right.
That sniper just walked up into melee.
He walked up, started reloading, and then it was like, wait.
Wait a minute.
Wrong class.
Thought I was on my other character.
That's a lot of people.
This is going well for a three.
Yeah, it actually is.
Not bad.
You're still alive.
Oh, ammo.
Oh, German.
Yeah.
Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, you got it.
Like I still live.
I keep smushing this guy's head.
He won't die.
Is he all right?
All right.
Oh, I can drop some healing.
Let's do that.
Oh, yes.
Is this a sponsor stream or can we say dick?
I mean, you could.
Minus 20 bucks for each time dick is set.
You should do that, dude.
Like a swear jar for sponsored streams.
Yeah.
Darktide is like a really family friendly.
There's nothing weird about this game at all.
No disturbing themes.
In fact, Warhammer is for the whole family.
This guy.
Come on.
Die already.
All right.
Oh, we all can heal here.
Got him.
All right.
So now.
Yeah, this is perfect.
We need all of this.
It's got four.
Yeah, four.
Oh, perfect.
Yeah, but I need to do it twice.
It's my character's fatal flaw that he has to heal twice every time he heals.
Sorry, guys.
I don't make the rules.
What is there?
Was there no ammo crates?
Um.
No, I didn't see anything.
There's one tiny one up here.
Who has no ammo?
Oh, is this the right thing?
Are you sure?
How much ammo do you have?
I a little bit.
I'll just melee.
I have to get better at melee anyway.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
I was going to give it to you.
Did I sneeze?
I just accidentally clicked.
She yelled Biff.
It wasn't even.
It was like a very weird annunciation.
Wait, what did you think I said?
Biff.
Hey, Biff.
What did you say?
I sneezed.
That was like a fake sneeze.
Someone sneezes just goes Biff.
Why would that come through like that?
I don't know.
It's exactly what it sounded like though.
I'm not making it up.
Get that ammo.
Throwing a grenade.
Nice.
Do you think everyone on Earth has a unique sneeze, like a snowflake?
Kind of.
I have a duck sneeze.
I saw like a duck one I sneezed.
Yeah.
I'm like.
I don't know if that thing's called.
Dog.
Call it by just the correct name or I'm not helping you.
What is this?
Scab dog?
Scab dog.
Hey, what's up?
A flesh rot.
Ooh, actually, I don't.
I wish this was ammo.
Mine's a cipheridin.
Cipheridin.
Anyone need grenades?
Hey.
Oh, yeah.
This part of the map has a weird song.
A weird song?
I heard that.
It's a little synthy thing.
I don't know what it was.
I'm still confused.
It is a different song.
Gotta go cyberpsycho on these guys.
Time to chrome up.
Time to chrome up, Chum.
Ooh, I kind of like it.
Guys, I'm not good at this.
I'm being attacked up here by someone with armor.
Come, come, come, go, go, go, go.
Like I tried to dodge and block.
I was failing.
I was bad at it.
So I don't know if they changed it for the launch, but in the beta,
your class, Vinny, gets the strongest melee weapon of the game at high level.
So that's kind of when your melee pops off.
I don't know if you have a lot of melee stuff before then.
I only have the most basic stuff.
I'm not really crazy about it.
I felt like when I leveled and got past level 10,
I just suddenly got a million more options and it was a lot.
Help!
Are you, are you in my class too, sir?
I don't know.
What am I doing over here?
Why am I so far away?
You just ran backwards.
All right.
Oh, you found it.
Oh, no.
Okay.
So this mission is a weird one.
We have to use press four.
You take out a little Game Boy and then we go to scan different things.
Oh, yeah.
And then proceed.
I got grabbed.
I'm getting smushed.
Izzy, you're going to have to deal with that on your own.
Okay.
I got one.
Nice.
That was huge.
You got two already?
All right.
No, yeah.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where's this guy going?
What the hell?
He lives to trap another day.
I do like that.
They actually leave like they missed.
They're like, oh, fuck.
I'm out of here.
Another one.
Izzy.
Oh, he just hang.
He's just hanging over there.
Here he comes.
What was he doing?
What were you thinking?
Grimoire over here.
Oh shit, really?
Yeah.
Grimoire.
Are we feeling brave?
I'll pick it up.
What do you guys think?
Yeah.
Dog.
Dog dead.
Not dead.
Dog alive.
No, I'm about to die.
If I die, Parma, I'm going to drop a Grimoire.
Oh, that's bad.
Shit.
All right.
They're coming.
It's gone for good.
It's gone for good now.
Dog on me.
Yeah, I usually want the tanky people to pick him up.
Oh, I didn't know that.
What the fuck?
They keep using the same exit strategy.
Smart ass dog.
Is the dog still alive?
He's roughing at me.
Don't forget to use the...
It's the bodies in here.
Oh, thank God.
I just...
What did I just...
Oh, okay.
We need ammo, don't we?
Does everybody need it?
You got it.
It's an ammo case.
I do.
You drop it.
Okay, I'll put it down.
I'm back.
Thank you.
Who's doing that?
What the fuck?
There it was.
There was the imp...
I'm dead.
For real dead.
I'm sorry.
I'm screaming too much.
Stressful situation.
Dude, I had a large coffee this morning.
I'm sorry.
My God.
Okay.
Are we all right?
We're okay.
Thank you for saving me.
I'm prisoner.
You're welcome.
Prisoner.
Make sure to get the ammo.
Are you a prisoner?
That's super smart.
If you guys didn't get the ammo,
make sure you get it.
You didn't hear my whole backstory.
It's a whole thing.
Hey, if nobody got it.
Seriously.
All right.
We have one more.
I think back...
It's where Vinny is right now.
I'll lead the way.
I do like this music.
This whole game has had good music,
but I check how weird and...
Cynthia it is.
Oh, I'm being attacked.
I just pressed F instead of E.
How dare I?
I'm throwing.
Oh, my God.
God damn it.
That's going to be the reason why we lose
because of that.
Because I pressed F.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
You know what it is?
It's that I have an axe,
and axes are not the best crowd control, right?
Yeah, they're really bad for crowd control.
A good one on one.
I have an axe for...
They're all...
They're good at single target,
and then I have this charge gun
that is good at single target,
and then I'm getting boarded.
They're coming from behind here.
I feel like I'm inside the game right now.
Is my music too loud?
It gets in your head.
You're definitely like very mercy.
They're shooting at us.
Is this the pile of bodies?
Was it here this whole time?
Oh, my God.
It was.
All right.
Head back, guys.
We did it.
We got to head back?
Okay.
I thought that was you,
Sturr, for a second hitting me.
Oh, yes, me prisoner.
I get that a lot.
Has anyone ever called you Sturr fry?
No.
Can I?
How did I miss?
Sometimes when I make a Sturr fry,
they'll say Sturr fry.
Oh, my God.
It hurts.
I just took 100 bullets in the head.
Thank you so much.
You need to use the stealth mechanic more.
We just got to run.
Oh, that was a lie.
I just crouched, dude.
I'm taking all my anger out on you.
See?
Look at how much I just fucked that guy up.
Just threw him.
Yeah.
There was a lot of anger behind that.
Oh, they should make like a melee thing
for the auger.
And we just grabbed someone by the face.
So this giant just chucks them.
I'll use them as a range.
What's that guy going?
That guy's just running.
Why are we all laughing at this guy?
I need to kill him.
I can't hit that.
Yeah.
Next time, let's call the elevator before.
Smush.
Oh, he's just blood thirsty.
I know you just fiending to kill,
but we're good.
Surprise.
Jerma's blood lust knows no boundaries.
Blood thirsty.
A dog coming in.
I love the acting in this game.
The voice acting is so good.
Yeah.
So pipe back.
Dog.
Ow.
Oh, ouch.
Owie.
Ogre.
Big ogre man.
Big ogre man just threw me.
Oops.
Save Copernicus.
Oh, no.
Put him down.
Oh, shit.
There's so many over here.
Did your guy actually just start going nom, nom, nom, nom?
Am I crazy?
What?
Enemy.
Okay.
I don't know what's going on.
It just devolved into it.
No idea what these things are.
Special enemy.
Ammo over here.
If anyone needs it.
Special enemy.
I could hear the strain in your brain trying to get the words out.
I can't even like rack my brain like appropriately because I'm just like scared.
Oh, look how pretty this is.
Yeah, this looks great.
Oh, what?
Demon host.
All right.
Do not walk up to that thing.
It's going to be like a icy ground.
Just walk around it.
Don't look at it.
Don't, don't.
What?
You did it.
Oh, no.
Should we run?
Don't shoot it, don't shoot it, don't shoot it.
Just run.
Don't shoot it, don't shoot it.
Wait, there's ammo over here.
Okay.
Oh, we're not okay.
It's bad.
Oh, my God.
It's on German.
Wait, did I, did I aggro it?
I thought it was already aggroed.
I thought we already aggroed it.
It was just waking up and then you kept going into it.
I thought it was already aggroed.
I, oh.
Oh, he's on me now.
This is bad.
All right.
It leaves after it kills too, I think.
Yeah, but I'm trying not to die if I can help it.
I thought it was already aggroed, so I thought it was safe to get the ammo
because I thought, fuck, we're going to fight it anyways.
Okay.
Nice.
Well, actually, technically, you got it, Kraken.
Oh, cool.
It said Copernicus got the kill, so.
Yeah, I'm a bleed build, so.
All right.
Oh, that makes sense.
That was the, hey, this icy ground over here
and every person in the party, I just watched like, oh, like this.
What, was this it?
We just waltzed on in.
It slips on ice.
For my defense, I thought it was already aggroed to the party.
Yeah, yeah.
In my defense, I actually, I acted perfectly and appropriately,
which gives me the high ground here.
Hey, remember when you died first that time
and said it was all your fault that we almost lost?
I was being nice to Vinny.
It's not so nice to reveal that.
That's very rude to reveal right now.
Hey, if you're going to aim your gun at me,
I'm going to pull out all my firearms.
Yeah, but Vinny didn't, I, you should have made,
you should have talked shit about me.
You, like, from my perspective, you are like a vacuum for Vinny
because I don't really know him.
Yeah, from my perspective.
I'm going to attack your friend.
From my perspective.
Yeah, like you got, you two are on like one side
and I'm not a part of it.
Can't we all be on the same team?
No, no, we're, we're, we're part of it now, Starb.
We're all in this together, buddy.
Come on.
All right.
And we all agree.
I mean, technically it was free aggroed already
and I just fall on aggroed.
It has two phases of aggro where it's crying like a witch
and then it stands up and goes.
Yeah.
And then, yeah, okay.
Now you know.
All right.
So you aggroed phase two.
So I'll, I'll take the,
I'll go 50-50 on somebody for the loss there.
I'll, yeah, I was the first one aggroed.
So I'll take the first 50.
Oh my God.
Did you see that?
What did you just do?
What the hell?
Vinny, it's remarkable that you grabbed the banister.
I know my character's reflexes are like.
All right.
That was like a gymnast.
Before he started.
Are they like precogs?
Like people that have like.
We can't.
Yeah.
Right.
Like psychokinesis and stuff.
Okay.
Let's, let's do it and immediately be ready to go.
I think it's going to start a bridge, right?
And then we run out.
Yeah.
Okay.
Can I play?
We're working on it, man.
Maybe don't die next time.
Oh.
No, no, no, I'm good.
I think I'm good.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
There he is.
Oh, yeah.
You're a squishy little boy.
Just keep going backwards.
Yeah.
I'm going to go backwards and attack.
And I'll just thank you for the grenade that helped.
Oh God.
They got guns.
Untie me.
Little one.
Terrogate the security stacks.
Holy shit.
It's a whole thing.
Yeah.
I think this is like, um, no, there's one more thing.
I think a skull.
It's actually a servo skull.
Come on, dude.
Technically, the consciousness is sometimes still attached to the servo skull.
Listen, I could tell you everything about the Blade Runner universe.
Yeah.
It's only two movies.
It's easy.
Name every blade.
Is that the one with the vampires?
Oh my God.
I fell asleep during the new Blade Runner in theaters.
Oh, no.
You fell asleep during Blade Runner?
I saw like 30% of that movie, but every once in a while, like dramatically in a scene,
it has like a big like, I woke up like a bunch of times instantly.
I went right back to bed.
So why did you go see the movie so tired?
Uh, you were just like exhausted.
I don't think I was tired.
I think the movie made me tired.
Wow, that's so okay.
I saw the first part of the movie.
That's crazy.
I went to see Mad Max Fury Road after pulling an over 24 hour thing with my friends.
And we like just showed up the movie like completely blurry.
I do love Mad Max Fury Road.
I think was made better that I was like so sleep deprived.
Like every single like rumble in the theater.
I like felt like it was rocking me to bed.
I'm trying to think if there's ever been a movie that I've fallen asleep to in the theater.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think I have either.
Not in the theater, but at home plenty.
Yeah.
I was I was watching Scorsese's last movie, The Irishman.
It's like four hours.
I fell asleep like five times.
Wow.
But I, you know, just to resume.
Sorry, I was supposed to talk about Warhammer, right?
Sorry.
Yes, Scorsese's Warhammer.
Right.
There's another one of his lost movies.
It's actually a huge 40k fan.
All right.
Starring the Rock, right?
That's it.
He's in the jungle and he's wearing like a tight brown t-shirt.
Someone like doesn't say something kindly about the emperor and he does the eyebrow
and the crowd is like, what?
Yeah, you know, you know, it's about to go down.
Do do do do do.
I'm surprised there's has there ever been a Warhammer like T movie or like TV show or
anything?
No, we can't talk about this anymore because drama did like the loud music over
our conversation indicating like he wants us to stop.
Yeah.
Like I don't like the award ceremony.
So I joined this conversation.
That was also the Rock's theme song.
And I was just being a part of the group.
Rock is a theme song?
yes oh oh oh no never mind sorry it's me the rock
he's like you can't see me and then he braces his eyebrow and gives you the people's fist
this is gonna be sick this is gonna be sick this is gonna be sick it was don't blow up though
well i blew up behind you copernicus i blew it up real good stay with the group sir it'd be great
if uh we wiped the mist because of hounds too the correct end for copernicus i got it true
a hound takes you down in a pit of fire all right i'm gonna come over here took me a minute to even
realize sorry about that like were you muted no i was checking my phone this button
five minutes till your birthday we've got to celebrate it
hey serious some chat member somebody in chat we're gonna celebrate it it's five minutes till
your birthday we gotta celebrate it hey serious you want to celebrate celebrate by playing more
warhammer yeah five minutes all right four o'clock specific ready then we go here looks like uh we
got another we got another thing i think it's one more new objective escape wait okay this
button should not be lit up that's a fake button go this way fake button fake button fake button
oh okay fake button yeah it's lit up for some reason but we don't actually have to use it
oh okay we just gotta go yeah all right now covering fire we are leaving soldiers
it's the same developers as vermintide it is it is the same developers really interesting like
musical motifs and chord changes i'm really enjoying it's also available right now on steam
launch day currently available just came out of beta it's available get it on steam getting all
these uh freaking rewards plus 20 bucks you know it uh music artist is just for kid he makes a lot
of my favorite video yeah so that was done just for kid he's done vermintide he did some assassins
creed uh he did borderlands i think it might have only been one of the dlcs i think it was all the
borderlands music goes super hard now i hit man games then i'm telling you the vermintide hitman
games yeah love though love that stuff that when when the rats are about to to rush with a horde
that i'm telling it's one of my favorite sound effects favorite pieces of any video game in
history you hear them all like screaming and you hear like the tide coming towards just something
about it it's that like they're like chanting it's terrifying it really it's one of my favorite
things i didn't even play vermintide that much it really is still one of my favorite things
that's the uh this game whenever you fight the uh the captain i just like mute everything turn the
turn the music up yeah that's the perfect look all right so i gotta buy some new stuff do um
oh wow if i'm watching your stream germa but it's paused or no do you get dry i don't know
that's a good question just for drops yeah i was like just to check your chat and stuff
but uh i can unpause it to give you i think it has to be unpaused i think you have to be like
watch time drop it down to 240p get a backpack minimize i like the difference okay getting the
job done i got you in 160p right now germa and you look like like i got a vaseline filter over
your screen can you do that well tell me how it looks now let me see um your pectorals are
bursting through the vaseline i don't think you've got the brains really because i didn't do
anything i just lean back oh okay oh what's this kubrick stare i i hate to do this to you guys do
you have a favorite kubrick movie um i don't know i have to like i'd have to list them out gotcha
because there wasn't very many right no it was there was only like what like seven eight something
like that 10 yeah all right let me go to the uh is the armory uh available yeah uh yeah the
armory's available there's also the other way first time seeing these microtransactions you
get like gucci pants for the zealot dude what's this ahoy but you can call me my lady i want a
hellbore laser gun i hear that one's good oh and don't bother telling me your name my darling
they are really fun i've been using it a lot but it gets hard to aim at things
oh really is it's uh it's like iron sights and then also the front of your gun glows red
but it's a really fun gun i want these i've got 2500 gamer coins yeah i do
oh let me look at these jacket oh okay i got the hellbore i'm gonna upgrade it and
see if i like it all right it is it is somebody's birthday happy birthday what was their name
happy birthday isaac is it your birthday today happy birthday isaac kicking ice cream is on its
way yeah and yes uh those chat members barry linden is my favorite uh kubrick movie i didn't
all right i don't know why i'm an idiot i need some kraken knowledge they edit they edit percentage
numbers to the uh the sliders on the stats for weapons i don't think that they had the
number there before oh yeah the number is new yeah i i guess you wouldn't know then maybe because
it's like 50 seems average and it very rarely goes above 50 it's so as it was explained to me
the eye level like the rating of the item itself is how much value is then randomly distributed
amongst these different uh you know what the hell is this thing have you seen any that are
actually like one of the bars is almost full um my pistol is 79 full on damage and 74 on mobility
so it's like it's i think like pokemon if you ever played that like yeah yeah like distribution
right i was just worried uh wondering because like every item that i've seen and have is like
it doesn't go beyond 54 percent yeah same here for yeah i think it'll get higher as you get more
so this the i i just unlocked the second row i guess of items that i can get a charm or something
yeah so curious you can equip and it will um you can like get additional experience per level you
can get additional money because it has a blessing and a perk it's like blessings and then perk
should i buy this i'm gonna get it buy them so i would buy one uh there's currently a bug
apparently that if your toughness if you buy a toughness trinket and it goes above 100
uh it doesn't actually protect your health like it's supposed to so i'm actually having to
unequip them on my guy so okay but other than that i think it's uh good for grinding experience
and good for grinding uh money even i don't think maybe i should get another weapon what do i got
does this thing better than i have yeah i got the hellbore laser and i upgraded it to blue
so i'm hoping it i like it because otherwise that would have been a bad choice i'm gonna try this
the plus one wound means you can go down one more time oh wait i can be downed twice yeah
and on the higher difficulties we start off with less wounds so it's good for um yeah limiting how
much times you go down or for higher difficulties you need plus wound trinkets that's cool i'm gonna
try this looks cool it's like uh i think i tried this once maybe before that's a good question when
do we get the warhammer um i already have it zealots get the warhammer no no time to time to
reroll it's pretty fun all right cool you beat the game then yeah well no you have to get to
collect 40 000 war hammers actually it's it's kind of a grind so what else is new um let's see we got
i think we hailed we did that we handled that pretty well oh no that's not i don't think that's
new actually um we can handle the three when we just did handle the three i mean it was a little
hairy but we did it yeah you want to do another hairy three yeah now that we have a little
practice and we know we know how to like shoot better and stuff i think we can do another three
that's so much money you get 14 15 000 gold to do um to do a four so much let me know what you guys
think of my new drip yeah me too oh nice i'd like a gimp's mask yo nice goggles smush yep what they
were saying earlier in the other group your mask is avoiding your hair yeah it's the perfect
haircut for this mask all right i think it's the other way around your hair is avoiding your mask
you are completely comfortable in that thing yeah all right lads
get ready the bat why do i do the bat chest face i know i do it and it's annoying to me
you do i do i go like and like i like i know i'm just the bat chest i want a pistol
so how does this oops okay no all right so yeah i've used this before it has a stab
so just to confirm everybody the audio levels music chat everything sounds good sometimes hard
to tell when uh yeah that's an issue i have too i always have to confirm it's such a streamer
paranoia thing it is germa there were okay so i do a lot of pre-recorded stuff too and um i was
having an issue with my sound drivers and my uh card and i recorded several full two hour long
like segments with bad audio i could not fix and and two times i had to like redo my commentary
that's the that's the worst you don't record it on like separate audio tracks
no no no uh you know i was pre-recording like just kind of a let's play kind of thing and um
yeah it was like yeah it was separate audio but my voice was totally ruined
oh because like um that's my vst hosts so i'll give you an example i sounded like i sounded like
this i was like hey what's up guys uh today we're gonna be doing uh what the hell that sounds great
you sound like you're coming coming out of an old arcade cabinet yeah it really does like a
pinball machine everyone it's me vinny we should be playing some video games let's all turn it on
everybody do it let's all turn it on for like a little bit what what do you mean turn it on
everybody turn it on just turn it on i always have it okay yeah i turn mine on what the hell is that
who is talking right now kermit the frog here kermit the frog dude you just sounded like
just a real different guy yeah do that again a bit cracked when it comes to voices do it again
all right yes sir all right i'm gonna do this for the rest of the level now
oh it's all you gotta do is really strain your jowls you just sound like a
strain your jowls force the air out the mail anytime chat member game if anyone needs it
strain your jowl oh fuck oh demon host don't shoot it you know what i had homework this week
to do that i was not straining my jowl i didn't do it this time nobody makes fun of me
yeah that was germa it's well it's trying to eat me now so it was probably me everybody because i
didn't know what i was shooting at i'm sorry all right see you guys on the other side of the level
good luck reload the gun already bye why i even shoot it why me why me why is he killing you
it picks two people to kill and then it leaves what what about this dog oh let's restart restart
restart restart restart no you can do it you got this just be brave you've been training for this
where do we need to rescue them we haven't spawned yet i don't think uh if you wait here i think it's
more likely we spawn closer to you i see uh kraken over there hey kraken how you doing huh
hey how you doing yeah should we just all talk in like kermit s voices but not don't over don't
overdo it though make people believe this is what you sound like like if people just join and they
don't know already and they're like wait yeah yeah yeah i mean that a little don't go too far though
just a little what does don't go too far mean that wasn't uh what i did like doing this is
a little too far but i'm just talking like just a little bit all right just a little just a little
bit hey what if oh it's a great title for uh for a video right where yeah kermit the frogs play
hold on let me just make sure i get through this
come on come on come on come on oh oh hold on
hold on restart this actually restart it's not a restart if you clutch it vini i'm sorry but
under i can get you okay all right
give me that he's gonna use all the healing just give me all the loot i don't care
what's your kick kermit you're the sniper
excuse me excuse you that is cool i need that where is he going i don't know
i thought that was an entrance i hate this kermit bit please stop well one person said that we
were we had to restart wait look we got spawned on by the big demon thing in the very very beginning
let's restart yeah we did get spawned on with big demon thing that wasn't our fault that was not
our fault just restart it was uh it was a bug yeah it definitely wasn't me that activated that so
for sure well good because i was about to blame you that was close that is delicious what is it
green tea a rarity it is a great it is a green tea energy formula not like a real coffee
i like green tea kit kats have you ever had those no they sound pretty good though awesome
what makes it green there is matcha powder in it so that's what makes it green
all right req redo i actually don't think i want to use this weapon it's just unfortunate
because it was eight thousand dollars yeah i kind of also made a mistake i got the hellbore laser
and i'm not sure i'm loving it yeah i did that to you i i'm trying to use other stuff but
i do think the shop reset did it reset yeah all right i'll try it again now okay where can i
get a reset also i didn't recognize that though is your instruction uh mine is not reset
sir you just lied to i mean probably two or three hundred thousand people watching right now
i think that they will enjoy the engagement created by their anger towards me
okay just the thing for you they will enjoy the anger they won't know that they're enjoying it
and they won't know that they're more engaged but they are where is um the
not the it's over here right if i can upgrade this
i afford to do this oh oh no how many do i need 150
shit yeah the upgrading is a little complicated right now it seems like
where it incentivized to wait till you hit max level okay but at least to get like purples yeah
the purples are what i'm looking for i'll use what i was using before i think i like it all
right ready to just req try that again yeah want to do the same one or do some different um what's
it something like oh sorry no whatever whatever you guys want to do is there's something like
navigators from dune in the boarhammer universe i don't know what is that oh maybe they're answer
they're juiced up with spice so that they can see the future as they light travel
through space yeah like practically another species from how much spice they've been juicing
up on and like yeah they're like weird fish creatures because they evolved because they
took too much spice and uh instead of using computers to navigate ftl drives they they just
use these weird spiced up fish creatures yeah so apparently that exists in more hammer they're
just called navigators and they they help navigate through space because space is chaos and
they're like on the brink of insanity at all times but are used as basically a tool
so we so we are of all the different factions and everything right so this game is it wait
wait hold on this game copied dune and starcraft i don't know when these these things were written
um the timeline hold on a minute hold on just a minute like through the roof right now hold on
just a minute warhammer was first motherfuckers wait wait what warhammer was first it was the
first of all these play of all these things actually well i don't want to lose you ad money
um actually warhammer excuse me the only book you need to be reading because it came first
is the bible everything copied the bible okay what what that's not a false statement
you want to do another three do you want to do two what's the vibe germa's choice
uh we'll do three we can do three we just we gotta lock in we gotta get in the middle
all right uh let's see this one all right guys lock in let's get in the middle all right let's
get them okay if you want i'm gonna be really careful about like those witch things whatever
they are what does what does get in the middle mean to you germa what does that mean like it's
it's like a three let's get in the middle like it's a three out of five oh like no i don't want
to do two i don't want to do a four i would do right in the middle three two and a half
i think i just cancelled i know it um germa is about to i don't know what that means where'd
my hair go look at my look at my hat yeah you know your hair is gone who shaved my head
it's like the first person to fall asleep at a slumber party dude your oh yeah your hair is
just it's gone completely quick check and see if you have any new tattoos all right it's gone i'm
i'm actually peeped what it is gone wait let me see in game let me see it's still gone
it's actually gone that was my whole character your whole character arc you gotta finish a run
can't die to a demon all right let's look your hair go i don't want to hear about other franchises
i don't want to hear about all the other favorite movies that you have or other
books that you've read in the last few years all i care about
oh yeah i don't care i don't want to hear about the bible i want us to to rock this
right in the middle three star okay right down the center it's a nice just three out of six
i don't care about the bible i did it i did long bomb i'm that guy oh you got the achievement
yeah for the hellbore laser do you recommend charging it fully each time or is it okay to
just kind of like well uh charge it if the if it's not a normal enemy
this is the god the edge but if you headshot normal enemies they should go down in one hit
without a charge how am i so dead already die i am dead i am dead already i am dead already
your guy literally just said i'm not dead yet i am dead already there's some narrative dissonance
right now between smush on comms and smushing game that's right they're big somebody said you
need to dodge about you flying a plane oh that's tomorrow okay plane tomorrow
that's the only explanation i'm gonna give yeah that's tomorrow all right
that's fine good luck don't die yeah i'm gonna be on uh you know austin show yeah yeah i'm gonna
be on austin show stream and we're gonna be you know we're operating a plane
a plane like a plane honestly it feels really weird that you're promoting something that
isn't warhammer right now because i'm like knowing germa he's probably like learned and
you know got his pilot's license put 10 000 hours in and is now actually flying a real plane
oh god and he did this all in the last two months like that's that's where my mind went
oh we're supposed to be focusing and you guys are still talking about the bible
and the plane sorry i'm just glad you're not like putting yourself in danger for a bit that's good
no no it's gonna it's gonna be fun okay it's gonna be a fun time i'm actually pretty excited
for it it seems very very interesting this is something i probably should have asked a long
time ago do headshots actually matter for most of weapons or no yes so even like explosives
explosives like if you hit somebody right in the head anything that has a projectile or a melee
that makes contacts it is better yeah so the mauler has apparently more armor on the head
once again i've forgotten i think i hear another demon host down the hallway
is that what that was i was hitting the whispers too yeah it might be all right i don't want to
waste ammo oh stuff in here we got uh gonna you should take that thanks
all these smgs feel like you shoot a normal enemy 600 times and then you just keep walking here
yeah you might like be uh your aim doesn't sound very good does it
oh i went down here oh man you just self-reported you self-reported that you can't get headshots
until you get the uh the bolters there it's gonna change it won't oh shit it won't uh-oh
what that that was entirely my bad i was trying to get the sniper i tunnel visioned and now i'm
gonna die goodbye everyone good luck with the demon host first
it's going to kill one other person so just pick uh pick who it's gonna be
i'll take full responsibility for that what was that that like laugh did you hear that
that's gonna be me oh hey just let it happen that's fine is live just don't worry about me
avoid demon host and live stir what's what's only you and me okay let's live
oh we this sniper is gonna kill us you can jump down down here where are you oh again
no they're chasing they don't care about me i am dude i'm not a threat they're going after you
they're running by me okay you got this you got this you got this all right let's do it
it shot me he shot me he came down the stairs right he ran back up the stairs
there be careful there are two there's a lot of people down here it's all right don't leave me
i'm i'm dead believe me leave me it's not worth it yeah stir they were running by me to try to
get you and even if i was standing there trying to block hey that sniper's still up here and i
think he shot me god that armor i'm getting blown up by this guy oh no there's just you right
well the sniper i died the sniper got everyone wait that was insane all right let's not talk
about this round this this round was an absolute failure i'll take responsibility let's move on
all right stay positive guys so the first one's gonna change things the first chapter of the bible
goes over a few things right yeah there's the apple there was the uh on the sixth seventh day
god rested and stuff there's a serpent serpent serpent huh who's your favorite 16 years i
remember favorite apostle what's your favorite tarot card page of swords favorite apostle is um
caleb hey mine's the ace of spades true yeah if you had your hair i think i think we could have
done better yeah i 100 believe also if i didn't have that smg i think um back now oh people hate
this routine what the bible us losing getting a lot of negative reaction to the joke that i just
said the ace of spades yeah it's not a good one if you like to gamble and baby i'm your man
yeah people didn't like it the ace of spades song motorhead that is cool right tony hawke
it's all the same to me yeah dude tony hawke seriously had i don't think a soundtrack could
ever come close maybe one of the gta's love tony hawke soundtrack the remake had a ball we're
talking about a different game now you know has a great soundtrack warhammer 40k dark tie
it does sound right just for kid killing it yeah the keyboard the gta i mean you can pull a
playlist if you want but that i remember listening to like gta san andreas gta 3 the radio was just
they had so much shit there it was awesome it's great all of it will get you nice and content
claim these days yep what uh what game osts do you guys listen to outside of the game you know
when you're like walking to school trono trigger final fantasy skies of arcadia wrong just for kid
dark side and vermontize yeah that one too wait when you were saying when you were walking to
school yeah yeah like like ragnarok a very very very long time ago i mean crypt of the necro dancer
yeah necro dancer is great yeah on my way to school i usually uh bump that up got the beatbox
on one shoulder all right hey kids i pop up my skateboard into my hand i am making an executive
decision we are to no longer make jokes we're not making any references we're going to only
talk about this game because we have to get through it because we look real bad right now
yeah if we don't beat a level then germa doesn't get paid all right let's let's lock in a big guy
over here let's make this contract a little bit more interesting oh shield guy yeah i like the
gun that instantly deletes all elite enemies rather than the smg that tickles people's toes
skill issue what gun is that i need that one i don't think you can get it until 15
it's like a blue plaz gun yeah hey hey oh that was a collateral man
oh wait somebody is behind us oops all right what there we go ah where are these guys coming from
you got a gram already things are looking up see all right we made it past the first
hundred yards of the level all right big uh big collection oh so i've been electric netted
the correct term is trapped that too all right a lot of people coming from over here big big big
big problem big problem huge problem grenade free fight fuck the grenades you guys have
i i have all the grenade specs i just talk oh toxic i have the one that you have a chance to
gain grenades when you kill things if you're near me too like everyone i'm gonna get this toxic guy
all right that was a little smoother that was great guys over here already
you go fix yourselves right up
i mean the respective quarter how many uh slots enough for everyone to heal
yeah i'll i'll throw you guys nice very good very good wow that was great that was great
well done all right guys looks like we're gonna have some special enemies up ahead
we already did that joke uh yeah we did that that was the other day we're only allowed to
talk about the game and no repeats yeah no repeats i'm learning the rules holy shit that guy went
all the way over there oh wait look there's like this there's no one here and then there's
a big old horde that's something right that's that's original right original do not steal
they were just like playing a game of dice
no idea how you almost completed a five it uh honestly it was the best game of dark
ever played in one of the like my top gamer moments all the time really i don't want to
save the bot because it was like so fucking clutch shooter shooter over here somewhere
watch out for the shooter dude i'm
all right nice we're okay we're doing all right we're doing all right
what i keep seeing the red that's a lot of people oh yeah i was also stoned for it
oh that well that not explains i got i got high for the
level five mission and i like entered a zone that i've never been in before yeah i literally like
saw between the code you saw the ancestors spirits oh i think about it though kraken in
the 60s jimmy hendricks was doing like crazy stuff on the guitar but us we're doing five star
dark tide you're right this is this is my jimmy hendricks moment yeah that was your jimmy hendricks
moment speaking of dark tide the game the game is available right now on steam uh it is launch day
i don't know why this is so goddamn funny uh the game is out right now it is on steam launch day
four player co-op in the warhammer 40k universe actually very fun game yeah get your jimmy hendricks
moment now on steam uh and join join the team wait anybody need this
oh go for it the grignard's now somebody's throw one yeah i threw one i picked it up
oh um does it repeat from a previous stream count for like a joker reference yeah yeah that's fine
that's fine okay um when i have my knife out and i tap block i can make it wiggle like a pencil
you know like in middle school that's right sniper sniper shooter sniper shooter sniper
this killed us last time top right i got it don't worry i'm on top of it already
that was not a sniper by the way pound nice shot all right move who has the best uh kind of like
hacking tool or whatever grenade um anyone that's not you sounds mean but it's true
it's real auger just has slower than us i'll do it this game has some pretty satisfying melee i
will say that it uh that's a lot of guns oh boy whoa that's a lot of guns a good chunk of i'm down
jimothy hendricks when jimmy came undone oh my god
oh
jimmy hendricks i was so locked in come on you have to have your moment
i'm just going to you guys respawn hope there's no trapping
that was real anger i'm nearby at the very least yeah all right all the way towards you
you just got a lot of dudes and some guns you see uh anything that can incapacitate
right behind you careful careful got me oh thank god i mean i could bite people right now you know
what i mean like this is i could i can bite people right they're kneecaps
betta station no no i i had that on me and i died maybe you could have used it well i
no not really through three people two people were down yeah i was trying to get you no hack
not mirrored all right i'll hack out okay great i got you i got i got my knife out i'm ready to
help you well you know what here let me hack i'm probably the worst at this so okay what oh this
person's dead rubber is nice packed nice job where we're good we're good nice shot who did that good
job that was awesome wow that was actually the revolver you're using uh yes revolver tox flamer
oh it's going again try to get it you should i'll get it if you should let me do it you're i'm not
super good at dealing with horde okay i got it oh god i hear screaming awkward oh my god
got me we're good yeah you're hacking again all right we're in shooter oh that's you oh where
how did i hit the railing you gotta be shitting me got him nice okay all right we're doing it
gang a little bit a little bit of ammo down here 21 needs it uh-oh he's a knife wielding maniac how
do you know i'm not gonna do that later in my life dude i'm like 28 i've got plenty of time dude calm
down what i'm i'm gaming what did you get away get on screen now that was
don't say that all right with a new diversion ai it learns and adapts to you the dogs levitate
that was sick that was a level three dog right down the middle you don't get those in tier one
no can i do i have a question uh right now just give me your actual honest like say it on a scale
of one to ten what's your fun factor right this very second right now like a two nine wow okay
yep i give it a nine like a jack you can like an eight out of ten i i would say i would say
i'm pretty much at that level nine point oh right now and just like how i'm fun i'm having right
this very second with my friends in a phone call that's nice germa playing dark tide really sweet
i think i i honestly hit a 10 during the uh the five missions we did yeah but there's another
reason why you hit that what the fuck where did this guy come from jimmy hendrix one he's dead
ways all in my brain some down there yeah there's a dude with like a chain gun down there
yes it's held down there be careful somebody said why are you not rating this a 10 with your
friends well because i don't write this very moment i don't have a nice fresh ice cold beer
what sponsorship are you gonna get next um delicious pores uh you need some place to go
if you if you go to a 10 right away you can't hit that next level you can't nothing is a 10
yeah you gotta like kind of save 10 for transcendental moments you don't even have all
your perks yet and your weapons yet like you're gonna have more fun later
you're investing in your future there should be a healing thing over here
put on your red shoes and that's right run
oh it actually is but though like no joking around no fucking around it's very fun
oh i keep doing that no i'm bad no i'm bad why this guy just wants to kill you star so bad
i'm jamming my knife in this guy's back he does not care he just wants you to die
i want that medicaid oh you do a pretty good joe well done you too buddy i knew we were friends
for a reason cracking yeah we do joe we do carmen you can do just about everything
any amount of voices you can do i feel like i really got some competition you know what i mean
i am alone over here i'm alone over here i'm alone over here and there's a lot of people
but you're not alone not alone you have friends in the boat my voice calls
fuck that dog wolf is so scary um help help help help help help help help help
okay i'm going out to get him i'm pinned he's wrapping around the other side he's going
uh stirring vinny the dog's near you thanks they just won't stop all right we gotta move
there's some kind of enemy with a gun all right give me don't you think it's don't you think
it's quicker just to say shooter there's an enemy up ahead with a weapon in his hand
i wanted to let my team know in the most descriptive way possible
where is he oh god what did you say last stream and ironically was like that just happened
and yeah i did do that so that just happened oh all right he just came to this tail behind
you prisoner prisoner prisoner it's me every time oh my god he's the worst it's me every time
geisters throwing i'm asserting yeah well when you see the stats in the end game page you're
gonna know how much i really did they add stats no oh god there's a big horde too that just appeared
what a huge horde oh that's bad i threw like four of them oh i'm down lads
oh i don't know what to do i don't know what to do i don't know what to do stir help
i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i can't get rid of it i'm down you're not dead you're just down
oh you got it oh my god saved the whole run nice it should respawn there's a healing thing here
although there's a grimoire but i don't think we can do it so let's just let me go you got the
med pack i dropped right yeah he's got it that was crazy that was intense but trust more in the
master of mankind
kraken you are playing like the trailer of this game you this is unbelievable gameplay
i fell all the way down i'm in a predicament down okay i'm not down i'm down i feel like i'm
watching somebody solo a five star mission right now all the dashes the kraken this what's this
character name well this is the zealot but i use the knife because the dash makes it go farther
so you get to like play a nice shot wow this victory nice stat thanks it just doesn't stop
kraken i feel like you've been doing this in the same breath
i did not talk for 10 minutes in the five run i just became a fucking silent
attack that that was incredibly unfortunate and then the horse showed up
let's do this talk versus bad two of them oh my god that's not fair how are you still alive
oh got me dude good job though holy shit that was actually great you gave it so much
damn dude that was amazing we were close we almost had it sorry man i don't think you're
getting paid for this you want it no we got the next one if we do a tooth and you can probably
get this money no we're gonna they said it had to be at least a three no we're doing it i want to
do a three we have to do a three we did we did a three on we just did one and we did it fine
we did yeah the first one we did was a three so what happened you guys got comfortable
cocky i yeah we started talking too much sorry no more jokes you're right yeah nothing about the
bible yeah what's what's tabooed by the way for the next run just so we know going into it uh
probably doing any kind of funny voices as well funny voice all right get out of the way now
i'll see you on the other side vader all right i mean uh all right all right lois i mean joe
my peter voice is just such a mess every time i do it i think i have to be drunk
it's the only way i can get it out i don't think mine is particularly good but i try anyway
i think it no matter what everybody just hates it guys can you give me one i just want to buy
a new weapon because i don't i don't know if i love this one i don't think it's reset the story
yet because we've lost three times within one reset but uh it will by the next time all right
we gotta go for it everybody lock in we need rolls secure everybody lock in roll secure i'm
gonna spend you know what i'm spending a little bit more time focusing on tanking and pushing
dodging this is the one right here and we're gonna pull it back sounds that sounds great dude
i hope we're gonna all right let's go we have we had a couple of a couple of bad ones but
i'll be very honest with you that that's hard that was hard the we got spawned on a couple
times it was like three or four uh you know um what do you want to call them uh
special or monsters special with guns special enemies enemies special enemies uh we got spawned
on a couple times so yeah can we get a can we get a breakdown from smush at the end of every level on
how it went that's what we can do to improve and everything yeah i could
locker room speech yeah yeah actually before we start the level how about you give us a lot of
speech a little ed germa you're so cringe more because i have pep talking friends to try to do
a harder difficulty mission dude there is like 15 comments that were like can you do my son's
like birthday he's turning 12 and you picked that one to read is it just a thing now everyone goes
through your stream for you to wish them a happy birthday well it is now because you both just said
it i i tuned in to strip and string earlier today and that also happened you also shouted out a
birthday wait what you know he you know he's never wished me a happy birthday like yesterday
and you guys are playing uh wilderness yes i did what um i know we're not supposed to
talk about other games what yeah i'm just curious that game good yeah i mean this is i'm having this
is so much fun i'm having a blast this is great why do you just ignore vinnie oh shit i did i
didn't mean to do that yes all right it's fine yes that it actually was pretty funny it's a cool
game okay cool thanks i'm having a blast i'm sorry i'm just having so much fun i'm just having
a blast guys hey thanks for the um the locker room speech by the way all right honest to goodness
let's play let there be gaming all right imagining ted lasso but it's just germa and he just gets into
the locker room all right guys honest to goodness we've got got our enemies on the right side
his big smile on his face pats him on the shoulder leaves the room that's the goodness let's play
all right are we all like a friend i was gonna say now got eerily quiet
i don't want to say the wrong thing anything will trigger this guy's be original
like does he also send you guys like review scores after you were on a stream with him
yeah i mean i've spent a while but like after wilderness it was like here's like the breakdown
of like like different rating like commentary right like this comment was out of line you
well it's the timestamps and it's the overall like your emotional level your commentary your
attitude one by one well i know i download all of your vods and i and i and i write over it in red
pen and i circle like oh over here you see you didn't you miss this part and uh your face came
glitched out at this point too that was you don't watch mine then okay cool all right
boys boys sniper one again what the fuck is he yeah he's like he runs up to the corner takes
your shot and then just like walks away i'm assuming gun melee even with a bayonet isn't
as good as regular melee right i believe so no you can still headshot with them and it'll kill
most guys in one hit but that gun with usually the bayonet guns have such a long time to switch
that if it's just one guy it's worth it okay i can't believe it's 70 i'm gonna die i'm just
puked yeah like in real life what the heck is happening to my character heresy he's with
nurgle this guy fucking puked streamer pukes live on stream i'm good we're doing the world
world warcraft dungeon with my friend a few years ago and we were doing perm death challenge and
he was healing and he got so nervous that he literally took a break went to the bathroom and
puked because wow and be his fault it was that high pressure of a situation yes wow
oh i can't like the nerve is building up there that's damn
yeah i think you're going backwards all right we're doing all right things are going okay
i'm lost dog where i don't know somewhere right there good shout out good call good reaction time
oh wait only way is down we go down oh here let's go down enemies with pus on them
i don't know what they're called over here uh pox walkers oh thank you oh nice shot
hi i don't think if you touch fire it removes all of your shields yeah does it really
it's like an instant like boom the fire punched you in the face
oh i've got a battery oh this is too many what the heck a lot got a battery oh good we can use
that to get a health station you're right wait there's a health station should be a net electric
net where's the uh should we just bring us i can carry this to the best right let me look
should be very close yeah there are drops enabled if you have uh drops on yep i think it's cosmetic
and camos and stuff i uh yeah from the other night when we uh streamed together germa i got
the drops oh nice it's like a sword skin that i'm using right now i dropped the uh things over
here this is the mid thing uh you're alone back there that dog took like you saw many
hits that's right yeah i did like a full charge shot yeah all right we got healing all right
everyone can use it oh that's such good you need what the oh come on i was looking over
at the chat room for one second the perfect timed grenade they were watching the stream
any um any uh secrets in here grenade uh i guess i'm not gonna drop down yet big guy
good here we go that he has a machine gun doesn't he he does yo wait hey hey friend
hey friend it's a friend yeah get in there uh-oh watch that back area watching the back area yeah
there's a lot of gunners over there just be careful come on if i were a criminal shooters
they all dead we got shooters i think we're good still this is the furthest we've been
how is it yeah this is the first we've been in like three missions
you're pretty quiet last mission dog the um you were gonna say if i was a grimoire
where would i hide right yeah yeah where's this dog fuck i'd go in a library
yeah a skull library any items to pick up because we have that button to press right yeah not that
i've seen i guess we just press it probably i've not done this level i've seen oh man where did
shaken where did that guy even come oh there they are big guy on the left charger on the left
charger charger guy charger guy cool all right you look i don't know you look just like that guy
you look like the same costume on what what i'm not an enemy i'm just wearing my way down there
uh i don't know i'm just killing enemies what are you guys doing uh we're watching you kill
enemies i mean are we supposed to drop down
okay the servitors have a colony really oh god there's there's a charging yeah
that runs fast he's up there he's just running down the stairs when i'm late to work oh god
i need i need help please anyone i got so i got ammo for later i got ammo for later i have no
more bullets left see when germa says oh actually do have a ring for you
one of them's gonna land i just kept shooting germa like i he's still big you need to check
posture you have a oh am i doing oh do i have i am all right i gotta i gotta check that posture
thank you appreciate it oh the the gamer slunch yeah i was like slunch is a good word yeah it's
lunch with an s in front of it it's like a a hunch but also a slouch i like that yeah
yeah slunch sounds freaking nasty don't it yeah like what'd you have in your slunch box this morning
wasn't it wasn't good nothing good well i think i think i see a grim what's that nasty nasty green
glow it's a grim there's like a servitor panel down here are we doing this or hold on they're
jingling keys the music's different again if we need ammo at any point let me know i have an
ammo box i can drop it great i can i can snap through this door they're coming i'm just hitting
the body oh wow that hurt i think there's a sniper over there behind us behind us behind it oh boy
some spicy hordes happening right now dog on me dog on me get it off get it off get it off
oh boy this is gonna be bad they're coming in the door all right we have a healing over here
though so let's get over here new dog just dropped give me it all right i'm here do we need ammo
it's all healed i've also got an ammo crate uh i'm gonna put mine down all right ammo what is that
you seriously oh my god all right ammo's down next to me all right these grenade placements
are ridiculous come on he probably built his whole old from that wait can we can we appreciate
this guys this is a fucking servitor colony look at this thing i'm gonna i'm gonna appreciate it
in a second hang on yeah make sure to grab the ammo if you didn't i have uh healing when needed
so yeah let's save it save it for like the middle of the fight probably sure oh my god look at this
thing yeah this is these are those like half dead half alive humanoid things that are used
for technology there's an entire fucking column of them rim dark it's fun that's creepy
miss point blank i'm scared of it what's that noise well a sniper i think so they are shooting
from a random spot okay we're good okay i think we're good ready to start it i believe we are
okay we should be in uh we should get it in this room or something i feel like it's gonna be a big
hoarder wave right yo yeah we should get into the bottom room yeah bottom room bottom room
well we're gonna have to run around and redo the yeah so we're gonna have to get up
oh shit oh shit explosion watch out oh it hurt all right yeah we gotta restart that
you can do as much i believe in you come on we put our oggren on it i'm good i got it yeah we did
he's very smart for an oggren i'm surprised they even let oggrens do it
what's your blood type please help me it's for a school project what what are you talking about
do not read chat this is not the time especially not that message that's true why am i reading you
i'm on it i've got this one around six a.m i believe i know that one on top of my head
they're gonna know you're rising they're gonna know your moon oh fuck you're right stars
oh my rising my star sign which as you know predicts your future so they'll be able to find you
oh behind us astralizes you behind us behind us behind us behind behind grenade grenade out
grenade out here i killed myself killed myself what i killed myself are you where are you oh i
got you my gun can blow up oh yeah i was worried about the sniper and i missed and then i missed
and it was the skill issue and germa's right i really need to go back to training i need to
go back to boot camp that's totally gonna be in your stream recap review dude sorry right here
in the vod where you missed these three shots uh the cost of the round all right oh they all turn
blue that means they're happy whoa uh stir you can apparently switch weapons to avoid the self damage
that's according to a chat message even after you've triggered it we have to wait for the
responses put in your pocket and wait wait wait for his response um and whatever it is ban him
because i didn't ask the answer is i believe it's yes okay well let's find out so where do we have
to obtain this thing where is it not ready yet nope can't switch weapons should i ban them
you just died yeah definitely ban them actually throwing actually throwing
germa was throwing because he read chat and we both we all told him not to
i didn't oh shit you actually are dead you are dead for real okay we can proceed
we proceed proceed uh i'm almost dead myself actually a person that said that is probably
holding their stomach laughing hysterically right now on the verge of like tears they're
slapping their knees like they're ham boning in place right now you know in the future like
cemeteries their gravestones are gonna have like clips of like the best moments of their life
playing on it you can go visit that's gonna be on there that'll be yeah yeah that's a great idea
embedded twitch clips on your gravestone yeah that'll happen someone will do that
kiss already the band kiss already sells coffins that play kiss music eternally so while you're
dead you can party all night and rock all day or whatever oh my god imagine eternally being like
in a room where that music never stops yeah all you hear is
ah wanna rock and roll your corpse retains senses and you're like yeah unable to move
or even if you're like in heaven walking around like that's still playing and only you can hear
it wait sir i thought this elevator was gonna go up but we're going oh shit sorry
someone ought to put them out of hand boning is what's hand bone when you look on your knee
yeah you're like like like like uh to make use of one slap in your body um healing bit here
yeah vinnie you just take this she gets it thanks jesus remember i still have a med kit if if needed
so oh look it they opened that door that was kind of creepy yeah i saw when i walked in that room
the door just closed and then i think like i walked out when you were there
oh was there a follow-up to the hand boning or just you know i just like
because the way i said that is like the chat member who tricked you he's ham boning in place
because he's so like he's so happy or it's hand boning always in place
i guess you can walk around while you ham bone it looks real silly but that's part of the fun
all right this people shoot my eyebrow is so itchy hey king take a minute
take care of it all right i'm gonna get prisoner help i'm in prison oh boy let me
warn me about your fucking friends in here they're my friends oh my god everyone has a gun aiming at
me stop vinnie there's so many people shooting weapons at me nice off i'm trying to shoot
weapons back at them lala i was dead for at least three minutes because i i've recovered
three grenades while i waited there wait when you said lala that wasn't a teletubbies reference
was it um no oh fuck i could see i could see how you could put the two and two together though
like that probably three no voices germa did you watch doug when you were growing up oh yeah
what from memory what was mr dink's job do you remember mr dink uh yeah hello douglas that guy
yeah yeah he was yeah he was uh he was like a tinkerer he was the dinkster you guys got it
thank you i'm just curious because some people don't know yeah he was like a tinkerer like i
don't know was he a teacher too i don't remember oh my god somebody's shooting from over there
well dink is actually an acronym for double income no kids so him and his wife had no kids
and they were just like gaming the system so that's why he was called mr dink no way
just like the dinklebergs it wasn't the finster his kid i don't know who that is the blue one
no that's skeeter dude the best part about that every time he would come on screen
it would always do like the
i like did you wait what did you just say
i was trying to say pox burser but you said talks and you shot oh i thought you said
something else we lose we lose a bit of ourselves to the rise and grind don't you agree douglas
the flesh rots yeah up there what the fuck okay i got it whoa every day we straight
listen i got you i'm scared i got you i'm scared got you i'm going down now thank you okay got me
back oh do you want health now do we health or no um i don't think we can even use it really
for the purple right yeah you're right i'm sorry i'm busy i was busy dinking and not playing
wisely of course of course we bring up no voices we bring up mr dink and and now we're gonna lose
the mission this is actually literally what's gonna happen oh no god damn it i'm still i'm still
thinking about the finster i just invented in my head who's not a character in doug but i've
somehow conjured he's my doug oc finster yeah he'd fit in finster are you thinking of um
me finster what are we doing today no you're talking about uh clever sir explains it all
that's ferguson yeah that was ferguson ferguson yeah i think that's and he's like oh that's me
it's me ferguson and i i annoy my sister no it's his whole personality that's your gaslighting
kraken right now chuck it's away from me it's from rugrats no it's not oh god you're right
chuckie finster chuckie finster did i take the last name from chuckie yep
can i have nothing original do i have an original thought in my head i mean that
there was a long time ago thank you oh my god thank you you got me back look guys i gotta go
i just realized my ocs a lie did you take the health kit that i dropped oh shit uh
proximity to excise something like a coward they all kind of are oh shit the dune world
access excise vault hl three two two seven nine one oh my god they're just aiming at us from up
here yeah i'm gonna throw down some ammunition up here if anyone was looking for some ammo
oh why would you put it before the drop down yeah like like in a very far spot uh you guys
are gonna want to come over to my house if you need ammo i've got a tv and a car anyone want to
hang out i completed a penance it's crazy looking nice i don't know penance so i'm saying somebody
somebody asked if i could look out the window and i was like all right why not is he there
grenades here sick that's you can't do that his character screamed grenade finding one as if
one were thrown at him right like if you're in a car and you scream like cat you would imagine
that you got a swerve yeah yeah cat i love mine i just gave him this new food and he's really
loving it sorry i'm still thinking about the finster the finster yeah i i think after this i
might find like an online doug for him and just dude i tried i dodged i tried to dodge i dodged
back but i didn't i reloaded and my face is sweating crank and i gotta show you this little
doug video it's in it's fresh in my mind because someone made a little animated short of some dumb
bit with mr dink that i did i'll show you after the stream it's fun every day off
douglas uh oh every day and what and again we are doing a mr dink impression
and getting attacked by a special enemy every time i do an impression i get attacked
no no no no i'm gonna stop i'm gonna stop it's so funny you actually did that and got hit by the
charge that was perfect it was actually perfect here this is the last thing before the end i think
yeah smush you're probably gonna fight everyone recalibrate your brain yes yeah seriously
serious no messing around i have heels i have heels i got grenades okay wait before hold on
before you press the button everybody just go ahead and do it because we all want to
do it only two of us did it but it's okay all right we got it out of us
there's a bomber behind us what the i already have my armor gone okay it'll come back it'll
come back but what are we actually trying to do here retrieve the contagion samples
oh are you just not saying anything i think i think doug that show is probably the same age
as some of your chatters no one knows what you're talking about play the game that's so true
nobody knows what this is my chat i see mr dink kind of became a bit of a meme for me years ago
so yeah i really haven't seen corner the doug demographic yeah we got the doug demographic
over on my streams i don't know how oh my god i'm down what got me that was a good reaction
uh here we are talking about the dinkleberg here here we are in the final battle
all right stop talking about mr dink or i'm gonna fucking i'm done all right i'm gonna
hop down here i think wait what is this we need to put uh some sort of canister in here
i'll get in over the canisters are though you sniper sniper hey
it's over no no we can do this you just went parachuting off my screen
we need to stay together stay together stay together thank you
no no no no no more dog again you dumped it i'm down stop i'm a casualty now is he dead
i'm just getting all right someone said we have to open these doors sniper and then yeah open these
doors and then we put the canisters in the middle all right in here oh bingo bingo bingo all right
we have to stay together stay together we have back i'm back uh look someone look to your prisoner
or crying i think um yeah yeah i'm right here we need to open all these get them all open already
all right this one right here you want to grab that i'm gonna bring it over here oh my god where
does it go where does it go where does it go over here just bring it over here oh shit i'm so sorry
no no get get us yeah get get us germa yeah yeah yeah that's unbelievable why is he screaming
are you okay no i'm not okay i'm almost dead for real i'm almost there for real yes you did it
i'm putting heels down right here heels on heels heels down heels down heels down everyone
gather for heels one two three four five six okay now don't run oh no we have to stay right next
to each other we need to literally be within one meter so we're going to move this canister down
here right that's why i'm loaded enemies and a lot of enemies you guys do the moving i'll do the
killing all right yeah yeah but just just baby i need that help again i need the health again
it's gone no it's not it's still here but i'm gone i'm gone now what the heck is going on on
the stairs all right dude yeah me and prisoner what the fuck a lot of fire what is this i'm
is it me am i putting the fire down where is this guy i got oh my god it's a flame there's two of
them actually i'll get the other one there's just so much fire there's three of them all right i'm
going back for prisoner all right come on come on come on stick together who even did i'm done
i got somebody shot me all right i'm back it's all right it's all right we got you we can get it we
can get it you did not pick me up huh no and there's two of us now in the same spot there's
two of us in the same spot it's fine it's all right we're gonna be all right we're good all right
all right yeah i think sometimes it does that it's happening i'll get stir i'll get stir
oh thank you okay we're back we're back we're back back in it back in it nothing happened
what the fuck
i'm just gonna do it all right one one down two to go two more two more together next to uh
safe or whatever together together together copernicus watch out stir you're gonna you're
gonna get behind you i think i'm i think i'm a laggy boy uh-oh come on you you guys just stay
there stick together i'll run up and grab it franken are you are we playing with three
unplugged controllers right now and it's just you playing the game i'm just trying to i'm just
trying to find the objectives man all right don't let him do that behind you the next one's over
here maybe we go over there make your way around from that angle yeah there's so many people with
fire it's ridiculous behind you you're good whole upper deck they just keep appearing behind you
what oh what is going on dude okay dog another one of these that we go to i don't know which one
ow we're good we're good just keep keep moving keep moving i don't know which one either i don't
know one of these should be blue there's a lower floor fuck off all right there is a lower floor
all right let's go to the middle ring there's too many people there's too many people too many too
many too many too many stick together all right come to the lower area with me everyone hop down
okay just be careful you don't want to do get fall damage i think i just did it all right okay all
right now we're gonna hop down again there's one i would have never seen this yeah me either i would
never have thought oh oh somebody downstairs everybody there's a blue okay there's a couple
oh my god die oh my god there's so many coming behind us there's a lot of them we need to go we
need to hole up in this room here everybody hole up in the room okay all right there's one canister
there's a hundred million people behind you vinnie i know throw grenade big guy with a big gun no i
don't know what that thing is all right we handled the crowd pretty nicely all right if you want to
carry the canister okay i got it can i climb ladders while holding the canister no right
i'm down okay we got you to find the ramp which is over here this way that could have that could
have gone a lot worse we can also throw it apparently because if smush carries it we go faster
i'll take it smush get it right here all right is right here put it in the hydron collider okay
good one more i think the last one was also down here stay together move as one move as a unit
try and get inside of it there's a lot coming yeah all right well inside where inside here where we
are oh i went the wrong way oh no all right nice nice to know you no no we're good we're good
all right did you find it is it in there i'm dead casualty oh send a letter home or something
okay we're okay though got it right here let's go let's go bingo let's go let's get it let's go
get it let's go get it all right i'm gonna go up and get vinny i'm going with you say pop out of
that door right like on top of you all right nice okay okay you got vinny this is another
phase to this oh my goodness get up the stairs oh oh i don't have any bullets or anything
we just have to go oh they're coming from every direction all right hit the button
see what it says let's get out of here action we gotta go down down all right it's down i'm down
i'm down i'm down i'm down i'm down i got you but not in the down the stairs kind of way
yeah all right now let's go down the stairs kind of way perfect excellent oh let's get out of here
i have never been more happy to leave a map in my life this this was an insanely difficult
level it's it's not over we still have to get out of here that's pretty far this is kind of
far still has a grimoire is that you kraken yeah jesus oh my god there's a d*** behind us
oh my god
we're only being the finster that was three stars that was actually kind of
racked out that was that was pretty cracked oh my god that was some of the most fun i've had but
it was also some of the most like sweat that was some of the most sweat i had i'm gonna get two
levels from that i got a ring out my underwear just all the piss you're just constantly
65 diamanteam that's pretty good that's what you used to craft stuff wow guys that was amazing
if you guys remember like 30 minutes ago when we were doing the kermit the frog thing
was i was that my idea i don't happen remember yeah i think we just kind of fell into it
it's pretty bad i do frog i would lay down my life friend here augren looks like trevor from gta
yeah tremors about that big i think that'll be it for me lads that that was a good one too
yeah it's a good one to end on um it's it's a shame i never got to play a match with connor we
talked for like 13 seconds and that was it but um i wonder uh i wonder if connor's still around
yeah we're just gonna swap them out you know but no seriously vinny that thanks for playing
it's uh no jerma this is great i'm down for more if you're ever in the mood to play some more war
hammer but uh i appreciate the invite as always man thank you and and kraken always always a
pleasure yeah buddy and uh stir it was really nice to meet you man i i think um i think we had some
good matches today yeah it was fun uh nice to meet you too well take it easy guys bye that's
what's all that's what's all about right there that's right douglas that's what it's all about
like you and your friend skater bye say a little bit uh that was crazy that was actually
i felt that one that was a intense one oh i got money too i got a lot of money can i get
oh this thing's 200 wait is this a shield oh my god oh my god i think the plasma gun is a liability
it's it's difficult to use well yeah i miss i miss my other gun we wish that but happy birthday
yeah we're not getting offered high level guns of good guns yeah what constitutes a maniac
maniac is an enemy title uh anyone who is a follower of your steam group the inhumane
maniacs i think yeah but i mean in the game um i think it's like the mutants and like the
berserkers like the cultist looking dudes with no clothes on oh psychopaths my bad yeah is this
thing better i mean it does a more a little bit more damage i like what this is better heavy
attack is better cleave is better weapons have a rating plus 100 cleave on three seconds for
multiple melee hit that seems pretty amazing how much money do i have whatever i want it
and stamina is stamina health or is no stamina is the bar that you do the running and stuff and
dodging right yeah so this is plus two max stamina what do we what do you have for stamina
is it out of 10 that is out of 15 hmm be paying honor that's like a 30 increase that's really
good really that seems pretty good class dependent that means two more little bars i'll get i mean i
is it better than what i have here is it better to be able to run more and dodge more or is it better
to be able to be revived more than another extra time higher difficulty levels you're gonna need
wounds which lets you get revived more because they automatically like reduce you by like two
i think of the higher level ones but for now i think running and dodging is also good i don't
i've never really noticed stamina upgrades because it's like it's kind of a percentage so i can't
really tell let's see i'll try more of it let's see if it's uh if i notice a difference new knife i
kind of need a new weapon or i need to upgrade this one i it's usually a good idea as you're
leveling up just to buy a new weapon every once in a while because yeah it your your armory
rolls based on what your current highest like level items are not the ones equipped but just
in your inventory yeah this thing's 167 damage this oh what that auto pistol is using earlier
is 21 on damage that i'll be right back oh yeah that was my entire time leveling all way to 30
i didn't understand that system at all and i was using nerf weapons and i understood it but i
remember buying i was like yeah i just i bought it because it was a high item level not because
i wanted to use it but then i saw it in my inventory like i'll give this one a try wait
what do you mean that it's it's kind of hard to explain the item level stuff is like kind of
complicated but so you take someone's rating just the rating that's on the weapon so i think that
it's like the rating is the number like a literal number of that goes into the the stats of your
item right and if you look at the modifiers there's like percentages for damage mobility
penetration yada yada and so those percentages are reflecting of how much of the number of the
rating has gone into each of those so i have a weapon with low percentage damage then it's
actually weak you know in terms of damage but the rating is the overall power and then the
bars are the distribution of that power oh that's interesting okay that's very interesting so
let me didn't realize that yeah it's a interesting system okay i think i understand it and the other
part is uh so you know those grays greens blues and purples and legendary you know quality
as you move up that quality scale it'll have they'll get a higher like item rating but it's
dependent on what it was first at as a gray so for example the dagger i'm using i technically got
at like level 20 so it's not an end game dagger if i got a new dagger at level 30
it would have a higher ceiling it could be upgraded further yeah so if you see a gray it
doesn't mean it's necessarily bad if it's got like a decent item rating level because you can
upgrade it and then it'll you know reach higher than your existing stuff oh okay yeah i'm still
figuring out too it's not it's not solved by any means but but how much money do i have somebody
said i should buy something i don't know i think connor might not be available we may need to
either do a random or fill i'm down it doesn't matter i'm down for either one if we can grab
somebody we can let me check with my other group yeah let's see if charborg is still around yeah
i'm down i'm down to play for like at least another at least another couple missions i really want to
i saw stripping to use this the other day and it was insane which one that uh the heavy stubborn
the heavy machine gun thing oh yeah twin linked heavy stubborn that's that's fun yeah uh charborg
said earlier that he was would be around but it has been a couple of hours so i think he might
be doing something uh i want to let me go to the where is the training dummy place i've never seen
it it's um it's like a big circular room with a lady in a tube do you ever you ever go to disney
world of disneyland like years ago and they had that one like alien escape ride yep there was like
an alien in a tube in the middle of the room yeah it was terrifying yeah that's what you're
looking for it's that room okay that actually is pretty helpful because i'll know that exactly
when i see it i'm gonna say it's right over here yep all right charbrooke says he's doing
something else right now but he'd be down later the meat grinder oh the meat grinder is what it's
called yes that's interesting uh unfortunately connor connor's game is not working yeah looks
like i think my other group is already a team of four so probably can't let's see i mean let me take
a look yeah any any game that has four player co-op a lot of times it's funny when you get like two
groups of three or two groups of like you know there's three and three and it's like well yeah
we can just do a random that's that doesn't matter we could also do that oh we could we could pull
i mean is it and who's who's playing it right now let's see is a raid coming in where oh what
happened my game a little fuzzy is it pussy yeah fuzzy that's back people saying love because
there's lovely playing it right now are you guys looking for a gamer i don't think lovely is playing
it right now i don't think it is wait love is raided no wait was love loving just live oh well
oh oh oh no he didn't oh what what did like a youtube to twitch raid i think that's illegal
uh he'd eat i think he sometimes would put like a link up but i guess he didn't do it i think
people just uh i'm being lied to um all right well i mean who is we could get uh let's see
who's in my mod group oh moderators who wants to play team pick me here we go
uh i mean i'll i'll take anybody in here they're in the mod group i mean everybody is calling for
very very particular mod right now and i don't know if they're available go josh go
oh me when he says germa says he needs one plus one all right we got it uh dr josh is gonna play
get him in this call yeah i'm down for like another one or two come on in josh welcome to
the party i'll invite you to hello hello hello there we go it's working cool what's up me uh get
the game up um before you join you should know that german doesn't want to do any funny voices
right yeah no no i've seen yep all serious business only yeah no absolutely no uh funny
and look what happened we i mean we did there was some mr dink in there but there was a little bit
of dink and a little bit of doug but we were very very serious i mean i'm not a professional
comedian so i'm very much just serious only so yeah this is the right place vr josh i know that
you know at least one or two yeah uh trying to think yeah kraken and then i think i played
pavlov with you in stir years ago yep yep good to see you the name pavlov after the dogs what do
you think discuss i don't know oh wait i just mentioned another game shit uh somebody said
vr josh is the stability that we needed i feel i feel bad for connor in the hub hub loaded yeah
connor would have been fun he was right he was ready he was raring and ready to go but apparently
the game just um was apparently was having some issues with it yeah probably you know launch day
there's always going to be some technical hiccups here and there but hey we got vr josh so we're
ready to go it's been mostly stable for me thankfully i i turned our rtx off and that
definitely helped the frame rate and everything yeah i do while we have a minute here i do want
to say again thank you warhammer for the sponsor i also want to say that the game is available
and get it right now you go to steam and let me just confirm this again i want to make sure
this is this is the game is the retail base price of the game is what uh 40 dollars i believe and
then there's a special edition for 60 40 dollars i think so yeah 40 dollars come on gwen um i think
you might have left the group i'm not sure what the did i i'm just sitting here oh i think maybe
yeah yeah oh it's because i i think i went all right yeah well uh should i do we remake the party
because uh because i got josh here yeah if you just wanted i'll just string yeah i'll invite you
guys i think i can't be can you not be in the training area i don't know i've done it before
but get uh wait how many dollars is it 40 warhammer 40 dollars okay i can't join you either
grump uh now i have to deal with the chat uh oh i mean it's not like we have only two mods we have
i actually might have dced maybe that's what happened oh no i'm good all right let me see
if i can get uh invites going again here i can't i can't invite to any strike team let me try to
let me just relog i think that's what's going on i should be online i think i dced and i can't
connect back in let's try it again relaunching there's around 60 minutes slow mode isn't what
was the longest slow mode 30 minutes i think 30 minutes slow mode so you get one message every
30 minutes that's is it even a chat room or is it a forum at that point are you making fun of my
chat you have 30 minutes slow mode on they can type faster you don't you have 30 minutes slow mode
no that's just how often people message no what do you mean people talking to chat all the time
yeah but i'm i'm getting them angry for the engagement oh i see what you say yeah yeah
yeah it blew up after that it's great all right paid by the message actually on twitch it's true
it is true all right should let's get this rolling here it's weird i maybe have to restart too i can't
join or invite you to my strike team i restarted just because why not yeah i relogged it just
figured i want to point out this wasn't happening before josh showed up yeah my bad
he infected our all of our computers i guess maybe i'll try restarting too it's not tuesday
steam no we can't we can't blame it on maintenance today i think i dced let me see if i can okay i
cannot invite anybody to a strike team i'm logged into steam right shows yeah shows you online oh
maybe can i do see i do have an invite from you though oh you sent me a friend request
oh shit i'll accept that okay now i can invite stir to my strike team it's the only the only
person i can right now though yeah i just logged in again hey there we go uh so would you mind
going over the backstory of your character prisoner again oh i i need germa's permission
because he's already heard it and i'm a non-double tell same story oh yeah that is another rule
cross my heart i hope to die need permission uh you have the backstory the prisoner your
prisoner or something uh so my last name is prisoner it's just a coincidence but also
crazier coincidence wait no wait we wrote the backstory okay start over you know how you have
a job and like people's like in fantasy times their last name was based on their job yeah that's me
so like three generations ago my great great grandfather he said that the emperor doesn't
wipe and they sentenced our whole family lineage into prison so now it's like it's a last name it's
a family name oh i got you ready thank you for asking i appreciate it oh uh i think we got
everybody uh we're missing your judge yeah i tried joining through steam and it said unable
i think it's because you joined me while i was joining him so try try joining again i just sent
you another invite see if you get it oh there it is now popped up yeah all right let's go there we
go just took an extra minute or so it's okay we thinking you want to stick with the threes
what are you feeling i think i don't know why why was this i wasn't showing the screen the whole
time sorry about that uh oh uh oh i was bouncing around a little i was bouncing around quick get
us in and get us in an instance get us in a new instance quick do you do you want to do a three
again um let's go with a nice simple two at this point right well nice little simple two let's
chill it out with the two why not have a relaxing session drops waiting room they're on how long do
you have to watch to get a drop like 30 minutes it's 30 minutes then you need to claim it and
there's like eight drops but you have to claim it in order to get the next drop
yeah so just go to the drop page every time you get it so you should be able to get everything
available with the course of three four hours right yeah i think they they did split some of
the drops under different like days i think there were some for the relaunch beta stuff
oh all right let's go for it it's time headphones going in squalor does not automatically equate to
sinfulness thank you for your patience by the way i put this gun on but i don't know if i
really don't really want it or the devil oh no that's just the symbol oh my goodness this guy
has a lot of health i do like this new knife though it's pretty good knife is the way to go
i thought you just died who was that body that fell over i thought was his body okay okay
okay a tactical nuke inbound calling it a care package
honestly i'm bringing it back i'm bringing it back i don't care what anybody says
bringing what back fireman no he's bringing fireman back fireman confirmed for next germa rumble
i got a big guy tackler mutant okay i can't wait to get that shield oh yeah i think you're close
like 10 you get it oh dude they don't get it they'll like i thought they just got it because i had
some uh i have some trash talkers in the chat earlier saying like germa really needs to get
a shield right now like he's if he's trying to tank he needs the shield and he's really kind of
throwing by not equipping one wow oh demoralizing if i heard that i probably would i would stop
screaming yeah you see what i'm seeing that's gross oh oh it's on my face oh
don't eat me you eat me he eats me every single time i've been swallowed every time
i'm trying to get away with him i know you got god put me in such a bad place all right we're okay
yeah might as well use this yeah yeah yeah you're gonna shoot that guy you're gonna let him shoot me
oh sorry i thought you were stir oh let me let me tone down my response
my god i'm sorry you talk to your mods this way dude you don't know what the private chat's like
man
watch out we got some zeds ow ow ow too many who there are people behind us
yeah we got some zeds i said that listen to my comms i think the scariest picture i have in my
phone is still when germa gave me the death glare when i try to take his chicken uh tender to the
dollhouse like a lot about it since then but i have this like just it's just something that
pops up every now and again yeah do you feel like how your phone's like oh three years ago
this memory it's like just this fucking death it's like this scary image yeah hop down hop down
you got trapped up there with a trap yeah that would have been bad nobody touches my chicken
tenders thought it was all this so cursed because i was taking the same time that jacob was having
an allergic reaction to oh yeah lavender hand yeah that is that is like a pretty cursed image
these references are making me feel kind of excluded i'm sorry sorry i'll send it to you directly um
you can watch it yeah okay stop excluding when we didn't you heard the whole story all the context
was there i mean hey stir kreikin wasn't there when you shit your pants in overwatch
well i didn't bring that up yeah but like so we can't have we can't have experiences with all
kinds of other people i would i would love to have a similar experience with him but i don't
know if he plays overwatch well we're both playing dark tiber now what's stopping you
yeah what's not go on shit your pants well all right all right fine here next toward
i got a power up a little so are you like sick or something is there more context to that or
uh i really wanted to win a quick play game and like i really had to go uh i don't think i was
sick i think i was it was just like i really had to go just really impatient and wait hold on wait
it's multiplayer you can't stir stir you forgot to say this was when we were live on on twitch
oh yeah yeah we were me and germa were playing we're streaming it was quick play
and i really want to win the match and i didn't want to like get up and like if i didn't keep
gaming we were gonna lose yeah ilios oh king of the hill oh yeah that's intense yeah it was like
one more point i i gotta win this night you know i shit myself a little but this is not made up
this is actually that people like oh what a funny story no he shit his pants when we were
streaming overwatch this is not a made-up story and i don't even know what to do in that situation
it sounds like you were clear and transparent with everyone about it immediately yeah when we
did uh there was like a twitch rival for overwatch i think i did and they're like hey write in any
extra info you want to you know say about yourself like yeah i shit myself once to win a quick play
like i'm open about it i'm pretty proud honestly i feel like it shows my dedication as a streamer
and a gamer yeah and yeah loyal friend like when the stakes are low they don't matter it's not
ranked and you're just goofing off with your friends i'll be the guy shitting himself to win
yeah the fact that it was quick play is just like you could have just walked away
wait you could have just you could have just left i think we gotta come up here and go up
or down wait would we oh go upstairs and then drop down here bet i looked at that wall like
four times like it looks like there's kind of a ladder there is no it's an optical illusion
rapper i mean honestly like could you could we make fun of you for that i i don't think so
i really don't i think you can only make fun of someone if they're ashamed about it
right like if you can make fun of me but like i okay yeah who cares all right yeah i don't i
don't think that's even oh whatever like yeah i shit my pants who cares yeah who cares
it doesn't it doesn't like define me but also if you want to define me by that i'm fine with it
you know oh this is a bit of a maze here right now yeah we just have to go down here
i think and then you go around scanning yeah i very often um you know going to the gym got a
trainer working out going hard um i i thought i almost was gonna shit myself doing like uh
a spot once like every once in a while you know i'll like do a squat and like fart
you know it's just shit happens you know i i i don't have the i don't know the word
vowel control no i don't sure the vowel control somebody ashamed of
sphincter fortitude i think i'll go with sphincter fortitude
like what's the point honestly in society where like oh i gotta like put this much effort into
holding a singular fart like i'm straining and sweating like why not just do it i think
that's what nurgle teaches i i am the wrong person to be in a call talking about this
dude if i have to fart i will go to a different country to do it you know what i mean like i i
don't want to be in the same room as anybody i will literally get on a train and like for an
hour and then to go fart not be around anybody is it like an abandoned train okay grab the people
here's the stipulation you show up to work out you go to you go you're gonna do a deadlift and
as you go down you know that if you like strain your body you're going to fart do you just you
wuss out and you don't deadlift like there's no way around you have to like hold on hold on i
gotta go like clear my bowels uh there's an ammo thing here i need an answer wait hold on say
everything again i don't think your chat wants me to know i don't think anyone wants to hear it
they're bored of it they've moved on
i'm what why i have to put this ammo down i need it
yeah good what what a lot of shame why am i a coward i literally just was like hey let's
talk about when we pooped our pants before oh yeah when overwatch 2 beta was out i almost
did it again with stripping did you realize it was really close i really thought it was
gonna happen again but i i guess i've grown a little over the years it's good to have like
markers for yourself at least that milestone well the worst part the worst part is when you
are like oh hey guys be right back i gotta uh i gotta call my mom or something right and you
go to another room and you just you just make sure that like nobody can see or hear you and
it's just like you just go for it and somebody ends up it's so long it's like a you know what
let's just can we talk about the bible instead you know what i mean like i think it's probably a
better topic who's your favorite apostle this look i love with the way this place looks
this is great i love these big chains with the spikes on them yeah oh you can pull this
oh wow that one is that stung that's sharp one of the uh there's one of the halo like
skulls up there you gotta get oh yeah i like this tractor get in here these two star missions just
yeah just like nice yeah they're definitely compared to the three star they feel like
kraken kraken i'm over here for a sec just back here for one sec
uh did you tell anybody else about what you hold on
i said what okay you know what never mind they detect conversations they don't want it i was
i'd never mind conversation that's not okay okay so i was gonna make a thing where you oh you took
that crafting material and didn't say anything but never mind we can't even make the joke yeah
they're also shared between everyone so oh okay well nice good pickup do a backflip holy
shit he did it oh we can just get to the elevator right yes watch for flankers nice man thanks man
josh your character looks cool yeah i mean i i got the uh the pre-order armor what the hell was that
that's the special center and sharpshooter thing that you can do where you like trip all of the
guys that would be so funny is it a big uh slug guy just a lot of little guys
oh my goodness sorry oh my god i thought you were a bad guy again well no friendly fire thank you
i wonder if that's gonna be a modifier oh yeah yeah i mean my feeling is that they had friendly
fire at one point and then after testing they're like this is actually not fun and really hard
so they decide not to especially when you like have different size characters that look like
yeah it's just easy to go they climb we're getting separated we're getting very separated
all right that guy oh this is the beat there was a charger guy but he couldn't climb the ladder
oh what that's the guy that's what the guy was just talking about like as you're saying he
couldn't climb the ladder i see him running up the stairs jesus oh we got a hack oh another one
that's pretty crazy how big the jump is from two to three yeah this is it gets even like three to
four and four and five are kind of similar in my opinion but uh just no room for error so is the
jump from three to four as big as the jump from two to three close yeah i'd say three to four
yeah it's probably two to three is big three to four is bigger and then four to five is just like
how would you even as hard as that was for us to do that three on that mission i can't even imagine
that on a five it's it's really about like positioning communication like there's just
constant board so you have to like you know auger in front with the shield like you know
the flamers constantly burning that around um and then like the marksman has to be sniping the
specials so it's like you just got to be on top of your game and everyone has like a very specific
role you kind of comp rather than just doing whatever you want yeah it's just that was just
tons of communication when it works it feels so good it's really really rewarding you also get
you get like two to three times the rewards that we're getting right now
just even if you fail just like getting farther
so really even if you fail it yeah yeah you get rewards for fail oh i just got launched
wait i'm alive holy shit how do i get back up there oh you're good
oh there's a trapper between me and you guys though i think we can run down there
it's actually a good idea okay i got it wow that was lucky but yeah i was gonna say i feel like
these uh developers have figured like the proper sequel to the like left for dead formula by like
adding all these objectives and things like that felt like for a long time nobody could figure out
how to how to do how to develop the yeah the genre any further i agree and it's yeah this
feels like a i i also like it's a weird take i guess that um it did launch with a lot less
content than vermintide has but i kind of like that because it gives longevity to the game it's
not like we just oh we played it we're done it's like it there's a lot of stuff to look forward
it's like the game is still fun and enjoyable like just like how we beat it it was more focused on
like polishing the gameplay loop than it was just like jam packing it full of well the thing is
people have tried to do that formula for a long time people have really tried i can't think of
anything i mean this is probably i mean i don't sponsor stream but i've honestly that
this feels the most fun to play out of any of the other games that are in this category
that i played in a long time yeah this is people shooting over there there he comes
flame oh my that's a lot of people right here a lot of gunners at the bridges now we gotta go
restart it again oh my god how did you get up there oh my goodness i just destroyed that guy
that was so cool too you didn't even know that was happening either don't knock me off
took a while for vermintide to get to where all the content has yeah they did like regular updates
for a long time and they added like sub classes and everything that's what i'm looking forward
to is like there's definitely going to be sub classes for each of these so if you're like i
want to be you know like an auger and that's all melee based versus like all you know protection
based probably eventually yeah i want to be i want to be a rep pallie yeah it's kind of what
sell it is oh i have no idea what a rep pallie is but i hear people say it a lot i just want to be
clear oh i got down okay one sub class added per quarter so all four should come into a sub class
in a year i saw something earlier uh somebody said why does nobody play the like psychic class
oh they do do they i think yeah i've seen a few people the consensus i've heard is that the
psycher is like kind of annoying to level but at late game it's like maybe the most damage in the
game like you yeah i've been hearing that a lot that like until you get to level 10 you have like
nothing to do yeah it was like yeah oh that was the end of level yeah this is just a quick little
two that was the two we'll do that let's do two i mean uh three sorry level up oh
jimmy what's your workout routine germa i'm not i don't want to show my armpits i got the shield
finally nice oh you do nice yeah nice and you can place that too right a new gray shovel
dude we've seen them at their worst why do you care yeah you've seen your pits at their worst
yeah i don't know dude i have a weird stream let me try this new gun i mean i'll take a look at
them after the stream is a sword now oh like dude what a sick shovel oh my god this shovel was
forged by the gods i got a blue sword and get a new bolt gun i feel like having these new feats
make it like it changes it's what i'm reading right now is literally changing everything about
this character like this that's what i mean like everything is is huge for the game and also when
you hit level 10 that's when you start getting like uh the armor you'll show you new weapons
that are class specific so if you uh i mean it just feels like it opens up a lot of new stuff
that you can do plus 50 melee damage and plus 50 damage reduction to these uh different um
enemies that seems kind of insane 50 more damage melee damage to these different enemies
Jeremy you should do a stream where you swim in the open ocean with sharks and see what makes them
tick uh i don't that's not a good idea what is this one so the ball the grenades actually explode
now i actually have grenades that blow up now and it's not just a box just throwing an empty box
yeah yeah i think i saw some there's like a cluster grenade thing for the
i think it the way it works is if you throw the box and it hits a piece of armor then it
turns into a cluster bomb and explodes i feel like i can't i have to take this though this is
it's just so it's that's so much more help all right cool i also regenerate your grenades
you do uh yeah if you're like near me there's like a five percent chance on every kill that
you get a grenade really that's cool yeah man that's synergy bro yeah bro oh on a lean enemy
kill never mind it's only elites but still chance chance for grenade all right what about money what
about weapons i need you know what i want a big chunky two-hander that's what i want can i do
is that in the game have you guys unlocked the uh yeah it's definitely in the game have you guys
unlocked the um weekly reward stuff the contracts that's 11 of them oh shit okay not quite a little
further let's go to the store oh there's one here but i can't afford it yes i can uh break
down weapons you have right you aren't using to get a little more money right that's true
is that the best thing to do with the low level ones right just breaking down yeah did you say
that a gray can actually be pretty good what's the number that i should really be looking at just like
the item level it's it's it's hard to say it's hard basically if uh if there's an a weapon you
really like using and you see a gray version of it that's new in the store picking it up is usually
good because you can then upgrade it and it'll become higher level than the other stuff interesting
but once you start leveling further then you're just gonna surpass it again so yeah i would
figure at your current level just like try out new weapons yeah see what see what like what weapon
style you prefer because yeah you're just gonna out level most of this stuff eventually anyways
okay well i definitely want to buy that all right i'm gonna be shield what slot is it in
oh it's the melee slot well that's not i need to change my feet then actually no that's still
all right wait you get a club oh okay so it's it's a combo oh battle mall and slab i see all right
cool keep it on all right fun basically you guys want to go for three oh baby a triple let's do
three wait a minute hold on i could probably upgrade that shield and mace because it's a
green i could probably turn it into a blue there's a low intensity zone good there's a low intensity
three low intensity three with grim wars oh that's perfect let's do that i think it means there's
more uh wait do you need time to upgrade germa are you good i i'll probably try it just to make sure
i like it okay no it says expect it's like yeah low intensity i think means more specials less
words i don't know why it's called low intensity or maybe it's less rewards because of the modifier
i don't know less reward it had a line at the end and i i read it three times but i'm like
i didn't understand yourself not to compare to another game too much but like the way deep rock
kind of does like the the level complexity in addition to the difficulty level maybe
maybe that's what it is like how many like certain types of enemies spawn then i'm gonna put on my
charge gun i guess there's not really the random generation
i'm considering buying the game but i don't have a squad of people to play with would i be okay just
playing by myself yeah i mean i've been playing it a little bit off like solo and you know you'll
run into the issue of on higher difficulties you got to really one and two you can survive just
yeah level one and two is good to start learning in solo queues uh three and up
until you get leveled up a bit more you probably don't want to queue into also because
right now i don't think there's any restriction like you can be like level three and queue into
a tier three and yeah everyone will be like mad at you and then you'll die and that's not very
fun um yeah it seems like because i think the reason why playing solo in some of the games
maybe is i don't there's no bots right it just you just queue up with people yeah it'll fill in
bots if somebody leaves admission but then it'll refill them like usually with another person
but you can you start a game with bots i don't know i think it'll try to matchmake i think the
bots are only there if there's like no one that happened to be yeah like matchmaking at your
current i think you can start it with bots but then if people join in progress they'll just take over
and they definitely have bots in the game so it's possible they could you know change that later
oh that's fun are you liking the shield yeah
but can you i think that's the first big upgrade for you yeah you can
does it use uh stamina when you block with it or is it just full immunity to bullets
i think it eats stamina when it gets hit you also have a thing though where you can deploy it like
put on the ground yeah i wonder how you do that and it blocks infinitely it might be the alternate
attack or alternate move um oh yep you can test it if you want but it's really fun if you like
put it in a there you go like that now now how do i get to shoot around you really they won't
like oh this will block everything whoa that's cool so if we like get to a doorway and you just
drop that let's go boom then everybody can just play yeah that's fun yeah let my friends play
yeah yeah i give me way less responsibility so i can just enjoy like enjoy you guys like beating
stuff i mean i think it's pretty like necessary in the higher difficulties to have an aggro because
like sniper you you become the oh yeah choke point sniper really sniper huh he's never gonna
stop holding the shield up now something else to the left of the head i think
oh what's that a fire person yeah i don't think you can block fire
so bad i'll make a loss so bad whatever whatever yeah betty never even get himself playing this
there's two of them oh there's another one okay
wait i remember your whispers yeah there's a grim war there's a spooky spooky light up ahead
before we drop down you know what this is the first time let's not alert it i believe in you guys
all right world's first world's first world premiere the darktide gang doesn't alert the
demon host now if we do sorry no voices no i'm sorry jeremy i'm so sorry please don't kick
i i typed out of the ice right i typed in slash let's go we go around who is shooting this oh
there's a lot of people with guns coming down here so we can avoid think the witch oh it's a
demon host not a witch you're thinking of let for dead don't let it happen again only uh referring
to it in the most positive light we good let's keep machine gunner shooting i'm blocking all
the bullets you're a king we're yeah we're going the other way right no okay actually it's a demon
host well i hear it sing buzz buzz buzz buzz buzz yeah buzzing that's how it looks unsuspecting
folks in the love bees they go away don't shoot it don't shoot it oh did i shoot it i might have
it's cackling just don't you were the one saying don't shoot it don't shoot it as you shoot it
just i didn't want no we're good we're good we're good green until it was halfway it's okay okay
we're good we're good yeah we're all right just keep keep fleeing which uh which way do we go
up here up further upstairs right keep going all the way up further up okay everyone to the top of
the stairs like all of it let's just right here i love this part you love this part does that mean
this part where it goes
oh man those guys take a lot of fucking hole i fell on a hole oh god i fell in a hole too
oh wait no come back up the stairs back up the stairs oh my goodness where's all my friends
we're good here the whole board hurt our comms we all right go down there should i move keep
defending keep defending oh they're trying to get by they're trying to squish me yeah
okay you can attack now i'm down here the shield seems to be working for you it was definitely
held up there they were just too many in this tiny room i can go up here i think right that
actually was pretty cool we avoided it actually so congrats judgment come nice anyone need that
uh i i think everyone's okay oh okay all right we got a heal for you josh
actually for all of us might as well just take it and grenades if anyone needs it
going in behind behind behind spine holy shit drop down drop down drop down if you get stuck
up there you're going to die down here okay yeah that's still gonna shoot us from above
yeah but i got i got guns get behind me all right i'm dying i'm dying we did not drop down
oh you dropped down all the way yeah okay i get you his mouth is moving more than he's speaking
what can you please stop calling attention to that i'm kind of uh
uh no i don't care about it i think you really pointed out in front of a lot of people
all right i got the uh i got the setup here let me know where you want me to place it
i'm thinking about right here check that out get behind it we're gonna need to do the hacking
thing so yeah all right i'll get it oops i like using the shield as a weapon i think uh
strippin's build with that same audren shield is you can get an enchant on your mace so that
whenever you hit with it it gives you 14 toughness back like your shield oh so you can like actually
tank really well actually really like this chain sword nice i thought it was gonna like take ammo
or something wait till you get the power sword that's apparently the best weapon in the game
oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit that was a bad move
i got it wait what yeah the timing's a little funky on that sometimes
it robbed me oh careful gunners
all right good it's chainsword only for veteran uh we get a double two-handed chain sword as
zealot and we also get a chain axe but i don't know about single so far so good yeah
you know we're just warming up at the beginning of the stream yeah well don't don't you stand
well i know you understand you didn't even have the shield you weren't even a real player no we
had our comedy time and now we're just it's our gaming time oh it's one of the uh the books
oh i'll get him hell yeah there's ammo there yeah i'll take it do not read it
do not look in that book you idiot what are you thinking
oh watch it did i get hit by that even though i was one that shot it and i told you about it
let's go behind us oh it is where behind us behind me behind get behind me and talks glimmer
fire oh yeah that's right i forgot good call and a bomber somewhere right there actually the
burster oh my my gun is way too inaccurate i can't hit him from that far away elementary school level
acting elementary school play level acting
is that better or worse than ubisoft e3 yeah that's i know that's what i mean
is he is that about the voice i didn't i don't know i somebody was very rude is being insulted
so that we can appropriately be upset and engaged true yeah i'm just gonna assume it was me so i feel
bad with myself that's cool i'm gonna assume it was me i'm also gonna feel bad i think it was
me so i'm gonna feel bad too all right sounds like a plan by the way i definitely i definitely
feel way more bad than you guys do no i think i i think i feel worse no i don't know yeah you should
i feel no i feel awful about it i feel the worst you go up the ladder it's definitely up here
up here all right yeah 100 what you just took no you just took fall damage and you were making
a joke to make me come up here and you're the one that got hurt i did i didn't i heard your guy go
when he landed it's in character that my guy does like theater level acting
all right uh josh probably get this feeling the thought is actually kind of funny of like a
middle school play being put on and it's just like a ubisoft e3 trailer reveal like they all
oh what's that oh boy get me back in here get back in here oh god trapper oh that was close
can't shoot through that that was e that was that was bad acting you're right what i just did was
bad hey bud can't shoot through this yeah hey hey friends get behind me that's i agree i have the
bulwark of ages we drop some uh did we need ammo i have some i think we're good actually i found
a big bag you ever gonna stream without the wig on uh no uh that's one of those big scary things
yes it is whoa scary thing over here by the emperor what is that
oh you guys actually did 50 percent of its health and damage in the time it takes this gun to
reload thought i was gonna help kill the target oh this is the boss one i like these ones these
ones fun it was paul bearer i heard that too oh the undertaker destroy him i love paul bearer
dude he's oops it's an inspiration he really is the health oh there's a health station here
ah dog oh shit dog we uh we need a battery oh boy station we got two large shield lads man
a lot of damage calling it a bad dog
that's what i got this big fucking thing for i got one of those two
show them the hand dryer servitor i think i did before you guys seen the hand dryer servitor
did someone use the thing no we need a battery for this need to find a battery for it
hey look sir you like lore stuff look at this oh it is a hand dryer servitor that's been turned
into a hand dryer is the destiny of mankind to conquer this troubled galaxy can they imagine
are they alive uh sometimes they're still sentient and they just have to watch people
pee all day and then oh my god i wish more things in here were servitors i mean every door every
toaster every radio oh the emperor oh you goal these stairs go up
oh i guess they just call out where you're supposed to go oh help yeah that why did we
kill that guy he was looking weird oh i think the last scrims over here i feel a little spicy
uh this is an opportunity for me to really shine here
what's up buddy saw you running over here you're gonna do about that hey buddy where do you think
we're going me and my friends got a couple of loot we're trying to grab hey smush you want to
pick this up what is it it's the last scrim one line someone said hey i'm watching this in 720p
just letting you know what the what the fuck dude seven come on uh maybe we should use the
ammo now oh do you want me to do it yeah let's use the ammo now oh my god there's like bugs in my
eyes there's a bug in your eye i don't know it's like just itchy get an eye drop and a nergal
anybody want to be the one to do the eye drop for germa this is an in-character eye drop
oh still big guy and you can put the eye drop in
all right we have to go down yeah i was down there a lot of gunners get behind me get behind me
behind i already dropped down get behind me good behind me big guy but it's okay all right i'm
gonna i'm gonna try keeping off your back stay behind the shield a lot of motherfuckers
watch out for these motherfuckers did you just oh my goodness coming gotta be honest i need a
medicaid got one coming up is it this is what's the song that's the song that goes like and they're
whispering something yeah it's my favorite song been all right medicaid is gonna be up here
chat is spicy tonight location that's all right we're having we're just having fun
wow you did not take well to dying all right we're at the boss medicaid is right here
yeah i need health so do these books do anything besides you just have to take a slot up
uh yes if you look at the purple that's currently re going um it's gonna be permanent purple on us
based on the grims we have so half of our health is just gone by default and you get extra rewards
for picking these up right yes more money more experience all right so for that medical thing
if you want to put it on the boss like halfway through the fight then we can just
regen while on him and then that will be easy peasy my voice is ear piercing it's so awful what
was it a question and i don't understand it what well i don't know if it was a question
i was just getting my like germa impression down for the future it's like adding that one
to the repertoire box buster that's gonna be a problem he hit me he's gone all right
come on come on come on come on so he's supposed to switch to melee when we're in melee but uh
yeah there you go what's the time to take some a minute reload the gun really rough
i'll see how you oh you're dead dead oh if you guys want to go get a stereo
uh four seconds he'll be up i'm up all this time in the room
oh there he is okay i'll try and go get to him but i'm very low on health too so
oh don't you dare no guards on you okay cool don't you dare do that oh did we drop
the medical thing dropped yeah all right one more one more we got this come on i'm the goddamn tank
come on gwen let's go got it well done boys what is that oh my goodness oh secondary boss okay
that was epic the game is available on steam right now if you go to steam
no that's yeah yeah it's fun game available on steam right now just came out of beta
the launch party today pretty fun yeah really fun we got all the grimoires oh that one's got
two oh just shy of two levels nice oh i got the bolt gun yeah oh you're in like the bolt gun
am i i do like the single shot thing it is a single shotter it is it is you say
yeah and it is it's basically you're firing explosive like red bull cans of people
red bull cans yeah okay see if i can get one you guys good for another one there's one more
you can do one more sure i'll be playing all night i think either way yeah yeah i have to uh i have to
just get out of here uh pretty soon i gotta go over get ready to fly an airplane
oh yeah you are doing that tomorrow should be pretty interesting oh there's another cut scene
oh yeah watch it how familiar are you with the concept of flying like what you have to do
i mean i've played uh microsoft flight simulator because it was free on game pass i played it for
like 10 minutes
we'll see
you did a five terabyte install to play for 10 minutes that's actually that's actually kind of
true you should memorize something really specific to impress austin yeah don't worry i'm gonna make
sure i go in there with a bunch of language in lingo i'm gonna know i don't worry oh it was an
emperor's grip i did get a bolt gun cool sick and it's actually really freaking good thank you
emperor praise be praise be praise be did i get anything new got this a while ago okay
i'm gonna spend my gamble currency oh you're gonna gamble give me a new knife oh my god it's
another axe i'm gonna fucking cry give me a new knife oh my god it's another fucking axe
every time i i've literally rolled 12 times with this and it's only been axes and it's my least
favorite weapon i think that's a sign from the emperor he wants you to use the axe i will not
i hate it i didn't even look and the weapon that i really wanted was available i didn't even look
so uh curios do those just uh those just appear at random or can you buy those too
you buy them i think i have this a lot but i don't have any yet i'm ready i'm gonna hold on to this
yeah hold on everything okay so what's the what do you want to do for one more with this particular
group and by all means if you guys keep playing keep playing hmm one more chill zone one or two
now let's do a three yeah you know what let's go let's go high intensity engagement zone
or now fuck that we'll do this one this one's really good ending i'm really close to some drops
yeah good you'll get it it's different this is gonna take definitely more than 15 20 minutes
go for a four i don't think we're ready for yeah i don't know i mean we could try but it
doesn't want to try getting destroyed i mean do you want to go out on a four and just see how badly
we get just absolutely decimated let's try it depends if you want to finish or not too late
all right well we're good let's do what we know what we know we know what to do i think a four
would be hard for an 11 and an eight i think you'd need at least yeah like a 15 to 20
yeah i'm trying out a new outfit i think i look pretty good
wait are you using pajamas and then like a little hat it's unfortunate that the uh you know it is
like a prison necklace i i want it to be an ascot but maybe when i get to level 30 and they free me
i i was gonna say it looks like an ascot so it it plays you know yeah i think i look good in it
for it being actual prisoner arm like a tire i think i pull it off yeah you definitely
just realized something really really important people have not been able to see how much ammo i've
had the entire stream i mean it's not like they're playing oh dude they said stop
shut up like you haven't done that before stop they couldn't even see yeah they couldn't even
tell how can they follow the action you thought you did that a month ago i saw it shut up
like you've never done that before bro
whatever come on focus up focus up forget about the ammo oh i got my bolt gun yeah what
uh do you know what the like special ability on the sword is is it like a parry yeah yeah okay
it uses some stamina when you hit back when you block that'd be such an awful way to go
just four people just smashing you just smushing your head with different like big blunt objects
and swords and stuff holy shit this gun is insane behind me behind behind behind behind all right
now move forward big guy that kind of makes me feel bad like how am i going to use other guns
yeah once you start using the bolter it's the reason i don't use it is it's uh just so slow
behind like load and get set up that i i like the slow gun the other guns and yeah the
bolter is definitely going to be compared to the plasma gun this thing like aoe god
uh i would get behind me i come up like turkey geez i feel a little inaccurate there's all oh
my god stay behind me oh dog oh my dog they did it again where's this fucking dog he jumped up
oh that guy's a scream wait maybe i mean i would i would feel that way too i just turn around and
see these fucking guys running towards me with a knife i think if i get like a really good uh
never mind oh trapped oh man oh i am i'm dead i went from 100 to zero that is so many
yeah i might just not have enough damage at this level but i don't know it's hard to tell
we're good i'm good yeah hey the armored guys what's the strategy on the uh the fully armored
um just dodge primarily because they wind up i just found out you can't really dodge backwards
does it like it goes in a line yeah yeah i keep having that problem style is there a particular
weak point on those guys too or not not their heads weirdly enough i always dodge backwards
and i get hit every time problem is like i go to shooting head but good to know yeah they're all
armored but their head is the most armored apparently um they're kind of a bastard but
i have like a bleed build so i just hit them a few times and they that stacks and die anyway so
for bolters we're fucking up too filters are like a huge ammo piercing
is the uh chainsword good for armor or bad um it's good if you rev it otherwise
that's what i mean i'm gonna stop swearing when you read it it does uh
they give me my arab armor piercing armor piercing this it is a grimoire look it's like in the
fucking uh inside the thingy that's weird do you think this is cool or hot this this is probably
minty fresh i'm thinking like spearmint chili do you think it's like a like 50 degrees 60 degrees
yeah it makes it look like a numbing sensation that's why i think it's uh
like the gas form of nickelodeon gas oh i wonder what that would be like heated up to the point
that it's gaseous yo it heals you oh shit so when katie perry got like a face full that one time
the uh you guys remember floam loam was where it is that loam way better than gack
yeah everyone's like oh gack remember gack gack was dog shit okay floam was way better i think
this sniper floam it was this had like little beads in it it was this squishy like yeah it's
hard to describe dots you ever had dipping dots yeah there's another heal up here it's the ice
cream of the future there's a station up here this with one more in it well we can't climb
back up there oh never mind yeah we also are purples from the grimoire it's not from damage
ah right right right right right old grimmy oh here they come remember uh astronaut ice cream
i do it's awful oh yeah actually i had it once dried yeah it's terrible was there like
i remember as a kid i was confused if i was allowed to have it because it was like i'm not
an astronaut oh is it you're not allowed yeah yeah i don't know why they like why they were
giving us it felt like every us like uh shit trap every gift store had them for some yeah every
gift store like every uh yeah any kind of scientific like museum astronauts hate this it's weird want
to buy some it's weird no one actually likes it you just keep spinning me around i'm trying to
pick you up all right get up oh fuck oh man you gotta be careful there's a big guy right behind you
all right time to get up thank you
guns oh okay everyone in the elevator no okay uh i am in the elevator i spawned up here actually
well wait you up where i respond right up here oh shit you did he's got me he's got me
brian griffin yep that's brian griffin yep
he can't stop himself from making family guy noises we i mean we were doing that earlier a
little yeah uh everyone do your best family guy ready um what's your excuse that also
he can't stop himself oh well i mean to be fair we also did it earlier
yeah that does it's kind of double downing on the can't stop yourself thing
well no i'm saying like i i all right i'll take the l stay behind me please stay behind me please
all right well they're all dead that guy got hit in like the fucking cheek with the grenade
i'm the only guy back here that is a sniper i believe is it i don't know let me wait the normal
dude wait wait wait let me can i get it oh it was right in the head from like a hundred miles away
oh you hit him oh this part oh come on he's been like beating the shit out of this guy
thank you sorry that took so long you don't like the bolt gun that's a big raid what is
stairs type 3000 people no i figured what it was called the hellbore last time i think really like
that still whoa wait wait whoa yeah the charge up rifle i never tried it thank you philly in for the
raid thanks appreciate it what's up thanks welcome everybody and actually the uh the revolver yeah
thanks for the rate bro hey what's up we're playing some dark tide oh you can buy now on steam
by the way what it's big i swear to god they're glued to me yeah i don't know what you uh were
streaming philly but hope you had a good one we're having a good time over here that's right germa
we're killing it in dark tide those guys i mean behind me i you really should get behind me because
there is a big machine gun person down here i'm running around is he dead yeah there's like three
guys behind you hitting you wait was i just getting like like the back of my head
you are 100 getting 100 oh that's why my health is so low oh isn't it better if i take the hits
and not sing a raid song we don't we don't do raid songs anymore this is like it's not 2018
could we do a raid song no because they will never stop asking and and anytime i raid somebody they
will they will just make that person sing a raid song i had no idea what it was in reference to
i thought it was a world of warcraft thing you know what i should have let you believe that and
asked you to do one i wouldn't have known one if i wanted you to do one so i could learn behind
behind behind me yep oh what the hell oh a big gunner behind you oh that's bad oh getting this
little uh getting this little area here behind me here then i'm telling you get behind me
i'm behind you everyone enter the alcove fine i'll sing the raid song thanks good nice work
and then did you bro fist the camera uh i need this
thanks and a bro fist that's right what did we do here i think that guy just died no this person
really hammer guy where coming up right next to you oh my god i dreamt down oh i dropped down
i am almost out of ammo do we drop ammo uh do we have an ammo yeah there's ammo over here
yeah ammo right there i get a little bit don't stop making stop making squeak sounds
all right sir oh that's a lot of motherfuckers down here oh i got trapped oh my god he's gonna
smash me i'm sorry man i can't help you no are you serious all right do you see what's going on
over here look look at look at look at the movie theater screen look at all that's what you can
see i got it i got it i'm good i'm good oh okay oh shit i wouldn't have picked me but oh shit
come on cranking cranking cranking cranking cranking all right let's do it come on stir i'm
coming i'm dead i'm actually down dude use your melee weapon dude i can't have to defend otherwise
i'm gonna lose you gain consciousness when you swing your weapon you don't know that
nice thing is we're all down oh i'm down it's all right i think you're all right i think you
because there's no big scary things is that there's that one guy with the green pods on his back but
that's it all right good job are we safe you guys if you guys are on us just be careful when we get
here we got it sorry smush oh we got it we got it wait did you i think we were behind you guys
i think you're up here i think you guys are up i think we're ahead yeah we're ahead
boy we have one of those green sword guys
shoot the big coming why can i not pick you up where's it right here i got him every time
it's just like a target he doesn't ever throw you he just fucking whales on you he just shoves me
behind uh two large lads on me yep grenade
what happened over there i don't know why i'm having a tantrum
okay miku's in chat right now hot city miku's no shit actually i'm a huge fan thank you you know
what to do boys oh yeah yeah boys oh my god they were all you know i think they were stuck i don't
think they could move i think almost a healing because miku's in chat miku's here really what
should what get down here first oh people people people yeah you need that oh he took
let's prime the goober oh this part here i almost just walked in anybody need ammo
i uh half i got a uh ammo box if we need it eventually here i'll throw it down
i'll do it after these phases maybe yeah don't fall in the lava
uh oh it's still happening how why i won't let you burn my friends oh behind you smush
oh it's why you stand still who stands still oh god two different grenade oh my god we're
separated yeah meet you at the next one goodbye this is a totally great perk disclaimer oh keto
right i can throw this underhand yeah someone just blew my mind with that as well
what why would you do it underhand like if they're slow serve but i don't know it doesn't really feel
well i'm always throwing grenades and i'm jumping into piles
also i'm pressing the button and it's my job
well i i knew it was gonna hit me for us yeah it was really
it's brave oh that's healing over there isn't it oh i would love some of that is that healing
oh that is going to work i'm gonna put the ammo down here too yeah all right go it's rocking
rocking rocking we got another raid holy shit
hold on hold on i have like three brain cells i have sorry hold on
oh there's too many and i'm supposed to be the tank and i'm not doing my job
you're good just get over to this side oh you fell off do the raid song no i'm falling down i
have fallen down thanks for the raid i appreciate you thanks for coming and having some fun
we're about to we're good we're gonna survive he threw this stun grenade
which is actually doing really good oh yes nice did it we're good we're good we're good i fell
i fell i'll try and cover you i'm gonna get him oh well my arms look good all right
tug the leash go no we're not getting split goodbye no just leave me just leave me you
don't actually get any minuses for uh for not getting everyone out oh okay it's not so smush
is canonically left here i mean i guess yeah we're not valuable enough to uh reward saving us
oh my god my screen but that was sorry it's like there's so many sounds in my head right now
uh lana lazar lana lazar appreciate it thank you for the raid thank you yeah yeah thank you
for the raid welcome everybody there we go who raised back to back let's go that was 20 minutes
ago oh i was there was a lock on yes you're dead in canon you're you don't get any experience
you're dead i'll be in the book nice job nice job yeah what a moment i missed the motive the
not the motive the note is wrong no it's just there's music playing in both my ears and i can't
talk when it happens what music does all the soundtrack i get speech jammed when this
sounds going to both ears talked about it many times this game is very overwhelming when like
everything's rushing at you that's really cute like funny little quirk oh boy all right check
the store see if you get anything cool that's right what's new anything good oh shit there's
a fucking 300 power diaper oh i'm so mad that was on camera and i'm taking this too are you
shitting me in this diaper yeah i can finally get a curio oh yeah that's so much man i hate it
when i hear things with both my ears at the same time you know for all the shit talkers out there
i'm just telling you when there when i have both of my ears blocked with it doesn't matter what it
is if i cannot hear myself talking completely without any filter on it it causes it just makes
it it's like muffled it's weird and i can't talk correctly i have to be able to hear myself talk
i have to be able to hear the ambience of the room i've i've known you for a long time and
i can confirm you do need to hear yourself talk
i reached through the monitor and strangled that was pretty good that was pretty good
i'll let you have that one okay i i have officially been allowed to have one
hey craig can you know what the uh like the primary action and secondary action numbers
mean on like a gun like on a laze gun i'm so roasted i don't know what to do anymore
uh primary action is i think like hip fire and then secondary is like aiming down the sights
i'm trying to figure out like the numbers are pure damage or what they yeah for the okay
for the knife for example light attack is a slash for my dagger and a heavy attack is is pierce and
it's a heavy that's the heavy attack okay i think yeah so crowd control means what exactly so the
shield has 40 this one i have 47 percent crowd control is that how far back you knock them back
when you push them what is crowd control all right um so it's when it's knockback so it's how
much knockback it is okay that's cool i need an opinion from criken sure oh there we go it shows
on when you inspect it'll show a crowd before level 30 or like really high item gear is it a
total waste to use any of my cubes for like the requisition stuff i would i would save the cubes
for 30 yeah but i would use the oh no wall what's the other stuff the requisition man
you can use the like the little pringles can looking things yeah but not i was i'd save the
cubes yeah germa's right there on that screen you were on um yeah crowd control and defensive
and like kind of describes what so that you can actually go look at all the this the weapon like
the details of the weapon like this 80s yeah there's a full you guys know this that's that's
a lot more info than i really i don't think that was in the in the beta was this is a full breakdown
of literally every single aspect of this whole weapon damage and stagger heavy attacks special
actions oh the guy crashed the game no that's really cool though well it's perfect timing
too much knowledge profane too much info yes that's one way to get out of trying to a level four
do you want to try a level four we want to try level four yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah sure
okay my confidence is growing my confidence is growing i think we can do it look at i'm growing
my confidence level level four should we do level four let's freaking do it do it oh but i don't
know if i have enough time i don't what if we're not good enough what if we can't do it well if we
can't do it then you'll die early what if i don't have enough damage then you just use your big
shield what if i say something stupid and people don't think it's funny oh i can't help with that
what if you guys never talk to me again i wasn't planning on it oh i went to the meat grinder and
it kicked me from the group you guys really do you actually i mean i left do you guys really
want to go forward or do we just you know let's go for it all right fine let's do it we might not
survive an entire round but we can definitely try why not what it's like let's go for it shouldn't
take long no it's going to take probably five we'll find out one way or the other really quickly
yeah let me just get back in again another moment why that's why what's going on people
are making moments here can anybody in chat make a moment or does it have to be a mod just the mods
i think you get five a month so you might as well use them right might as well you only get five
moments a month what if you had more moments and i you i thought i used them all for the year or
something didn't i make all the ones that month in like one stream oh the longest stream or whatever
if you have more than five moments in a month they're not really moments they're not special
enough oh we had like 30 month no you didn't yeah i noticed that there's not i only had one
moment from your stream this uh last couple months i don't know did it very much happen i don't know
um it's out of notification we have one new moment from stirs channel i was just like oh
i don't think i've ever made a moment in a while it is the 41st and uh i i'm sorry that i burned
you so bad earlier i i apologize you know i know you're trying to get back i'm trying to get back
i'm trying to get back in what do you got going on stir i have going on what do you got going on um
well my life is totally derailed um i just have myriad is all i have what only thing in my life
what is myriad i have nothing else what is the myriad myriad is my tabletop game that kraken
played in a while ago and it takes a lot of work to make and stuff so not much has been going on
because it is the uh holiday times and all of my players are doing other things
and where can they find this uh this game uh the myriad is uh tabletop streams on my channel on
twitch tv slash stir is that stir like uh like the star or with an e s t e r so like stare it's
pretty cool i don't why do why do people pronounce that stare why doesn't he suddenly get an a
let's start with an e at the end right no no s t e r
do we want me to make the party you want to throw some invites around three logs i went to the meat
grinder like a fool so you can make the party again i will just throw out invites are we all
in the game uh yeah i'm still in do i need to leave the existing party uh probably i would say
it leaves strike team okay there's the old smush there you are i can invite you here
and then stir all right let's try level four let's do it up all right so i like to hear
our options are that one's pretty straightforward well it's the only four so i guess that's what
we're doing that's the one we're doing all right so if we're going to lose in in literally five
uh it's always an option reagan what do you got going on um honestly i've just been playing
a lot of dark tide a lot of uh what else i've been playing played wow the expansion launch
yeah dragon flight someone my friend playing that is it any good looks actually entertaining
i'm not even a wow player it's yeah it's been the most fun i've had with a launch
of wow since like for many years the thing that i was surprised was the uh how fast the dragons
fly yeah it feels like the first expansion where blizzarded like values the player's time
which is saying something so it doesn't feel like you're made to do a really repetitive
shit over and over again every single day to stay you know like did you did you like legion
yeah i think legion's my favorite i think that's the best state the game that was ever in i so this
is honestly this feels like the most like legion since uh really yeah in terms of uh
in terms of just like what the start of the expansion feels like really okay
put two headphones in for this oh boy two headphones you're gonna hear yourself that's
how you know we're getting serious godspeed everyone you'll notice things take a little
bit longer to kill and we don't have more ammo do we no we don't anything we might have less
ammo i think i know why this gun has so much higher damage it's slower firing but it might
be better oh that would be horrible ranger oh all right archman why is it being so weird
what did i do where's this guy going he just walked into the fire it's this guy i walked right
by him he's hiding in there he's always a weird person i mean am i always weird i don't think it's
always holy shit you know what to do yeah i'll hear yeah you hold there i'll just cut there are
so there are there are many gunners all right that's more people than i've ever seen in this
whole game yeah they like exponentially increase holy shit i couldn't stop that guy i couldn't
stop that guy oh my god what the fuck get out of my way dude we can't even fit in this right
just spit all over my computer they can't even dude what the fuck doing fine is the
gunner in here with us now all right back it up back it up back it up back it up
is that big guy in the corner alive or dead okay that's that's turbo no no there's one
like in the corner looking at the wall that guy this gunner this they're all on the stairs too
i'm going in yeah i'm i'm actually really surprised we lived through that
yeah it's just like he's got a coordinate a lot better i haven't been paying attention
at all i forgot we did a four and i've been like talking to my chat and just like
and then i saw that like the doorway jam so does it increase the amount of enemies per tier
uh yes i mean the answer has to be yes there's no way let's get it there's no fucking way
yeah it makes endless forward i think is the default for four and then also more specials
so and everyone's got more help yeah this is unbelievable yeah it starts to feel like a
different game once you like the bomber across the way then once you get good at it like you
don't want to play anything lower yeah i feel like you end up wasting your time all night
no it's okay oh boy oh
i even have like
everyone to be attacked oh really i mean i'm standing still but all in the back
i did i guess i did shoot him a lot i don't know dude you're good dude all right let's go
dude i i think we're doing okay i think we're doing all right the next area is usually pretty
hard and so i'm worried we might have to like all back into a corner we have healing coming up
who's taking the grenade and technically we can wait to heal until after the next word in case we
want to you know save it i i don't why am i getting targeted all right i think i even
turned that off never mind what'd you do um i died oh that's i thought that was you i died and i blame
the game all right we'll get you because i uh take a health oh holy shit somebody's doing a
lot of damage going down oh they hit very hard oh it's sniper it's a sniper
you can get him
what the hell
oh it's gonna be close okay no shit just in time both of us i'll respawn
oh my god i have no more help i have no help i have no more help
keep hitting them keep hitting them wait there's a healing station right here
we're good we're good we're fine okay they're up there uh shall i use it now yeah all right
let's go get them there are a lot of gunners defending us good to know like three machine
gunners all right let's not hit it yet we're just gonna just gonna try to get them up first yeah
that's a good idea they do take a lot of hits now one gunner got away yeah thanks bro all right
we're good all right thank you all right we'll save the other two healing for after this i have
a heal kit thing do you want me to put it down now uh let's wait till a little bit into the fight
and that way we can use it in case we get
do i shoot through germa if he's like in between yeah there's no friendly fire so
i just wasn't sure if my bullets would go through yeah to make it clean exit i have an ammo box if
we need to as well all right let's activate it uh usually i think if germa's here with a shield
guarding the front there's a lot of gunners usually come from the front and then we watch
the sides his back all right well shield up you guys snipe the gunners so i'll watch the melee
and you guys dog he's gone he's gone just keep watching vampire they're approaching
vampires they're approaching music oh okay they're coming from our right okay do you take over melee
take the right on the left on the left gunners up
on our left again left and right where what's going on i got grabbed i got grabbed
nice all right we got through the thing i'm dead i'm dead i am also dead unfortunately
what the heck what did i do what did i just do oh shit my knife just barely nicked a uh
explosive thing and it literally threw me down that's it well it just takes one oopsie oh that
was that was i got surrounded by ragers i was incredibly unlucky we literally would have had
it if i didn't pull myself up no i mean we made it further than i thought yeah i thought we were
gonna die in the first 10 seconds you know like practice i think he's able to get practice makes
bad but so we're gonna get a okay amount of experience you got level 10 out of that so
that's not bad oh yeah and again i think 10 is a pretty big power boost generally
yeah like all the money we just got so that is a lot of money for failing
so auto guns versus laze guns what do you think is better for laze guns for kicking out elite
targets auto guns for horde probably openness on the cleave beat helps a lot with tanking
good to know all right that was fun yeah thank you that was fun yeah thanks for playing everybody
uh see you guys all probably soon i mean i i think the game's really fun if um maybe i'll
keep playing it you guys still playing you know it i'm probably level a new character and then
i will because i want to try what yeah i want to try one of the other characters i actually do
want to try the uh the psyker or whatever it is yeah that's that's my next one too
yeah i feel like a lot of people are saying oh that that's my second character there's gonna
be a shitload of those running around in the next like few weeks yeah i think i mean the ogren looks
looks fun too it is it is guy yeah over it's fun all right guys i'll uh imagining some of you guys
probably gonna keep going if not then we'll uh i'll talk to you guys soon thanks for playing um yeah
sorry about the early confusion with the party set up that's my i guess i sent too many invitations
out yeah i did that actually i i goofed blame me well no i wouldn't say that no please please
i like it off on it like just i see fine thank you warhammer for sponsoring the stream i really
appreciate it uh that was a lot of fun games really fun games great uh looks like it's going
to be continued to be supported warhammer big huge shout out go grab it on steve if you like
what you saw it was fun it's on steam and i went is it on any other platform right now let's see
so it's on x is it on xbox oh it is on xbox oh it's coming to xbox maybe well all i know is
it is on steam it's 40 seems like there's quite a lot of content so i'm very happy with that i'm
very happy with getting sponsored too so that's really cool thanks guys for watching that's going
to be it i will see you guys uh i'll see you guys tomorrow on austin's channel austin show
i'll be flying a plane which is going to be very interesting so see you tomorrow good night goodbye
follow austin's channel there's no such thing as a host anymore on twitch so you know we'll just make
sure that's in the chat here i'll see you soon thanks for sticking around thanks for the race
too if you were here from one of the raids there was a couple of big raids that came in
thanks to those who that decided to raid this channel appreciate it see you guys tomorrow
don't really know what to expect but i'm sure we'll find out yeah the time when is it starting
that's a good question i know austin tweeted about it what time tomorrow is it starting
it's set for 4 p.m eastern okay 4 p.m eastern all right so that would be 1 p.m pacific call your
mother see you later take care of yourselves goodbye ta ta talks too loud because i know
people don't expect it but i just got called out so hard and i have to just explain
somebody said omega lull that manual lexus music change like i i don't know how you can tell i did
that you're like ah that manual that drag the volume slider down how did you even know
i don't know how you knew i did that i slowly grabbed it and was just like let's go
really really quietly slowly to the left was it that obvious is it though all right whatever i'll
see you guys tomorrow take care yourself see you soon bye