Early. Well, I'm early because I have food here, and I don't want it to get cold. How are you guys doing? Hope everybody's doing good.
It's gonna take a lot of concentration for me to do this. I'm gonna try as hard as I can, but I'm gonna hope I don't crack.
Today, we're going to begin by eating a Whopper from Burger King and a few other items.
So, uh, this is very specific. If you know, you know. And I'm not gonna explain it again.
So if you have no idea why I'm doing this, then just hate me in about 15 minutes. I know, I know.
The people that weren't here a few weeks ago, they're just gonna be like, what the fuck is wrong with you? Why are you doing this? I have to do this.
It's been, this has been burned in my mind. I have to, I have to do this. I need to.
But anyways, stop stalling and eat it. Hold on a second. That's why I started early.
I have a Whopper with cheese, a Chicken Junior, and some Burger King french fries. And let's get, wait, no, don't eat anything. Don't touch anything.
Please, I can't, I can't read what you said. I can hear the Whopper. You hear that wrapping paper? You hear that wrapping, hold on.
Oh, don't open it yet. Hold on, people aren't here. I can't believe he's doing this. Well, believe it.
Because it's, I'm doing it. And I'm gonna try as hard as I can to do what I told you I wanted to do.
I've like tried to like get like a bunch of laughs and shit out of me. I've tried as hard as I could.
I did like some breathing exercises to make sure I can do this. Eat it in 20 seconds? What?
I have to get it out now. That's why I started a little early because I need to like get it out of my system.
I stole a french fry. I'm sorry. Everybody's going to fucking hate this. I don't care. I like this. I'm doing it.
You guys ready? Eat it through the paper? Eat, eat it through the paper. Hi, hi, how you doing?
Why am I like blinking? So what I have here, I have a Whopper with cheese. Pretty cool.
Now, I also have a Chicken Junior. I don't know what the numbers mean. One to, one to twelve? What's the twelve?
What is one? Eat it with the shell on. Eat it with the shell. It's the range of what?
But what is the, I don't understand, one through twelve. The numbers are so you can rate it afterwards.
One through twelve? That doesn't make any sense. Ooey gooey. I know, just wait. What if he doesn't eat it with the skin on?
Okay. So I've got a drink too. I've got a Coke. And I've got french fries, obviously.
So, as you guys know, I don't really eat fast food. I'm not a fast food guy. I don't really like it.
I find it to be, it's not for me. So I'm not sure I'm going to like this. I really don't think it's going to be something I enjoy.
Not a fast food guy. Me. Don't eat it very often. So I'll give it a try though. I'll try it.
We're going to start with the Whopper. This is the Whopper with cheese. I don't know about this. I don't know if I'm going to like this.
Let's see what it looks like. Okay. It doesn't look that bad. It looks okay. This is the Whopper.
I don't know about this. I'll try it. I'll try a bite. And we'll see.
Okay. I'm going to go for a bite. Oh my God. Oh my God. It's so good. Oh my God. It's good. It's okay. It's good.
Let me try another bite and find out. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. It's so good.
You can't see me. Fuck. I already ruined it. It was so hard to do that.
I took two bites.
I knew I was going to fuck the whole thing up. I'm sorry.
Somebody wrote in chat. I shouldn't have looked at chat at all. Somebody wrote, why the fuck is he doing this?
And it was no capitals. It was just a random name. Oh my God. I couldn't even get through two bites of doing it.
I fucking hate this. All right. Let's go. It's not bad. It's okay.
Oh my God. I can't do it anymore. I'm not going to do it anymore.
Actually, Burger King sauce went through my nose. Burger King sauce went into my nostrils and out of my nose.
And coke at the same time. That sucked. That was not fun. That was horrible.
Anyways, let's hold on. I need to wipe my nose. I have whatever's on here coming out of my nose.
Please stop this. Let me describe how it tastes.
Okay. What I really love about this the most is definitely the cheese. It's got this ooey gooey cheese on it that just melts and gets all over the patty.
And the pickle, perfect amount of acidity. It's actually pretty good. I don't hate it.
It's a cheese with some adjectives. Thin. Sliced. American. Fresh patty.
That one wasn't for a joke. This one was real. You're describing yourself.
What's the right amount of acidity exactly? I don't know. Just enough for you to get the little sourness. You get the vinegar flavor.
Potatoes. They're perfectly crispy. They're a little gross. But they're pretty good.
I actually like Burger King fries. 10k people are watching this cursed garbage.
All I wanted out of this was that first scene of the, oh my god, because I want you to use it wherever you want.
Say, Ushi, no. And you guys, seriously, you wanted me to do that the entire time I ate this fucking hamburger?
There's no way I would have done that. Every single time I take a bite I was supposed to do that.
I took two, three bites and I went into a full meltdown. I couldn't do it. I can't do that.
What would you use that for? I don't know. For a fucking school project. You could use it as a school project.
Is it weird that I find this part to be disgusting and I don't want to bite that part? You know what I mean?
Oh my goodness. It's like in my nose. Bite that part? I don't like tomato and shit.
I don't like it. There's too much stuff on here.
I'm going to part your hair down the middle. No. Okay. A little bit of sourness.
Why is the toothbrush still there? Because I feel like I want it there.
You know, actually, I'm actually excited to try the chicken sandwich.
Stop looking at me in the eyes when you chew.
Why? You don't do that when you're hanging out with your friends?
You go to a restaurant? You don't do that? Is it weird that I do that?
When I like them out of the restaurant, I usually do this. I usually take a big bite of the food like this.
I don't want to make a mess. Fucking God damn it.
Whoopsie. It's kind of weird, but it's not that bad.
I don't do that. We're just having a fun routine here.
This bite right here, that's going to be a zonk bite. Zonk bite.
He's absolutely zonked. What is it? Zonk? What do you guys say?
How's the sauce? It's pretty good. It's kind of a combination of...
Although I'm going to give Doc some points here on the Whopper.
It's a little runny. I don't like runny sauce.
So this is a little runny. Once you get to the middle here.
Yeah, that's too runny. If that's too runny, you get minus one full letter grade.
Put on predictions. For what? For what? Is this man going to die?
I mean, like, eventually? Probably like 50 years?
Predicted if you can eat the whole burger in one more minute?
The whole rest of the burger in one minute? Um, no.
Actually, you know what? I could probably do it.
Let me take... Can I? Alright, hold on. One minute's a long time.
You can do it. You're far.
The rest of this in one minute? Wait, I can wait money off the debt if I get to do this in one minute.
Why don't you predict? I can do it. I know I can.
100 million? That's not worth it. I'll have diarrhea in like fucking four hours.
No, none of this is worth it. Nope, not doing that. I'm just going to enjoy it.
If you eat a hamburger as fast as you can, guys, you're going to shit your pants.
You're going to go... It's going to be horrible.
If you eat a full fucking cheeseburger in less than two minutes, you're going to have diarrhea.
It's going to happen. It doesn't matter from what restaurant.
You can make it in your house, on your sofa, on your sewing machine.
You can make it in your own house and it's still going to happen.
Okay, the french fries have still got the crisp.
Get a look. Pretty decently salted. Okay?
Alright, I'm dripping shit all over me. Hold on.
Quarter pound of beef. Quarter pound is way better.
Yeah. You want my review of the Bird King Whopper?
Quarter pound is a hundred times better. Done. Done. Like, that's it.
Do I need to give this a score? Quarter pounder is way better.
Yeah, that's my review. Quarter pounder is better.
You cameras off center? I'll fix that. How about now?
The chicken sandwich, I'm going to give it a minute though.
Jeremy, eat a salad. You're getting fat.
Good. That's what I want.
I want to just grow in size. I want to be...
I told you I was trying to put weight on. I told you that.
I was like 130 pounds like five months ago, six months ago.
I've put on like 25 pounds of pure, absolutely fat.
There's none of its muscle. I haven't really worked out at all.
I've been trying to do some walking lightly.
Oh, it's all fat. All of it.
I've been gaining weight.
I want to top out somewhere around like 155.
That's where I'm like, all right, slow down.
And no, and guys, I'm not eating.
I'm not eating like Burger King fucking Whoppers every day.
To get, to gain weight. No.
I'll give you an endorsement here.
This is the endorsement part of the stream.
Those heels, I got that heel for a reason.
I drank that shit every day, morning and night, to try to put on some weight.
And it's not, it's not like bad calories.
They're not like, there's no dead calories in that.
It actually helped a lot.
Being able to take the extra calories with liquid.
That's not just junk.
And there's no soy in that. Stop saying it.
I keep seeing that in the chat room and it's making me very upset.
There is no soy in Huel.
It's soy free.
And I know you linked a bunch of bullshit, but the ones I have don't have soy in them.
There's no soy in Huel.
You're upsetting me.
Predict it. No, no, no, no, no.
Don't predict it. You could just game this.
How many guys, when you have a french fry, how many folders we got here in the chat?
How many folders we got?
We got folders in here? How many folders we got, right?
That's what a serial killer does.
How many serial killers are here?
If it's too big, you have to like spring it in there.
You can't fold little ones.
How many guys are, when you get the little thin ones, you go like this.
Kind of like a bunny rabbit.
I mean, when I know nobody's watching, I do that.
How many guys are just, are full swallowers, you know?
We got folders, we have chompers, what about swallowers?
You know, you just, it's gone.
And sometimes you're hungry.
This is, dude, I choked and fucking, I'm so glad I got out of the camera's way like 10 minutes ago.
I read that chat message saying like, why the fuck is he doing this?
And I hope, did I get down fast enough?
Did I get down there fast enough before like this liquid started coming out of my nose?
I hope so.
What about splitters?
Dude, the thing that everybody, onion, onion ring, I got an onion ring.
Burger King just got a half of a point right there.
You always get one onion ring, treasure chest, buried in the sand of french fries.
That's a huge moment.
I'm kind of freaking myself out because why would, how does that happen?
I didn't like, hit the ground or anything, right?
Why does that happen?
They use the same vat, okay.
This is an area where like they just like fell all over the counter and somebody was like just scraped them in.
You're paranoid.
Don't, cigarette bullshit.
I want to try the chicken sandwich.
Ah, already hate it, already hate it.
Oh, it's getting everywhere.
I already hate it.
I don't know about this one.
I know what a McChicken is like and we'll see, we'll see.
It's a little sloppy.
The lettuce is not perfectly packed.
Let's give it a try.
I'm going to give it a solid bite.
It's not even close to the McChicken.
Not even close.
The outside has this weird texture to it where it's like they tried to make it crispy, like a pretend crispy.
It just kind of tastes like you're chewing on bread crumbs.
No, McChicken is 10 times better.
Nice try though.
Nice try Burger King.
Nice try, not even close.
The King is in chat.
You got King, whatever, clown in chat.
No, it's just not as good.
All right, I have to give points.
If we're going to be real here, these, these are, these, if they're fresh and they're hot and they just came out, these are better than McDonald's.
I have to be honest.
But almost everything else.
And I mean Burger King has onion rings.
And you get an onion ring treasure, that's a big deal.
But I, I don't want to, oh, it's here.
I suppose I play with it for a little while.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
This sounds like I have the filter turned on, but I don't.
This is just me normally talking and there's something really wrong.
Start talking, Morty, Morty, Morty, Morty, Morty, Morty.
We got an adventure to go on, Morty.
Nobody, nobody heard that.
I almost puked though.
I'm so glad I got out of the way and stopped when I did.
I almost fucking puked on stream.
Just like, not because the food was bad, but because I was choking.
I can't read chat when I eat.
You guys just fucking do it to me.
12.4k people here watching you do this.
What?
Yeah, that's fine, right?
More than 12,000 people here watching this.
But this wouldn't happen every day.
If I just ate like McDonald's and Burger King and Wendy's every day on stream,
do you think you'd really stick around for that long?
Would you really stick around for that long?
You, yeah, you say you would, but in a week, half of you guys just be like,
this is fucking, she keeps doing this.
I'm done. I'm out of here.
I would watch you more.
You say that, but like in two months,
I'd be eating like the 30th McChicken on stream.
You'd be like, all right, I'm going to find somebody else to watch.
He keeps doing this.
And by the way, these are too big.
Like these are huge.
Where do you put these?
I mean, I like it, but these are too big.
You mean small.
How much liquid is actually inside of here?
This is a large Coke.
I feel like the two liter bottle is in here.
Okay.
Final review.
The Burger King Whopper is going to get out of 10.
It's somewhere in the sixes.
It's like 6.4.
Yeah, 6.4.
I think so.
A quarter pounder is honestly, a quarter pounder is not very much better, but it is.
But it is, but I know it is.
I would give a quarter pounder like a seven and an eight.
7.8 for a quarter pounder.
I just like McDonald's better.
Arbitrary numbers.
Okay, so something's in here.
I can like feel it like blocking my nasal passage.
I'm going to like go into the sink and go, and like a fucking french fry is going to come up.
It's a worm.
It's not a fucking worm.
What about Chuck E. Cheese?
But that's pizza.
They don't have burgers at Chuck E. Cheese, do they?
Move out of the way for Otto.
All right, let me clean this up.
I've eaten.
That was the, oh my God.
The Burger King McChicken gets five.
I don't like it.
I can't believe I almost puked on stream.
There's no way I will like puke on stream.
No way.
It was really close.
All right, I'll be right back.
All right, let me clean up.
Best puke of 2021.
Well, it'll be the only puke of 2021.
All right, I'll be right back.
We're going to go back to that little console.
Figure that was the best thing to do today.
So I'll be right back.
We'll get started.
See you in a bit.
Oh my God, that was fucking ridiculous.
I just blew out so much like junk.
We heard it.
Now I'm fine.
Oh, pog, pog moment.
A little piece of like weird lettuce on the counter.
Oh, nice.
All right, let's play this little thing.
Wait, is there a link already?
What's the, there's a link already.
No, you can't do the Kubrick stare again.
With the hamburger.
I guess you could.
Oh my God.
Let's take a look.
Oh boy.
That is so creepy.
That is scary.
I need to like cough because like anytime something goes up your nose and down the wrong pipe and just through your nose and shit like, hold on.
Oops.
Sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
Oh, I'm so glad I got to do that though.
Oh, all right, let's go.
We still have hundreds of games that I haven't played.
Probably not going to do this again, by the way.
This will be the last time you see this console.
He's taking a rip.
Now, really important, I need to delay the audio by a certain amount of time.
You can test it for me to make sure it's working.
Okay, so let's give you, let's give us a little test here.
So ready, one, two, one, two, three, four.
How are we doing?
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, all right, let's go.
Let's play.
Where do we start?
Where do we start today?
Jungle Book, licensed by Nintendo.
Probably not.
Okay, Walt Disney Company.
Press select for options.
This is, I think this is just the game.
Jungle, okay.
Version, get ready.
Where, oh, is there a slide?
Is this just the game?
This is not bad.
Purple, purple background, purple grapes.
I thought I just bounced on like a spring.
All down.
He loves it.
It's not bad.
Isn't the warthog, isn't the warthog my friend?
Wait, this is a different movie.
How do I get that?
What the fuck?
Bear necessities, those simple bear necessities.
We'll have a lot of fun when we are friends.
I'm done.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
How do I do this?
Do we just hold the jump?
Climb the vine.
Where?
This vine.
This is like dancing.
I can't get up there.
Go left?
I feel like I'm playing this on a Game Boy Color.
Is this a Game Boy game or is this a Nintendo game?
Oh, wait.
Okay, hold on.
I can hold, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's, you can run.
Here we go.
Bounce, okay, snake.
Where can I go from here?
Get the diamond.
Time's up, it's not up.
Holy shit, I got it.
Yeah, time has a bit extended.
You can jump on people too.
Do they have Aladdin on here for Super Nintendo?
Even though it's not the right console?
And yep, the Super Nintendo Aladdin is better than the Genesis Aladdin.
I'm done.
All right, what else we got?
We did all these, these are all done.
We got Ninja Turtles 1, Ninja Turtles 2, Ninja Turtles 1.
The SNES sound card sucks.
That's a fake comment, it's a troll.
This is just the game.
This is just, yeah, this is just the Ninja Turtles game for a regular Nintendo.
I remember this.
You actually do get games in this.
Yeah, this is just the Ninja Turtles game.
I remember this game being hard as shit when I was younger.
You suck at it.
Yeah, whatever.
Okay, this game's ass.
It's got great music though.
I love the overworld music, it's the best.
Oh yeah, that's right, the swimming level.
I forgot about the swimming level.
Dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun.
Dun dun, dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun.
Oh, get back up.
I gotta go up that way, across that way.
I gotta eat the pizza.
Yeah, this full pizza, this slices pizza.
If somebody dies, don't you play as the other characters do?
It's wicked cool.
Oh, there we go, here's Bebop and Rocksteady.
It's Flinter down there.
That image is Flinter, that is a great Steam profile picture.
Michelangelo's my favorite.
He was the funny one.
I like him the most because he has the lowest vocabulary.
And he has the incredibly good talent of being able to use nunchucks without accidentally hitting himself on the balls like I have done a hundred times.
He has the lowest IQ.
Hey, give us back April.
Where should I go?
You know, when I was younger, I don't know why, I thought this was his tongue.
I thought he was going like a snake.
Oh, let's go in here.
What are the two now?
Alright, this one, okay here we go.
I see why you relate to him now.
Why?
Don't kill me, I'll kill you first.
Nobody said that? Yes, they did.
Why would I have read that? Alright, don't die.
Well, who cares if I die?
Alright, now I'm going to see what Ninja Turtles 2 is.
Why does he read chat?
Why wouldn't I?
Alright, this is Ninja Turtles 2.
Ultra games is...
Wait, what?
No way, no way, this is like the best game ever made.
This game is incredible.
The arcade version?
Holy shit, are you serious?
It is.
This game is awesome.
Yeah, that's right.
Okay, I'm going to play the hell out of this.
Holy shit.
Forget everything else I planned on doing today.
I at least want to get to the first boss.
I love this game.
I used to play this all the time.
We have this arcade game on my college campus.
That sounds like a pretty awesome college campus to me.
Turtles in Time?
I have beaten Turtles in Time.
I've probably completed that game one to two hundred times.
That game is so good.
Liar?
No, I'm not lying, no I'm not.
Friends and I used to sit there, we would rent it.
And we would beat the game like five or six times a day.
Until we were forced to return it to Blockbuster.
Okay, so one to two hundred times.
Yeah, yes.
Very much yes.
Is this a Pizza Hut?
So you beat it two times.
No, two hundred!
My favorite part about these old beat-em-up games, especially the Ninja Turtle games,
is when they were blinking that means they were almost dead.
I think we did that back.
Back before health bars were over every enemy,
when they started blinking it means they were close.
They should start doing that with wow raid bosses and shit.
Get these health bars with like ten million HP on them.
No.
Is he blinking?
He's blinking, he's almost done.
Up to DPS, let's go.
Oh, come on, don't die.
Look, it's an arcade version.
I'm supposed to have like three people here.
I love the X-Men arcade game too.
And I know I've done the Colossus like a thousand times,
but every time I bring it up I'm going to do the Colossus sound.
You know that, right?
Shit, worst noise incoming.
No, that's not.
Listen to this.
You cannot nominate something or an award if it's been done a bunch of times before
and you didn't nominate it before.
Like years ago you had a chance to nominate this.
It was never on the nomination list.
Can't nominate it.
I've done it like a thousand times.
Sorting algorithm.
Who's the first boss?
It's the Blob in this X-Men game.
It actually is the Blob in the X-Men game.
Swallow your spit.
What?
Why did I read that?
I don't know.
Here comes the Blob.
The Blob.
You can start hitting him before we stop talking.
Nothing can stop the Blob.
Who is it?
Is it Bebop and Rocksteady or is that later?
Get over here, you little shit.
It is.
Am I getting infinite continues on like the bootleg Nintendo?
These are flamethrower troops.
There we go.
I forget who it is.
It's Bebop.
Oh, I love it.
I love that sound.
Excuse me, can I get a he's blinking alert when he starts blinking?
I'm going to need some help here.
Sorry.
Here it is.
He's blinking.
Don't let him win.
Up the DPS quick.
That's from Turtles in Time.
Turtles in Time had the best music too.
At first level in Turtles in Time.
Big Apple.
It's the best.
Back when video game music was good.
Back when OSTs were good.
And there was passion in them.
Sing the entire Ninja Turtles theme song perfectly.
What?
I don't think they're on national television doing this.
He's like camera shy.
April O'Neil was just on there going, help, help.
And then it cuts to him.
It's like, Shredder, you're on.
There's this camera guy pointing at him going, Shredder, you're pointing.
Come on.
He's just frozen.
So nervous.
You're all doomed to die.
So you're going to get killed.
Okay, cut it.
His face is starting to get bright fucking red.
He had this elaborate thing he practiced in the mirror for like three days straight.
And it did not sound like that.
It was way cooler.
And then he like ran off.
He like runs off backstage with his hands in his face going like.
You're projecting.
What?
You think I've never, when I was like younger, got all the lines I was going to do.
Like an old school play.
Those of you that have never had the experience of being on like a stage in a school play and forgetting your lines.
While just silence surrounds you and all the other kids on stage.
Are looking around and staring at you.
Like, oh God, you are ruining the entire play.
Dude.
And you're sitting there like.
I don't know.
I never cried and ran off stage though.
I did forget.
And then when you fuck up and you start saying a line that's wrong.
Guys, here's something you need to know about drama.
About theater.
Back in like middle school.
We all of us just memorized the last person's last sentence.
To cue us for our sentence.
So if you do not give me the exact sentence that I've memorized.
I am not going to be able to remember anything I'm supposed to say.
It's an incredibly fragile chain of events.
Where we all have to memorize the last thing that the last person said.
And it's an extremely volatile environment.
Because if one person doesn't fucking remember.
Everyone doesn't remember.
And then the curtain has to close and you skip a whole scene.
And then the audience just starts going like.
Clap.
And here we are at the next scene.
It's all everybody's parents.
I can still feel that sauce.
Oh we're living the olden days.
Get off.
I want to see the next boss.
Wait I remember this is the Robo Turtle right?
Because they remade it for Turtles in Time.
I believe that's who it is.
What's up with the lore with the Robo Turtle?
He was bad right?
And then Donatello like reprogrammed him and made him a good guy.
And then after he was bad he turned into a good turtle right?
Oh no wrong.
I lose.
That happens right?
That's a fake fan.
Oh I got continues we're good.
No I don't want to do that again.
I love this game though.
Acting challenge.
Raphael eating a sloppy burger.
I already did it.
Raphael has like a New York accent.
I'm from Boston close enough.
And I just ate a gross cold whopper.
And I think I was like oh what the fuck dude.
I just did that.
Where's Ninja Turtles 3?
There it is.
Which one is this?
Turtles Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Heroes in a half shell.
Turtle power.
They're the world's most fearsome fighting team.
Close enough.
I like all the turtles.
I love them all.
Michelangelo is my favorite.
But I'm not against playing as Raphael either.
The turtles are enjoying their vacation on a beach.
In Florida.
When suddenly.
Turtles report is just about to start.
Is that a glass of wine?
Here in New York crime is escalating every day.
We went on vacation?
Gee what happened?
Bummer dudes.
It's me Shredder.
I'm stealing all of New York City.
The whole thing.
What?
Wouldn't we know that was?
Turtles I'm taking April along with Manhattan Island.
If you want them back come and get them.
I love how Manhattan Island is like tacked on to I'm taking April again.
Yes I'm taking April.
And the entire all of New York City too I guess.
But I got April.
I don't remember this game.
He took it all.
How?
Is Shredder kind of like a reverse Batman?
Is he like a trillionaire or something?
I feel like he kind of has to be.
He always has to do like experiments and has like all these new things made.
And tons of money going into stuff.
Like the Joker laughs and like has a gun that has a fake pow on it.
And like tries to stab people.
And he has all this control.
Yet the Shredder has a whole research facility dedicated to creating like new animals.
Shredder is probably like one of those powerful villains I think in all of like comic books and stuff.
Isn't he? He has to be.
Who is more powerful than the Shredder?
In regards to like how much money they have and how much like stuff that they've developed.
This motherfucker made a Death Star.
Shredder made a Death Star.
The Technodrome.
Yeah and okay in the grand scheme of things okay like Bowser.
Mario I'm going to take Princess Peach on my flying pirate ship.
And I have a bunch of little shit kids.
Ah I'm so powerful.
No you're just a fucking weird uncle.
The Shredder has like fucking laser beams in a research facility and thousands and thousands and thousands of projects.
And hundreds of billions of dollars worth of shit.
Bowser has an army.
Shredder has an army.
Yeah of little like Goomba people.
When you step on their heads they die instantly.
Look at these guys. These guys are like trained professional ninjas.
Are you telling me that these guys are less powerful than a Goomba and like a Koopa?
Goombas wouldn't be able to pull that off.
People turn into...wait what?
Shredder is Dr. Doom.
Shredder is just Dr. Doom.
No that's not accurate.
Shredder is incredibly powerful.
Like he's got like skills like fighting skills.
Dr. Doom just like injected syrup into like his fucking butt cheek or something right?
He's not a trained like martial artist like Shredder is.
I think the Shred...you put Shredder against Dr. Doom Shredder wins every time.
Wrong.
Gonna have to settle this in the next rumble.
Shredder.
Incorrect.
I think Shredder is one of the most powerful villains.
He just has everything.
He's got the...okay he's got like the Wolverine claws.
He's arguably potentially even more trained than Wolverine was.
Somebody said NA aim.
He's just aiming into the sky.
He gets beaten by four super mutant turtles.
Yeah at the same time.
When have the...I'm sorry has there ever been a scenario where the Shredder fights Leonardo by himself and loses?
That's not happened. They're all ganging up on him together at the same time and they beat him.
In the comics yeah.
Yeah he probably was already injured though. He was already injured.
Raphael like shot him in the chest with a crossbow and like Leonardo fought him one on one.
Not fair.
I keep jumping into this fucking fire.
He's coping.
Shredder whatever.
Shredder Stan.
How did you do this this quickly? Holy shit.
This was fast.
Very fast.
That's good shit.
If you like Shredder so much why don't you marry him?
He's already taken.
I don't know man.
I would love if there was a Shredder and like a Shredette.
Oh yeah that would be fucking awesome.
I would love that. Include it.
I want it.
What the fuck. Look at that synchronized move.
Oh the Goombas can do this Jeremy.
Oh yeah they could.
They could do this.
Yeah.
There are only two species on earth that can do that.
The Foot Clan and birds.
And some birds can't even do that.
You lost that argument.
This is going so slow.
This is lagging so hard I can't even.
About dolphins.
Let's be honest though dolphins are pretty much just birds under the water.
Yeah.
Everyone think I'm crazy. Why don't you look it up.
Go ahead. Look it up.
Are dolphins the birds of the ocean?
Sure. Jerma is the crazy one right?
Did you go to Shredder's wedding?
I was in the wedding.
I was in the wedding party.
You guys think that like 40 years from now.
You think like the Ninja Turtles would be at Shredder's like son's wedding.
Or daughter's wedding or something.
And they look good old and wrinkly and shit.
Clapping and just in the audience.
I think so.
Shit.
They're turtles.
Yeah turtles live to be like 150.
You don't think they'll be alive?
I'm confused.
Shredder is going to still be in his armor at the wedding.
Maybe.
Look at me right in the face.
I just want to see the next boss and then I'm going to move on.
Yeah but they had like radioactive goop put on them.
That probably increases their life by a little bit.
They have like super powers and they're radioactive.
Like right.
They have extra powers.
The gas lighting.
Thanks for the tip. Thanks for the help.
Appreciate it. Thank you.
Three four five jump.
One two three four five jump.
I will say about the.
I almost said Simpsons.
The Ninja Turtles really have surprisingly stuck around for a very long time.
The Ninja Turtles are still cool right.
To younger kids.
They still are yeah.
That's great. That's cool.
It's cool that something could still be around and not sort of be tired I guess.
The kids love the Ninja Turtles still.
25 years later.
Everyone's saying no.
Am I just. What do you mean they don't.
Absolutely not.
Really.
They have like a new TV show and a new line of toys and stuff.
I thought that there was a whole new thing with them.
Peppa Pig is.
Two year olds.
I'm talking about like 10 to 14 year olds.
A two year old does not watch the Ninja Turtles.
Maybe like.
Once you cross like five six seven eight.
That's probably what I would say like okay you're starting to get interested.
I don't know who this is.
What character is this.
Holy fucking shit.
Oh God.
It's Peppa Pig.
Oh shit.
Environmental attacks.
What.
He still has it.
Stop.
Charge.
It's not blinking yet.
Stop saying it.
Two three.
Watch out.
Doctor Doom.
He's so strong.
I just dropped my fucking god damn mouse on the ground because of this.
Hold on.
What does Doctor Doom do.
Tell me.
There's sauce in my nose.
Doctor Doom owns a country meaning he has significant political power.
He's got magic powers on top of superhuman strength and has amassed a robot army with a superior intellect.
All Shredder has is claws and a rent a ninja he hired with ham sandwiches.
Shredders is a bug to Doctor Doom.
Okay.
That's something that.
What I just fell off.
It's a bug to Doctor Doom.
Let me ask you another follow up question though.
Do you really care.
Yes I do.
Well so do I. All right.
I was trying to pretend like I didn't.
Doctor Doom has got nothing on this Shredder.
Oh Doctor Doom do that.
He said Doctor Doom owns a country or something.
Can he float the entire country on.
You said he has magical powers but how is Shredder doing that.
Probably. I don't think so.
He has rent a ninjas.
This is actually kind of brutal.
Oh shit.
I knew it was coming.
My favorite thing about the little Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is how every word throws you a new curve ball like teenage solid starting point.
Popular protagonist demographic.
I can understand that.
Suddenly hard left into mutant and oh shit that's wild.
We are going to X-Men territory.
How are they going to play this.
Let's wait and ninjas.
Yo this can't possibly get cooler.
Ninjas are wild right.
I don't know what to do.
This crumbs all of my keyboard.
I have to clean up later.
It's a Redditor spam.
I forgot this game is before 1995.
Doing the special move hurts you.
But you can do the special move a million times at 0% health.
Shredditor.
I knew it was coming.
I wasn't going to say it.
He's going to fucking hit by a car.
Okay that's it.
And the Ninja Turtles are cooler than Doctor Doom.
Because we got our own Yoda here.
Splinter is like a kind of a cool.
I mean Yoda is cool but Splinter is really cool too.
The Ninja Turtles.
Okay you want to play this game.
Name me the last fantastic four piece of media.
That had higher than a two across like Metacritic.
And Rotten Tomatoes and stuff.
How does that sound.
I think the Shredder wins.
What's next.
What are we going now.
He's well written.
He's directed much better.
He may be acted much better.
He may be written better than.
Yeah that's a point.
Three Eyes Boy.
Binding of Isaac.
Was it.
This one's kind of fun.
What's Tien.
Tien.
I don't know.
I don't know what Tien is.
Why am I killing all the neighborhood animals.
What am I doing.
One shot.
Next game.
Hold on and wait.
We got to give it at least like a minute or two.
We can't just leave immediately.
Why am I doing this.
I hitched a ride on the back of a truck and just started shooting all the dogs.
This game's fun.
This game's like challenging and fun and stuff.
It's probably a real game.
Health pack.
A baby dragon or something and an egg.
An extra health.
Oh this really is.
Smoking is cool kids.
Why are you saying that it's not.
It's not cool.
What the fuck am I playing.
I'm confused of the enemy types here.
Usually they fall like a certain theme.
But it's like a bunch of just happy looking dogs.
Mixed in with.
Like.
I don't understand.
What am I fighting here.
What's the goal.
Why would this be this high.
I can't jump up here either.
I have to go down the holes.
I don't think that's what you do.
Can I climb this.
Next.
Journalist.
Stop.
How about a.
How about mighty final fight.
The stories start.
Right now.
Definitely not Capcom presents.
This is Metro City.
Within the walls of the city.
Jessica her beauty.
Raddy.
Aids throughout the city and gives the citizens.
Power to survive.
To survive all you have to do is not get caught.
This beacon of light all to himself.
With the girl she will be mine.
What.
A couple days later.
Jessica kidnapped.
Why.
What have you done to her Cody.
Me.
This is the work of the mad gear gang.
What do you think guy.
This is not a moment to spare.
Let's go.
Mighty final fight.
Cody.
A tough street fighter who is skilled with knives.
Guy.
Descended from ninja.
He possesses incredible agility.
And.
I thought I said Hagrid.
And Hagrid.
The hot tempered wrestler and mayor of Metro City.
This is the guy that you hold your arms out and you go.
You spin.
Old town slum.
Was that Australia.
This is definitely not final fight by the way.
This is.
Figurine.
Pop version.
That's kind of fun though.
This feels like a arcade game inside of a game that wants you to very clearly see that there are fun arcade cabinets to play in the game.
It's the same background for Contra.
Yeah it is.
It's the exact same one.
Auto Hotel is back.
That's swallowing that shit.
Maybe like puke.
Except we lost some real estate up top.
We can't see Auto Hotel.
This is a real NES game.
How come this experience points.
How do I do the spin move.
There it is.
This smile is so creepy.
Those eyes.
Holy shit.
A movie.
Of some kind.
Statue of Liberty.
Uh oh.
Other guy with big head.
Other player.
This feels like a second player.
Good Link.
Oh shit I'm dead.
I can come back though.
When I beat the boss I'll click the link.
Hold on.
What the fuck.
He just stun locked me.
4, 5 sec.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 5.
You guys ever do that in your head.
You play beat em up.
You just repeat the same like.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
I am Thrasher.
Ruler of this city.
Bow down before me.
Uh yes.
I am superior.
Maybe you're stronger than you look.
Why don't you join us.
Uh.
Yes.
I don't believe you.
You're too much of a mama's boy.
What the.
He's like.
He's doing the big brother thing.
He's just like rubbing my head like.
Come on little brother.
Oh mama's boy mama's boy mama's boy.
Stop stop saying that.
Get out of here.
Get away from me dude.
Mama's boy.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Dun dun.
What was that?
Dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Come on let me get the.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Fine I'll do what you're doing.
Hurry up I need to watch.
Do what you want to do.
We're going to Riverside.
Keith out.
Purple.
My favorite color.
Alright let me click the link.
Most popular kids characters.
Um.
Fortnite is Bugs Bunny.
Doctor Doom is.
This is not like.
Alright thank you.
All caps all caps all caps.
My link is better.
Is German suplexed that lady.
I just German suplexed.
I added an ED on there.
I don't know why.
Instead of just saying suplexed.
Like T.
Constantly screaming.
Jax.
Is he holding up like a football like Charlie Brown.
Is Lucy going to come over and kick that.
Who is he holding that for.
Okay here we go.
Here I come.
I'm going to get that football.
You dope Charlie Brown.
Why.
He doesn't need to like a curve of the frog thing.
He goes like.
Like Pee Wee Herman.
What's the Charlie Brown yell.
It's something like that isn't it.
I'm not trying to do it.
I'm just asking about the cadences.
I'm not talking about doing a voice.
I'm talking about the cadences.
Lucy holds it.
Yeah that's what I said.
Yeah and he turns his head up.
He has no mega lull mouth.
And it's like.
Same guy.
I kicked this guy's ass like five minutes ago.
Best feeling when you get a.
On two or three people at the same time.
The city in the background is melting.
Oh no.
There must be Cranky Kong.
This is a long level.
How dare you.
How dare you dress up in the same outfit as me.
Holy shit.
No.
There can only be like.
80 Darth Vader's walking around Comic Con.
81 is too much.
You're too fat and lazy to oppose me.
You're no match for me.
I am the slam master.
Get out of my way before I stomp you flat.
Are you done flapping those lips of yours.
Good.
Because I'm going to chop you down to size.
You think you can mess with the slam master.
Oh well I'm still alive.
Okay if you put graffiti on the ground.
It just says fighter.
Just fighter.
Is it.
Did he put that here to like give me like a finish line to cross so we fight.
Fight.
Fight here.
But he didn't have enough room to write fight here.
But he didn't have enough room to write fight here with a space.
So fight here.
The crowd is split on that one.
Ow.
What's next.
We could do kick master.
Did we do kick master.
I don't remember.
There's one of the scummy.
Oh that's shaking around.
There's one of the scummy living skeletons who attacked.
You humans think you're a match for belt head.
You can't even defeat me.
Thornalan weight.
Look at that like nerd.
Look at that like nerd neck.
My brother my steel is no match for these creatures.
Only with your great kicking ability.
Wait what.
Don't die.
Save the princess.
You're the last hope.
You'll pay for this belt head.
Your kicking ability.
Oh okay well I think I got a pretty good kicking ability.
I sure do.
It's great.
It's like the Rockets.
That's full range.
We have to go kill belt head.
Okay if you didn't kick so high.
You'd be able to hit them in the chest.
Therefore having a much larger hit box.
Kicking directly straight up in the air into the head.
Gives me such a small range to hit anybody.
Oh Diablo 2 Paladin Scepter.
Sorry I have to do that every time somebody says that word.
It's like you pulled the string on the back of the woody doll.
What is that?
You have found a bouncing bulb spirit.
This spirit will shoot bouncing balls to damage your enemies.
Don't drop it.
How do I do that?
Okay at some point you just punch in the air.
Right.
I get it but it's very impractical to do that.
Kill belt head.
I'm going to try.
I'm trying to collect all the jewels.
Taking power.
I have experience too.
I'm interested in this one.
We're going to stay here until I level up once.
MP huh?
Seinfeld?
Why am I Seinfeld streaming?
Watch out boss.
Is that belt head?
No that's definitely one of belt heads just chumps.
It's a witch.
It's Megalovania.
That was just Megalovania.
Holy shit what was that?
Did you hear that?
What the hell?
I almost want to die again to hear that.
Shit.
That hit me.
Really?
I hate the stupid kick to the side.
It sucked.
Come on.
I didn't pick it up.
What do I get now?
You have found the life up one magic.
G5.
G G O R C.
Magic.
Leaf and urn.
Caverns of no return.
Oh shit what's this?
Does it work?
The orb's not shooting at anything.
It's just a warcraft pet.
Doesn't do anything.
Here comes Megalovania.
It's close.
It's maybe one or two notes up.
That's the I want to avoid the copyright so I changed two notes version.
Man this game came out in the 90s.
Can you guys believe that?
This game came out in the 90s.
I got some super frogs.
I'm supposed to go up in the 90s.
20,000 upvotes.
You guys are terrible.
Play Melee?
Like Smash Brothers Melee?
Yes.
I'm not very good at Smash Brothers Melee.
I'm good at the one that I'm going to Smash Brothers Brawl.
Game where you can accidentally fall down.
Can I go up?
I can't go up.
It reminds me of Battletoads.
This part right here.
This exact section right now.
Play the Subspace Emissary.
I guarantee you you will love elevator action.
Where is it?
How about Saint?
Wait what?
It's supposed to be first and last name.
How do I go?
Can somebody help me here?
I have to write a paragraph?
What does this want me to do?
This is a puzzle.
This is a password screen.
How did I get to a password screen?
I just press start.
What was I called?
I have no idea why I didn't end up here.
I pressed start before.
This is the same sentence?
Somebody help me.
Seven senses.
Cosmo, life.
That was abrupt.
Cosmo and life are different stats.
Am I getting points for this?
I'm not getting points for that.
I did it too.
I watched them do it so many times that I did it.
I don't have to fight or anything.
Just walk.
They all die anyways.
This is freaking me out.
I can't do it.
It's freaking me out.
Hold on.
The jump is so weird.
It's like a Jump King jump.
That's the only way I can describe it.
Rocks?
Are we getting a finger wag?
What does this say?
It's a selector.
I apparently made them very angry.
Stop that please.
I don't know what happened.
What are these?
I don't have a crosshair.
It's barely showing up on my screen.
What are these?
Up right, up left.
Fight, call, friends, talk, and data.
Fight.
It doesn't want to fight me.
What did they say?
It's the same elevator action waiting room.
Where is it?
I'll find it.
There it is.
Elevator, action.
Is this supposed to be me?
Why am I Indiana Jonesing into an apartment building?
I just shot the guy in the head.
What the?
Are they going to get in the elevator?
They're getting in the elevator.
Don't shoot me.
He got me.
What's the goal?
Just get all the way to the bottom?
I can control the elevator.
Imagine being able to do this in an actual elevator.
There's a button and you can just go up and down yourself
and not have to open it.
I'd say like, hey, meet me downstairs to somebody.
Take the stairs.
And I just wouldn't show up.
I would make them find me on the middle floor,
like open the doors and be like, hey, dickhead.
And then close it and keep going down and keep going up.
I don't think...
Who shot me?
I just took the lights out.
How do I get...
I got to go in that orange door.
Go in the door.
Wait, stairs.
Where am I?
See that shit?
That's called a duck.
Getting down to the bottom.
This is going to be tricky.
Down, down, down, down.
Shit.
Oh, man.
Oh, shit.
How about just wars?
Wars?
Is it a tournament?
I'm the penguin.
Just dumb lock him.
Don't let him get up.
Keep hitting him in the head.
Until the referee stops the fight.
A get perfect game.
A get a set.
Let's go.
I know what to do.
He's going to get all the balls on the other side.
Shit.
I like this game.
This game's fun.
Why can't they have...
I want to play this game in real life.
I've got time.
Come on.
No, shit.
Come on, get it over there.
I love this one.
This one's so much fun.
Shit, he's got more over here.
Get it.
What is that boomerang?
Stop, stop, stop.
That's got to be it.
I win.
Oh, yeah, I win.
Goodbye.
Perfect game.
Be good, be good, be good.
I'm overwhelmed with the hell out of him right now.
You're in trouble, dude.
That one's going fast.
I have a spoiler.
I have to say it.
I'm going to talk about Star Wars for a second.
Star Wars Rogue One.
If you haven't seen Star Wars Rogue One, mute the microphone for five seconds.
Mute the microphone for five seconds.
Just mute.
I don't have to say anything.
You know what I was going to say.
You know exactly what I was going to tell you.
I don't know if it's against Panda.
I heard Panda's a pretty top seed.
He is.
You guys don't know what I'm talking about?
I have to say it.
It's in Rogue One.
It's the movie.
Whatever, I don't care.
I can only know.
I'm going to say it.
I'm going to say Rogue One spoilers.
Seriously, don't come back and tell everyone this chat says to come back.
Here we go.
Here comes a Rogue One spoiler.
I'm not kidding.
This is the fucking movie when Darth Vader shows up.
And it's like...
It was that exact same sound effect.
And now I lost because I was paying attention.
Okay, you're good.
Everyone can come back.
Star Wars fucking sucks.
Get off me.
Oh my god, he just perfected me.
All right, where else are we going?
How about...
Did I do baseball?
I didn't do baseball.
Here's your team.
CDGs, SSTs, or Ws.
All right, it doesn't matter.
Me swinging.
161 kilometers an hour.
How fast is that?
Isn't that like 150 miles per hour?
I just want to hit a home run.
Let me hit one home run and I'm done.
That's close enough.
Clap, nice homer.
Nice run.
Where are we going?
How about brush roller?
I like it already.
Is that a loading screen?
Instead of collecting the things, you just have to paint the ground?
Yeah, it is.
It's actually kind of cute.
It's Splatoon.
Look at the cat.
Why are there cats everywhere?
And a guy driving a car into a wall.
Does that guy just get into an accident?
The car looks a little scrunched, doesn't it?
It looks like squished.
I think that guy's in trouble.
Get away.
Okay, Volgaard 2.
Or how about Xevious?
Oh, it's just a vertical shooter.
Those rings?
They're just like bathroom washers.
This is like one of the bins at Home Depot.
This is it?
This is my favorite game.
Your taste is...
How about...
Arena.
I'm gonna pin to the wall.
I don't understand what's going on.
Do I have a projectile?
I don't see a projectile, and I can't...
I was about to hit the reset button, but I'm gonna try it again.
Battle for Home Depot.
I can't get both of those guys at the same time.
Go for the guy on the left first?
This is impossible.
It's not possible. The game's incompletable.
I gotta go to RNG. This might work.
Tell the muted people to come back.
Fire alert!
I did Bird Week already.
How about Bugs War?
Yep.
Do I have a spider?
I have a bomb.
Wait, what happened?
Wait, this is Battleship.
It's Battleship but one flare.
I have to drop it on caterpillars?
Okay, yep.
I got him.
It's Minesweeper?
No, this is just Battleship.
Is he dead?
Two more. The head and the tail?
I kind of feel bad. I'm killing him very slowly.
This is horrible.
They don't even fight back.
Yeah, they don't fight back. I don't like this one.
You sunk my caterpillar.
I didn't want to see what Squoon was.
Looks very interesting.
Yep. I have no idea what's going on with this title screen.
Those sharks are eating people.
Holy shit, this is horrible.
It's just the Mario level from Mario Land on the Game Boy.
Why is there a city down here?
Wait, there's an entire...
It's supposed to be Atlantis?
This one's good.
This is a fun one.
Pretty good maneuvering right there, I think.
I don't think I can kill the sharks over there.
I think those are my friends.
What's the first boss, what do you think?
I'm going to say Giant Squid.
What do you think?
I thought that was health.
It looked like health.
First boss incoming.
Ooh, this one's good.
I like this one a lot.
That juke.
Come on, continue.
Submarine is cute?
Yeah, submarine is cute.
Wait, hold on.
That's the Star Fox font.
I have a lot of hopes for this one.
It's training, command, and adventure.
I think this is supposed to be text.
Oh, we have E's and B's.
Wait, is this like an old text-based RPG?
I selected B.
There's a dot on the screen, but what is it?
Am I facing the right direction?
How do I get the dot on my screen?
I don't get it.
Oh, shit, I'm flying.
Where am I supposed to go?
I'm going so fast.
That's me right there, but where am I supposed to go?
All right, we're going to E.
That was blinking.
Oh, there's something here.
Alien life.
I'm on a stale.
I could be flying upside down right now.
I have no idea.
Get the fuck out of here.
Get me out of here.
Wait, I want to do adventure.
I want to see.
Uh-oh.
I don't even remember what it was called.
Was it Squoon? Starluster.
Adventure.
Here we go.
Let's see.
We're going to go over here.
What's here?
Radio.
I'd like to have a radio frequent.
Who cares?
Ready?
This is a cooking game?
Watch out for the dogs and collect all the food.
This is Donald Duck.
It's Chubby Cherub.
I'm going to sneeze.
Sorry, I can't hit.
Nice, Ron.
I sneeze.
I'm not allowed to sneeze.
There we go.
That's better.
Now the reference can be complete.
I never have to do it again.
Did that kill me?
It's been two.
You have a choice.
2021, year of the nice Ron.
I can fly.
That would have been nice to know.
Is this the life of a seagull?
Like a pigeon?
I'm just flying around eating apple cores.
I'm done.
Not allowed to sneeze Andy.
Did we do Banana Prince?
We did, right?
Bomb sweeper?
No, 10 yard fight.
We're close to 10 yards.
Isn't football 100?
Do I have the ball?
This is a dance.
Do I get to pick a play?
Tap dancing.
We're going to get it.
First to 10.
Interception.
Did you intercept it?
No.
Look at me.
This is another interception.
If I throw for an interception,
why am I throwing?
No, it's just putting me back 20 yards.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
What the fuck is this?
How can you even understand American football?
Look, here's how it works.
When somebody has the ball,
they have to just go 10 yards somehow.
If they do not go 10 yards,
they have to try again.
You can only try four times
before you have to give the team the other ball
and they do it the other way.
That's it.
Yeah, you're probably like,
what the fuck are those for?
There is like a bonus feature.
Are you fucking kidding me?
By the way, this is not supposed to be happening.
If I throw an interception,
that's a safety.
20 yards back, I'm in my own goal.
Wait, I can't leave?
What was that gun?
What?
What was that?
How about pack land?
This one should be good.
Oh, yes.
And all the directionals are just jump.
It's really weird.
This is the smash stage?
Why do you have a zoomer haircut?
It actually is the smash stage?
I don't think there's an end.
I think we just walk forward forever.
It's break time.
What song is this?
I've heard this song.
Where?
It's the pack land stage one.
What is it though?
It's toxic by Britney Spears.
Don't you know that you're toxic?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it close?
It's not even close.
I don't even care.
I'm not going to play through the speakers.
No, it's not.
It's not even close.
In some way, it could be.
It's very much not even close.
But I kind of understand what you mean.
Don't you know that you're toxic?
I can't help it.
Can we stop this game?
Okay, where are we going?
We didn't play Street Fighter.
Street Fighter 12 peoples.
USA, Japan, USA, China, India, Japan, USA, Brazil.
Is this supposed to be a map?
Is this supposed to be a map of the world?
USS the United States of...
What?
This is supposed to be R.
China is below Russia.
And then Japan.
Japan's right there.
Japan's there.
There's two USAs.
And then there's India.
And then Japan again.
United Soviet States of America.
Okay.
I don't know what to press.
Name, Chun-Li, birthday.
Resize, B, 80s blood type.
Wait, okay, that's bullshit.
Try that again.
Do the...
I can't even get up.
Hadouken spammed.
Zero.
Actually skip this stream.
What?
How about challenger?
Real time action adventure.
Something's wrong with that text.
Level, L or H.
Low or high.
All right, where should I put the gas tank?
Should I put it at I don't have to go to the gas station?
Or that's the next thing I have to do.
I'm going to break down.
These are spoilers.
I don't want to see this.
I didn't stop the express.
I'm coming, princess.
I'll get it.
Don't you know that you're toxic.
Don't run too fast.
The game's really laggy.
There's a guy up here.
There he is.
Come on.
Stop.
I can't help it.
I'm going to keep going.
Where was I even looking?
My eyes weren't a chat.
They weren't on the screen.
Where was I even looking?
Where were my eyes?
What was I looking at?
Above the monitor?
I have no idea.
I did it again.
I'm going to get to the end of the train right now.
Let's go.
Oops, I did it.
Oops, I did it again.
I'm lost in the scene.
Oh, baby, baby.
Is he throwing shit underneath?
They're coming from all angles.
They're coming from all angles now.
Jerry, they're coming from all angles.
The storm?
Is that alive?
This is a mess.
When I walk forward, it comes with me.
What the fuck?
I did it again.
I'm lost in your heart.
I'm lost in the scene.
What about War Wolf?
Right, that's it.
It's just AAA.
No idea what this says.
War Wolf is coming to town.
One player push start.
Which one of us is the War Wolf?
Is that the War Wolf?
You guys can figure that out.
Okay, wait.
Look at that neck.
Is there anything I can do?
I have an anger meter?
It's punching him in the groin over and over again.
This is the most coward way to fight somebody right now.
Really?
I will challenge you in a one on one battle.
We'll see who the strongest grappler is.
I'm going to crouch down and punch you in the groin and run away every time.
I think I just transformed twice.
Okay, we went from beast to raccoon.
What is going on here?
Okay, please stop that.
I have to turn it off if it keeps doing this.
Alright, so you saw the transformation.
This is not the type of move I would expect from that elaborate, insane transformation.
Ah, shit.
What's that?
Rise from the grave.
Altered Beast, right?
You guys ever feel like Altered Beast is the type of old, nostalgic kind of Genesis game that they're going to make into a Netflix series?
I could feel that, couldn't you?
I could see that.
Because there's absolutely no lore there and they can just make up an entire thing.
Maybe that Genesis game?
Altered Beast.
As long as they get like 10,000 streams, I'm sure it'll be worth it.
Climb this.
Nice.
This game's actually pretty rad.
I want to do the boss fight.
Don't knock.
Well, I have to knock it now.
Wait, don't knock.
Of course I have to knock that now.
I lost my...
I shouldn't have knocked.
Oh, we're going.
Did Rockin' Cats.
Did Bird Week.
Did Bomberman.
Crackin' Pop?
Crackin' Pop was a bomb.
This game sucks.
What is that guy with the pill doing?
Bubble Bobble monster is here?
Am I taking too long?
Those legs.
Tonight's gonna be a good night.
Tonight's gonna be a good, good night.
That meme is going parabolic.
I'm sorry.
What about Spelunker?
I died.
I'm dead.
And again, I have a machine gun.
There's a gold coin, I can get the gold coins.
Here's the item shop.
Really?
That's not very far to fall.
I've had enough of that one.
Can we do aimless?
Nope, but I can see...
I would be...
This would be very impressive for an 11-year-old school project.
This would be like, holy shit, this is incredible work.
The 12-year-old that made this in the computer lab, you are really going places.
You really are.
I'm not even kidding around.
You're getting into programming and you're learning.
And this is such a huge step in your journey to kind of do like online programming and game development and stuff.
This is a huge deal.
I kind of want to see what happens if you kill five.
Do I get to kill five more?
Three more.
I did it, I did it, I did it.
I win.
I don't want to play Sudoku.
The Exder?
Too close.
I'm a person.
I thought I was a plane.
No, no, no, no, no.
What are you thinking about, Jeremy?
You're the Exder.
Part man, part machine, part plane, part boat, part person.
Holy shit.
This is awesome.
This is actually really cool.
This is the most elaborate Mario Maker level I've ever seen.
I cannot aim that, by the way.
How do I transform?
Did that, did Mario...
Did we do Ninja 2?
I don't believe we did.
It kind of looks like Bart.
Mario Homer.
I love that sound.
Did I just kill a bird?
What did I knock down?
What the hell was that?
I'm hurting animals in the tree.
I don't want to do that.
All cartoon music comes from the same place, doesn't it?
Do I have health?
No, I'm not going to do a Simpsons impression.
No, I'm not because it's going to get on the list.
Nope, not happening.
I will never do a Homer Simpson impression again.
It's not going to happen.
I already know it's going to happen.
You don't.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to do any of the Simpsons.
Nope.
I'm not doing it.
There's 500 million off the debt.
What?
I'm not doing it for anything less than that.
No deal.
Yeah, I've seen a lot of no deals.
It's not going to happen.
Hey, when does the Cuphead DLC come out?
Isn't that soon?
Springtime or something?
Pull, pull, pull.
Ow!
What the fuck?
Why did pausing that just...
Oh my god, I can't pause the game.
Why did it do that?
Holy shit.
Okay.
I'm going to...
Can I just confirm that that was what was happening?
Turn your volume down.
I want to confirm that that was happening.
Yep.
Oh my god.
All right, straw poll.
Let's see if you guys really want that.
I'll do it for 500 million.
Okay, Simpsons impression for 500 million off debt.
It's just yes or no.
The only way I'm going to do it.
Are you serious?
Are you kidding me?
This is the easiest bet I've ever made.
This is the easiest amount of...
Of course I'm going to do this.
500 million.
Are you guys kidding me?
Wow.
This is a freebie.
You guys are throwing me a meatball here.
500 million off the debt.
This is 60%.
This is an absolute majority.
Okay.
All right.
Here we go.
We better take 500 million off.
Is there a certain line you want me to say as Homer?
Say, eat my shorts as Homer.
That's not what he says.
Okay.
Mmm.
Beer.
Duff.
And let me tell you something, Bart.
Can you go in the fridge and get me an ice cold duff beer?
Mmm.
Donut.
Beer.
Sure thing, Dad.
I'll go and get you a beer.
Waka waka.
Oh, Homer.
I don't like the fact that you're drinking so much on a weekday.
Much.
Can you just stop complaining and stop telling me to do things?
Mmm.
Beer.
Oh, Marty.
You need breakfast?
Mmm.
Breakfast.
It's me, Lisa, coming down the stairs.
Well, hi to the holy neighbors.
I'm in your window.
I'll take the 500 million, please.
I'll take 500 million removed from the fucking debt.
Where's Bart?
He already ran in.
He skated on a skateboard.
He didn't ollie.
Double or nothing for the entire Griffin family?
Are we taking a billion off if I do the whole Griffin family?
The entire Griffin family?
One billion?
Are we kidding?
Okay.
Hold on.
I'm going to be wiping my fucking debt clean right now.
He does this for free all the time, but I have banned it completely as of four days ago.
It has to be all of them.
You have to say welcome to Germacraft as Peter.
Oh my.
Okay, fine.
I will do a welcome to Germacraft as the entire Griffin family for a double or nothing for
a billion off.
I'll read the copypasta in the whole Griffin family.
That like little paragraph section.
I'm going to do a poll.
Griffin family.
Never in a fucking million years, like 10, 20 years ago, would I have thought that I'd
be sitting in a chair here going back and forth arguing with 11,000 people about removing
debt from my fucking name to do like the entire Griffin family in a Germacraft copypasta.
Like, this was not even possible in my brain like even five years ago.
You have to do it with the face cam on.
Face cam on on no deal.
Griffin family, Germacraft, copypasta for another 500 million, right?
So that would be a total one billion with cam on.
Okay.
Fuck.
It's going to be so embarrassing.
This is going to be embarrassing, but whatever.
It's worth it.
I need the copypasta.
Who's it?
Who's in there?
It's Chris, Meg.
Oh, I don't know how to do it.
Oh, this is 80% of the, okay.
There it is.
Let me get this like ready.
Okay.
Let me get on cam.
All right.
This is, this is, this is good.
You ready?
All right.
So we start with, we're going to go Peter.
Let's do like the family guy kind of list here.
Peter, Brian, Stewie, Chris, and then you have Lois and Meg.
Okay.
You need to do Joe.
Joe's not part of the Griffin family.
Quagmire is not a Griffin.
Quagmire is in the show family guy.
He's not a Griffin.
You have to add Joe and Quagmire.
Joe and Quagmire have to be in there.
Okay.
That's it.
All right.
I gotta like write, I have to write this down.
There's Peter, then Brian, Stewie, then Joe, Quagmire.
Oh, Chris is in there.
There's a lot of fucking people I have to do.
Chris, Peter, Brian, Stewie, Chris, Joe, Quagmire.
Lois, Meg.
I'm only gonna be able to read two words per person.
Okay.
There's too many people on this list.
Principal, no, no.
We have too many people.
The copypasta's like a paragraph.
I'm gonna be like, I, it's not gonna work.
Do the whole thing per person?
That was not part of the deal.
The whole thing per person, excuse me.
It was, if I'm doing the whole thing per person,
I am removing like three people on this list,
because they're not, I'm removing people not in the Griffin family.
Griffin family, Germacraft copypasta.
That's not Joe Griffin, it's not Quagmire Griffin.
Okay.
Peter, Brian, Stewie, Chris, Lois, and Meg.
Remove Meg for Quagmire.
That's gonna have to come down to a vote.
Paul, no, Meg for Joe.
All right.
If you want me to replace Meg so bad,
we're gonna replace Meg with Joe or Quagmire.
You better get it right.
I keep like changing colors.
You see that?
That was weird.
All right.
New straw poll.
Okay.
Can I have like the family guy background music on,
or is that gonna get in trouble for that?
That might make it hard to do.
I might like laugh.
That like, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Okay.
Who am I replacing Meg with, Joe or Quagmire?
Oh, I fucking hate this.
You have to know I did this for a reason.
Wow.
This is surprising.
There's a midi version?
Joe won by a lot.
Can I get like a family guy midi version?
Family guy, family guy midi.
I can't do this.
That's so fucked up.
I don't think I can do that.
That's gonna be so hard to do.
Give me the pasta.
Joe won by shitload.
So, okay.
Okay, here we go.
Eh.
Lois.
All right.
I think I'm ready to try.
Here we go.
We start with Peter.
Family Guy is brought to you by...
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Germacraft.
The series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely.
Because I am an idiot in this game.
You're gonna see lots of fails.
You're gonna see lots of triumphs.
At least I'm hoping.
So grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee.
Hot cup of cocoa.
I got apple cider right here.
Freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
That's good cider.
Okay.
Got it.
Who's next?
Okay, Brian.
Get over here.
Let me see that coffee pasta again.
Peter.
Hey, Peter.
Excuse me.
Peter.
What are you doing over here, Peter?
Family Guy is brought to you in part by...
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome.
People are saying it's Obama.
Peter.
I'm not going to be able to do it now because you said that.
Oh my god.
This is going to be so hard.
Because I can hear this shit.
I need this fucking closer, man.
Get over here.
I can't.
Peter.
This is a fucking CIA level of training.
Shit.
I hate this.
Focus.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dermacraft.
A series where it's fucking Obama.
It is.
It's Obama.
I can't...
Let me do it again.
I can't look at the chat.
I cannot look at the chat.
I have the thing right here and the chat is right there.
I just keep seeing fucking people screaming.
I need it again.
Paste it again.
Just lean into it.
I know I'm trying, man.
I need the pasta.
There it is.
I got it.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, three, two, one.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dermacraft.
A series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player Let's Play.
It's too fucking hard.
Brian's Brian the hardest.
Can I turn the song off?
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dermacraft.
The series where I play Minecraft.
This is gonna be a single-player. Let's play and when I say, let's play I use that term pretty used loosely fuck
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of stop spamming. I can't read it
Stop spamming. I can't read it. Oh
Hello. All right. All right. All right. This is the one right here. One two three. Hello, ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to episode one of germa craft the series where I play minecraft Peter
This is gonna be a single-player. Let's play and when I say that
Let's play I use that term pretty loosely because I am an idiot in this game. You're gonna see lots of fails
You're gonna see lots of triumphs
At least that's what I'm hoping. So go grab yourself
A nice hot cup of coffee Peter a cup of cocoa. I've got an apple cider right here freshly brewed. Let me take a sip
That's some good cider. Fuck. Yeah, it's doing I'm gonna nail Stewie. Here we go. I
Say Peter I say
Okay, here we go
when did why did Brian sing is Brian sings in like fucking 80 episodes because Seth McFarlane is like a good singer and
Brian's pretty close to his speaking voice. So he just makes sure that he's gonna sing as Brian so he can show everybody
How good of a singer he is?
Greetings fat man
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of drama craft the series where I play minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and I say when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I am a stupid idiot dumbass in this game. You're going to see lots of you. That's a fake one
That was a fake copypasta you added stupid fucking idiot dumbass. Let's reset. Here we go
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome John Oliver. Oh
It is just John Oliver. I don't care. Hello, ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and I say when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I'm an idiot in this game. You're going to see lots of fails
You could see lots of triumphs at least that's what I'm hoping for. So grab yourself a nice hot cup of coke
Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the steer
Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I'm an idiot in this game
I only have two more to do after this. I said I say fat man
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I am an idiot in this game. You're gonna see lots of fails. You're gonna see lots of triumphs at least
That's what I'm hoping so go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot cup of coke
That was another fake one
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I suck off
This is gonna be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely because I'm stupid fuck
In this game, you're gonna see lots of fails. You're gonna see lots of triumphs
Lisa
Give me the real one, please. I gotta get stewie quick
I gotta I gotta end this bit just write it down because I'm lazy and I'm a lazy streamer
No, that's his penis in it. Okay, pretty loosely. I'm an idiot in this game
You just lots of fails. There's lots of triumphs at least that's what I'm hoping grab something
I have a cup of coffee. I've got a cocoa. This one's the real one. I'm ready. I
Say hello ladies and gentlemen, I'm stupid Griffin here
Welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play Minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I'm an idiot in this game. You're going to see lots of fails
You're gonna see lots of triumphs at least that's what I'm helping. So grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot
I checked it. I'm just gonna put I'm just gonna get it myself. This is the one I mean no deal
We're talking about deal off. What are you talking about them? There's no sense. Hello, ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play Minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I am an idiot in this game. You're going to lots of fails
You can see lots of triumphs at least I'm hoping so go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot cup of cocoa
I've got apple cider right here freshly blued. Let me take a sip. Ah
I say that's some good cider. It's doing done. Here comes Lois. Uh-uh
Lois hey, hey, wow
Hey, oh, honey. Okay. Here we go. Mm-hmm. One two three. Hello, ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play Minecraft
This is gonna be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I'm an idiot in this game
All right, I'm starting to see resident sleepers, I gotta go I have to get this done right now
I don't care. It's a billion off the debt. I don't give a shit how it sounds
I'm seeing president sleepers. I gotta go. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of German craft. It's fucking
It's fucking spongebob, I have to block my ears or something. I have to block my ears
Cuz I if I hear it is gonna make me laugh. Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode
I got it. I know how to do the voice and I won't hear it. So it will not make me laugh
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play Minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that
Making the music louder in my ear. Oh
My fucking god, I have to get out of this now
I'm gonna focus covering chat. I'm gonna get this done right fucking now and then all I have to do is Joe Joe's easy
One two three
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft. It's being Lois the series where I play Minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I
Use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game. You're gonna see lots of fails
You're gonna see lots of triumphs at least I'm hoping so go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee a hot cup of cocoa
I got apple cider right here freshly brewed. Let me take a sip. Oh, that's a good cider
Bye
Counts accounts accounts accounts accounts accounts accounts that one counts that fucking counts
That counts that counts that counts
No deal what about Chris fuck how does Chris even talk?
I don't know how Chris talks. Oh, it's part square fine. No, okay
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of German craft the series where I play Minecraft
This is going to be a single-player. Let's play and when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely
Because I'm an idiot in this game. You're gonna see lots of fails
You're gonna see lots of triumphs at least I'm hoping so grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot cup of cocoa
I got apple cider right here freshly brewed. Let me take a sip
Oh, that's some good cider
Chris Griffin done. All I got is fucking Joe
Hey, ladies and gentlemen, it's a bitter bitter bitter. Okay
Hey, it's me Joe. Just want to say how are you? Hello, ladies and gentlemen, it's me Joe
Welcome to episode one of German craft series where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single-player. Let's play
What I say, let's play I use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game
You're gonna see lots of fails. You're gonna see lots of triumphs
At least that's what I'm hoping Peter. So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot cup of cocoa
I've got apple cider freshly brewed right here. Let me take a sip. Ah, that's some good cider Peter. That's it. I'm done. I win. Oh
That's you get minus 50 million for a bad Chris and a bad Lois fine. I'll take I'll take
950 million dollars off the debt now do Rick and Morty. No
8,000 people will leave. What do I get for Rick and Morty and
Okay, another 250 million and I'll do Rick and Morty separately. No, fuck this. I'm done. I'm done
I'm going back to playing video games. I feel like I just was in a fucking nightmare
I was just in a nightmare. I just woke up from a fucking nightmare
Say later. Good to see you. Oh my god. My like a head hurts. All right, let's continue and what we doing before
Oh, I can plug this back in don't what shampoo do you use? I want hair like yours. I use the stuff from Lush
I'll give you the exact products. I use
two products I use a product called big it's just a shampoo and
Shampoo card and a conditioner called a vegan ease
Vegan vegan. He's a soy vegan. I don't care. I'm not a vegan. I just I just like the way it smells
I've been using that for like the last five years. Okay, so after that, we're gonna continue to do what we were doing
Well exactly that exactly that was about devil world tactic. Oh, it's just the okay. I
Only know who this guy is because of Smash Brothers. I don't like it already
I'm so glad I got a billion shaved off about pyramid. Ooh, all right
What did that say? You guys hear that? I kind of like this one. I like shapes when Scooby-Doo be
Scooby-Doo be
It's getting a little more complicated. Hold on. Yeah, this is Tetris, but with shapes. I like it better
This is my little teapot
Short and stout here is my handle
Pour me out it's not I'm gonna get this I didn't oh this one. I don't like this one. This one's too complicated
Diggity you don't you know that you're toxic
Patchy calm. Oh, okay. What's this?
Time I'm just counting. I have a little thing down. Oh get up there yet. I've been the balls aren't going up
Oh, oh, oh
Yo
No
This is stupid do a Metal Gear Solid 3 playthrough. I'll start it tomorrow. Just kidding. It's a lie. I'm not started that's more
Hmm. How about we have don't Donkey Kong? How about Donkey Kong 3 sit in the bees?
Oh, I remember this one like Chrono Trigger. Sure. Oh
No, Donkey Kong got me that was just toxic
No, don't you dare
How about we saw fruit pig X to X's another vertical shooter fantastic
I hate these times up
How about gate the gate oh, I'm this little guy get all the heart. Okay get all the hearts
Maybe I like this. This is kind of cool. I like all the hearts. I have to be level one at least fuck you
I don't I'm a vented
I'm really kind of interested in door door. Okay
Door go in the door. He got in the door first. What I don't understand go in the door
Okay up do doy doy
What the fuck is going on let him in the room and then close the door do doy doy as Peter
You can you can only make one sound?
All right, get over here get in here in the door close the door door. All right, I get it follow me
Didn't go in the door door door door door door door door door get in that fucking door
He's got me one more turn
Oh
Left left left left left left left left left left left left left left left left. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh, I didn't think they both could go in. Yeah, look gant
Garden war. Holly who holly who I looked like Mario. Didn't it it's the same one
We just played this is the same music as when we played yesterday to are you kidding me?
No, we're not playing this one. This one sucks. All right. Oh seven. There is no Mario seven
We already looked you must be zonked. What's another good one? It's still bubble no not block sword blocks world
I think I mean candy workshop is has to be played
Candy workshop, that's a pog face. Okay. What do we do make candies obviously?
I have this and it goes into what does it go? What do I do with it?
Have a waffle. I don't know what to do the waffle put the waffle on the waffle maker. Oh, okay
Candy has to be in a row. I think it has to be in a row wait what?
Oh, I'm making like a candy cake. I I don't understand. I'm starting to think this game sucks
Oh, we did hyper a little bit. We didn't do hyper sports. What is he doing? Okay to qualify any 2400?
What am I doing? Oh, I'm shooting a gun. I don't I don't know which one of those is mine. No idea
What's going on? I understand this guy is a fucking absolute maniac. I'll get it this time. See if I can get every single one
The tiny it's hard. It's hard. Fuck. This is hard. God damn it. I'll do it again
I'll get it. I qualified a qualified. It's fine. I got it. What's next triple jump foul?
But I get a foul shit. I can't understand that ball. Wait. It's it is a triple jump. It's like a yeah. Oh
What's the qualifier? I got it. I said why am I not on rust? I don't know. Could I be this is a archery?
That wind is drastically changing every second. Um, okay, okay, I get it ten points
2,500 there you go. Come on, dude. That's a bull's-eye fuck angle
Wait, how do I change the angle? I don't think I can hold it down
Okay, I should be going for what five looking for like 5.0. It's almost right in the middle. Come on. Come on
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh
2,425 fuck. Okay late. Cheers to you with what the following is encouragement. I can still get it
Ah, I can still get it. I did it way too early
I don't care. I'm done performance deserves a big swig of soy too bad
I don't have any access to any of these soy based products. I do have access to a Huell which is not soy based
It's got 400 calories 20 grams of protein Omega threes all your vitamins not over not not overly sweet
It's only got five grams of sugar. I drink this shit and it helped me. I'm telling you
This is not a fuck. I'm no one's paying me to do this. I actually actually helped me. How about uh,
What is doughboy, oh, yeah, he blows up the building right we've seen it mmm
We can try excite bike. Is it just excite bike? I just games good. I need to play chess
All right, I'll play chess in a minute after excited bike after I play excited bike. Nice. This game is so fun
unoptimized
Yeah
Excite a bike. All right, you know, this is to be one minute and 24 seconds new deal
I'll take a look at a second. Hold on currently playing excited bike. Come on. Go
Link suck. Oh deal deal deal. Let me guess
Recreate my little pogchamp as catboy jerma for a billion off the debt. I don't know what that is
Recreate my little pogchamp. I don't understand. I don't know what you're talking about
Astro rope. I think we did that b-wings badminton. I love badminton. Let's play
Okay singles game. I'm gonna be the United States. This looks fun. This game is sick. Okay, hold on
I'm actually really like this. I gotta get the controls down though. I
Dropped the net. I dropped the bad paddle behind me
Shit, okay. I love this
Where's chess? I'll play it right now
Hey, remember the deal. This is my little pogchamp. Well, I'm not I'm not doing my little pogchamp
Just hit it. What do you think I'm trying to do?
Why did he how do you miss that? I?
Had to press left, sorry, I don't understand it's a and B the great deal come on my little pogchamp
You want me to recreate this I don't understand it's like three seconds for a billion dollar for a billion off the debt
Um, I don't what's the big deal. No, don't do it bad deal. What game's fun, but I'm terrible dude as catboy
Um, no, no, no, I'm not gonna happen. How about zippy race?
Wait, is that LA like LA to LA to Las Vegas LA? Is this LA to Vegas? It is
Let's go. I go faster. How are they doing? They were trying to kill me. That person was trying to kill me
Dude, they're all trying to kill me. Let me pass
Fucking L. Yeah realistic. Yeah, LA drivers. I'm just trying to get to Nevada. Can you get out of the way, please?
La drivers, I can't tell who the who's the bad guy here me going like a hundred miles per hour or them for trying
To hurt me while I'm driving. I mean, who's the bad guy here? What?
Okay, I'm good. God. They don't make this easy. Okay, stop
He was trying to some this guy's fucking making me furious. Just get out of the way. I'm almost there
Did I make it I made it to Vegas?
There it is. Oh shit. I'm driving on the wrong side of the road
This is terrible. I gotta get to the casino
Holy shit
What the fuck are you people doing?
Las Vegas drivers LA drivers don't want you to pass and Las Vegas drivers are going to run into you
What the fuck? Where is this supposed to be? This is great. This is from Vegas to where?
HT Arizona, what's HT?
Houston that's a long drive
Well, that was zippy race that was fun check the deal we have an actual a good deal
I don't know if I'm doing any more deals tonight
250 million off the debt if you chroma key the image to the left into the background of the next five games for the
Entire time you play them
That's I I'm pretty now. I've seen a lot of no deals. Yeah, I've seen a lot of no deals. That's a no deal for me
I'm vetoing that one. Sorry. That's an immediate veto about our route 16
you'll
What's the point of this though? I'm just driving in a circle
What the fuck is going on here?
I we just zoomed out to the rest of the computer parts
Am I the blue?
Holy shit. What is going on? I'm that we're not doing that one. Who wears the blood?
Okay, we'll play chess maybe even number for me. I don't remember where it was. It wasn't
69 if it's not okay, if it's not 69, you're in deep shit. Oh, you're in deep shit. I've 21
234 why this is mad Christmas. Holy shit Santa is evil. Why is he so evil?
This is not even an evil thing going on right now. Why is this so sinister?
He's raining down like candy and presents and food, but very very menacingly. Oh, that's why because now he's
Throwing bombs he's trying to get you to
Accidentally grab the bomb. Why is Santa up in the sky?
Okay, if they had a sleigh that he was leaning out of or something
But the fact that he's just Zeus up there throwing down presents. Oh, that was evil
He just threw like an evil face and maybe slow and to killed God and took his place
I'm gonna pick up a bomb. Just see what happens. It was anger behind that one. You threw that hard. I let me see bomb
My god, that's Jesus bro
All right. Where's chess? There it is 93. I don't know how to play this version. I don't know how to do this
I get checkmated already. What I got immediately checkmated you won. I did. Oh, okay
We got I like these two. These are two of my favorites golf. Yep. It's Mario golf
We're going right straight ahead right here. Good hit the funny through the years Mario has oh that was way too hard
Through the years Mario has had like a normal human body
It's always funny when this you see him pop up in random little Nintendo games with just a couple of normal person's body
I was just so why am I going so hard? No, it's cuz I'm just
One wood. Hey, let's put it fuck what just happened. Okay
I we're going for we're gonna go for a hole-in-one first try straight over the water in work. Okay
Well, I feel like we've been neglecting the four hundreds
cyber cyber annoyed
Okay, Nintendo program choose level of difficulty using the select button, whatever
Cyber annoyed I'm just falling forever. Okay, what can I ever go down?
How am I supposed to do this? It was awful
All right. What was the nav? That was something Star Force space ET. It's just space invaders. God damn it
They put ET on it though. This is a classic
It didn't
Guys getting tired you guys getting like a little sleepy here. Yeah, it's okay
You can go to bed for a little while. I'll wake you up in a little bit
It's a nice relaxing space invaders in the background. I'll wake you up soon. Fuck. I lost this game sucks
Vigilators is actually really fun. Wait cub adventure my little panda polar bear
That's one of these to collect everything and then run to the exit. These are the worst games ever
I did all the work that guy didn't do anything after them have this song half of them are this game
one game Andy
Let's go back to the 400s Venice Beach. Wait Sanrio Carnival. It's a carnival
Hello kitty after a good start
And can I read this great deal? Let's take a look just real quick new deal play video game for $3 off the debt
All right time the person up for 30 minutes
Accept this this one. Oh, it's another Tetris game. Oh, it's dr. Mario, but hello kitty characters
No, ooh
shrub rage
Watch this gonna get a double one
To what I was I don't double like this shit up
Bang and then bang and then bang take this area. Check this shit up bang
Take this out
Check this shit already
Bang. I just say so bang
Yeah, take this one up
Take this shit. I lose bang. It is a fucking bang
Yeah, I've ever watched cowboy be Bop. I have yeah
This is a good. It's a good animated television series about
Wisdom
Wisdom boy. I'm on easy. I don't care. I love a one
Wisdom. Oh, it's one of these
That is to put pieces in here. No, I'm done. Don't I don't play it. I'm up on that one
Quarterback, yep, John Madden. No, that's not John Madden
It's a different John who is that John Elway
Like team New England. I'll be New England. I want to hit start on New England. No, I don't fucking San Francisco. What?
Shit. Oh nice. All right. We're gonna do a bomb pass every single play. That's not past that's dive pass
Must be a B. Okay, try that again
intentional grounding
What's happening? I'm European. Oh, just just American things. I got it. That's the first down
Who's the ball? You know, I play every football game. I
Okay, tell me if you guys did this shit, too
So my brother and I used to play like Madden all the time and I was never very good
But how I always played is I would always just cycle because you could only control one person at a time
So what I would do is I was cycled to every single person
So let's say it was a to cycle to your defensive line or your your tailgater or whatever they are
I would cycle to every single person and hit the dive button immediately when the indicator went over their head
So it would just be like
And maybe I would hit the person that had the ball sometimes and it would be infuriating for him
so it would just be
Select dive select dive select dive select dive and it works
But if it doesn't work, it's a guaranteed run back or touch down
So my brother would win a lot of the times we played Madden like 80 plus points to like six
So I was never very good at it. Oh
First down 20 yards just bomb it into the end zone
Got it. That's a cool story, bro. All right time the person up is 17 days. Oh touchdown touchdown touchdown touchdown. Oh
Your nose still wheezing. No, I'm fine
17 how many seconds is that?
That's a touchdown if I've ever seen one touchdown if I've ever seen one
Go Patriots go Patriots that's terrible this year and like Tom Brady left
So like what are we gonna do now? What are we gonna do now? Like Brady's gone, man?
Brace fucking gone
He's gone man
Muscle, who do I want to be to be the base? Just bald. I don't know. What should I be the night? Oh
It holy shit this game awesome, I don't know what character am I okay, I think I'm green guy
Who's out there who is that? Hey
Did a little kid somebody shoot something in here?
You got a smash ball. Are you serious? You think I'm watching down there? What the fuck?
God damn it. I tried for a big play going on top rope fortnight dancing. I got the smash ball this time
Throw an axe at him. I got another one. Oh, he's done. I taunt towards the camera every time
Yeah, I got him. Don't let him tag in don't let him tag in fuck. This is grandpa Homer a grandpa Simpson
Shit, he got the pill just avoid him run away. I gotta tag out tag out tag out tag. Come on, dude
Tag out tag out tag out. I think I broke it. They break it. Oh, I can see we're good
Alright, what do you guys think? What should we do? How about bowling? Yeah, definitely play macross. All right
I will after this ball. I always go to seven pound ball lighter. There's more room to move
That's how you get a guaranteed strike right down though Mario seven ball. It has to be lighter for your scrawny arms. That's fine
It's okay. I yeah, I got I got smaller. I can I get big arms. Are you talking about?
Well, what if I go I'm gonna roll it down really really slow
See if I can get a diaper strike
You've got a big dump truck. You think so? All right, let's see if I can have it go right down the middle
Kind of slow, but whatever I want to be all the way down
Come on. Nice and slow
Oops, I got it. There goes zero power. That's what I wanted. Oh, well
Bowling is fun. Goodbye. You invented bowling. Holy shit, dude
You must be like a millionaire or something right back to the 400 space hunter transformers
634 Ken, okay. Oh, there's like a low strike a high strike. Am I in a race with the dog?
Look at the top. This is a race with the dog. I have to beat the dog to the finish line
Okay, wait, hold on
I'm going I'm going I'm going the dog doesn't have any obstacles only I have obstacles
Shit, how much help do I have? Oh my fucking god. I gotta beat this. I gotta beat this dog
I gotta beat this fucking dog. Okay, we're good. Come on, dude. Seriously
I'm not sure those I don't need to collect those swords for anything. Just taking up space
My inventory. Watch out. I'm winning by a lot
Kind of hurting my eyes looking at this so fast dog is way behind. I'm doing good. He's way behind
Now it's raining caterpillars. Just don't get hit again. I can take my time
Whoa, it's the seven plagues
This is ridiculous, dude, how am I supposed to do this without getting killed? Are you so I'm so mad
I'm so mad. I don't want to do it again, but I have to now I get it. I just do what's happening
Why do I have to race the dog? What's the point of racing the dog?
You can walkie-talkie sound Roger. Yeah, I hear you loud and clear dog till behind you
Yeah, yes Roger that. Oh my god. I hate this game. I don't care. Okay, we have
Back future is this back to the future
Back to the future. This looks like the real game. I believe it is
Never even seen these movies start to finish. I've seen like him ride on a hoverboard
that I've never seen I've
When the and when the when the when the DeLorean
Is it called the plan? Yeah
The
Dandelion the Mandalorian. Yeah when the Mandalorian gets to like 75,000 miles per hour, right?
Okay, this game is not good. It's very bad. Even it was the official game. It's very bad. He's on the reddit shelf
I have to play it this control. Okay
Yes, what's grill master doing here? Let's go. Let's go Cupert
This game is what a classic Super Nintendo game I forgot the controls get away from me
Get away from me. I just completed Cupert level two
What's what you got? What do you mean? What's square? Do you think he's saying? I think it's shit. I think it's ass
It's balls balls. All right. Everybody say your favorite youtuber three two one. We did toy factor. We did utmost warfare
We did we didn't do wild worm pretty wild do an ego check
Sure. Wait, this one looks fun. I have to eat the fruit to get stronger. Probably. Yeah, that's exactly what it is
Avoiding all the chaos get big enough and strong enough to eat them
I played this game on PopCap defeating the fish game. Yep. Let's get huge. Am I big enough to eat anybody?
I don't think I'm big enough to eat that. Am I I'll try. Nope, whatever
Caterpillars don't eat other bugs. Don't they eat like that? They're decaying bodies or something by the goonies
It's just like the bumper sticker where it just shows how many people are in that person's family on the back of their like window. I
Got one bomb. This looks like the official game not blow them up. I blow them up. I was too late
All right, it's time for a macross. I'm in I can't blow up the wall. Oh, that's unfortunate
Why more like macross what? Yes, it's boring macross time. Where was it?
528 macross you start push that would really hurt your ears. Yes ready Valkyrie three left. It's pretty good
The ship doesn't move very fast though. This is actually the anime. What anime there's a macross anime. Well, that looks weird
I don't know what I'm doing. But I guess the world is changing behind us
Macross is an anime attack. Is it is this the intro of macross?
Get out of here. God, it's a side-scroller anime
He for power
Total corruption total power
Total power
I'm not doing a good tonight. I'm not doing a good tonight. I usually can do it way better than that
I can do it way better than that. I'm kind of pissed off that that's annoying me
Actually, that's pissing me off. Why is there an HP meter in a shmup?
Because this is an anime dude, you're watching second episode
Why do you think this is a shmup late TF2? I think it's on 547. That's gonna fight the second boss
Your shmup shmup. Hey, you know what you're you're you're shmupin
So people that play lots of shmups are they are they like considered? Would you be called like a shmup it?
Okay, did these we didn't do Mickey Mouse Mickey Mouse to the little to little house
This is so cute. Look at how cute this is. I love this
It key can't jump on him. Okay. I love this little minimalistic Mickey and Minnie design
I love it. It's cute. Look. I'm trying to jump. Why are we the ice climbers? This is annoying. Oh my god. Where's that key?
What is going on in your house Mickey? This your house is fucking insane call an exterminator. Oh
Wait, the exterminator would be like get rid of you too. That would not be good. You should be able to shoot
Oh, I have just have a jump. I got the key. I'm good. What were they thinking?
What do they think we mean? What were they thinking? You have to buy a gun for the door. What I don't have the key
I just got the key didn't I wrong door. You need the mickey
Hate it
Okay, let's do a ghost buster is if this is the original bed. This one horrible. Yes, it is
This is so bad. I don't what the hell is going on. You need a beam
I
VGN
See, it's just a bunch of donkey turds
This is a fucking ball sack full of donkey ass
This eats more shit than a fucking donkey's ass the original video game youtuber pretty much
I think I've watched a majority of his first like a hundred or two hundred videos were over there
Hey, he's still going isn't he? Hey, he'd been around longer than all of us
Are we pushing the car because it ran out of gas. He's immortal
Why are we pushing the car?
Fill it up. I got his autograph once at a con. He's a genuinely nice guy. Oh, I'm sure I'm sure he is
He's like he's funny too. You need a beam. What do I get in the shop? Oh my god
I don't do this anymore. He's supposed to run over the barrels. I'm afraid to touch. I have
$9,700 somebody said the Ghostbusters are broke. I have like 10 grand
And by the way 10 grand in this in the car
I don't know how much is in their bank account fun fact Huey Lewis sued for the Ghostbusters song. Yeah, and he won
You got to add that part too. He won that lawsuit
Only 200 meters to go
What's there? Oh, no
I'm not doing this anymore. We're going somewhere else. Okay, we did boot cat Aladdin 3
the side-scroller
This is the philanthropy revenge of Jafar. Yeah, this is what they came up with for the game
When that shit right to DVD you'd always tell what Disney movies to not watch when it was just in the bin at your local
Blockbuster they didn't put it out on the rack to rent. It was just in the bin like ah, I'm probably not gonna get that one
I don't really want to watch that one. I've never seen it. Thank God you do. You know that Cinderella 3 exists
Yeah, yeah, you feel like that could have happened to Shrek
But it was too popular for them to put it into like the Walmart bin the universe sold. Oh
I thought we were gonna be buying and selling planets and stuff
Just easy and hard. Okay, I don't what character am I? Oh, it's pac-man, but the song is pretty sick though
This is a great song
Not very hard. It's toxic. No, it is not nice try though
Oh
What's the star do that was a fake that was a fake guy it was a fake apple now
You pissed me off you pissed me off. You pissed me off. You pissed me off. You pissed me off
You pissed me off. You pissed me off quick trivia. What is that from? Click trivia is there any
German 985
YouTube fans in here I guess is none I just zero people zero fans of German on eight fives YouTube channel
Channel zero fans here thought I had a few fans in here thought I had a few people that were like fans of the channel
Okay, ooh
fuck off
Somebody was looking for this one earlier twin B
You pissed me off you pissed me off really a sly Cooper
I don't know maybe I tried and I just didn't want to play a ps3 was like burning
So I just didn't do it. I tried to get an emulator and the emulator looked like shit
I gave up I actually loaded up sly Cooper on the the PlayStation 3 the remastered version
My ps3 started to smell like burning plastic so I had to turn it off
I was gonna give me a headache buy a new one. Yeah, I know but I
Look, I've been busy. They're on steam sly Cooper's not on steam ps3 emulator that I had I tried so many settings
But it just looked so awfully
Scanlined and artifacted it was a ton of ghosting every time I would move around there was input lag on the control
It was a mess. I tried I tried so many things to get it to like not look horrible. Please get the bells, dude
All right
See 28,000 28,000 that's the amount of community subs
I will give if I get hit in the next one full second one. Thank God. We're good. Hey
I was actually doing okay, and then I started laughing at something. That's fun
You still do you still care about me if I'm new and don't know all your old jokes
Yeah, you don't have to know I mean this 10,000 people are I figured one person would have seen
Raven's cry minute number three second number like eight in the video you pissed me off
I can't I'm just surprised. It's not this 10,000 of you here. How about
Colorful dragon. Oh this dragon is absolutely fucking zonked. Why do they all have to be this hop down collect things?
How do I pick anything? What am I supposed to do? I was a bite. What's the good?
What is the goal step on each one of these to lay an egg on those?
Game sucks. Yeah. All right. I have to play castle excellent. Wait, did I do this yesterday?
Castle excellent play RoboCop. We did all the RoboCops yesterday. We did all the RoboCops yesterday and they were insane
Castle awful
How do I attack wait, can I only it I can only attack if I'm moving Jesus
Why?
He has a fucking bow and arrow. I'm done. Holy shit. This is the best comment. I've seen all night
Snorty I gotta shout your name out here. This is the best. This is unbelievable reference here said you're playing dish
Satellite games. Holy shit. That's unbelievably accurate. That's unbelievable
What a great
What an unbelievable reference. I think we're running out of material here
What should I play? Have we really gone through all 600 of these fucking things? We've done almost all of them Bruce Lee
We did Bruce Lee to isn't that we?
470 which one pond pond Valley. I think we did this about
Buggy popper. Oh that was gonna be like popping bugs like insects not the actual vehicle, but okay
Let's go. What's wrong with this car? Nothing wrong with your transmission, dude. Holy shit
Where did all these cars come from? Wait, did I just jump him?
Wait, why is my character doing that? I guess it is called buggy hopper. I'm not pressing a button to do that
It's just randomly happening. Good thing I got a warning
Great we're good. Oh
Do I need to be in first place or something or just survive? I have no idea
This was actually kind of fun what under repair Oh, I'm plugged into a wall socket
Oh, man, that front looked pretty fucked sus to me. I know I know I know I know I shouldn't have I know
all tasks completed
Have to say it though all tasks completed
What the fuck did I just miss this guy sucks? All right, you crashed 14 cars
Why is that a great thing? Shouldn't that be like a be more careful next time?
That's a great job
They're all crashing into the wall with it. Can they not jump that seems sort of unfair?
I'm the only one with a buggy popper. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. He pretending to be this bad. I haven't lost once
Fucking whatever. I know Ricky
South Park character. It's like Clyde from South Park. I like this one so far. Hey look Chad. It's you
That's you right there
Yeah, it's you. It looks just like you. I don't want this kind of speed. Oh nice
Diamonds. Oh, this game's fun. This is hard to control remember. This isn't comedy. This is warfare
Didn't even know you could jump. I don't know what light anymore. Is this Toho just to who?
Wait, no
Cosmos Cup bar games
Absolutely. Oh, this is a casino for
Amusement only not for real money good thing. They told us. All right, let's go. I won. Holy shit
I just won the whole thing. I just won the whole thing. I just won
I beat the whole game big win. How much did I win? I didn't have a bed in not fun
I was watching the demo. What do we got? What was it? Well, I saw another one. I wanted Cosmos Cop. Someone looks good a
2010 the terror legion from alien nation space invaded galaxy
Universal Defense
Headquarters attached Cosmos Cup to destroy them mission one cross over outside
Defense area pretty fun. It's just that other game. We played it's just that Sega game space harrier. Hey, it's me
All right
It's making the noise that I feel like it's a dentist tools make if they touch the wrong part of your tooth
I'm gonna get that. Ah
Yeah, I hate it
This is they they like are doing the drill and they move a little too close to the tooth or a different side of the
Tooth and it makes that I can't hear this anymore. Ah
Fuck I have to I gotta leave firehouse rescue
Get on the ladder I've shaved you okay, let's go. Let's rescue somebody
We have to go to the house. But do I need gas first? You have a really elaborate driveway. It's just a cat
Alright, get on rescue complete store. I got the cat. I rescued the cat. I did. Alright, what's it? What's happening here?
Oh, come on out. Come on out. Everybody left. When's the jump scare gonna happen? This game is for actual babies
I mean the splash screen had Fisher price on it
I don't think it's gonna be very much thought involved in this what happens if you don't rescue them
They just stay in there. What is the danger in this house? Are we practicing they die? What there's no date?
What's the danger? There's no fire. There's no what if it's a gas leak?
This is a game for actually five-year-olds just teach them. I don't know basic skills
I don't know chop lifter. Let's try chop lifter. Please do 545
I will that a shoe on the ground then we see a chopper
Okay, that was chop lifter. It already was lifted. It got lifted at 545 somebody said Puyon. Ooh, look at this
I like that alligator box thing. Holy shit. What you gonna pop the balloons? This is awesome
Okay, I'm gonna be good at this. This is just balloons tower defense, but I have to control the one tower
This is amazing
Watch what you're pulling you pulled too tight son. If you pull too hard, you're gonna tip it and I'm gonna fall
I thought they're throwing shit back pulling too hard. It was shield. He's fucking blocking it
You gotta wait and I'm wait get out get him out of here. What does that mean?
Did he get into the town? He's climbing up the ladder. This is actually kind of scary get out of here
How do I get him? Oh shit. Don't let him up to the magic rock
That like our family stone or our family meat don't let him up the communal ham
And that shit and Dr. Seuss don't they eat a giant communal ham in that movie and that book and everything whatever
The Grinch the Rose Beast. Yeah, it feeds the whole town, right? Oh shit. He's going fast. Oh my god
He's taking the communal ham. How do we stop him?
How do we stop him from stealing that?
No, he can't do it. It's like a little dog that gets a huge bone. He can't walk anywhere with it
Oh, take it and push it off
No, do I win?
Wait, they're gonna kill you. They're gonna wait. They're gonna drop the communal ham on my head. Oh
My god, they're gonna drop the community. Fuck. I'm dead. I kind of want to do it
I kind of see it happens. I want to see what happens. Let's see what happens when they drop the communal ham on me
Oh, fuck you. God damn it. I know I wanted to see you 390. Okay, and three one
446. Oh, what is 446? Oh sick. It's actually amazing paperboy delivers earns honors big bucks
Mysterious vandalism baffles police. Okay, nice
This game's actually I'm pretty good at this game. It checks out but you can't try what you can't drive over a grate on the ground
Watch out. I don't even know what I fucking ran into. Nice toss. What's going on with that guy?
That's a really hard itch to scratch apparently
I can't even read that one. Get away from me. Why is that person trying to grab me? Training course start
Not bad go for the jump canceled subscriptions. Oh, whatever nobody gets the paper anyways anymore
No, nobody gets a paper. Why is a grim reaper here? The grim reaper can take you. Okay. What is that?
What I don't okay has many in devil cool paperboy calls it quits
You try having people try to throw shit at you
I've like death chase you have tornadoes attack you have people like lying on the sidewalk trying to
S their own D shit their own diaper police versus thief
Violent chasing. Okay, it's just the pathing for Sim City. You just follow the cars around like this is horrible
What was right above it? Nothing was right above it that I wanted I thought that was tiger hell spider-man not cracky
Police dog lazy. Oh, it's Lassie police dog Lassie. We're gonna get that thief
Stealing diamonds ladies burying stuff. He's burying bombs. He's burying guns. He's burying coke
These are bags of cocaine another gun. You have a lot of shit. Okay, so I have to find all that stuff
Where's a bag of coke? It's a gun coke. He's just
Crossed across the ground that one that coke. There's a gun over here bomb
Oh, if you don't touch the bomb, you don't dig up the bomb. Okay, good to know gun one more. Where is it?
I'm
Yeah, we've seen everything time's up. Okay. Now I want to do crystal ball pin dabble crystal ball
Immediate next we'll try nutcracky
After egg contest what I have to do. I have to collect the eggs. They're gonna fall. I don't understand
Oh, I have to I can change the direction
Look that hen up there is an absolute fucking unit old Megan and I'm done got it not cracky
Not cracky save I don't know what that said who knows I'm the nutcracker with a gun
There is it to run away. Oh, there's a bullets. There's no car to shoot stuff. There's a nutcracker food
What am I's voice doing? All right, I win. I actually kind of like this one. That's not Parker. It's up. That's me down at all
It's just speed running these I saw I saw Jay Leno and I just had to start doing it
Yeah, you know, it's the easiest voice to do. It's just just move around and just go like that
There's this house is on fire. What do I do? Oh
The versus wait, it's just dropped a fucking missile on me and then get in get in get in get in get in
Get in wait. I don't
Think it hurt watch out and get it get it get it get it get it and go go go go go go go go go
I don't have any weapons or anything. I did it. Okay, I saved everybody
It's just the same game over and over again with a different
Spot that they walk out of all right three more and I'm done and this thing's going
Right into the recycling. Are we gone?
573 somebody said we did flappy already. What about magic jewelry?
This one doesn't count as three give it to a kid to disappoint them. That's mean
All right, which one we got three more where we're gone one. We haven't seen yet three
Three I can remember already did that one or eleven
Star all right, it's just it's actually just a star floating around. I don't know what the goal is you just float around
It's not really false advertising. The name of the game is just called star
So it's not like this is a problem or anything. I'm kind of growing does that mean anything?
Backgrounds making me sick. Now that you mentioned it is me. I mean to me too next two more. This is 260
Which one is that?
Candy workshop
Where did the candy workshop? Sorry circus Charlie, which one? Yeah, I didn't want to play that. Where is it? Where's circus Charlie?
Circus Charlie there it is. All right, let's play circus Charlie nice. Okay, so we have to jump through
Double money up there. I'm losing bonus, but I'm doing fine. Ooh, I have to beat circus Charlie. I gotta get to the end. Oh
Fuck you. I'm right there. All right one more after this
That's gonna be the last one circus Charlie done. What's next? Oh, okay tightrope
He's back there. Oh an elephant. This one's way easier this good game
Actually, I kind of like it fast monkey that one too
Is there another event there is this one looks hard. Ooh
Let it gonna split to that's it for that one
All right, where we going final one last one of the night and then this thing's going away
It's fun to play them though. I'm glad I put it this one do 83
I think we did there already didn't we we did 83 already. We did boot cat already
330 I think we did we did all the 300s. I think yeah we did didn't we do this human human creative presents
Egypt story mode rank select digest. No, I just
Can't read this trick to you. Did you know that you're toxic?
That's so stupid
Jesus Christ. I want nothing to do with this one
I thought this is gonna be an adventure game where you go around the tombs and stuff
I was the actual last one 334 was robbed
334 was robbed a Koto no Ken. I think we already did this. Yeah
Final one is gonna be
579 let's take a look ice hockey
That seems there to end it by 58 feelings and where did to
for
480 Sansu for
I guess it's a
Pop-up windows. I have a virus. It's a math game. Do you hear Otto? He's like, hey
How's the 22 divided by 170 out? Why don't was that there for what is that?
Why is there a math problem over there? What the hell is the point of this if I stab him? Does a number come out?
Terrible
Alright, I'll see you later
If the final one that I'm gonna pick right now ice queen ice ocean break out
I think it's just break out
That's just break out. It's kind of cool. It's kind of cool version of break out. I
Think I can't hit the fishes that fly that go around still playing this not anymore after this
It's fun for a while looks good. Yeah, I mean, it's like kind of fun
What a shirt and I have a shirt on I have a shirt on look I'm sure
Take the shirt off. All right, I'll see you later
I'm not straight. I got a doctor's appointment tomorrow. I'm not screaming tomorrow
But I will see you guys on I'll see you guys on Wednesday
Yeah, the big delay right because I have to capture this thing. That was the family computer system
621 that was a lot of fun
Thanks for joining me on the last couple of nights. I'll see you guys on Wednesday
Head to the end here. Let's show the credits. Thank you as always everybody for the subs community subs new subs old subs
We've been here for four or five years or if you just decided to show up today. Thanks a lot
I really appreciate it
Hope you're enjoying your new year so far only seen you for a day or two and I've wiped out a billion dollars from the debt
Today, I feel pretty good right now. I feel great
I mean granted that was one of the most horrible experiences probably I've had like just trying to get that to happen
It's I mean I thought it was kind of funny. I think I thought it was funny
I'm trying to cope so bad with doing that whole thing
That's a billion dollars off the debt. I'm happy you can't still hear this annoying song. Can you it's very loud
That has been updated very good very good very good. How much is left in the debt?
Um what is the actual official debt it was 2.5 billion, and then I added like 2 billion, right?
So it was like four and a half billion or something so
So now it should be down to three or like three two point eight or something with three three billion there there is
We're gonna make sure that's updated still four billion. It should be updated three point five billion, okay?
That means it was four point five billion. That's the update what the fuck it was five point six billion before you kidding me
What did I do? How's it even possible? All right? Good night guys
I'll see you on Wednesday probably around same time around three o'clock Pacific. Take care of yourselves. We'll see you soon and good night. Goodbye