Having a cigarette? Yeah, sometimes I'd like to smoke down here.
Oh, that was a headshot.
I'm pulling off my headphones.
I'm gonna pass it out.
Did you hit that guy right in the mouth?
Did you hit him right in the mouth?
Look at this guy. Look at this. Is this an EMT?
Is he empty? He's like, what the fuck happened?
He's walking away.
He doesn't want anything to do with this, I don't think.
I just took a drink. I was about to start spitting up. Oh my god.
The EMT around the corner just doesn't want any part of it.
Yo, the EMT. This guy's like, look, he's driving away.
That might have been the funniest clip I've ever seen in GTA.
I'm serious. That really might have been the funniest clip I've ever fucking seen in this game.
What? Where? Where am I? Where are we?
What? What's going on?
You're disappearing when I drive here on my screen.
There is no where I'm seeing like underneath the ground.
I'm not even on your bike. Try to like keep going.
Where are we? Oh, wait, where am I?
Why did I turn into you? Press to get off the bike.
It says you're on it, but you're not there.
What is this guy doing? Yeah, you're invisible.
There's a guy in here too. Can you see this guy?
No. He just got on the bike.
What? What?
Who is that phantom? Who is that guy?
Am I on the... Keep going.
What? I don't know if you're invisible.
Whoever you're fighting isn't here. I'm so confused.
Dude, this is insane.
There's another guy on the bike in like the ghost world.
Just smash into something. Can I fight this guy?
This guy had a machine gun.
Can you kill yourself? Apparently I'm falling now.
I'm doing like a dance.
I'm doing like a Blues Brothers dance.
I'm trying to find a way to like get out of here.
Like another way to like another dimension.
Like we're just both quiet. Just like, yes, yes.
Yeah, well, you don't like hang on doors for fun.
Every pedestrian that walks by too looks at you and is like,
What the fuck? Where are they?
I want to get somebody over here.
You don't think you're not going to say anything?
That was weird. You should have said something.
You should have said something about that.
Get in the middle of the road, Jerma.
This guy's an idiot. He's aiming the gun at you.
You're not even close to being over here.
What is he doing? What is he doing?
I'm like hanging out with the cop.
He's utterly confused right now.
So lady, do you know how to get to 42nd Street from here?
Well, yes, it's very easy.
What you want to do son is you want to go.
You got to listen to this guy.
This guy just said to pull over.
You have to listen.
Okay.
All right. He said get out of the car.
I'm sorry officer.
I got a gun.
I don't want. I don't want to get.
What is this? What's going?
We'll see one eventually.
Yeah. Look for one. Look for one.
I'm trying.
Do you see the subway?
I think so.
I think this one over still alive with my parachute.
Put it on.
Oh epic.
Epic.
Absolutely epic.
That shouldn't have killed me.
What is?
Oh, right.
You're in a helicopter.
What is this place?
I don't remember any of this.
Are you getting the weird territory though?
Because I don't like you.
I saw a sick jump.
Hold on sick jump.
You talking about the slide?
Yeah, it's like a ramp.
That was so stupid.
Are you on this?
What's going on?
Who's on it?
You're on it.
I can't.
I'm trying to get off.
No, don't.