Good afternoon, everybody. No music, what happened? Why is it muted? I didn't do that.
I swear to God, I didn't do that. Already upset. Hi, how are you? Welcome back to another live stream.
Today, we are going to be playing No More Heroes. We actually are going to play it today.
I was going to play it yesterday, but had a little bit of a Bluetooth problem.
That problem has been resolved. Troubleshooting.
I'm gonna explain something. Yeah, it's all set.
Go to the dentist, you idiot. Did you brush your blue teeth? Why would I have blue teeth?
Why would I have blue teeth? I don't understand this reference from what?
Oh, because of Bluetooth. I had a Bluetooth. Jeez. And you guys. And you guys. That was weird.
You guys minus two shit. If I said that, it'd be minus two all day. You would clip that and say
worst joke of the decade. Come on now. Don't throw stones if you live in a glass house.
What are we doing? Oh yeah, right. We're gonna play No More Heroes. This is an original Wii game.
Actually, you could argue this is one of the best games that came out for the Wii.
We're getting a No More Heroes 3. Took a long time to get it, but we're playing one of the
best games on the Wii. This game has lightsabers. So you could argue that this is a better Star Wars
than the sequel saga. You could if you wanted to. Sure you will in this chat. True.
True. Why did I just say that? Now I'm gonna like ignite the fan base. I should have done that. Oh
well. But we just started too. Jerma sucks just gave 20 community subs. What fan base? Omega LOL.
Okay. You don't make an entire theme park around Star Wars unless at least 100 people are gonna go.
Jerma sucks really just gave 20 subs though. Thank you Jerma sucks. We'll see if I suck
because this game's hard. It requires skill, requires timing, and patience. It's a third person
slashing, dodging, blocking game. 70 yeah channel points have been changed a little bit.
It is now prices have changed and if you accumulate 75,000 points I'll wink on camera.
After the 20 community subs, $100 by Phylactery. 10,000 bits. Thousands of dollars that Phylactery
has given over the last few months continues to grow. They say missed the last few live streams
so had to watch the VODs. Here's some money for sucking on that used Wiimote and putting on
lipstick. Jesus. Thanks a lot for the huge fucking money drop man. 10,000 bits from Phylactery lich.
I didn't even tweet that I was live. It's because my phone was dead. Give me like two minutes. We'll
get going. Get comfortable. Get comfortable. My words hard today. They were hard last night too.
What's wrong with me? Be right back. All right. We've been tweeted. It's time to move over to know
more heroes. No more heroes for the Nintendo Wii. I got my Wiimote. I got my nunchuck.
Do you have to use both? This is where we pick the difficulty. There's only two difficulties
right now because you have to beat the game I believe first. How did I get the remote to
connect? A lot of bullshit. I mean sure why don't we go off on this? No I'm just saying I don't want
to go off every stream. I don't need to go off. I feel like every time I go off I'm just leaving
you guys a really long annoying string of 10 voicemails on your machine in a row. We don't
got to do that today. Let's just put it this way. Let's put it this way. It didn't work. I have
internal Bluetooth. Bluetooth sucks by the way. The technology never took off.
But it took off for like three years. No, I'm not going off. No I'm not. I'm just telling you. I'm
just going to give you some facts about what happened with this story. I'm just going to get
the bullet points. Everybody's motherboard has a Wi-Fi card built into it. Most of it.
You know internal. I have an internal Bluetooth. It's not good enough. It picked up five, six
probably houses down the street. Somebody's like fire stick. Okay. But it won't get my
Wiimote and it won't get anything in my room. So I had to go get a couple of different dongles
to test it out and try to get it to work. And I finally got one dongle in particular
that worked to connect my Wiimote. But there you go. It didn't even go off. We're not going
to do sweet. We're going to do mild. This game's hard. Many strong men await you. Yeah, it's going
to be hard. You're not going to shout them out. You want me to shout out a Bluetooth adapter?
Okay. So you would like for me to shout out a Bluetooth adapter. Special thank you to
I don't even know what the name of this thing is. What is it? No, that's the wrong one. I don't want
to shout out the... Is it dinner time? What was that? I want to say this right because if I say
it wrong, I'm going to be like a dick. A Targus? Is that correct? It's guys. It came in a package.
Hold on. I have to go under my desk. There it is. Yeah, it's a Targus. Yep.
So you can thank Targus Gaming for letting this happen. I know a lot of gamers out there don't
have much patience. Special thanks to Targus Gaming. Oh wait, you're not supposed to see this yet.
Okay, we're gonna see. Yeah, Travis Touch. By the way, I want to make this prediction now
because that's what I do. That's what we do in this channel. Travis Touchdown is going to be DLC
pack number two. Fighter's Pass two, character number three. There you go. Just that's going.
That's what's happening. All right, let's do it. Mild. Mild. Here we go. No more heroes.
You do ride a motorcycle in this game and notoriously all the motorcycle
driver but whether that's a full letter grade because you do get to drive it.
Unfortunately, the motorcycle it slows down the entire game
and no more heroes on the original Wii in the motorcycle segments ran at probably 15 frames
a second. I know a lot of gamers out there don't have much patience. At least that's what Bishop
the dude at the video store said. So I'm at the register and then I realized I got no money.
I was seriously broke. Why? Because I met this smoking hot chick last night at the death match
bar. Man, she smelled good. So being the gentleman I am, I bought her a drink. Anywho, I decided to
get a job. The gig? Assassinate the drifter. I love this game. So I went where I was supposed to
and waited for the guy to show up. And there he was. This cat. Well dressed, cool. Couldn't
tell if he was the shit or just plain old shit. Yeah, so he's stylish, fast, aggressive and packing
heat. Bada bing. Or at least it was supposed to be till she showed up. Her name? Sylvia Crystal,
an agent with this watchma call it association. The assassin skill. Congratulations. You are
certified as the 11th best hitman. How about that? I'm so pumped up for the new one above you
and aim for the top. How's that short and simple enough for you? It's gonna be a long hard road.
But who knows? Could kick ass. Could be dangerous. Could tell you suck. What do you say bro?
Yes, that is. Let's see how far we can get to medic. That is.
That's the medic. And he does a handful of voices in this, by the way.
And you're finally going to get to hear you're going to get to hear it. I can't wait to get here.
How many times have you guys heard me say on this stream? Are you prepared to have at least 100?
Fuckhead. Yes, I'm so ready for this. Help me out here. Where's this death metal dude?
Bad answer. It's from Star Wars. Star Wars movies. And you upgrade. You can get like different
lightsabers. You can get like this like 10 different lights. There's like 20 lightsabers
across the whole. I can't wait. Let's do it. Uh, I actually do not need to do the tutorial.
I don't. I know what the fuck I'm doing. Oh, it feels so good to play. It feels so good to play.
Now those of you that want to know, there is two stances in this game.
I might have to turn it down a little bit. A little bit on the loud side for you.
So you see the Wii mode. I'm tilting it right now. You have high, obviously. You blow.
And you have to choose between the two. And if you're facing the same- I'm so excited. I'm
so happy right now. All right, let's go. Let's go. I can't wait any longer. I gotta go.
Let's do it. The one- the best part about this is everybody has that same voice when you kill
somebody. There you go. That is also Robert Atkin Downes doing that voice.
Oh, this looks like a prototype from Metal Gear Rising. This is a better Star Wars game than Metal
Gear Rising. I'm sorry. It is. I know I'm going to probably offend people. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I was looking to chat. I was looking to chat. I know. Plus house. I hate everything about this.
Everything. This would be the worst stream of the decade if I could make it.
Get that person out of here. Get him out of here. Get him out of here. That's- that's unbelievable
for me to hear that. I have to be careful though because I will use the Wiimote and because I'm
sitting close to the mic. I will smash this into the mic. I can't be hearing this right now. I
can't be hearing this. This is a classic video game. Like one of the best fo- I would say this
is- No More Heroes. No More Heroes 2 is some of the- one of the best of the last generation.
You know what I mean? I think it is. Got a trading card. Don't anger Jeremy. He's in a good mood
today. Be careful. I'm going to get a double. Oh, you guys think that this- oh, you do- wait,
hold on. You don't like this game? Did somebody say they didn't like this game?
We'll- we'll see in about five seconds. Wait, I don't want to die. Here we go. Oh. Get him.
I'll show you. I'll show you why. I'm just having fun slicing people up. Here we go.
Oh, I got a power up. I can't even tell what's happening. All right. You sure you don't like
this game? Your grapple moves are all wrestling moves. He just did it. He said it. He said it.
Are you prepared to help? Wanting one more? That's that block. Trading card number two.
I think there's a hundred? Two hundred? This is what it's like when a kid is showing their parents
their Minecraft house. Look. Look at- look at my house. Oh, wait. You watch. You can do this.
That's how you charge the battery. It's- it's got like that solar LED technology.
It's not a Minecraft house. I know for a fact that I- half you guys have never even seen this
game before. So I- yeah. Maybe it is my Minecraft house. I'm happy to show it.
All right. What- this- this is a Minecraft house. Where are they? This guy- look at- he's got
lightsaber fist weapons. They didn't put that in any of these Star Wars.
Ow.
That's legit. Yeah. Are you excited for No More Heroes 3? Oh, you better believe it.
That's why I'm playing this one. We haven't even gotten to the open world yet.
There's mini games. You have to work. I remember hating that part of the game. Do- okay. Do you
think I'm going to hate that part of the game again? It's been like 12 years. Do you think
I'm still going to get really mad at like collecting coconuts? Wait. Check that one.
They're mildly fun. You're going to like it more than the main game. I mean, it's possible,
but I don't think so. Oh, I gotta go back down. The only bullshit one is the one with the scorpion.
I don't remember it. The scorpions? You have to like step on a scorpion? Turn on the camera
when you charge the saber. Well, do you have 75,000 channel points yet? That's how you get
the camera to turn on. I don't see anybody with 75,000 yet. All right, let's do it.
Pain. You're a joke. What a pain. You're a joke.
Fuck that. Battery. All right. Who? Oh, there you go. Oh, this guy's also a Jedi. He's got a
lightsaber. Yep. See you later. 4,500 bucks. I love the aesthetic of the whole game too.
I love the little blocky quest markers. All right, I gotta actually pay attention there
because this is going to be hard. First checkpoint. Oh, he didn't say it. Fuck. I cut it off.
What's this? Oh shit. This is one of the superpowers. Get it. Am I even hurting anybody?
Right down the road. Fuck. Oh, here we go. There we do it. Let's do it again. They're blocking now.
Smart. Thank you for playing this. I've been waiting. I've been waiting for a true announcement
for No More Heroes 3 to get in here. What's this one? Oh, this is the crazy one. This is
like the Super Saiyan one. Give me more people to hit. Come on. I think that's it. Yeah. I was
very disappointed at the one that was announced with a switch. It was that weird top down one.
I'm not going to say it's a bad game because I didn't even played it, but it might be worth
playing. I heard it's bad. I heard I didn't hear it was bad. I just heard it was not great.
I heard it was very passable. Very passable in huge underline under the word very.
Not perfect equals bad. No, no. I just didn't hear it. I didn't hear fantastic things about
it, which doesn't matter. I'll probably play it. I'm going to do two. This is the start. No
More Heroes 1 and No More Heroes 2 at least will be on this channel very soon. I love these fucking
games. Oh yeah. Right. I can, I can actually do a dodge roll. Oh, he's got a gun. I can block
the bullets though, right? Yeah. Another one. That slot machine comes in handy so many times.
Playing No More Heroes 2 so we can see you fail the cooking mini-game. You better believe it. I
think you want a lot of combos too in this game. If I remember. Oh, I just fucking, that guy just
shit. Yeah. Okay. You, you can. That's right. That's right. That's right. All right.
Anymore? When are you going to play No More Heroes 1? Uh, now? Today? You're going to fight the secret
boss? Um, I don't even really remember what that is. Does it work? Can I like answer the phone?
Will it come through the Wii mode? It's not coming through the Wii mode. Shit. I have to turn on
subtitles. Oh no. Uh, okay. Sounds good. Pretty cool. Is it in the options? I don't, actually,
I don't think I can do that right now. This is a prank call. Go into the Wii menu. Broken Wii mode.
Wait. No, no. I, I, I, this is being emulated. Press home. No, no, no. It's not. This is not real.
This is emulation. All right. Let me turn on the subtitles. Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
guys, guys, relax, guys, guys, relax, guys, relax. It's not a burnt coffee. That wasn't a piece of
paper. But hold on. Now that I got this here, let me see if I can just get it. I'm curious.
I don't know if I want to fuck with it. Let me see. No, I don't want to fuck with it. I got it
working. I don't want to fuck with it. You have to wink. Well, we'll just turn on the, here we go.
Here. See? There. Problem solved. Speaker is on. It, it don't matter. Look, there's subtitles now.
I, I, I will read the subtitles. There's no, nobody has 75,000 points. Turn the speaker off.
Oh, what am I doing? I can just turn it off. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, look what
I got for Christmas. All right, let's go. Awful hair. I'm getting a haircut like tomorrow anyways.
Don't relax. There's the save point. You guys have seen me with my Wii U. I, I, what are you talking
about? We already went over this yesterday. I've, I've shared photos of me with my Wii U. I wasn't
here yesterday. Fuck. I'm sorry. All right, let's get some help. Uh, what does this thing do? Oh,
it's a new move. Right. That's the, you unlock moves. I forgot. Travis, do you remember those
golden days in Calgary? The path of pro wrestling that you have long forgotten. If even a fragment
of the spirit of a wrestler remains in your blood, remember the first suplex that your master taught
you. Yes, that's right. The darkness piercing. Front neck chancery drop. You remembered an old
wrestling move. Look, it's easy to miss. Trading card number five. Save game. Travis the suplex.
Yeah, don't worry. There's no, you don't see anything. Those of you that want to tell me TOS,
Death Stranding did this and everything's fine. Look, there's literally like
six minute long shower scenes with Sam Porter Bridges. I think I'll be all right. Did you say
poop? Uh, you did. All right, we're good. Are you guys ready? Are you ready? Are you ready to see
like the real game? Let's go. Remember, this is on hard. No, it's not. I know. I'm just saying
that's what people think. I'm cool. Beautiful, you say? Paid for with the lives of many.
When you have the strength to take life for yourself. Pretty good red blend. I am free of
desire. So long as I had the scenery to look upon. Imagine having a pool 10 feet away from a beach.
You're the one leaving in a body bag. I'll only say this once more. Leave here now.
Melee. You obviously don't know me. You don't get it. Do you? Hey, you know what paradise is,
right? Paradise. This is paradise. The place where dreams are fulfilled. You don't know me.
Well, you've had your dream old man. Time to wake up. This is no paradise. All right, then what is it?
It's a place to die. Whoa, covered in tattoos. I'm glad you and I are on the same page here.
What kind of lightsaber do you have? That's this game. That was all it was cool. You have no idea,
do you? What a pity. You make an old, arrogant, crude little shits like you come around from time
to time. Listen well, young one. The wall is high, higher than you will ever know. Ultimate sacrifice
now draw. Yeah, you can take that to your grave. No, I got, I got, I got Luke's
lightsaber. You can't fight me with that shit. Here we go.
This count. I feel as if I'm looking at my future self. Make a box, big ass box.
Trusting nutrition is counting every calorie. A team of hot yoga instructors, nurses,
and
that shit out of here.
That'll be my life. I thirst for selflessness.
I'm killed by young rookies like me. This is how it goes down. And for the old
I realize there's really nothing here.
Yes, there's this sense of doing running down.
He's still fucking talking. I need to get rid of it before I bail. Instinct. Ow.
Fuck, he's gonna kill me. He's gonna kill me. He's got me to combo. All right, slow down.
My battery, my battery, my battery's dead. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Back it up, back it up, back it up.
I got it. It's all up high for that one. Get it again, super flex.
Oh god, which one's the real one? One in the middle? It's one in the middle.
Pass it. That's the right one. No, it's this one here. God damn it.
He doesn't know. Well, I actually don't know. I don't remember.
If I take like two or three more hits, I'm gonna die.
First boss. Why am I reading chat right now? Leave me alone. All right, I need battery.
Wait till he swings.
I need help. Well, I gotta get help. I think there's one in here.
Wasn't very much, but it's enough.
Yeah. Fuck, I just dodged. Easy. Just don't die. I'll be fine.
How many hits is that? Dodge around it. I didn't even need to do that. What the fuck am I doing?
Cut. See you later. Completed the tutorial. Great job. That's the easiest thing in the whole game.
The moment I've been waiting for, the name Holy Sword is now yours. You're joking, right?
I don't care about titles or power. I just want to be number one. Then master the ways of the
assassin. Was this before Bayonetta? I think this is the first like real violent game that came out
on the Wii, right? There it is. Rank B. That's all right. I'll take BBB. Total money. Cool.
Open the chest, please. Wii Sports was really violent. Um, no, that's maximum vitality
increase. Nice. No, you're right. Wii Sports was very violent. You know how many people
accidentally hit their friends in the face with the Wii mode? That's the first time motion controls
took off at all. You know how many TVs were fucking shattered? You know how many accidental elbows
and like to your little brother's face they were? This is probably the most violent console to ever
exist or ever will exist. How many ER trips from 2006 to like 2010 existed because of the Wii?
That data is somewhere. Is that all the uh, yeah. Nice kill, Travis. I didn't think you had it in you.
It was rather exciting. Congratulations. There she is. You are now ranked 10th. 10th, huh? What? Do I
get anything? How about some cash? That should help you pay the bills. I'm not feeling the sense of
accomplishment that I should have. So I just got to do this a few more times, right?
If you so choose, yes. Ten more times, Travis. And you will keep your promise?
There is nothing the association cannot do. And if I refuse? As the 10th ranked assassin,
you are now a target for those who want to replace you anytime, anywhere. Number 11 could be right
around the corner, ready to put a knife in your eye. So what you're telling me is that I got to
continue fighting. There's no way out of this. You set me up, bitch. Quit your bitching and get with
the program. There's only one road out of here. No turning back. Okay, how about this? If I become
number one, will you do it with me? Maybe. Maybe not. Come on, just once. I did it.
Ranking list, marvelous. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, death metal.
Travis touchdown takes over death metal. It was just Galaga this whole time.
I believe this is where the world opens up. And yes, it is an open world game.
Rank 10. Explore the house. Yeah, there's a lot of stuff here. It's time for chores.
Time for chores. The open part, open world part, sucks. Yes, it does. Anytime. Gotcha. He swallowed
the gargle. Didn't wipe. It didn't and swallowed the gargle. All right, let's do, let's go to the
closet. What do I got? You can change clothes in there too. All right, go sunglasses. I only have
the defaults. I think you can buy better ones. T-shirts. Just go shirtless. I don't, I don't want
Kingdom Hearts box art, whatever this is. Default, default. That looks good. Let's go to the drawer.
What's in here? I think you can look at your cards. Yeah, this is the beam katanas. This is
where you keep your lightsabers. You have blood berry. Wanted at a net auction. A beam katana
wanted an auction. Okay. What about map? Let's see. Santa destroy guide. Yeah, you can take a look at
stuff here. Is the burger suplex. Burger suplex. A burger joint with a distinctive sign. There's
the house. Here's a suplex pizza. Atomic drop ward. Santa destroy high school. Bodyslam beach.
Yeah, it's open world. You don't skip. I've skipped what? All right, let's go play. Let's play with a
cat. Here we go. Yeah, you can play with the cat in this game. Get it. I'm gonna get that thing.
I'm gonna get it. All right, we got cards. What are the cards we got? Let's try a card. Mask of
the Legendary Wrestler El Extremo. Yeah, they're just wrestlers. I did get all the cards in that
level. That's cool. Look at this room. All right, what about the fridge? What's in the fridge?
It's a mini fridge. Was it beer and pizza? All right, what about TV? No More Heroes. The first
trailer of No More Heroes. Should we watch it? I think we already saw this. Did we see this?
He's got a bad nerd neck. This is the trailer for the, this is the Helter Skelter. Yeah,
Skelter Helter or whatever his name is. Yeah, you don't see this fight.
Helter Skelter. It is Helter Skelter. Is this spoilers? Is it? No, this is the trailer for,
this is like the official licensed Nintendo trailer for the game. Actual spoilers.
Hear the lullaby? Rest in peace, baby. Are there spoilers? All right, no, we won't,
we won't watch it then. Not spoilers. It's all right. You already saw it. It's not. Why?
I don't know. Fucking one guy. All right, let's go. Let's play the worst part of the entire video
game. But it being pulled through PC might actually be better because this is the segment that is the
reason why I didn't play it on the Wii. This right here is the reason why. What you're about to see.
It ain't bad right now. It ain't bad. All right, back up. You watched a shitty Coke ad for this.
For what? Well, I guess that just answered you. Yeah, like for what?
The next fight has been arranged. You don't have a lot of time. So I'll just tell you what you need
to know. The ninth ranked assassin is currently Dr. Peace. A doctor? Actually, a detective. A
dirty and unscrupulous detective with plenty of dark secrets about him. Illegal investigations,
illicit sales, black marketing. He is your one stop shop for marketing illegal goods.
And on top of that, he is a trained assassin. He's been doing some work for the mafia.
And before you know it, he's up there ranked ninth on the list. To be frank, he's good.
You won't stand a chance against him. You're as good as dead. What's it going to be cowboy?
Put me in coach. All right, please transfer 150,000 LB dollars. What? 150,000 LBs?
Your entry fee, my overhead costs. Don't tell me that you were not expecting so many zeros on
that price or that I am ripping you off or some shit. We have an elite staff in the thousands.
150,000 dollars. Okay, I gotcha. But you really think I got that kind of dough on me? What the
hell am I supposed to do? You are supposed to do your job. You've been hired to kill someone. So
just do it and quit your whining. Plus on the job, turning in would be good for you.
If you're interested, I can introduce you to an agent. Coconut time. But really,
they're racers. I'll tell you where it is later. I'm running late for my facial. Catch up later,
Kay. What? No. That's the scream. There it is. What a distinctive voice. You can take on assassin
missions from Kay Entertainment, earn enough money to enter the next ranking battle.
Yeah, so there's, here's your open world. Not much of an open world. It's kind of just a map
to go do things. But yeah, we'll just do this. Make some money. Go do the facial. I can't.
Members only, we only need high ranking assassins. If you don't have an introduction
ticket, please leave now. We only offer work to those who have proven themselves as hard workers.
May you find your true path. I'm not good enough. Now, apparently not skilled.
The job center is now open. You can take on part-time job missions from the job center.
Earn enough money to enter the next battle. Press the one button to call your bike.
Sit next to your bike and press the A button to get on. Yep, yep, yep. Press two to change the
mini maps display. Let's get the bike here. All right. Yeah, you have to actually go do
just part-time. Who the fuck is this? All right. Give me a sec. I have to let Otto,
let Otto out of the room. Hold on. He wants to get out. You can't be in here. Well,
then he wanted to get out. He was like, let me out, Cheruby. And I was like, okay.
So he can leave. He's, he's free to roam where he pleases. All right, let's go get on a bike.
Here's the real test. It didn't run so much better. Let's go check out the jobs. I mean,
it's still pretty janky, but those of you that played the original actual original hardware,
this was horrible. This is way better. Yeah, like by probably by 10,000%.
Let's go to the job center. Get off. The sharp turns are fun though. Yeah, they can be.
How much money do I have right now? There's no blood in the Japanese version.
Really? Why are you here, third raider? This is a place where third raiders get together.
So you're a member. Well, I'll teach you some good stuff. All first raiders in the world were
once third raiders. So third class is the first step up the ladder. First class. Your life will
change if you work here. I'll tell you one more thing. How to third raiders become first raiders.
It's easy. They worked their butts off till they were puking blood and then work some more.
Want to be a first raider? All right, just work hard. You chalk up jobs to survive in this town.
I'll hook you up with some more work if you do this job well. The job has been posted on the
golden board. Just work hard. Here it is. Coconut collector. Collect coconuts perform a rolling
sobat against a palm tree to make coconuts fall. Here we go. $2,000 for each delivery.
Yeah, this part of the game sucks, but I'm going to enjoy it because it's nostalgia. Take it over.
Okay, the client head to the client point marked on the map. Let's go. I think, yeah, if I smacked
the weed, if I, I think I can go faster if I double tap and then like, that's jump.
Just like in GTA. Here we are. We're here. You can drift too. Yeah. Wow, Jeremy, this is such an
interesting Minecraft house. Thanks, mom. The unspoken rules of Santa Destroy are okay,
but the coconuts of Santa Destroy are more my thing. Coconuts from these parts fetch a high
price. This town is built on coconuts. Coconuts are worth more than human life. Coconuts are
God, so gather them now. Gather coconuts and give them to the storekeeper. Use combo attacks on the
palm trees to make the coconuts fall. Press the A button repeatedly when carrying coconuts to walk
faster. Here we go. Get the coconut. How many can you hold? One or two? Three? Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. That's the way. Any more in this tree? No, no, no, I gotta go.
This is a strand game. It's easy. Why would that? That's not, that makes no sense. All right,
I gotta get three at a time. Get in front of it, please. Oh my God. What the fuck is going on?
Why can I hit that one? What? No, don't pick this one up. I want the, whatever. That's the way.
I want to get like two or three of them to drop. Let's do this. No, there we go. Grab them.
It's easy. I get 2000 bucks for each one of these. At least I'm good at running. I'm still
got a full minute. More than 15 or 10 is good. Okay. Nothing on that one. Nothing on that one.
Nothing on that one. Come on. Come on. Coconut brain. I should be able to do two more deliveries.
The other side, the closer trees. Right. I see. You're right. You're right. You're right. You're
right. I can get one more coconut. Okay. I got 11. That's like a shitload of money. $22,000.
That's a gold rank. That's not like a silver rank. It's got a gold rank. I can get platinum rank.
I'll try. I'm gonna do that one again. Hey, you third rater. I've got another job for you.
Something a little shadier, perhaps, but work all the same. I've sent an introduction ticket
to my associate. The road becoming a first rater is long and hard. Get your ass in gear.
Hey, you third grader. You want to be a... That doesn't make any sense. Hey, you third grader.
Want to be a first grader? Oh, nice. Okay. An assassination mission. A brand new free
fight mission can now be selected. Ah. Time to kick some ass. Free fights suck.
It's better than carrying coconuts. There's a list of jobs in my current rank. Here we go.
Assassination gig one. Pizza butt. Chain restaurant pizza butt plans to open up in Santa
Destroy to crush their plans. Kill pizza butts CEO. Or a snake haul. Kill until you die. Mission
ends when your life runs out. Two thousand thirty thousand dollars. Do this one. I could do this
one clean. Kill someone. Thirty thousand dollars. Collect eleven coconuts. Twenty two thousand
dollars. Yeah. All right. Speed it up. I didn't even hit that guy. These corners. You can't just
turn on it down. Let me just try and hold. Yeah. Z is boost. Yes, it is. Yes, it is. It is boost.
You got it. Uh, where is it? Right here? On the other side? I don't think I can jump over this.
Can I? Shit. I gotta go down there. Oh, right. That's how you do it. That's how you do it. You
go really fast and you can instantly stop. I forget how I just did that. Oh, shit. Okay.
I wish I had some sourdough pizza. That sounds like bad. Is that actually good?
Sourdough pizza? Wouldn't it be too chewy and weird? All right, let's go.
This is my favorite part of the whole game. That part.
Three, two, one.
Just fucking burger boy. No, no, no. Don't burger boy. Get them all. Oh, let's do it sideways.
God damn it. I would have hit like five people. Shit. Guns at me. I have 10 seconds. I gotta go.
Get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I didn't forget about the time. I forgot about the time. All right. Let's do it again. Let's
do it again. Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Oh, shit. I forgot. I forgot. You have to go get
you. You have to... I forgot. I forgot. That's the worst part of all this game. You have to go get
it again. Okay. You gotta go back and get it again. Fuck. I forgot about this part. That part. This
part sucked. As far as the worst. You actually have to go get the mission again. Jesus Christ.
Damn it. I forgot about that. Yeah. You can't, you can't mess around. If I had only swung left to
right, if I was able to swing left to right, that would have been perfect. I'll get it this time.
I think I hit that lady, I guess. Kick the dumpsters? Oh, yeah. That's right. You can't
kick the dumpsters. What side is this on? This side. Oh, shit. I almost had it. All right. You
gotta, I gotta be real quick with this. You only have 30 seconds. Welcome, Travis. Uh-huh. Pizza
butt. Let's go. I bet you can't do this in 30 seconds. I will do this in 30 seconds. I promise.
Don't forget to use the charge attacks. Uh, do I have those on? Do you have to unlock those?
Let's do it. Straight down here. Down, down, down, down, down, down, down. Pizza butt. All right.
This is the one. Better ingredients, better pizza. Pizza butt. 30 seconds. Don't fuck around. Go
right in. Go right in and kill everybody. Hurry and quick. Get in. Go. That's what I wanted. Right
there. This is the one. Left to right, left to right, left to right. Ah. German suplex right in
his neck. Dead. Just kill the dude? Yeah, but if you, if you kill, you get bonuses if you kill more
people. I got a bronze for that because I didn't kill everybody. If you got time, kill everybody.
You have enough money for the entrance fee for the next ranking battle. Make the payment at an ATM.
I got $158,000. Buy shirts and stuff. Yeah, but one of the things that happens to you in this game,
in this whole series, is you'll have enough money to do the next entrance to the assassination
that you'll buy like five t-shirts and have to collect coconuts for two hours.
I don't even hate you. Do it anyways. $2,000 on that one. $2,000 on that one. Why would you throw
$2,000 away? Basketball? What is that? Found a lovikov ball. What the hell? What is that?
I don't remember that. My bike. Dumpster diving. Yeah. It's a Japanese game, right? So that's,
that's like 20 bucks. Is this? All right, let's make the deposit.
Is he actually using a Wii controller? Yes, I am. $150,000 deposit. Why am I using a Wii
controller? Because I have to. This game has like a gyro feature that has the up and down and left
and right swinging and you just hit the mic. Just throw a wad into the ATM. All right, I'm good.
Can you please turn up your mic volume? Uh, it should be up. Is that better? Can you hear
me now? Can you hear me now? Can you hear me now? Your mic is fine. That's just, I just got hurt.
All right, where do I have to go? I was looking to chat. Get back to the house, right? And answer
the phone. My home is inside of get out of the way. Yeah, it's like my, my, my house is the hotel.
I forgot. I know the mic isn't muted. Yeah. Bring, bring that shit back to like 2013 Twitch.
Oh wait, what's this? Preparing. Oh, it's not open yet, right? It's not open yet. Why did I just go
in the fuck? Look at chat. You're muted. Wow. Oh yeah. You want me to prove I'm not muted?
You guys could be like, Oh, just don't say anything. Just don't react to anything that he says.
Really? You think you can keep that up? Hmm. I wonder if you can keep that up.
The Witcher three is not a good game. See, I told you. I told you just say something.
We're actually, that's wrong. You're wrong. Yeah. You're not a very good at a,
you're not a very good stealth artist. I never even played the Witcher three.
I know it's supposed to be legendary, but let me tell you something.
I played the Witcher one and it didn't get it. And I was like, Oh, this is kind of cool. I guess.
And gave up on, I think it was the Witcher two after two hours of playing it because every time
you opened a door in the Witcher two, you had to sit at a loading screen for two to three straight
minutes every single time. So I was like, I want to play this game. I think eventually they fixed
all that, but I never played them. Really. I played a little bit of them. I got it. Maybe
I got to go back and give it a chance because I've heard they are fantastic. Save the cat.
The cat is fine. Wait, there's other, what are the controls? Oh, any button just, we're just like
vibing right now. Right. Witcher one didn't age well. And that was, that was, that was back when
it was almost like a rhythm game, right? Wasn't the combat, you had to click, try to click, click,
click, click. It was weird. It was, it was different. You had to like time your clicks, almost
like it was a rhythm game. I remember, I remember not hating that though. I thought it was interesting.
All right. Let me get healed. Three's not like that. Yeah, I know. Maybe one day I'll give it all
a chance and play it all. Cause I, you know, I don't want to look, I don't want to be one of
those bandwagon assholes that plays cyberpunk and goes, wow, what an incredible studio. Oh,
I'm such a fan. Been such a fan for so long. What a great studio. I love this studio.
And like I played 10 minutes of the Witcher and I was like, I just can't, I don't like this.
What's the studio? What's this timing stuff? Whoa. Cyberpunk. Wow. Who made this? Oh,
all right. I need to go. No, I'm not putting a shirt on and nothing else I can do. It didn't
unlock anything. I'm going to save it though. Is this, it's freaking me out. Is it weird that I
have to go to the bathroom every time I see him do this? Like I, it makes me need to pee.
That's weird. Do I have any message or anything on the telephone? All right, let's go. Bye Gene.
Is this game on steam? That is not. Unfortunately, I don't know why. Ranking battle nine is now open.
Uh, so this is grasshopper, grasshopper and Ubisoft, right? Ubisoft, I believe,
has the rights to this game. This is an Ubisoft published game with no more heroes three coming
out. You think that they would, I'm surprised there's not a no, no more heroes and no more
heroes to remaster coming out before, right? I feel like they would have to do that because they
did a port for PS3. It was one game. It was this one. They ported it to PS3. They didn't do the
second one. The second one's still only on Wii. It's just kind of all over the place. Like it
would be nice to have it in one spot that was remastered. I think they were actually talking
about remastering them or porting them or something, but it was like an off-handed random comment in
an interview that I think that Suda did a lot like, like a year ago, right? Like yeah, we would love
to do that, but it is not like real. Like we're going to do that. I think it would be in their
best interest though, because some people would buy it. Two is better than one. Two is definitely
cleaner than one. They fixed all the kind of annoying bullshit that is in this game,
but I still think this game's really good. I still like this one. All right, here we go.
Listen. Yeah, they're all good. Yeah. Dr. Peace. There it is. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I knew that was going to happen. I knew it was going to happen. Kill him.
You knew it was going to happen at least once. All right. These guys are all baseball players.
I remember when I wasn't walking low, he would break. Two had better bosses, but the story was
bland. Looks like the story in three might be pretty cool. If that trailer was any indicator,
it's going to be fucking crazy. Although the story, does the story really matter that much
in a game like this? You know what I'm saying? It's just fun and just has, it's just an interesting
concept. It does. Well, to an extent, I would say, yeah, but you're an assassin. You're climbing
the assassin ladder. That's all the info that I need to have fun. He's backtracking. Wait, what?
Because I don't think the story matters for me in this game. How's that backtracking? I still
stand by that. Backtracking. Oh, backtracking Barry at it again. I don't think the story matters in
this game. Looks over at chat. Fucking, what are you talking about? You idiot. Stupid. Whoa,
is he serious? No way. Oh, I'm going to unfollow. Well, you know, the thing is,
if you think the story is cool, then that's fine. But I don't, I mean, I think the story is cool.
I just don't, I mean, for me personally, in my personal opinion, unfollowed and reported.
Wait, did I get everything? I mean, just the story in general, I'm not going to be backtracking
Barry anymore. All right. I love this game's atmosphere and this game's setting and this game's
whole thing that's going on. I don't, like, I'm not going to, I'm not going to be backtracking
Barry anymore. I'm just telling you that I love Travis. I keep backpedaling. I misspoke. I really
did. Let me just, let me correct my gap. This game is fucking awesome. And the setting, fuck I'm,
this is like my favorite game made for the Wii. Like one of my favorite games,
one of my favorite franchises. What am I supposed to say? Get out of here.
Now fuck, can I turn up the music? No, I can't. If I turn the music down and I turn it back up,
I'll be backtracking on that too. Oh, this is, I remember this part. You got to hit the ball,
controls, hold up the Wiimote to prepare the beam katana, swing the Wiimote like a bat,
hit the ball and send it flying. The strength of your swing will affect the speed of the ball.
Hit the balls to defeat enemies. Three balls will be thrown. I thought I was going to get it first
try. I'm scared to do it hard because I don't want to hit you. I'm going to pee my pants.
I don't know what it is about peeing, but I'll do it at the same point. Backpedaling. No,
all right. You know that I like a game when like I won't go to the bathroom.
I'm like a fucking three-year-old. That's a lot of money. Yes, I am. Get him.
Show off the charge attack. I don't think, I don't, I'm not sure I have it. I'll try.
Does it have to be a full battery? Yeah, I'm not sure I have it. Oh, I do. Oh, it took a lot of
battery. Oh, fuck. That's actually pretty cool. Losing a lot of battery. Nice. It does, this is a
lot of battery though. Do some wrestling finishers. I only have one wrestling finisher at the moment.
Yes. Or I think maybe two. Did I get all the goodies? I believe I did. Turn on the webcam
for one of those. I'll do it eventually. Get him both. Yes. There he is. Come on, knock him out.
Low, low, low, high, high, high, high, high, high, high. Boom, bang, boom.
Boom. Just kill him. Somebody said I should play Lollipop Chainsaw, but here's the problem
though. I love No More Heroes. Am I going to judge Lollipop Chainsaw unfairly because of how
much I love these games? I probably will. All right, let's get it out. Let's get in one go.
Yeah, I know how to do it. I'm standing back for this. Holy shit. I almost just peed. I almost did.
Oh my God. I almost just peed. I swear to God. Yeah, I'll be right back. That came out. That ball
was thrown so fast. I got to check. Okay. Damn. All right. He really did pee his pants. No,
that's not why that took a little while. It's because there was a lot in there.
Oh, I didn't pee my pants. I would tell you guys that. Do you think I would hold that information
from you? Of all the strange things you've heard me say, you think me telling you I didn't pee my
you know, you think I'm going to lie about that? Please don't tell us that.
All right. Oh yeah. Probably shouldn't. Yeah, I probably shouldn't.
Backtracking. Oh, all right. This is going to be tricky. Oh, I thought I timed it.
Oh, damn it. Just tracking. What does that even mean?
Pee pants, Peter. Relax. Whoa, camera. Oh, I got him. Where am I? What? Oh, shit. I had a chance.
Proof of peeing your pants. You can't prove somebody peed their pants by
muting my mic and left the room. Show your pants. But how do you know I didn't change my pants?
You know, I could have paused to come back with new pants on. I said exactly. Yeah, but
then why would I need to turn on my webcam and show you my pants? Oh, there's nothing in here.
I gotta charge this.
I got one. All right. Stop using all my battery. Get up. What is this? What are you doing?
All right. You, you. When I look over here sometimes, I see a sea of clickable purple
links. I get nervous. It's you peeing your pants. No, it's me. I know that. I don't even know. I
don't have to click it. I know what it is. Let me explain to everybody that keeps putting that
image in for the last like two or three months. There's such things guys as like mustard and oil
and eating at a restaurant and putting your finger on your pants after you eat like a pulled pork
sandwich. Why would I pee my pants? And what? Who cares? No, stop talking about food. This,
I'm not, this is not going to be an hour and 25 minutes screen. Every time you talk about food,
it all gets fucked up. No, stop saying no. I got diarrhea last night from the pizza. So I'm not,
I don't want, that's not going to work. The worst part about this is I don't know if it was the
pizza or putting the Wiimote in my mouth. True story. Get out of here. Two lightsaber duels.
Shit, that hurts. Get him boy. Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill,
kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill. That's it. I got everything right.
Psycho. I'm like, cause I was going kill, kill, kill, kill. All right. Let's see if this works.
Does it, can you guys hear it? Let's find out. Yeah. The moment you step onto the field,
the fight begins. If you win, you will be ranked ninth. If you lose, well, there's no need to go
into that. If you pop a breath, hit the restroom, brush your teeth. When you are ready, step inside.
Your chances of survival are slim, but trust your force and head for the garden of madness.
Okay. How come I never say anything back? Actual Star Wars game.
Okay. New move. Coming up. Travis, you've made some progress. I caught the podcast that said
you're getting your edge back. Do you remember your second suplex? Terrifying trip to the moon,
the reverse arm salt. You remember no professional wrestling move. Uh, am I going to get full health?
I think you do. This is an Xbox game. This is a Wii game. Only for the Wii. Well, no, that's not
true. It is an Xbox game, but that one, it only came out in Japan to the next box. I've been,
by the way, why? So there's a PS3 remake or remaster of this game and it came out on
Xbox 360 as well, but only in Japan for 360. Weird. All right. Number nine. Here we go.
The ballpark.
Nice set of pipes you got there old man and nice golden guns.
Courtesy of me and my entry fee. No doubt. My ex-wife called me the other day and I
met my daughter for the first time in 10 years. We dined at a fancy restaurant.
One of those that are impossible to get a reservation for. And then afterwards,
karaoke. Who got you the reservation? The association took care of it. Of course.
Yes. Fuck my entry fee. $150,000 is not the fact the reservations are hard to get.
In fact, no one gets reservations. The words reservations only apply only to those outside
of the circle. It's getting into that circle matters. And the food good.
Unfortunately, the atmosphere was a facade. Not once did my own daughter look me in the eye.
This guy's food tasted like blood. You're a junkie for blood, old man.
Nipples. You just did this there. It's just a bear.
People like us, we're shocked. You smell blood too, didn't you?
You got it, old man. And for some reason, I feel this sense of euphoria.
Don't die on me too quickly. I want to gorge myself.
This guy shoots. You gotta watch out for the projectiles.
Man, this is what I live for. Fighting your own kind. Nothing's more gratifying.
See you on the other side.
All right, do I have to?
Not that easy, Travis. All right, here we go. Can I do that? I think I have to block.
Good music coming up. Oh, oh, oh, oh. Block low, block high. Oh. Block low, block high.
Block low. Oh, fuck. Watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it.
He's not gonna kill me. All right, back up, back up. Wait till he shoots. All right,
when he goes down to his knees, it's low. Can't block these. All right, I got it.
More. How many more? Oh, fuck. He's gonna change up. He's gonna go to the next phase
here in a second. Oh, fuck. I got it. I got it. Get it. Oh, shit. He does more than that.
All right, I'm fine. I can't knock him down. Jesus Christ.
Get him. Back it up. I need health. I'm fine. Oh, my fucking God, I have no battery. I have
to wait till he does a big one. Oh, shit. Kill, kill, kill. Oh, don't get hit. I'm trying to get
another Breastland move on him. Back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up. Don't
be an idiot. What's he doing? What's the next phase? I know there's one more thing he does, I think.
We're good. He's dead. If I ever found out Jerm was secretly serial kill, I wouldn't have trouble
believing it. What are you talking about? Wow, this guy's a chump. That probably would have
killed me if I didn't walk high. I need to stop being an idiot. He's dead. One more. Oh, fuck.
Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot. Holy shit. He's a fucking idiot. What? Yeah, he's dead.
Don't kid yourself. Playtime is over. Oh, I think you have to. Uh oh. Do I actually have to do this?
Oh, no. Do I? I, I thought, did I? All right, let's get him. Let's get him. Let's get him. Let's get
him. Let's get him. Let's get him. I thought I had to just press A, but did I though? Because
he, I thought I had to wait for him. I thought, but that'd be, don't worry, I'll make it quick.
Just fucking spam him. Oh, fuck. You actually don't have to dodge it. Bloodborne boss health. Yeah,
it's, it, I can't believe I lost. I can't believe I lost. I thought I had to wait for like him to
pull an eye pull. Spin wheel with a gun. Look, he's already at 30%. We're good. Die to gun wheel.
No, this is not gun wheel. Can I dive? I wonder if I can go through that. Battery. Can I dive
through that? Maybe. I'm too afraid to try it. You lost a doctor piss.
Come on, knock him down. Shit. Jesus. Need to recover quick. I feel like you guys can hear that
and you can feel it. Can you hear the wind I'm generating with that? I feel it in my bones.
How would I do that? You can't even hurt him when he's like that. All right, close. It's close. It's
close. I'm not going to fuck it up this time. Give me it. Give it to me. I'm going to go. All
right, hold on. I can't. I thought I could charge up and do it. All right, we're good. Let's press
A next time. Get it. Get it. Get him. Battery, battery, battery, battery, battery, battery, battery.
Good. It's not so bad. Okay. Oh my God. Don't die. That was a gnome. All right, there we go.
Just press A. Press A. I have to just press A.
Okay, it's A. Got it. I thought I had to go. I can't believe I fucked that up.
That's the easiest QTE. I forgot it was a QTE. I thought it was just the guy. I thought I had
to wait for him to start to draw or I would fail the mission. I don't know. Travis, that's rude.
Like the only reason why I get C rank is because I had to restart. 150k. Max health has increased.
What is this? What is this spoiler? I don't understand. I want to go see that movie by the
way. Isn't that movie like apparently one of the worst movies ever made? Didn't they remake CGI on
it because they desperately were like, holy shit, this has like six on Rotten Tomatoes.
It was a patch. Day one movie patch. Marvelous. Dr. Peace. Am I going to do Katana's upgrades?
Yeah, I think I unlock that now actually. I think I get that now. I think this is when the
store is open. Scott Pilgrim ripoff porn game. No, no, I'm sorry. Hi, this is Diane from Beefhead
Videos. This is a message from Mr. Travis Touchdown. Just calling to remind you that you haven't
returned one of our rentals. Big German jugs collection number 23. Be sure to return it soon.
Have a nice day. Do you guys, I don't know if you guys remember Blockbuster video,
but do you remember there was a back room at Blockbuster?
And it was the porn room.
Very much for your cooperation. In addition, we have faxed you some information about the rankings
in case you wish to continue your ascent. As a friendly reminder, there will be a small nominal
fee to participate in ranked fights. It was like another, and there was another, you went into the
main store and then there was the pornography section that was behind another door. I'm not
making this up. Is this the same, is this the right video store? Blockbuster porn room.
Which, wait, what video store had the porn room? Okay, hold on. Yeah, yeah, no, this is real.
Right by the anime section, they had this little curtain that went into the adult section. The
place would be pretty open pretty late at night. And as I got into my late teens, it wouldn't be
uncommon for my friends and I to be there past midnight on weekends playing fighting games.
It was then that I learned that the place stayed alive because of its porn clientele.
During the late night hours, a barrage of men would walk behind that curtain and walk out
with stacks of porn to rent. It was nuts. Literally the busiest time you'd see at the
rental counter. So, no, this is real. I guess it wasn't Blockbuster, but it was other just like
rental stores. That's not a lie. There was a secret porn room at a bunch of rental places.
All right, $200,000 deposit signed. Travis Touchdown. Not at Blockbuster. Yeah, but,
is it a lie if I'm saying it in the same two sentences? Wait, no, maybe it wasn't. Let me
check. No, a lie would be like, no, it is Blockbuster. It's Blockbuster. And then
six days go by and I go, no, and my Blockbuster had it. That would be me lying to you. This is
me trying to get my facts straight in the same two sentences. I'm just gonna play the damn cat.
Hey, girl. That's a little cat. Save it. Do I have any more videos? I don't think I do.
I'm gonna unlock some new jobs, I think. How much money do I have? Like 150, 160?
Yeah, we're good. Now, let me see if I can actually buy some shit. Naomi's Lab is now open.
Thunder Ryu building is now open. Area 51 is now open. A new part-time job is now available.
All right. Very, very cool. Let's go. I need $200,000. Let's go to the katanas first. This
game is fucking awesome. Yeah. Oh, it is. It's fantastic. To pay no attention to that.
All right. It's back there. Yeah, it's ready. Lift up the remote to jump. Yeah, I've jumped a few
times. Play a single finger on anything. What do we got? Oh, it's you again. Something to drink.
Weapons. The Tsubaki. $98,000. Beam katana created by Naomi. The prototype model. What about parts?
Accelerator. Beam katana accelerator. A sensor that can locate buried treasure when
attached to the beam katana. Pretty cool. Let's get the new weapon. Yes. And let's get the weapon
part too. I want to find buried treasure. Now I have no money. I wonder what color is this one?
That one looks pretty cool. I know there's at least a handful. I gave him my motorcycle.
Let's go check out the new jobs. Hit the dumpsters. Yeah. Did he just get on it and park it
in the same spot that I just left it? $2,000. You can get shirts and a shirt in that dumpster.
Actually, let me take a little look. I'll go shirt hunting. $2,000. Yeah, I need to go train.
Actually, you can increase your attack power and shit. Yeah, that's important.
Find seven of those balls. I got plenty of time for that. Get out of the way. Thunder Ryu building.
I can learn moves here, I believe. Other stuff. There's stuff to learn. Is this your first ever
Jerma stream? Can everybody please welcome Jonathan L1037 to the channel, please? Welcome.
Oh yeah, that. You want to do that. Get over here. I'll teach you a little something. Take off your
clothes. Off, off. Need your clothes off to do that. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Want to start? Get naked. Now
stick your butt out. Out. Can't kill them unless you have strong stance. No, not your arms or hips.
Haven't you ever taken a dump in a Japanese style toilet? Strong stance. Excellent. Just like that.
Now you're under pants. That's okay. Keep your clothes on. All right. Dumbbell. This is strength.
Uh, let's see what it is. Training that will extend your beam katanas combo attacks. Yes,
that's pretty damn good. You can do them all. Increase your strength. We'll just do this one
first. I think I have to tap. I'm going to be damn good at this one. You know it. Is it A?
It's hard to do it on the Wiimote. It's actually hard to do that on the Wiimote because it's not
an easy button to press. That's not an easy button for me to do the vibrate on.
You guys know what I mean by that. Let's do this one. Squats. Come on. This is bad form.
This gets way harder if I remember. Vitality increased. And now let's do this one. How do
I do this? I think it's alternate. Come on. Is it two pounds?
Your beam katanas combo has been extended. Nice. Oh, that already leaving already. That's
that's it. Come again. This dude didn't even re-rack. Oh, fuck. Didn't wipe down equipment.
That was okay. Re-racking. If people just throw 30 pound weights around and just leave them in
random places. I would rather have to find the dumbbells than have to sit in a seat that some
big motherfucker sits in. It's sweating profusely. They get up and the chair is wet.
Soaking wet. I'm not going to sit on that. And then I have to go and go get the spray bottle and I
have to clean up this person's gross body liquid. Or I just walk by and I go I'm not using I'm not
doing that one today. All right here we go. Come on in brother. Don't judge a book by its cover okay.
This is just my personal style. A man should stick to his guns you know. Make a good selection now
bro. Be sure before you purchase okay. If you don't make up your mind soon I'll have to stop
letting you in here bro. I'm going nuts here. I'm hard on myself and my customers but that's
just my the right way to do things you know. Okay new jacket. I want black. Yeah oh shit I don't
have any money. Heat. Radioactive. All right I'm gonna put on the banana shirt. New jeans.
These are expensive. All right these ones. Belts. Who gives a shit about a belt? Nobody sees it.
I know I don't get I don't get the belt thing. You can go to Walmart and get a belt for
12 dollars. Nobody who cares about your belt. Guys I could probably unwrap a fruit by the foot
and put it in as a belt and you probably it would take me to have to tell you that
that's what's there for you to notice it. I need different sunglasses. I don't have
enough money for this. I want the blue ones. All right let's go. See you in another life brother.
What the fuck was that? That guy had the game like hung up for a second and that was weird.
Hey remember all the money I just spent? Uh yeah now we have to do coconut missions for like an
hour. If you think I'm making this up go read any review on this game. You'll see all the reviewers
gave this game. This game got like sevens like high six low sevens when it was reviewed when it
first came up because everybody complained about having to do coconut missions for an hour.
That's because it is. No this is no that's a high seven. This is a high seven game.
I can't I can't hear that this is this low a mid-six game. I can't I can't hear that.
Let's do a job. This is uh this this this is a seven this is like a seven six on a on a sunny
day. This is like seven nine on a rainy day. Third class man I have not mastered the secret
of the first class yet. What is he talking? It's not too bad. The first rated god will give a
hard-working man a little smile. Today's job has been listed on the bulletin board. Lawn mowing.
Looking for lawn mowers cut as much grass as you can inside the required area
within the limit. Three hundred dollars for each acre. Let's go.
Do you can still do assassin missions? Oh yeah that's right there's there's one available.
We'll do this one first. Locate the client. Yep yep yep. Um what are the pink blips on the map?
I don't remember what those are. All right do you think I can jump a house?
I'm trying to jump. Why wouldn't you jump? All right we won't have enough battery.
All right don't kill the client. The blips are oh the treasure all right nice. No I won't
get out of here. There are dreams in the unspoken rules of santa destroy. A verdant law awaits you
in your future. Amazed like manor house with a huge pool and a brilliant green lawn.
Just as the god of hard work handwork waits at the end of a long day's work.
The god of lawns shall smile upon all who mow them. Cut cut cut and mow.
Handwork. Yeah this one sucks. Cut back the wildly overgrown grass.
A and B. Twist the oh I have to twist the Wiimote. Z button turns. Wait what?
What do you mean turns? I feel like playing farmer's dynasty again. This is a generous acre.
Oh shit I have to get it at least. I have to do it the whole thing.
This grass is so bad. This is it really is. I know this didn't even exist back then. Did it?
This is the default unity grass. I don't even think that it does this.
No yeah unity wasn't the thing back here. Yeah unity didn't exist.
Maybe it did but it wasn't out to the public. Could you make a game in unity in like 2005?
It came out in 2005. Maybe. I don't know. This is gonna drop me nuts if I don't get this whole
thing eventually. I'm gonna have to do this a few times so I can get all of it at one you know what
I mean. Oh look at me. Look at me. Shit I'm not gonna get it all. I have to get at least 100.
No I'll get 80. 86. Damn it. How much is that worth? Coconuts are like 20 to 25 000. This is 20.
This is is this longer than coconuts? I think this might be actually easier than coconuts.
A third raider. I've got another job for you. Something a little shadier.
Sent an introduction ticket. The road to becoming a first raider is long and hard. Get your ass in
here. There's better jobs. Yeah that's new assassin is available. Cool. Well put it put us right in
front of it. Let's do it. It's an easier job but it doesn't bop. Yeah I feel you. Okay we got the
bronze on pizza butt. Snake hall 2000. 3,000. 4500 per kill. Baseball battle. Going to batting
killing spree. Oh let's do this one. 4500 per kill. I think I just didn't play baseball.
Jeremy you'd look a lot cuter if you were 20 years younger.
I'm sorry that age exists. Maybe one day it won't. I want to dig. Maybe one day you can live to be
like 200 and not like get saggy cheeks like I do. You'd be 14. Oh shit. Hey whoa. What the fuck?
Fan that guy. He just did the math in his head. Where's this treasure? It's right here.
Am I not on top of it? Where is it? Got it. Well this this is where that person says,
oh well Jerma I thought you were 55 years old. He's like oh well that's yeah I see you making
like a joke. You making you making fun of me. Okay it was a joke. Yeah it's a it's a you look old
joke. I'm aware of those. All right I know. The car hit boxes are huge. Yeah they're enormous.
All right let me go do this one. He's getting tired of them. No I have some really really
important news for you guys. When you turn 30 you don't care about that anymore. Like I don't.
I know. I know. Like I don't like it doesn't bother me. After you turn 30 years old it's just like
it don't matter. I'm gonna still it's I'm getting older now. That's it. And people go wow you look
old. I mean that's because I'm getting older. It's okay. When I was 29 I was like no I can't turn
30. I'm gonna be old. And then the second you turn 30 it's like oh okay everything's fine.
All right. No. You're really handsome. Don't let anyone tell you otherwise.
That's a shitload of money. It's 36,000 dollars for that. I'm just doing that one again. How does it
feel to have both feet in the grave? Oh well let's see. 30 34. Let's figure what's the average age of
a U.S. male? What is it? Is it 80? 75 is it? Well what's the 77? 75? Okay. So now what is the
average age of a U.S. male? Oh the shitload of medical problems. You know like I've got like
I've got like a hernia. I've got fucking colitis. I have costochondritis. Like what how low is that?
60 65 30. All right yeah so I'm so what am I halfway dead? Oh shit.
You I don't have oh fuck I do. I've got two feet in the grave. I'm going to the beach to get this
one. I have to get down there. Do I fear death? I'll just come back as a butterfly and fly around
for a little bit. Yeah you could just that'd be fine. And then and then when somebody likes
when I get squashed into somebody's windshield I'll I'll wake up again and I'll be like a fucking
ant. See that's the thing about still like oh what about like do you believe in like reincarnation?
I mean that's a very interesting concept but how what determines there are like 600 trillion ants.
Ants. You respawning as a human is is like 0.000000001 percent.
Like there are 600 million ants for every one person probably.
You're going to be an ant. You're going to you can respawn as an ant over and over and over and
over again for millenniums. And then maybe you'll. Holy shit I'm a baby. Oh my god took 600 fucking
eons. I had to live with an ant like 600 trillion fucking times. Ah don't step on me. Oh fuck.
No I'm okay. The hive's being invaded by killer bees. Oh no I'm a person again.
Can you imagine having to live 500 million lifetimes as like the the worst life ever like that?
All right all right yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna carry this piece of sand
in my mouth. Oh okay I'm gonna walk and place the sand one grain of sand down. Turn around do it
again do another grain of sand. Do this till I'm dead. And then you respawn again. Oh fuck I gotta
get that grain of sand. Oh let me make sure I lay down a chemical trail so my blind friends can see
where I'm going. All right where's my fight? Reincarnation doesn't work like that.
Yeah but I mean if it did what but if it did if it was just luck of the lottery if you
respawned 500 million times an ant the one time you respawn as an as an anteater you're gonna
be like oh my no no no no no I can't do this. I can't do this. I know what it's like to be that
guy. You're gonna respawn as a fish like a goldfish in a bowl and be like oh thank god
that's your cooldown period that's where you get to just chill. It's gonna seem like five minutes
the three years that you're a goldfish in a bowl is gonna feel like five minutes. I want to go to
the where is it how much money do I need? A lot. I want to go the other way. What's some of the new
ones? Let me try one of the other new ones. What if you get a turtle? I mean that's pretty that's
not bad. That's pretty good. That's like a hundred years. Can't some turtles live to be like 150?
That's not bad but it's still it does not even come close to the light years of time you'll be
an ant or a beetle or something. Kill using wrestling moves only. No other moves are allowed
for this mission. I'll try it. Would you want to live as a turtle? But if that's what you got it's
better than living as an ant. Is it though? Yeah you you can like swim around and just like lie on
a rock for six hours. You guys have a some of you guys might even own turtles. They get to just sit
down on a rock it doesn't have the sunbeam down on them for like 14-15 hours a day. That's pretty
that's not bad that's pretty cool actually. Respawning as an ant over and over again is
the equivalent of waking up and nuclear bombs are going off around your house all day until
you're dead. Just every all every second it's just just mayhem. I would I could I would be able to
I could sit on a rock for a little while as a turtle. What if you're born as a pigeon? I could
fly. You can just fly around. Okay some of you guys that want to what do you mean be a pigeon?
You know that a lot of that a decent amount of pigeons like fly around New York City and eat old
french fries on the ground. You that's what's wrong is that bad? What's wrong with that?
In fact that's like kind of like that's kind of how my life is now. You know like just eating
french fries and like junk food and going you know what I mean like that doesn't sound bad.
Only wrestling words. Pigeons are like the goats of the bird world. All right only killed with oh
right I can only because isn't isn't a goat stomach made out of like rocks? Like can a
goat eat like a can't goats eat like anything? Isn't there like a what what no I swear to god
there's like who has like the iron stomach? They ever anyone can eat anything. No I swear to god
there's like something about it's some it's it's goats right? I mean they're not supposed to like
obviously you're not they're not supposed to without you know but there's something about
the way that they process the food or something. It's called a gastrolith. I know I'm not crazy.
Hey bro they can literally eat razor wire. I didn't know that.
That was fucking awesome. Tombstone again. Yeah. What was this 3,000 for kill?
People are shooting guns now. Bro please bro what? Why can I not hit B? All right 13 that's an
unlucky number. I don't like it. Ah shit. That shouldn't be bad. 30 uh 40,000. Chill bro. I'm
fine. That's well that's the first time we get to see the new sword. How much money do I got? What
about if you spawn as a whale? All right I got 114,000. I need more money than that. Damn I need
that shitload more. This is why you don't buy clothes until you have five million dollars.
What are my thoughts on goat cheese? I wonder how polarizing this is going to be. I don't think it
will be very polarizing. I'm not. I don't think it will be. I think it's disgusting. I think it
tastes like dirt. I think it tastes like actual physical soil in the ground. Dirt. I hate it.
Third class man. I have not mastered the secret of the first class yet. It's not too bad.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. Anyone? All right I gotta get gold on this one.
It's way too overpowering for me. I can tell when goat cheese isn't anything. It's like the
princess lying on the mattress with the pee under it. I'll I know it's in there. If you give me even
a tiny little crumble of goat cheese I will take a bite and just I know that there's a pee under my
mattress. PEA guys. You guys don't know that. That's like a classic fairy tale. You think we
don't we think we know? All right I gotta get gold on this one. But do you like cream cheese? Yes
I do. I love cream cheese. You know forget about technique. I'm just gonna try to get as many
acres as possible. Who cares if I don't get it all? Already much better pace than last time. Cream
cheese is dank. Yeah I'm not I actually don't like I mean something I don't like it but I uh I'd rather
there be stuff in the cream cheese like chive onion salmon like salmon on the cream you know I
it's got to be uh dressed up a little I mean I I love it I do like it but if I had a choice
I would eat the one that had something in it. Vegetables. Vegetable medley whatever it's called
the vegetable one where there's little carrot chunks and celery chunks. Don't make this a
fucking three-hour stream guys. What are you doing? Get it all. There's only one more piece.
There's one more nose hair. Trim the last nose hair. Got it. Yeah liver and cream cheese is pretty
good. I can't eat liver. I've tried chicken livers and no I can't do it. It's too it's too
heavy for me. It has too strong of a flavor. I know it's so good for you too. I know eating
chicken liver is new fight mission. Oh cool. Chicken livers are they're they're packed with
so much nutrients. I know I can't do it though. It's just not for me. Would you eat cream cheese
pizza? Uh probably not. Pizza's already heavy. I don't think I'd want to weigh pizza down even more.
My mother used to make chicken livers all the time and I would ever I would try it every time
and I would not like it every time. Jesus Christ. That was horrible. That was that was really bad.
We've already had the cheese debate in this channel. I did the cheese tier list.
I hate to bring politics into this chat but what's your opinion on stuffed crust pizzas?
They're unbelievable. They're unbelievable. But you have to be in the mood for it. Stuffed crust
pizza is disgusting except for the one occasion every maybe few months where you are just sitting
on your couch and your eyes bing whip open and there's a light bulb over your head and you go
I want a stuffed crust pizza right now. Then it's a 10 out of 10. It's apps it's the best fucking
thing on earth when you have the light bulb and every other scenario know it's horrible
but that happens sometimes. Free fight mission kill until you take a single hit from the enemy.
Kill them all within the time limit. Oh this is gonna be hard. Don't take damage. Use stances
with this weapon. Now it's not embarrassing if I die. I mean it would be but not even. Cross.
Yes. Crossing. He's still alive. He's still alive. That guy's still alive.
Greedy. All right I'll take 10. I'll take 10 kills. Now it's gonna get. Oh I did it. There we go.
Cheese is disgusting. Um I mean it's a lot of people can't eat it. If you're lactose intolerant
cheese kind of balls up in people. So it does. I don't find that to be Lego. What'd you say? How
could you say that? If you're lactose intolerant you it kills you. It's I mean I love that stuff
but even it's hard to eat that. It's hard to eat cheese in large quantities. False. It's okay well
it's not hard to eat cheese in large quantities. It's very easy because it tastes really great
and you can sit there and eat it all day. But what I mean is physically after you do that
you might feel quite ill. Barry's back. No can we change that name because it's not backtracking.
Can you call me like Clarification Crisp? That's more accurate. It's backtracking the name. No
that's uh it's just Clarification Crisp. Additional Statement Aaron.
All right I want to get. Do I have gold on both these? I do. Oh shit I do have gold.
No I don't want to do any. I've got gold. I don't want to do them. What's the other one?
Juxtaposition Jill. Correction Kevin. All right I'm gonna do another one.
Let's get this one. I guess I look cool doing it. Addendum Andrew. Addendum Andy. Addendum Addendum Andy.
Why does it all. I wanted to turn the other way. Why does it always turn this way?
Maybe it's the other way I'm holding the Wiimote. Hold down drift. Is drift uh
buy a new sword? All right I have a new one right now. I'm not going to buy another one. No I won't
be able to have it in the next mission. Simpsons hit and run flashbacks. There we go. Oh no this
is not. Oh this is another free fight. All right I'm trying not to get hit again. They have guns.
They have guns. No they don't. It's not guns. I thought it was guns.
Oh he almost hit me. Whoa. Whoa. Okay I'm fine. Whoa. No I'm not. He almost hit me. Whoa. Okay.
In the corner. I gotta get in the corner. Please look. Okay get this guy first.
Oh shit. Oh shit. I want to run run run run turn. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I almost got hit.
Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Watch it. One more guy right here. Come here. Got
it. That's it right? Any more? Yeah. These missions are the hardest thing in the game.
Yeah they are. They are. Give me the gold. This game is inherently satisfying. Yes it is. All right
I got enough money for the entrance for the next fee for the next germa rumble. Two hundred and
twelve thousand dollars. Okay let me go back. Let me go back to the house and save. I have the new
blade on. Yeah I do because I'm using one hand to hold it. The other one was two handed wasn't it?
Travis with the next rumble. I already told you what's gonna happen to smash.
It's fighters past two combatant three. I just stole somebody else's prediction.
What? I'm playing no more heroes today. That's why I'm saying that and then he's a Nintendo
character. Well let me have this. Let me have. You can tell them to talk with my hands.
We don't need any more sword characters. Well that just. Oh no I can't say this. Never mind.
No. Well then. Well then delete like the 12 fire emblem characters that are the same character.
I tried to stop. I tried to stop myself. Pick me up. Pick me up. Come pick me up. Oh what's that?
Hold on. Oh well I mean here's the thing though. If you're a big fan. If you're a big fan of uh
of fire emblem. I look if you like those characters that's really really good.
I'm happy that you care about that series. I'm just saying that very very clearly if there's
already like 10 12 sword characters in the game. I don't we don't need that many more.
I guess is what I'm trying to say. It's a cool series though.
Fire Emblem is awesome. I played it. It's very very good. Play with the cat. You hungry? We get
to watch the cat eat. You thought there was only one or two cat interactions. It's like 10. There
there. Hungry cat. Moments like these is what makes me know that Travis isn't that bad.
Yeah let's go to the draw. Let's see. Yeah that's the original one. I'm using the new one. It's the
Tsubaki. Yeah I got it on. All right let's go to assassin mission number eight. Travis is a
shithead. Travis is a bad dude. Yeah pretty I mean yeah. Fuckhead. PS3 remake sucks. Well that's
I'm I'm I know that strong opinion. I'm not I'm that's I'm not playing the PS3 one. This is the
Wii version. Wii version of the game. I hope you could hear the air quotes. How do I dig into
concrete? Where is that? What version is the Wii version? My control is rumbling.
He means Wii guys. Yes he means this is what he means. Yes yes yes yes there it is.
He's got to prove he owns the game and the console. He's got to prove he owns the game and the console
in his closet. Play rhythm heaven you coward. That's part of the plan. Yeah the next fight has been
set. Wait a sec why the hell you telling me this over the phone? Why? Because I cannot. Oh shit is
she naked? I didn't even look. I was looking at chat. Big shots from across the nation will be there.
This is serious business. So serious that I'm going to spray perfume on every square.
Oh shit that's close. That's close. Yeah whatever. Your next opponent to the school
and then what? Just go. You'll know what I'm talking about I think. What do you mean you think?
You know you really suck at your job. Life is more important than some job. That is why I am
busy shopping right now or busy killing people because that is all you ever do. What am I wrong?
Well I guess not. Omega porn game. It's not a fucking omega porn game. Omega porn game.
Ranking battle eight. No guys an omega porn game is just you going to Pornhub and opening up a tab.
That what are you talking about? That's not a game. Let's play that game.
Relax.
Ranking.
I'm not gonna know what that is. I don't know what that is. I'm not gonna say the rest of that. I
don't know what the fuck that is. I'm not saying any shit.
Just look at him.
Kill. Kill. Kill. Kill him. Fire axe. Any goodies that I missed?
That's my favorite one.
What the how many combos do I was it five hit or six hit combo now?
Date the AI from AI dungeons and get its number.
What are you talking about? I'm on team Travis. Travis.
Can you play the rest of Nancy Drew? Um no.
Not today.
No not today.
What was that? That's a based response. Uh oh.
Based. What was that? Easy. Double. Oh no. Damn it. Damn it. Money.
Money. Someone just said I love money. Let me see what this does.
It just makes lots of smoke. Do you love money? Money. Oh it extinguishes you if you're on fire.
That's what it does. Of course it does. Hey anybody in chat love money?
Idiot. What's that? I need it. Holy shit. What is this one? This one is all bar bar bar. What
does it do though? Oh my god. Okay it's an instant kill. That's unfortunate. You turn into a creepy
pasta. I got it again. Shit. What does he say? Raspberry chocolate brownie. Strawberry on the
fucking shortcake. Oh there's nobody here. Uh doesn't that make you ineffective? Oh it makes
makes me.
Uh where where do I go?
I gotta go. I gotta get out of here. He's doing a German walk. How is this a German walk?
How do I stop this?
Dude get to a bathroom. I've what are you talking about? Yeah I got it.
I can't. There we go. Now I can do a bunch of combos. It's the rocket wheelchair.
I think it'd be a pretty good uh swing sword voice for a video game. You know what I'm saying?
Shoot. Come on. Give me. Please. It's link. No it's not.
That's not link. No it's not. Yeah that one is. Yeah. How am I getting so many lucky rolls here?
Imagine saying that and then getting destroyed. Wait what?
I got that guy like five times. Oh fuck I don't know which way I was going to the hall.
What a pain. You're a joke. What a pain. You're a joke.
Grab. Grab. Grab. Grab him. I left for an hour and a half and he made the same joke from an hour and a
half. Which one? What do you mean? What are you talking about? Which what what did I say?
You're a joke. What? I'm just. No I'm repeating the. What are you talking about? I'm
repeating the word that he says when he says you're a joke.
What? Are you prepared? I'm gonna say that a bunch of fucking times guys. I've. Kim told. I've
probably told this story. Kim walked down the stairs one time and I was for three days straight
was repeating the same Thanos lines from Infinity War. She came down while I was going like this
universe is finite. It's resources finite. The will. I just I did his entire monologue
all the time and eventually she was like can you stop doing the Thanos monologue and I'm just like
what the what are you talking about? I don't even know I'm doing that. It just happens. I just do
that one time. Okay I was taking a shower like three or four weeks ago and I was just talking.
I was just doing like a scene from a movie and I didn't know I didn't think anyone was home.
She just walks in and I and I look at her and like oh hey hey she's like what are you doing?
I'm like I don't know I'm just like talking. That's the last time you showered.
When this stream is over today I'm going to be just hanging out in my room
just going are you prepared huh? Are you prepared huh?
Over and over again until I go to sleep. I don't know it's just fun.
Stop hitting me. Stop hitting me. You're annoying me now. Now you're annoying me.
All right that was a tricky room. His brain can only hold so much data.
My brain can hold a shitload of data. Thank you very much.
Look one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
fourteen uh one in the five from the number um uh-oh a new sith lord.
Wait for the opportunity. Damn it. Did it hit me?
Shit these guys are kicking my ass. No no no these guys shoot me. Holy fuck I cut through that guy
like holy holy heck. Battery battery. Fuck I don't know what he's doing.
There it is on his neck.
Go back to Nancy Drew. This clearly isn't your pace and you think Nancy Drew is my pace? I had
to use a walkthrough to complete the puzzles in that game. I'm confused. I have your statement
I had to be on gameboomers.com the whole stream. I knew it. I called you cheater. We already I
already talked we talked about that already. That wasn't a secret. I was only using it when it was
completely necessary. Like anytime a fucking math problem would come on screen. Your next ranked
fight begins the moment you step into that room. Win and you'll rise to ace in rank.
Hit the can. Pick the tartar of your teeth. When you're ready step inside. Tartar tartar sauce.
Fried fish. Fried fish sandwich. There's only one way to find out. I'll be back tomorrow.
I want to go I'll make a fried fish sandwich. I am uncertain you're returning from this battle
Travis. In a body bag. The garden of madness. Oh come on you don't give me give me a break.
You can't give me a break. Come on really. Come on give me a break. Give me a break. Give me a
break. Your ADHD is an overdrive. Sometimes it does feel like that though. Remember the Bing
commercial? Where it was like fried fish. Fried fish $2.99. Fried fish $2.99. $200. The people
all yelling at each other in grocery store and stuff. Somebody would say something and somebody
would say something after that that was connected to that word. You guys don't remember this
commercial? Yeah search overload. That's that was a not even that long ago. That was like
five years ago. Travis now you're getting back into the groove. Remember the 18th suplex of your
master. The trust building exercise gone wrong. Captured. You remembered an old professional
wrestling move. Search overload. It was 12 years ago. Those commercials were funny.
I'm sorry I didn't mean to upset you with the reuse joke thing.
Um rank eight. Here we go. A rankings fight? Yeah how about it? All right will you give me a minute?
Wait for me in the hallway. Right. Mind if we do this somewhere else? You're the boss.
Stop checking me out like that. You killed them? Such a gentleman. Are you asking out of
tactical curiosity or are you just fucking with me? Bet they didn't offer much resistance.
You got a problem with that? You got no idea how hard it is to hide your true self around here.
Hey I'm not accusing anybody. How? Real gentlemen. I just turned my back but you didn't strike.
You are fucking with me. It's actually pretty hard to take cheap shots when your enemy is as
bloodthirsty as yourself. People like us think alike. Don't. Is there a cabin over here? Shall
we? Does it need to be explained? Go. You will pay with your life. Have my chance. I will now
avenge my father. Something tells me you watch too many samurai movies little girl.
What the hell was that?
Robert Atkinson really does add so much to this character. Seriously. That like. Only he could do
that. Easy. Low. I think she's going low mostly. Yep. Oh that hurts. What's with my stamina? My
beam stamina? Get it. Whoa. It's low. This song's really good. It is pretty good.
Got it. No mercy. No mercy. No mercy. No mercy. Ow. All right. Don't fuck around.
Do we move? What? I didn't catch you in a combo? What? Watch that battery power. Oh fuck. That hurt.
Ooh. Did I get it? All right. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I need to charge.
Oh shit. Not good. What the hell? Fucking battery. Why? Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Don't do it.
Don't do it. Oh fuck. What you doing? Oh no, no, no, no, no. Don't kill me. Please don't kill me.
Is that a kill? Is that an instant kill? Where am I? Oh this health. Oh shit. My fucking pants.
Oh shit. I tried to dodge it. I'm dead. I'm dead. Fuck. I tried. I dodged it. You got.
Shit. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. This health right over here.
Fuck this. Fuck that. You actually just hit me. How dare you?
Bastard. Easy. Slow down. Battery. Still good on health. Shit. Sonic Sword is the best
option if you go in. Oh shit. My pants. I'm good. Battery. Get it out of the way. Oh shit.
Don't blow it like last time. Dead. Why is she invincible? My hair.
Jacob's was my mentor. I'd never kill him. I watched Master Jacob's teachings on video
over and over. Video. We never met in person. I watched him over and over again. I admit it.
I lost. Do it. How about kill yourself after you kill me? Sounds like a bit straight out of a
samurai movie. Don't it? Shut up. Shut up and kill me already. You've already dishonored me enough.
Do it yourself. I watched Master Jerma on stream over and over. What would you learn? I'll fight
you anytime, anywhere. How to wicked easily get headaches. How to sneeze and like get a hernia.
Which one? That's A. Clear time. A. How to slap yourself. How to put together masterful comedy.
I see what you're saying now. Thanks. Appreciate that. HP upgrade. How to backtrack. Not yet. What
else is in here? I can't talk. I think we just leave. Jerma, you must go forward.
Which Dark Souls did I beat on stream again? Multiple. More than one.
Then let her live. Wait, this was that guy? Welcome to the channel.
Kill when you can kill. That's bullshit. All I want to do is fight someone better than me.
She'll grow up. Why not kill her when she's stronger?
Yeah, then I'll kill her. You are sick. So are you. Oh damn. Got him for eight. Shinobu. Not anymore.
Moving up. It's gonna be hard missing her arm. Yeah, but we'll just get a robot one. We've
trained with the other hand. Why is there an ad for the game in the game? Uh, is there an ad?
Beathead videos. Just calling to let you know that one of the videos returned yesterday
wasn't one of ours. It doesn't have a label on it, but it seems to be a recording of a guy
pumping a pillow. The video you should have returned was, um, how to please a woman in bed
101 part two. Please return it to us soon. Thank you. Jesus Christ. Congratulations, Mr. Touchdown.
Your registration for the eighth UAA rank is now complete. In addition, we have faxed you
some information about the rankings in case you wish to continue your ascent. Please transfer
the money into the designated account. Have a nice day. About 300 grand? 500 grand? It's probably
three. 250? I'm gonna say 250. 250. Entry fee for your next rank fight is $250,000.
All right. Just lounge it. Every time we come back, we have to play with the cap. The phone
recording guy is, uh, Ryden's VA from Metal Gear Solid 2. Pretty cool. And for, and rising. Yeah.
Pretty cool. Gold Town is now open. Beefhead is now open. New part-time job is available.
Is there any, uh, is there a new sword available? Let's check. Let's check Beef Town. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Am I going to finish this game tonight? Uh, probably not. No, no way.
We'll do, we'll, we'll, we'll, I would assume we'll get it probably exactly. It's like a 12 hour
game, right? It's like 10 to 13, 10 to 14 hours, something like that. Probably do it over two
screens. Hey, how's biz? By the way, that thing you wanted hasn't come in yet. So what will it be
today? Video volume one. The title is Masked Panther. Tiger's Roar. Did I get it? That's
chilling, Travis. You've got the eye, man. The eye for cool. All right, let's get it. Let's go
watch it too. Don't die out there. Oh, for wrestling moves here. That makes sense. All right. We also
have to go to somewhere over here. I want to check the Katana place. Let's see if there's any new
stuff. Is this going to be a 100% gameplay type deal or are you just going to beat it?
Um, I don't, I wouldn't say a hundred percent, but I'm going to play it until I don't care. I mean,
I want to play. Ooh, there it is. T-shirt enough until I'm done. Cause I do want to play the second
one too. Probably not a hundred percent. A single finger on anything. Don't lay a finger on anything.
I'll kill you. All right. You got anything new? You do not have anything new, any new parts. You
do have new parts. Power up parts for Tsubaki exchanges the crystal parts inside the beam Katana
with pure crystals to greatly increase its output. Energy saving part. So this is for longer battery
life. Adds a, I thought that said motherfucker adds a motherfucker to the beam Katana increases
in it. I'll get this one. This is the power one. Let's go extraordinary power. I don't have enough
for the other one. Adds a fuck head to the Katana. I don't have enough money to get it. We have to
do more jobs. Can we get a little wink? I think I see 1200 points, not 75,000. Yes, you do. I
don't know. I don't want it. No, I don't want it. I don't want it. I don't want it. Wait, what?
You have 125,000. I need money. Wait, how much money do I have? Oh fuck. Okay. I don't know why
I thought that was 12,000, not 125. You did 75,000 points. Don't fuck yourself for raising the bit
amount for highlighted messages. You asshole. Well, you don't want to see a sea of purple
highlighted messages in chat wall stream. Well, you do. Yeah. Essentially before it was this chat
was just purple text. That's what it was. See now it's intended purpose of, and here we go.
Here we go. Open up the slot gates. Let's go. Imagine not having enough channel points.
Well, hold on a minute here. I, I, I decreased, I increased the one for highlighting a chat message,
but I decreased the unlock what the, uh, changing an emote that used to be 1250. That's now 750.
Just save for the wing. I told you that there's a huge play here where if you guys just don't spend
your channel points in like two years, you can all spend them to get me to wink and it'll ruin an
entire stream that will, it'll ruin everything. You will, you're guaranteed to fuck up at least
one full entire live stream like in six months. What do you want? What do you want? Make it in
the hundreds. I'm not going to go home to mommy. Leave me alone. I want to enjoy this moment.
I already got six K. You got six K. Find the seven Lovikov balls scattered across Santa
destroy and bring them to this drunk. How many points for a date? Uh, 500 million channel points,
which would take probably 10 years of me streaming. So I don't think you'll ever get
training. Here we go. Bench press, increasing your strength. Let's go. Tapping, tapping, tapping,
tapping. Just pull your points. No, it has to be from one single account.
I can't just pull all your points. How much to have a chat message go through text to speech?
Well, that would mean that I would have to have text to speech turned on in the stream and there
is, that is never going to happen. Why? Uh, because I don't like it. I don't like it. We've talked
about this already. There's somebody just talking while you're talking at the same time.
Somebody could just be talking over me talking, telling two completely different things at the
same time. You already, you already randomly just picked stuff from chats or read. Anyways,
it's pretty much text to speech already, except it's text to Jeremy. And there's another reason
why I don't like text to speech because not just for the stream, but a majority of these streams
are cut down and put on YouTube. And it's watching a video where there's just a TTS,
just talking on an edited video. It just, it's, it's messy. It's messy. Now he cares about YouTube.
I mean, I care, I care about the channel being like a watchable channel for people that don't
want to watch streams. Yes, of course I do. Yes, I do. The intended purpose of that channel is to
make it so people that don't have time or don't want to catch a stream, they, you know, I've got,
I only got maybe 15, 10, 20 minutes of time and, oh, but I did want to see some highlights from
that. There you go. That's, that's for you. There's VODs on Twitch. Yeah. For 60 days.
And then they get cut down. If you don't got time to sit through a six, seven plus hour stream,
you know, Barry, get the fuck out of here. All right. How did I get bronze on this one? Disgusting.
I actually watched the YouTube highlights, even if I watched the stream.
It's, it's for anybody that wants to, if you wanted to catch up on something, if,
you know, let's say you wanted to watch the last few streams, but by the last, you know, let's say,
oh yeah, I heard about that Simpsons hit and run stream where didn't he like fucking bite his
controller? Oh, wait, it's a 13 hour VOD. I, I don't really want to do that. I got like 10 minutes
today though. Went the wrong way. Shit. Make channel point 100 K for Nancy Drew again.
No, I can't start doing that. Cause that if you, if it's like, oh, for a hundred, I'll play like
league of legends at a hundred thousand channel points. I don't want to, I don't want to do that.
Nancy Drew is fine, but that's, you open up the, you open up the can of worms there.
No wrestling moves. They take too much time. Fuck. Oh, I'm sorry. Do it. Don't kill the CEO.
That's a, that's a gold right there. 100 K points. You have to be jumping DLC bronze.
All right. That's surprising. I thought I did. I had like 20, 15 seconds to spare any jobs.
Speed. Just nuke the boss. Third class. Not bad. The first rated God will give you a smile. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Garbage collection. Cleanup Santa destroy, pick up as much garbage as you can within
the time limit. $1,000 for a bunch of garbage. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Garbage collection. Clean up Santa destroy, pick up as much garbage as you can within the time limit.
$1,000 for each piece of garbage.
Garbage is the easiest one. I do remember this one being okay. Has redeemed 1 million points
for Lord of the Rings stream. Dude. Pog. Lord of the, really? That's a Pog champ right there.
I've never seen that. Naked Lord of the Rings stream. No, that would have to be a million
dollars. And then I, no, I'm not, no, no, no, no, no. I wouldn't stream naked for a million dollars.
What am I saying that for? I wouldn't do that. Unless, what? He put out a price.
Freedom and anarchy. There's nothing much here, really. Just remnants, cast offs,
ruins. The garbage that litters our streets. Mark the remnants of lives. You following me?
Each piece of garbage is a lost soul. So what better way to spend your life saving lost souls?
A true garbage man can bring peace to the dead. It's taken me 12 years to realize this truth.
You've got potential. A soul that can talk with garbage. The God of Garbage would watch
you and go save that garbage. No bikes that pollute the air are allowed in this environmentally
friendly mission. Pick up garbage. Get all the soda cans. Oh, this, I love this song. This is a
good song. Here I come. And easy. Shit. Now pick it up. That's a huge can. It was like 80 ounces.
Easy. Is it a thousand dollars per one? Yeah, this is like probably 50 grand. This is probably the
best pound for pound for money. Save your winks for April 1st. Maybe you'll get it. April 1st
is gonna be a wink stream. Terrible stream that's gonna be. Remind me to on like April 1st or March
30th or something to make sure the thing that I was planning on doing on April 1st or April 2nd
or whatever is something that does not require any fucking brain power. Any. I'm gonna have to
turn my cam on and wink like every five seconds. We want to damage your eyes. And I'm the serial
killer. Me. This guy. I'm the serial killer. It's 40 grand so far. 50 grand. Let's get it. 44. 45.
46. Gotta be an even number. Come on. Even number. Get an even number. Please. Jesus, Jeremy. Fucking
get an even number. I freaked myself out. That's a lot of money. Monka Omega. Monka Omega. Hey,
third raider. I got another job. Something shady. What is it? A brand new free fight mission can
now be selected. Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. Can you sing at my nephew's birthday party? No.
$50,000. Pizza butt returns. Chain restaurant pizza butt plans to open up. To crush their
plans to kill pizza butt CEO. 50 grand. Let's go.
What? What's wrong with that? Sing at my wedding. I'll give you $2,000.
May you find your true path. I think this is what it is. How many points for you to
like nephews? He didn't even respond. What do you want me to say? Oh yeah. When's your
wedding? Oh me there at six o'clock. I don't know what's going on. What song am I singing?
Why didn't you invite me to Christmas? Why didn't you invite me to Christmas?
Why do I have to invite you? Why didn't you invite me? I'm going right to the CEO as fast as I can.
That's pretty damn fast. That was like five seconds. Six seconds.
Just do this one over and over again. It's $50,000 every time. Do I have enough? Almost.
Let me try one of the other free kill ones. Farm pizza butt. Let me try to not get hit.
See if I can go three for three. Don't get hit. We got people to throw stuff.
Double. All right. Kill, kill, kill, kill it, kill it. Almost got hit. All right. Get in the corner.
Who's running? Anybody running over here? Nope. Just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
He's behind me. He's behind me. He's behind me. He's not behind me. One minute, 60 seconds.
If I kill you first. Actually sucked. Oh, this actually sucks. Back up, back up, back up.
Just blocking everything I'm doing. Got it. There is no such thing as bronze on these. You just do
it or you don't. $40,000. Why didn't you set my Christmas tree on fire? That was mean. My mom's
still crying. Why did I or why didn't I? Why didn't you set my Christmas tree on fire? Don't read this.
Well, it's using channel points, so I'm going to see it. All right. I'm going to buy the...
I've done all the other upgrades, right? Yeah, I did. I could buy like a new jacket. No, I want
that. No, I want that yellow jacket. Or that black one. Don't read this. You're going to get a new
inventory. Jackets. The yellow one. Which one? Black, tan, or that's just another kind of red.
Let's go black. What's this t-shirt? I want this one. Wait, there's more t-shirts. Oh, yeah.
What the hell was that? Okay. No, I want this one. I want this one. Jeans. Yeah. New belts.
No, keep this one. Who wants shoes? The anime ones are the expensive ones.
I didn't see the back of the jacket. I don't like it. I thought it was just black.
There's a big skull on it. I need to do another job. Let me do another one of the
don't get hit ones. That's enough money. Sunglasses? Not yet. That's like 30,000.
Let's do this one. Oh, I already did that one. Wait, is this a different one?
Don't these disappear from the map when you do them? What happened to Viscera cleanup detail?
Well, Joel. Were we supposed to do that? I thought we were going to keep talking and nobody explodes.
Don't get hit. No. Almost got hit. Almost got hit. All right. Sideway. Sideway. Side. Side. Side. Side.
Yes. No. What? I thought it was dead. I thought this guy was dead. I thought that guy was just
dead. What happened? What? Oh, come on. And I can't do it anymore. Fuck. I was waiting for a spawn.
I look over there. The guy's like a sliver of health left. And he just hit me just in the chest
or the whatever. It's only one more wave after that too. You can't win them all.
Quitter? It's not even on the mini-map anymore. I failed it. We should be able
to redeem a million channel points to have him delete his channel. No,
a million channel points would be like you get to stream. You get to stream on Jerma's account
for five minutes. Oh fuck. He's going to hit me from behind. Good. Turn. Turn! Turn! Turn! Turn!
Now I'm in trouble.
Wow.
Fuck I knew it. I had the wrestling move fucked it up
It's okay. That's I knew it was gonna happen wrestling move fucked it up and I lost it. It's fine. Let's do a jump
Does your mom know that you hate Joel?
why show
God damn it. I have to do after like mola lawn. Okay, I'm picking up trash and then I'm like, that's it
He didn't jump in time. Oh
Yeah, geez
Dermot spray them with water. It's chat spray chat with water
Wait, hold on. I can do this one. All right, let's go. Come on. Don't get fucking hit
I almost I did like three in a row. I'm gonna get hit three times in a row now
Dermot, if you're reading this copy Cheeto chicken
You got it. You blocked every one of my moves. I went up. I went down. I went down down. I went up
I went down. I went up up up down and he blocked them all
Dude, you fucking suck, bro
Oh
Yeah
Ross, dude. Hey, I think you can't do shit
Let's pick up garbage
Any plans for another emote contest not anytime immediately
Hi pasta and the Tupperware on the bottom shelf on the fridge when you're done streaming. Love you
pasta and the white whatever Tupperware what wait wait this pasta this wait is pasta
Oh
Available now
Really and the scream not yet
No, not yet. That's head. I'm still playing no more heroes
Trash time. I'm like eight feet tall. Why am I so tall right now?
Ledge
shitty route
Actually really really bad route. I gotta get 50
I'm gonna focus here
terrible route
This is not how you get 50
What an awful fucking job. I'm embarrassed
I'm actually embarrassed right now
My face is like slowly starting to turn red
And my speech is starting a little different. You know, I mean like you never see god damn it. Oh
Why did I just hit the edge in operation what the fuck was that don't read whatever he's an electric fence I
Wonder what the speedrunners of this game do
Do you just rush to garbage and then you collect garbage like 50 times is the best possible route and then just blow through the rest
of the game
Which speed run it has to be a speeder. This is this against popular
This is a fairly. I mean, it's not insanely popular, but it's popular enough
It's probably a glitch. Yeah, I've seen roblox roblox games look better than this
That's just it's just
objectively incorrect
Are you you know, are you actually gonna be like talk about no more heroes like that
Go what I get last time 46
I got it. Thank God good account at the buzzer
29 the world record is an hour and 30 minutes or so. That's crazy
All right, let's pay that fee move on to assassin number seven
Yeah, let it die is bad. I streamed let it die
The first six but probably like the first four hours of let it die was fun sort of and then it just kind of
It was not I didn't didn't keep me
Didn't keep me at all. I just walk across the goddamn street. It's right here
They really need to let it die
It was good for 30 levels and then it got really into free to play mobile game territory. Yeah, that's what I heard
What happened? Did you respawn as an ant? Oh wait, that was like three hours ago
But you guys probably weren't here. No, never mind. Yeah, that's what people have over here of like three hours
Why is cat made out of metal? This is a squeaky cat. We need to put some oil around the the hinges there
Doesn't sound very good
Frosty cat
All right, let's watch that video the tape yeah, I know I know I know I know I know that's a huge changer paper
Did you guys call it? What'd you guys call it remote? I?
Called it a change your paper
Anybody else do that clicker?
It was in my house. That was the change your paper. Learn the new pro wrestling move
cabradoro conguero
Cool. Yeah, there's just like what we called it. That's that's in our house
Dear Travis, the next ranker is one dangerous dude, but there's no going home now
You've set foot on the path of a real man. No amount of tears can wash that choice away
Now hurry to the subway get on a train and find him waiting for your life on the line
We called it a change-o lantern. Yeah, whatever and that would be like, oh, that's like a fun like cute way that your family
All agreed that that was what that was called
Let it out. Chairman. Let it out. No
We called it a remote control like everyone not everybody calls it a remote control
clicker
remote
changer
Not a soul says changer
We said change your beeper and that's how it's that's final and that's final
Destroy man your family's weird and they were on stream once they'll never be on stream ever again. Did you watch that stream?
You'll be waiting. That is the Metal Gear Solid combo, isn't it?
Sort of is yeah, it kind of is trading card. I gotta go look at those. I haven't looked at him since the first level
Destroy man is Metal Gear Solid 3 Ocelot's voice actor
Cool tidbit of information. It's not this song. It's got a great theme song
Stopped on
Tackle me get off me. I want to try the new
New move, let's see it. Don't feel so good. I
Don't feel so good. You're about I don't feel so good. Mr. Germa
I
Think is there a move listen, let's check it out. Would you be like on the side of somebody on the right on the left?
Still like fuck go. Oh, yes. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. I
Can't use it
It's not useful
What does it do? I can fire beams at that target and it instantly kills anybody it touches. It's awesome
I'd love for you to see it
For a chest there we are
Ready card 18
Is worth a shot your lips sound dry
They are they always are am I excited for no more heroes 3. Yes. Yes. Yes
One of the reasons why I wanted to play these on stream
was because of
That trailer and that actually it's coming out in 2020. So I'm like
Damn, I want to play no more heroes because I remember how fun those games were. So let's go. Let's play it
2020 release good luck
You got to play no more
Why don't I just go back outside? Oh
Right out here any chests. No. Yeah, this is we're on destroy man right now HP
What how much
That's
That's two. That's twenty three thousand. That's two hundred and thirty dollars worth of bits
dear Lord Freddy dread
Freddy dread two hundred and thirty dollars in bits
Twenty three thousand fucking bits. Thank you. Jesus. They just say love you. Jeremy Jerma. It comes out by a wink
Seriously, that's a lot of money
Can you guys that give this kind of ridiculous amounts of money look over and just like
230 fucking dollars in one go. Thank you
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah, I get to use it. I get to use it
Yes, finally you can see it. Would you sing at that person's wedding? I don't know
That I can't
But that was Freddy dread
Jumping a monumental amount of bits on the stream right now. Thank you so much again
fucking crazy amount of money I
Go upstairs
Do you say my hair looks like shit I want to try that right hold on
It's not quite it
Let's see. Is it a blue list?
ranking side job config data exit
Data now data is safe
There's a move list. It's called Google
Yeah, but if it was in the game, it'd be easy for me to just grab
You know what I mean burn because it random each time it might be
Chest always check the edges
Jesus
Do another move stop tripping
Battleaxe
We get to do this it's this instant kills
Z what am I taunting?
See, ah
again
Yeah, see
Again anybody else be I can't count to the wall
Nice waste
Germa you getting the lip tonight
If by lit you mean eat a bowl of spaghetti and go to sleep and sure
It's kind of lit to me. I think that's what they mean. Yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah, then yeah
All right free lightsaber
He keeps saying fucking me up and I'm gonna lose I haven't saved in a little while hold on
Get out of here
Hey you I'll kick you in the nuts, it's so stupid
And they speak so quickly too. It's like hey you I'll kick you in the nuts
It's almost like it's sped ups
Get up, oh I had to finish that
These guys actually a lot of help
Oh, they've really fixed means
To the mini bosses and glad they got nerfed in the sequel
They're quite tricky. There's somebody alive
Be careful. Oh
Okay, I blocked it but it knocked me down
Jesus that's fast. All right
Get him easy
No, don't get cocky. I don't lose here
Stop you fucker
Hello
That's a stupid trash talk that's
We're about to get a fight you and me
One on one here. Yeah, let's go. Let's go get your hands up. I'm gonna kick you in the nuts
Fuck you, dude
The mind games he never actually does that yeah
Of course, I'm gonna read it
What are you doing? I'm gonna read that
People that think oh deep to the this stream. It doesn't read chat. I've read almost everything almost maybe like 40% of everything
Close enough new move Travis. Remember now the most fundamental among fundamental suplexes made famous in Calgary
It's the all-natural amusement machine the German suplex. I don't know
Don't I already know how to do it. I've done that a few times. That's the dragon suplex
German suplex is just around the waist right and backwards. It's not even full health
Like edit for a cutscene cuz that would suck if I don't
right
destroy my
Thought I wouldn't make it here on time had to take care of some customers that filed complaints my apologies
So much to do with so little help. Yeah, I can't stand these people with all their nonsense complaints
I think they can just say anything. It's crazy. But anyway, I'm here. I made it on time. That's the important thing, right? I
Take it. You're mr. 8
You you're ranked not me
Well, actually it is me. I remember this guy that that's great. Never mind then you've got a job to do
But first I need some time to get ready. Would you mind turning the other way? I need some privacy privacy
Yes, I need to prepare
whatever
Don't mind me pretend. I'm not even here. I just need you to look the other way for a second a second
Yes, just a split second. I don't think it's too much to ask do you?
Then we can get on with our fight
That is correct. All right
bastard dishonor, oh
Sorry, I was aiming for your nuts
Whoa, that was close for a second there. I forgot that you were a killer
Sorry if I scared you I didn't mean to do that. Something's wrong with me today. I
Let my guard down
Getting sloppy. I got changed fast. I
Asked you something. Yeah, what is it? Mr. Cosplay? We're both assassins, right?
Why do we have to kill each other? Anyway, this game is ridiculous. I love it. It's absolutely meaningless
It's about determining who's best. That's what it's about
Can't argue with that
Well, then let's get started
What you want to shake hands? You just tried to kill me from behind
Not killers at least for now
This is a sign of sportsmanship that we respect each other before and after the fight good luck likewise
destroy spark
Is this guy an idiot or what hey look it's chat
You fell for the oldest trick in the book. Oh, man, you are something. Oh, this is the best
You really crack me up
I'm just gonna kill me
Seriously, I think I might really die from laughter. It hurts
He ate the blueberries and look at you you look like you're dead I guess it's time for a wake-up call
This is where it gets good good night
This is just what it's like to play Smash Brothers online
That was quite a move. I'll admit you've got it's like it's not fucking fun challenge had a taste
You'd be quite delicious
Fight for the seventh. Yeah, sure. Bring it on. I love a challenge
You're as good as dead
All right, destroy man. Let's go
Destroy pound
He's got a few he's got like someone to be in when he does that he does like three or four
I have to dodge underneath that or I think I can block it
Okay, I think I can block the the team I block that
All right, destroy spark. You gotta get behind him. Just dodge around him
All right, that's all right
destroy what
You can only hit him. You can only hit him like three or four times
There it is new move
Yes, oh
Shit you have to I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot
Here we go face to me. Does he know he starts flying around or something?
Shit, I don't remember. I don't know
Okay, you gotta get the bug. I got it. I get it. I get it. Yeah
Christ
Don't hit that
Jesus no
Just break it break. I can break it. I can break it. I can break it
Watch it. What the fuck are you doing? I lock on to him. Oh fuck
I need help. I could block that to stay up. I need help block it block it. What is that?
Hide somewhere
Can I run around it that's a very well-made table. Yeah
Fuck you. Oh, I'm dead. He's got a phase three. You gotta be closer
He's gonna hit me in the nuts
I'm not running into that shit
He's gonna do destroy buster right now
Come on. He's almost dead. Do it. He's dead. See you later. Bye destroy man
Bastard, come on. I'm so scared to go over there
Give him the old one too. Oh
That cutscene could have played earlier don't cry like that
You're a killer aren't you? What? I can't hear you
Help me. What is this? I hear from a seventh ranked killer
Whatever. It's over. Anyway
Please
You're the had one in the middle should have had one in the middle
You're the had one in the middle should have had one in the middle AB
$10,000 that's it
If I destroy men
You were cheater
We're not destroy
I'm starting to think that you may be for real that fight was nuts. Yeah, that's fun
Hey when I hit number one, you better be looking the best
No need to pretty up. I want you to see me
I really am
Marvellous
Destroy that speed up the emulator for a joke. No, why would I do that? I don't want to do that. I don't risk
Messing the whole thing up. It's not real hardware. It's I got real hardware in my hands. I got real hardware on the desk
The real hardware doesn't run the game. Well, I don't tell you
Just calling to let you know that the video you reserved is here
Title is how to please a woman in bed 101 part three. Oh
One of the girls here said that you might need a new pillow cover for this one, you know, just for protection
Thank you
Congratulations, mr. Touchdown your registration for the seventh UAA rank is now complete
As always we have facts you some information about the rankings in case you wish to continue your set
Please transfer the money into the designated term and get your nasty shit off the desk where you and Kim eat
We don't we mean Kim don't eat dinner up here on where my computer desk is
Why would we do that?
300 gram
You're hungry. You're in your one-room apartment
Well wouldn't if that wouldn't she just be in here she is
Save it again end of the stream. Not yet
No, man, that's end of the stream voice. No, how is that end of the stream voice?
New job. What is it? Why do I know like another katana? I'm almost ranked six. Where's the new katana?
There's a stupidest way to take a left
And we got to go to the gym we got to get the katana part if it's available
What the new model dumbass otaku? What's it look like? Of course, it's not done yet
Right to the gym no, no, no
Okay back to the gym. So we're this way take a right
Remember drive on the right side of the road. What are you doing? Remember when I was playing Grand Theft Auto and how?
Furious people would get because I only drive on the left side of the road into traffic. I
Remember it's cuz it's easier. You don't have to wait for people to burn you. You can go just weave around
All right bench press again
This hurts
Not gonna make it I have 30 seconds
Pepsi versus coke
coke
It's the same. No, it's a little different
Coke is spicier than Pepsi. Pepsi is smoother
Coke has a little bit more of a bite than Pepsi does Pepsi's tastes almost like it's not flat, but it's like a little spicier
It's got a little more bite than
Pepsi does
Dr. Pepper is the best
You know what actually in recent years, you know, it's really been taken over as the drink of choice for me for a soda
It's just regular ass sprite. I've kind of like it. It's crisp
It's refreshing I actually really like it just a little bit just you know, like those little baby cans
The ones that are like they look like they're like a jokey little display like a cartoon can I like those you just that's it
Just just a little one. Not just enough
All righty. Three hundred thousand. Let's go do the new job and we should unlock more assassin missions, which I haven't done all
McCrory, no, no, no, I don't like I don't like soda water like that
For me if I'm gonna drink soda, I gotta go all the way
Drinking something like LaCroix is like halfway for me. And it's just like if I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna go the whole way
Where's Mountain Dew? No Mountain Dew sucks. No, I don't know. They somehow made it worse over the last ten years
I don't know what they did. It's just it's too sugary. I don't know. It's like 44 grams of sugar or something
It's not too bad the first rate God, that's me. Okay
Gassed in fill up cars with gas $2,000 for each car filled up. Absolutely
You know, what has objectively gotten worse is cool ranch Doritos. Oh
I don't I haven't had cool ranch Doritos in a long time
No, it's not that I had cool ranch Doritos. I don't even really eat regular Doritos anymore. I mean I
Not really
Cheese, it's a nice snack choice if I just want to just crunch on something
Oh, you know what's awesome?
Dill pickle lays potato chips. They are very very very great
They had trust me. They're pretty good Dill
lays potato chips
Rules the unspoken rules standard destroy dictate perseverance perseverance lends to money
Which during leads to wealth the world will forever remain closed to those who do not persevere
The god of gasoline is cruel lose your perseverance and you'll burn up. That is what perseverance means
Get working get working
Kettle chips. Yeah, I like kettle chips do that. They're up there at like a tier
Press the B button to pump gas into the car. Be sure to fill her up just the right amount. I
Don't remember this one
That person didn't even get any gas
The person drove in and just drove out with the same amount
Fuck this one actually sucks. Was that not it?
That's perfect. That was a pixel. Perfect. Well, you can go over you just can't go under. Okay. Well, it's it filled to the right amount
I'm overfilling it. Isn't part of the job that it's supposed to suck
I was gonna say yeah, that was a Mario damage sound
But I made a Mario reference like yesterday. I you got I can't make too many in a row
That was perfect. Let's go. It did sound just like it. What cut look at this car
What was that car that car didn't make any sense that car that car was made out of marshmallows
Goddamn it. It's a birthday cake car
Big cake that really isn't car cake. It's a birthday cake
These are hard to do. Look, it's gonna blow up on me
Was it $3,000 per car? That's actually gonna be a lot of money
20 probably 23
just as many
Cars filled up as there are categories for the New Year's Eve stream. You go ahead and check out the
Voting there is a poll going on right now
23 categories
Get your votes in the best and worst shit that happened on this stream over the last year
A lot of interesting stuff on there. Take that poll poll is open until the 31st at 12 p.m
Pacific and then that evening Pacific we will watch the ball drop and go over all the nominations and see what you guys selected
He's doing an ad. I'm doing an ad from my own stream
So the money just went in a circle
23 of you start from zero. Well 24 if you count the would you recommend Jerma to a friend? Oh a new mission nice
New assassin mission. Hopefully it's worth a hundred thousand dollars
Good job, what we got? So we left up pizza, but returns
Kills many as you can within the time the mission ends when time runs out. So I just to kill as many people as possible
4,000 per kill that's a lot
Kill a hundred enemies mission ends when all targets are dead
No time limit. Just that's a hundred people. That's a lot of people though
I feel like that's not good on a batting killing spree
We've done this before and then kill all the enemies within the time limit dark side mode will be activated mission ends
I'll do this one. This is the power
Let's go
Travis
100 enemy one is the one I used for big money
well, eventually when you get strong enough that you upgrade your attack power and you upgrade your katana to a point where
You can kill people in one hit
So that mission probably becomes pretty easy money
once you have like the third katana and
And plus seven in attack power
Big money. We'll try this
3k per kill is more money than 90k for a hundred
That's true. But you do you do have a time limit on the other one. No wonder
All right dark side here we go
Trying to remember the way the wee buttons like ZC it's
At least we get to see these animations no, don't slap the button
They kill both
For some reason I know B is the trigger on the week
But B for me, I don't know. I feel like it's a it's the face button up here at my thumb
It's been a while since I felt a wee controller. It's been like two years, right?
What's last we stream?
What was the last we stream?
I'm ever played the Wario. Where's
You
What else did I play on we I did the the new Matt the mad dog games right all those laser disc ones
Don't pickle flavored laze tastes like ass and you know it you tasteless boomer
Why can I move?
Did I not play rhythm heaven? I bet you 20 was gold too. Fuck we need a bar. You were I already played it
I did all of it
You didn't I'll do it. Did I swear to God? I didn't I didn't I play it
the one for we
The
Yeah, post for the fans. Am I just thinking of a cool part of that game that I didn't play didn't I play that?
No, we made videos of it. Oh, that's right. It was a green screen entry
Yeah, and then she goes whoa, you know big guy, yeah, I know that song
Did you do mad world I have never played mad world I didn't play mad world because it
I did it hurts my eyes
Mad world to me was like looking at a newspaper. It just that kind of hurts my head. I
Wish they did a remastered mode where they just like call it in all the spaces. Maybe I would want to play it
All right, don't get hit don't get hit don't get hit
Whoa, watch it. It was this guy again. Remember this guy. He wasn't even on the screen
Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it
Jesus holy fuck. I just got it like scared
like actually scared
Now you fucker I knew he's gonna go through
Bros the screen froze for a second and I knew it was gonna stop
I saw it happening from my fucking face and it was the I knew it
Right when I hit him for that last time and it paused to do the swipe. Hey
Oh
Damage that was the end to shit
I'll get this one. Oh, I'm so disappointed by that and I'm I got
Fuck this message, but it's funny. Don't read this. You now have bad luck for the next three days
This is real voodoo. You can only undo this by spinning around three times on camera while screaming
That's stupid. Oh
No, I've been cursed
Don't get it
Did it's real voodoo I have to be careful. All right, I gotta pay attention because I want this 50 grand
Almost baited me there, didn't you?
Don't fucking do this to me get the guy with the lightsaber first back it up
No, I'll do it
I'm not doing that. Fuck. I don't care curse me. I
Can't do that here right now. There's not enough room. You can
big my arms
Take your curse off motherfucker. I have removed the curse. Oh, thank God. Where's my bike?
What I have two chairs in the room. Sometimes Kim comes up here and sits down and we
hang out look at stuff play game or
There's a ball term. It's time for you to eat dinner
It's not time for me to look I'm gonna do this one more mission and then we're gonna finish this tomorrow
And by mission, I mean like assassin number six
Not one more of these money missions. I mean like a full assassin ways another ball
Do you eat dinner at your desk? I don't eat dinner at my desk. All right, let me get one of these
I haven't done one of these in a long time. I did like the first two or three in a row without a problem
Get hit don't get hit
I
Was okay fuck I'm just gonna do a regular mission these are too I get it. Oh my god. Damn it
These ones are fucking hard. Ah
That's worse meltdown. What I'm just expelling demons out of my mouth. How is that a meltdown?
I'm trying to pick up trash. It's reliable these like $15 if to know it just get it out of dumpsters
Yeah, let's just get it out of a dumpster
Yeah, I need to do this like three dumpsters go play Lego Star Wars the complete saga. It's the best game
I played this whole decade
Okay, just two more. What is back here? What's on the mini map there? You gotta play the Lord of the Rings games
Yeah, the the Lord of the Rings ps2 games are on the list
And so is Mickey Mouse the magical quest starring Mickey Mouse
It's a hell of a game. Yeah, it's really good. You have a lot to play. Yeah, there's a lot of games to play
I give him my bike
Feel bad for that guy. I just need one more. I need it two more dumpsters and then get me on to the next battle. I
need a dumpster
anywhere dumpster
Dumpster there's gotta be a dumpster in here play Peggle. I think Peggle at least a few times
Seriously, what was that ball in here? I must I have a I got like four of these in a row
Where's WarioWare? I already streamed WarioWare. I did all of it. You play urban chaos. I think so was on the ps2 list
Do it more well tell Nintendo to make them they made one 12 years ago
And then they made a fake half WarioWare game. Where's the WarioWare switch?
Where is it? I'll be fair to Nintendo though. This probably I mean how many more different types of weird?
Micro games do you think they can come up with?
Maybe they could do some more
but
They could but maybe this don't feel like it but they have had a bunch of new games released
They could do a lot of it's t-shirts. It's kind of not what I wanted
Dumpster give me a dumpster. I need two dumpsters
There's one
Alright, I need
$400
Blind dumb blind dumb blind dumb blind dumb blind dumb
Where do you see this? What did I miss from trying to have a meltdown while I'm going to bed? Oh, don't worry
There's not gonna be a meltdown
Another t-shirts. There's not gonna be a meltdown. Don't worry
I don't do those anymore. I watched like a portion of Jump King VOD and I was like, I'm not doing this anymore
I'm not gonna
Not happen anymore
It happened yesterday
No, it didn't. Where is this thing? It's the pink thing on the map. Where is it? Wait, what?
Hey, I was just standing on there right here
Jesus, where is this thing?
My Wiimote keeps brin brin brin brin brin brin brin brin
Okay, I'm this is
Freaking me out
Let's pay the fee
Missing Nancy Drew right now
Don't worry. She'll be back when there's another technical problem on stream and I just go what the hell am I gonna do today?
Nancy Drew will return
Pay the three hundred thousand dollars. Let's go rank six
Let's go
God hand play God hand. I think I tried to play God hand and I was during one of those PlayStation 2
fuckface streams
Really?
I've played so many old games. I
Probably have played
60 to 70 PlayStation 2 games on this stream and like a hundred PlayStation 1 games or something
The beach
Let's go ahead and
fridge
Go to the toilet
Save it up and go do this mission. What's the objective of the game to be the number one assassin?
I'm currently rank seven
Trying to climb to rank six
Trying to be number one. You know it the cat. What about the cat?
Cats fine about the cards. Well, look at the cards. Don't worry. We will we will we will I promise I promise I promise
To the beach end of the stream voice coming up after this
After this ranked mission, we're gonna probably call it. I'm gonna go eat some dinner
We'll pick back up tomorrow afternoon
And we'll probably finish the game tomorrow, too
Thank you. It's an invisible wall. You can't
Let's go
All these summers me you serious did it when did I put that shirt on?
No, your next opponent is here on this beach
Just up ahead so I'm supposed to fight on the beach is that is one of the conditions why
That's for you to figure out
What other hidden talents do you have Travis go any higher and I will kill you myself
Not until you become number one. We have a deal remember so hurry up and go get him. Yes, your highness
I
Joke
Should be tackle. How's a nice little that's a nice little shimmy go to the end of the beach
Holy shit. That's the Nintendo 64 Goldeneye. That's the standard pp7
shooting song damn
Stop move. I love that part
Dermot you see this look like something with Joel soon
I'm sure we best thing to have right here because I don't have to go anywhere stay on the beach
Come on. Give me somebody
Somebody else come on, it's fun. Yeah, maybe maybe Joel and I will play
Super Mario Brothers free
Where I
Get blindfolded and he puts plugs in his ears, and we both have to try to find a way to play the game
Wait, wouldn't he would just be able to play I?
Love when you get the parry and you get the kill instantly
Good come on don't blow it spawn spawn spawn spawn. Oh, you're not dead. Yeah
He gets the screen, but you get the controller
Where am I that might work in games that are a little less complicated than enough things in the Mario's complicated
No, it's not that might actually work. Oh
That's one the best one the best one the best one. That's the best one. That's my best. That's that best
Please still be in it
Landmines
I
Thought I had it again
Popping in to say hello. Love you guys. Hey, what's up? What's going on my dad?
Guns that but my head hurts after that. Let's give me headache. Nice aim it is
Yeah, that's pretty good
Just just just just
Can look at the cards to yeah, you're right. You're right
This chest over here to hold on. Oh
No, I can't go back
No, they're gone forever
Damn it. You should play metal wolf chaos. All right, I beat that game
That was where the greedy Grinner was originated. Yeah, how many?
Where are these people?
Not soft-locked
All right, that's it
Let me something wrong
Yet, I don't want to do this for anymore
Shake the we both
Right. Is that it? That's it
Damn, that was a lot
Of course every time
Every time I could have used that I could have used that shit. I
Would have loved to have had that five minutes ago. I
Think it's most of the money. Yeah, it's money mostly money the mini-map. Okay the mini-map has them
Don more
Levels it goes on forever. Yeah, this is a long one. Oh
I guess to be fair. It's
It's just the beach. The other levels are in buildings. So I guess maybe it's the same length, but
Car that's what I want
After you after you swing for finishing blow swing again during the slow-mo motion part to cut for more people
I thought that was a foot grenade. Hello
All those things actually apply to me
You've gone from dodging your meteoric rise of stupidity is truly painful to observe
Top seven streamer
Full health save the game
No more mines right now you have to go shit in the ocean to save no, it's probably a poor party writer
There is
It's not really a poor body. Is it?
Travis this is just common sense in Calgary. The king of suplexes. Remember now Satan's ferris wheel the belly to belly
Belly to belly
There are bathrooms at beaches, yeah all over the place no, I mean
Bathrooms that are at the beach
stalls toilets
All right, Holly you and me
Frank-6 go go go
Yep, do you like killing? Yeah live for it
Can't say never felt it do you accept death death never crossed my mind
This is the only truth. You are still a mere but that's not a good thing, you know
Seeking meaning in everything
Especially killing. That's a bad habit among smart little girls these days come closer and you will understand
I'm ready
Anytime just your ordinary assassin
No one else has a light normal assassins don't shoot the shit like this they see their target
And kill them let's see you get out of this predicament dead
What
Let go those
I'm good. Nice trap. I like your style. Maybe I can steal a kiss before I steal your life
Grenades work. Oh
I just blocked it with my back
missiles
Jesus Christ, okay
God damn it shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake
Watch out for the stupid hole. What are you doing? She's all she covers
Shake shake shake shake shake shake shake take her in the hole my fucking god
Kick her the whole kick her the whole kick her in the hole. Oh my god
Yeah
Don't let's fight. I don't like this fight. Oh
My god
I'm not good at this one. I'm not good at this one. I'm not good at this one. I'm not good at this one
Hug wall hug the wall
Into the ocean how do I avoid this shit?
dodge
Get stun lock in the corner
Belly to belly that was really really amazing damage. Oh fuck what's I'm coming. I don't I can't get the help
Stop doing that. That's not fair. I can't get in
Oh
Don't go in a hole shit. I'm gonna fall. Don't follow me. She's almost there. I gotta I gotta I have to use a battery
piece of shit, really
Rock what does that mean? What's he doing? What the fuck is she doing? Hey
Not fair
Greedy, how did I not hit you? Oh my fucking god. I'm so stupid. Oh
This is like a super move. I don't know it does she throws grenades
Where am I my in the hole?
My hands are sweating. Okay, I'm good. You shouldn't be able to do that with every time
Fucking kidding me. She's invincible during that move. She just did it like four times in a row
She's in it four times in a row. She's got like 15 moves. I hate this ball
Hates buff. I'm trying to talk the fucking walls, man
I oh I had she was like two hits until she's fucking dead. What a pain in the ass
How did you get stunned out of that? I should have I mess around anymore. I'll put the wall hug the wall hug the wall
Let's go. I
Ain't messing around. I'm good. I'm getting in there hard all the way in
Run run run. Just don't oh, no pressure. No pressure. No all pressure. We mean no pressure all pressure. I guess do a full health
No, I know the mechanics. I know what you're doing. It's not even a big deal. You've got nothing on me now
Where are they? There's one like right here. There's one like right here. There's one right here. There's one like Stan
It's just standing on I knew it. What no mercy. No mercy
That's fun, this is not mercy
You can't kill a woman did say no mercy. So if you can't kill a woman you are less than a thug
You'll never make it to the top
That's okay. I seem to have a thing for stupid pathetic men like you. I can accept defeat. It comes from your hand
I will let you in on a secret
Assassins must die when they lose
Clumpy mascara look back doesn't look like looks painful
Never forget me, huh? Thank you the moment you hesitated I felt your embrace
Hold up academics like to fantasize too, you know
Wait number six. No
When that kill me too
I'm standing two feet in front of you. Forgive me number six. We're meant to shame you
Not a very smooth victories that Travis but a win is a win is that's all that matters I
Hate to award you these but you are now sixth in rank
What was her name? That's a special grenade. That is not important anymore
You're right
But I owe her at least that
Holly Summers born is no
Just her name
Hey, hey, hey, hey
What's the question marks for what does that do?
What what am I doing? I might like letting her out to rest at sea or something
I don't remember this part. Don't carry this lady's body around
Obtain the US military secret, please give to dr. Naomi
We try cook this wasn't available. I
Couldn't do that before it was grayed out Holly. I was late in saying this but I love your soul
Rest in peace
That was not a respectful way to put somebody to a grave
Could have leaned out in the late
Sand
He just
dropped her
Tossed her into the hole. Oh my goodness. That's bad
six
So started at 11. We are at the pretty much exact halfway point of the game
Perfect timing. I do want to see the other weapon though
I'm gonna see the cards and I want to see the new weapon and I'll play with the cat. Yes
How many videos do I have why would they still allow me to
Mr. Touchdown, we don't have any more porn videos left. You have all of them
UAA rank is complete. We look forward to hearing from you
350 I think it goes up by 50,000 every time
Yeah
350 look the cards cool. I like this one. I like this one. I
Like oh, I like this one. I
like this one
Like a like the praying mantis. I like this. It's like spider-man one
Some of these are really cool. I missed this one somehow. Oh
Well, I missed one
Is there a mask for a killer seven guys? I never played killer seven
Get it get it get it
Good cat. Let me save it here
So we can have a place to start from tomorrow. I don't know if I'm gonna I don't think I'm gonna buy the sword right now
I just want to see it. I'm gonna look at it. Maybe I will buy it. Oh, righty
Let's take it
It'll be too expensive. Anyways, yeah
Job, let's go. See the beam katana upgrade
You gotta go through here in the ass in the ass
and
Turn TV is the worst emote on twitch. I'm actually stuck. I can't drive this
Yeah, I mean, that's I'm not gonna what am I gonna get rid of it? Why would I delete any emotes right now?
When I
It's doing its best
Is it the most use this has ever gotten did somebody just do a giant F and then say fuck you in the middle scroll up
Did you see that?
One two three four counts five accounts made a giant F and it says fuck you in the middle
Somebody grab I want to screenshot that that's insane
It was unintentional
Where the hell did you get this I swear you can get your hands on almost anything these days
Scares me to think a thing like this is out in the world. See what I can do. It's not available yet
Did you get it let's see
Fuck you with a big F. That's insane. That's awesome
All right, that's uh, that's gonna wrap it up for tonight. That's a that's a perfect clean six hours
Plus that gives us time to do probably like six to seven hours tomorrow to finish the game
And then after that is the New Year's Eve stream
Save it again. I just did I just did right before. Oh, well, you want to save because I gave them. Yeah. Yeah
I'll do it again. What time is the New Year's stream gonna start 6 p.m. Pacific is the New Year's Eve stream
starting at 9 Eastern it's to make sure that we can do all the festivities and
Count down the ball drop
Eastern time and then for Pacific time, I'm going to spend it with Kim. I did not spend New Year's Eve with Kim last year
So her and I are going to hang out
stuck again
I'm trying to back up and I won't let me
I'm right in front of a cop too. Whatever. I'm just walking. Yeah, we'll continue no more heroes tomorrow. We will beat it tomorrow and
then after New Year's
Depending on how into this I am how into no more heroes. We might just do the second one right after
Well, maybe we'll do it the week after maybe next but do something else for a few streams. I don't know
But I do want to play the second one. All right, save it here
Rhythm heaven rhythm rhythm heaven. I will I will we but I will play rhythm heaven. I swear
All right. I will see you guys tomorrow. If you stick around we're gonna do the bits and subs and everything
Thanks again for watching
Maybe we'll see you tomorrow that will conclude part one of no more heroes. We addition
quotes
This music's pretty good. But you know, pretty good pretty good. He doesn't he doesn't hate. What am I? He hates the cat
What do you mean? He hates the cat?
That's not true. Let's get the fun. I'll get this music. I played with the cat every time. I
Played with the cat every time. All right, let's go. Let's do it. Let's do bits
bits bits bits bits we had a
Lot of subs came in today
derma sucks gave a shitload
German sucks gave 20 community subs right at the very beginning of the stream too. So thank you for that clown connoisseur gave 500 bits
Hey German, thank you for the content
Thank you the five dolls clown connoisseur. I'm glad you have fun. Glad you like it
Evil program. Thanks in 300 bits. No message. Just three dollars 300 bits. Thank you evil program right after that
We had respected disrespect for 500 bits five dolls. No message on this one. Just
500 bits. Thank you. Thanks a lot guys
Gnarly gave 250 here. I feel like you just streamed this game as an excuse to put Travis in the next rumble and honestly
I'm off for it. He wouldn't be a very hard character to make
Just brown jacket glasses and that hair would be pretty easy character to make when is the next rumble? We talked about the next rumble
Yesterday at the end of the stream and I don't really have any details for it, but the next rumble is gonna be a charity rumble
So I'll give more details on that when I have them fruit charity. Well, it won't be live-action. It'll be in a game
But thank you, darling. Thank you sad vague of the 250 man. Nancy Drew finally got barely interesting. I'm really glad you hung with it
It's at least becoming a wannabe Godhand poser game now
Are you implying that no more heroes is a poser Godham Godhand poser game?
It's not there are no lightsabers in God him
Hey Bacchus, thanks for the 500 bits. I'm so glad you love this game, too. It's my favorite game on the Wii
It's probably one of the best games to come out on the Wii. I don't have the Wiimote in my hand
And I'm still moving my arms around like an idiot
Yeah, it's one of the best games to come out on the platform both one and two
Thank you Bacchus though for sure
Zoogily, thanks for the thousand bits Zoogily ten dollars. Thanks for all the laughs over the years. Jerma heart Jerma auto
Is there yeah, there's an auto now from BT TV, right?
There isn't one enabled you
Thank You Zoogily for the 1,000 bits
Appreciate it
Gooberry juice. Thanks for the 500 bits Gooberry
This is definitely one of my favorite games and I'm so happy you're playing it
But I guess I wasn't prepared for how much the Drew crew would hate it
Because of the shame I now feel I'm going to go home
watch anime take a piss and
Commit to puke coo with a beam sword. Well, thank you for the 500 bits Gooberry juice drew crew approved. We can't have to
Fight in communities. They can't be Drew crew versus everybody else
The Drew crew didn't even hate this. Yes, they were. Yes, they can be there will be
Drew crew versus team Travis
Wow, never thought I'd see the day that the community would be so split now
Thank You Gooberry appreciate it though, it's boo. Thanks for the 400 bits boo
Just want to say I remember you mentioned hash house as your favorite place for a sit-down burger
Went with friends and that place was great. Thanks for the recommendation never went even though I live in Vegas
It's the best burger I've ever had
hash house ago go
At the link. It's it's just one of the best burgers ever
It's so good. It's so I want it right now
Why can't I just have it right now? Yeah, I'm glad you liked it. It's
Awesome. I'm in one of the last time I went to hash house. I
Actually was sitting there. I don't even need the menu
Okay, don't even need the menu. I know what I am gonna order. That's right, sir. The waiter comes over. Okay, I was like
the blue cheese stuffed burger, please
The blue cheeseburger and he looked at me he goes
We don't have any more but we ran out of meat like we don't have any meat that it's all gone
Because they when it's gone, it's gone
They had that their meat is fucking phenomenal and they ran out and they were like we don't have any more
Sorry, like we'll have some probably the next couple days Dave tomorrow the next day. I'm like god damn it
I hear the saliva dancing in your mouth
It's it's awesome
If you ever find yourself in Las Vegas and you go to the strip and you like hamburgers hash house at gogo
Glad you liked it though boo. Thank you
Noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for the 500 bits
German do you celebrate Honda days or Toyota fun?
Is that when the cars are they just try to sell a shitload of cars in a row? I
Don't know what that is. It's just like there's a you can it's better. I don't know what that means
I think that's just like it's just no, I don't celebrate either one of those
Just two hundred dollars off like a thirty thousand dollar car or something, right? I don't know
Hey Snillins, thanks for the 800 bits. No message. Just almost $10 here. Thank you
Thank you Snillins. Let's get these subs rolling
Moving right along here. Here they come. Thanks everybody
All the subs every single one of you every single sub
whether you got it because somebody gave it to you and you just hear and you got it or
you've been subbed for five years or
You don't have a sub. Thanks for fucking being here. But seriously, there's a lot of subs now
a lot of people
Thank you so much for your fucking support
You just run you you run this channel. Well, you don't run it but like you're
You're the blood your blood. You're my blood
You guys are all just moving around in my body of like
Bringing oxygen to my various organs for the channel. So seriously, thank you
My channel now. No, it's not
That's not hey boogers. Thanks for the sub boogers
4 4 4 4 4
Five years old. Thank you. Very nice for the 250. Please. Please do another
Please please do another stream of heroes of might and magic 3
I really enjoyed fanboying with you over how good the game is
Particularly since you seem like you were generally having fun with it. I would probably want to make a custom scenario if I ever did
it again
it'd be nice to do that and actually make a an
Adventure that happens that is played out on stream. That'd be more fun. I think
But yeah, I mean I'm terrible at that game, but I do love it miss Lily T
Thanks for the 255 two dollars and 55 cents. It's good to see you playing games that you enjoy. I
Love no more heroes. I do enjoy it very much. So
Hill Sint
What Hills NT thanks to the 500 bits they say team Travis?
Thanks for the five dolls team Travis. I mean, I know I don't want to tear the community apart here
You're gonna get team Travis you're gonna get drew crew
The different days are different things
Appreciate it though. And finally we have blueberry juice for another 500 bits from blueberry juice. This is my proudest accomplishment
Oh, you were in there. You were part of that. You were part of that. I
Still I can't fucking believe it. I have to show this on stream for people in the bod to really understand what the hell is going
on here
Because I'm sure people are gonna be like, what's he talking about?
Look at this. This is one two, three, four five
I think there was even a sixth person, but this is five different people all in the middle of spam, by the way
so people were just spamming the German TV mode and
We got a one in a million a fuck you spelling out the F. I mean the the one
Then what the person under the fuck you is the only out but that still don't matter. That's just that could be a thick line
And that's it guys. I'll see you tomorrow
Thanks everybody for watching. We had right now actually five more subs just came in from Wesker run
Thank You Wesker run right at the very end bunch of love to you and congratulations those of you that got this up
See you tomorrow. What is this?
Yeah, I've already seen this image. This is the mega jump. Whatever. This is I've seen you guys. I've seen this before
See you tomorrow. Have a good rest of your night
Take care guys