Whoever knows where they're going, or where they'll be, whoever can see the rainfall on a misty Sunday afternoon.
You see, I write poetry. Could you give me a line or two from your favorite poem?
Please, please tell me it's Robert Frost.
Hey, it's me. It's me. I found you guys again.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
What is your guy doing?
I'm kneeling in the back.
Are you guys running?
You guys are doing a running animation.
Oh no.
My dad can be up your dad.
Watch out, there's a guy behind you.
Oh god, the guy is shooting at me.
My mother is an acclaimed author. She wrote a book. Did you have my book?
Help me out here. Watch out, he's shooting you through the window.
Who's in the police station?
Oh, police. That guy's got a gun. That guy's got a gun.
That guy's got a gun.
That guy's got a gun. That guy's got a fucking gun.
Am I messing around with somebody with a gun?
Oh, jeez. Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
When the plague hit, all kinds of shit went down. Even guys with their trucks thought they could go through anything.
Turns out, that's not entirely true.
There were two brothers, but ever since the plague hit, they haven't been seen for months.
It's too bad. I'd really go for a slice right now.
God, I remember this bridge. I used to cross this bridge every day.
That's before the plague hit.
See, traffic on there used to be pretty bad.
Wish I could drive in that traffic now.
That's back before the plague hit.
Lucy's Diner. I had my first kiss here.
That's before the plague hit.
I remember her hair. She had the brightest blonde hair you've ever seen.
God, that memory always makes me laugh.
We used to come here every Saturday.
The memory of her hair?
I don't know. That's before the plague hit.
Oh, there's a guy on the bridge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, easy, easy.
You don't got much ammunition for that gun. Don't waste it on tubes.
Hey, easy there, partner. We ain't in no trouble. We ain't in no trouble.
I got like a bow.
There's a guy behind you too. Watch out. He's coming up on the other side.
Guy coming up behind you. I just like shit. He just like shot a gun
I was like a knee-jerk reaction. Can this guy talk to?
You know before the plague hit I was hey you
Come back to the gas station
All those who would wish to enter the gas station must first answer three questions from the fire troll
You there you must answer my three questions. That's not a question. You dare punch the fire troll
I'm stuck. I'm stuck. Help. You just don't punch it me, please
please I
Someone please needs to just come sit down to this and listen to we need to like run to that trailer park
Get water and come back
Cuz I'm gonna die
Waiting for a survivor. This is dumb. Let's go this way other way other way other way. Fuck other way
I'm done today. I'm done today. Oh, there's a survivor. Hey, hey, you survivor up there
Hey for some survivors out here. Don't go up after him. Don't be aggressive. I'm not gonna be aggressive
Hey, is there I heard there was a survivor just got headshot. What he just died something killed him
Oh, wow, something he is dead. What happened? Oh, we're looking for some survivors
I
Have 1% help do something do something
Wow
Just kidding. Oh, that's you. Dr. Mosquito. Oh, there was some other guy
My shoulder. Sorry, right? You got to pull it out
Pull it on it hurts so much. Oh
I
Can't take it out. I can't
You gotta pull it out man. I won't look it'll be just like the doctors when you what if when you get a needle shot in
Your arm, what if I put another one in the other side? Okay, try that and see if that works
Tell my kids tell my kids. I hope I hope Michael goes to law school
And I hope I hope Cindy becomes a doctor just like me a mosquito doctor
Just like her father a mosquito
By the poles I'm by the Verizon Fios poles Verizon Fios now everybody can have the fastest upload speeds
Really coming through zombie cease and desist
What is
He's just like a riding on the front
Looks like a puppet
That was like Kermit the frog throwing his hands in the air back up over back up over him
Why does he know what these bears don't make any sense?
Whoa, whoa. Whoa. Yeah. Yeah, get him on top of the car. Get him on top of the car
The hair but whoa, whoa, whoa, he's sweaty. Can you hurt us from in there? What? I don't think so
Try God. We gotta get him on top of the car. That's like that's absolutely
Are you bleeding are you okay? It sure does look like fun