Hi, welcome everyone. How are you? Welcome to another day playing video games and streaming it.
A little early today, yeah. Well, technically early. I did say I wanted to start around 1 or 2.
It's like 1.30, 1.40, somewhere in the middle there. You just started going to the bathroom.
Thanks for telling us. Hey, speaking of the bathroom, uh, I didn't even tell pre-stream chat
this because I was waiting. I dropped my phone in the toilet when it was very dark at night.
This was way worse than the April Fool's video. And it sucks because I got a new phone. But it's
fine. There's nothing wrong with it. Let me explain. So, you know when you get up to go
to the bathroom in the middle of the night? Or if you wake up really early and it's still...
How many guys have woken up? I have to go pee in the middle of the night. Sometimes, right?
It doesn't happen all the time, but sometimes it does. Like, you drink like a shitload of water
before you go to bed and you're like, oh wow, I shouldn't have done that. I know I'm gonna have
to go pee later. Anyways, I had to go pee and it's like, it's pitch black. There's no real...
There's a little light in my bedroom. That's it. So, I did what every normal, sane human does.
I grabbed my phone and I used the light on the phone to go to the bathroom because I don't want
a big bright light in my face. Ah, my eyes! So, you might be misconstruing what I'm talking about
here. I'm not talking about the flashlight on the phone. I'm talking about the home screen.
Like, the home screen is bright, is horrible. So, I'm aiming the home... I go into the bathroom
and I'm aiming the home screen into the toilet bowl so I can pee into the toilet. So, I can see
and it's not bright enough where it's gonna hurt me. And like most people, I have my home screen
to just auto turn off after like 10 seconds of being on. So, you get to this weird, like,
goose chase where you've pulled your home screen down to go to the bathroom
and it turns off and it's pitch black again. You're like, oh shit, I gotta fight. Turn it back on.
Well, while I was holding it down with the home screen, I remember I'm mid-piss. I'm peeing
it's mid-piss. It's like a 20 to 30 second full piss. 10 seconds into the full piss.
I drop it right, right, and I'm pissing on the phone. I'm pissing on the phone and it's in piss
water into the toilet, peeing on it. And I can't stop pissing. I can't stop it. You cannot turn it
off. So, I am just pissing all over my new iPhone and I just, I've reached into the toilet and I
pulled it out and I was like, oh shit, no, no, no, no, no, no. But I still have to pee. So, I'm sitting
there holding, I'm peeing into the toilet and I'm holding this pee phone and I don't know what,
I didn't know what to do. So finally, like, I finish peeing and then I scramble to, I put the
phone down on the little, on the sink and I'm like, I was like, I was running around, I was like a
Scooby-Doo chase. I didn't know what to do. I'm like running from room to room. Should I use a
towel? No, that's disgusting. Should I, paper towels? Oh, do I put it on ice? Do I put it on
rice? Oh, so I just started wiping it down. I got paper towels, got it. It was dry, right? Completely
dry. Took it out of the case. Dry, dry, dry, dry, dry. I looked into the inside of the little,
the hole where you plug in the lightning thing. It's an iPhone. And that was dry too. And I was
fine. There's no damage to the phone at all. Zero. And I mean absolutely zero. Yes, I washed. Yes,
I washed it. Of course I did. So, let me just tell you that the, the new iPhones apparently
can be pissed on and dropped in your toilet for at least three to four seconds. I am not
kidding. This act, this is, this is a real fucking story. This happened. There's nothing wrong with
this phone. It is perfectly fine. Yes, I have pissed on my phone for more than a few seconds.
They are waterproof. No, they're not. It works for now. No, it, it works. There's nothing wrong with
it. Guys, I've had water damage on my phones before and you get that weird gray line of the
gray spots that just take over and they just sit there forever. No, this thing is completely fine.
What does it smell like? Guys, I didn't like, I didn't drop it in the toilet and piss on it and
then like take it out and dry it and put it in my pocket. I washed this phone. I scrubbed it. I
wouldn't, I scrubbed it with soap. I kind of did scrub it with soap and water. I like, I like washed
my hands with my phone in my hands. It still works. I didn't, no, that's not completely accurate.
I like did enough water where I could like on top of the phone with a little soap and like alcohol
and I didn't, I'm kidding. But I am not kidding when I say that this one, that this one could plunk
underwater and pissed on for at least three to four seconds. And it does nothing wrong with it.
It's fine. None of that is embellished and none of it's made up at all. That is a 100% true story.
Show the phone, show the toilet. You need to bleach it. I've, I alcohol,
but isopropyl alcohol is not good enough. Isopropyl alcohol, it kills everything.
Show your microwave. Microwave.
Piss on it again. It's still one percent. Yeah, you know, there might be,
it might be 1% piss somewhere in this phone. I don't know. It's probably dried up by now.
Piss in your microwave. All right, we're going to move on. So I had to tell you that story because,
you know, you guys like, oh, I didn't even tweet this stream out. What the?
I'll play in Hades again tonight. I really like it. It's really fun.
And I'm going to see how far I get, see if I can beat it. Tweet out the pee story.
No, I don't tweet. I do tweet. I tweet, but then I hit go to drafts because I don't care.
So I tweet to myself every time I have a tweet that I'm like, you know what? Here we go. I'm
going to make a tweet. Save to drafts. Yeah, that's a good one. I don't care though. I don't want to
have nobody to see that. All right. Let me, let me prove to you. Let me, okay. I'm going to read
you one of my drafts. Uh, and then sometimes the tweets that I come up with, I just say at a stream
the next day, for instance, holy shit. Parents sit your kids in front of Sesame street. Do not
let them touch the fucking bath salt kids channels where they narrate over the Sims pretending to
talk while eating red, green and blue foods every day. That's a draft from like probably four days
ago. Uh, after that, uh, you can probably determine where these tweets came from. Uh, if I hear the
words democratic stronghold one more time, I'm going to eat glass. You could probably dictate
where that's from, what, what time period that's from. LOL. Why is Mortal Kombat 11 turning into
eighties movie smash brothers? That was a good one. You've heard me say that. Oh, here's a good
one. A sneeze coming on with a mouthful of food is the yellow traffic light of eating.
Like that one. Didn't send it out though. Oh, here's one. Serving sizes always make me laugh
about three cookies, 12 chips, et cetera. Why don't they be realistic? Eat out of this bag until your
stomach hurts. There's more. Tweet all these out. Do you tweet? No, those are, those are tweets for
me. Those are my tweets. Those are my, those are tweets for me. That's pretty good. Stand up. Yeah.
My drafts are just me writing down like future jokes that I'm going to make on stream.
It's just a notepad for me. Release the drafts. Like I can't look, I, I, you don't think this
scenario where I'd be like, let me tell you something about eating when you have sneeze
coming on. Let me tell you. It's, every time you have a sneeze coming on and you have a mouthful
of food, you got to make a choice. You either eat, eat, eat, eat, eat quick before you sneeze,
or you hold on tight and you'd wait for it to pass and try not to sneeze the food all over yourself.
It's, it would have been pretty good. Sneeze the food out. What do you do?
No, I'm serious. What do you do? If you have to sneeze after you take a bite of a sandwich,
do you spit the sandwich out? Do you sneeze the food out? Do you swallow quick before it happens?
It's tough. You hold, you hold your nose. You hold on. You sneeze it out. I, I'll tell you,
I usually try to swallow it as fast as I can. Well, it depends. And just like a yellow traffic
light. Where are you? Have you chewed four or five times? Did you just take the bite? What happened?
How far, how close are you to swallowing it? That's virally important for you to know.
I close my eyes. You cover your mouth and just like sneeze the food into your hand.
It sucks. It's a horrible scenario. Sneeze in your mouth and eat the boogers plus the sandwich.
Okay. Why did I, of all the ones that people were saying, why did I read that one?
You guys are disgusting. You guys are disgusting. Where do you get it from?
I just went on like a five minute talk about how I pissed on my phone in the, in the bathroom.
Where do you guys get this from? You're ridiculous. You guys need to settle down.
All right. Let's, uh, we're gonna play Hades. I'm into it. I love it. It's a 92 right now.
We'll see where it ends up at the end of the stream. We'll see. This is a contender for
nastiest stream. There's no category for nastiest stream. It's obviously $50.
Zurich Doug gave 5,000 bits. Gave it a lot of money recently. Thanks for the 50 bucks. 50, 50,
five zero. My favorite streamer playing one of my favorite games. I can't watch the whole stream
live, but I hope you enjoy yourself. I love it. Hades fucking sucks. Um, I, I, uh, I, look,
you need to relax. Okay. Let me get back in this. Let me, how many would I have? Two, three. Should
we ban people for their opinions that I don't like? I don't like doing that though. Oh, audio. Yeah.
No, I don't like doing that. If somebody has opinion that I think I don't like, what do you
want me to say? You're not allowed, you're no longer allowed to hang out here. Get out of here.
No, I'm going to publicly ridicule, ridicule me instead. I just fucked up the word ridicule. All
right. I want, I want money. If you don't know what Hades is, it's a rogue like shooter action
RPG, top down strategy game. All right. I'm good. I remember the deal with the traps. Oh, no, no,
no. I may, I made sure to play over that. I want money. You just, you just tubered yourself.
How does one tuber themself? I forget what I don't know. What am I? Oh yeah. I'm doing the
ice mode. I'm doing ice guy ice guy. Right. Come on. I get that right. I was my quote medical
appointment. Oh, let's talk about that really quickly. Okay. This would be the probably the
last time I talk about medical stuff unless something major comes up, but here you go.
Here's what has been concluded over various doctors, medical professionals, medical personnel.
I have two discs in my spine that are black. They're dark. And that means that they're
degenerating. So I have essentially the onset of some disc degeneration and it's mild enough
for it's manageable. It's not going to, it's not a bad thing. It's actually good to know.
And the muscle tissue around my spine is not having a good time. On top of that,
I also have a hiatal hernia, which may have been causing this kind of chest problems. So I,
the doctors think I'm getting combo'd essentially where I might have, it's the couple of discs in
my back that are kind of slowly degenerating and this little hernia that's in my chest and the
muscle tissue and the fiber are kind of fucked up around the spine. So I might have like three
different like combo attack on me. So what we're going to do is over the next few weeks, I'm going
to be getting trigger point injections, which is they go into the painful points of my back and
spine area and they try to shut it up. So that's step one. If that helps, if that really goes away
and it really has a huge effect on my, you know, my physical ability, then I'll be good. If it
doesn't, and let's say my back pain goes away or it's easier to live with, but my chest problem is
still there, then I'm probably going to elect to do a hiatal hernia surgery repair. I'm just going
to essentially, I'm going to shotgun blast this and try everything that's possible. But there's
your kind of definitive things that people have come up with. There are two or three, the third
disc in that area. It's in, it's right in that spot where it hurts too. So I have two shitty discs,
but they're not shitty enough to cause any, it's like, it's not shitty enough to do surgery on.
It's not like, oh wow, look at how horrible these are. We're going to do spine surgery now.
It's not there. I just kind of have to do pain management to it because you can't fix it. It
really never goes away. I can just get a sort of injections and, you know, the theory was a few
months ago, three or four or five months ago that I would do like an intercostal nerve block just to
like shut the pain receptors off because my pain receptors might be going crazy too. So I don't
know. We're going to go for it. That was his last break dance. Hey, you don't know that yet. You
don't know that yet, but that's sort of where we are now. I appreciate all the, everyone obviously
has been concerned about it. I have been too, but the good thing is almost every single
possible thing that could be very major wrong is not wrong. There are a couple of small things
that I still need to keep my eye on over the years. And one of them is I have a prostate problem too,
but that's not causing this problem. That's sort of just incidentally, it was like, hey,
you kind of have like a prostate problem, dude. So I do. Yeah. Oh, let's keep an eye on that.
Oh, but remember, I have, I have done like, I've probably done like, I've been to the doctor like
30 times over the last like six to seven months, realistically, right? So it's like,
they're going to incidentally find something. That's a new enemy. Not doing enough zirking off.
Okay. Can I even say that? Can I even say what I just said? Am I, is this allowed to talk about
that? It's off. Why is it off? Oh, shit. I can't do it. Oh, these guys, these guys here. Here we go.
Oops. Oops. Oh, it bounces around. Right, right, right, right, right. Hi. I donated $15. I demand
a face cam. What? No, no face cam. Guys, don't you have, have you figured, has anybody figured
this out yet? I only do face cams when I like feel handsome. When I go, I look in the mirror
and I'm like, oh, I got, ooh, look at this guy today. Let's go. Face cam. You know, most of the
time I look at the mirror and it's like, ah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We don't need to see that
today. And plus that's a good excuse because I'm, I'm naked. I don't have a shirt on. I'm bare,
bare chest right now. You should always feel handsome. No, I don't. Look, I have confidence.
I do. Uh, I think I want Hermes. Oh, couple cats. Why are they cats? Show your prostate.
Hey, take a look guys. Like, like an X-ray, like a MRI of my prostate. Why would you want to see
that? Oh, I forgot about my skeleton photo. I have to get a, I have to get a copy of that.
It is. Ooh, attack speed or movement speed? Probably attack speed, right?
I would say one. How much faster is 10%? I mean, it's not making the charge faster though. That's
what I care about, but I can still, it's still cool. That's your special, not attack. Is it?
Huh. Hermes sans reveal. Uh, another $50 comes in from Zurich. That's a hundred bucks on the,
in the 30 minutes, the 20 minutes I've been streaming. Also, I won some money so I can shout
our handsome streamer, Jerma's special meal from Maccas. Maccas. McDonald's? You won some money.
Well, I hope, I hope you got a lot. That's a, oh, that's a restaurant in Australia.
Maccas? Oh, it's not McDonald's? It is. Oh, I don't know. I don't know. All right. You cast,
all right. Any effects are more potent. I cast right now is the, isn't it the lightning beam
thing? The cast fires longer and inflicts chill. Actually that's probably, that's probably much
better. I like this too though. I'm getting a casting. I haven't even done it. McDonald's
officially changed its name to Maccas in Australia. Why? What? Maccas? The cast is unbelievable,
by the way. Who's shooting all this? Oh, it's these dickheads. What? Oh, it's cause the thing,
all right, the thing he's shooting is blue. It's like, wait, what is happening? What is the
little blue shit shooting from the sides? Oh, that's Poseidon doing that. Dick. Hey, JPQ plays.
Thanks for the five community subs. You deal more damage when slamming foes into barriers.
Call polls in foes and effect, holy shit, that's much better. You poll people in? All right,
that's really good. I don't want to sell anything. I want to buy things. Poseidon's literally the
biggest asshole in all of Olympus. I don't know much of the lore. Ooh, all right, I got 294.
That's enough for Dionysius, Travis Scott meal, and can I get them all? Oh, a bunch of you guys
weren't here yesterday. That's like, that's just what we call this. No, no, that's just what we
call this. Okay, those of you guys that weren't here yesterday, that's just what we've been
calling that. That's not like, oh, I'm making like a joke today. No, this is what we call that meal.
Oh shit, it's okay. It's a, this is a boss fight. I need to heal. I need, I have to heal and extra
health or heal and Dionysius. Maybe I'll do the heart. Yeah. All right, let's kick some ass.
I remember this fight being very difficult. Run is literally over. It might be. These guys are hard.
This, these guys are crazy.
Even though I was outnumbered. Take the wrestling belt.
How was your date last night? I went to, I didn't go to, I was out of medical
professional's office. That's not a date. That's the sound it makes? One, two, three, action.
What the fuck did you just say? Whoa, I forgot. He ain't got shit. Well, these guys have a lot of
health. I forgot. It's time for father's call. He's blocking it. Oh shit. I stood still. What
happened? Oh, this is when Aphrodite comes in. Run into something already. Oh, that hurt. Father's
blessing. I thought there was an enemy. Shit. Get in there. No. Way to go. Father's call.
What? Oops. Father's call. Run into something. All right, let's go. Way to go. Oh, that's a lot
longer than I thought it was. Charge. Oh, he's getting close. Okay, we're good. Run into
something, please. We're good. Good thing I had that father's call. It's your uncle. It's your,
well, whatever. I'm just like every character in Marvel versus Capcom. I'm just doing all kinds of
moves and then when I do my special, I just say the thing that it is. That's a Marvel versus
Capcom reference. That ain't nothing to do with those other four games. Oh, go to the fan. Yeah.
Hi. Look, it's a fan. How come I only have one fan if I've done this twice? Don't they know
already? Does the agreement carry over? Yeah, because I haven't paid up yet. 145. Oh, that's
right. I get full healed from all the fountains now. I forgot about that. That's not a fan.
What would you call it? Give me it. What do I get? What do I get? Perhaps deal 500% damage to foes.
Another $50. Five thousand more bits. You guys are crazy. Why are you giving me this much money
today? This is from Ishanji. Another $50 bit drop. They say bounty claimed. New prostate funds.
Thank you. Thanks. Bounty claimed. When are I going to play Demon's Souls?
Uh, when I get a PS5 maybe. Whenever that is. Oh, also I saw the sad news. Real sad news, guys.
Hitman 3 has the complete VR mode, right? Oh, that's so cool. It's only PSVR. And you can only play
it on the PS4 version of the game. What the hell? That's horrible. The PS5 version? You can't play
it on the PS5 version? Why can't you? Please tell me they're going to put that for, you know,
like the Vive and the Index and stuff, right? It's such a wasted opportunity. POV, your Jerma's
phone. There's one thing wrong with this image. It is the fact that this person is wearing,
uh, like cocky shorts. Do not wear, I don't wear cocky shorts. I wasn't even sad about it,
though. I was just panicking. Cocky. Pax, whatever. I'm not from the part of the world that you're
from. We talk differently. No one says it like that. I'm originally from Massachusetts, from
Boston. I'm from Boston. I'm from Boston. Sorry, that was really loud. This is it, man. We're here.
I'm here. Can I do this? Am I going to be able to do this shit? Let's go. Probably not. All right,
we got to save money because I, I want, okay, what do I want? Definitely the health. Let's see
what's in here. What do they do? I don't even know what they do. Holy shit in my pants. That's what
they do. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Good. We're good. Drink bath water. Drink bath
water. What? Just stun lock them. Very cool. All right. Almost got that HP upgrade. Why did I read
that? I don't know. Why did I read anything here? He won't raise it. Oh shit. That's shooting blades
out of me. Out at me. Out at me. Well, this room sucks. Die. Die. Poison. Poison. Poison. Who's left?
Oh my god damn it. I'm fucked. These saw blades, man, are killing me. All right. Good. All right.
I'm all right. I'm okay. Can we see you with your, nope. When is house flipper? Oh, well,
tomorrow is going to be chat's choice. There'll be a handful of things to choose from. Maybe it'll
be on there. I think I'm just going to buy one of these now. All right. Should I? I don't know what
to do. I mean, I feel like my weapon is really good. I'm just going to do the health. Do the health
and then I'm going to buy that one too. So what's available? All right. I could do another one of
these. Money, right? I could do them all, but it's dangerous. Earn him. I'll get a final upgrade to
this. Oh dude. Germa reference. Shit. I can't sell anything. Just because there's a rat in a video
game doesn't mean it's a Germa reference. Yo, Germa. Dude. Rat. Yes, it does. Well, wow. I almost
got hit. Give me those. I want these back. Stupid. Wait. No, no. There are no boons worth giving up.
I have a Germa reference infestation. What does that mean? I have a Germa reference infestation.
This is interesting. This is interesting. This is interesting. This is interesting.
Hold on. Whenever you cast damage foes around you and inflict chill, applying 10 stacks of
chill causes a blast. That's definitely what I want. Arctic blast gum. All right. And let's get
this too. I don't think I'm done. I want the money. Three plus your cast equals hog. That's true.
Maybe I should just go kill him. Should I just go for him? Is there a way to see how many revives
I have left? Where is that? Do I have two? Oh, bottom left. Okay. I have one revive left.
Shit. Do I go fight this asshole? Or do I try to get enough? I mean, I got full health.
Do I go? I'm going to fight him. Let's go. Let's go. I might lose a lot of HP. I have full health
and a revive. I'm going to play smart. All right. Here we go. See if I can beat this
motherfucker right now. Come on. Second try on Hades. Let's do it. Come on. I'm going to go for
it. Let's go. I'm going to go. I'm going to do it. Quiet. Not you be quiet. Me be quiet. Play smart.
Don't play smart. Not hard. Are you winning, son? Yes, dad, I am, if you want to know.
All right. I'm ready. Get it started. Already fucked it up. That hurt. Fuck you, dad.
Stop. Stop. What am I doing? Stop. The fucking goblin's taking over.
Where is he? Come on, father. All right. Let's go. Come on. Come on. Come on. I got a full revive.
I got to throw. I'm not throwing. This is the end. It's all right. Bring me back. Bring me back.
Holy shit. That was insane. I'm dead. That was fucking insane. The whole entire area just
exploded. Every inch of everything was exploded. Second try. I didn't do it. I had to stand on a
pillar. Oh, what the fuck? The pillars blocked the laser. Yeah, but the whole area was poisoned.
All the ground was poisoned. I fucked it up. All the ground was poisonous. Oh, whatever. That's
attempt number two. I'm going to kill this motherfucker on the third try. That was intense.
I have to unlock the other weapon too. Should I unlock the fourth weapon yet?
I need the spear. I kind of have to use the shield wands, right? What's all this other stuff?
I have like two diamonds, three blood, two super potions. What do I do with these?
Fishing. Wait, what? Scoop creatures from the river? That's an entire diamond. Okay, I got it.
So I can fish in the waters? That's kind of crazy. What do you have to say, Nix?
I trust that the mirror in your bed chamber has proved satisfactory, dear child.
That I could have possibly imagined, Nix. You mentioned there was something more that it could
do once I had grown accustomed. I think I'm ready for that now. I think you are as well.
Then it shall be as you wish. Thank you. New talents? Oh shit, I can upgrade more stuff in
the mirror? Hey, the lounge is open. What is this place? What the hell? This is cool. A
commemorative ball of the stoicals within the celebrating and proclaiming the accomplishments
Meg, it is. I pissed on my phone so I can be like you. People happy.
Don't do that. Don't do that. I want to be like you. I peepee on phone.
I like the voices. They're good. Who's this? Slimer? Oh, it's Medusa.
I just wanted to say, don't bother picking up my room today.
I've been out for a while. May the box scrumptious kick. Greetings, chef.
There's a chef too? This is so cool. Can I do anything else in here?
Why does this guy look like a vendor? Oh, he is. Greetings, broker.
Oh, a diamond. This diamond's worth a lot, huh? Okay, I don't think I want to do any of this.
How many keys do I have? I have enough keys to unlock the mirror. Very, very cool.
Very nice. Awesome. What else can I do? Check the bottom. The bottom. 200 gemstones
for what? That's a lot of gems for just somebody's blood. Don't do it. It's not worth it. No, no,
no, no. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't do this. But that's a lot of gems. Actually, I don't even
know what these things are for. So let's do that. Let's figure out what the blood is for first.
Upgraded the mirror, right? Don't listen to the Reddit chat.
Well, they're a Twitch chat. If it was a Reddit chat, I'd be streaming on Reddit, wouldn't I?
Okay, hold on. I got a lot of these. Boiling blood. Deal bonus attack and special damage
for foes with that in them. And this is Razor Supply. I can do more casts. I think I want that.
Check the left. You can switch every trait on the mirror now. Wait, I don't understand.
Press A to activate fiery presence instead of shadow presence. What the fuck? All right,
so deal bonus attack and special damage when striking undamaged foes versus people from behind.
This is restore some of your health when you collect that. 30% of the amount of the
dark power you collect versus... I think this one's better. Restore 50% of your health when you...
Wait a minute. What's this one turn into? Restore 30% instead of dying when your life
total is depleted one time per chamber. So you get to die just once total versus once per chamber.
That doesn't sound very good. 50% damage and dodge chance for two seconds when you dash
right before getting hit versus... You can... No. This one is... You do bonus damage to people that
have the diamond in them. And this is reduce movement speed and damage of foes with the
diamond in them. I like this one better. This is raising the supply of casts versus regenerate your
cast rather than pick it up. So you don't have to pick it up anymore. I kind of like that more.
Wait a minute. So that means I can cast and then four seconds later I can cast again.
So I can cast every three... That's awesome. Yeah, I'm gonna keep that.
And then I'll upgrade... Let's upgrade this. All right. 30% of all that collected we can keep that
on. Your dark regeneration was at 0%. How can I have a reset talents? Reclaim any? Oh, that's cool.
That's really cool. I can get all my talent points back. More dialogue from Skeleton.
That's not a wild reference. There's talent points in other games.
You can reset your talent points in like 20 RPGs that are on the market right now.
Okay. Spear. The range on this is insane. What? Hold for a spin attack? Skewer and recall?
Does it go through them again? It does. Dash strike. Cool. All right. Well, I have to try
a run with this. Let's put on the money thing. Wait. I don't want to just be like a like a two
trinket loser, right? This gets ranked up. Yeah. Put this on. Oh, I can dash with the charge? Wait.
Hold on. That's pretty awesome. That's really awesome. Two trinket Andy. Right.
I don't want to be that today. It's not that orderly really. That's a hundred damage. All
right. Somebody said I can upgrade the weapons. How do I do that? Have I unlocked the ability
to do that yet? You can't do that yet. Oh, all right. I'm going to give the spear a try.
Berries again. Is this doom too? Spoiling Andy. Okay. I can do doom or your cast sends a blade
rift. I did. I, yeah. Didn't I specifically upgrade the cast thing? That's pretty cool.
One, two, three. So I, can I reduce the casting time? Cause I'll just be rift Andy.
Fucking God damn it. I'm sorry. Like you guys just were saying it recently.
That's insane. Okay. Good. I still have to give him a gift. All right. We're going to go. We're
going to try doing rift. Spear is pretty good. You just did a rift. Oh, and I get the heal from
this, but it doesn't even matter. Cause I don't have any lower. Oh wait. Chaos, chaos, chaos,
chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos. I give chaos a gift. Can't. Oh, well whatever. The next three standard
encounters, you face 78% more foes afterwards wounds have a 33% chance to be rare or better.
Okay. The next four encounters get killed foes, toss an inferno bomb at you. Afterward,
you do 73% damage striking foes from behind. That's insane. The next four chambers chamber
reward previews are hidden. Afterward, your dash strike deals 41% more damage. I mean,
that's a, that's a lot more foes, but there's a third of a chance for them to be rare or better.
Try it. I'm probably going to get, I'm going to get my, I'm going to get my ass kicked.
This one for the health. Oh, by the gift. Okay. What is he going to rift? I'm just going to be very,
very cautious. Oh, right. That. Yeah. Cautious. He just shot at me. Stop shooting at me. Stop
doing that. Stop it. Backstab, backstab, backstab. Oh, there's a lot. Actually,
this is going on for a long time. This is going on for a very long time. Nectar, money, fame,
money, or fame, money, or fame. What I've noticed is money or upgrade. It's going on them all there.
Whatever. Yes. Oh, bad idea. Oh, what is that? Oh, that's like, I think that's the original
Macintosh you screwed up some. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Adventure time when
Finn's dad loses his leg. I did not watch enough Adventure Time to know what that is.
Is that a spoiler? What? That's like a major spoiler. Did I just ruin Adventure Time?
I didn't, I didn't mean to do that. Stupid. Oh my God. Oh, doesn't that just make the devil mad?
Oh, come on. Don't you just want to make the devil mad? Oh, shit. I'm going to die.
Just kill this fucking asshole. He's off the screen. I don't know where he is.
I've been killed in Diablo 2 by that exact problem like a thousand times.
You shoot out of like a sorcerer's orb and all of a sudden you hear,
and the lightning just comes off screen and kills you.
Oh, okay. Settle down. Settle down, clown. Oh, it did, did it. Yeah. All right. I have one health.
I think I need to go in here. Only 20. What? Okay. Now do I get the pomegranate? Do I get the
palm pomegranate or do I get the mystery bag? Oh, I don't know what this is. Okay. Your dash
causes hangover, right? Or you take less damage while it's 50%. 15% less damage. That's pretty
sick, dude. What do you think? 6k Andy, hyper omega low. But usually it's like 10k. But usually
it's like 8k. Cry, cry, cry. Feel bad for playing Hades two days in a row.
Go for Artemis? No, 6k, 10k, 5k, 4k, 12k, 100k. I don't care. I mean, I would care if there was 100k.
That would be a huge deal. That would be a huge fucking deal. So yeah, of course I would care
if there was 100,000 people here. Okay. So thankfully this is going to help me. Wait,
do I still have that one? Do I? Wait. Oh, take, get rid of this. Oh, I can't get rid of this.
Go fishing? Can I? How do I go fishing? Looks like it's blinking over here. Right? Oh, okay.
Fishing spots are gold sparkles. Wasn't that a gold sparkle? Whoa! Thank you. Never sub,
I never donated you. I don't care. All right, let's go. This is going to be Poseidon. Oh,
it's a boss. I'll block you again? All right. Just, just be easy. Be easy. And it's not an
ideal build for this situation. Although it very well could have been. Actually, it is pretty good.
What am I talking about? It's fantastic for this exact scenario. That hurt. Oh my God,
what's happening to me over here? Stop hitting me. I said stop that. I've given a gift to Zeus. Yes,
I have. My brothers will not die in vain. I can make as many Diablo references as I want today.
This is great. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Which one of these is a good one? Lightning Strike is pretty
good. Call makes lightning. Wait, do I have a call yet? Um, shit, I think. It's definitely this one.
It has to be. You're attacking with chain lightning. I mean, of course it is. Thunder and lightning.
Kind of, I'm not getting, I'm getting a lot of different gods. His Xanax kicked in. What?
Survive for 45 seconds. That chain lightning seriously is pretty good.
The purple thing was an enemy. That doesn't activate chain lightning. Oh, no.
Done. Nine health. Yeah, I'm kind of getting my ass kicked a little bit here.
I don't think I've given a gift to Chile. I have not. Here we go.
Lady Demeter, you've shown me warmth and generosity, and I am very grateful for it.
Please accept this as a small token of my appreciation.
Well suited for the season there, young Zagreus. In turn, as you are honorable and obedient,
you'll have from me what the mortals have not.
Breezing lightning slash? Ross Bitten Horn. Cool. I'll see what that is later.
This has reached you prior to me, Zagreus.
She seems cold. Sort of. Holy shit. What is that?
Your cast drops a crystal that fires a beam for five seconds. 24 to 12 every half second.
What does that do? Your call creates a winter vortex that grows over five seconds of licking
chill. 11 damage a second. Who cares about that one? This is a heroic one. Slicing Shot.
Wait. Slicing Shot replaces the spinner that I have with a crystal every 0.2 seconds,
but it's super rare. The Rift is better though. It replaces the vortex. Oh, that kind of sucks.
Ah. Jesus, it's not rocket science. I've got a, I've got a, look at, I've got a legend,
I've got a heroic boon here that I'm trying to decide if I want to keep it. I'm just deciding.
I'm not going to write a thesis paper about it. All right, Dementor's Aid. I think I want this
one. I want to keep the Rift. Yeah. I want to keep the Rift. I like it. I like it slow. It moves.
I like it. I like it. So that's a call. I'm probably going to live long enough to care
about it anyway. All right. What's this? Oh, restore a hundred health. After I do this. I
forgot this. Okay. Well, wait, wait, wait. We're going to use Dementor's Call. It's like,
did you call security? I'm dead. I don't, well, that sucks. I already wasted a death.
I just, I forgot the, whatever. Bullshit. I'm annoyed by that. Reset? No. This thing does have
huge range. Why am I getting so close? I'm treating it like a sword. This thing has enormous
range. I'm treating it like the sword. What's wrong with me? Many things. All right. Time that
guy out for two hours. He was right though. Time that person out that just said that for three
hours. They were both right. I want you to time that person out for six hours. All of them are
right. I want you to give that guy everything he's ever wanted and hope his life is perfect
from here on out. That's a flex. I didn't know that did that. Okay. That changes everything.
That's why I wasn't using it that often because I was afraid to get hit by projectiles.
Boon of Germa. I don't even know what I would give. All right. What like element would I be?
Water, fire, ice, earth, air, chaos, metal, meat? What element? Imagine taking a what element are
you quiz and you get meat. I feel that's pretty good. Ensure a chaos gate will spawn.
I'm doing that one. I bought this game because of you. It's great. I'm glad you like it. It's
very good. All right. I think we're going to. All right. Here comes Meg. All right. Goodbye.
I refunded this game because of you. Odd. Odd thing to do.
Tell me something, Zach, because I'm curious. Do your Olympian relatives know the real reason
you've been trying to escape? Get around to that in due time. A family. Did anyone happen to steal a
red spy? You're in over your head, you idiot. You'll fray what bonds are left between Lord Hades
and those ingrates on Olympus. How often do I say that line? I feel like I do it all the time.
Too close. Here she goes. Excuse me. All right. I'm going to do Mother's Mayhem. I don't even know
what the movie is called. I'm just going to call it what I'm going to call it so I can have it in
my own brain. I know what move I'm talking about. All right. Let's do Mother's Mayhem.
Mother's Mayhem is pretty good. Ow. Right into the trap. It just threw me off. What?
Double tap. The only damage I've taken this entire game in this boss fight has
been from the fucking floor trap. Almost happened again. No. Screed. This game seems a little easy
or are you good? Yes. I don't know. Look, it has four buttons. That means I can do okay.
I've refused to believe he's good. I almost beat the last boss on my first try. You gotta
give me credit sometimes where I deserve it. If the game has four buttons, I will do okay.
It's the games that have WASD, mouse, 10 items, a bag full of stuff, crafting,
and a giant quest log that I have to keep track of and oh go talk to this guy and go look you're
gonna go through that it's like a maze you're gonna find this guy at the end of that tunnel.
No. Give me four buttons. Give me an analog stick and I will smoke that game. Let's just do it.
All right. So a lot of these god boons are just to make it so you get their boon first.
What difficulty am I on? I dragged the slider up as far as it could go. I don't know. It was
easy, medium, hard, insane, psycho, and torture and I think I was somewhere between insane and
psycho and torture. I think it was closer to torture. It really is too bad that this is so good.
Two more encounters and this ranks up. Does that mean I get to come back three times?
No. It's more life. Oh, that's still good though. All right, let's go.
I see you, Tartarus. Give me back my tooth. I've been timed out for 3.627e plus seven minutes.
What? Why did you just break your iPhone calculator? Oh, there it is. I can fish down here?
What? Oh, come on. I couldn't have got a chaos fish. That's too bad.
No fish. No fish. Well.
The next three encounters, each time you special, get hit minus four. Afterwards,
you gain another... Oh, well, that's exactly what I wanted to do this run. Or just a bunch of max
health or... Oh, that's really good too though. That's so good. Any money you find is increased
by 45% after that happens. But this lets me cast two rifts and it's a three second cooldown.
I'm going with the rifts. What was the downside? I didn't care. Oh, for the next three encounters,
each time you special... I don't even press triangle anyways. I don't play... I never press
Y anyways. Who cares? Great. These guys, I'm either doing not very much damage or these guys
have a lot of health right now. I don't think I'm doing a lot of damage. What the hell? Not
doing a whole lot of damage. This is not looking all right. Get out of the fire. One, two, three.
Oh, what am I doing? One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two, three. One,
two, three. That's right. That video where the guy, he goes, that's an old one. I want this.
Oh my fucking God. That's a really good meme. It's the guy trying to do the old like first man
ever voice, right? Like the caveman voice. Oh shoot. Oh shoot. Lucky tooth ranked up. Nice.
And a shop with money in it. I mean, with hearts in it. Thank you. Wait, what else is on there?
I want that too. Oh, well, I hate this thing. Just queue it up for when they eventually spawn.
Don't do it. Blow it up. One, two, one. Hey, that was unfair. Oh, come on. Can I please.
You're making me look bad. He's a slippery one. Peewee Herman voice. I gave him a gift. All right.
I did not. How have I not given a diet? I have not. Great getting to know you. So please accept
this humble offer. Play the one, two, three video. Hold on. I will. All right. What is this? Is this
it right? Let's try male human voice. Count over three. One, two, three. Just pitch up your voice.
One, two, three. Let's just add a bit of nasal now. One, two, three. Now the other thing that
would be happening, which would actually increase that quality is a very heavy skull that seems to
pull down into the throat there. Now speak. One, two, three. Now let's make a sound. Just
let's make a huge R. That's one of my favorite videos. One, two, three.
Here's something. A right princely gift there, Zack. And just so happens, I got something here
I have been meaning to give you. Get a big really heavy skull. Overflowing cup. I like this guy the
most. Ionite is my favorite god. Uh, well, okay. This one's good, but this one's better.
You've re-gifted it back to you. Oh, did I, did I give him like a bread maker for Christmas?
And he just doesn't even know how to, he doesn't have the, the, doesn't even want to open it out
of the box. Doesn't want to take it out because it's a ton of work. I don't want to do this shit,
man. I'll give this to somebody else. I don't think, you know, I don't think a bread maker's
ever been opened on Christmas. Somebody, it just gets rewrapped and gives to another party
over and over and over again. Stab, stab, stab, stab, stab him, stab him, stab him.
That's a stand-up comedian joke. Whatever. Look, all right, so whatever, whatever, whatever.
Oh, oh, I can do two casts in a row because, right, right, right, right, right, right,
because of the thing that I got. Right, I forgot, I forgot. Ooh, hey, oh, did I gift?
I already, wait, should I do gift two? No, you already had a gift. What does two gifts do?
Just one gift, okay. What's going on with his eyes? That eye is filled with blood. You should
probably go get that looked at. Okay, here we go. We can either do two random boons of yours are
upgraded to the next rarity right now, four random boons gain a level, or the next three boons will
have upgraded rarity. Probably this one, this one, or this one. Wait, don't I already have the
upgraded rarity thing already? So would this eat, that would be even more. They might be legendaries.
That's a big deal. They might be like heroics and legendaries. This is nice. Dude, one time,
I don't know why this reminded me of this, but the original Punisher movie had a song in it
that was like, you may come back someday, live once more, die once more. So forget about that part.
The part that I'm referring to is in college. I remember in the DVD player, that was what played
on loop at the menu screen. And I remember falling asleep with that in the DVD player,
the Punisher DVD, and waking up every, I would say, five to 10 minutes over the course of like
three or four hours to, you may come back someday, live once more. And I just don't care. I'm too
tired to get up and turn it off. It was at least three or four hours. It was just on the cycling
the menu song. It's very funny because I kept waking up to you may come back someday. So eyes
open, you may come back someday. One day, maybe I'm going to sleep. You may come back. So I'm
coming. I'm back again, but please, I'd like to go to sleep. Why did I keep doing it? I don't know.
Eventually I just like stumbled out of the bed and just like smashed on every button on the DVD
player and hope that it turned it off. Oh, actually, I think I walked up and just hit,
you know what the quickest way to turn a DVD off was just open the disc tray. Just walk up,
press open disc tray button, go back to bed. But then you'd have the problem where you just have a
blue TV. That's stuck too. Because now you have a new problem. You have this blue burning light
that's just always on you. So you got to do open the disc tray, turn the TV power button off and
go back to bed. Uh, this is, I kind of want the health. Damn, that's pretty good. After using a
call, you deal more damage for 15 seconds. Your lightning effects make foes jolted. Yeah. Jolted
really is just so broken that this is cool, but this is broken. I'm doing a cool one.
Oh, here we go. This is it. I should have taken the health. What am I doing? It's not broken.
It's bad. That's what I mean. It's like, so it's just broken. It sucks so much. Like why would you
even use it needs to be updated. What did you think I was talking about? All right. This one
shouldn't be too bad considering I have the, uh, the rift. Yeah. Why? I was so complacent. Don't
give. All right. Quiet. All right. That's good. That's good. That's good. That's good. That's good.
Now we're going to do this. Come on, dude. What are you doing? What am I actually doing? I'm
getting so close for no reason. What the fuck am I doing here? All right. Let's go into the fire.
Into the fire. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
into the fire. Stop the fire. My favorite God in spite, by the way, best character,
coolest move set. You didn't get enough love. Go, go do it. We're good. Play smite. I played
smite for like 10 minutes. LOL. What the fuck is going on today? Uh, you know, I replaced words
with just like a laugh, I guess I'm busy playing a game. So I don't have, I can't like really talk
that much unless I'm taking a break like this. So replace like words with just laugh in a weird
way. That's odd, right? I'm like every bad guy in a children's show. They say a sentence and then
they laugh like that. This is good. Oh, this restores 100 health. You have to micromanage
brain RAM. Yeah, guys, I don't know how many of you guys might know this. Some of you might be new
viewers. I have like two gigs of memory, but it's incredibly fast. It's very fast, but there's only
two gigs. It's two gigs of like DDR five 6400 megahertz RAM. This is not a whole lot of it.
I don't have any money anyways. You have a 24 max FPS brain speed. What about your CPU?
Um, that's okay. My CPU, my CPU is like a 32 core 10 gig overclocked CPU, but then it runs
into my two gigahertz tube, two gigabyte RAM. It gets stuck. My graphics card sucks ass too.
My eyes are terrible. I'm running. I have like a, okay, I have a mobile graphics card up here in my
head. My vision's not very good and I miss things. I'm really slow like visually a lot of the time.
I have like a, okay, I don't even have a G force. I have old ATI, old AMD. See back in the day,
AMD graphics cards. We're not the cool thing. I have like an ATI mobility radion 1100 M.
I can fish here. Where's the fishing spot? Oh, come on. Just a lore.
So what's the point of the fishing rod? Hammer, always hammer. Blow it up. Oh my
God. Those things attack you. Good. Who's next? Bring it on. Oopsie.
Don't let him shoot you. Another one? Who has the, who's shooting at me? It's not you.
I don't have your bow out. Who the hell's aiming at me? Who was you? Your special becomes a shot
that deals 50 base damage in an area. Boring. Hold special for up to 200% base damage and minimum
range reduced. Your special deals 50% damage. Wait, that's pretty good. So the special deals
plus 50% damage and plus 50% critical chance on recovery. What does on recovery mean? On recovery
when you call it back. But, oh, right. Okay. I don't really use the special that often. I really
don't. Maybe this would be better. 200%. There's a lot though. I'll try this because it crits,
right? So when you pull it back. Okay. Maybe I'll use it sometimes. Eh, I'm not happy with any of
that. Oh, I mean it's, it's good. It's good. But it's a lot to pay attention to. It's good. It's,
it's 135 damage is a lot. I said to remember to use it. Ah, trap. Hey, hey. Two gigabytes can't
load the image. No, I just get stuck. Oh, more singing. This is different. This is different.
Most covered chambers cut of stone stand untold numbers of eternal monuments in tribute to the
greatest heroes which mortality can offer there to honor them in life as well as death.
This is a new character. This place is near as gloomy as the house.
This is a new character. Oh, it's the bod. Hello, bod. Go on stranger. More shades looking to fight
with you out there. I'm just passing through. You seem less warlike than the rest. May I ask
your name, sir? I'm Zagreus. My name is the bod. Names are there to be forgotten, stranger.
You shouldn't be here. May the fates favor your journey. But just in case they don't.
Oh, he's a wicked cool character. Oh, the shade offers one of several premium goods.
That's good. That's also very good. Holy shit, this guy's unbelievable. Oh my god.
One but ten encounters. How many encounters are left in the game?
All right, hold on a minute. If there's only a few more rooms left that means I'll have
60% more damage for the last boss. Refill me. He's a shield user. I want this. Excuse me. Did I
get by a trap? I did. Of course I did. Don't you respawn. I got to drop this somewhere.
Who's alive? Again. Holy fuck. Oh my god. Very bad. Very bad. Where are the bows? You
asshole with the bow. Almost did actually. Delicious. Delicious. Okay. That's really good.
Number three is unbelievable. You're attacking its chain lightning. So it's just better chain
lighting. But this is a full almost 10% more damage after hitting right trigger. This is extra.
Oh, don't. What are you doing? I think they're all very good. All right. What is better just
statistically doing 15 damage every 0.25 seconds or doing 8% more damage after doing it? Probably
the third one, right? You want to use it more often. Please click that link so they stop posting
it. I don't know. I want to do more all around damage. I'm going for it. Whatever. All right.
I'll open the link. This is my boon. I didn't get a chance to see it yet. Let's see. All of your
attacks lose 50% damage, but you get a slice of bologna. Take it. Do it. That's worth it.
That's actually worth it. How much does the bologna heal? Boomer. Oh, my God. I almost quit
the game. Boomer sense of humor. What? Come on. That's cute. Um, I need that. I got to heal.
Sorry, Ares. Do not hit me under any gosh darn circumstances. You hit me. You hit me. They hit.
Okay. Oh, no. I'm not done. Oh, shit. Who the fuck? Oh, it's this guy with the bow
back here. You dick. I hate you. Of course, you guys get to hang out in these like traps.
God, why can you shoot across the whole screen? Game just went down one point.
Game just went down one point. It was a 92. Now it's a 91. You just went down a whole. You went
down one millipoint. Spam your cast. I'm using it almost every time. Uh, I'm gonna have to do
this one. This is a 92, but Lego Island isn't. I've never played Lego Island. I have no idea
what Lego Island even is. What do I do? I'm gonna heal 10% for the next few rooms, which is
like 15 health. I could take the boon or I could take the even more HP. I could get this and I
don't have enough for that, do I? I could do both. Always boon. Always boon. Always boon. Always boon.
Oh, yes. No. Yes. Oh, no. Your special is stronger and it looks chill.
So much more damage, but, uh, we're going. I gotta go long term here. I have to go long term.
That's it. One is long term. Yeah. But three is longer term because now I heal from more,
no matter what, from every source. And I needed that health because I'm about to fight the boss.
One away from the meal. Yeah. Oh well. Three is a short term, a hundred percent. All right.
Really? I didn't get a chance. Don't hit me. Come on. The little guys are going back.
Literally have no idea what just happened. I think I killed them. Just actually hit me.
No, you didn't. There's more? Jesus. Ow. How did you really just bounce off that shit? Come on,
dude. Lost HP already. Yeah. These, these rooms are fucking crazy. I'll get it back. Do not pick
that up. Do not pick that up. No, I hate this place. Kill, kill, kill. More? More? More? More?
I just spit. I spit everywhere. It's everywhere. It's so bad. It's like I sprayed my mirror in my
bathroom with Windex. It's insane. Hold on. This is disgusting. It's horrible. It's everywhere.
Oh no. This is not good. Gotta fix that. It's okay. I got it. I'm getting it. The thing,
there's a shop. Oh, I missed it. It's okay. Show the spit and that's gross. Boss time.
It's boss time and I'm not ready. I'm in deep shit here.
That's good. Three dashes is always good. 16 extra gold per chamber is really good too,
but I need this. Thank you. All right. Triple dash. I have a revive. I don't think this is
the one. I'm not sure this is the run. I can dash five times? Wait, wait, wait, wait. I changed my
mind. Can I change my mind? That's unbelievable. That's cool. Okay. But I don't, I'm not very good
with the spear though. Whatever. Let's go. Don't give up. You got it. That's true. I have a full
revive and I have five dash. That just changed everything. You got this king. Thanks.
Thanks.
I feel like I'm like abusing it. Oh my God. Okay. Pay attention. Just play smart. Wow.
What the fuck am I doing standing still?
God damn it. This build is not good. I'm not going with the spear. I feel like this is taking
it forever. They haven't even called it Athena yet. I'm dead.
Crushing this up, you fucking truck. This is so long. Get him, get him, get him. Oh, here we go.
This is bad. Get the fuck away from me. Will you walk into this, please? Ow, that hurt. Jesus.
Oh my goodness. I just wasn't doing any damage. Spear is not for me.
Sounded like Gary when he ate. Sounded like Spongebob when he ate Gary's food.
I just don't, I wasn't doing enough damage. Oh, you're back. Did I give him a gift? I needed
that special boon that you gave up. Yeah, so that's just how the cookie crumbles, isn't it?
Made one wrong decision. I like shield and I like bow.
And if you're also concerned about our court musician,
why don't you commute to sentence yourself? Seeing as I haven't gotten around to it yet.
Howard, that's fine. Sure. I get to live. I'll just ask the house contractor since you're too busy.
Contractor, mind locating the court musician's sentence when you get the chance.
Oh, I actually, I think I have some quests to do, right? I'm going to give him a gift
because I haven't given him a gift yet. Hey, you think you can butter me up with such trifles?
Give me that out of here. You're welcome, father. Shall we get back to work? What the hell? Wait.
Well, next. Did I give him another one? He needs two. Why are you here? More pets. I got more pets
here, boy. I see. I've heard enough. Granted. Granted what? Oh, all right, let's see. I got 20.
Court musician, free Orpheus from solitary confinement. In the name of Hades,
I commute our court musician sentencing effective now. Hello? Ah, Orpheus. Am I composed entirely of
gemstones? I mean, I have another one. What do you do? Hello, Zagreus. I understand you liberated me
from my eternal punishment, and so I have returned to serve your father here. Thanks.
Morpheus, Orpheus, Dickus, Malicious.
What the hell are you doing? I was in all caps, by the way.
Morpheus, you're back. Look, don't get on father's bad side like that and you're going to be fine.
Besides, right now I think he's angry with me. You guys are fucking hilarious.
Now, some people don't like the insanity, but I love it. I love the stream of just insane
consciousness. Are you 12? No, I'm 35, if you didn't know. You're not gonna be 36. What the fuck?
I gotta, like, stop wearing suits and, like, pants and ties. Once I turn 36, 37, I guess I wear,
like, clothes. I have to start combing my hair all the way from one side to the other. It doesn't
matter what kind of hair I have, I just have to start doing that.
I felt that way about 25, then 27, then 30. That feeling never goes away.
I think that feeling turns into acceptance. Act broken. Shit. Can I give a gift?
I think at 40 that just turns into life, you know, that's it. Like, okay, you're 40 now.
There's no more like, well, you know, I'm like 30 still. I'm like turning 37. No, you're 40.
Oh. All of your teachers are 40. All of my teachers are 40. Like, I'm an old teacher now.
Midlife crisis? Yeah, at 40. I'm gearing up for the midlife crisis in, like, five years.
What's this? Prophecy fulfilled.
It's intended purpose to enliven the house's grim inhabitants.
All right, this is pretty cool.
It's better than nothing.
Fresh pomegranates and bread? This actually sucks. A steady diet of pomegranates,
French bread, and fish. Is it? I'm not into that.
Wretched broker, what's new, my friend?
I can still do that. I don't think I'm going to do this, though.
Where's the mayo? No, where's the...
Anything but onions, pomegranates, bread, and fish. Oh, hi.
To the point where that head gets attached to something and then all of a sudden she gets
powers and can control stuff again. And then all of a sudden it's like, oh, no, I'm not, like, I'm
not, oh, no, no, no, I'm going to kill you all. That probably happens, right?
Here we go. Ooh, 80.
Very cool. All right, what else do I got?
Oh, who have I met? I've not met three other people.
Merciful End. Wait, there's two other weapons?
What the hell are you talking about?
All right, I think I want to do a key run. That makes that so much better.
Okay, 60% now. Damage is from behind. 40%.
Yeah, I did get a bunch of gems. That's right. Oh, wait, you're back.
Oh, let's eavesdrop.
You are not to aid him in these matters, Nix. His foolishness is to be scorned and reprimanded.
Do we have an understanding?
We have an understanding, Hades, yes. He is your own son, after all,
and therefore your responsibility. I, in turn, have my commitments to this realm and to this house.
You're gonna read chat? I do. I'm way more than you think I do.
It is not necessary to remind me. Surely all those who once defied my brothers and myself
would much prefer a post within my house over eternity within the lowest depths of Tartarus.
Not that the darkness there would trouble you.
You know how a lot of you guys say, how did you miss what they were just talking about?
Oh, is it possible that you missed everything that you said? They just said it.
Well, because I wasn't paying attention to them, I was paying attention to you.
I was reading your lore during that. I have no idea what they just said.
I have absolutely no fucking idea at all. I was looking at over here.
I was seeing, like, what's going on over here in, like, the stadium.
The arena. The stadium. The stadium with 6,600 people in the stadium for tonight's game.
We are, like, the Cincinnati Reds. Is that sports?
Yeah. Wasn't there a season where the Cincinnati Reds lost, like, 14 games in a season or something?
Yeah. Oh, that's so sad. That's sad, man.
Okay, chambers may contain urns. I think it's time to get this.
To smash everything, right? Or a fountain chamber in Elcium.
Underworld fountains, holy. Fountains provide more health than usual. That's even better.
Mash pots. Smash pots and add a fountain to Elcium.
And I want new curtains. I want a scrying pool.
And I thought, I thought it said bug safety.
Excuse me? Pardon me? Listen to what? Oh, I could have just listened to something. Go back.
No! What's this? Renovate. Oh. Can I go in that?
Escape attempted. Oh, it tells you how, okay. Killed 1,700 people, let's try to escape six times.
Go to bed. Earlier. What is this?
All is quiet at this time. Ever dreaming Hypnos put a spell upon the house,
as Wilful Zagreus had asked of him. All are fast asleep, save for the prince.
It is exactly as he planned. Okay.
Lower your voice, old man. I'm trying to be sneaky here.
I'm trying to sneak around my dad's quarters. I'm gonna put peanut butter in his slippers.
He ventures toward the stately throne of his lord father, but ill, expecting what he is about to find.
I said shut up, old man. He does not know exactly what he seeks.
What? Is this like a- He only knows that something always has felt off to him,
that he does not belong. Who is he, really? Lord Hades never would indulge such questions.
So Prince Zagreus would find out for himself. I'm not listening.
Let's see, what? We're gonna look at his- Who is it?
He rifles through his lord father's possessions. Who he's been writing to.
There is not much of any import there. Ledgers and administrative partment work.
Correspondence from Olympus, which he had ignored. No trace of any reference to his son.
But then, there is the note. The note.
Written finally in a hand and voice, the likes of which the prince had never seen or heard.
Hades, I can no longer tolerate my life here in this place.
Oh, it's from Persephone. So I'm leaving, even if it kills me.
I won't be returning to Olympus. If there is a place where I belong in this world,
it must be somewhere between heaven and hell.
Perhaps it's on the coast and has a little garden.
Take care of Cerberus. I shall miss him. Persephone.
Stephanie.
Thus did prince of the underworld-
I- I said that wrong all the time.
absorb the contents of this hidden letter, written in his mother's hand.
I think Steve rule. Persephone is Stephanie.
My name is Persephone. I sh- I should put you Stephanie, Stephanie.
You're saying this Persephone that she's my-
What? Oh, what the heck? No way!
I always said that Nyx was-
Persephone is Zagoras' mother, and Hades is Zagoras' father,
and he thought his mother was Nyx, and they've been keeping this secret from him forever.
Thus did the prince discover-
But why?
...advertently the well-kept truth about his lineage.
Let me know in the comments what you think, why they're hiding that from Zagoras.
I'll see you next time for episode 145 of our playthrough of Hades.
Sinner, is he?
To find the wrong questions and his rage, the prince decided his lord and master.
145 streams of Hades.
Uh-oh.
Mommy, you've been lying to me this whole time.
Wait, or should I say, not mommy?
You, all this time, you and my father, you-
My dear child, so now you know.
So now you know.
But only half the truth.
I can explain the rest, so please, it never was my wish to hurt you.
Who cares?
I mean, you are my mother, who cares?
I kinda wanna-
This is too good to take off.
I'm never gonna be able to take this off ever again.
I like all this, but this one, I can die so many times.
This is 50% I get to die once.
Isn't this better?
Restore a small amount of health when you enter a chamber.
Three health when you go in a chamber versus-
No, no, no, no, I like this better.
I like it, I'm keeping it.
All right, let's go.
I don't have enough to do anything anyways.
You can die twice if you buy more of those.
Well, it's 600, that's a huge amount of-
So many of you are here to enjoy this game.
Thank you for being here each day.
I didn't say shit, that counts.
Whatever, 20 subs.
There's another-
There's another weapon?
I didn't know there was another-
Oh, I thought this was gonna be DLC.
There are two more weapons?
What?
It's a giant glove.
Oh, it's eight keys.
No, they're trying to keep me here forever.
All right, this is the next one you find will be from Dionysus.
All right, we're gonna go with the meta here.
And, hmm.
I am absolutely a shield guy.
I'm a shield guy.
Let's go.
Use bow?
Not yet.
All right, this is specifically what we're doing here is-
We're getting a cutscene?
Hold on, are you telling me that I almost beat the game before getting all the abilities
and before seeing the first, like, you're out of the tutorial cutscene?
Holy shit.
Wow, well, that's too bad.
It's just the edge I need.
Your dash drag deals 50%-
That's, okay, that's really good.
That's the bounce.
This charges up faster, but I'm going for the dash.
50% more damage.
Die Dallas hammer.
He doesn't know.
I-
No, I don't.
I don't know what you're referring to.
I'm absolutely a shield guy.
No, no doubt in my mind.
Chthonic coin-
What?
Perth.
Received-
Oh, that's 125 now.
Play portal two?
No, it makes me throw up after 45 minutes and I have to stop.
Ooh, and Dionysus.
Here we go.
It's time for a bleed build.
It took me like two weeks to beat portal two when it first came out.
After 45 minutes, I have to stop.
Hangover damage.
Here we go.
That's probably the one I want.
Because that bounces around.
Why?
I don't know.
It's something about it.
Something about the falling through the portals and seeing the-
I don't know, it just fucks with my head and makes me sick.
Especially the first game.
Actually, one's probably better.
And we get chaos right off the bat.
This could be a pretty good run.
Ooh.
Wait, I gotta break the-
Okay, do I-
Is it-
Wait, I got a question.
Is the-
Should I just break every single vase now?
Or is it very specific?
It looks very different.
It's just gold pots.
Okay.
What artifact?
It is considered a defensive instrument, I do believe.
No ice defect you have discovered or soon shall discover.
It is nothing of the sort.
What is he talking about?
All right, for the next three encounters, you have-
That's awful.
Afterwards, boons have a 16% chance to be rare, but that's not very good.
Take 370%-
Okay, I die instantly from traps, but afterward I get 33 more max health.
Or each time you attack, get hit for 4 damage,
but any money you find is worth 35% more.
I'm just gonna kill myself.
How would I do this?
Would I have to kill everything with my cast or with a special?
Just use your special.
I'm gonna try it.
I'm going for it.
Let's see how this goes.
Because that's not an attack technically, right?
Does it get hurt?
All right, just play safe.
Just don't attack.
And look at this.
I hit the jackpot.
Free encounter.
Wait, fish?
What the hell?
I was trying to activate fish rod.
No fish?
Oh, this is gonna take a lot longer than I thought.
Oh boy, this is a bad idea, wasn't it?
Shit.
Come here.
Come on.
Kill that little shit.
That's not bad.
We're fine.
Aphrodite.
I haven't seen Aphrodite in a very long time.
But I can't do that one.
Wait, is the only door I can go in?
All right, plus 50% more damage on your special.
None of these will help me.
Gain plus one for your cast.
That's so much money though.
I have to take it.
Otherwise, I'm not gonna be able to complete this next encounter.
I physically won't be able to do it.
This is an elite room.
This motherfucker has all my cubes.
I'm so dead.
It's over.
Why did I have to get so greedy?
Block?
If I...
I can't...
All right, whatever.
Just...
I don't care.
Just restart, restart, restart, restart, restart, restart, restart, restart, restart.
Why am I not...
Why am I still alive?
The curse can't kill you.
Yeah, that was...
That was over.
That's why it's called a doomsday.
Just rip the bandaid off.
Let's go.
Remind yourself that overconfidence is a slow and insidious killer.
That was very bad.
I'll redo that.
Remind yourself that overconfidence is a slow and insidious killer.
That was much better.
I had to give it some effort.
Still bad.
And that guy for life for saying that about me and my voice acting skills.
To say there isn't another death.
Another underworld.
I got his dad of old age.
What are you doing here?
Isn't like...
Isn't this supposed to be like serial killers?
I'm in hell?
That guy just died of old age.
He didn't...
What did he do?
What's new?
Hades is...
Oh, wait.
It's not heaven and hell?
What's hell in...
Greek mythology.
Tartarus.
Taurus.
Hades is a place and a person.
All right.
And serial killers not die from old age.
No, but wouldn't you think it would say like was a serial killer underneath it?
50%.
Let's go.
All right.
I got the shield still.
I want to unlock the glove.
There's other skellies?
Every time I get into a little string like this,
I just feel like I'm playing Smash Brothers.
Just like get in it.
Mash buttons.
It's not mashing buttons.
You do a string of things together.
You go...
I put this...
This is on, right?
Oh, this is even better that I restarted.
It's 125 gold.
Oh, he's dead now.
You mash them in the right order.
Aphrodite right off the bat.
And Aphrodite has not received a gift.
Take one.
Blessed simply to have made your acquaintance.
So this is for you.
Lasting relationships are built on reciprocity.
Given all my gifts to Aphrodite.
Gifts why?
What if I give you something in return?
Eternal rose.
Here is why Lord Hades would have kept your mere existence hidden from us all this time.
Perhaps he knew that once you met us...
Her icon looks the tastiest.
That's how I've been determining which one I want.
I feel like that one would taste the best.
The icon.
The icon, folks.
It's like a candy heart.
We have like crispy, cold, chilly, like spearmint gum.
We have like the wing, like the baby back ribs for Hermes.
I'm basing it on the icon.
Not?
Okay.
Relax.
Well, that's a good start.
That's also a good start.
I don't need to relax.
He wouldn't let me finish my sentence.
I'm like, oh, I base it on what I find looks the tastiest.
He's a sicko.
Icon.
He didn't let me finish.
Uh...
Death first.
44 damage already?
Sick.
All right, let's go.
Focus time.
And I like how there's little hearts after you do stuff.
Who's left?
Oh, there's nobody left.
Ooh, this is two good upgrades right in a row.
I can't even.
You guys are fucking crazy.
Bam.
Your attack hits twice.
I mean, it has.
Dude, you're looking like a snack.
Oh, me?
Yep.
That's good.
Go, boy.
I'm sorry.
That was very bad.
I may have just been trying to do like a hillbilly voice.
Oh, bad.
That's good.
I can't even.
You can't even do that.
I forgot an urn?
What?
I didn't even know what they were.
What does it look like?
I missed out.
Oh, he's stupid.
He's stupid.
He's dumb.
Don't let him forget it.
Give me more.
It's going to be just like the certain thing in a certain game
that shows up that I miss all the time.
And it's something in this certain thing that I will not make a reference to.
And it shows up in some rooms.
And it's differently colored.
And it's hard for me to see them sometimes.
I don't.
I want the.
Why is it?
I want the heart.
Don't keep me going.
Dash deals damage when you end up inflicting weak.
Weak afflicted foes are also more susceptible to damage.
I mean, it should be.
It's two.
Does that say 35 unmarried is embarrassed by his job?
Physically deformed.
What did I have?
What did I do to you, man?
If I provided you with, say, a thousand coins,
would you be willing to give me a ride in your beautiful boat?
Or I should say specifically.
What did I do to you?
That's like I just gave you two seconds to scream at me.
You got to get it all out.
Another Aphrodite door.
Actually ban that guy.
That was rude.
I can't.
I mean, he's wicked mean.
But I can't ban everybody.
Alicia, this is a great build.
It's just revenge damage.
But when you.
Definitely two.
Yeah, they blow up.
Remember, don't let anybody shame you for your life.
All right.
Let me be honest.
Let's break that down for a second.
Yeah, I'm 35.
Who cares?
You just get age gets better with wine.
Except in my case, when you have spinal disc problems,
you have a hernia that needs surgery,
and you need to take baths every day.
All right.
Hey, how dare you?
Second of all, unmarried.
What if I don't want to get married?
What if I want to be complete?
What if I just want to live for me, man?
OK, number three.
What was third one?
He's balding so hard that I was physically.
All right.
Let me play my fucking computer game.
Let me play my computer game.
Dude, this triple hit.
Look at 300, 400, 500, 600, 700, 900, 1,000.
Give me some synergy here.
Come on.
Crystal thing.
Give me some synergy here, please.
Synergy since you began your quest.
It's cool.
You have.
I'm keeping count.
Most impressed.
Everyone's going to marry his computer.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
Who cares about Blade Rift when I can just go like this
and they take a shitload of damage.
Get VR married.
You know, I'm surprised there is not a VR get married simulator by now.
Where you're the groom and the bride comes down the aisle
and you exchange vows and stuff.
There is.
Well, then I'm going to play it.
I have to play that.
I have to play the get married simulator.
Sima Shanzi just gave 10 community subs.
Thank you, Sima.
Appreciate the subs.
10 subs just dropped in.
What happened to me?
Oh, that's his move.
Yeah, dude.
This shit is a get in and get out move set.
Get in.
Get out.
Pomegranate.
What?
I missed another.
In and out.
Animal style.
I'm missing so many things.
Fishing.
I don't let me miss that.
I want 1,000 people to unsub if I do not.
If I miss that.
Imagine not being shield guy.
Imagine thinking anything else in this game was as adequate as shield guy is.
Power.
Delicious.
Oh, yes.
94%.
Pogged out.
I'm pogged out too, man.
I can only pog so many times.
Fish.
Knucklehead?
I got a perfect catch.
Oh.
Of Charon's ways.
Um, should I just take that?
No, not worth it.
I need to get him from here.
All right, well now at least I know what that looks like.
In and out style.
I love it.
I love this shield.
It's the best weapon.
I don't think glove can compare.
I really don't.
I'm just cleaning up.
Do you see any fish?
I don't see any fish.
Is Greek mythology pog or not pog?
It's pog.
It's really pog, actually.
Come forth, wretches, and stop this meddler.
Survive for 45 seconds.
Their attention.
You got more than that?
I'm talking about a shield user.
No, I don't think so.
I should not be the supervisor here.
Well, that's better.
How many keys do I have?
Three.
I'm just hamstringing myself for no reason
because I just leave the...
I just go.
I'm like, let's go.
I'm ready.
You need to relax.
I am very relaxed.
I just want...
I'm ready to open the door.
Uh...
No, no, no.
I'm so mad.
He's defeated.
I mean, but I just got a little happier right here.
Your call fires a seeking arrow with a 35% crit chance.
The arrows do 120 damage, and it fires 10 arrows
if you let it fill all the way, which would be
just base 1200 damage with a 35% crit.
If even two...
If even one of those crits, which you would assume
that statistically three out of three and a half of them will
talk about like 1500 damage.
1600 damage, maybe.
Let's hunt some dead.
I'm gonna fill the bar.
I'm gonna take a pee break after this and get some water.
Crit is 3x.
Give up already, Zach.
Was that a sneeze?
Bless you.
I have some bad news for you, Meg.
Little by little, I'm getting stronger.
Aren't I killing her over and over again?
She's talking like she's killing me over and over again.
He's got this kind of backwards, I think.
Look at that damage.
Already sick.
Look at cocky.
Oh, I was trying to stay in the middle.
You just call that an airstrike?
Our UAV is online.
Our UAV is airborne.
Excuse me.
Watch out for the guy behind you.
Get the fuck out of here, Meg.
Yes.
50, that's a lot.
Anybody see anything?
A paranoid to open the door.
Go get water and pee.
Yeah, I will in a second.
Well, I don't even need to.
Doesn't even do anything.
Full health already.
Here comes a family guy funny hell moment.
Wait, what is this?
Oh, it's just you getting Aphrodite gives you this thing.
I have the money, so I'm just gonna buy it.
All right, bear it back.
I'm just gonna pee and grab a water.
I'll be back in like two, three minutes.
Fucking hate streaming.
Fucking I'm so done.
I'm fucking never streaming again.
Like after tonight, it's fucking I'm done streaming.
I'm here.
I'm just, I'm eating.
Now, you know, I've been into these new streamer snacks.
These little turkey jerkeys.
They like Slim Jims, but they're not full of trash.
I guess you could say.
And this is coming from somebody that I love Slim Jims.
I do.
But they are dog shit.
Did you guys know that if you ate, if you ate 1600 Slim Jims in a row, you die?
Did you know that?
1400 Slim Jims, actually.
If you eat 1400 Slim Jims, you will die.
Because of the sodium nitrate in Slim Jims.
That's so fucking funny.
Just eat, yeah, just eat the thousand of them.
You'll be all right.
Okay, if you type in how many Slim Jims kill you into Google, you get a IGN forum of somebody
saying being very concerned that they ate 15 Slim Jims and they're concerned.
My mouth and throat are coated in grease.
Or whatever that orange slimy goo is that oozes out when you squeeze a Slim Jim.
I feel so gross right now.
And I think I'm having chest pains.
What the fuck?
20, like 2013, 2014.
Holy shit.
Okay, I don't, it's not, I'm not talking about me.
I'm not talking, I didn't just eat 15 Slim Jims.
I had these, they're organic turkey jerkies.
And they're completely and totally good.
No bullshit.
No crap at it.
It's just like turkey smoked, smoked turkey links.
And that's it.
And there's nothing else.
And they're little and I can have them on the street.
Look, I don't eat, I eat Slim Jims.
Once every like five years.
Slim Jims are fine.
They're good.
They're delicious.
They taste good.
Just don't eat more than 10 of them in a row.
Don't eat 1,400 at the same time because it'll give you, it'll kill you, apparently.
By the way, if you eat 1,400 of anything at the same time, it's gonna, you'll die.
You're gonna die.
You could eat 1,400 bags of kale and you're dead.
You could eat 1,400 grams of salt.
Yeah, any 1,400 of anything will kill you.
1,400 pieces of rice.
That's true.
You're right.
But actually, that's a lot though.
How much, wait, how much, how much rice is in a bag of rice?
How many grains of rice are in a bag?
Probably not that many.
One pound of rice is 7,000 grains.
All right, well, there you go.
You could eat 1,400 rice pellets and be fine.
Going up.
All right, let's go.
Let's do it.
I have a good build.
We're gonna, we're gonna totally own this.
Change of scenery at least.
What are we, what about, I'm not gonna say that.
Pomegranate, perfect.
Looks big.
Look bigger than usual.
Don't, no jokes, play.
Trying to beat the game tonight.
Don't make like a funny remark.
Oh, funny.
Idiot.
Oh, by the way, when I was downstairs, I was getting the jerky.
I started laughing about like the 35-year-old like meme guy.
I just like thought about his sentence.
I was like, holy shit, that was like so fucking mean.
I wonder if that person's still here.
There it is again.
Attack damage.
Or, no, so, or, no, that's 14%.
That, no, no, no, this is better.
This is straight up better than this one.
I could get, yes, Hermes is gonna bail us out here.
We're gonna get bailed out by Hermes.
He's gonna give us like 30% faster attack speed or something crazy.
We're gonna get like a legendary from him.
Can't wait.
I don't even have, I don't even have a cast yet.
All right, we gotta, I gotta figure that out.
We don't have, there's no cast.
Oh, shit.
Taking way too much damage right now and I'm not happy about it.
Please play something else so I can watch.
I don't want spoilers.
Um, shit, what do we do?
I don't know, man.
I don't know what to do.
It's too good to not take every time.
That's very good.
For 10 seconds, but I just always dash.
Always dash.
It's always dash.
It is every time.
Don't have enough money to do much in the shop.
So I'm gonna go hard mode and get more Aphrodite bonus combo duo double barbecue bacon bunker burger.
All right, Aphrodite.
What is it now?
Your weak effects are more potent.
Weak damage reduction 10%.
Victim deals at least 30.
It's gonna be 40% less damage now.
But, uh, am I just gonna be a one-button Barry?
I guess so.
I forgot you were in the game.
It's been a while.
Get away.
Oh, that's the thing that hits me.
Are you really hitting me?
Come on, just bully this guy.
One shot.
There it is.
Your health, your health, your health.
Cry.
Cry?
Why are you saying the cry?
You guys are crazed.
Only 2%.
Damn it.
Now I kind of wish I took the special from the last one.
This can be upgraded though, right?
That can be upgraded.
Probably like 5% or 6%.
This is interesting.
I need to take the health, I think.
It's getting bad.
Well, thank you.
How much more jerky do I have?
I want extra jerky.
Did I see the Power Stone news?
I did not.
What would do better with this build?
Ares or Dionysus?
Probably Ares.
Hope I can do it.
Wait, I don't get my ass kicked.
Oh, God.
This is not good.
Not good.
Holy shit.
Come on, get over here so I don't...
Get closer.
Even closer than that, please.
Closer than that, please.
Get closer than that.
I can't hit...
I don't want to die here.
Yes.
Didn't die.
Coachcraft, what can you do?
Three is, I mean...
Does that include bosses?
And does it stack?
Capcom's making a new Power Stone game?
Then that's what I want.
The act of sorcery often ends in an untimely death.
That's pretty awesome.
Took him long enough.
I took him like 25 years to do that.
So some are able to perfect the trade.
And take up permanent residence elsewhere.
I'm sure the witch's circle will reconvene soon enough.
Anybody see an urn that I can break or something?
Or health or treasure or anything?
Tell you something funny, funny man.
No.
Huh.
That was a slow one.
That was like a I'm just pressing it down and letting it go because you told me to.
Must be Uridice.
Oh, okay.
This is good.
I can upgrade the crit one maybe.
Uridice, how can you cook so much with all the searing heat around these parts?
Has it been magma flooded like this all the time?
Say something unfunny now.
No, you got your one guy moment.
You're not getting another one.
The searing heat?
I'm dead, your royal majesty.
Searing is just a cooking technique to me.
Don't need to sleep either.
I can just keep cooking up a storm.
It's not so bad.
Love up to four random boons get a level.
Two random boons are upgraded to the next rarity.
We just have to pray that it's...
Wait a minute.
I only have two.
I only have two boons.
I have five?
I do?
Look it on the left side of the screen though.
I don't know I only have two?
Up to two could mean just one.
You have eight.
Okay, it's either that one or I level it up.
I'm going for it.
Two random boons get upgraded.
One, two, three.
They get it?
One of those is legendary.
Oh, that's crazy.
What?
But that's good though.
That's good.
I need health though.
It's straight up more damage across the board.
Yeah, that was worth it.
Good dice roll.
No health.
I have to be so careful.
All right.
Don't blow this.
I'm going to get some health right here.
All right, let's go.
Whoa.
Burn.
Burn him.
Burn this thing.
Get out of the fire.
I can't hurt you.
Whoa.
Wowee.
Wow.
Kill these little shits.
Didn't even take a single lick of damage.
I mean, at this point, I think I have to hope for health in the shop.
Pomegranate's good, but I need to be sure.
And nice work.
Excellent, excellent, excellent.
That's very good.
I'll take it.
Time for the boss.
I wish I could afford all this, but I can't.
75 health is not good for where I am in the game right now.
It really isn't.
I need like 100 plus.
Use the call at maximum.
I'm going to try to this time.
I still don't have a cast.
This is absolutely mutilating though.
We just got a bully.
We got a bully the second they come up.
It's bully.
Absolute bully.
Careful.
He's different.
You notice that?
He's like got different stuff.
What's going on?
Why is he back there like that?
Come on.
Jesus.
Don't use it yet.
Don't use it.
No, don't use it.
All right, now use it now.
Watch this.
I'm going to kill them one shot.
Goodbye.
Something for the mirror.
And it's full health.
So what did we learn today?
We learned that during a boss fight, no matter what,
wait until you are at full.
So my idea here is when we get to Hades,
don't even use it during the entire first encounter.
Once the second encounter goes through, kill Hades in one shot.
Once I get through phase one.
That should be.
This should be.
And I put that in quotes.
This should be the one.
We'll see.
I'll save my money.
The money needs to be saved because we're at the last area.
Make sure you hold it.
Wait a second so you don't waste it on iframes.
Yeah, that's why I held it there too.
I'm going to give it a full one or two seconds.
And I don't want him to disappear.
He goes invisible sometimes.
I got one more zone here.
And I've still got lots of upgrades to do.
Like, all right, it's time.
I need max HP.
This is terrible.
This is actually awful.
What the hell is that?
I might actually be in a little bit of trouble.
This is taking a long time.
WM1 gameplay.
Use your cast.
I don't have one.
It's just dumpy.
Always hammer.
I'm not fooling around here.
I'm not fooling around.
Don't crash on me.
I mean, don't actually don't do that.
It's like, true.
Fuck.
All right.
What was I swinging?
I was swinging at the wall.
Whatever.
This is not a melee place.
Let's see.
After your special hits, your next two attacks deal 80% more damage.
That's unbelievable.
Your ball rush gains power, it does 500% damage.
So now that gives me a reason to use my special.
Roll the Captain America shield.
Get in.
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
My shield grows stronger.
Gold earned.
Five gold in there.
That's horrible.
I don't have enough for anything in the shop.
So I'm going to go money.
Where are the enemies?
Hello?
Where are they?
Bad place to fight is those guys on the bridge.
Who else?
Oh, he's just hiding.
Will you come out of hiding, please?
Now I got enough money to really mess around.
Artemis, for sure.
Or I could get the lightning jump thing.
I don't want to get any projectiles.
Just kill them.
Spamming.
Really?
Who is it?
All right, there's a chest in here.
Don't let me forget that.
Got to kill them faster.
Good.
There's a chest.
There, I see it.
And the shops.
Oh my god.
What do I have on now?
Wait, but no, I don't want that.
That replaces the double tap.
The critical effects deal even more damage to armor.
After you deal a crit, your foe is marked.
Yeah, in the odd event that that does happen, that's probably better.
That's all right, must be nothing.
Kill things fast, right?
Give me my money.
Wait.
I couldn't even kill these guys faster than that.
But I will take some HP.
Goodness.
Excuse me.
Holy shit, that was horrible.
Get the bombs out of here and I'll be okay.
Shitty room.
Make this motherfucker killed by his own beams.
Come up here.
What did I do that for?
All right, get hit by this.
Damn it, it didn't get hit by it.
I just freaked out.
Nice shield, asshole.
I haven't blocked in eight rooms.
Yeah, but I mean, come on, I'm trying.
I'm all offense.
Well, it looks like we're going to go left.
This guy is so good.
This guy is unbelievable.
He's so good.
His upgrades are incredible.
Don't need that this time.
Oh man, that's greedy.
It's greedy, I know, but it's damage.
It's a lot of damage.
Oh my fucking God.
They're all bow users.
Who's next?
That guy's marked.
That's what that means.
The grip.
Shut up.
I have no idea what's going on.
God damn it, man.
Where is this guy?
Did you actually come back?
You piece of shit.
Let me get in there and kill him.
Piece of shit.
You piece of fucking shit.
I hate the shield guys.
These are my least favorite enemies
in the whole game, by the way.
They take forever to fucking kill.
And then you have to kill them twice
when they come back.
Fuck these guys, they suck.
Oh my goodness.
What happened to being a shield guy?
I gave up on that.
Let's see how quickly I can-
Oh, these guys jump around so fast.
Isolate them out.
Oh, that's a pretty good idea, guys.
Nice work.
Look at all the damage you didn't take.
Yeah, I know.
Bully, bully, bully.
Don't let these two assholes get new bodies.
God damn it, he got a new fucking body.
Fuck these guys.
You actually hit me.
You're hiding behind a fucking wall.
Get out of here.
Worth enemy in the fucking game.
Shop time.
I can get them all.
This is perfect.
And it's boss time.
All right, I gotta be ready.
Kill Bull first.
I will.
I'll try.
All right.
So now I can go whack, whack.
This is just going to be a game.
Get the hell out of here.
Gold earn.
Where?
Kill the Bull.
Dodge.
Dash around.
Be careful.
Be good.
The hell did you even see that?
I have no idea.
All right, I'm ready.
Kill Bull.
Backstab Bull.
Get out.
Dodge the fire.
And save.
Do not do Artemis.
And block.
Hold on, not so fast.
Come on, get over here.
Give me a Bull.
Oh, you double fuck.
Triple fuck.
That's a triple quadruple fuck right there.
Right, huh?
I'm ready for the Bull.
Don't call me a fiend.
Damn it.
Oh, fuck.
He does, oh my god.
I'm just blowing it so bad.
Oh my god.
I keep, he does three swings.
I'm blowing it so bad.
It's just so, but hell.
He hasn't done that fucking move
the whole entire encounter.
Eat shit.
What just happened?
Don't do it.
Where's the, where's he?
Where's the Bull?
One, two.
Wait, he did three.
He didn't, what?
He didn't run into the podium.
He didn't run into the pillar.
What the fuck?
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my god.
It's a choke.
Ready to admit defeat as yet.
You block everything, you fucker.
Hold that.
Oh, shit.
They call for a friend.
I forgot about that.
Flow and steady wins the race.
The hair gets run over by a car.
Don't remember, forget that story.
Oh, oh, I don't know.
That just scared the shit out of me.
Why's he, why's he blocking?
Oh, right.
Goddess Dementor.
Okay, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Oh, he's right there.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
It's fucking so hard.
Holy shit.
Oh, no.
No, it's so hard.
I want a rematch now.
Damn it.
No.
Hey there, Doosa.
How's your endless toil treating you?
Mr. Hypnos, do you maybe think that you could, you know,
keep an eye on the procession line before Lord Hades like you were supposed to?
That's no problem.
I can definitely do that.
I'll just add it to the list.
Afro damage falls off if you don't find the right stuff.
Damn.
I thought I had it, too.
I just got caught in the purple circles.
I can give the fish to the chef.
That's cool.
Hello, Zagreus.
You look a little down.
So I was just wondering, would you perchance fancy a song right now?
Song?
I think this is important.
The lament in the blood or the argonauts?
Uh, the argonauts.
How about argonauts?
Didn't you sail with them?
Oh, fancy that one, do you?
Alas, I'm not the heart to sing it anymore.
I'm glad you like it, though.
Do I have enough to unlock the...
I don't think I do.
All right, let's listen to the shirt.
Wait, you don't know the song?
The head chef is going to want this fish.
What are your sisters up to these days, Meg?
I've not seen them around.
We're stretched a little thin, as you can see.
I have no idea what you just said.
I wasn't looking.
All I heard was, I swear to God, this is what I just heard.
I smell success.
What does that have to be?
I didn't hear anything else.
I didn't hear...
I didn't...
I couldn't understand anything.
I love this voice, though.
Whoever this voice actress is, fucking great job.
Good.
Very good.
This is my latest hole.
Oh, 20.
They're all good.
The ancient casks of wine.
It's actually kind of rare that you get a game that actually has good voice acting.
The toxic-hitting vintage they contain.
And few are still admitted to anywhere in the vicinity.
Still waiting for the fest of occasion when we'll open one of these.
Main character, too.
Zagras.
Very collected.
It's not over the top.
It's just subtle enough, and it's just interesting enough.
And he did a great job.
Actually, perfect job.
What's new?
Two keys for 20 gems.
No, thanks.
Wait.
How much is it?
Can I get a key?
Is this a psycho thing to do if I buy four keys right now?
Always use more keys.
I don't care.
So what did the fish do?
Nix must be someplace else.
Oh, the gems, right.
Okay.
Let's unlock the gloves.
But first...
I like that better.
I really do.
Let's just save the keys.
Get Death Defiance II.
I need 600...
Lopules.
This?
Oh, I just get the weapon.
Hey, pal.
Watch where you throw those bloodstone things of yours.
You drop them, you go pick them up.
You understand?
But if somebody gives you grief,
you got my permission to check one right in his eye.
I just got 5,000 bits.
50 bucks from Freakout.
Says, you missed my bits earlier, daddy.
I don't know if you've been here for a while,
but I no longer read bits during the stream,
or after the stream.
Bits are done.
Unless, of course, you give Mike that money.
Pretty much, it's all done.
I don't know what you're talking about, bud.
...since the eyes are a lot harder to hit in my experience.
3D bastard.
And you know what?
I think it's time.
I think it's time for me to say this now, too.
I think from here going out,
I don't think I'm not going to read bits anymore.
I think it's fair that way.
I think it's fair.
Because when I stopped doing the at the end of the stream bits,
the intention was for, you know,
I wanted to be able to spend more time streaming
and not time, you know, at the end of the stream.
If I have to sit here for an extra, you know,
if I'm sitting here for four, five, six hours,
and I have to get up,
and there's like an hour and a half of bits,
that's the first part, right?
The second part is,
I don't want people to think they have to give more money
now for me to read their message.
I'd rather just say it's over completely.
Because that puts a sort of dumb precedent in place.
For people to say,
well, he doesn't read anything that's 200 bits.
I just give 5,000, he'll read it.
So I don't, I don't like that precedent.
Just raise it to 200.
No, like I said previously,
I said like a week or two ago,
if you want to support this stream,
and you like what you see here,
and you like this community,
and you want to subscribe to the channel,
do that.
Nobody at this point going forward
should be giving me 50 to 100 dollars in one drop.
And people say, dude, I've been watching you for years,
like, let me give you 50 to 100 dollars right now, right?
That's not necessary.
You don't have to do that.
In fact, I don't want you to do that.
I've seen that message plenty of times.
And then, but this community subs, right?
It's like, what about community subs?
I think community subs is a little different
just because it, oh, well.
Just completely going just against everything
I was just saying, that's funny.
But anyways, first of all, let me, let me,
all right, let me get through this first.
Community subs are a little different
just because when you give a community sub,
somebody that you're giving somebody
access to the emotes and the, you know,
ads that I, wait, that doesn't,
that's not even real anymore, is it?
You're giving them the sub,
they can use the emotes,
and they can, you know, sub only mode,
that's available, right?
So you get those perks,
you're giving those perks to somebody.
So it's not just me that just gets,
you know, money and that's it.
When you give a community subs,
you're giving somebody that might not be able to
potentially afford to pay $5 a month,
that, hey, you can use the emotes.
So rather than just be just accepting 500,
you know, 1,000, 550 bucks, 100 bucks,
200 bucks from one person,
I just, I think it's more fair that way.
Just admit it's because you can't read.
It's been an elaborate scheme this whole time.
If it's more stuff to use channel points on,
I want to turn on that like gambling thing,
like the predict thing.
I don't have access to that.
I wish I did, but I don't have,
I don't think I have access to it.
I looked in my thing.
I don't have it.
It won't give it to me.
All right, let's open it.
I don't care.
What is it?
I want, that's what I saved it up for.
Old?
A rising cutter?
Dash strike.
Dash uppercut.
It's a monk build.
So there is no, all right, that's going to be weird.
I'll give him a try.
I'm probably going to get my ass kicked.
But let's go over these subs.
Just really quickly, because there was a lot.
Addy cake gave 20 community subs,
which is a ton of money.
That is more than I even said to not give.
Right?
Thanks to the huge amount of money and the community subs.
Labster five community subs.
Nondescript civilian 25 community subs,
which is a shitload of money.
Litigation.
Thanks for five subs.
And destroy.
Destroy, dude.
You can play with boppities in this game.
Go left.
It's a secret area, but he's still reading them.
Well, community subs.
I feel like acknowledging community subs is like,
oh, look, some of you got subs.
I don't know.
What do you think?
But then that brings in the, wait,
but I could just give a bunch of money
if I give a shitload of subs, right?
Yeah, I don't know.
I just don't want people to think they have to give
an absolute shitload of money to get me to read it
when that was not the intention in the first place.
Just acknowledge nothing.
Just harvest money.
I'll try the fists.
I feel like this is boring.
My blade.
Not the fists.
Like what I've been doing.
Just the meta of take coin purse, replace with tooth.
I feel like I, is this boring?
At just 25 health, but they're not.
But this upgrades.
If I use this enough, this is okay.
Does this eventually get up to 75 health?
That's a huge deal.
50.
That's a big deal.
Level up all your trinkets of a lad variety
and you will understand what you want from it.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's try these.
But I'll try those after I put on, I want the money.
It's all about the money.
It's a good start.
Your attack becomes a three hit sequence and each deals 40 base damage.
You are sturdy while you use your attack.
You take 30% less damage.
Your actions cannot be interrupted.
Oh, three is really good too.
Three is insane.
It just breaks any armor instantly.
They seem like they're kind of fun,
but the holding down X thing is probably going to mess me up.
I feel like Little Mac when I have these on.
I love the dash uppercut.
It's awesome.
Try getting Artemis.
The fast firing is awesome.
Yeah, that's true.
What about Zeus?
Zeus like the chain lightning going chain, chain, chain, chain, chain, chain.
So now I understand why, okay.
Oh, you beat the game.
No, it's not even what I'm doing.
That's like saying that if you beat mom's foot,
then you win Binding of Isaac.
That's five more subs.
What?
Oh, well.
25?
All right, I got to shut up.
Let's get something good.
Why do I owe subs?
Because I signed a contract yesterday
when I first started playing the game
that I would not reference Binding of Isaac,
World of Warcraft, Dark Souls,
and I forget the last game.
I seriously don't know what it was.
I forget what it was.
What was the fourth one?
Hearthstone.
Right, right.
So if I've referenced those...
No, that's not fair.
We're in a timeout right now.
This is a pause.
I'm...
No, that's not what this is.
We are not referencing that in the game.
We are referencing the fact that that was what the con...
I'm stating what the contract is.
And the person that just asked that,
they're probably like, what the...
Who fucking cares?
Like, what are you talking about?
I have a tendency on this stream
to always call back to those four games
all the time, like every stream.
So I'm trying to give myself a...
I'm trying to get away from it.
Your special causes a bolt...
Lightning Bolt to strike nearby foes.
That looks pretty good.
Your dash causes a lightning bolt to...
Ah, that's actually good too.
I like this one.
Ooh, all right.
Water or fire?
How about Poseidon?
Pretty good.
Uppercut.
There's a pretty heavy reach on this thing too.
Do you know why I like this game so much?
And why I'm very into playing this game?
It's mainly because it has actually been a very long time
since a game like this has come out
that I've actually enjoyed playing.
This rogue-like items and upgrades room to room.
It's been a while.
No, not any video game.
I'm just saying just in general, like the genre.
It's been a while since the genre has had a game like this that I enjoyed.
That's good.
Well, I need a dash.
This is just safety.
Fish.
Play Transistor.
It's even better.
I was told that Transistor is not like this.
Is that correct?
See that shield break?
Transistor is not like this, but it's still very good.
A Cylastrocyon.
Cylastrocyon.
That's what I said.
The next boon you find has an upgraded rarity.
I like that.
Well, we're getting the key.
Given that one took you 50 tries.
Is that good?
That's great.
This game's good.
It's very good.
Hey, remember when I took a point up?
Maybe I went at a 91.
Oh, the point came back.
Plus two keys.
Is better fish?
Oh, that's cool.
Fists are cool.
You just absolutely shred people with the armor crusher.
I did Aphrodite last time and it didn't work out.
Look at that shred.
Nice.
250 damage.
That's pretty good.
See the urn?
Oh, I want to play this again.
I don't think I'm going to beat it tonight.
But I hope I'm going to play.
Here we go.
Here you go.
Ready?
Here's the plan.
Plan is tomorrow we're going to change it up.
Tomorrow's chat's choice.
I'm not done tonight.
I'm just saying.
Tomorrow's chat's choice.
So pre-stream chat tomorrow like an hour before the stream.
Somewhere around like two o'clock or so.
One to two o'clock.
We will play something else.
Then after chat's choice tomorrow.
We're going to go back to this and I'm going to play this again.
Because I'm into it.
And it's been it's been a pretty long time since I've been into a game like this.
So I'm playing it.
He's addicted.
Yes, I am.
All right.
Should I get the cast?
Oh, that one.
And keys.
He doesn't like Noita.
No, I just I'm not.
I it couldn't it didn't click with me.
This skill based wise.
I was like you may as well just put a I've had a paper bag on my head that whole time.
That terraria style mouse kind of aiming keyboard side scrolling.
I'm not I'm not very good at it.
Let's get hit.
Is there an error here?
It is.
This game feels like right up my alley.
I just I like playing it.
That's not to say I didn't like playing Noita.
Just this is much more in my wheelhouse of video games that I like to play.
I only got two gigs of RAM.
That's punch.
Yeah, punch is like 200 megabytes.
Dash is probably 1000 megabytes because you need to get that correctly.
And then special is 200 megabytes.
And then move.
Don't get hit by stuff is another probably 800 megabytes.
If I may be so bold, your highness, I was wondering what brings you back around this way again.
Same story as last time.
He's out of space.
Look, I have to level with you, Sisyphus.
I'm leaving the house quite enough.
You understand.
I'm sure I'm going to the surface.
Data leak.
Yeah, there's like some kind of acid leaking out of the motherboard.
If it wasn't you yourself proposing it, I'd like to call it madness, truth be told.
Though you're just mad enough to pull it off.
Oh, hey, I hope you make it.
Good fortune out there.
Okay.
Let's give him money.
Or no.
Yeah, give him money.
My dear.
Cheers, mate.
I have any.
Can I gift you?
That's it.
I don't have any nectar.
Oh, that's too bad.
What is it now?
Let's see your relatives upon Olympus get you out of this.
Survive for 45 seconds.
That move is so good.
Hope I can upgrade that move, too.
That's the best part.
Lightning, lightning, lightning.
Five, four, three, two, one, kill them.
That's enough.
Peace and quiet.
From a quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
What is that?
Is that a lizard?
It's a lizard.
That's a pretty cool lizard.
Wait, what day is it today?
This is October?
Oh, no, it's November.
Oh, oh, shit, look at this.
Lizard of days past.
That's a cool lizard.
Or Gecko.
That's just level two.
Probably three.
Three or one.
Two?
Three is more damage than all of them.
Oh, I guess because it's a double.
Right, I forgot.
I can dash twice.
So far, so good.
Let's just hope it scales.
We should play Gex tomorrow.
I played Gex already and it was dog shit.
Oops.
I should, I, all right, you can tell I'm a little...
It was okay.
It was good.
Hi, Mies.
Kind of swiftness, travel,
bringing souls of the departed to your boat.
Whatever.
He calls you his professional associate.
You and he, you've been working together for a while, haven't you?
He's high?
No, I'm not.
Well, I can get it all.
Take it all.
Take this one.
Aphrodite.
I want to give you more gifts.
I want, you, you can be,
there's romance in this game?
That's good.
Wait, Aphrodite's call.
Your call fire is a seeking projectile that inflicts charm.
For a short time, the victim fights for you
with greater strength and speed.
Oh, this thing is 200, 2500 damage?
Does it work on bosses?
It does.
This is almost too good to ignore though.
But I'm going to make the wrong call
and I'm going to get the call.
Damage is only if it's max.
Yeah, but how much more strength and damage do they do?
Says when they're charmed, they do more damage, right?
Shitload.
After using call, gain dodge, chance,
dodge chance, and move speed.
After you dash, briefly become sturdy and move 100% faster.
Yeah, it's that one.
It's not very long though, is it?
All right, let's go kill Meg for like a thousandth time.
She's different.
What is this?
Is this Tissyphone?
Not Meg anymore?
Is it because I killed Meg too many times?
Well, let's go.
We have a new moveset too.
Is it poison?
Looks like poison.
Is there a poison cure here?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Why do I have hard Meg?
I don't want to fight hard Meg.
I want the easy Meg that I kill easily.
Oh, she's my friend.
Oh, we have a new moveset.
This is not fair.
I don't know what the hell.
What?
What the hell's going on?
Beat her up while she's charmed.
Oh, it kind of works.
Well, where'd you go?
There you are.
Oh, fuck you, Tissyphone.
What the fuck?
What the hell is going on here?
This is such a shitty area to fight somebody.
Why are you so much harder than the other one?
What?
I'm dead?
Well, that was unexpected.
The symphony.
Can't beat Tissyphone.
This is where I pick grenade up.
Put grenade in my phone pin.
Just lob it over there and just go like this.
New stuff, hold on.
Now, if only Twitch would do this.
That would be great.
This musician need not be so indulged.
Oh, so what does it do?
You are home.
Listen.
Some new music.
Does it spend a diamond on the sound test options menu?
I don't have two.
Nix, sometimes I get the impression the Olympians look down on those of us born at the Underworld.
Is that my imagination or what do you make of it?
Gods of Mount Olympus tend to think themselves above us, child.
Or so your father often likes to say.
You have to buy the rest for more diamonds.
Well, there's your end game, Sync.
Anything new in here?
Yes, there is.
What do you got?
Here's what I caught.
30 bucks.
I think that's worth 100.
How many keys do I have?
Okay, I need to buy.
Ambers may contain 10 gold.
What a waste of 60 gems unless that's the final thing you ever upgrade.
I need keys.
Too good to pass up.
Somebody said you need to feed her some bug snacks.
There she goes again.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Go back to, go back to Undertale, Temmie.
I just almost ended my stream.
I need four more keys.
Thanks.
Achilles or Riot?
I don't know where he is.
Where's Achilles?
Where is he?
He's not in his usual hiding place.
Oh, there he is.
You're much too modest, Lord Achilles, for someone with such a number of heroic deeds
and glorious decapitations to his name.
You ought to be more like ever boastful Sagrius and talk it up some more.
Oh, fear not, Orpheus.
I was quite boastful of my day.
Would you look at where it got me?
Besides, I've not the imagination to come up with tails as tall as those of Achilles.
Achilles or we Trojan horse you?
So you're all gonna deliver a horsey to my house and go in it?
And then I'm gonna open the door and you guys are gonna all come in and murder me?
Okay.
Well, I'm here.
I'm talking to Achilles.
Ow.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Achilles or riot.
We did it.
No use.
Talk to dad.
So tell me something, father, if you please.
Since we're more candid lately in regard to matters of my birthright here and all.
Did you and mother how to put this?
Any brothers or sisters I should know about?
I thought I told you never to invoke her here.
Bastard kin.
It was like a ace attorney.
Why would you think I'd risk another such as you?
Sure.
That's fair enough.
It's just not all such things occur.
I almost said attorney's law.
From tales of your brothers and so forth.
Blast to my brothers and blast you as well.
All those who know me know I have no heir.
You could not rise to the occasion if you tried.
And there is no one else.
You have only me and I have only.
Those these expensive gems and stuff down here.
But what do you buy with it?
This is one weird ghost to the trade.
What do you even buy with this stuff?
Look at all these gems and jewels.
I mean, there's no Denny's here.
There's no mall.
What are you supposed to do with this money?
Gotta say, you're really getting somewhere, boy.
Oh, I'm pretty impressed here.
And they don't even pay me to do that.
I'm just supposed to stand around.
Paying for the Denny's breakfast combo with gems.
Yeah.
What else are you going to do with this stuff?
He's wearing it all over him.
And money doesn't really have value anymore, guys, when you have a belt.
That the belt buckle is a golden jeweled skull.
And inside of the skull's mouth is other skull jeweled rubies and stuff.
He's wearing a championship belt of money.
He doesn't really think he cares about gems anymore.
It's a decoration.
Oh, this is a gun.
That's a Falco gun.
What is that?
It's eight.
Oh, I need to get it right now.
I want it now.
Let's see here.
Oh, right.
I died because I threw at the end there.
All right.
I'm going to keep the purse on.
But we're going up.
Oh, time.
My first win was with the gun.
That works.
What is the explosive shot?
It takes us such a long time.
Does the explosion hurt me?
Let's find out.
It doesn't.
Okay.
I gotta get that timing right.
300% damage is insane.
Yeah.
I don't care how long it takes.
The bosses, though.
Oh, this might not be very good.
If I get chaos with this, then.
Somebody said chaos?
All right.
This is important.
This is really important.
If I can get this to be insane, this could be huge.
Let's look over at the image.
All your attacks lose 50% damage,
but you get a slice of bologna.
It's just still on my other monitor.
I mean, it's one.
Can't earn money.
Who cares?
This is the run.
Don't throw.
I'm going to try.
Don't need a full charge.
That's important to understand here.
Full charge is not even necessary.
Just land it.
200.
I love the charge sound.
Like, I got hurt?
How would I get hurt by?
I don't have enough to wait.
I can get the health upgrade.
Wait, is it another chaos?
Did I miss a chaos?
Shut up.
No, I didn't.
Did I?
No.
Oh, my God.
You scared me so much.
Oh, my chest is on fire.
Guys, I don't understand.
I don't know what's happening to me.
Stop it.
I got to relax.
Thank you.
This is really awesome.
Just need a ton more damage on this.
And this will be unbeatable.
The timing is a little weird, though.
Oh, come on.
Really?
Hey, Artemis of the blue.
You're of the grain in this game,
but thank you for the five subs.
Okay, your special is hangover,
which I like,
because I can just kind of fan that.
The cast lobs a large explosive
that bursts into festive fog.
This is just a stun.
Yeah, let me try that.
To my health.
It's a very long cast.
It hurts me.
Okay, no, it doesn't.
And aim it.
Okay, that's not bad.
And when they're stunned, I can blow them up.
That's great.
That works out pretty well.
More health.
Thank you.
Any fish?
Do not see fish.
That actually works really not.
It's all right.
Oh, yeah, the bow is great.
Bow and shield are my favorites.
Defeater.
Defeater boons.
Puke.
So this is a good combo here,
because you can,
I could do that and the stun
and then blow them all up.
So it's like you go wham, wham, boom.
Or you go wham, wham, boom.
Remember, I just watched a TikTok
of somebody making soap.
Probably cool.
I don't know.
The ACDC freak gave five subs.
Thank you, ACDC freak.
Didn't they just come up with a new album?
Didn't ACDC just release a new album?
And it's good.
Don't they sound exactly the same, too?
They haven't changed at all.
How do they still sound the same?
Aren't they 80?
It's pretty good.
It's good.
It's very good.
There's a chest in here, too.
Don't let me forget that.
10.
This chest is for up to 100 gold.
Just combo the hell out of me.
Transgressions are not tolerable.
Slay foes quickly.
Oh, I could have killed them
that much faster than that.
Who's going to clean all this up?
You have to have an insane build
to be able to kill things in a second.
Missed anything?
Me, me, me.
What are you doing?
Survive.
Uh-oh.
Come on, then.
I have the explosive.
I'm good.
Just keep him on that bridge.
Oh, shit.
Watch out.
Oh, right at the end, really.
It's a good strategy, too.
That's that.
Did I get to the final boss yet?
Yes.
A couple of times.
I've gotten the final...
Well, I don't know if it's the final boss,
but I've gotten the...
I got the final boss
of the story mode or whatever
down to the second phase.
One more key gets me a gun.
It does.
What's for sale?
I want that.
300 damage.
Tringers.
Tringers?
Oh, shit.
For a second, I thought I had a different move.
What's it hitting?
Where's the treasure trove?
Did they say the treasure trove was going to spawn?
I don't see a treasure.
Oh, I do.
100 gold.
Let's go.
Give me a good spawn.
You truly are an idiot, aren't you?
Die.
71.
What did I just get?
20 gold return.
21 gold return.
And I lost five health or something.
Not worth it.
Use this.
If you dash shoots a gust,
10 stacks of chill cause a blast clearing the effect.
While all foals are chilled,
they are 10% slower and decayed.
K damage.
So I just...
And they all get chilled anyways.
Sounds good.
It just adds to the potential.
All right.
Am I going to get the harder mech again?
Damn.
Wait.
This is a different mech.
How many mechs are there?
Somebody said step on me.
First thing you write.
It's just...
Oh, who's this new god?
Who's this new character?
Oh, I don't know.
Step on me.
What's this rage?
She's got a rage meter?
What exactly does that mean?
Well, you're not nearly as bad as the other one.
Can I stop her from doing that?
She's impervious.
These traps have blended in with the ground.
They're the same...
I've only taken damage from the fucking traps on the ground.
I was stepping on the area that was...
I was avoiding the actual ground.
I got plenty of health.
I'm fine.
Good build.
I'm going to step on me.
Can I ask you guys what element I was?
What element am I?
I know what animal I am.
One of those fucking parrots that you see at the pet store.
Not even the cool one.
The one that just yells out the thing that you just said.
Like a parakeet.
Yeah, it makes sense, right?
Look at half of my mannerisms.
Just like, step on me, bro.
Just say the shit that you're writing.
Figured it out.
All right.
It's time to change to...
I feel like this is a good run, though.
The meta is too good.
The run is too good.
I can't change it.
Don't stop hating yourself.
I don't hate myself.
Parrots are incredibly intelligent.
They're really cool and they're really fun.
I didn't say parrots were stupid.
They're bad.
I'm keeping the tooth on.
This run's good.
If it's going to happen tonight, it's going to happen right now.
Why is it locked?
Let me back in there.
They lock it after you equip something?
That's unfortunate.
What up, my fellow germites?
You forgot to add the A.
It's germimites.
So you can't just get free money from the purse.
Oh, that makes sense.
Oh, my granite.
It's a good build.
And I got good health, too.
This is going to work out pretty well, I think.
What do we got?
Your special is stronger and does chill.
Your cast lobs a large explosive that bursts into festive fog.
Which one?
One or two.
They're both good.
Although this is probably better.
Pretty good lobs lock.
Can I interact with this?
Money or Poseidon?
Probably Poseidon.
Get away from me.
Get away.
It's good.
It's working out pretty well.
Dad, I'm coming for you.
There's a certain chill about you.
Received an ice cold blessing courtesy of Elder Goddess Demeter, correct?
Now, firstly, I think water's best in liquid form, but who am I to judge?
Push high.
Attack deals more damage and knocks people away.
That's just that's just great.
Here is that's good, too, though.
It's more insane explosive damage or have a call that makes me invincible.
Or just a huge amount of rewards.
These are all good.
I don't know what to do.
And I'm taking the call.
Fishing time then.
Too early.
How is that too early?
Just bobbed and I hit.
That was late, if anything.
How was it too early?
You guys are jumpy.
Bow is best.
Bow and shield.
I like bow better than shield.
I keep I know I change my mind every single run, but I mean, I love the bow.
Just does it for me.
Perfect.
Dad, every weapon is good.
You're bad.
Oh, arguments.
Fighting in the chat room.
That's not a bad trade.
I'll just take that's a 20.
That's nothing for 10 gems.
I know people are going to say, look, you could have.
I couldn't have bought it.
I couldn't afford it.
Aphrodite.
Time for the chat bar fight.
Crush me.
Where am I?
I just stopped freaking out.
Did you go into the lava?
What happened?
I kind of want to give Aphrodite another gift.
I'm going to do it.
My lady Aphrodite, if not for our acquaintance, I'm certain that my days or nights would be
much drearier indeed.
Dearest, such a wonderfully thoughtful gift for me.
I love it and I would be lying if I said you shouldn't have.
Romancing Aphrodite.
I got a, oh, another one.
Wait, how much more stuff do you want?
One, two, three, four more hearts.
And then you talk two more hearts and you'll talk to me again.
What?
You know how hard these are to get?
Air is beautiful and brisk.
The garden's lush.
The feasting plentiful.
Why, it must be the opposite of everything to which you are accustomed.
That's not bad.
I mean, that's just 13%.
Why not just do it?
Revenge damage is good too.
Do it.
Pomegranate time.
Grow up, Jerma.
I'm what?
I'm pretending to romance a woman in a video game that has like a romance feature.
I'm just playing the video game.
This is the intended feature of the video game.
Get over here.
Into the water with you.
Oh, shit.
Mini Medusa heads.
Shit.
Wasn't fast enough.
What's going on with my screen?
You see that?
That's weird.
What's going on with my screen?
It's like going black for a second.
It's like dipping black, dipping black, dipping black.
It's a smoke effect?
Oh.
Even more damage from the fog.
Super call.
Or a 16% reduction in all damage.
Yeah, it's between these two, I think.
I, yeah.
I gotta get better at hitting it though.
Ooh, Aphrodite and Dionysus.
Or Pomegranate.
Yeah, don't here.
We want upgrades.
Cast ignores armor.
Yeah, that's good too.
Who's favorite to choose?
Yeah, man.
You know what it's all about.
Using a fountain restores all your health
and gives you bonus damage per fountain.
That's good stuff.
Surely there's no way that could have been
one of the wiser choices that you've lately made.
Lady Aphrodite, I'm sorry.
My dear Aphrodite.
I'm so sorry, my queen.
I'm so sorry.
I'll never do it again, I swear.
Get away from me.
Stop doing the hearts thing.
Get away.
Get out of here.
Into the fire.
Cool.
Didn't take that much damage for a double.
I'm happy with that.
Just do not anger me again
or I'm gonna kill you there myself.
Bro, just accept her love, bro.
Calm down.
And it's a heart that flies out now.
I don't have enough money to buy maybe health.
Maybe try to get attack speed with Murmys?
Yeah, this is, this is free.
This is a fountain?
Why is this just for free?
All too quickly for you, boss.
Way nice as it doesn't.
As you're probably aware,
there's quite a feast though.
Move speed.
Your special is faster.
Hmm, that's just, yeah.
And here we go.
Just move a little bit faster.
That's fine.
All right, let's fight this boss.
No one gets hurt.
I mean, look at this damage.
It's unheard of.
Hey, bring out your little friends.
Shit, I missed it.
Just long shot it, man.
And here we go.
Okay, now let's do the, get out.
Throw yourself.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
I'm taking a lot of damage.
This is bad.
Okay, we're good.
Oh, I want to end it on a, hi.
He's going to choke?
No, I'm not going to choke.
Choking is for the third boss fight,
not for the second one.
For safekeeping.
Did I miss anything?
Fountain, this is a full heal
and it's plus 3% damage permanently, right?
That's pretty awesome.
That's pretty good too.
I'm only 20 gold?
I'm taking it.
Save the money, save the money.
Well, I'm good.
Yeah, whatever happens here,
this is going to be the end.
I'll see you tomorrow for chat's choice after this.
We'll go back to this.
Maybe I'll just beat it.
You know, let's just, let's just beat it today.
Let's beat it right now.
This is the run to beat it.
I'm going to go for it.
Hammer.
Why did I, that was a weird throw.
I'm having so much fun.
Oh, all righty then.
How far away is far away?
Because that will kill almost every single enemy
in the game in one hit.
What do I do?
Hey, my mouse is being stupid.
I mean, it's that.
Your attack fire is two shots side by side,
but reduce damage only applies to distant foes, right?
But how far is distant?
Reduce range.
But okay, so this is double damage.
This is more, this is two times.
I made my decision.
That's it.
Holy shit.
It's two.
That's going to be insane though.
You want to know the best part about this?
I don't even have to worry about charging the whole thing.
Just get it and move around.
Land the perfect shot.
Land the shot you know you can land.
Get out.
Test it.
Am I there?
No, not you there.
You there.
I don't, I'm overwhelmed.
Useless.
You there.
That's all right.
I don't know why I think that's funny.
You up?
All right.
I got to play.
You up.
That's 500 damage, man.
Holy shit.
That's 700 damage.
You ain't got nothing.
This is game over if I don't act like a dumb ass.
Hey, you there.
Are you there, man?
Hey, don't.
This is a super boss killer.
And we have another opportunity for Hermes for increased super damage speed.
Oh, shit.
That was bad.
This is so good.
I can't blow this.
Get out of here, you little mutant.
All right, Hermes.
Bail me out here.
You attack it 10% faster.
Charge more.
Got to survive, man.
I got to survive, man.
I've got to survive, man.
I have to.
I don't the attack speed.
Is that really that big of a deal?
Because it's not charge speed.
It's just how fast I draw the bow, right?
But that's OK.
10% is nothing.
Having the third dash is a major deal.
Don't worry.
We're going to get something else right here.
Look, it's already OK.
Sidon's aid got leveled up to level one.
There we go.
Your dash damage disposed in an area.
Your boons with knock away also rupture.
Victim takes damage while moving.
Does the explosive count as a rupture?
I need a dash.
Yeah, I need it.
It's true.
I do need a dash.
You're right.
OK.
Fish?
No.
Dementor.
That's so much fucking damage, man.
It really is.
It's so much damage.
Hey, where'd you come from?
All right.
This is bad.
Hold on.
Get that shit off my body.
Who else?
It took a lot of damage for that.
Like 10 chill stacks causes a blast effect.
Any health.
Yeah, it's time.
I need this.
While you have no...
What?
So throw out the...
Oh, no, that's not good.
Because that doesn't synergize with what I have.
Doesn't synergize with what I have.
Don't I have the thing?
Because look.
It's just going to recharge it in three seconds.
I have it again.
I mean, if I had the other one right,
I'd throw it out and I just don't use the casting again.
I can go around and do more damage.
So I'm just going to get the crystal back.
OK.
I'm going to say money because I can get a boon before the boss.
Sidon is better.
Sure.
Well, that was a really good choice.
I don't know how you guys knew that was going to happen,
but I just got more damage.
How did you guys know that was going to happen?
I'm the dev.
Oh, OK.
That's one.
Slamming foes into barriers.
I don't even know how...
How do I do that?
How do I slam?
If I dash into them?
Three.
It's too late for one.
I'm just going to...
OK.
I'm pulling slot machine.
Good.
You've got breakfast wraps.
Pretty pog if you ask me.
Good timing on that one.
This shit bounces around.
Not fair.
I would call that a clean room.
I'd call that a clean room.
Even more health.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eat shit.
Don't let the little bulbs get away.
Wait, just let them come to me.
Let them come to me.
What's the point?
Health is good with this build.
Yeah, it is.
Ow.
Give me a break.
You're bouncing this shit everywhere.
You're not even trying.
You're just spamming in random directions.
Where are you?
This is the first time I've ever had 200 health.
All right.
Do I want...
Up the shop.
Chaos?
Where?
You lying?
Oh.
All right.
This is it.
Here we go.
I mean, there I have to take three.
That's just me.
I just...
When it's out, I do more damage.
Take this too.
Why not?
Boost to the boon.
Frost flourish.
Got upgraded.
What does that one do?
Who the hell is it?
Oh, it's wicked good.
It's wicked good.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm going to kill that Minotaur.
I'm going to rip his eyes out.
You seek to break through to but you shall leave.
All the equivalent of it here in the splendors of Elysium.
I'm spamming the bomb.
I'm going to hit B over and over again.
Can you leave me with little choice but to make you...
One, two, three.
Go, go, go.
Ow.
That did a little damage to him.
Come here.
Where is he?
Where's the bull?
Ow, that hurt.
You fucker.
Oh, good.
Somebody just made me laugh.
Somebody just fucking...
Why did I look at chat?
All right.
This is it.
You block everything.
You fucking punk.
Hey.
And I got full health and two revives.
Dad, I'm coming for you now.
I'm coming for dad.
I might even have to break out something really important for dad.
We'll see.
I'm going to have to whip out something for dad.
No, I'm something else.
I'm going to have to whip out...
I'm going to have to whip out something for you, dad.
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop it.
Oh, my God.
Why did I say it like that?
I'm just going to buy this.
It's 15 bucks.
All right.
Let's go.
I got to be careful.
I'm going to save Poseidon's explosive.
Why would you waste your money on that?
Doesn't that work at dad?
He did that.
What?
Did you swap out the first already?
I hope so.
Yeah.
I'm ready.
No fish in here, right?
Oops.
He just even told me.
All right.
What do we got?
We've got pomegranates, Poseidon.
Wait, there's a fish in this last...
Okay.
I don't want to screw this up.
So you can get faked out here.
So wait for the ding.
So we're going with...
We're going with...
Okay.
That was...
I kind of had no idea what the hell was going on in this room.
Good.
Come on.
This is the one.
This is the run.
Oh, shit.
Final room.
Holy shit.
Those things fall down.
No poison.
Don't get touched by that shit.
Who's left?
Oh, you.
Ding.
225 health.
And a shop.
No, no, no.
None of it.
Does it earn?
I don't have enough money.
All right.
Frozen time.
This is so good.
It's so much damage.
It's so wonderful.
An itchy nose for a second.
Sorry.
I had to just rip my hand up and just smack into the microphone.
Almost got hit.
Very close.
700.
And out.
Don't get poisoned.
Poison.
I'm poisoned.
Where's the cure?
I can feel it in my loins right now.
Don't say that yet.
Don't say that.
What's going on?
You are so uptight now.
Just ease up a little there.
Let's see what we can do.
Are you gonna duo?
You're...
Wait.
Your cast blasts an area with freezing fog that inflicts chill.
Plus 30% more damage.
Wait, what?
What?
Teamwork.
And it sticks around for a while too.
Okay.
All right.
This should be...
I should make out pretty well here.
This is the best build I've probably had since playing the game.
Money or pomegranate?
Bet it's in here.
I'm gonna get like quadruple combo'd by dad and somehow.
It's gonna be like...
I was in the air the whole time, by the way.
What's on me?
No.
Does this count for dad?
Oops, I missed.
Holy shit.
I didn't even know those were there.
That's good to know.
Holy shit.
I was trying to move into a safe spot.
This room sucks.
Okay.
Your attack deals more damage and inflicts weak.
Cast lobs, a larger area, or your call is better.
Did I do more attack or the cast damage does more?
Definitely.
Just let's go straight up damage.
All right.
I got two revives.
Still haven't found the sack, by the way.
This is kind of unlucky, isn't it?
This is...
I need health.
And I got two more left.
I'm going to go with money.
Right?
All right.
Do I buy Poseidon right now or pomegranate right now?
I think you guys are very torn on this.
Don't spend it all in one place, mate.
Fog, I think.
Yep.
All right.
I got a heal.
I need a fountain.
Give me a fountain here somewhere.
Money.
This one, I guess.
Nope.
Don't sell anything.
What?
A codex update.
Did you hear about this guy?
He's not even in this room.
He's cool, though.
What do we got?
Boss time.
This is horrible.
Holy shit.
That was horrible.
I still don't have the...
Still don't have the sack to give the dog?
What are you trying to do to me here, game?
This better be a fountain.
Buy another palm?
I don't want to do anvil.
Anvil scares me a little.
Anvil scares me.
I don't want to lose something and gain something.
Palm is double.
It's a double palm.
It's a double...
Wait, Poseidon has a heal.
He does.
But what if I don't get it?
What if I don't get it?
Palm is two levels.
Oh my god.
What happened?
Why?
Your call pulls in...
Your attack and special is stronger in the first 10 seconds.
Any boons you find are more potent as there's no more.
Should have done double palm.
I actually might still be able to do it, depending.
Because that means...
Is this going to be...
Maybe this way.
Give me some money.
Doesn't taste like anything.
Run has been ruined.
Not yet.
Man, I might die in here once.
That's not good.
Shit, they're everywhere.
I need money.
Come on.
No urns?
Urns.
Please.
Tasty.
200 gold?
That's not enough.
Not enough.
Cerberus must be starving.
Oh my god.
Cerberus.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
This is the one.
Unless I accept this message.
Your attack deals more damage.
Plus 53% damage.
But wait, it replaces what?
Your boons with knockback also rupture.
A more rupture.
I can't...
I don't want to replace heartbreak strike.
Who's the only good option?
Full health, two revives, god build.
What could go wrong?
We'll find out soon enough.
I don't have enough money to buy anything.
All right, this is it.
Let's go.
Don't throw for views.
Why would I do that, man?
Okay, I'm not going to do...
I'm not going to throw for views.
Have you seen how I've been playing?
I'm not just throwing.
I'm not like walking off a cliff.
I'm not throwing for views.
Plus, why would we throw for views?
Like, like 2,000 people have left by tonight.
By right now.
Am I going to go die now and be like whoopsie-hee-hee?
I should have done that four hours ago.
All right, let's go.
This is it.
Just relax.
I'm good.
Antic Cerberus accepts the prince's foul offering.
It's just regular.
It's just a normal...
It's a regular video game.
And just you get to kill the boss.
That's it.
I'm not going to look at chat.
I'm not.
All right.
Come on, dad.
Let's go.
Just always keep your cast out.
Move around.
Take a bunch of less damage.
Just get the shots in.
Just be...
Just do it.
Hide behind the pillars during the lasers.
I hope I remember that.
I hope I don't forget that.
I'm looking for full first phase without take...
Without using one of my lives.
All right, let's go.
I feel like I got to get the cords off.
It was a time when Cerberus would never have permitted any soul to exit.
What you're about to hear is encouragement and praise with cheering applause.
Oh, that can possibly be true.
Just for you.
What about Orpheus, Theseus, Hercules, Odysseus, Calvus, Tails, or these men delving into the...
They left on my authority alone.
If there's a situation that does not apply to you, just listen.
You believe you are entitled simply to walk out there.
DMCA from cheers to you don't think that's going to happen.
Let's go.
So sit back.
Get ready.
Here it comes.
We don't want to think you're the one who steps up and gets things done around us.
And then you go the extra mile.
You're doing a great job.
A great job.
We'll tell them.
Job.
Slow down.
He's coming back.
I can tell.
We want to tell you that we have faith in you and we know you can do it.
We know you've got everything it takes to accomplish whatever your heart desires.
That dream you're going, that career you want, that recognition you're seeing, it is yours.
Just listen.
Everyone agrees.
We're on your side.
We're here for you.
We believe in you.
No matter what has ever happened in my life, you have always been there for me.
And that's the greatest gift anyone could ever receive.
The greatest gift anyone could ever give.
You've got the biggest heart of anyone I know.
Look of love in the dictionary and there's your picture.
Thank you, my friend.
I can't even hear what they're saying.
The crowd is too loud.
The crowd's too loud.
Come on, say it.
All right, the crowd's dying down.
The Cerberus is doing very well.
Cerberus is doing very well.
Good.
We did it.
Hooray.
I beat the game on normal difficulty.
Wow.
What excitement.
That build was, it's so good though.
Many favors here.
They'll answer me one question and I'll give it some thought.
How's that?
I thought I was going to choke at the end there.
When I took the second death, I was like, I'm dead.
I was like, no, because he only had like 60% health left.
I was like, what if I'm going to die here?
Ask it anyway.
I'll just do that nine more times.
Okay.
Thank you, Pattycake, for the 20 community subs.
That's an insane amount of money.
And Daddy Warbucks with five.
Thank you, guys.
For Stephanie, your mother.
Oh, we're getting lore here.
Hold on.
Why did she leave?
Because she escaped.
What?
Made it.
Barely.
Oh, this is like, hey, you did it.
Clear time, 56 minutes.
New record.
Current streak, one.
Best streak, one.
Total clear, one.
Hooray.
Well, here it is.
I got a lot of things to spend, too.
Ah, that was hard but fun.
This build was disgusting.
That's the only reason why I beat it.
Very cool.
Now what?
Oh, you know what was the big run saver here?
The double.
Shooting two of these together.
Just too good.
Ish, no.
Leave.
It was the cast that did it?
Probably.
Well, I got the duo cast, right?
Beyond the frozen overlook.
Await the first glimpse of the sun to your left.
Made it to Greece.
Now onboard through the cold.
Sure hope this works, Nix.
Wouldn't it be kind of funny if instead of Greece,
it just sounds like, I don't know, Cleveland or something.
Be like, wait, what?
The surface.
Wind swept.
Wracked by freezing cold.
Nonetheless instills within the prince a sense of awe and the sublime.
For it is unlike anything that he has seen.
Circus goes to Cleveland.
Beautiful.
It is beautiful, isn't it?
Oh, that's nice.
Thing.
That's the sun.
Can I not be outside during this?
Is it a fire or something?
Something to do with my skin burn?
Am I like a vampire?
There's not a final final boss.
Is there?
I feel like there could be.
Wow.
I made it to Greece where they have only one food instead of three foods.
Oh, fuck this place.
All you have is tomatoes.
We had at least fish and bread downstairs.
And I think, I don't know about this.
Pray, who might you be wandering all the way out here?
You're trespassing on private property, you know.
Speak up.
What about the cabbage?
Oh, yeah, I'm not going to eat like grass.
What, would you eat like trees?
Grass?
No, thank you.
Meat and cheese only.
Persephone, is Zagreus and might be your son.
Get out or I shall make you.
I thought it said make out with you.
I didn't read the you after the second line there.
Get out of here or I shall make out with you.
So then you are, if you hate me.
But I'm not leaving until I get some answers.
You existed.
Why did you leave me?
What is Persephone the god of?
You died.
Verdure.
Verdure?
What is verdure?
His burning feet.
They sputtered out when you were born.
Beauty.
Are you standing here before me?
It's harvest, yeah.
What beauty?
How?
What do you mean permanently died?
But I'm alive.
Thoughts.
You never even knew I existed either.
Zagreus, he even kept your name.
How can this be?
You live, fate, my son.
Settle down, mom.
I'm not Frankenstein.
I'm a boy.
I'm a real boy.
Shut up, Jerma.
In short, I beat him finally,
though he did everything he could to prevent our meeting here like this.
But there's something he wanted me to tell you in the end.
He said to tell you Cerberus is doing very well.
Ah, he told you that, did he?
That's good.
Though, tell me something, Zagreus.
How is it that you found me?
To have journeyed all this way, I scarce believe it.
Zagreus?
I don't know.
Just walked over here.
Oh, it's...
Guess I'm just a little tired.
That's all.
I have a live sickness.
...accustomed to the weather, as I think you call it.
I definitely have a live sickness.
I'm not supposed to be alive.
No, that isn't it.
It's that you cannot stay here.
You can't stay here.
Really, you're kicking me out?
Why?
The fates are cruel, Zagreus.
You're bound to that place.
Same as your father.
So they would have us say goodbye for now.
My heart soars knowing you live.
But then it breaks that our time together was so brief.
No, I can come back.
I can come back.
Now that I found you, he...
Maybe he'll just let me come back.
So I have to fight my way out of Hades
to hang out with my mother for 15 minutes a day.
You tell him I demand it.
And I demand he also tell me how come he,
or for that matter Nyx,
never sent notice that you lived?
Olympus is all rife with schemers.
But I was so naive to think that they were different.
I'm telling him I feel awful.
I have to go.
Does it cut scene us or do I have to actually walk back?
The stick shall take you then.
Oh, Zagreus.
Farewell, my son.
Won't you come back to me?
When you are able, please come back.
I shall be waiting here.
Can't hold on.
This is a pretty sick prank by dad.
Mother, I have to get back there.
House of Hades, ha-ha, hooray.
You've finally returned.
Oh, hi, yeah.
That was fun.
You are late, boy.
Does he remember that I killed him?
No. Wait, what?
I vanquished you in single combat and finally found mother
and that's all you have to say to me.
Nonsense.
Don't you think I would recall such an event?
You can't be serious.
So I went back in time or something?
It never happened.
She wants answers same as I do.
She demands you let me pass.
Let me go to her again.
Silence.
This discussion is over.
I hardly think this is the time or place to indulge
your overwrought imagination.
Gaslighting, right?
I know where we can continue this discussion then.
Got to kill him a bunch more times.
Well, might as well just get the fountain upgrade.
Hey, I'm going to call it here.
I like the sound of this one here.
That's a good place to stop for the day.
But I'm going to do my upgrades first.
Are you the one whom I should thank for this most wondrous
music stand, my friend?
Why, it is positively splendid, isn't it?
Go to the quests?
Yeah, I'm going to go make sure I do all my tasks.
I'm pleased you like it, Orpheus.
Tell me something.
How could it play your music when you're not even here?
Who can explain the secret art of Daedalus, my friend?
Know only that whenever it produces music for your listening
enjoyment that the sound you hear is coming from my soul.
Amazing and a bit unsettling.
Bye, Nyx.
Your father felt to you as once his father felt to him.
Although you were substantially more merciful.
I know it is a bitter victory at best.
Bye, Daedalus.
Tell me what transpired subsequently that you have returned.
Did you locate your birth mother?
I did.
She was there.
She was where you said she'd be.
And more than I imagined.
But I had so little time with her.
I can't survive up there for very long.
Why didn't you tell me I'd just die no matter what?
Oh, my child.
I say this seldomly, but I did not know.
It is through for views to believe that the service would
have such an effect on you.
But it seems you share your father's fate after all.
Oh, he's playing cheers to you.
I've really got to take a bow on this one.
Every time he loses with cheers to you, he gets really sad
because that's supposed to give him super powers.
Right.
My father's fate, but he was smugly waiting for me up there
and seemed quite healthy all in all.
Though maybe the farther we get from this realm, the worse we get.
Because he.
So I now presume you are bound to this realm by powers greater even than mine.
Tell me something.
If you knew that you could only see Persephone for but a moment's time,
would you still make the journey to her there?
Yes.
Yes, I would.
I had so many questions left for her.
Then go and ask them, child.
Settle your resolve and find her there again.
And use well what brief time you have with one another whilst you can.
As mortals do.
What does Tumblr game even mean?
I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
I haven't given Nick's a gift.
Zagreus, please tell me that the rumors are untrue.
You really vanquished him.
Devonka Trump.
Have you completely lost your mind?
You're going to destroy this blasted house.
Holy shit, that took a long.
That was holy shit.
That took forever.
I was trying to figure out who it sounded like.
Make father had it coming for some time.
What's your concern besides the house is safe.
He's not going to take this lying down.
He'll find some way to take it out on you on all of us.
You watch yourself.
All of us will pay.
I will not let that happen.
I didn't get a new fish.
Take that back.
It's a great voice.
It's a great voice acting.
It's time for me to give my final review of the game.
Voice acting?
Incredible.
A 98 out of 100.
Very, like, just across the board.
Just fantastic.
All the characters are perfectly cast.
It's fucking, it's phenomenal.
Two, the combat.
It's great.
It trickles you new weapons.
You can play with them.
You find the ones you like.
Then there's still ones that I don't even have.
Very good.
Very awesome.
The upgrade system is, whoa.
All the combos.
The duos.
The rarity.
It gives you the rarity itch.
Where, oh, RNG, I got a fucking epic.
All right, cool.
Perfect.
Great.
That's a 10.
The enemies that can shoot you across the map.
That's a 4.
I don't like that.
But that has, like, 1% weighted on the index here.
Sometimes it can get a little confusing.
There's a lot of stuff going on on the screen.
You can get lost.
I like the areas.
I like the art style.
Looks cool.
I hope they have Greek and Roman mythology.
It's cool.
The 94.
And it's not over.
Oh, I know.
I know that.
Weapon room or no balls.
I'm going to walk over there.
Just hold on.
There's only a matter of time, I suppose.
Wow.
That's...
I broke free after all.
Okay, that's how you get that.
Thousand.
Holy shit.
Okay, hold on.
Nothing else, right?
14 out of 30.
Renovations.
Okay.
What am I still missing here?
I need more keys.
Where's Thanatos?
He's asleep.
I don't know.
The exit.
Once in a while, pal,
you're going to see a real fancy bozo
try to ruin your good time.
You'll know him because he's glowing like a light.
But that's his special armor, see?
You got to punch right through it.
He's going to shrug you off until you do.
For a good time,
beware the fancy glowing bozos on my quest.
Let's try it.
Exagriff.
The rail abatement.
Annihilate all who oppose me.
Wow.
Wait, it has bullets?
Hold them and release to bombard.
That's awesome.
That reloads.
Push in R to reload?
Can I change that keybinding if I ever wanted to do that?
I don't like that keybind.
It's kind of, it's awkward.
It's kind of like the bow and the gloves combined together.
Look at the window.
What the hell does this say?
Prepare.
Congratulations, your deeds have compelled Lord Hades
to serve you a pact of punishment.
Here's how it works.
The pact can make escaping more difficult
via various nasty conditions.
Each condition you accept adds some heat to your heat gauge.
While your heat gauge is full,
you can earn valuable bounties.
You earn one bounty
the first time you vanquish the boss of each underworld region
while your heat gauge is full.
Once you successfully escape,
you can earn more bounties if you turn up the heat.
And you can earn bounties for each weapon.
How much heat you need is per weapon as well.
Oops, can I take that off?
Choose any condition if you dare.
Get out using the,
get out using the adamant rail.
All prices are 40% more.
Don't need to turn the heat gauge so high to earn those bounties.
Heat gauge exceeded.
This is ridiculous.
You have fewer choices when offered boons, bounties.
I get one heat and I use the rail.
I get bounties for doing this.
Achilles or I'm going to die.
Um, hold on.
I got one to see.
Hold on a minute.
Just quiet.
Quiet.
Another day in Tartarus.
I demand silence.
I'm a punching.
Get off me.
Hey, room.
Let's see.
And I have so much.
I don't, I don't want to spend anything.
I'm not spending anything right now.
Come here.
Do, sir.
Turns out that I may be stopping back from time to time like this.
But please don't bother picking up my room.
Sure, but I'll just keep an eye on things in there for the time.
In case you change your mind.
Um, so.
What's this deal?
Um, goodbye.
I'm going to go talk to Achilles.
Oh, that guy is going to like smash his laptop into the ground.
Here.
I found her, sir.
My mother, she's alive and well, and I just couldn't stay up there for very long.
I have to get back to her.
You really made it all the way.
You must have gotten past your father.
That's amazing, lad.
But wait, what was she like?
What happened to you there?
She was, she was great.
Nothing like father, more like you a little bit, I guess.
Though being on the surface, it just seemed to suck the life right out of me.
Even without the wretches of the underworld trying to do me in.
But then you had a little time at least.
Sounds like you have unfinished business with her there.
You got to her this once.
Surely you're able to again, isn't that right?
It is.
I have to speak with her.
Hey, why did you want, what was,
why did you want me to do that so bad?
That was just a regular, just sort of lore conversation.
Because we like him.
Oh.
All right, I'm going to call it here.
Uh, I might still play this next week.
We're going to change tomorrow.
We're going to play something else.
Chat's choices tomorrow.
Thanks for watching everybody.
I will give you a list of games to vote on.
There'll be a poll tomorrow pre-stream.
Stream will be tomorrow around the same time it started today.
Between somewhere around 1.30 or 2.
I'll just set it to 2.
And I'll see you later.
Let's do the credits.
I missed a few subs here.
We had Bo.
Thank you Bo for the five community subs.
And Litigation, thanks for five community subs.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a great rest of your night.
Let's get the, actually I'm going to pee while the credits roll.
Have I peed all day?
I don't know.
I'll be back.
I'll be right back.
Okay, I have subs to give.
So let's do them now.
What was it at the total?
25?
25 subs I believe.
What it was after the contract has now expired.
Here come 25 community subs.
Do it right now.
25.
Thanks again everybody for watching.
Oh, don't leave yet.
Don't leave yet.
Here they come.
People didn't think I was going to do this.
See you guys tomorrow.
Have a wonderful rest of your night.
Take care of yourselves.
I'm going to get up.
See you tomorrow.
Take care guys.