Okay, let's finish the thing. Make sure I can hear what's going on. Kind of can. Can you guys hear
this? You can, but you can't see it. Why? Oh, shit, there we go. Let me just redo this. Finishing the
thing. The game name is The Thing, obviously. All right, where was I going? Anybody remember what
the hell was going on in this game? Well, that's not correct. It'll be correct in a moment. Back
down to zero. Put this back down to zero. Should be good now. Okay. Hey, there you are. Now I should
do this and then this. We're ready to go. All right, so the last thing we did, 459.12. This looks like
it, right? Is that correct? Is this correct? Right, because I have to, okay, so I go down
through, you just had, I had to run. Oh yeah, I remember I said this was going to be horrible.
Okay, well, all right, let me like remember how to play. All right, I was going to run. That was the
idea. What's going on? Because we're being, we're under attack right now. There's huge monsters in
the way and I was going to run by and go down because the elevator is there, right? Okay,
I remember. I think DPI got like reset somehow. All right, it's right here. Monster comes through
the door. Run, run around the circle. All right, all right. Money stream part two. No, no money
stream part two. Get me out. And then it's this way. Who did that? That was Gibbler. Gibbler just
gave 10,000 bits. They said money stream part two. No, and then they said LUL. Thank you for the 10,000
bits. Thank you for the extreme amount of money. Thank you. Cream, corn, wine. Should I just play
the thing every day? Should I just play the thing every single day? I think I figured out the meta.
It's just put on the thing for like an hour stream. Cream, corn, five community subs, potato
chief, 10 community subs. What the fuck? Here we go. Thank you guys, seriously. But now I,
okay, there's a monster that's over here. I'm going to burn him. Thank you, both of you.
Okay, don't want to fuck this up. Hey, you boy, 10 community subs. Gnarly, five community subs. What
the fuck? It's the, the thing just does it to everybody. Why is the thing doing this to you guys?
All right, I can't die here. This is like actually annoying and hard. Wizard, Ribbit, thank you for
the five community subs. Hey, thank you. Flissenberg, five community subs. Thanks, both of you.
Die. I could probably just run by you too. No, I can't because they spawn. All right, will you die?
Die. Burn. RoboLamp just gave five community subs. Come here. All right, for the love of God.
KpShit, thanks for the five subs. I said that name so incorrect. K, what'd I say? KpShit?
ClassicBanana, thanks for the five subs. Shardopus, thanks for the five subs.
Oh my God. But thankfully now I have healing. How much health do I have? Five health packs.
Don't fuck it up. Thank you guys, seriously. The thing money streams.
Niershue, another five community subs. RarePepeBodyLotion, thanks for the five community subs.
PixelMike, thanks for the five subs. Fuck. Did Niershue give another five subs right now?
Another money stream. EvilCrucifix5, I'm telling you, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna test this theory.
In like, in like six months, I'm going to play the thing again. It's time for slime five community
subs. Thank you, slime. Die. Come on. I need to get back to where I was. Pog. Not even a thank you
anymore. Just the number. No, that's not true. That's not true. I got cool on at least three
of those levels. No, thank you, seriously. All of you. FraudyWeapon5, you boy. Ten, thank you.
I thought you were dead. Holy shit, it's happening again. It's actually happening again.
All right, here we go. This, that guy's a bad guy though. That guy's a bad guy.
I don't care about that guy. I just want, I need you to stay here. We're just gonna make it to the
bottom. VGB200, thanks for the five community subs. Thank you. I just gotta get to the,
fuck that guy. Remember that guy's a bad guy. Remember that, that's important. All right,
this is where I left off before. This is the tricky, stupid, dumb part that I hated.
I may have been a little tired. That's why I hated it. I remember now. Now I remember I hate this
because if you get sprayed with water, it takes off more health than getting shot by a gun.
Okay, that's why, that's why I remember. I remember this. He hates this. I do. Give me out my gun.
Watch the steam. Watch the steam. Okay, give me a different, I need something different
in my offhand. I need a fire extinguisher. Yeah, because I need to use it in a minute.
Thanks for the gift sub. Yeah, thanks. Yeah, whoever's given them, all of you.
Right, this part. Okay, now you do, you gotta do the, this part. It's a rocket launcher.
Jill Krungus, thanks with five subs. I think I can just shoot that shit. I can. All right, here we go.
I need a, do I need a flashlight for this part? Yep, put on the flashlight, Jeremy. Don't be an idiot.
This is the part where, yeah, I get swarmed by the little things.
Where is it? There's one more. There's one more. I don't want to back up into the steam. Where's the
last one? ChunkyBeloni10 community subs. Thank you, ChunkyBeloni. Thank you guys for the other, like,
guy sits down and receives huge sums of money. Thank you. Thank you for the money.
Thank you. Who was that? Who was that? Thank you for that money. Hey, number. Thank you for the money.
Five subs. Just forgot to give me, thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you. Appreciate that.
Thanks for the, thanks for the 10 community subs and thank you for the $50. Also, thank you to
BigJunkus for that money you gave me. Who gave the money? Somebody gave $50. Who was it?
I don't, I need to know. I need to know. What am I? What am I without my fucking shout out money?
What am I? No, no, no, it stopped. It stopped. What do I do? Oh, hey guys,
playing the thing here. Oh, gnarly. Thanks for the nine community subs. Thank you. Appreciate that.
Thanks for the money. Nine more subs just came in. Tier one. Unbelievable. Gnarly62, you are a
fucking legend. Let me just tell you. Nice work. Here we go. Wait, it's behind me, right?
What is this hip tracking? I only have two, I can't say the word. Magazine. That's right.
Magazine, magazine, magazine, magazine. That's got it right. That's got it right. Yep. Okay. Fire
extinguisher. I was already at like one health pack by this point. So that zombie guy is not
going to come down here, is he? I don't think so. Not that I remember. What the hell is this guy
doing? Not the behind me, right? I only have, okay, this is bad. I, is there any, okay, give me my
rocket launcher. I don't understand what happened there. That didn't hit it. It hit the corner of
the, what did it do? What happened there? What happened there? What happened? I don't understand.
I'm so mad right now. This is sad. Yeah, I know. That was bullshit. That thing has a hitbox
as big as the screen you're seeing right now. I'm almost there though. I have to wait because
this, this is what screwed me up last time. Shoot this. Wait. Okay. There are aliens that come out
from this guy's body, right? Did I kill it? Did I? No, I didn't. I remember this part. It has to die
on screen. Yes, I know. I get it. Just like every Game of Thrones character. If they don't die on
screen, then they didn't fucking die. That was good, right? How am I going to do this? Remember
this happened last time? What do I, I can't, I don't know why it's not dead. This is, this is,
this is the worst thing. This is one of the top five worst things that have been done in the video
game. I can't, I, what am I supposed to do? I soft-locked myself because I shot the barrels
before, but if I came over here to get it in my view, I would have gotten blown up by this barrel
because I would have to stand right here and they did. What the fuck? What the fuck?
Shoot the, why does it not fire? Dude, this gun is, doesn't make any fucking sense.
You gotta be kidding me. I can't even go around him. This is the stupid, this is the stupidest
thing I've ever done. By the way, the shotgun shoots 8% of the time that you click the button.
Like when I click to shoot the shotgun, it happens every 10th click. I am fucking around with this,
this dumb ass shit. I'll tell you. Not, not on a hard. All right. I want to do a test here. Ready?
Shotgun. It works now. So when I'm clicking, doing this, you know, an actual fight,
why does it not fire? Does it make any sense? So go back and watch the, like every time I've
used the shotgun in a fight and you hear, and it doesn't do anything, you'll, you will physically
hear the clicking like this. It just happened. Now, now it just shot like four times instantly.
That's why I can't, you can't use a shotgun. The shotgun sucks. All right. What, what big bits?
Did I miss bits? Wipe your tears with money. I don't, I don't even, I don't see them on here.
It was 20,000. It was like 200 fucking dollars came in. Are you kidding me?
No, I'm getting baited. Why do I have to go all the way from, why can't you have a save point
anywhere in between here and there? You throw so much junk at that stairwell. Dude, I almost
want to go get like a hack to fucking save state the game. This is one of those fucking
stupid ass games that has like segments like this. Report and report. Don't report me.
It's a fake gamer. Get out of the fucking way. Oh, this guy's a stupid ass gamer. I went the wrong
way. So I'm not even gonna, how do I do this without wasting ammo and shit here? I thought
that was a rumor because there's this guy in here. So I'm going to, I guess I could just make the,
no, cause then you get spawned. I have to just kill this guy now. I actually missed 150 dollars.
Did I seriously? Come on up. All right, run. I'm so glad there's no stamina in this game.
Watch it. Stop, stop, stop, stop. He still doesn't know to shoot them and then burn them.
I thought that was only for like the humanoid ones. Is that all of them? It's hard to tell
because there's like, there's no feedback when you shoot anything. Bullets just kind of disappear
into enemies. It's not, there's barely any feedback. You only get feedback from this.
Is he still alive? What are you doing? Dead? Dead. Okay. All right, let's try this again.
This time when I get down to that part with the barrels, I'm not just going to shoot the barrels.
I'm going to wait till I can see it, but it's going to kill me. I don't know. Not jubated.
All right, here we go. What? Who said that? What?
What? Can I go? Oh yeah, this part.
Shit. All right, give me, is it more? There's more. How? Okay. Give me a weapon.
I'll give you a weapon. We'll see if we can use you. Stop, stop moving. Get over here. Get over
here. Stop running up there. Don't be so stupid. Why are you going over there? Follow me over here.
Oh, I hate you. He just stands up there. Oh, it's getting hard. It's getting hard for me to not
just pretend I beat the game. What? These guys just spawned and he is infected.
He's, he's infected immediately and I can't run away because I'm going to get sprayed.
No, I remember shooting him in the head with a rifle. Oh great. This is where it gets all
fucked up now. I actually remember shooting this guy in the head with a rifle. I mean,
it was like four or five days ago, but I remember, I remember shooting him in the head with a rifle
when he was up there and he turned. This is so bad. Oh, it's tough for me to, cause they spawn
here and you can't, I can't go this way because of this and I can't go this way because of this.
So the fucking claw monsters just keep spawning here and jumping on your face. And if you burn
them, you burn yourself. Shittiest fucking long spiral hallway. Oh wait, what's that? What happened?
I walked five feet. Did we spawn underneath my body? Can I walk now? Please. Where is it?
How the fuck am I going to kill the gigantic thing that takes up the whole hall? That shit
ain't going to happen. How am I going to do that? The guy that takes up the whole thing.
I got to run backwards and burn them, but I'm going to get burnt by the fucking steam.
Okay. I'm not going to blow this up. Can I spawn that guy without,
I don't know, I'm going to go very, very slowly. All right. This one, I remember this one. This
one was stupid too. So I have to do this up all the way up there without having it somehow hit
this one or this one. I don't, I don't, did you see what that grenade did? That grenade went
like a pit man's suitcase over here. That doesn't make any sense.
He looks like the greedy runner. I just, I don't. Okay. So now what are you supposed to do here?
I don't even have any health packs left. I'm so fucked. Just the casino. I'm so fucked right
now. Like, I don't know what they even expect you to do here because if I stand over there,
it doesn't destroy it. If I stand over here, I die from this, but I have to, I don't get it.
Use a grenade and run. It's going to shoot at me and blow up the, it's going to blow this up.
Sniper rifle doesn't work, but the sniper rifle doesn't do anything. Now I'm in trouble. What?
If I shoot the barrels here, I can't see that it's, this is just a rock and a hard place,
but I can't shoot them from over here because it doesn't blow up the gun. Don't reload the save.
Why not? That's not a new level. Is it an, is that, wait, is it a new, new game?
Save the medic. No, you can't save the medic. He's fake from the beginning. I'm going to prove it
right now. I'm going to shoot him in the head. The second I see him, the medic is pretending.
Yeah. Let me just see what happens if I do this too. If I die in there, can I just restart the
level? Uh, Bob boy, this one, hey, Bob boy, this one's for you. Thanks for the five community subs,
Bob boy. All right. So if I die in here, like if I just die right now, like let the, well,
I restart level and start here. Okay. Here we go. I'm going to stun this guy just because I'm going
to. Okay. Oh, that would, why did you take so long to do that? Okay. For the love of God, please.
Jax is online. He hates gifts. No, I don't hate gifts. I love gifts. Thank you for everybody for
the gifts. The current any percent speed run of this game is 40 minutes. That's, that's pretty
ridiculous. Okay. I got to just get in there now. I wonder how fucked up it is. Yeah. I wonder how
many like actual like skips there are. Shoot. Let's go. I'm going to make sure you don't get
touched. Stay, stay, stay. Come here. You and me. Let's go. Did he get touched? He didn't. By the
way, that's just a dice roll. If he's going to get hit or not, because he can't kill three things
like that in five seconds. Follow me. Let's go. Yes, sir. Are you, are you going to do this thing?
You can do the stupid thing. They're getting hit by the steam. Okay. Let's go. Follow me.
You turn right now. I'm going to be so pissed off. Wait, watch out.
Hold still and I'll fix you up. Oh my God. You're a medic. Please don't just turn and make this a
complete disaster. Please. He's going to fucking turn right when it matters. Save game. There is
no quick save. I needed to test. Somebody said to test that to see if you can just give the body.
You got fucking kidding me. That was a joke. That was a, that was a joke. That is, I actually just
got joked on right there. Don't stand there like me. You got it. You got it. You got to kill that.
Kill it. What are you doing? Shoot it. Oh, come on. Are you fucking kidding? That's why he wasn't
shooting. No, he's, it's, it's not real. He's, this motherfucker is infected the whole time.
He just wasn't even shooting the gun. The medic is scripted. I knew it. I, oh my God, I hate this so
much more than anything. You know, like the, like, like all bald because mad, whatever the fuck that
meme is. Oh, it's happening right now. You, you shot me with a shotgun from that far away and it
did that much damage. Who are you? I hate this game. Okay. I got it, right? I got it. I got it. I had
to. I had to. You saw the explosion. I was even past it. Like I, this is just, why is this in the
game? It's just there to be annoying. Dude, it even made the explosion on it. It even did the,
it exploded thing and it's still there. You have to be within like 10 feet for those things to be
destroyed. What on earth? What on earth would, what on earth? What were they thinking? Because
now I have to run forward and spawn all the enemies and then shoot a grenade and then get
swarmed. This has to be another way to do this. That has to be. Can I like bait the swarm?
This is fucking dumb. I can't even aim down. This is dumb. D-U-M-M. Is this just never going to stop?
Because every time I run for it, the big guy is right there and then he blocks, you can't run by
him. So I have to turn around. You can run. I can't. It's scripted. What kind of script is this?
Just run and gun with the SMG. Don't work. I tried it four days ago. Rare Pepe body lotion. Just
gave five. Thank you for the five subs. Rare Pepe body lotion. Appreciate it. And don't be that way.
Also gave five subs. Is there like a way just to exploit this part? Because this feels,
this feels like a weight. This feels like a thousand pound weight on my chest.
I don't want to do this all again. How do you cheat? I would love to cheat right now.
Ask your older brother. I just don't have done it in a way. Max Games was a mistake. Thank you,
Max Games. I'm putting this on easy. I don't care. I'm putting this on the easiest difficulty.
I don't think I care about my ego taking a hit for not being able to go through this
fucking bullshit staircase and the thing. In fact, I don't even know what the hell this does.
This makes this, this is like auto aim, right? This is actually making it harder.
This makes, this is worse. It's trying to aim at them and I'm so close to the end of this game.
I just want to beat it. It's trying. Heal me. I'm not using a mouth pack.
What just happened to me? What happened to me? I just landed and got hurt. Remember this is all
canon. Oh, I would retroactively get rid of that. You coming out or what? What are you doing?
This game is torturing Jeremy. I mean, it's, I was having fun. It was like eight and a half
hours of a fun game. And then this part is just stupid. It was, it was. This is Mario,
this is not Mario tennis levels. I haven't, I haven't like talked shit to somebody I don't
know online. Just watch a play through to figure it out. I shouldn't have to watch like the speed
run where the guy has played this game 4,000 times to be able to know how to play through once.
What? I shouldn't be able to do this to do it. All right, let's go. Let's do it again.
Now comes to some of the toughest fighting you'll do in the entire game. When you drop out of the
ductwork, Koman will run by or just behind you. He'll run all the way up to the top of the ramps.
When you hit the ground, quickly give him a weapon to follow him. Once you reach the top,
have him follow you and fight any troopers on the ramps. But that's, that's what I'm, I did that
already. But then I have to kill him and that sucks. I literally need him until he turns
and it goes to shit. What are you fucking aiming at game? Auto aim in a tunnel.
Fuck. Get over here. Don't run by me. Shut up. Take a machine gun now. Let's go.
Follow me. Fight. Fight. Shoot. Heal the fuck out of me right now. Heal me.
Oh. Heal me. Heal me. You're a medic. Please. He's already turned. It's already over.
He just standing still like an asshole. Hurry up. Go. Help me please. Where are you?
Where are you? Get over here. Turn. Heal me please. I have no bullets.
Fight. Fight. Fight. What is even hurting you that much? What the fuck just happened?
It all goes to shit here every time. He's dead. Good. Give me my gun back.
You have any health packs on you or anything? It doesn't stand up, right?
Steam. I'm going to, I'm going back to the shotgun. Okay. Now it's this part. I get swarmed, right?
No, it's the, these guys trying to beat this. I just got so mad at that person that beeped.
That was like a, the fuck did you say? What happened? That was a direct hit.
Somebody fucking help me. Nobody help me. Nobody help me. Three hits needed. No, that's not true.
That's not true. That can't be true. No, you can't. That can't be true. If I don't do it here,
I'm watching a YouTube video. Okay. This is the part where it goes to shit every single fucking
time. We're going to change. We're going to change that. I'm going to, okay. We're going to make a
wall of fire right here. I'm going to, I don't know what I'm going to do. I get, I run. No,
I don't have any idea. Should I watch a video? Yeah. Timed that so well. It's like, it's,
the hit box is so big and it doesn't stop. I did, I didn't do anything wrong there.
I'm watching a video. What's this called? Uh, the thing, stupid staircase, the thing staircase.
What would he call it? Winding staircase. Uh, the thing staircase game spiral, the thing spiral
staircase. Somebody already has a video. It's a ramp. Okay. The Sims four is I'm getting the
Sims four open chat that what a brilliant fucking mind you have. Seriously. I'm like, I can't alt
tab. What a brilliant mind. I'm going to open up the chat, but I'm going to be logged in twice.
Am I going to get like, you've been hacked? Can I do this? Okay. All right. Let me see it.
Can I even open this? Okay. I'm opening it. Let me just take a look. The thing any percent. No,
I don't want the speed run. I don't want the speed run. I don't even know what to look.
Okay. Hold on. I'm looking, did you just hear that sigh? Okay. So he shoots, he just shoots
everything and then he, and then he gets angry. And this is a speed runner by the way. See
Oh shit. I'm shooting, shooting, shooting, shooting, shooting,
stealing. No, I'm just trying to see what to do from an expert. Wait, what's he aiming at?
Are he runs by? All right. What do you do here? You can shoot them. You can shoot them. You can
shoot them. You can shoot them, but there's no feedback that that's possible. Are you kidding me?
Don't even say that. Don't tell me this is real. I shot that with the hunting rifle like 10 fucking
times. There's no spark. There's no feedback. Your bullets disappear into the wall just like
they do over here. This feedback here. Unbelievable. Okay. I'm going to go bait the fucking big guy.
Let's go. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Stop steaming. Yes. Yes. All right. Fucking hold on.
Where is it? What's up? Well, you just know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. There's another one. I just go, go, go, go, go, go. Just go. Just go.
Is it dead? Is it dead? I'm going to pass out. I think I'm having a heart attack. Okay. I think
I'm fine. This is a small heart attack. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
okay um swallow it swallow it it was bad swallow it though it's like when a pitcher gives up a
fucking grand slam you don't just like roll around on the mound like no i didn't do it
no you just you go next batter next batter next batter why is that room have to after out
just go next batter but at least now i know i can do that oh fuck i was so close it was over but
they just there's two of them and i was i guess i could have shot but they would have shot me
i don't know i don't know i'm sad no next batter shotgun works now it's because i'm holding it down
i'm not pressing it it's hard it's hard to get over what just happened after all the bullshit
and all the dumb shit it's hard for me to get over this i'm trying i'm just trying to get back
there so i can just pretend it never happened i'm just gonna try for a lady thanks for the 10
community subs and your boy 10 community subs back to back thanks guys turbo do you know that
you sucks at video games that does that's not gonna okay when you let up like four grand slams in a
row uh if somebody in the stands goes you suck it doesn't do anything like it does i i knew i've
given up fucking 16 runs like i know like i don't i don't like it's not gonna do anything i already
know you got further than i it's all right it's all right i'm good it's the next banner he's on the
verge of tears oh god damn it i'm so upset the medic's right here it's okay medic is right here
it's gonna we're gonna give him the gun what the fuck is that noise where are you and stop doing
this i don't i'm not giving up any more home runs where are you going oh he does he just runs
right why does he not get hurt by the steam i know i i know what to do it's not gonna be a problem
i know what to do no more home runs what what happened still and i'll fix you up he's infected
not yet not yet i still need the heels don't go all right now wait a minute i i can do it from
anywhere can't i let me just test this hypothesis can i just shoot this from here okay all right got
it got that one turn around let's get this one too you're fine this is one i have to wrap around
okay we're good a little bit more this one's destroyed this one also has the obnoxious spawn
should i kill him now i think i'm gonna kill him yep i'm gonna i'm gonna headshot him like three
times give me my gun back yes sir i'm not dealing with that scripted bullshit i'm sorry guys
i just fucking panicked i should have i should have used him down here i should have used him
down there damn it i waited i waited oh the tears i'm gonna start crying i waited twice somebody get
in there and fucking patch that dude moment of truth incoming in about one to two minutes
i'm patching it right now are you seriously thanks man appreciate that
i seriously is this a bait your boy 10 more subs your boy that's like 50
holy shit your boy thank you i already got this one well that's great what a waste of ammo okay
this is i at least i have enough for this no but seriously your boy that's a lot of subs
okay this is it right okay all right all right all right all right
what happened what why they just they disappeared why i'm out of bullets i'm out of bullets for this
gun oh my god it's the stupidest fucking thing where is the big guy is he dead where's the big
guy did he jump off the cliff is he in the wall oh my god i forgot shoot the shotgun
shoot i just was holding it down you gotta be kidding me i was holding the button down
and he was just going like this i don't i don't have any bullets i need to use the the rifle i
think what the fuck am i gonna do this return this game to blockbuster you don't hold the
trigger with the shotgun but if you shoot i know i can't even explain this if i click the button
the shotgun sucks it's it's bad the game's mechanic with shotgun is a fucking full a full
like two weeks full diaper worth of shit full this is gonna be a living hell i don't have any
what am i gonna do i don't know if this is even hitting is this hitting and that's not how a
rifle works either okay if there's enough safe point in here is that right here i hear something
fuck you fuck you fuck you just go and go go go go go and go and go and save the game right now
i don't care i don't this might softlock but we're gonna do right here it's only giving me
shotgun bullets man i could have turned really i could have turned these off i could have turned
them off what was on the ground okay well i have plenty of shotgun ammo that's great because it's
it's the least favorite fucking gun in the game i actually got a safe point
i turned it off what is there another one that i turned off instead of this one
there are two of them you turned off this is soda machine i don't have any bullets to shoot that
with besides the pistol but i'm not going to kill this thing with a pistol so there's this one and
then the other one so go through turn it off and what on the name of god
are you alive you put point blank with a shotgun and you're still alive
hold rifle ammo somebody just gave uh germa sucks just gave five community subs thank you germa
sucks i appreciate it thank you all right rifle ammo i want more smg ammo this is not going to
go very well at all i know what's going to happen open it okay so why is that happening
with a pistol i'm wasting ammo it doesn't matter that's the same shit that's happening with the
shotgun clean it's clean your mouth my mouth is so dirty that that's what's happening the computer
can't handle the advanced game all i need is one shot you know what that's true let's go
what hold on six where is this thing i'm going in oh turn the fucking thing off what the fuck
i pressed it where oh my goodness i cannot believe this game now i gotta go around those boxes
in fact we're gonna make this easy so i this one's off right i hope so i don't what i turned this one
back on did somebody make this area in mario maker it's just so it turns that one so i have
to destroy it okay so again we have this one here i have to sneak across open door go
oh turn off duck sneak through here wait did i get all the stuff just let me even just get
a fucking item on the corner and then watch out for the monster but hold on i was waiting so long
for you to show up that i hurt myself there okay here we go now i'm gonna heal i want full health
for this let's take a look i now have two from here just i'm gonna destroy this one right now
there's two of them i think i hope this is hitting is that one too is it now that it is okay now we
turn off this one give me ammo and i think i i was trying to pick up something over here okay
back in business this should not be another one in this room what what's that wait why they what's
that one i'm not taking chances here i have no idea they were both off i don't care okay cut scene
thank god i can restart at this level please can i please let me be done with like this stupid shit
where's cohen i thought he was with you no he went to the medical supply area to pick up more
antibiotics and you let him go alone what the hell are you thinking oh relax the area is secure
secure are you crazy those things are everywhere then why don't you go find him no i think i'm gonna
stay right here why would you let him do that shoot him why would you let him pull the gun up
stoles you should have just shot him right when he started the loop again i don't know what kind
of game you're playing here but it ends now yeah and it ends with you if either one of them shoots
right now they win hey guys wait follow me uh pick one what do i give them something here
take a handgun can i have your wait can i take his handgun test i don't have any tests kill one
stick them with the adrenaline that might calm them down all right yeah hey have a little bit
of adrenaline oh shit who's what's up okay well that we settled that um you just see what
you did not just see what happened there here take some bullets really i'm one one magazine
away from you being my friend forget it are you friends no i just gave you adrenaline uh
necromancy thanks for the five subs heal him i don't have any heals i don't have anything
i'm gonna let you be but it's not seriously the necromancy thanks for the five subs uh oh
maybe you will get us out of this all right me and your buddies what is it what is this thing
stun gun zero to zero oh it's because i have two all right uh i'm gonna give you the shotgun make
it work give me the you take the shotgun where is it have you lost it i just gave you a better gun
like i just gave you a much better gun why would you be that even now you don't like me
i gave you something way better than what you had okay i have a health pack uh let me go in
what did i go go on the computer current tests on the smaller alien fragments have proved successful
full skill testing will commence when a sub-suitable test subject has been obtained
all right you and me let's go okay i need ammo oh we can go this way or we can go i hear beep
is this guy an engineer okay well it looks like we're going over here what do we what are we
doing that neck i can't i need to look at it in my phone that's terrifying my neck is terrifying
what does it look like did i miss a raid joel came in with the raid oh shit well what's going
on welcome hey what's up joel how long did that happen was i too busy being angry somebody said
crackhead hold on i hope you had a good stream i don't know what you were doing but hopefully
you had fun and those of you that just joined us we are at the end game of the thing for pc
and it is quite a video game i've been a little bit upset by this game but it's okay we're almost
done with it i just have to get to the end all right what do we got let me see this image but
welcome thanks a lot joel appreciate it we have to play something fucking sometime seriously
now i know this is i know that's doctored you're not going to get me again with this shit i know
that this is a fate i know that's a doctored image not this time it's not going to happen this time
because i know that somebody fucked with the eyes that's fine here look take a look at the
eyes somebody's i do i that's okay i know that it's fucking not real so we can move on it's
not real that's fine it's not a real picture okay we have to play oh engineer i hear the uh
electricity where is it what the fuck is going on in here oh yes quick somebody load a softball
and put a dunk tank up maybe you'll dunk them all right do we have an engineer please yes get it
yes sir i hope you're not infected i hate playing this game alone it sucks all right uh how much is
that what are you doing how much that's five fifty thousand what are you doing what happened
50 000 bits holy shit you just gave that's 500 dollars right now why does the thing do this
that's a shitload of fucking money the thing has like there's something about it i missed a ton of
bits too earlier god i'm so sorry that's a fucking lot what did they say did they say anything
i can't alt tab and it's not hold on can i do this i need to hold like there's a save game
right here right yes there is all right i can i can save it and then i'll tap because i want
to see because that's a lot of fucking money all right that's saved let's see if i can because i
have to like switch to here jesus christ they say terminator terminator terminator hey germa just
finished up really tough day at work it would make me feel a lot better if you could do if you could
for me let me thanks for the the read the ridiculous the insane amount of bits
too many you want me to oh woo for you do i have to do it on camera i don't have to do it on camera
because on camera is like that's it's 500 dollars have to do it on camera i was actually just thinking
about right now of disabling clips of my channel for like the next 30 seconds but that's too much
to i think actually can i do that don't uh but i feel like if i do that i might delete every
clip that's ever been taken on the channel so that's like kind of a bad thing to do thanks
to the 500 bucks that's two that's too much money i can't even comprehend it i can't i can't do it i
can't do it it's too much and i'm not stalling i'm just i can't do it i can't fucking do it
oh thanks for the fucking huge amount of money uh here take some more ammo now we're best friends
both earphones have to go in was it worth it i don't know i just i can't believe someone just
did 50 000 bits and there was more earlier too that's that's a lot i'll be i'll be i'll be getting
like steak at some point maybe i might get an engineer is that some kind of like dig that
you're not that good of an engineer or something because you're right here how are you not an
engineer you just god damn it i need an engineer i just i just got one there's one right here
oh i need an engineer there we go okay do it yes sir gonna go to texas roadhouse
now i'm gonna go to i'm gonna go to chili's and i'm gonna get the steak at chili's
oh wait that panel controls the time security door to the black tech lab i can jam the door
from the inside but you'll have to stay here and flick the switch that only stays open for a few
seconds so give me some time to get there first what that was a lot open security door wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait he just gone he's gone you gotta repeat instructions is he there why is
he coming back we got company what where is this guy is he dead clear the room and then open the
door i think he's dead i think i might have soft-locked it somebody another five thousand
bits and then tibetan hovercraft thanks for the five subs numble num legs thanks for the five
thousand bits please for the love of god read the big bits like these ones 50 dollars can i even do
this did he go through a door jesus help me he's good he's good but that's a thank you for the
fucking 50 dollars now tell me what you know let me see if i can't figure it out but maybe it'll
make sense to you he's yeah he's infected for sure without a single doubt in my mind yeah i know of
course he's locking me in here what what do you mean 30 seconds breathe deep blake what do i do
leave shoot window that's the danger shoot it shoot vent on roof what do i do i have 1.3 seconds
hold on a second let me see the ones that i missed he just locked me in there and like poison me and
i die come on let me see i see numb legs gave 10 000 bits they said will this get your attention
for a hundred dollars and it didn't so sorry about that that's um that i you it did not
but it's got it now because that's a ton of fucking money thank you numb legs for the 150
dollars right there will this get your attention unfortunately it did not and then fitty gave
5 000 bits i think we missed that too they said did somebody say money stream it's the thing i
should just i should just rebroadcast the thing just every day that i'm not live just start it
from the beginning you know people do reruns but sorry i missed that that's that's a huge amount
of money to miss oh only a hundred dollars uh whoops where was it i didn't see sorry that's a lot
of money thank you for thank you for the money stream holy shit if you do that it would include
owo it would not owo awu not aw it's awo not owo
awo is what it would be get it right all right here we go same deal hey can you do this
yeah kill everything for me please won't you i need an engineer he's got owo on the mind
yeah because it's it's every like 110th comment in the stream what do you mean i have it on the
mind more like 30 probably something like that that panel controls the time security door to
the black tech lab i can jam the door from the inside but you'll have to stay here and flick
the switch that only stays open for a few seconds so give me some time to get there first
you got it don't just kill him now
area looks secure we got company
he just ran through it die save okay then go find him all right he says
ha ha ha you're locked in here you can't get out and then i say oh shit how well this is crazy
and then what do i do what so good he can't he turned how did he turn this is the room where
so i can't get locked in the room now jesus help me look i can only help you if you get
your shit together this is another guy check out that turmoil different guy but maybe it'll make
sense to you all right i gotta be quick to grenade the door dude bro all right get everything quick
and get everything okay grenade the door that didn't do anything i tried it's all good
uh we don't even need to go in the other room who cares the guy's dead
like where i don't even have to go in there okay go power on okay now turn off turn it off
turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off just turn it off turn it off
all right so now i don't because it is a safe point there just checking to see i don't want
to miss anything got all the health packs do i have as i've six hp packs safe point in here
good does this do anything does this do anything does this do anything
does that do anything does that do anything nothing in here does anything does dessert
all right i've come all right here we go guy in here he's uh he's not even in here all right not
not even in got it so back here then I didn't really do anything any computers
to look at testing is going well and there is a very positive feel within the
team today Stoll's work is impeccable as usual and Ryan is picking up the new
technology at a reasonable pace cool the anti-thing virus is proving to be our
finest work to date none of this could have been possible without the fine
people I work with on this groundbreaking project all right that
was that sucked that hurt my brain burn and then save get out of here that was
pretty clean that was clean super grenades on the way out that way what
did you miss dude you have no idea it was fucking insane found a large hole in the
ventilation strap this morning yet that that that that that that that I think
some animal must have went in there it that that that that must have been either
retreated and died or whatever I don't know I've informed security and they
are investigating the beast has friends the security team is dead and I can't
find anything to defend myself with it everyone is reading this somebody
grabbed him when he was typing somebody just like he was they got his laugh okay
I gotta say he was literally shaking all right what's going on next oh this is
not the way to go I thought this is gonna be like an and I don't know what
oh that sucks so where do I actually go I mean in here but what about this way
no no this probably opens open door to testing range how the hell do I do that
open the door to the testing range did I miss something in this room back here
like this a computer or something no I don't think there's anything I missed
and this is a one of the consoles up here can I touch anything with this
I didn't even I didn't do that they did they opened that door okay all right
here we go save and it's time to fight no you're not gonna Mario maker me right
now sorry not right now not gonna happen why am I panicking oh hey I gotta I gotta
torch it I gotta get in there and torch it oh you motherfuckers burn all right
there's a button to press here why is there a button here there is gain access
to weapons what does that mean like a fee flinched German's a broken man not
really maybe like a maybe like 5% broken like maybe 2% no god more what the hell
kid is barrels blocking this one why do I hear code anything of interest
not really whoo he's in there there he is just looking at the wall two guys
here I don't know what this is all right can this open I gotta go this way he's
gonna see us I mean us he's gonna see us well here comes
what the fuck just happened whoa I just got electrocuted I couldn't
pause the game because it's gonna happen like three more times okay we're
good I hear a big guy this doesn't open tons of ammo and weapons and armor and
gear tons of gear nice look at all that gear what else is on here what are the
other what are these like an Easter egg or something I think I scared everybody
up there absolutely infected but you'll do you'll do I need you to open a door
itchy itchy itchy face and eyes today what's going on with me you'll do just
like your last girlfriend okay come back here you do this do your thing he's
deranged I know but I think everybody here is deranged I just need you to open
a door and then maybe shoot it a couple of zombies and we can be best friends
good and there's a safe point in here too so that's great that means I can
give you more than that take more ammo you should be good what is this is it
like a grenade launcher or something that's a microscope I thought this was
a scope I thought it was a fucking attachment I didn't think it was a
microscope whatever okay and how do we get these doors open that's fun what a
fun journey this is gonna be I don't know this door doesn't open this door
doesn't open there is this my stream froze hit the refresh button okay that
powers this room from me to be able to okay there's that okay that thing is in
here not that concerning to me but this on the other hand oh shit would you look
at that just kill it all first anything else that's a giant cannon it's got to
go I needed to you need to check check for mimics all right hold on save the
game the weapons door is now open it's down here right right wait wait wait
wait wait don't just go in there was the safe point over here yep okay safe point
is over here yep okay I can't with you to turn now because you've all your
usefulness is gone key card what is that a key to one of the doors it is a giant
cannon I was right I was actually correct so now I have the key to open
this door you imbecile but you know what I like it that you're stupid because it
makes so I can beat this game easier oh hi okay so what's in here there are
grenades in here I'm not gonna hit myself with these grenades fire grenade
this is really fucking messy all right I I guess I'm just gonna shoot him round
in a circle and fire I think let me use a stun grenade oh I forgot you guys are
here fuck shoot him all right so how the fuck does this work so I'm gonna stun
him and then I have to kill the thing can you please come in here with me get
in here why am I on that what he's fucking how is he hitting me this is
fucked up the key what hold on there's a key in here we get to fight another
boss that makes no fucking sense oh I thought that was bad guys okay kill the
soldiers and say that's a good idea okay so you can't really go anywhere I'm
gonna try to not I mean if I throw a grenade the things gonna open fuck you
don't even have what the I do it's a ground on fire I'm dead
it's spam stun grenades but I yeah yeah but I have to heal too and I can't put
this on it's like they have to get the so I'm just gonna run to the back of the
room but every time I switch okay let's try this what are you doing that's done
I have a girl fucking ridiculous and I love it automatically puts me it
automatically puts me on the fucking stun gun now on this what's the speed
runner do because this is fucking ridiculous I just like rage opened my
phone and this is the first thing that I see I know I don't I can't even do it
is there a stand underneath him someone said stand next to it go just give me
the broken thing to do third boss fight which is a giant tentacle I'm saying
there's it's seemingly no safe place for you to hide without getting hit by the
boss forcing to keep moving around dodges there's actually a very easy way
to prevent this how we stand literally so you know so you have to stand
literally right underneath them is the only way I just want everyone to be
aware of this this is what we like to call I can't what he won't even say it's
a bad program good point don't swing at me watch this can't reach so now light
him on fire whoa what the fuck is he doing what just happened why is he just
watching should I let him on fire again I think I have to burn him Christ stop
stop stop just die die die burn burn burn die die burn burn die die die die
burn burn die burn burn die burn burn burn what what what what what what what
what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what
for a lady thanks for the 10 community fucking subs thank you thank you
seriously okay stop so so I'm not gonna move when it says escape I don't even
want him coming out of there use the shotgun only how many clips should
it be I know it's a slug it's a slug I know one more
break them why won't you this is ridiculous and I have the same amount of
fucking health help help me help me help me help me he's on my team I'd say dude
the thing just spins around in a circle and you're gonna get killed every time
the thing you light it on fire and it just goes in a blender in a circle is
there a reason why they decided to make every boss fight in a tiny fucking room
why are we in this small room together why do we have to be in this in every
boss fight has to be a fucking shoebox it's maddening it doesn't make any
fucking sense why do we have to be in such a small area don't don't light them
on fire well I have to that's the only way I can progress I can't progress any
other way just use normal weapons I did I was almost a 12 slug magazines on this
motherfucker how many do you want how many slug
magazines you want me to do use all why is it why are you doing this why are
you doing this health-based or time-based um I guess I could just sit
here kill the other dude first I mean I can't I can't move though I fucking
can't move if I move I'm gonna get hit I think it's stupid why do you pick the
stun gun every single fucking time when I'm just trying to cycle why do you
have to do that it's a bad idea that's a really bad idea because now I have to I
think spawned in here don't fucking you dare oh my god please I'm out of health
facts now if this is on easy do not use fire what if I run out of bullets I have
to finish it with fire so I'm so fucked how do I do because when I light them on
fire here I am absolutely 100% guaranteed to take like half health just
stun him throw but will he get stunned if I throw this into the wall back here
like but this is gonna hit me it's gonna hit me why did I move cuz I was gonna
get hit by the grenade oh my god this shit mmm my goodness it's fucking
ridiculous when you enter the room run along the middle seam of the floor to
the junction to the fourth or fifth row of tiles deep into the room you'll be
in an excellent spot from the boss because it can't hit you shot and till
you damage it to red shoot imagine just fighting a boss imagine just fighting a
fucking boss what was that again go to the fourth tile in the room and take two
steps to the right what was the middle seam go through the middle seam of the
room and then then what the hell happened use flame grenade and run away
this boss can only be killed by fire but can be damaged middle seam of the floor
to the junction of the fourth or fifth row of tiles you'll be in an
excellent spot from the boss because it can't hit you so the fourth or fifth row
of tiles let's go I'm gonna go to the full one two three four fourth or fifth
junction of tiles this is one two three four fifth junction of tiles I mean can
I move on the junction of tiles no I have to stay in the scene I guess and now
I'm gonna die so what's the next part is just damage him a bunch but this guy's
gonna get out shoot him and then use a fire grenade and run away but then I
gotta deal with this dickhead shoot it to red yeah I could hold on I'm gonna
show you something no because I downloaded a patch to make it so I could
use hold on okay so I have a patch that lets me use the mouse it's not a it's
not a mod it's an official patch so it's already red I just shoot like four
times so it's ready it's ready now so it's like you shoot it five times and
now I use fire kill the other guy use flame grenade and run hold on I gotta
like check I can't like even move my hand do you understand like this is I
can't even move the mouse now it wants me to do page up and page down okay so
now how much I don't know how much health I have fire grenade and then
fucking run kill other guy first wait kill other dude first then use the
grenade because it'll get out of the I kill I keep I have to move fire grenade
let's go now you just broke out without even I'm on the I'm on the junction I'm
on the correct junction of tiles the AI doesn't know okay all right wait a
minute burn burn burn burn I'm just gonna burn fuck okay forget about
throwing grenades I'm gonna I need to go immediately to the machine gun
please oh my god supposed to be red it was supposed to be red why was it not
red that was supposed to be red I did it it was red and in here I delight him on
fire like five six times I have no health I am going to die I there are
gonna be people soldiers everywhere I just have to get in that door oh my
goodness all right let me go back in here is there anything else in this room
there's this shit grenades grenades super grenades I have all those that I
can fill there's a key did I get the key already well didn't think I have a
key they already get it did I get the key I don't think so maybe I don't know
all right save it again okay save all right so what what does that even do for
me like I won I guess anything else to do in here just escape you mean like
just run away okay I looks like we're running away we're escaping escaping to
where just leave yeah that's so I came in this way didn't I I lost my friend
that's great just haunted house explosions great don't make me go back
up here don't make me go back up this shit with the steam I'm not soft-locked
I'm fine it's infuriating it's infuriating actually soft-locked what
that doesn't even I can't what am I whether the complaints can I have I gotta
go near the door to activate the explosion to hit me and kill me how far
can I get before it health pack anything please so what if I just don't walk
forward yet I mean I do what I think I think I actually am soft-locked because
it goes boom boom what does it do it does it just timed it might be timed
because I just you just explode here what the fuck is going on I'm afraid to
take a step forward because of the landmine fire I don't know what should I
take a step forward should I wait is it done can I go forward wait hold on
explosion I wouldn't even near it I wouldn't even near it I wouldn't even
near it this is bad this is bad I wait go wait go wait go just watch the ending
on YouTube we've come so far I died to steam we're getting the Simpsons hit and
run level but I you just get hurt I just you just it doesn't matter you have to
take some damage and I guess I don't I must need to have like a health pack by
now I think the less of his face you can see on the camera that's how you know
how angry is because I lean forward and I go I'm not moving I'm not moving you
were off-camera the whole fear playthrough notice how this is that not
how long that steam was or it's different every time don't move don't
just wait it's this is an escape of run away segment shouldn't I be able to run
away what's happens right here okay somebody tell me how that's fucking
fair at all for the whole game every second of this game the game the whole
entire video game explain to me why what just happened was okay enemy there's an
how did you get down here how did you get down here it's fucking impressive
this I hear two big things where are you where are you where is this person
where are they oh they're fighting the fucking kidding me you gotta be fucking
kidding me you gotta be fucking kidding me you gotta be fucking kidding me you
gotta be fucking kidding me you gotta be fucking kidding me you gotta be fuck
kidding me gotta be fuck kidding me you gotta be fuck kidding me gotta be fuck
kidding me you gotta be fucking kidding me you gotta be fuck kidding me you gotta
be the ex but the explosions when did it happen the explosions I don't know I'm
fucking terrified cuz that sucked please don't blow up on me please don't blow up
on me please don't blow up on me please don't blow up on me please I'm so close
just don't die to the steam and don't explode where's the explosion oh no it
if something comes out of there you want you guys realize if a fucking little alien jumps
out of there which way to go use a help use a heal what heal I don't have a heal
well where this med kit you have a med kit where's the med kit what are you talking about
what do you mean med kit you heal heal you heal you why would you do that to me right now that's
not funny that's fucking horrible why would you do that to me right now I'm so fucking dead
I hear a little a little guy and he's gonna peek around the corner and I'm dead
this is the wrong way wrong way he can't get in he can't get in this game is unbelievable
do they spit do they spit anybody know if they spit they spawn little ones
okay they spit do they I don't know if they spit or not don't light the vent on fire Jeremy
but there's I'm gonna go sit through a grenade he's still alive okay he's still alive okay okay
okay okay okay literally my life depends on making these shots I don't hear anything
are you sure they spawn every time nothing spawned nothing spawned
but there's probably something else down there I need to heal there's another one okay
oh god oh god oh god oh god that one just tried to bait me did you see that did you see that little
thing try to he's gonna okay this is this is a problem this is a problem I just this is still
a little one right there that's gonna be the end of me it's gonna be the problem there's a little
one hanging out somewhere that's just that's the fucking worst thing that's ever happened to me in
a game without a doubt that's the scariest because I know I have zero health and that's
it's like 30 minutes of that was really really really real that was real that's what would
happen if a monster tried to kill me in real life like my heart right now was going that if
a monster ran down a hallway and tried to kill me that's that's the worst thing ever holy shit
I don't want to do this again it's like a 30 fucking minutes segment and it sucks there's
no other little ones right they would have come is the game just spawning these things at this
point I'm gonna run out of fire don't back up what do you mean stop backing up if a small one
comes in here I need room to shoot it otherwise I'm dead oh shit little ones little ones little
ones how many little ones just one there was two he was blocking the bullets he was blocking the
bullets with his body what the hell is going on here die back there die back there die back there
die back there die back there go go go no not go what do you mean go what do you mean go
little guy okay get back in here it's safe in here I wish I had a flare
I saw a little one running by and that thing's not dead where is it oh fuck yeah this sucks
why won't he come over here get over here get over here why are you doing this
oh little one tires in please I have 30 bullets please I saw a little one running around I'm
gonna go super slow like extra slow because is there I think I'm just gonna throw some grenades
down there because there is a little one I saw it run over here do I just to get on the elevator
where is it um do you see it I don't hear it oh my god heard it I heard it where is it where was
it was it on the right side back up back up back up back up oh that's so bad where was it it was
laughing at you it was one of the ones from the big guys that died it just starts walking around
down here okay I'm gonna do something that might seem a little ridiculous but I'm gonna go for it
that's too dangerous that's really bad it's a day it's very dangerous
no no no I know I know it's very dangerous it's not a good idea it's a very bad idea
is he over there I think I just saw a movement I don't know I have no idea
you motherfucker you're standing right here I knew you were over here oh my god he was trying to kill
me he was trying to kill me he was trying to kill me he was trying to kill me I have 17 bullets
left of this gun I have 17 bullets so honest to god I hope that was the last enemy that I need
to get rid of run now but I can't run now there's another one over here somewhere
just gotta land the shots my god oh my god oh my god I don't know oh my god oh my god
that I did it I can't I'm not it's not over that's too much stress am I gonna get a health pack
it's okay because I restart the level I don't I restart the level that's it don't worry
everything's fine it was a new screen it was a new area see thank god there he is
I just have to make the shot I'm so fucking glad I don't have to do that again
please give me a health pack I I deserve it I earned it that was a no scope okay I'm just
gonna throw grenades I'm just gonna shoot grenades I have like fucking 15 of them
I have like 20 just fire grenades down the goddamn hallway fuck it why is it not fire
I swear to god man like I'm trying to shoot the gun oh my god how many motherfuckers exist
how many motherfuckers exist how many motherfuckers exist I have to do this
with zero HP you have to do a boss fight after this too oh that's fantastic I'm I can't wait
I'm looking forward to it how many motherfuckers are there get warm get warm warm up I have health
packs I don't have health packs okay warmed up what we got anybody running down here eat
grenade to heal if only if only that were real all right I need dual headphones for this one
get the hair on my face there's something to blow up over here right there how we doing who's there
one guy I wonder can I sneak it wait till he comes over here oh shit okay warm up this rub
of banding is killing me well I might have to snipe that guy I'm gonna go for it I have to
land this shot though if I don't land this shot that I'm it's over I get one chance ain't gonna
fool me not at this stage cold cold cold cold cold I'm cold go back to it go back go back run run
run run run run run cold I'm good okay I'm fine back again I can't imagine there's that much left
shoot the flamethrower for warmth that doesn't work no I don't believe you and I'm afraid to do
it because I have zero HP all right where we at careful careful I was doing so well
and then the most arbitrarily stupid game mechanic that has only shown up twice
in the entire game it's from the movie I can't fucking believe it this shit is fucking
whack as it's whack this shit's whack that's a bird that's the best term for it this game
sucks omega lol and now I gotta do this shit again I got the muscle memory this entire fucking
level cave dude if I get one bullet I die I was do I was like doing so fucking well juggling back
and forth killing guy wait get the guy and no if you stay outside from you get colon and you die
this just happened twice in 14 hours of video game didn't that fun I'm fucked and now I'm
gonna watch the end on youtube look if that shit was throughout the whole game and it was like a
core mechanic of the video game no it's just been like it's been in like 12 minutes of gameplay
what's the point it doesn't have a point why can't the guy just go like oh it's cold out
I don't understand it doesn't do anything it I shot myself in the head with a sniper
cave cave cave cave cave wait like you mean like cave like cave in you can't even see me come on I
can't if that guy shot me aiming like that I would have been fucking furious cave on left coming up
cave on left coming up hold on he's so angry wouldn't you be wouldn't you be see we don't we
see we don't we don't get to see we don't get to see you playing this game and going like this
like fuck fuck yeah right like you do and you go and like you don't want to wake up your mother
over there so you just go like I know I know just hurry up and crouch walk over here both of you
that's all of you okay where's this cave you got a special cave let me just headshot this guy real
quick damn it what cave I gotta go back I have to run back now where's this what cave all right
the guy's not showing up he's not showing up I gotta go back there's no cave there's no cave
there's no cave there's no cave there's no cave there's no cave there's no cave there's no cave
honey yeah is everything okay in there yeah I just uh I just I dropped something okay you sure
yeah I just dropped something I like that it startled me it startled me a little and then
the door closes and you're just like but you know you yeah you can't you've already burnt
your fucking like mom came in the room cool down so you can't do it again did you guys hear the
speedrun of this game we listened for less than 30 seconds and it was like fuck this game this
game sucks and that was just a random portion of the speedrun and those you might be asking
about the turbo just fucking turn it off I can't I don't know why I can't do it I can't fuck it I
can't do it I've got to do this I have to play this it's just the way it is I don't have time
for this the zero hp run has to be finished target spotted where the fuck are you oh my god
that was a stress burp go back go back go back snipe them it doesn't work that way if I if I
turn the corner and snipe one of them's gonna shoot me with one bullet and I'm dead if you
miss the cave I'm gonna leave there is no cave you just want to leave and that's all right there
is no cave you just want to leave and that you don't have to make that excuse you can just go
I'm it's cold hold on cave in an area with sniper there is a cave no there's no cave
there's no cave why am I talking like this okay where's the cave where's there's a cave I'm so
much I'm in so much fucking trouble right now like I pulled that guy before I can't reach
from there I got to snipe this guy where's the other guy all right here he comes here he comes
here wait wait wait wait is that the last anymore I can go back okay if there's a cave up there
I will give you a wink and say cool there's a cave over there that's all you get if I could even take
one single bullet it would be it's not as horrible all right there's a guy right here he's standing
there I have to snipe him there's no other way I have to hit this guy with a bullet in the head
or at least close enough where the fuck is he there's another guy right here it's cold it's
gotta run back it's cold it's too cold too cold here comes the cave it comes the cave wait just
wait a minute I don't think there's a cave I can't just wait I need to go back here there's a cave
on the left and the right there's no cave he doesn't trust us no of course I don't why would I trust
everyone it's like 40 percent of people are actively trying to get me to die
what do you mean why can't I trust there's no way okay you're telling there's a cave to the left and
the right those are not caves they're indents this doesn't do anything that doesn't do anything
other side other side there's a guy to kill this guy wait holy shit you were lying oh my god oh my
not only is there a cave here there's like full thank you I guess thanks a lot oh so there's a
secret cave okay whatever uh whatever oh there's a secret cave that you didn't get now I need a
save point holy shit there's a person here okay what is that you are inside this is not even a
cave this is fucking underdwelling this is a hobbit hole cave would be like bigger I'm just
gonna stay in the hole why haven't come out there's a guy with a flamethrower right there
and you're alive fantastic I don't know how that's possible holy shit he's doing the thing I'm doing
wow oh that's holy shit that's ridiculous good let's go I remember cave right there
I knew there was a cave there it's a sniper
uh nice aim how about this aim how about this aim it's cold it's too cold why can't there be a
save point in there what were they thinking what were they doing one two I'm getting like an itchy
body down another cave cave cold too cold too cold way too cold okay get in the cave dear how's my
IBS uh I have IBD but same thing kind of same general idea uh it's um it's really fucking
annoying actually but I'm not even sure that's what the problem is right now having all kinds
of strange medical mishaps he's not dead didn't I shoot him in the head another place to go
another is it too cold get back to the cave cave safety cave yeah we there's another there's
another cave where's the other cave he's he's nerd necking slightly very slightly you guys want
me to click a link when I'm in the middle of like the end of this game that's been very hard for me
oh I got an alt tab right now and click a link I don't know if I can't where's the other cave
you guys talking about there's got to be something back here like a secret like a health pack
yeah of course there is something back here of course there is can I get a fucking save point
save point game over Whitley I didn't know he was standing there I don't think so
I control you right now I control every man on this continent oh your pathetic sabotage
of the consignment at the airstrip only delayed the inevitable it's been him the whole time
there is an evac team on its way to this location once I take the chopper I will begin global
infection game over this game is just beginning oh great that was chapter one all right save point
thank god and there is like a million health packs over here and all oh man is this gonna
is there any cheats for this one is there any cheat codes for this one anyway like stand
cheat codes for this one anyway like stand still and he can't kill you he can't hurt you
can I jump what are you doing in here holy shit ah well I'm sometimes walk into that
wow what an idiot something just acted I just took unnecessary damage like big time
but I had to see what was gonna happen these guys are boneheads boneheads
there's some saving ammo moving blind what save the game in the dome all right got it oh careful
you probably put that there that guy placed that c4 there oh what the fuck he shot me point blank
with a shawty oh I'm playing a different Stephen King novel now what are you talking about
what's what's the other Stephen King no under the dome invisible good how do you have this
many people that are working for you that are just this willing to just just to die for this
like what do you why you guys know that's an alien right that's an alien I'm human that that's an
alien he controls them you don't control me otherwise I wouldn't have shot that c4
fuck this guy oops a daisy somebody died that was like three people somebody else walked over the
c4 oh my god this is so stupid I don't even I can't even react to this anymore it's just absurd
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god
we're good oh big thing of items why I how do I get over there save it save it boss time is
this the last boss it has to be what a journey I hope it's easy where am I going uh I think
eventually I'll end up back where I was I can feel my face being strange I can hear it I could
hear the like it's weird okay let's go final encounter let's go done with this shit let's do
it and it's cold outside and they're they all have snipers what the is that it that's it that's it
that's it that's it that's it that's it up up this is not a shelter though is it this is one of those
games that like the you go to blockbuster and you rent this game at the first like six the first
like five to six hours are like great oh that was awesome we've rented the thing and then you have
to return it don't get a late fee for this one you know I'm saying just play the first like four
hours of it it was good the first like four to six hours just pretend and bring it back to blockbuster
you don't have to play this game again all right am I okay behind these boxes I think so I should
be right but I've been fighting the cold too thanks for standing still I have to go now I
have to go now is it warm in here it's not it's not warm in here it's not warm in here it's not
warm in here I have to leave now it's not warm in here that's all right just two two broken legs
it wants me to use this that's for sure how am I supposed to go from here is it a save point why
am I people's the size of raisins I don't know what's that mean means you're on drugs I can
assure you I'm not um okay so this way this is a way to go I just took damage what was the I took
damage that was bullshit oh that's the kind of special sound my cat my cat puke whatever that
it's too loud for me to talk finally I get to be outside an area that's not tiny I get to actually
look at how huge this is too thank god are we just leaving can we just leave need some help
yeah no shit I need you to circle close once I fire you've got 10 seconds to get this chopper
as far away as you can why is it all blue murder shoot that thing hey easy easy where you're
driving shoot it why did I get all the grenade launchers for that's not it excellent timing there
pilot early retirement from jan ink no not exactly on my way back from an extended arctic
vacation uh-huh so what's your name sir kurt russell mccready rj mccready us outpost 131
just didn't happen he's just a helicopter guy thanks kurt russell we don't even get a song
we just the guy the guy got it like called for dinner that's it that's the credit song
it was just the start it was the two chords and edit that's how we get it the game ending
ruins the movie ending why did it give me a huge stockpile of weapons what was my least favorite
part uh all of today give or take look at the link all right hold away that might be like a secret
after credit scene hold on wait wait wait what does it after credit scene this isn't marvel
this is before marvel the thing came out in the 50s okay what are you linking let's see what it
looks like I know that you like separated my eyes you separated my eyes look you took my eyes and
you like separated them a little bit it's not that's not right I'm telling you these are not
real images you went like this and you shaved shaved shaved and then you like pulled back a
little and then you like made the bridge of my nose bigger oh my god we're gas lighting him
oh well that was the thing it was worth playing except for the last three hours but I did it
I got to the end scale of one to ten the first six hours was like an eight in the last
five or six hours was like a four now do it on hard I did do it on hard absolute quality
now play the outer worlds uh so here's let me wait I gotta talk we gotta talk about a few things here
so as of the oh man this is I'm gonna sit down for this one so all personalities voices are
impersonated okay uh so I the Halloween stream is gonna be on the 31st it's gonna be fairly
elaborate if you have anything that you like to suggest right that you for secret slime actions
that channel is going to be closed on the 28th there's not going to be any more time to do it
because after 28th I need to compile with the people that are helping me produce this whole
thing all the actions and get them into a template for the stream and I can't see them I cannot be
looking at them how do we pick and we vote for them you don't I just want a shitload to pull from
so then there's a ton of options how many per round that is to be determined probably probably
we'll do like one or two per round until we get later on to a point where there's like some upwards
of like five to ten going on at the same time so this also means because this was kind of short
notice and the production team that did the carnival was doing is helping me do this too
they're doing they're doing all the production stuff it was too soon to do this in Vegas so
I'm going back to the east coast as of the this coming week here so I'm going back to the east
coast and I'm going to kind of do a two birds at one stone scenario where I go visit my family
so I'm going to visit my family because I haven't seen a lot of them in a long time some of my family
I haven't seen some of my family members and some of my friends in just over a year so I was in
Boston like three or four I think four months ago whatever it was maybe for a day or two
trying to remember when the exact day was but I really only had like one or two days there
so I'm going to go down there do the stream so I won't be around next week go down there do the
stream and then I'm going to stay for a few days and then come back so take a hot air balloon back
it takes too long I'm going to hide this tape when I'm finished if none of us make it at least
there'll be some kind of a record but yeah that's so I'm not the the Halloween stream is not going
to be here not going to be in Vegas I'm going to be traveling for it and that's pretty much all I
wanted to say also another important thing to remember is I still have
the shooter blade and shooter blade 2 in fact they're right here
that is something that I want to do probably I kind of I don't know if I want to start that's
the thing about starting something like the Outer Worlds I know I have to play the Outer Worlds
because it's Fallout New Vegas just again but different I want to play it but before starting
the Outer Worlds I think I'm going to wait till I get back from the Halloween stream because I
don't want to just play it for like one day and then disappear for three days do the Halloween
stream and then come back three days later so we'll do tomorrow we'll do the shooter blade and
shooter blade 2 because they're classic uh they're classic video games and might as well
get rid of the rest of the ps1 stuff that's here and we'll see how that takes us see how we go
from there sire I also have siren that's another one shit that's right I gotta do that before
Halloween I don't shooter blade and shooter blade 2 won't take that long oh fuck siren's like a 30
hour game whatever fucking happy Halloween Thanksgiving whatever shit this I mean I've
applied like four times all right and that is going to be the end of this stream but it's not
because we're going to go back uh this is going to turn into a just a chill
session we're going to do the bits that I missed from a couple days ago three four days ago
uh let me just I'm gonna hide this tag when I'm finished if no stream is officially over as of
right now so let's go over the bits that we missed and I will be right back see you guys in a minute
all right we can get started here with the outro I can't even tell if this is still broken or not
because there's been such insane gifted subs I think this is from a few days ago but so because
we're doing two streams worth of bits and one of the that last this last stream was nine and a half
hours so we're going to try to go through these at a decent pace and I always say that all the time
but it has to happen now because it has to two hours later no no no no no no what's happening
909 see you in like see you in like 35 minutes all right how about that how's that sound anyways
this is from a few days ago I didn't do these I missed them I had to go I streamed for too long
and my stomach was all fucked up so here we are now uh we had 250 bits from Peaceful Haley they
said hey Jeremy how you doing hope all was well just wanted to ask if you're planning on going
to Galaxy's Edge at Disney uh probably not anytime soon I know many people are very happy
with it right now but I hope for the last one anyways have a good stream talking about building
a lightsaber oh shit you can build you can build a lightsaber there like a real one well it's not
real but is it though those things are shit what uh probably not I don't have any plans in the
immediate future to go to Galaxy's Edge I kind of want to wait until nobody cares anymore
and then just get to go on all the rides and just get to eat all the food and not have to
wait in line for anything so I don't know if I go like somewhere 2020 but yeah I am interested
all two of the rides oh yeah there's only two rides but there's aren't they good though
Galaxy's Edge is already empty oh well maybe I'll go soon I don't know
but thank you Fitty for the 550 bits yo my dude man person I really appreciate you making the
streams more EU friendly can I get some slugs in the chat yeah I'm happy to pull it back a couple
hours because it's better for me too can we get some slugs also Fitty for five dollars and 50
cents they say adding to my previous message it's okay that the past few streams have been a little
bit shorter I understand how tough it can be for streaming for eight hours while on thermonuclear
laxatives yes this is true but I am not on them anymore I'm on another medication still though
and it's really it's just fucking me up but not to the point where I have to stream for like two
or three hours and then leave that only happened one time though there was only two streams all
of last week or all the last two weeks that were like three to five hours long so it worked out
okay but yeah thank you appreciate the concern Marv Ashbegali thanks for the 250 you maybe watch
The Thing in order to fully enjoy this stream hope this game is as good as the movie it's not
uh not even close it was all right thank you Plank for the 550 bits
there's a fun fact Quentin Tarantino's movie The Hateful Eight was loosely based off the
1982 film The Thing he also used unused music from the original score of The Thing and of course
Kurt Russell interesting interesting hmm Quentin Tarantino I have not seen the new movie I have not
seen uh Once Upon a Time Hollywood I would like to I haven't seen Joker yet I'd like to need a
movie night at some point here but yeah that's interesting that's cool hey Dart Lane thanks for
the 550 I hate things why bit slave thanks for the 400 bits this is a cool game make sure you
try out the cheat code insane furry suit owo to have all the characters and monsters be in
fursuits epic gamer experiences thank you thank you sir canine for the 500 bits okay so I know
I need to re-earn your trust after yesterday's rick rolling so I found an actual quality video
for you to watch I'm not going to click it thank you for the 500 bits appreciate it fool me once
shame on you fool me twice shame on you for trying to fool me over and over again it's not nice
can't we just talk hey thank you wreckers d wrecker said for the 250 hey germ glad you liked my
ankle tattoo my one face whatever it is the chat face the chat face me it's me right there you go
I'm from Northern Ireland and as of midnight here same-sex marriage was made legal
that's pretty sick is that for real did that actually just happen
oh well nice that's good that's really good good to know breaking news from four days ago
file actor lich just gave another 5 000 bits on top of their like 10 grand from four days ago
they say hey jerma here's the money I owe you for letting me use your blood weird results though
might want to see a doctor because the blood tried to eat me because I am the fucking thing
this is where it gets crazy because there was like seven or eight thousand dollars four days ago and
I'm not making that up it's not like a laugh-out-loud hole hey there's like seven there was like seven or
eight thousand dollars four days ago so this is it gets nuts here and I tried to go over as many
as I could a few days ago but if there's any that I missed let's see if I can pick them up
because holy shit it was over 8k I it could I yes hey you guys ready to watch more thing in a few
days uh eshanji was one of those people that gave a ton and this is a thousand bit message chat take
bits test to prove you aren't infected well you did you did you did you did you did trust me you
did because I about five to ten minutes after that it went insane thank you streaky KL for the
thousand bits why does this exist is it what is it a jerma versus star amv I don't I don't know why
this exists is this something we're gonna have to we're gonna watch on community content night
or should I not is this all right I I'm gonna copy this because it might even be in in the
discord already but I'm gonna I'm gonna save this when I come back this looks pretty fucked
they paid money now no I have a very specific rule if you have a community created video or
artwork we do it on the community created nights I've made that clear like 10 times
if they pay money you have to show and do it on commit what what do you mean now what about
links and chat yeah a link in chat for like a face edit is not a three and a half minute
fucking video this video is five years old what this was not made like last week this was made
like fucking five years ago this is fucking freaking me out that man gave you a thousand
dollars for this no they didn't this no they did not it was ten dollars and it was really
really appreciated why do you have a theater screen for this all right let's all right fine
um I will I will watch at least 30 seconds of this video he was peer pressured peer pressure
for 30 seconds is this even gonna all right here we go no don't start playing now don't start
playing stop no it's gonna fucking frog video again stop I don't want to play this one
god damn it man no get over here why is this permanently saved
all right here you go let's see
me
all right well thanks for saying the thing the vod is going to be destroyed from this
so
what the fuck was this from where did you get these pictures
oh I smashed my fucking face that's what I hit my fucking head like really hard
what do you mean story time I made a video on it like fucking seven years ago it's not even a
fucking cool story it's just a fucking sad one I got up too fast waking up in the morning and like
have low blood pressure that's it that's the story play that video instead no but the scar I don't
have a scar god damn it all right turn it off turn it off turn it off get out of here turn it off
with the music on I was watching that that's too bad you can you can watch it any minute of the
day he fell down injured himself it was actually really fucking strange it was very very strange
by the way I'm fine this was like six and a half years ago uh thank you streaky KL uh they said
why does this exist I don't know because somebody decided to make that video and so I watched it we
watched it thank you gnarly for the 250 gnarly hey I need to decide what game I should play I was
going to try to beat Luigi's Mansion before Halloween but I just beat mother three and I
would really want to play mother three mother two in earthbound which one should I play next
earthbound absolutely hands down yeah earthbound got it done seal it cv fd thanks for the thousand
bits I'll be your friend jerma thanks I appreciate it glad that you can be my friend mini clips thanks
for the thousand bits this stream is a gold mine for noises I think yeah any horror game like that
is just stressful and horrible but thank you for the thousand bits appreciate it Freudian weapon
thanks for the 500 bits the thing is a personal favorite horror movie of mine the original by the
way I never knew they made a game of it random question if you could create direct a horror
movie what would it be also thanks for streaming uh it'd be about the and it would be an invisible
monster and they'd have to like throw water at it and stuff to like get those glistening
do they can see where it was no I'm not talking about like it's invisible and it like affects your
mind no no no like it's just an invisible monster and they have to like spray paint they get like
spray paint and shit and they like they get ready and that's they get spray paint they get
buckets of water buckets of ink and stuff this is a spongebob episode whatever that's what it'd be
thank you sad vega for the 250 is definitely a new germote germote emote
no this is the this is the face from oh my god uh can I tell you guys that I was in bed
laughing at this image I was sitting around seriously just lying in bed the last I think
maybe two nights after that stream I was just I was fucking dying laughing I was cracking the
fuck up Kim was actually sleeping right next to me and I I think I woke her up like twice
I wasn't even looking at it I was just thinking about it emote material though yes I would say
so too thank you hey blue thank you blue for the 550 you posted the same image twice that image I
don't know thank you Jules for the 250 hey German sorry I haven't been keeping up lately about your
stomach problems but I heard that you were on a FODMAP diet and progress of what types of food
you should avoid or what the doctor said I'm not doing it anymore because it didn't really do
anything for me I was on it for a few weeks and it just wasn't changing anything and then I
I had a colonoscopy and you know a few months ago and well there was these things in there that we
wanted that maybe you should try this and maybe you should try this and maybe you should try this
and then now I have another um I have another endoscopy I have to do instead of going up they're
going down so they're gonna see if something's going on inside my stomach I don't know it's
been why it's been a very strange uh eight months we'll say that I am just not fucking around I'm
gonna try to see what the hell is wrong with me because it may not even be my stomach it I don't
know it's very very annoying though we're trying to see what's going on I'm just we're just going
we're just each appointment what are we gonna try now till we figure it out that's pretty much it
and now I'm gonna just keep doing that I have an endoscopy camera can I help why do you have one
it's weird but thank you don't worry about me I'm fine I am in good spirits and then the ball of
koala came in with 3,800 bits and then 3,800 bits my brain is trying to do that math very quickly
68 and then 69 70 71 32 32 75 76 76 dollars and 50 cents this is just no message just to try
he was trying to do a money jupiter it's just I'm not sure if it went through I hope it did
because that's a that's a very expensive jupiter thank you so much ball of koala thank you thank
you c4g for the 250 hey germa bad news the in-house team I usually get to write my chat messages
decided to unionize and they went on strike apparently they want wages I don't know but
when I told them I spent my last 250 on these bits and they got really angry thanks thanks for
the 250 phylactery let's just give another 5,000 bits 50 dollars again again again germa don't die
if you do I'll have only italics to watch and he is go team makes me feel things thank you for the
50 bucks and I'm doing fine don't worry about me I'm fine it's just something I need to figure
out what's going on and that's it I'll figure it out don't worry I always do I always do
appreciate the concern though thank you but hey uh swiggity swanky thanks for the 250 thank you
for playing this fun fun game I have a fond memory of the film which was from the old 1950s version
my mom let me let me put 1950s version my mom let me watch one day I asked my amazing distant
dad to watch film again and he showed me the 80s version without any question or doubt in his mind
and this was when I was around 10 years old life was never the same afterwards for better or worse
I don't know but I have a thing for gore fests did they actually do a thing from like the 50s
I don't remember that it's weird thank you sticks renegade for the 275 I remember getting this game
back when Benny's used to be around it was $12 I bought it at least 12 years ago it was scary and
so hard for me I could not beat it at all and had to use cheats I don't know how you like it since
I'm watching the VOD five hours after you started well you know now thank you slow update for the
275 how's it going my man Jermis 100 987 that's not that's not even what you wrote Jermis 987
it is what you wrote here to tell you that this game is too scary for me so I'll be crop I will
crop everything but the face cam and have it on mute the downside is you'll look like a crackhead
screaming for no reason so if you can look like a meth head screaming for no reason that would
greatly improve my viewing experience anyways uh war and hate peace and love you got it and then
this is uh this is where it goes completely and totally off the fucking rails there is I think we
got almost all these already four nights ago but it is I have to I'm gonna have to scroll
it's gonna be like to get through this and there are some in the middle here that I did not touch
upon four days ago but my god uh roid burto gave 11 hundred bits fuse us create me father I don't
know whatever that means fuse us martin had a meme thanks to the 550 derma it's time to man up and
kill him the only hitbox that matters is the fat dude in the bottom of the monster use your grenades
before ever running out throw them over the box in the middle of like the money stream is like advice
I love it thank you though and thank you to the fucking hundreds I'm just going up bob boy thanks
to the 500 bits remember when you had like to spread the infection this stream makes that into
a joke years in the making that's true I should have said it at least once I'm not sure why I
didn't I'm looking at all these subs and shit oh my god streaky KL thanks for the 1500 bits in the
middle of all this not as much but here add to the pile it was a pile it was I I'm still going
ACDC freak thanks for the 400 bits it isn't much but here if you're gonna give this channel money
don't ever think it's not enough because even if you give a cent a quarter it doesn't I I can't
believe it that somebody would do that so click the link click the link click the link what is
this germa oh what is this why is it not loading I saw that all right what okay all right so why do
I need to click this one that's oh this is real is that real is that a real picture what holy shit
that's real is it no hey yeah but yeah I can't even fucking believe I'm this it was hard to
process when it was happening but looking at it now this is ridiculous bait thank you bait
naley for the thousand bits big funding for the next germa rumble I already told you guys that
the halloween stream has already been paid for as of that stream yesterday paid for it there's more
you're looking more of these what is this the single eye okay you guys are fucking crazy
put that thing back where it came from thank you everybody that gave subs and bits four days ago
seriously I'm trying to scroll through and find the ones that I uh that we didn't do
Avery drop dead thanks for the 500 bits they say hopping on the bit train hi germa I got a job at
taco bell a couple weeks ago and I'm so glad I get to finally catch a stream uh love you and
your content so much man you the best we stan a himbo king I honestly don't know what that last
sentence means we stan a himbo king thank you thanks a lot appreciate that thank omega lull you
why did you write that but thank you Avery thank you martin had a meme for 5500 bits I'm not sure
I saw this one germa you've helped me keep my mind off some crazy shit I went through over the past
year I'm happy to finally be in a place where I can pay back both you and your community for
all the good times this stream has been a big mood I think I remember maybe hitting this one
but regardless that's a fucking incredibly nice message everybody here's awesome thank you for
the huge amount of money you gave a lot four days ago thank you and then there are hundreds of
community subs ecap thanks for the 500 bits I only have bits but I'm joining in love your work
jeremy thank you my goodness it just keeps going peaceful hailey thanks for the 275 hey again I
just bought my star wars tickets since the new trailer dropped oh yeah the neutral the new star
wars trailer I was about to just say something that people would be really upset with I'm glad
I didn't do it I'm very happy that I just zip because I was about to do something that people
would have been like dude what what the fuck man I didn't even know and I would have been like
how do you not know how do you know the trailer did what about the trailer and then we've been
really mad at me he hasn't seen the trailer yes I have I will say one word for you to know that
I've seen the trailer ocean waves on the ocean that's how you know I've seen the trailer don't
tell me I haven't seen the damn trailer but I expect good things from this last movie since
george lucas had some say in it did he that's interesting I thought they like voted him off the
island anyways enough to be talking about star wars I used to love this game as a kid and I'm
glad you had a good time with it have a good night Jar Jar's the key to all this
you guys are fucking hilarious thank you disinterest for the 250 jerma people gave you so much to you
tonight because they love you for being an extremely entertaining streamer and one of the most
genuine kind-hearted people any of us have ever met I'm floored by that I can't I'm just trying
to do I'm just trying to do me you know that's it I'm I don't know if I'm the most genuine person
ever I just try to do as best I can that's it you know but I am absolutely floored that you feel
that way I mean you lie sometimes but we forgive you yeah 90 of all the things that I say are not
even true and I've said that that's a statement thank you seriously that means a shitload ah t
mccabe from four days ago says 1500 bits keep it going you cowards they did they did
feeling his ego tear him down quick you have bald oh shit thank you t m kb for your huge
contributions and your 1500 bits thank you sroy it thanks for the 700 bits pog champs necromancy
mage 300 bits don't let the flame die out novas thanks for the 250 stream it becomes millionaire
on stream this is unbelievable I can't even I can't even understand this I'm just keep scrolling
sage the ghost thanks for 500 bits big love to you buddy thanks for always making me laugh thanks
for always watching the streams whenever you can and supporting this live stream
of a weird guy on the internet I can't believe it thank you did you check the toilet I did he's a
weird guy I'm like weird and quirky and odd right I'm like a weird thanks thank you for supporting
this weird quirky stream I get to have him sometimes I get to have him sometimes I'm
unfollowing no please don't please God don't do that please God thank you for supporting this
we're just a couple of we're just we're just a bunch of like all right I won't I won't I'll
stop that stuff I'll stop the thing broke me yes it did because that game was fucking hell on earth
in a video game coded to have graphical interfaces show up as monsters and make me angry just a
couple of humans just no sorry just a couple of humans I can't even say it just a couple of
humans I can't even say it no but seriously though all jokes aside thank you thanks for
watching the stream that was sage the ghost with 500 bits eager oatmeal 500 bits you deserve every
one of those subs you magnificent bastard I'm glad you think so thank you mentosi and thanks
to the 500 bits congrats on recently walking a thousand miles a thousand miles you called hurry
up run back in cold too many links I like how he pauses when he's flustered he gets flustered
okay what is this is this a song jerma walks a thousand miles I can't play this it is okay
this is just me walking this looks fucking good like really funny and shit like I want to watch
this when people are like for a community stream because I don't want to nuke the vod for tonight's
stream when the community content nights can just get nuked yeah we're saving this this looks like
a lot of effort went into this one say nuked again nuked somebody just wrote I don't give a
shit show it easy come on easy come on jerma say the line that guy's pissed don't be it's all right
don't worry you'll see it I don't give a shit
I actually said five a shit yes you did but I was I was putting a g there because I didn't know if
you accidentally pressed f so I mean I do that shit all the time I write like you know I don't
give a I don't like you have a shift you know what I mean admit to say I was just making it so
you know what I mean I do that all the time but we'll see it soon because that second community
content stream is gonna happen just a few days after I get back from the Halloween stream I think
that might be the first thing I do we'll see probably don't quote me on that but put quotes
around this multi-trip gave 5500 bits I think I caught it but I'm sorry I can't only afford
50 bucks this time please don't hit me I yeah I got it already I remember that one sushi p thanks
for the 2884 bits I just got here I don't know what this number is why do we care about it
open the damn meme I have two personalities nicest person you'll ever meet twisted fucking
psychopath oh I hate this I hate this so much it's unbelievable how much I hate this oh god damn it
uh necromancy mage thanks for 300 bits germa use this for a bus ticket out of town before
the IRS gets you for money laundering money what do you I'm not supposed to be laughing I have to
do a no laughing stream tomorrow because like every time I laugh my stomach hurts IRS official
no I pay my fucking taxes he's already see I saw I saw click the link I did I did I did
I have two personalities yeah and I'm not showing that on my own stream
laughing is healthy yeah and unless you have some kind of strange mystery medical condition
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me but thank you uh necromancy mage uh Peter thanks for
the 300 bits cool guy thanks Peter appreciate it and then I remember the ishanji 275 dollar
message that said I've been trying to get flaccid lock trending phylactery lich came in my will be
done another 250 niall orion thanks for the 250 you guys gave too much money now germans are gonna
retire that's not gonna happen that just means that I'm gonna do more videos like more streams
let fate choose now what I'm not videos you know what I mean streams hey man I just wanted to let
you know that you were my gateway drug to watching pro pro wrestling this is from gleam for 250 bits
I always love the rumbles and after re-watching them with my sister uh apple shift I decided to
give real wwe a shot I started watching raw and immediately fell in love it's so fucking fun at
first I thought that the fact that it was all scripted makes it stupid but in reality it makes
it even more fun it's like theater with punching thank you so much for introducing this to me
everyone's gonna call me a boomer but you can watch all the old shit on youtube I think all
the attitude era stuff with stone cold the rock the undertaker cain that you want to watch that
mankind getting thrown off the goddamn roof they don't do shit like that anymore mankind
got thrown off the roof of the cage actually they really did it and it almost fucking killed
them yeah it was it was unbelievable that guy would uh what's if I could why can't I think
of his name Mick Foley it was ridiculous he just didn't give us he just didn't give
that guy was just legendary at doing crazy shit in that ring I think they've dialed it down
in the last 10 years or so but I don't know I've only seen a few things recently is there's a new
wrestling thing in town though isn't there that AEW isn't that the new hot thing right now is
AEW is like really starting to get people to come over and it's better than the wwe because the
wwe is like not as good anymore now speaking of wwe things that aren't good anymore can you believe
they even released 2k20 wwe I am so happy that we will probably never get a fucking wwe 2k game
ever again I hope not oh god I pray every single day yukes decided they were like no this is like
boring and sucks in his wicked shitty every year and they left so please everyone put your hands
together and pray that this the thing that yukes comes up with is like it used to be back in like
2013 2012 am I going to use 2k20 for the next drama rumble probably not because it's fucking
terrible I mean like bugs are funny but when they get like when the game can't even function if I
spend like two weeks or like a full week making wrestlers in that game and we can't get a rumble
to even work I'm not even sure that's worth doing and that shit's 60 bucks yuke isn't on the series
anymore no because they went to do their own thing they do make it funny though maybe I don't know
I'll I'll check it out but I don't know do 2k14 again I can't I would I just can't it's on the
PlayStation 3 and it's the last one that it was the last 2k game that was on the PlayStation 3
and it just chugs it doesn't it really is not supposed to even be on there it was the final
one that they stuffed as much bullshit into and it's just it it takes like 60 seconds to load hair
in that goddamn game if you have too many layers on a character I would but it was too it's too
painful to try to put to make a character anymore it's the effort that is respected plus I don't
have any of the old wrestlers anymore I mean I made like 60 people in the old 2k14 2k13 games
can you get it on ps4 I wish unless it's emulated but emulating a ps3 half of the games don't even
work more than that more than half actually I think I don't know I'll let me I'll see what
I'm gonna do but I'm glad you got into wrestling it's a really fun sport to watch
Dubski dude thanks for the 250 hey Jerma I heard you were having health problems recently but I
missed the last couple streams so I've only gotten small bits of the story uh according to chat you
took a bath and your skin turned yellow and to treat it your doctor prescribed weapons grade
gamer laxatives this sounds really serious I hope you're doing okay you know what I'm just gonna
say yes yes thank you rat boy for the 525 and rat boy says nothing but this which is
here's some dunkly donut because you're epic what is hold on this is the fucking dumbest
thing I've ever seen why do people make these here's some dunk it's just me screaming that
what the fuck thank you rat boy appreciate it and then finally from four days ago it was
the ball of koala to end it with 550 bits hey jerma glad you're feeling well enough to do a
full nine plus hours can't put into words how much your streams mean to me haven't had many
people to talk to since I came home from uni and you and your community keep me on the up and up
while I make friends at work fuck yeah I'm really glad to hear that don't usually do don't know is
this personal but you and everyone here is awesome thank you so much ball of koala I hope
you're hanging out in the discord it's a great place to be and that is the bits that we missed
from four days ago thank you everybody that contributed there were three thousand forty one
dollars of bits 1,294 gifted subs and 347 regular subscriptions four days ago that is the most
outrageous number I've ever seen cannot fucking believe that thank you guys and now we are going
to do today this shouldn't take us that long so don't just strap in too much too far how long has
it been like 45 minutes I told you this one could be that bad I tell everyone say hello it's gonna
be like three hours uh thank you to Kazzy gave five community subs I think off stream thank you
Kazzy uh jerma's stinky feet thanks for the 500 bits I cannot wait for glue man to suplex perappa
and break his fucking neck in this year's rumble uh I don't know thank you to snowflakes am I right
thank you for the 250 bits I did some portraits of you and kim hope you all enjoy portraits did we
see these ones already I think we may have seen these and then bob boy thanks for the five
community subs we did it for you bob boy holy shit we have I've not seen these this is fucking
ridiculous I don't I just tied I just named this image to put on my desktop bob boy
all right I have to get okay kim's gonna lose kim's gonna lose her fucking mind when she sees
this one she's gonna fucking lose her mind okay that one's called kim bob boy that's just
just a reference to what I know it is all right you ready for this shit you ready for these
oh my goodness it's so huge it's such like a big resolution image it's so good community content
night only I know but all right so put these in the we'll put them in the community content
folder but I just need I just I need to download this for kim this is for kim isn't that fucking
crazy though that's awesome look at the one look at the look at kim kim's kim's is like it's as if
you just took a picture of her can't be watching the stream right now that's fucking awesome who
did that that was snowflakes thanks for the 250 bits thanks snowflakes thanks for the 250 bits
and like the the seven thousand dollar images thank you put it on the fridge maybe killer
crockmeyer gave five thousand bits and I didn't see they say long time no bits thanks for the
50 fucking bucks leave the title screen on for an extended song it's amazing and should share
with everyone also wwe 2k20 is now available and dear god does it suck talking about parapa
yeah I heard it's not good yep it's sad sad that after 2k14 2k was like you know let's turn this
into a madden you guys madden's fun isn't it sure who's on the teams this year I don't know
update him he was on the patriots he added a couple new people cool that just made me really
sad um I am really sad about that now well anyways killer crockmeyer thanks for the 5000 bits
it's a huge amount of money even especially after fucking four days ago thanks a lot dragon bret
thanks for the 250 I had a dream of you last night you're at my house just hanging out outside
so I went outside to talk with you you wanted to do your chase me joke from duck game and ran off
so I was chasing you and Joel called me and was wondering where the fuck you went
you heard me explaining to Joel what you were what you were doing and you've realized how stupid the
situation was and started laughing hysterically you sat on the ground and laughed but I thought
you were crying so I awkwardly walked away I am insane in everybody's dreams why can't anybody
have a dream that I'm in or I'm just at a restaurant just sitting there eating and enjoying
dinner and like something else fucking crazy happens and I go whoa that was insane dude do
you see that why am I was the weirdo I always have to be the monster in your dreams hey vin
vertigo thanks for the 500 bits germa you're the best I've been watching your videos for a long time
now but only recently started using twitch this year welcome to twitch it's a fun place interesting
place uh thank you nut for the 500 bits hey germa I'm driving right now what do you mean driving
right now like you're in a car and somebody's driving or you're driving the car right now and
saying that let me be the let me be like hopefully I mean this was a while ago but get off your
fucking phone don't do that shit is you gonna give him the dad talk no I'm gonna give him the
the the fucking real talk put your phones down put them down your attention should be on the road
not on snapchat your attention should be on the road not on the funny thing that was in the group
chat today you want to call this a dad talk I call this a fucking human talk I really hope that's a
joke because that's don't don't fucking don't fuck around seriously don't fuck around germa if you
want to lecture me you're gonna have to adopt me no I'm just I'm saying like come on you gotta be
careful and you can't just remember this is I think a lot of people just forget this shit
for some reason when you are driving you are in a like three two or three thousand pound
death machine you are just and you are going 30 40 50 60 miles per hour in a three thousand pound
weight cars are actually terrifying you gotta be fucking careful please do this for all people
donating saying this is their savings or they don't have enough money what do you mean what
he hates cars talking about donors that say that donators that say that they don't have any money
and they donate oh I think I see what you mean um I think I've made it pretty clear before
but I'll do it again just in case anyone has not heard it yet that you need to take care of
yourself first and I am not a priority for you take care of yourself first make sure you're
doing all right your life is going fine financially if you want to give me money I will absolutely
take it you know like I'm not gonna be like no don't but please please please make sure you're
taking care of yourself first I am not a priority for you I'm a broke ass student and check it out
no sub and you don't ever have to sub you never have to do that if you let me tell you the orange
bread if you never sub to this channel ever and you never give even a cent to this channel sorry
that's fine that's oh are you having do you are you having fun do you like watching the streams
do you have fun here good fuck it you don't have to you don't have to give this channel money
I think people understand that I hope they really do I'm not having fun you said you hate cars and
that's my favorite movie I like that one does it make us a monster if we never sub
why would that ever have why would I ever think that that why would I ever be like well you know
I mean you should sub no if you if you can't afford it if you can't afford to pay this stream
money then then don't just don't you still contribute to this stream even though if you
don't think so like think about it let's say I mean the streams have been the last
three or four months or so I mean there's been a lot of people here and even if you're not paying
money to the stream you're still contributing to the success of this stream does that make sense
so don't ever think somebody gifted you a sub
all right somebody gifted him a sub cool thank you I guess cool but anyways long story short
get off your fucking phone when you're driving a car don't do that and if you don't have the money
to pay this stream save it take care of yourself first take care of me somewhere somewhere like
down the bottom like you know if you have if you have still cash lying around you're like you know
fine fuck it take care of yourself first always back to the moral of the story but we also we had
a ton of community subs this stream too a ton of them I it happened again for like about 10
straight minutes 15 straight minutes and I remember because I missed numb legs given a hundred dollars
and they asked is this going to get my attention and it didn't Jesus thank you gnarly for the 250
thank you for the thank you I probably won't be able to gift sub anymore but just know that
you are worth every penny also the URL of the clip of you thanking me ends in pogchamp which
is a sign from the heavens I think it actually is it actually is pogchamp
nice work I look so fucking deranged on camera turn my more face cam and then I watch a clip
and I look at my eyes and I go that guy that person's deranged but thank you gnarly and yeah
pogchamp boneless bacon thanks for the thousand bits thank you boneless bacon determine this isn't
me giving you bits this is me this is you owing me bits you owe me ten dollars also you still smell
go shower I well I can't give it back to you so it's mine forever I want to give a very special
thank you to bob boy they had a bunch of community subs today thank you bob boy greedy moss lion
thanks for the 250 just want to let you know that your hair is very lush and full for your age and
like really anything that chat says about your hair is invalid I know we know you and I know you
and I get it and then Vilemi oh my goodness I uh Vilemi gave this is from earlier I remember this
is five five hundred and fifty dollars fifty five thousand bits that happened about two or three
hours ago we touched we already went over it but man that is that's you okay when you start to
cross that threshold of like in one bit donation it's more than a fucking video game console
it's just like holy shit man thank you so much Vilemi I really really really appreciate it
germa is actually a hot successful person who would be a steamboat to be around just imagine
this strong guy walking around the vegas strip and his aviators and tight button up being like
I got money for that I'm self-employed what why am I really I don't know I don't know it was a
paragraph it was a paragraph and just put a fish on it it doesn't matter put a paragraph or a fish
and I'll read it I don't know I don't know why I read that it just happens I don't know why
because they called me strong and like cool and funny and I read it but Vilemi thank you for the
fifty five fucking hundred fifty five thousand bits my god he's an egomaniac
germa is so weird and annoying I'm sorry clueless sniper thanks for the 500 bits wait is this stream
of playing the thing this is my entire life saving germa please take it this is like playing on what
was thank you numb legs thanks for the 50 dollars germa please read the big bits doing it now doing
it now shoot him with an arrow what the fuck are you talking about thank you numb legs for your
hundreds of dollars 150 at least today thanks a lot huge bits and then Vilemi gave 300 bits
after the ridiculous 550 drop really though thank you jeremy even without the awu being able to come
home after a long day and watch my favorite streamer makes everything more bearable
thank you Vilemi take care of yourself take care of yourself because you're you're taking care of
me big time so take care of yourself I really appreciate it I'm glad you're gonna have fun
it was awu not no no no aw000 not the other one thanks a lot Vilemi pretty radical potato
thanks for the 500 bits itchy face itchy face equals he's infected CFD thanks for the thousand
bits you can do it germa you just got to believe oh this is when I was going nuts
yeah I was going like fucking crazy here oh yeah I forgot about that I was being a weirdo
thank you little dinosaur little dinosaur little dino little dinosaur my god it's a zero in the
middle that's why my brain little dinosaur thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks hey germa tomorrow
or today it's the 26th not quite here in uh Vegas but we'll be soon uh tomorrow's my birthday
if you could give a shout out to my boyfriend who got me into watching you that would be great his
name is hunter and we love and appreciate you thanks for being so amazing hey hey first of all
happy birthday happy birthday to you and now I got something to say to I got something to say to a
guy named hunter hunter you introduced Jillian or whoever it is Lilden Lilden I saw Lilden
and I'm saying okay Lilden let me tell okay hunter not Illidan Jill Jill Jilleden no not
okay it's lil dinosaur not Lilden not Jillian not Jillian hunter you and I got to talk first of
all shout out to you for introducing Lilden to my stream and my videos you two are fucking awesome
I've heard you two are the you two are the best I'm doing a cameo right now cameo.com
hey guys it's me germa985 just want to let you know I heard this is not fun no it's not a fiver
anyways hunter you and me sit down for a minute let's talk no happy birthday seriously uh little
dinosaur and hunter that's two viewers you brought a viewer you're a viewer you guys watch thank you
for being so amazing thank you for watching father can we talk about cameos for a minute here do
people do cameos and they make the like celebrity talk about their products like I swear to god I
think I've seen like sub shops like local like Philadelphia sub shops that have like Mr Wonderful
talk about their sub shop what do they just put it up on a fucking screen up above the door
hey everybody Mr Wonderful here just want to tell you about the best sub I've ever had best
absolutely delicious from the berry subs in Philadelphia I came in and they took care of me
I'm telling you no I'm telling you they people get people to say stuff about their local businesses
they do testimonials with I I wouldn't do that if I got a cameo and it was like well hold on
a minute here also some of those cameos are like a thousand dollars but I would never do a cameo
because I don't know I don't want to just be like the fiver guy hey guys German985 here and let me
tell you I am so excited for Steve's Laundromat they have the best freshest ingredients they have
the most wonderful staff and if you like dogs they've got a dog too there I couldn't do it
okay okay if it was like anniversaries and stuff right like I would have a strict policy where like
anniversaries birthdays shout outs but if like the name of your product I'm not going to sell
your like multi-level marketing fucking makeup or something hey everybody German985 here four uh four
uh what's that what's the popular one what's the popular one what's the popular one what's
popular one what's the popular one I actually know I'm not gonna say it I'm not gonna say it
because that what a fucking reverse IQ play that is no I'm not gonna sell your like multi-level
marketing campaign I'm not gonna fucking shout out your like sandwich shop but anyways hunter
talking to you no seriously thanks both of you I really appreciate it I'm glad that you guys can
enjoy the streams and content thank you hey errorless gave 250 250 250 and they say sorry
I just love that video clip of Otto I'm not clicking this link I I don't know what this link
is I'm glad you think Otto is cute thank you so much for the seven dollars and 50 cents but this
is a link I've never seen before I don't know what this website is P pack Vim what is that
it's like a porno thing I don't know what this is it's malware virus what am I having to just
happen something like YouTube pee pant pee pack no just click it I'm not clicking it I can't click
no and I don't want to I don't want to give it to you guys either because I don't want you to click
it it's a clip of Otto all right let me click it all right clip of Otto that is really cute
let's see oh that is funny that's cute
he's barking at the mailman what the fuck
I remember that that's true man the mailman puts the mail in
yep that was so fucking cute I love my dog show us I I oh I oh I can't I where is it
would that link I can't find that link thank you thank you Mr. ADHD for the five ten fifteen
hundred bits wipe your forehead don't wipe your forehead I'm kidding you look fine anyway how's
your day it's been pretty good I'm pretty good phylactery thank you for the hundred dollars
ten thousand bits where was the the blood thing and they said germa don't die don't worry I'm
gonna be fine don't worry thank you for the thousand fucking dollars and that's not me making
that up that's actually eleven hundred dollars over the last week so yeah porn and chat get that
fucking porn out of here I I let me tell you something there was one time where somebody
linked porn like twice you guys have been really good and I do not want to delete this privilege
from you guys don't don't do it do not do it and that was the same person did it like three times
are they here are you here do you like are you here I remember they were like oh sorry I linked
my like porn right does anyone remember this it happened like three times from the same person
and we we gave the benefit of the doubt like twice I what I remember this
is god what the fuck hey piss chugging thanks piss thank you thank you for the 500 bits nice
to meet you streamer I've been enjoying this game lots thanks thanks for the 500 bits thank you bob
boy for the fucking five community subs everybody loves bob boy hey labster thanks for the 500 bits
it's an emote version of the fucking like discombobulator face thank you so much I
appreciate it and it's available now oh we'll see maybe it'll be there and now it's time for
the credits see I told you it wasn't gonna take that long took like 45 minutes everybody's like
it's gonna take like three hours it's been like 42 minutes 50 minutes maybe well oh god that's
off-center this is going so fast too this dude loves credits an hour and a half no it was it was
like 52 minutes 50 minutes maybe tops look at all these subs lots and lots of subs but thank you
labster that will probably become an emote but does should it though I feel like it just if it
becomes an emote then it might lose its magic as being like the funniest picture I've ever seen
that's a tough one flug boy thanks for the 250 having kind of a weird night I hope you're doing
well Jeremy was happy to have you as a pick me up when I got home thanks plug boy glad to be here
hope your night gets better thank you snoozing copter for the 250 these subs for today yep
this is just today I actually had a dream once where I met you that was before I went to pax
and actually met you and we played mario kart together all right cool fairly fucking normal
now when do I eat the controller and like shit on your bed let's find out after that you modded me
and twitch and I thought holy shit that's awesome and then I woke up and was actually a little
bummed out because of the first few seconds I thought it was real next time we will meet
I'll bring mario kart for real also can we please listen to this parappa remix
that's pog moment right there I didn't shit on your bed all right what's this remix thank you
snoozing copter literal dreams are the worst don't bring up all the fucking videos this is the
romantic love remix I will have this play itself it's pretty good hey koh lucia thanks for the
250 hey germa that one bit message just reminded me of my own germa dream I had a few weeks ago
okay hold on where here comes the I like blow a snot rocket into your eye and then like burn
down your house here we go I had a dream of you of my own basically you came on stream one day
and announced you were making a movie that would premiere live on stream and everyone was so
excited okay I don't even know what the movie was about but you were like a train pirate and
you only spoke in old English and nobody in the movie liked you anyway it was so bad you lost
almost all your viewers in the span of an hour dude do you really fucking weird shitty dumb content
seems to increase viewers on twitch not decrease them I sat here with a vacuum cleaner going for
five straight minutes with no other sounds and I full screen cammed my face sitting there with no
emotion and the stream went up by like four or five hundred viewers maybe it was boring people
don't people like bad but they don't like boring you know what's here you know what being boring
might be worse than being bad in an entertainment sense damn that is true wow holy shit that's a
next level think about that huh who said that who said that modem and then on modem
did it but thank you co lucia for the 250 keith king crimson thanks for the 250 hey germa I visited
steve's laundromat at your suggestion the ingredients weren't fresh at all and the
owners were huge dickheads about it also the dog tried to bite me what the fuck yeah that's why
I don't do shout outs for businesses or for like that's why I don't do that finally at the very end
we had go dot thanks godot for the 250 hey germa just had a weird dream with you in it okay
here it comes I know it's gonna happen when do I like light a fart and like the flames from the
fart like break you tv here we go hey germa just had the weird dream about you I was looking for
on the strip when I saw you okay I went up to say hi but you suddenly looked at me with hate in your
eyes and snapped your fingers immediately your six bodyguards grabbed me and threw me off the strip
and into the mojave desert at 12 p.m pacific time anyways when are you going to pay back those
people for starting the money train you planned threw me off the strip into the at 12 p.m pacific
time I don't understand you skipped my bits I didn't skip bits it's 250 bits to be read at
the end of a stream we've talked about this we've already gone over this many times I've got many
many times I've talked about it people just don't listen they don't want to listen to me
trump trump go away
wait people listen
go to bed not yet I'm gonna do a good trump and she was talking and we were seeing all the
no what what did he say and then she was just talking and he does that sometimes let me try
again one more okay it's me doing the donald trump steven cold bears trump oh I can't believe it
let me try one more time thank you g bear wolf one more for the 250 one more last one bob boy
hold on everybody everybody everybody shush bob boy just gave 10 fucking dollars hiya there's
a song you might know called alice's restaurant I'm I don't know what this bob boy fuck yeah
oh wait I'm supposed to play this what is this fuck yeah boy shout out to bob boy what was I
doing oh yeah oh no there's a this is called alice's restaurant I've never heard this
he zoned out yeah I did alice's restaurant is 20 minutes long this is an 18 minute song
okay cool my vod is gonna get muted instantly did I just get fucking ruined okay I was gonna
do okay one more try no 500 bits people are preventing me from doing my doing my my donald
yubire thanks for the 500 bits hey jerma I had an odd dream with you basically if you're reading
this jerma you've been in a coma for almost 24 days now we're trying a new technique we don't
know where this message will end up in your dream but we hope it works please wake up we miss you
that's classic is shanji thanks for the 275 bits I had a dream where you played the thing and you
convinced me to give you my life savings weird huh that is pretty strange okay here it comes
see you guys tomorrow for basheeda blade and basheeda blade 2 vilemi gives $10 he can't leave
if we keep giving bits I'm trying to do a uh impression squimp thank you squimp pst for the
400 bits what do you have to say about the allegations well no I don't want to do hold on
thank you for the 400 bits yeah I gotta I gotta like slice that one now I can't okay now I can't
even okay fine you win I'll do another no all right good night see you tomorrow
basheeda blade basheeda blade 2 take care guys have a wonderful night much love to everybody see you soon