Hi guys. Uh, today, there's not supposed to be a stream here, there's just not. Uh, I
have a little bit of an apology for you today. Ass hair. I haven't- okay, I get- listen,
the microphone's down here right now. Listen to me. I haven't washed my hair in two days.
I've conditioned it twice. I haven't done that because after VR, my hair gets wicked
fucked up and I'm afraid to wash it because I'm afraid it'll fall out. So I haven't washed
my hair in two days. I'm gonna do it today. Alright, so you're probably asking, why am
I doing this? When I very, very clearly said that I was streaming on Thursday, well I fucked
up the sus. The sus said there was a stream today for the last two days. And I didn't
even know there was a stream that was scheduled for today until, uh, like half an hour ago?
Forty minutes ago? So, come on. What's this? Get up there like that. There you go. Now
you look better. I didn't know there was gonna be a stream today, but now apparently there
is. I told you guys, anybody that was in the bank pre-stream chat that we were gonna
do an auto stream, sleeping right there. Uh, this is literally gonna be like thirty minutes.
I'm just doing this because I got guilt tripped by pre-stream because I- you know, I- this
is a guilt trip stream. You got me. Chat, I'm not gonna turn the stream on. I'm not gonna
do it. I'm only gonna stream for like thirty minutes. Alright, maybe I'll do- yeah, that's
fine. I'll do one stream for thirty minutes. Okay, well, uh, two hours. No, chat, I'm not
gonna do two hours. Okay, I'll do three hours. Chat, I'm not gonna do four hours. How about
like a twenty-four hour stream? Is it okay? No, no, I won't do that. Didn't I actually
say two days ago that I wasn't going to cave to things people said? I said this two days
ago. I said I am- when I say goes, and then literally I'm turning on a stream on a day
that I'm not supposed to be streaming. I don't know. Whatever. Alright, anyways, let's break
this down. I have never done a stream where auto just hung out right here. And the camera's
never been pointed down here. You've never got a full body shot of auto for a long time.
Let's see what happens. Ready? Watch this. Auto. Auto. Over there. Who's sleeping over
there? Auto. Come over here. Come- come- right- go there, exactly. Oh, here comes a full
body reveal of the dog. Oh, no, never mind. This is the only fucking time you're ever
gonna get this, by the way. I'm never doing this ever again. I'm only doing this because
people bullied me. Let's just get off and leave. Go the dog? I have his favorite toys
out there. He doesn't even know they're out there. Bullying works. No, it doesn't. I did
this because I felt like it. Hey, come over here. You know, I set this up so you'd be
seen. You're not even being seen right now. Come over here. Hey, lazy dog, go over there.
Right here. Go. Come here. Come on. I know what it'll make you get up. Watch, he's gonna-
Toy. He'll move for his favorite toy. Just you wait. Flamingo. See? Oh, dude, auto reveal.
Is this what you want? Yeah? I have Mr. Flamingo. There he is. Finally, I reveal my dog after
12 years. He loves this thing. He's ripped the stuffing out of this thing like 10 times.
He's a little chunky. He actually has lost some weight, believe it or not. He's lost
like five pounds. He was like 27 pounds. He was huge. Now he's 24 pounds, which is still,
he needs to lose a little bit more weight, but it's okay. Auto is perfect. No, he's not.
Remember, he's a Dachshund mix. He's not a Dachshund. He's a Dachshund rat terrier, Shetland
Sheepdog Chihuahua. It's been confirmed. That's been completely confirmed. I didn't get to like
get the fuck out of the way. What if he's just like shit on the carpet right now? Don't, hey,
don't do anything. Get daddy in trouble. He just like spins around and just like dumps right here.
Oh, people are giving me money. Get out. Get out. All right. What the fuck? Leave? He's not dead.
He does. Hey, want this? You want this? You want this? You want this? Get this. Get this. Get this.
Get it. Oh, he got it. He got it. Let me see. Let me see. Let me see. Let me see. Let me see.
Let me see. Let me see. Let me see. Take it. Get it. Does he know any tricks? Um, some. All right.
Yeah, let's, let's, we'll have Otto do some tricks. By the way, he's one of those dogs that he knows
like three tricks and he does them all instantly if you have a treat in your hand. You already
watched this. He knows, he knows paw, he knows sit, he knows lay down, he knows roll over. So,
if you have a treat in your hand, he goes like this. It flips over on his back as fast as he can.
Hey, let's show, let's show the people what you can do, Otto. All right, I'm going to leave him
here. Is this going to be like a toy story scenario where like I leave the room, he doesn't
know that this is recording and he gets up and starts walking on fucking two legs.
I just fell up the stairs twice. I went out and fell and then hit my shoulder on the wall
and fell again. He loves these fucking things. Hey, hey, hey, hey, chat. He doesn't know.
Okay. Itchy? Okay, you ready? Hey, what is this? Ready to do some tricks? Okay, lay down.
Paw? Paw? No, I didn't say roll over yet. Come back up. Come on. Okay, wait. Lay down. Lay down.
Roll over. Paw. Oh, he's so fucking smart. Only my boy. Sometimes he throws this too. Let me leave
the room. Sometimes he just picks it up and whips it. He'll pick it up and he'll just whip it into
the wall. What? Wait, what? What? What's going on? There's 13, there's 14,000 people here right now.
What are you talking? No, there's not. It was a raid? Oh, no. A raid? Who raided? It's supposed
to be like a... Oh, shit. Hold on a minute. Oh, no. I gotta get the dog. I'm blocking the view of the
dog. Hey, you that just joined the stream, welcome. Today's a subscriber... What day is it? Tuesday.
Today's... Welcome to Subscriber Wednesday, where I do a quick little for the subs. I do a quick
little 40 minute stream with my dog. Welcome to Sub Wednesday. What was it? Was it Kitboga?
Thanks a lot. Thanks, Kit. Hope you had a good stream today. This is a dog stream. It's a bonus
stream. That's so many people. Thank you. Thank you. Welcome. I'm Jerma. This is my dog, Otto.
You don't know who that is. We're just playing around for a few minutes. This is a guilt trip
stream. This is better than the robot carnival. It is not at all. Close. I eat bugs thanks to the
10 community subs. All right, now let's play a fun game called Chase Me. He's gonna get me. He's gonna
get me. I'm not the dog. This is not like dog. I'm not the dog. If you just got in here like a
minute ago. Let's start putting this in my mouth and start rolling around. I think he's done. I
think he's over it. Hey, I think he's over it. Where'd he go? Hey, Otto. Hey, what are you doing?
He's done. He doesn't even like want to come in here. Oh, you thought you could be really sneaky
and sneak in here and try to get this toy. All right. Is this weird if I put this in my mouth?
Is that weird? Why are you so itchy? What's going on here? What are you itchy? You got an itch?
What's with the itch? You didn't catch it. I haven't pet him yet. Oh, right. Sometimes we do this
and he'll just sit here all day and just stare at my face. Hey, time to be asleep.
What is it? What is it? Full sleeping dog stream. Oh, I get it. Right now he smells
the treat that was in my hand earlier. And now he's like, where's the other one? You have another
one, don't you? Look. All right. See, I'm doing it. I'm doing the thing. Look, I'm doing the thing.
Look, Otto. Hey, are you a good dog? What is it? What are you going to show? Hey, show everybody.
Your penguin stripe. Show everybody the penguin stripe. I'm pogging. So I can't believe there's
10 fucking thousand people here. I'm about to leave. Wait, hold on. Oh, he's talking shit,
Otto. What are you going to do? He loves this thing too. This thing has been beat up so many
times. It's unbelievable. Look at it. Otto, kill. Oh, he kind of just, he's just kind of curious.
He's like, what are we doing? Go over the schedule for this week. If I could get in the way for a
second here. Sorry about that. Go over the schedule. What are you doing? What are you looking at?
All right. So let's get, look, I'll tell you the schedule from down here.
So the schedule, so the schedule this week is, oh, I'm going to fall down. I'm going to have to go
pee. Uh, he's been outside like an hour ago. Uh, anyways, we'll play Watch Dogs Legion tomorrow
at launch. And then after that, we're going to play Little Hope with Italics on Friday.
And then after that, we're going to go back and VR on Halloween night. It should be fun. Big bits.
I don't even, I can't even see them. I don't see anything. What were they? I don't see them.
Big bits, huge bits. Where are they? Move. I, I'm moving. Hold on. I want to track down these bits.
I don't see anything. Is this a debate? I see. Oh, look at all these followers. The new, oh,
there we go. I see. All right. Captain Nemo give 50 bucks. Thank you, Captain Nemo for the
$50. Probably said something. So hold on. It doesn't say the actual message, but what is it?
What are you doing? Having a good time? Are you having a good time? Face the floppy ears.
Dog flip. All right. I'm, I'm out of the way. More people are here at the auto stream than were at
like my last VR stream. That's so funny. A show werelord. Okay. He actually loves werelord. He
lies on top of it. If I bring it up here, you might line it. You want to know how I can prove
that this is a dog bed? Look at werelord. Look at this perfect dog sized crevice right here.
He's been permanently squished. You look at yardie. He's like, excuse me. That's my bed. Yeah.
What about it? What about it? What about it? Just sit on it. I feel like I'm trying to get an AI
in a video game to do something. Why are you so itchy today? What's going on? You're never this
itchy. Is he anxious? Are you anxious for being on TV? Oh, big eye crusty. That was a big one.
Did you see that? Eight actor. I feel like I'm like setting up like a, I was going to say a hitman
level, but I don't, that's not what we're doing. Well like, oh, I'm trying to get the AI to like
walk through a certain door. All right. Okay. I'm going to leave the room. Right. That was a burp.
It was like burped at me and then you had to burp and that's why.
Oh, this has been a 20, what'd I say? 45 minutes. How long has it been? 20.
Teach your dog, teach your dog vape tricks. We're halfway there. What else do you do?
It's been 25 minutes. You promised 45 minutes. Uh, all right. Yeah. So hold him. He doesn't want
to be held right now. Right? Such a good dog. Every time this dog goes to the vet, the vet
always talks about how everybody loves him. He's the sweetest dog ever to ever come into our
practice. And I know they say that to every single customer, even if your dog like pissed on the
ground and like jumped on top of the counter and like fucking knocked a bunch of shit off the,
I know, I know. And he said this to everybody. He really is. He really is like the sweetest boy
ever. Tell us a story about him. Hold on. Let me move. Hold on. I, look, it's, it's my stream
right now. Okay. He's an actor. He's a guest on my stream today. About me. It's about me, baby.
Cause it's not, I can't see him. Even he's like, what the fuck are you doing? Tell us a story,
a story about Otto. Okay. Oh, you're irrelevant. It's crazy. This is actually the first time ever
that I've done this. I guess I've always seen Otto, like me holding him like this. And I go,
Oh, look, look at the camera. It's never just been like a, an auto cam for more than five seconds.
Sometimes in bed, he'll just roll over like this and stay that way until, until you touch his
stomach. He'll do it for an hour. He'll just be like, um, excuse me. You haven't fucking done it
yet in like 30 minutes. And then finally you'll do it. And then he's like, Oh, okay. Thank you.
And then he'll put his arm down, scratch the dog's belly, pet the dog.
What he's dedicated. Yeah. Nothing makes us happier than seeing this kiss. Otto,
Otto, can I kiss? Like, uh, you haven't, excuse me. Okay. See. Okay. Getting rejected.
Am I getting rejected? I, I'm going to take you back. Hey, uh, guys, don't you think
this looks like a really comfy bed? Oh, I would really love to lie on this bed because it's mine.
I'm going to go ahead and put this right here. Ooh. Oh, that's, that's comfy. Oh, this is a
comfortable bed. Don't you think Otto? Usually he gets up and he'll be like, excuse me. What the
fuck? I feel like I'm about to tell you guys a bunch of stuff about how my day went today.
Yeah. Hi guys. Yeah. Today was rough. I'm on the phone with you right now. Yeah. Fucking
bullshit. What are you doing tomorrow? Yeah. Don't even tell me about it. Don't even. Okay. I was
about to turn and like put my feet up like this, but nope. Muted? I was muted? How? Bless you. I
sneezed? Oh, the limiter. I was saying like, yeah, today was a bad day today. I was just talking on
the phone. Muted. Yeah, it's because I'm too far away from the limiter. That's all right.
Irma, is your what? Watch the No More Heroes 3 trailer. I did that like, like a year ago. I saw
it live and I reacted hard. I was a fucking react Andy. I was. There's a new one. What? New what?
A new what? There's a new trailer. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
move. I'm not moving until you give me a link about the new trailer so I can react Andy.
There it is. That's it. No More Heroes 3, a triple threat of No More Heroes. Why does this only have
20,000 views? Wait, does this come out like this? Is this like right now? Dude, did I catch this
right now? All right, hold on. Let me see. I need to get this on the browser. I need my headphones.
Okay, let's see. Oh, move. Hold on. How come this is not coming through? All right, there it is. Mine
too, actually. All right, hold on. Here we go. Let's check it out. This is the, uh, no, I almost said
Fallout 3 trailer. No More Heroes 3. Let's go. My stomach hurts. I need a toilet. Perfect location.
Okay. Good.
Nice.
This looks pretty good.
No More Heroes 3. What was once a fight between assassins is now a battle to the death on the
galactic scale. Take on galaxy. Just destroy all those nasty aliens. Now, fight. Dude, I'm going to
play this at fucking launch. I'm going to play the fuck out of this at launch. Wait, that means it's
a release date. Probably bring it on. I'll give you a little kiss. Release date. No More Heroes.
You've got news. Does it have to be like now? The first No More Heroes is getting ported to
Nintendo Switch. Pretty cool. Heroes 2 desperate struggle is coming to the Switch too.
I kind of wish I could play it on there. Holy shit. Nice. Nevada. Make a plan to vote early
by the October 30th deadline. If you don't vote early, you can still vote on election day.
You can vote if you can. Go vote. I don't know what this is. I can't turn it off. There it is.
Oh, vote. It's your duty and it's your right. But not in Nevada unless you live there.
Otto's gone. He's right here. He's right here. I'm blocking him perfectly. Okay. Are you ready?
Wait. I'm going to snap my fingers and Otto is going to be disappeared from the room. One, two.
Wait. One, two. He's gone. I don't know. He just he just he fucked off. He doesn't want to do this
anymore. He just went over to his blanket. He's lying in the okay. See this beam of light.
He is making sure his face is in that beam of light. He loves to lie down in like a little
strip of light. Perfect. That's a lie. Show him. He's like over he's like I don't know. It's been
like 32 minutes of where I'm just annoying him. He got bored. Move the cam. All right. Ready? Watch
this. See if he comes over. All dogs always go over to you if you lie down on your back.
I don't he doesn't want anything to do with me. I know. I know. I can't seem to move.
I know. Please. I told you have to rescue me. Oh, I can't get up. Oh, no. Oh, no. I can't seem.
I'm trying to do it. Oh, no. Oh, no. Please. Oh, no. Oh,
ah. Those of you that are wondering he wanted to eat the puke that may have come out of my mouth.
He wanted to uh he he's like oh you've hurt you're on your back. Oh, I don't fucking care. But oh
you're about to throw up and I can eat your puke. I'm here. I'm ready. What do you what's with the
itchiness? Right here? We have to bring you to the vet and say did you itch again? He gets like this
allergies or something. It was just at the vet like two or three weeks ago. What happened? Why are you
such an itchy belly? Oh, you know what? It's it's getting colder here. It's dry as hell.
Somebody just said you're fucked up, dude. What? Why? You're fucked up, dude. Is a good link here?
Okay, this is pretty good. This is stupid. Okay, it's not this but just let's look at this for a
second anyways because this is like scary. Not even my real face but okay. All right, where is it?
Not that one either. What did I do with this image? I hate when I desktop. What's going on here?
On the desktop. So what the fuck? Even like painted his even got his like hand in like oh we are T
we are T minus nine minutes before the stream. I'm turning it off at exactly 45 minutes by the way.
Just to get auto by the way his left. Now you just got me and only me and I'll see you tomorrow.
Well, I look at the title. The title of the stream says 45 minutes. It doesn't say 30 minutes.
It doesn't say 45 minutes. No, it says 45 minutes. It doesn't say like two hours.
You're always late but you can end it right on time. I wasn't late today. Today was never
supposed to happen. I was supposed I look I was just sitting here and I looked over at my discord
and I got a dm uh from from the hive mind dev. We were just talking just quickly about like just
updating each other about some things and he's just like oh hey man I can't wait for the stream
today. VR is so cool and I was like today and then I went and I like scrambled over here and
it was like 2 10 at that point and I go into the chat room and it's just wham it's like a thousand
messages a second and I'm just like I was like well today there's no stream today and when I
and obviously when it doesn't matter if the sus was wrong it don't matter you were here for like
an hour waiting for me to stream and that's what the sus said and I wasn't here so obviously
I look like the bad guy I'm the bad guy in that point right I am the bad guy I admit it
then this is your this is the sub Wednesday 45 minutes this is the this is patreon tier fucking
five okay all of you here had to give me two hundred dollars a month to let to do this stream
that's what this is I have one auto fans not for real I will see you guys tomorrow blank blank
blank you know like you know I'll be okay but hold on let's like hold on blank I'll see you
guys tomorrow honestly stream like this every now and then it's cool yeah what are you doing
tomorrow watch dogs legion gonna play more streamer life probably after Halloween I would say once
Halloween comes and goes we'll do that one Nintendo labo did they come up with another one is there
a Nintendo labo stream possible because the VR one was the last one right I already did it watch
dogs yeah I don't know look I don't have I don't have early access to watch dogs
I'm probably only gonna play for like four or five hours I don't know I might love it
I'll tell you I didn't love the first two so playing the third one third time third time's
a charm right I played the first one it was all right and then me and italics played the second
one and I remember just like getting stuck in the ocean and like falling forever in the ocean the
game was like fucked up and I never played it again so yeah we'll see you tomorrow we'll try
it again third time's a charm something on there lick whale lord oh dude that wouldn't that be so
gross oh get out of here with that fucking bullshit five more minutes count it down here it comes
oh maybe I should do like a quick dance for you no I'm not this is not comedy man stream
see I am more than five feet tall see and I can prove it see how fucking big this is
that's you that's you down there oh oh hey oh hi there hi there junior oh you sure are getting
big and strong lately wow are you doing good in school I hope so you need any help with your book
bag son how are you by the way just cut the stream not to not to 45 this is a fetish stream
oh no your cock was out I'm telling you I've had nightmares before what I'm like talking like this
and next week what we're gonna do guys is we're gonna make a dick like you know like I've had a
dream but that's happened and I freak out I even though I know I have pants on I have I have pants
and underwear on when I stand up I'm just like no I gotta be careful there I don't what's that
I have like fully clothed person it doesn't matter it anytime because I had two nightmares
in a row about this it'll happen one day and that will be my final stream and then I will never see
you again holy shit that link oh that link is getting removed now I know why now I know why
it's there oh okay somebody added to the wait wait wait I gotta be ready to turn the stream
off in exactly three minutes somebody added to the uh to the auto has the weapon oh auto quick
auto auto auto auto quick come on before before it turns the timer turns off he doesn't care
he's done because it's so quick on these images I swear to god okay that's horrifying
the streamer is kind of short I am a little short but I'm not that short I am five seven
with five eight with shoes on I have my official driver's license is five seven and a quarter
I'm five eight and a half with shoes on five like eight I just say five eight who cares do you care
that much you're an inch taller than me see I'm huge five seven is tall five seven is normal tall
what about this link oh yeah it's like it's like junior year of high school
let's see how I already I've shown this before look at look at look at how much I've aged
you ready for this hey take a look at this shit you want to see somebody that just has like wine
in their blood that's not me although it could be look at that look at this excuse me that was
like 25 fucking years ago it looks like five years yeah that was like 20 plus years ago
I'm probably like 16 in this picture I haven't aged a minute thank you I missed it by the way
it's 46 minutes now thanks a lot thanks a lot we're in overtime aged like milk uh if that
milk happens to be cheese aged like cheese I'll take it aged like cheese oh by the way I saw
somebody call this my orangutan stomach I mentioned that the other day and it was very hurtful but
funny it was funny still what the heck who said that who said hey who said that right where's
Otto he's got his claw I'm sorry I'm just kidding I don't care all right this is it I'm gonna do it
at 47 because 47 is one of my favorite characters from high hitman 3 can't wait for vr here it comes
here it comes what no it's okay wait I need a little I need a longer outro than that
a little bit longer outro oh your dog's feet seen it like a thousand times he was here for
like 30 minutes nice talking to you yeah I hope you guys enjoyed the Wednesday sub stream remember
every time oh I hate I saw that I saw that remember every time you sub we get we do a
Wednesday sub stream where I hang out and play with my dog every Wednesday you're gonna see me
Jerma and I play with my dog on camera but you have to sub don't ever fucking say I'm not
fucking talented I can fucking do anything I want pre-recorded all right it's 49 we're gonna end
at 49 because I love the 49ers no 50 because that's how old people think I am
decent ah something must be wrong with the fucking internet cord fuck the 49ers I don't know I don't
know I've watched a single game of 49ers in my life this guy's literally insane what if I just
this guy's 50 oh he will be in about one minute just waiting how the hell what oh before we end
yeah I'll see you tomorrow for Watch Dogs Legion remember I'm playing Watch Dogs Legion tomorrow
and so is everyone else on the whole website pretty much but watch my stream because I'm
gonna start probably three or four hours after other people have started so I'm missing the boat
by about four or five hours probably but watch my stream tomorrow Watch Dogs we're gonna do something
funny we're gonna do funny stuff on the Watch Dogs Legion there's gonna be a grandma on it
I promise it could be a grandma we'll wait for you and I'm gonna play on easy too so remember
that's already putting me kind of down on the streamer list I'm playing on like normal and
I'm probably gonna miss a bunch of cues look at those nails they're perfect I won't watch
other streamers play that game that everyone's gonna play tomorrow only watch mine and oh well
we're gonna do five five five five no that means 55 minutes no we're gonna do five 50 uh attention
span whatever it doesn't matter 50 hey we're doing a 50 50 he could turn the stream off but he might
not at that exact time it's a 50 50 shot here let's go you ready I'll see you tomorrow for
Watch Dogs Legion watch my stream don't watch any other people's watch my Watch Dogs stream
if I if I if I hear that you watch somebody else's Watch Dogs stream while I was live doing
Watch Dogs say goodbye to say goodbye to sub Wednesday with Otto here we go all right bye