What's up? How's it going?
What's happening?
No fucking way.
What do you mean? Like no way that I'm here?
No way. No way.
What? What's going on here?
Are you that shocked that I'm streaming?
I can't believe this dude's actually streaming.
What the fuck?
Who the heck has he been?
All right, let me tweet this in one sec.
There we go.
My Twitter analytics must be absolute dogshit.
All of my tweets are either sponsored tweets or they're go live tweets.
And then sometimes, like once a year,
I'll have a tweet that has like five million views
and everything else is just way, way, way under that.
My analytics must be awful.
Must be like the shittiest analytics of any Twitter account.
Whatever. Who cares?
Did you tweet something funny?
That's, I guess, up to you.
Oh, I did have a fake Mario movie tweet that is...
I could read a draft or two. Why not?
Let's see what this one is.
Did I tell... Did I talk about this one?
All right, I'll read it.
Well, should I wait till people come in?
I actually like this one.
Chat faked an entire stream.
Yeah, I heard about that.
We'll get a chill.
Yeah, we're going to play...
All right, here's the plan.
I want to go over the weekend.
Yes, the plan is to be live today, tomorrow, and Sunday.
Today, we're going to play Papa's Freezeria.
Was it Freezeria?
Freezeria.
What the fuck?
I'm just realizing right now.
It's Freezeria.
Freezeria is what I thought it was.
For five, ten years.
Ten years ago, I called it Freezeria.
Why would I do that?
I'm just... Why?
That's weird.
Anyways, you can't read?
I can read.
Freezeria isn't a word.
Oh, wait, if you look up Freezeria in the dictionary,
is Papa's face there?
Is it better me?
All right, anyways, we're going to play this today.
We have Papa's Freezeria.
This is the deluxe version.
The deluxe version is on Steam now, apparently.
I don't know what that means.
I'm just going to chill and play it.
Tomorrow, we might play something else.
It depends on how long this one goes for.
Also, tomorrow, the plan is to do 90s ads.
Watch some old 90s ads.
It'll be fun.
And then Sunday, I want to do the House Flipper Farm DLC.
Looks like a pretty extensive update to that game.
But there's your weekend plan.
I think you can build your own house now
in House Flipper, right?
It looks like you can build a whole house from scratch.
I don't know why I made that sound
like it was a chocolate pudding recipe.
All right, anyways, let's read this tweet,
this giraffe-ed tweet.
By the way, I want to make it really clear.
I have not seen the Mario movie,
so I don't even, we're just going to read this.
I've not seen the Mario movie.
I just watched the Mario movie
and was getting really fidgety and visibly annoyed.
They took way too long for the first Yahoo.
It was all right.
Is it great? Send it.
I'm just imagining somebody sitting there
just fucking pissed, like fidgeting around,
like, where is it?
Come on.
Fucking God damn it.
And Holly said something funny.
She's like, we haven't seen this movie.
What if Mario does a Yahoo in the first like 10 seconds?
Like, wow, that really sounds fucked up, doesn't it?
Does it happen in the first 10 seconds?
Oh, they took way too long for the first Yahoo.
And if it happens in the first five minutes of the movie,
I don't know.
I thought that made it funnier.
He literally does.
He Yahoo's really quickly.
But that's the only reason he went to go to see the movie.
It's his first word in the movie?
Who cares?
It's literally the first word in the movie
and it's in the trailer.
Oh, they took way too fucking long for the first Yahoo.
I was fidgeting and annoyed in my seat.
All right.
Well, that's, there it is.
This movie is fired though.
Oh, we're definitely gonna see it.
Need to find some time to see it.
Okay.
So we're gonna play Papa's Freez-Area.
I'm a, I don't wanna say I'm a huge fan of the Papa games.
I've played them a few times.
Relax.
Pull up a chair.
If you're already sitting, then good.
I guess if you're already sitting down.
I actually don't even know how you play these.
They're kind of like Diner Dash, right?
They operate similarly.
If they like serve customers and they get mad
if you take too long, right?
No.
Oh, wait.
Oh, that is how it is, isn't it?
Okay.
Well, let's go.
Here is Papa's Freez-Area.
Hey, there we go.
Okay.
Let's get started.
We'll do this one.
Create a custom worker.
I mean, we kind of have to do that, don't we?
Custom worker?
Yeah, this is, this is deluxe.
I don't know what the deluxe means.
Okay.
Wait, you can change the position of your head?
I can't, I'm all right with this.
You can do gamer neck or normal.
Oh, this is actually a lot.
How are there more hair options in Papa's Freez-Area
than half of the AAA games I've ever played?
Doesn't that kind of make you a little annoyed?
And I'm talking way more.
Okay, how about that?
Is there hair color?
It's 2D.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
Let's be fair.
We're definitely, we're going with the mustache 100%.
I could, hold on.
Where's Bald?
I kind of want to make the Pringles guy.
What does the Pringles guy look like?
Can I change the eyes?
Okay.
What does the Pringles,
the Pringles guy doesn't really have a mouth.
No, it's not like that.
The mustache covers the mouth.
The Pringles guy has hair.
He does?
Oh shit, he does.
He does have hair.
He has hair.
Why do I think he doesn't have hair?
I'm telling you right now,
the Pringles guy just did not have hair until right now.
Until you just all said it.
It's a middle part, isn't it?
It's like this, right?
Oh, let me look this up.
Pringles guy.
What does he look like?
He does have hair.
I'm thinking of the Monopoly man.
The Monopoly man has the mustache and is bald.
The Pringles guy has a middle part and a mustache.
Okay.
Well, now I know.
It's kind of this mustache as well.
Monopoly man has a top hat.
Yeah, he's still bald.
That looks pretty good.
This looks good.
I think this is fine.
Ooh, eyebrows.
Wait, should we get rid of the hair
and just do eyebrows for hair?
Kind of like that, isn't it?
Ah, that's too much work.
I don't think the eyebrows can be big enough
for that to make sense.
What's the biggest eyebrows?
These ones?
I can't make these bigger.
No brows.
He has no eyebrows.
All right, what was it?
It's the middle part or is it right here somewhere?
Should we get, no eyebrows he's saying?
Okay, I think that's good.
What about glasses?
This feels like they updated the Pringles guy, right?
Doesn't it feel like, oh yeah, no, no,
we took the Pringles guy.
We wanted to update his look a little.
I don't like the updated Pringles guy.
Hey, we gave the Pringles guy glasses.
Oh, okay.
Hipster.
I'm gonna keep it like this.
What do you mean no?
Hey guys, is that, my character's done.
No, it's not.
Yeah, it is, it's done.
I'm done, my character's done.
I'm keeping it like this.
I love the no.
All right, your chef's name.
What's my chef's name?
I don't know.
Oh, is the window too small?
No, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Oh, wait.
Oh, shit, wait.
There we go, okay.
Name.
How about just, Peter Pringle.
Melvin?
I like Melvin.
Melvin's kinda nice.
Yeah, I'll do Melvin.
Just Melvin.
All right, Melvin.
I'm ready.
Melvin's new job.
Let's go.
Worker's guide.
Calypso Island population.
Isn't there like 12 people that live here?
12 people on this whole island?
All right, hold on.
I was trying to make Papa.
Why have I combined every one of these characters?
I just look like a dickhead.
I look like I'm showing up to work pretending to be him.
I was trying to make him the whole time.
All right.
He really does look like the Pringles guy.
He can look like that, but I can't.
Okay, day one.
Welcome to Papa's Freezeria.
Let's get started with training, okay.
You'll copy down each customer's order
onto an order ticket.
Garlic on your,
what kind of person wants garlic on their ice cream?
Switch to the build station
and start preparing ice cream and ingredients, okay.
Watch the meter on the ice cream machine.
Wait until it's centered, then press the pour button.
Good.
All right, and now we need a mixable
from the mixable machine.
They want strawberries.
That was not very good.
They want strawberry syrup.
That's a little too many strawberries, don't you think?
Okay.
And then drag the cup onto the blender.
I've always wanted to see how this worked.
Watch the blend meter on the blender
and wait till it looks like what they ordered on the ticket.
Huh?
How long does this take?
Okay.
It's blended.
Ooh, it looks pretty good.
Now they want, oh, it's whipped cream.
Okay.
Well, I didn't know that when I,
I thought I had to click it.
It just goes?
It just starts going when I let go of the button.
I didn't press to do that.
Tap the shakers button.
What's your type of shakers?
This is too elaborate.
Okay.
Okay, and then drops.
Free cherries.
The sundae is finished.
Drag this over here.
All right, here you go.
What do you think?
It was awful.
Wait, the whipped cream was next to it.
Yeah, I thought you ordered it on the side.
It's like salad dressing.
All right, you want a medium blended Reese's
with chocolate, chocolate whipped cream,
double chocolate Oreos.
And then, okay.
I'm gonna do Reese's.
Reese's in there.
Chocolate, looks good.
Blend that up.
Needs to get to this consistency.
Medium rare ice cream.
Good.
All right, get it over here.
Next, I need a chocolate, chocolate whipped cream.
How do I stop it from doing that?
All right.
I go middle, I go middle out.
Do you guys do that?
How do you guys do it?
Do you guys go around the rim
and do a big swirl into the middle?
Or do you go middle?
So it goes and fills kind of out.
I like doing it like that, actually.
I think you get a good top from doing that.
You do a swirl.
All right, let's put some of this on.
Okay.
And then you want Oreos like this,
right in the middle, like this.
Let's go.
I gotta stop that from happening.
$5 tip, nice.
Not bad, not bad.
Took you a whole day to do two orders.
Well, that's because over the course of the whole day,
only two customers came in.
Gotcha.
Mini game show?
Use the game tickets you earned to play
in Fudini's daily mini game show.
What is this?
10 baddies.
What the?
Are these baddies?
What costume?
What is a baddie?
I don't get it.
Am I winning?
Okay.
Ooh, I got a new shirt.
Let's do it again.
I've hit 11 baddies.
Does this keep going up?
Do I have unlimited ammo?
Is this the only thing I can do with this?
I feel like I'm playing the Resident Evil mini game
all over again.
Let's go.
Ooh, I got a table.
Decoration?
Okay.
Cool.
New clothes?
Yup.
What's that mean?
Okay.
New.
Ooh, I can decorate my lobby.
Tap the open button to view and choose items
you purchased in the shop.
All right.
Here's the table.
First items that can be dragged to the front
or back areas of the floor.
Drag furniture to the red x-ray
to remove from the lobby.
I think it's fine there.
Stickers?
Do I have any stickers?
I don't think I have any.
These are achievements.
Okay, they added achievements.
What's this?
Start a parade.
Does this cost money?
That cost money?
I'll do it later.
All right, let's go.
I get it.
New customer.
Pink lemonade syrup.
Okay.
Sugar plum topping.
All right.
What do you got?
Medium.
Blended.
Strawberry.
Lemonade.
Whipped cream.
Magical.
Whatever fruit that is.
Okay, let's go.
I got it.
Let's do this quick.
Okay.
Go, blend it.
Anybody else?
Just you?
All right, good.
Oops.
Why is this taking so long?
This machine sucks.
Medium.
Blend.
Reese's banana.
Chocolate.
Banana.
You got it.
All right.
Take us to the line.
Organize them.
Okay.
This thing's still going.
All right, all right, all right.
Keep going.
I want to get a good view of this.
How do I get a good view of this?
How do I get a good view of that?
There it is.
Okay.
Is this thing done?
All right.
What do you want?
You want Reese's.
You want banana.
And then.
Okay, good.
Put that on.
Take this one off.
You wanted whipped cream.
Okay.
And then you also wanted.
Is it plum?
Oops.
Okay.
That actually looks pretty good.
And then you want three cherries.
All right.
Let's go.
Take that.
All right.
I got to hurry up.
Anybody else?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Is it a brownie?
Brownie.
What is that?
Okay.
Brownie chunks.
What is this?
What is this moon?
All right.
You wanted chocolate with cream.
Coconut.
Where is it?
And then one Oreo.
Is this the right order?
Fuck.
This is the wrong order.
Oh, shit.
How do I change this?
I fucked it up.
It's okay.
It's all right.
I fucked it up.
It's okay.
You still liked it.
You still gave me three dollar tip.
This one's wrong too then.
I got to throw this away.
All right.
Reese's.
And then.
Nana.
This customer is a closer.
They're very picky about their food.
They'll be tougher when grading.
I can handle it.
You're going to get fired?
I am.
I'm going to be fine.
All right.
Really picky about their order.
How's that not perfect?
This one's still going.
Anybody else?
No, that's it.
All right.
So this one's coming off first.
So don't be stupid about this.
And this one is chocolate with cream.
Chocolate rocks.
And then three bananas.
Chocolate, chocolate, banana.
Banana.
Make one for yourself.
Cost money?
Does that cost money though?
All right.
Here we go.
Good.
They wanted these.
Chocolate.
Whatever.
What are these?
Chocolate.
Whatever there.
And then you wanted bananas.
Good.
Go.
There you are.
Sorry for the wait.
Let's get a ticket.
All right.
I see.
Oh shit.
Take that off.
All right.
This person's very picky about this.
So we want to make this perfect.
That's, it was close.
All right.
Then you want peanuts?
Shit!
How do I clean?
I would hate to hear that.
I would hate to hear that from the back.
Shit!
When they, you know they're working on your order.
What do you think?
Not bad.
All right.
I mean, we could have done better on the building.
That's for sure.
I got money though.
I'm doing all right.
Rank two.
Chili works.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Give me one second.
I have a very important thing
that I have to take care of very quickly.
Give me one second.
I'll be back in literally two minutes.
Quick BRB.
Give me two seconds.
Okay.
Sorry.
Just had to do something very, very quickly.
We're good.
I told you I'm right back.
I'm right back.
We didn't go anywhere.
All right.
Here we go.
So this is Rico's Chili Works.
How does this one work?
Oh, great.
Okay.
Just connect everything and then do what?
I got this.
Yeah.
Everyone's going to, oh, know me on this one.
But I, when they're not that difficult, I can get them.
Like this is not that bad.
I can handle this.
I can handle it.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Look.
See?
Payday in four days.
I get a hundred bucks.
Okay.
I'm just going to put on every new piece of tire
that comes in.
Top and trim.
Countertop and wall trim.
Okay.
Oh, that's my counter.
I need, I need German 985 green.
There you go.
That's not green, but I support you.
What do you mean?
This is teal, like aqua, kind of green, coral, spearmint.
I don't know.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Should I do parade?
No, it probably costs money.
What is this shop?
Is that actual money or no?
New customer.
It's definitely not green.
That's definitely green.
All right.
Let's go.
What do you want?
Medium, blended, blueberry.
What flavor is this?
All right.
What is that flavor?
Moon flavor.
Yeah.
Well, what is moon flavor?
Wait, don't get me wrong.
It looks awesome.
I'd want to try it.
All right.
Just you.
That's good.
Want me to make one for myself?
I'll make one for myself.
All right.
If it were me right now,
I'm doing an Oreo cookie
and I don't know whatever this is.
I'm going to cream.
I'm going to get fired.
All right.
Oh, yep.
Special recipe.
They'll be tougher when grading their order,
but you can earn a new recipe to serve.
It's a tough recipe.
Why is this so tough?
Okay.
What do you want?
Shit.
Okay.
It's fine.
How is this so different?
Banana?
Come on.
That up.
This went off.
Perfect.
All right.
This looks good.
Good.
Okay.
And you also want,
you want blueberry sauce?
Oh, white chocolate.
Oh, you've ruined everything now.
This is ruined.
Wait, what is that?
Okay.
Why did I make that?
I don't even want to give that to anybody.
I just made it for fun.
All right.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
This one goes in the middle.
And then two of these.
Go.
I like very plain ice cream orders.
I know that there's a lot of,
donut places.
Have you seen the donut places do this too?
I don't know.
I'm not in,
I just want it to be like,
give me like Oreo cookies in it,
or give me chocolate,
give me vanilla,
give me like banana.
I don't,
too many things in each order.
I like,
if you give me an ice cream,
I want it just to be that one thing that I want to taste.
That's pretty perfect.
Peanuts?
I don't like peanuts on anything really either.
I like eating peanuts by themselves.
Here you go.
Strawberry brownie.
Oh shit.
Is that an eggplant?
What is that?
You can get eggplant on ice cream?
All right, let's go.
Hurry up.
Strawberry.
Get that on there.
Another one.
This one is,
cake and moon.
And moon.
Good.
Line that up.
Is that it?
Anybody else?
Yep.
All right.
This is,
this person's angry.
And I want sprinkles on it.
And I want cherries on it.
And I want cookies on it.
It's like, all right, come on.
Relax.
I don't know how you order this angry.
Yeah.
And I'll take a large blended ice cream please.
And I want strawberry sprinkles on it.
And I want whipped cream on it.
And I want that,
the fancy little cookie thing on it too.
How do you order that angrily?
I feel like you can't order that angry.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop talking and play the game.
Oh shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I got time.
What do you want?
Strawberries?
Shit.
Okay.
All right.
This is this one.
Uh-oh.
What do you want?
Chocolate?
Hey.
Quiet.
Everybody stop talking.
All right.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
I gotta go.
I have to take this one off now.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
I gotta go, gotta go, gotta go.
This one's overblended.
Fuck.
Overblended.
Ruined it.
Okay.
You want a coconut?
And then you wanted,
you want this other,
what is this?
Like Lucky Charms or something?
Go.
What is that a 60?
Oh, cause I overblended it.
All right.
This one has to be perfect.
And then this one is sprinkles.
Nice distribution.
There you go.
Overblended a little.
Oh no.
Well, I mean,
what is that purple thing?
Please help.
I don't know.
I thought it was an eggplant.
You're done.
Hop us raceway.
Sure.
Win the race.
Collect points to go faster.
How do you drive?
How do I drive?
I thought I was the person,
I thought I was the person at the bottom.
I don't know why I was,
I thought I was the person at the very bottom.
I would love to restart this.
All right.
Let me do that again.
Also, the frame rate of this game kind of hurts my head.
I gotta be very honest.
The road is kind of making my head hurt.
How am I supposed to collect the coins?
If they're in the way.
There we go.
All right.
We're good.
I got new pants.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
Good.
It's all mine now.
How was he playing this?
This is now on Steam.
This is the deluxe version of the game.
It's on Steam right now.
I guess they made some changes to it.
I don't know what they are.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I can make a special.
Ooh, strawberry brownie.
Look at that.
Looks elaborate.
Okay.
I got some new stuff.
Did I get some?
What about shop?
I got 61 bucks.
Doorbell.
You'll hear when new customers enter.
Oh, that's helpful.
Customer coupon.
Send one to a specific customer to get them to visit again.
Lender booster?
Really?
Okay.
Well, I don't think I need any of these.
What about some of this?
I mean, this table is a must have.
Look at how tacky this is.
You know how annoying this would be to clean?
Because all the food,
all the syrup would just get in the crevices.
It'd be so annoying.
Ooh.
Hold on.
Get the doorbell.
The doorbell's way more important.
I guess it is only $4.
Thanksgiving.
Oh, look at this.
It's got marshmallows on it.
Midnight freeze.
Okay.
How do I do it?
Oh, that's good.
This gives me points, right?
Now, we gotta make sure the kids can see.
We gotta make sure the kids can see.
Let's go.
I got my special selected.
Marshmallows are now available.
Mint syrup is now available for one person to order
every three days or every week.
Can we hold in that bottle till expiration?
And I love, I like mint too.
I like mint chocolate chip.
I like that flavor.
I'm just telling you.
Marshmallow, mint?
Marshmallow, mint.
I kind of feel like this is gonna be kind of good.
That sounds actually awesome.
Can I help you?
I want a strawberry brownie.
Okay.
What?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Well, it's ice cream.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, I got time.
What the hell's in this?
Chocolate, strawberries.
And then it's a bunch of other shit later.
Okay.
This is where I would just, I would start dancing.
Just kind of with my hands, moving back and forth,
smiling.
And then when they take their phone up,
no, no, no, no, no, no video or no photography at all.
Allowed.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, go, go, go, go, go.
What am I doing?
I'm waiting.
Coconut and a cherry.
This is still good.
We're still good.
We're good, good, good, good, good.
He's talking about dancing behind
an imaginary ice cream counter.
I'm good.
A little bit overblended, but it's all right.
It's the special.
All right, then now we need
chocolate whipped cream, chocolate sauce.
Okay, now strawberry sauce.
Okay.
And then chocolate chips and cherries.
How many cherries?
Three.
73?
All right, I gotta do these quick.
This one's kind of elaborate.
I'm gonna do this one last.
Thank you for your patience, by the way.
We appreciate it.
What do you want?
Medium blueberry with whipped cream,
strawberry sauce, coconut, sprinkles.
This is kind of, oh, this is like too much.
That's a little too much.
I gotta put three of these up.
Blueberry, strawberry.
Blend that up.
Keep going.
Oh my God, I forget everything.
I forget everything that everybody ordered.
Which one have I not done?
This is blueberry, strawberry.
This one is blueberry, strawberry.
I haven't done this one.
Did I just do this one?
Did I just do that one?
I just did that one?
What's the one I haven't done?
Blueberry and moon, okay.
Who's is this?
Oh shit, who's was that?
Is this one right?
Yep.
Plant, cookie, banana.
Get it out.
This is a kids' game.
Papa's games are not kids' games.
They're incredibly stressful games
that require a ton of work and time and work and thoughts.
Oh, this one's just sitting here.
Which one is this one?
This one is strawberry and this one, okay.
Somebody's gonna be pissed, but whatever.
It's all right, I fucked it up.
I gotta go, this looks like it melted
for like a half an hour.
This is why I always wanna eat one of these before,
you pull over, you park and you eat this.
Because if you just let it sit in the fucking tray,
in the cup holder, it turns into this
by the time you get back.
You pull over and you park and you eat it.
Serve it already.
I'm going as fast as I wanna go.
But fine, is it?
Oh, this is actually really long.
You were here first.
Oh, fuck.
What are your thoughts on Horton, Here's a Who?
I don't think I ever saw that movie.
Just checking to see if you're still here.
It's a book.
Yeah, I know.
Promise that one is yours.
You can hear it right now.
I wanted to make sure it was fresh for you.
I wanted to make it fresh.
Working on it right now.
Hey, I just opened a fresh can of white chocolate for you.
These sprinkles?
Oh, these sprinkles, I don't wanna serve these to you.
Let me open up a new thing of sprinkles for you.
All right.
Hey, by the way, thanks.
That wasn't that bad.
I will allow one comedy.
I'm gonna allow one comedy order
where we just give a person a cup of cherries or something.
That's fine for me.
We'll do it.
Why am I?
Okay, I was like, what the hell?
You guys ever want the actual tactic to do that?
So always keep your mouse cursor right in the middle
and don't shoot at any of the discs that come out
until kind of close to the end.
Don't do this.
Stay right here.
They're gonna cross the middle plane.
You won't have to move very far from here
to get most of them.
You know what I'm saying?
Why did you instinctively point that?
I don't know.
I just was like, shoot this thing.
Always make sure you come right back to the middle
after every shot.
I was distracted by you.
Ooh, nutty buttercups.
All right.
What is this?
A carnival table?
Should I make a bunch of obstacles
so it takes them longer to get to the window?
See, I think that's a big mistake.
A lot of businesses that have lines,
there should be a handful of those mall toy stands
that have like the back flipping dog and shit.
Just give people just shit to do.
And put like kinetic sand samples over here.
You know what I'm saying?
And make that part of the line.
Time to hire some help.
Customers can now call to place orders for delivery.
You need to hire a driver to deliver the food.
All right, they can get delivery.
Should we give them hair?
Make Miku.
Why do you guys want me to put Miku
in every single video game?
Do you understand?
What does Miku's hair look like?
Why am I even entertaining this?
Where is it?
Like that?
No, it's like that.
Like that, I don't, like this?
Like that?
This one?
This one.
Oh, wait.
What about the front?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I got it, I got it.
This is close enough.
Okay, and we need, okay, I guess.
Correct, right?
That looks fine.
Can you change the eyebrow color?
I don't think so.
Different color, different color.
Like that?
What is closer?
It's this one then, isn't it?
Is it though?
I feel like it's not.
I don't, I feel like that's not correct.
No, that's too green.
Yeah, that's way too green.
This one's definitely closer.
Although maybe, it's between these two.
This one's too blue and this one's too green,
but we have to live with one of these.
I'm gonna keep this one.
Pull up an image, I got one right here.
In the mod chat, I got some help.
Okay, this is fine.
What about the neck?
That's not correct either.
Okay, it looks pretty good.
Longer neck, longer neck.
This is fine, this is fine.
Okay, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
Nevada, okay.
Strawberry wafer, all right, let's go.
Medium blended, blueberry, strawberry, strawberry.
I have to keep, okay, I'm putting these in a line
so I know that the first thing that I do is this one,
every time.
This is one in this descending order, strawberry.
All right, who's next?
I'm just gonna get one ready.
Should I pre-make?
Oh, hold on, hold on, telephone.
Your driver will take orders from customers
who call on the phone.
They'll also deliver the food to their home when it's ready.
Okay, you got it?
Marshmallow mint, go.
All right, this is the second order.
Two is in this slot.
Pico's working really hard.
Yeah, no, we're good.
All right, first one, I know I should do it the other way.
Other way around.
That's the plan.
That's way more efficient, that helps way more.
Let's go.
All right, we need strawberry whipped cream.
Coconut syrup.
These, the strawberry wafers, that.
This actually looks kind of good, just 100%.
All right, come on, hurry up.
I actually would much prefer you just scream this to me
when I'm in the back.
Where's Marshmallow's?
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Hurry up, I'm gonna get that phone.
Somebody get that phone.
You want to, okay.
What the hell are you ordering?
What was this?
You just walk in here in the sun?
All right, I gotta hurry up.
Get this off the screen, I can't see.
Stop telling me that I'm playing poorly
and just get off the screen.
Get off the screen.
I don't want the help page.
Throw this away.
All right, what, I was in the middle of something.
It's this one here, okay.
All right, go, go, go, go, go, go.
What am I missing?
Strawberry lemonade bullshit, all right.
All right, sounds good.
This one spinning, this one is this one.
I need the strawberry brownie quickly.
I don't even know how to make it,
so I'm gonna do this one first.
This one here.
All right, strawberry brownie is brownie.
No shit.
Who would have thought?
And then strawberry, shit, all right.
All right, we're good.
This is coming off first.
Okay, we need this.
I know people are mad that I didn't give anybody
the strawberry syrup, but I know.
Pretty happy.
This is, which one is this?
This one?
All right, go, go, go, go, go, quick.
I'll get all these out at the same time.
Peanuts and then a cherry.
Very easy order.
Very easy, good.
Almost perfect.
All right, now this is chocolate syrup, strawberry syrup.
Wait, what's going on?
Yep, good.
Now the last bits are chocolate chips
and three cherries, perfectly placed.
This is so much sugar.
Yeah, this is like 4,000 calories.
That's a lot of calories.
Marshmallow Pro, blender ball.
There's a lot of these little mini games.
I like these.
Am I at max power?
I just won the game.
Okay, what?
Food truck free play.
Looks good.
Is that the parade?
The food truck is the best shit
in the most recent mobile game.
I'll check it out.
I left the parade.
I got work to do.
I haven't seen any stickers.
All right, let's go.
Oh, I wanted to do the free play.
Wally.
I'll take a medium blended blueberry
with some strawberries,
some whipped cream with the blue in it
and then also would like some plum and some peanuts please.
Thank you.
That's it?
I can sit right here.
I look like I'm in a costume.
Some days your dining room will be open
and your driver will take orders from customers
who are dining instead of delivering orders.
Oh, they actually come sit down.
Okay.
Do you want Oreo cookie?
All right, Oreos.
How blended is this?
I think we're good.
Chocolate.
Put that up there.
How we doing?
Good.
That one actually sounds pretty good.
It does, yeah.
Yeah, I'm taking it.
Okay.
This is still blending.
Get this out of the way.
This one is the one I need to be focusing on.
So we need...
God damn it.
Whatever, fine.
This looks good too.
I can't remember the last time I actually had
a wacky, wild-ass ice cream.
I would consider this to be a wacky-ass ice cream.
There's a ton of different flavors and toppings
and it's been a very long time.
Things are definitely done by now.
All right, you wanted this.
Chocolate.
White chocolate does get a pretty bad rap, doesn't it?
I think it makes sense in some places,
but I really just don't like it in a lot of places.
How did I backtrack that before you guys
even yelled at me about it?
That was interesting.
87% cake.
All right, the hardest thing to make
in the whole restaurant.
Okay, let's go.
I gotta memorize this.
And then it's brownie, strawberry.
Another person just came in.
All right, it's strawberry.
All right, all right, all right.
What do you want?
White chocolate is usually good for two bites.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's fine.
All right, the system is working.
Please make a funny drink.
Okay, I'll make a funny one.
I wanna at least make enough money.
Cherry, and we're good.
Now get out of here.
Tropical treat?
Well, you took me too long
for telling me about my new tropical treat.
All right, what the hell is on this?
It's this, too late.
Then it's three brownie.
Ah, it's even more bullshit.
Come on, we're good.
Take it off.
Is there really a complaint though?
My blended ice cream was blended too much.
Doesn't it hit a point
where it doesn't blend at all anymore?
How would you even tell that?
It's just because it gets soupy?
31%, you did one really unhappy.
It's really soupy.
Don't overmix.
I like these mini games.
Slider escape, okay.
Slide the burger slider towards the goal.
Oh, it's one of these.
If only it has to move the whole way into the wall.
Got it.
He's not gonna make it?
Well, I already did.
I got it.
All right, I'm rank five.
New special.
All right, I wanna do the tropical treat.
I would probably like this.
Yeah, just put a bunch of shit everywhere.
Stickers.
You can now send your driver out in a food truck
between work days to make any food you choose, okay?
Customers won't place any orders at the food truck.
Just make whatever you like and see who shows up to buy it.
Oh, all right, let's go.
I'm gonna make my favorite.
This is exactly what I would be doing.
All right, bingo.
Oreo, moon, not blended at all.
Look at that, lightly blended.
Still tons of chunks.
And if it were me, I'm topping this
with a little bit of regular whipped cream,
just a tiny bit.
Well, nevermind.
And then a little bit of chocolate at the end
and really give him something to take a picture of.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm the only guy in town
that gives you a whole sleeve of Oreos as part of it.
By the way, this shit's only fucking $4.
Holy shit, it's awesome.
Okay, hold on.
Can I change the flavor of ice cream?
No, how about just plain?
Oh, can I just do plain soft serve?
Marshmallow, marshmallow, banana, blend that.
And you know what?
Check this out.
Blend the fuck out of that.
Oh, my mouth is already salivating.
My mouth is watering.
I wouldn't do anything else to this.
Look at that.
That was 100%.
Don't have to make ice cream again.
That would be amazing.
All right, we have to make a Miku shake.
All right, we're gonna do blueberry.
And then the moon sauce.
We're gonna go right in the middle here.
This Miku, whatever, Miku branded, okay.
And then this, and then this.
Look at that.
And that's it.
That's a full 100.
Cool.
Okay, now let's do something dumb.
Cake, lemonade, lightly blended.
And then strawberry whipped cream.
I can't add any more strawberry, wait, I can.
All right, no, I can't.
And sprinkles.
And this has to be a joke how much sprinkles are on it.
How many can you actually put?
A lot?
How much is a lot?
Skip two hours?
Vod watchers?
It's unlimited?
I don't think this is,
I think it's replacing them at some point.
I don't even think it's,
I think it's just kind of coloring over them.
What do you think?
A little too much on the toppings, but that's all right.
All right, last one.
This is gonna be called the triple strawberry.
Oh guys, we're making a triple strawberry.
Look.
Okay, I need to,
there needs to be like ace, king, king, ace, two.
I want it to be like card themed or something.
That's fun.
That would be a goofy ass shake.
Cool.
It's payday.
Go.
Large cup has been at, oh.
That's my favorite dessert ever.
People sleep on s'mores so much and it's infuriating to me.
Like that is the greatest kind of dessert.
It is, people just sleep on it.
It's like so hard to, you know, it's annoying to me.
Okay, this is a large.
This is a large s'mores.
Ooh, that's probably so good.
S'mores are amazing.
I mean, I get it.
S'mores are a pain in the ass to make.
They're kind of messy and they're kind of annoying,
but I think they're the best dessert.
One of the best at least.
Especially fresh.
That is a medium.
I made s'mores in my dorm room with a candle.
Dude, you gotta be careful, man.
With a candle?
Come on.
Why?
All right, wait, don't distract me.
This is important.
I'll take your order in a second.
We gotta do this one.
Peanuts, all right, you lost me with the peanuts.
Everything else here is perfect.
S'mores.
I gotta take an order here in a second,
but I don't want it to overblend.
Go ahead and do this.
No, no, I honestly, peanuts.
I feel like that's very divided.
I think a lot of people really don't like
nuts on their dessert.
You want a tropical treat.
You want the hard shit.
All right, hold on, I gotta,
and this got all screwed up.
Why did you move this?
Blueberries?
This looks kinda good.
Blueberry cream is really good.
Pecans are literally the only S tier ice cream topping.
I, no, no, I disagree.
All right, what is this tropical treat?
It's blueberry lemonade.
Is this a large or a small?
Medium.
Blueberry lemonade.
That thing up there, this is the tropical,
I'm gonna separate these.
Any nuts, really, I don't really like on ice cream.
All right, this is a medium,
rubber banana, good combo.
I kinda did these two close to each other, I think,
because I'm gonna mess it up.
But we'll try to get this one fast.
So I need blue whipped cream, blue sauce,
blue whipped cream, sauce,
wait, wrong one, coconut sprinkles.
Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on.
So much shit on this one.
All right, hurry up, hurry up.
I'm wasting time.
Uh-oh, um, uh-oh.
Oh shit, how do I, what just happened?
Where's the other one?
Which one is this?
Okay, I need this.
Which one is this one?
What just happened?
Okay, it's in the queue, all right, good.
Pretty bad, but it's all right.
Good, it was an easy one.
Placement's pretty dog shit on that, but it's all right.
What's my favorite topping?
Is it weird that I can't answer that
because I haven't had an ice cream like this
in a very long time?
I forgot what all this tastes like.
I like blended up Oreo cookie.
Cookies and cream is one of my favorites,
but that's not really a topping.
Customer cravings, I got six tickets.
What is it?
I don't know, I think it's this one.
I have to remember orders.
Marty Grave.
I don't know, we haven't even served him.
This is a new item.
Oh, I got a new flooring.
It's Mitch Grave.
I'm pretty sure it's this one.
I think Mitch orders the blue whipped cream.
I believe this is s'mores over here
and this is Oreo cookie over here.
I got this, okay.
Yep, this is you like this and you want this.
There's usually a ton of stuff on, he's cheating?
There's not even enough time for you to tell me who did it.
There's a delay on this to the stream.
All right, you, it's, wait, who is this one?
You want one of these.
I think it's this one here.
So I missed one.
Oh no, I got a bunch of new furniture.
This place fucking sucks.
I get points for these being here though.
That's not as horrible.
This thing is so ugly.
I don't even know what to do with this.
Maybe put this in the very beginning.
It's like, oh look, checkpoint, you've made it into the,
yeah, I could do some really, yeah.
Oh, checkpoint, you made it into the restaurant.
So here you are, you've made it.
I think that's like a funny little cute thing
to have at the front door.
Checkpoint.
They walk by it and it goes like,
that should tide them over a little bit
when they get to like the 50 person line
and they forget to have looked at the Yelp score
for this restaurant and it's like a two out of fucking five.
Bring, bring, look, come on in.
Why are you so patronizing?
And why did I just go like this?
I'm definitely getting older.
I just, and you know, I can just tell.
I'm kind of getting old guy voice.
I'm getting old.
My voice is turning into an old guy voice.
It just is.
And I'm okay with it.
I don't really don't care.
Strawberry, where's, nope.
Got permanent milk voice, kind of.
Hi, you want medium?
I am gonna wait to put this up here.
Actually looks kinda good.
Okay, now, now I'll put it up.
Come on in.
Why are you so patronizing?
Bring, oh, welcome.
Patronizing, who?
There is a, who am I patronizing with that?
I've never seen a like Mario checkpoint flag
at the beginning of any restaurant.
This is not a real place.
All right, hold on.
What was it?
This is large.
Check the blend.
This is why I fucking always gotta check
the goddamn blend first before I do anything.
Hey, go, go, go, go, go.
No, that was wrong.
You need a blend alarm.
I need to focus.
I didn't even, why did I just do that?
Take it off.
What the hell do you want?
Okay, and this.
I gotta start styling it up a little more like that.
That's like cool.
Peanuts on the left.
Dunk, I just blended a little too much.
All right, this is a large and you wanted Reese's chocolate.
Get this on a blender.
We need a tropical treat.
Tropical treat, I believe is medium, right?
Yep.
Food critic has arrived.
Okay, I don't care about anybody else's order.
This is a medium.
No, wait, this is a test.
Sorry, sir, you're gonna have to wait.
Oh, he waited.
He's making me, there's another customer.
Strawberry.
Is this the critics?
I'm gonna wait till this is ready,
although I'll start to blend on this one.
It's a medium.
Cake and chocolate.
Perfect.
Put it up there.
Good.
It's cookie, cherry, cookie.
All right.
All right, we still got plenty of time.
First up is whipped cream, coconut sauce, sprinkles.
Whipped cream, coconut sauce, lucky charms.
Coconut sauce, lucky charms,
and then there's something else on it.
Go.
All right, perfect timing.
Good, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
No!
Hey, hey, can you come back tomorrow?
No, honestly, at this point, I'm sorry.
At this point, I have a stuffed squirrel in the back,
like a stuffed animal squirrel,
and I just run out, holding it against my neck,
like, God, just give me the squirrel,
and I pump like fucking squirrel,
like yippee, yippee, the sound effects through the PA.
I'm sorry, you're gonna come back tomorrow.
Gym carrier routine.
Yeah, but I mean, at some point,
I gotta check the business here.
Make another one?
He's been waiting for too long already.
No, I can't.
This is fine.
It's a little blended, but who cares?
We got the blue ribbon, we're fine.
But there would be a squirrel in your restaurant.
Wouldn't that be worse?
No, dude, you have to plan it.
So I have to come out to the,
all right, I've gotta come out to the lobby,
be like, oh, I'm just checking to make sure
everyone's doing all right.
God, it's a little stuffy in here.
And I open up one of the windows,
like, and I have somebody throw
the stuffed animal squirrel through the window,
and I grab it, holding my neck with it,
and start running around the circle.
Oh, let me 100% this real quick.
That sounds like a Disney Channel sitcom.
Are we sure that didn't happen on like Sweet Life on Deck?
That may have, that may have happened.
That actually might be a plot from that show.
Shit, God damn, this is hard.
Ooh, I got a sticker.
Ooh, did I actually get one?
All right, chunky alarm.
Set this alarm for when Sundays are blended to chunky.
Hold down the booster to blend Sundays faster.
That's kind of good.
I feel like it's this one,
because most of them are coming through like this.
Okay, and then maybe the first level of this,
I can speed it up, and then send one
to a specific customer to get them to visit again.
Um, I'll get these two, why not?
So I'm imagining those are just installed, right?
Now celebrating Starlight Jubilee.
New customer, boomer, pomegranate, mulberry medley?
You earned a blue ribbon for the next three days,
customers will give better tips.
Ooh, all right, what even is that?
This is medium.
That's bad, throw it away quick.
What if it's this thing?
Hold down to boost button.
Oreo cookie, strawberry, chocolate.
That's, I guess it's not that bad.
I have the alarm set, right?
Tap a blend alarm, okay, yeah, there's the alarm.
Speed this up.
All right, good.
What is the max level in this game anyways?
And then pomegranate shakes?
Those pomegranate seeds?
I would, on ice cream?
I feel like that'd be kind of annoying.
I can do it quick.
Okay, you wanted this.
Syrup on there, this on there.
Chocolate chips, and then almost good.
Max level's 100.
They give extra tips today.
It's almost 10 bucks.
Do I have anything blending yet?
What did you want?
All right, all right, we got two mediums.
Get them up there.
Want these, I don't even know what these are supposed to be.
Those are supposed to be like Mike and Ikes.
This is blueberry, strawberry.
Where's my comedy milkshake?
Oh, you missed it, I did it in the food truck.
The wrong syrup.
What, wrong?
Yeah, I know, hold on.
It's lemonade, not strawberry.
Pink pomegranate, okay, cool.
A large Reese's chocolate.
This is not a bad one, this is easy.
Okay, that's a tropical treat.
I gotta hurry up with this one.
So it's, oh, right, I screwed it up, it's fine.
Again, large.
It's Reese's, it's Reese's.
Oh, all right, banana cake.
Banana cake, strawberry.
How's that not perfect?
This is the tropical one, right?
All right, what is this?
Okay, it's whipped cream, coconut syrup,
and then sprinkles.
Good.
They had to wait a long time, but it's all right.
We should be fine.
Oh, quiet, quiet, quiet.
Close as this one, all right, just get it off.
Who's been waiting longer?
You have, okay, let's go.
Oreo, carry Oreo.
That was a tuber reaction?
Yeah, that's true.
Nothing but just toppings, all right.
Toppings, I hate that word.
Ooh, toppings, something about it.
I just don't like it.
Toppings.
Hey, those of you criticizing
that I'm not playing the game right,
I've got a 98% service quality right now.
I'm doing pretty fine right now.
What's going on here?
Wait, I don't have to use them all?
I thought I had to use all the pieces.
What is actually going on right now?
I'm confused, what does it want me to do?
I don't understand.
Wait, really?
Wait, what's going on right now?
I have to, what the hell was that?
Performance IQ.
No, I didn't know what,
they don't give you very much time to be like,
oh, by the way, you have to connect everything.
Good luck.
Red clothing that matches the holiday.
This dude is stoned.
I am not stoned right now.
I am fucking fine.
Oh, fucking, I'm gonna, no more swearing.
Check this out.
Oh, there's this popsicle.
Oh, that's gross.
Medium.
Wait, are we wearing the right clothes?
Can we change?
I can't change.
And then go like this.
There, I just want a smoothie now.
Yeah, me too.
This game just makes me want to go to Sonic.
I feel like that's where you get stuff like this nowadays.
All right, this one's almost there,
but I can take one order.
Come on.
Second order is wrong.
What?
What's wrong with it?
How did I do that?
This thing is huge.
S'mores, strawberry.
This person's gonna shit their pants.
I'm not supposed to be swearing.
Who cares?
What am I talking about?
All right, let me get back to this.
This one is this one.
This one is, no, this one's this one.
This one, this one, this one.
This has to speed up before I put anything else on.
Ow.
Okay.
Blueberry.
Cookie.
Ooh.
Do a poll.
We should bet to see if you won't square for 30 minutes.
Um, you can bet if you want.
I'll try.
I actually will try.
All right, should I make sure to tell this guy
that there's no returns?
You know what I mean?
Okay, I want you to want to understand
you know what you're ordering.
There are no returns or anything, right, dude?
Like, just make sure this person's well aware of this.
Look, this guy doesn't walk back in here in five minutes
and go, hey, this thing was gross.
Yeah, I know.
This person's been waiting.
Just try to get the worst score ever.
Hold on.
I gotta unlock stuff first before I do anything stupid.
This one is large.
Oh, throw it away.
Throw it away.
Wasting time here.
Oh, we got a Charborg raid.
Charborg, thanks for the raid.
Welcome, everybody.
Charborg raid.
Hold on.
Which one was this one?
I don't remember.
This is this one.
And then this, I haven't done this one yet.
All right, hold on, give me a second.
Hey, hey.
When Charborg plays this.
Hey, we'll check and see how they do.
You know what I'm saying?
Check and see how he does.
Yeah, you know what I'm saying?
What is this one?
Okay, good.
I didn't swear.
No, I didn't.
What's happening?
Oh my God.
I thought that was the phone.
Oh shit.
All right, I have to pay attention right now.
I already did that.
What is it?
What?
What did I do?
Did I say something?
What?
What did I say?
Did I say something?
I don't even remember.
Oops.
Why would you ever trust me?
All right, you can trust me now.
You can trust me.
As of right now, for 30 minutes, I won't.
I don't even know what this person ordered.
How is that not perfect?
I am hand cranky.
Oh hey, I'm gonna get the stuffed animal squirrel.
I might need it in a second.
Don't leave, don't leave, don't leave.
I just found that so, all right.
Wait, wrong.
Not a bad day.
All right, timer starts now.
30 minutes from now.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
There's not very many people that believe in me,
but we'll just prove them all wrong right now.
I know that those of you that lost everything
on shrine bets in Breath of the Wild,
now is the time for you to make it all back.
I would have gone all in on yes,
that I can not swear for 30 minutes.
I would have gone all in.
Believe in me this time.
I have a question with the committee here
that's gonna be judging this.
If it's allowed on regular TV, is that allowed?
No.
So, okay, where's the line then?
Where's the line?
If I were to say, oh, like a children's birthday party?
Okay.
So, what?
Oh, what the heck?
Oh, dang it.
That's okay, right?
Those are okay.
Okay, so just pretend that I'm at
a children's birthday party.
Okay.
It's almost similar right there.
Why did you get to be in the front?
It's dangerous too.
You have one dollar?
All right, I'm being it now.
We all can't collect the same coin.
Yeah, there it is.
All right, we're good.
Finally.
Ooh, what was that?
Oh, cool.
All right, keep that.
Oh, don't I have to dress up as,
we have to dress it in a certain outfit, don't we?
Does that matter?
I don't think that matters.
Is this a Facebook game?
This is a game on Steam.
You need to be the family-friendly version
of Die Hard that airs on ABC.
Okay, I can handle that.
I mean, we've already talked about it,
but when they did that joke in Mr. Show,
Bob Odenkirk and,
why can I not think of his name?
They were a comedy duo.
David Cross, yeah, there it is.
I'm gonna pause this because it's important.
They did that bit where it was kind of like
a Sopranos-like that was airing on regular,
kind of just cable television.
And it was, oh, whatever, the Sopranos parody,
whatever it is, brought to you with lots of,
what, it's not paused?
They need to do a bunch of edits,
so it was edited for television.
And it's just so funny.
There's only like two minutes of footage
in like a 30-minute episode.
Was it Mr. Show or Mad TV?
That was Mad TV.
That was Mr. Show?
That was Mr. Show as well.
Mad, it was Mr. Show.
It was on Mr. Show first.
Just wanna make sure you understand that.
Just in case, we just make sure this is really clear.
It was on Mr. Show first.
Let's clear the air here.
Oops.
They are waiting.
Cool, dude.
Whatever, cool story.
You're trying to get me to say a bad word
and it's not gonna happen.
These are both mediums, right?
This is the large, did I get this right?
Okay, this is the large.
We've got two mediums.
This one is Oreo and strawberry.
Same as well.
Holy smokes.
You're not winning.
I just wanna make sure you're aware of that.
You're not going to win.
I'm gonna make you,
I'm gonna put you on the edge of your seat
the whole entire 30 minutes.
Strawberry, plum, pomegranate, whatever.
I almost just got angry.
I just have to not be mad at random stuff
and I'll be fine.
Somebody at the counter.
I got it.
Do I even have that?
There's rocket whipped cream now?
There's rocket whipped cream?
What does this taste like?
You got that wrong?
You put so much stuff in there,
how would you even tell the difference?
I would like a tropical treat, please.
All right, this is medium, medium, medium.
The three mediums immediately.
How long have you been listening to the same
Poppist Freezeria music?
I mean, what are you?
Are you telling me to turn this down
and put on the Twinsons Odyssey soundtrack?
Is that what you're asking?
Because that's what it sounds like.
And then this is strawberry.
Is that gross?
That's kind of gross, isn't it?
I don't care.
Dude, do you even GAF?
Do I give, do I give a,
is that what you're saying?
The medium.
And it is,
this one's not even on here yet.
I gotta speed this up.
We'll do this one.
And okay, this is medium.
What is in this stuff?
Oh, which one is this one?
I'm, I'm, I'm actually,
I'm actually really messed up right now.
I gotta slow down.
Just wait till these are put these in queue.
Do this one first.
That's not even right.
What's even in here?
Is this this one?
I don't know which one this is.
I think this is the right one.
No, what?
No, it's this one.
Whose is this?
This isn't, this isn't,
what is this?
I think it's this one.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I just got, look,
I have to just pay way more attention than I am right now.
It's this one.
Somebody's been waiting for that tropical treat
for a whole day.
Okay, I got it.
It's a medium, right?
Medium.
I have to get this going.
Peanuts, chocolate chips.
There's so much stuff on here.
You're not even gonna taste half of this.
And you want a cookie,
and you want a cookie,
and you want to,
you want all cookies.
You want every cookie we have.
Strawberry, sprinkles,
and then,
all right, I think we're fine.
Zero tip.
All right, I apologize.
And then it's coconut, sprinkles.
This one looks kind of good.
It was going so well, too.
That really annoys me.
How is that wrong?
It was wrong?
Okay, give me a sec.
Making a quick change here on the soundtrack.
Get that Twinsons Odyssey up there.
Why not?
Let's live a little.
42.
What about Doom OST?
You're gonna have to wait.
Let me get through this first.
Fingerless gloves?
That feels, I don't know,
fingerless gloves at a restaurant,
to me would almost be,
I don't know,
I saw someone with fingerless gloves.
They'd be like,
why are you wearing gloves in the first place?
Just don't even wear them.
Right?
I mean, the lore?
It's about the look.
What does this mean?
You're built like the bottom of a table in Chili's.
I don't know what that means,
but I don't know if that was like an insult or,
could have been.
But what does that mean?
Oh my God, he is.
I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
Oh right, I was gonna do this.
Get our own music in here.
Not that the pop is music is bad or anything.
Let's go.
Should I buy something?
Pizza tower OST?
We'll do that next.
That sounds good to me.
Booster two?
This is pretty good anti-swear music.
Yes, it is.
Why would I swear to this?
Medium.
Hey, it's my birthday in a few months.
Can you swear right now for it?
You don't ask for a birthday present that far out.
That's a little too far out, I think.
I think within 30 days is reasonable though.
All right.
No more birthday stuff.
How much time do I have before I can speak?
14 minutes?
Okay.
I'm running right now.
All right.
Let me get this out pretty quickly.
This is this one.
Medium fudge brownie moon.
Ooh, this looks good.
All right.
Where's this ice cream that's gone?
Where's this ice cream?
What happened to the ice cream?
Oh, thank you.
Goodness, it's easy.
This one's pretty easy.
Ah, now we slow it down a little bit.
I like this part.
You play with such a little urgency, it infuriates me.
Um, how is this not urgency?
I'm being very urgent.
I'm just not effective.
Calypso Island coconuts.
What was that?
That's a medium.
That's a volume.
Volume good?
See if I can do this one by just memory.
I believe it is.
I don't know.
I can't do it.
Okay.
Lots of mediums.
Let's go.
Medium.
This is Oreo chocolate.
Good.
Get it up there.
Alarm.
Good.
Avoiding speaking is cheating.
I've been talking this whole time.
Okay.
I need that.
What?
What's going on?
Coconut syrup.
How much time do I have?
Music is ominous.
Sorry.
Uh, um, okay.
Ooh.
This one is white chocolate syrup and peanuts and cherry.
And then get the heck out of here.
The music is too loud.
Peanuts.
I can see this one.
This one looks pretty good.
You should play Peglin.
That's actually been on the list for a long time.
Peglin's been on the list.
Just haven't played it.
Blender ball.
All right.
Let me get this one right.
Is that not high enough?
No, I got it.
The shoes.
Ooh.
Gold tile.
Let's check it out.
I almost just said a bad word.
Cool.
I like that.
Everything's a little too ugly at the moment.
That looks a lot better.
Buying some money with replay.
Oh, let me change this.
Let me change the special.
Pink pomegranate.
Let's try that.
Oh, what about this one?
This one's much less complicated.
Time, six minutes left.
Star sprinkles.
What's the next infomercial stream?
Well, tomorrow we are watching 90s ads.
So I think that's part of, kind of fills that, doesn't it?
Large, let's go.
Strawberry chocolate.
And then this is whipped cream plum star sprinkles.
And the auto carrot is well tomorrow.
That's right.
It's more strawberry.
Large.
No, it's more first, right?
Doesn't matter.
It does.
This is the right one, right?
Yeah.
Those are cool.
Okay.
How are we doing?
Did you swear or no, I didn't?
When?
You're full of baloney.
This one goes hard, by the way.
I didn't say anything bad.
What?
When did I say this word?
You, I said, what?
We need a clip.
I need a clip.
You're trying to get me to say that in chat.
Cause you're trying to make me believe I already said it
and I already lost.
Wait, you're confusing me.
Hold on.
Maybe two mediums.
That's large.
Cake and moon.
All right.
So what's happening here?
90 seconds left.
Yeah.
You, you made it up.
I don't say, hey, I don't see a single clip.
I have not received the clip.
I have not received a single confirmation of this.
Oops.
Don't replace what I was doing.
Somebody said, someone do something.
I told you to believe you didn't want to.
Someone do something.
Okay.
Now where's this clip of me magically saying a bad word?
Let me see it.
You got two waters left, huh?
10 seconds.
How do I make this?
This is, is it a medium?
This is a medium, strawberry and two mediums anyways.
Well, I, I don't want to, I don't want to lose.
I can't pause the game.
Cake and chocolate.
Let's go.
All right.
So what, what is this?
This is the clip they keep linking,
but I don't hear anything.
You only say baloney.
You're full of baloney.
This one goes hard by the way.
I didn't say anything.
I think you guys are, I think you just a little salty
that you actually lost.
Believers win.
I think there's no hard evidence here.
Jermis's bad word.
No, there's no spurs.
We're good.
Wait, you're doing it again?
Double or nothing?
No, I don't want to just,
I don't want to not be able to say a swear for an hour.
That's actually annoying.
And then it's pomegranate.
This one looks kind of tasty.
And then it's wafer cherry wafer.
Cool.
Right away.
How come there's no alarm on that one?
How come you can't swear for an hour?
Are you five?
It was just a fucking experiment.
I was reading chat.
How did I, whatever.
You're a paraffin charlatan.
Delete your Twitch.
What?
Here you go.
What's coming up next on the Twinsons Odyssey soundtrack?
Oh, good one.
Almost level nine?
Oh, yeah.
No, no, you're supposed to be bad at these.
You're supposed to be bad at these.
No, you're supposed to be bad at these.
Just wear the same outfit.
What's the music?
It's Twinsons Odyssey.
Little Big Adventure 2.
This is the longest I've ever played a Poppa's game for.
Without a doubt.
That looks pretty good.
Get rid of the toppings and you got a believer out of me.
Can you play Ghostbusters, like the Ghostbusters music?
You know what I used to do all the time?
I used to listen to Ghostbusters theme song remixes.
It was like one of my favorite things.
I would just listen to them.
If there's one thing,
the Ghostbusters theme song has like thousands
of unbelievable remixes.
Oh fuck.
Good thing nobody cares that I just said that.
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
What did I just do?
All right, we're fine.
Oh, should I put one on?
I think I'm gonna go find one.
How about Ghostbusters remix?
This one's probably good.
Find out.
Oh, whoa, let's go.
Did you fly us down?
What?
Whoa.
I'm saying, if there's a DJ doing this on stage,
I'm trying to take an order.
If a DJ was doing this on stage, I would be screaming.
I would be fucking screaming at this guy.
Like, yeah!
Yeah, you're the fucking man!
Yeah!
Yes!
I would be so pumped up about this.
You'd be able to hear me over the entire club.
This is wrong.
Good thing you, I don't even care.
Wait, which one is this?
Shit, sorry.
Dude, I'm gonna be dancing.
This is so bad.
All right, that was pretty sick.
All right, so what else we got?
There's a ton of these.
What is this one?
Ooh, sorry, I'm busy.
You guys need something?
Maybe don't even go faster.
Oh, that was cool.
What about another one?
Wait, let me finish this.
This and then that.
Okay, the medium.
And pink pomegranate is strawberry and this sauce.
Shoot, hold on, hold on.
People are begging for this.
Please, please, please.
We're begging, we're begging, we're begging,
we're begging, we're begging.
Well, you're gonna have to wait a second
because we're way overdue on this.
I'll play it, just wait.
I can't pause the workday.
Okay, this one is pink pomegranate.
This one, wait, what's going on?
Oh, it's this one.
Okay, I just wanna smell this stuff.
I don't even wanna eat it.
God damn it.
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna play this for like a minute.
This whole stream's gonna get copyright claimed.
Okay, this is classic.
Can you please draw a butt with the sauce?
Oh, you're in a sea of people
who are, you know what?
I'm gonna listen to that request.
This is the last one of the day, right?
Damn it.
Oh, there's another layer?
Oh, I didn't draw a butt.
How do I do this?
I can't draw.
Whatever, they got extra sauce.
I can't even, you can't draw a butt, guys.
I can't, let's, all right, let's go.
How about, oh, how about Just Dance 2014?
Ghostbusters.
There's so many versions of this song.
This isn't Just Dance.
I think this is, oh, this is just a regular one.
Here's a dubstep remix.
This one could be really good.
I don't remember.
I think it's this, oops.
Oh, oh, hell yeah.
What is he like?
Awesome.
How about the epic version?
Ooh, epic version, like Joel's?
Okay, after the epic version.
Dude, these are, they're all so different.
Here's another one.
The ghost, I ain't afraid of no ghost.
He no afraid, I ain't afraid of the ghost.
There's more?
This one is pretty, this one fucking slaps.
There is no main fridge.
Yeah, that was Joel.
That was Joel's version.
There's no milk in my fridge, so I get pissed?
Ghostbusters.
What was this one?
The game's frozen, right?
That was fucking awesome.
How about one more Ghostbusters theme remix,
and I swear, have we done?
I thought this video had over a billion views.
I was like, holy shit, I told you this was popular.
I thought this is over one billion views.
I was gonna say, some of those are me.
A billion.
Luigi's Mansion theme remix?
Woo, hold on.
Nice.
Ooh, new toppings.
Cupcake, is that like red velvet?
Oh, you only want a little spin.
Imagine calling an order here,
and you're hearing that in the background.
All right, I need to focus.
Ghostbusters theme on eight floppy drives.
Are you kidding me?
This is actually impressive, this is really impressive.
Someone explain to me how this person's room
is not smoking right now.
This one's large.
Wait, can I still, I didn't even put this one to order.
This person's an order.
Whatever, let's do this.
You want it regular, okay.
And what do you want, regular?
Good, this is, they bolt this way, good, okay.
What do you want?
That's pretty cool.
Okay, I need to remember which one's which.
This one is this one, this one is that one,
and this one has not been done yet.
This one's a medium, let's go ahead and get that started.
Doesn't matter, it does matter, throw it away.
They have an envelope, and this one is medium as well.
All right, let's go.
Chocolate whipped cream, this game's fun.
I mean, it's the same kind of stuff over and over again,
but it's fun.
Be overblended, not by very much.
All right, I gotta hurry up.
This thing's gonna be overblended.
No, we're good.
Okay, this one is this one, let's go.
Good, good, hurry up, hurry up.
Stop putting this shit in front of my order.
You idiots, I'm the only person that works here.
Okay, this is a medium, and this looks good.
Some pomegranate on there, cool.
All right, it matters where you put the cookies
and the fruit, yeah, I know, but I've very, ooh.
Is that spinning?
Wait, this is a critic, this has to be good.
Let's get this one out first, that's right, right?
Yep, all right, it was a large, good.
Brownie, everything has to be perfect.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can on this one, good.
Throw it away, no, throw it away, it's not good enough.
Gordon Ramsay is here right now.
That wasn't perfect, throw it away.
Why is it not perfect?
Okay, you wanna blend it all the way?
Play two trucks, oh my God, hold on, hold on a second.
Is strawberry whipped cream, strawberry sauce, pomegranate.
Pomegranate, and then it's wafer, cherry wafer, yep.
That was a good one.
This one has to be perfect, remember?
All right, let's go, that's pretty close to being perfect.
Fuck, actually, that was really loud, I'm sorry.
That's good enough.
Oh yeah, pizza tower.
Yeah!
Pizza tower, OST.
Two trucks, two trucks, you're good.
I'll do it after this.
I've been playing this game for three hours, how?
I'm just gonna chill in this school, all right.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Ooh, lime.
Yeah!
Ooh, a cat, can I get them all?
Yes!
All right, this outfit's gotta go, okay.
Jacket or no jacket?
Gum balls, chocolate syrup balls?
This matches the holiday, double points, ooh.
Really?
You ever gonna P-rank any of these levels?
No, no way.
I can just enjoy the fact that I loved this game.
It was very good, and that's it.
All right, I get double points.
Do two trucks, all right, I will, what, two trucks.
I will play your song, Two Trucks.
Two Trucks is about two trucks having sex.
Oh, is it not?
Two trucks having sex.
It is.
My muscles, my muscles involuntarily flex.
Two trucks having sex.
Two bigger trucks making love.
I screwed this up, hold on.
Anybody else?
That's pretty fucking sick.
We're back on?
We're just jumping around, we're shuffling around.
Two huge trucks.
Finish that song now.
Two trucks having sex.
I'm wasting time, okay.
Nope, any more?
Nope, beat this one up.
This one's very easy, it's a pretty good drizzle.
Nice.
Welcome new viewers.
Yeah, hi.
Are there new viewers here?
Two trucks.
The weird thing is that I'm a new viewer too.
Two trucks having sex.
Whatever.
This is a large, right?
Yeah.
Peanuts.
Good drizzle, good drizzle.
Pretty damn good drizzle.
That's a perfect.
Sick, all right.
That's a funny song.
It's a classic.
I want the pizza tower time song.
Where is it?
What's it called?
This is it, right?
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
This is one of the best soundtracks I think I've ever heard.
I think it just is.
I really think this is probably one of the best soundtracks
in any video game that's ever released.
That's true.
Every single song is fantastic.
I don't think this one's not good.
I got these flips by the way.
Is this, this is a different version though.
Where's the other version?
Where does it go into that version?
You got the other one in mod chat?
Yeah, yep, yep, yep.
This is it, this is it, let's go.
This is the one.
All right, we're gonna do this one here.
Medium.
Go faster, I'm trying.
Is this making me need to poop?
Well, that's, is that a bad thing?
It might be, it's making you more regular?
I don't know.
It's a medium, right?
Both chunky.
Go.
That placement was awful.
Did I get the order wrong?
No, I didn't.
Shoot.
Uh-oh.
Go, go, go, hurry up.
What?
What is this?
This is the wrong, why is there another one?
Who is this?
I'm going too fast.
Hurry, hurry before he, I'm going, I'm going.
Ah!
Okay.
I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't.
Sorry.
I'm a fucking porky pig over here.
But you just don't have to use any of this shit.
No!
I don't like these, it's fine.
Is that gonna do it?
I had it and it was gone, it was there.
And I just, I, you know what?
Let's fucking get funky.
What's this one?
That's a good one too.
That's a good one.
All right, after this order, after this day,
I'm gonna take a quick VRB.
We'll come back and we'll decide what's gonna happen then.
I'm kind of just enjoying hanging out and playing this.
I got another game I could move to, but we'll see.
I will tell you the time tomorrow.
The 90s commercials stream is going to be tomorrow afternoon.
It's not gonna be six o'clock.
I'm gonna start a little bit earlier.
Cause I know that, okay.
So do you use a grand charm that adds 11 to defense?
Oh no, not throw that away.
Sell that immediately.
Grand charm, 11 defense?
That's, no, that's not good.
You're looking for plus skills or resistance small charms
or plus a bunch to life small charms?
Just trying to help somebody out.
These are both largest, okay.
And what is in this one?
That's that one.
All right, this one is this.
What time tomorrow?
Probably around, somewhere around three or four Pacific.
Not six.
I'm gonna shoot for 4 p.m. Pacific.
I forgot everything that was just going on.
I'm talking.
I can't be talking.
I didn't even put the strawberry in this.
Okay, this is this one here.
This one is already over here.
New topping, whatever that is.
Atoms, electrons, like what the hell is this?
Nerds, okay.
Good, okay.
I need a medium with Mike and Ike's
and just another, whatever the vanilla I think it is.
Put that up there.
Banana butter is a medium.
Banana and, yep.
Okay, whipped cream, let's go.
I feel like I would really like the taste of these sauces.
I went to a 100 gecks concert and before the show
someone was playing your breath of the wild stream
on their phone.
What?
I didn't even select this.
Isn't that what I wanted?
It's banana and Reese's.
Invite some streamer friends over
and make smoothies like this for them.
What?
What's happening?
Okay, what is this?
This was this one?
What is this one?
This one here, okay.
Go on, hurry please.
Hurry up.
There we go.
That was $294, $22 tip.
What?
Okay.
I was impressed by your ability to not cuss.
Still in there.
Pop there.
Oh boy, that's a lot.
Okay.
This is whipped cream, chocolate and nuts.
What kind of whipped cream are?
It was nuts, right?
Yeah, of course, it's peanuts.
Free bananas.
Hey, can you play Cod Zombies with me?
I have to go to bed soon.
Sorry, I did medium.
Strawberry and pop.
Go off.
Why does this look incorrect?
Because it is.
Was it?
Was that wrong?
Wait, what's happening?
Was it correct?
Hey dude, can you shout out the New York Mets?
The New York Mets.
Let's hope that they do a good job this year.
Let's see some winning games.
You guys got it in ya.
Let's go New York Mets.
That was really sweet.
92.
Can you shout out the Yankees for me real quick?
Nah, that's not happening.
That's not happening.
I don't think so.
Ban that guy, actually.
Nah, nah, sorry.
That's not happening here.
Nice.
What about the Phillies?
Yeah, let's go Phillies.
Come on, Phillies.
Let's have like 10 games over 500 this year.
Here we go, Phillies.
Here we go.
Oh yeah.
What about the Minnesota Twins?
Let's go Twins.
Minnesota Twins.
All strikes, all strikes.
Let's go, go, go.
Strike them out here.
Nice, let's go Twins.
What about the Yankees?
Yeah, okay.
Yankees.
Fuck out of here.
Get out of here.
What about the Cubs?
Oh, my Cubs.
Of course.
Of course I will.
Don't ever say that again.
They're driving crazily, I'm not.
This person's trying to kill me.
Hey, don't forget who makes your Sundays.
Yeah.
Rick, whatever your name is.
You come in every day and get a Sunday.
You take me out, that's not gonna be a good idea.
Ooh, I like these.
I need more holiday spirit, right?
What holiday is this?
What holiday am I dressing up for?
It's the Fourth of July?
Wait, how did we already get back
to the Fourth of July again?
It's been a year?
It's been like 12 days.
Hell yeah.
I don't think I've ever had four on it one time,
but I'm gonna get it.
It's the other Fourth of July, oh.
This town is very patriotic.
All right, I'm gonna take a beer break.
We'll do a, I'll come back chilling.
See you guys in a minute.
I'm gonna go refill this drink.
I'm gonna go pee.
I'll be right back.
Hello.
How's it going?
So I think I might just stick with this.
There was something else that I was gonna play,
but I'm just, I'm having a good time.
We got House Flipper this weekend,
which I'm really looking forward to playing that.
90s ads tomorrow.
And I didn't realize I was streaming for four hours already.
We'll keep going.
Without music, this is ominous.
Did I do this?
No, I have a lot of upgrades now.
New customer.
Did I put on Club Penguin?
Club Penguin like music?
Did Club Penguin have a good OST?
I never played Club Penguin at all.
70 tracks of Club Penguin.
This is kind of nice.
Yeah, I've never played this.
This kind of fits this game too.
Oh, that's really cool.
I don't have to forward anymore.
Hello.
Okay, what came out first?
Club Penguin or World of Warcraft?
What came out first?
Did WoW come out first?
Interesting.
This is medium.
Do I have time?
Oh, no, I don't.
It's just toppings.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Get it out the door.
Was it a year before Club Penguin was 2005?
Yeah, cause WoW was 2004?
2003?
When was WoW?
Wait, there was a very early Club Penguin version
that might've been first.
I'm just trying to figure out if it was the...
I mean, EverQuest was a really popular MMO,
but was Club Penguin the first popular MMO?
How much more popular was Club Penguin than EverQuest?
I need a large.
Ultima Online was the first one,
but I mean like really popular.
World of Warcraft popped off.
I feel like Club Penguin popped off big time.
I'm talking to more than a million concurrent players.
Was EverQuest more than a million concurrent?
More than five million concurrent?
Probably RuneScape?
Oh, probably RuneScape, yeah.
All right, hold on.
This is this one.
I need that large cup, and then I need a medium.
Okay, beat this up, let's go.
Somebody at the door, right?
Okay, good.
Coconut, come on, hurry up.
That's good.
RuneScape always seemed like a really fun game,
but for some reason,
I always felt like it was a lot to take in.
I feel the same way about RuneScape
that I do about Path of Exile.
I see clips of it, I see people playing it,
and I see the UI, and I see all this shit going on.
I'm like, hey, this looks kind of,
is this complicated?
I don't know, I can't tell.
I know, I know.
Try to play RuneScape without the nostalgia.
RuneScape is pretty simple.
Does it remind you of Diablo?
That's why you want to play it?
No, it just always seemed kind of interesting.
Okay, we're closed.
Large, this is strawberry chocolate.
It's pretty scuffed, but it's all right.
It's medium.
Dude, do you even like video games?
I think so.
Prove that you do.
Um, hey, I got 150 kills in a row in the mercenary mode.
What is, that means I kind of like
playing video games, doesn't it?
I like some video games.
Beat Hades?
Yeah, whipped cream chocolate.
Play OSU.
I feel like I'd be really bad at that game.
I'm, that's a rhythm game, right?
Rhythm games I do very well,
but not if I have to go very, very, very fast.
Didn't even know this person was here.
Being good or bad is not the point.
It's about having fun.
That's right, I agree.
It's better if you're good.
Uh, it depends on the game.
But yeah, if you play Dark Souls
and you lose to the first four enemies 100 times,
then it can get kind of frustrating.
Like you, I did not, you are changing the record.
I thought I did a pretty good job on stream.
How many people do you think actually think
you died to Pinwheel?
Probably everybody, because why even,
well, why would you even argue that?
Why are we dressed exactly the same?
That's a weird thing to have to argue.
Oh, hey, dude, he died at Pinwheel.
He did?
Yeah.
Oh, let me research that.
No, you're probably just gonna go,
oh, he sucks, that's funny.
Actually watch the VOD, the collateral, it's propaganda.
He did actually die to Pinwheel.
Better get a new t-shirt for that one.
Nice.
Banana butter, berry blast.
Yep.
I just took a picture of my sandwich
because it looked so good.
Oh, that's cool.
That's cool.
Hazelnut swizzle?
Tiramisu?
I can surf tiramisu now.
You want a tiramisu in your, wait, what?
It seems kind of amazing.
Tiramisu, vanilla paste, whipped cream, and hazelnut.
That sounds awesome.
That sounds really good.
Still gonna do the courthouse stream?
No, that's a long, long time away from, that's gone.
Tiramisu?
That's how you say it, right?
I'm saying it, right?
This one's easy.
Where are you playing these now?
There is only one available on Steam at the moment.
This is Poppa's Freezeria Deluxe.
It's on Steam.
I don't know what their plans are for the other ones.
If they do have any plans, I don't know.
But this one is on Steam.
Got it perfect, yeah?
This one's gonna be done in a second.
All right, let's go.
Chocolate whipped cream.
You know what other games really,
here's another banger of a game.
Do you guys remember Hand of Fate?
That game is awesome.
I forgot how unbelievably good that game was.
I feel bad I didn't play it way more.
There's a second one, yeah.
This too?
All right, I don't know how to make a berry blast,
but we're gonna try in a second here.
Medium and it's blueberry, strawberry.
It was amazing.
I think the developers went out of business, really?
Did they really?
That's such a unique game.
That's a cookie, right?
I'd like to see you do a RuneScape stream one day.
Is RuneScape the kind of game where I would open it
and then like 1,000 people would follow me around
and kill me for like the two logs that I have?
Is that gonna happen?
Probably.
This is a strawberry, right?
Yep.
You would be protected.
They can't kill you, but they will follow you.
This is, what is this one?
Oh, okay, we're good.
That's berry blast.
This is tiramisu red velvet.
I made a character on RuneScape named Jerma Walken
and made it look like you a year ago.
This is a nice song.
This one's coming up.
Which one's easier?
Probably this one.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This one's harder because I don't know.
It's all right.
Cream, cream, cream.
What was it?
Cream, cream, cream, cream.
And it was just cream, cream.
And then nerds.
And then the wafer, cherry wafer.
It was the wrong cream.
This one.
I got it right.
Peanuts.
And then a cinnamon stick.
This is whipped cream, peanuts.
And a cherry, a coffee.
Are you ever gonna play Pirates of the Caribbean online?
Years ago, we did an MMO night
where we played a bunch of free MMOs.
And it was kind of a disaster.
It was like five years ago, a long time ago.
This many years later,
I wanna say that it would be way harder
to do a free MMO stream or free to play MMO stream.
I think back like five years ago or so,
or whatever it was,
I think there were like two or 3000 concurrent viewers here
and that it was already hard.
If I did that right now, I don't know if that would work.
It might be hard to do that now.
It was already hard to do that back then.
Shit.
Hold fast, hold fast was a lot of fun.
Sire, we must do something.
The enemy is playing copyrighted music at us.
That's a classic.
Really, how is that not going in?
Pizzel?
They're clowns?
You're gonna play Project Diva again?
I think I really got most of what I...
Played the hell out of that.
I did like every song three times.
What's your favorite Minecraft Steve copy?
Oh my God.
My brain only works in one fucking direction.
That person asked me what my favorite ice cream flavor
and topping was,
and then they did an emote of Minecraft Steve.
That's the only thing that I could see.
Whatever.
Dude, come on.
Why did I just do this twice?
Throw it away.
Throw this in the trash.
Shit.
It made me sound so strange.
Ooh, it's one of those cookies.
I like these.
Have you watched the new Resident Evil movie trailer?
No, because correct me if I'm wrong here,
but every Resident Evil movie,
all of them,
I feel like have been just,
like they're not even Resident Evil movies.
It's like an AI came up with the story
for what a Resident Evil movie might be.
And I'm not even,
I'm not talking like chat GPT three or four.
I'm talking like chat GPT one.
Whatever that technology was.
I have not paid attention to Resident Evil's movies
in at least a decade or two,
because they're all seem like kind of weird.
All right, there's people waiting.
Need a berry blast.
That's blueberry and strawberry.
They are fun garbage.
I just, I haven't even said,
I haven't had any interest in them at all.
Should I watch them?
I don't really have a,
I don't really,
there's a lot of movies I think that are gonna come
in front of that first,
if I'm honest.
Watch the CG movies,
not the live action ones.
Come on.
Perfect timing on this one.
On some of these,
I've got like a paragraph complaint here.
Mr. Elberson,
if you continue to anger the Steve Jackson
sorcery enjoyers high council,
your continuing animosity for sorcery angers us.
Do not comply,
there will be dire consequences.
You have two months, Mr. Elberson,
to do another stream of the hit adaptation
of the Choose Your Own Adventure book,
Steve Jackson's Sorcery,
created by Inkle Studios.
The consequences will be severe if you do not comply.
Sincerely, Steve Jackson sorcery enjoyer high council.
That's enough time.
I got two months.
Here.
It's not berry.
Oh, it's this one.
Oh.
What about Tears of the Kingdom?
I have to finish Breath of the Wild.
There's no world where I just start playing Tears
of the Kingdom when I have one more Guardian
to beat in Breath of the Wild.
You guys would never let me do that.
I would never let me do that.
Do you don't get to the last hour
of a movie that you've been watching?
Turn the movie off and just play the sequel instead.
Okay, this is pink, blue, red.
I haven't had a cotton candy flavored thing
in a very long time.
And I know exactly what it tastes like,
but I forget everything about it.
Anybody else here get like that?
Where you almost just want to be reminded
of a very specific flavor,
because cotton candy flavoring,
nothing else is like it on earth.
I don't know what concoction of weird chemicals it is,
but it is nothing on earth that it tastes like.
Only cotton candy flavoring.
Is it wrong?
Like sugar?
No, no, I'm talking cotton candy flavoring.
The fake cotton candy,
just like how there's fake banana
and it does not taste like a banana.
Bubblegum flavor, yep.
Now you guys get it.
I do like banana.
Banana cream pie is my favorite.
Oh, somebody wanted to ask what my favorite dessert was.
Did you?
I don't know, whatever.
Banana cream pie.
S'mores are probably one, two, and three.
What's the third one?
Banana cream pie.
I just tasted artificial cotton candy flavoring right now.
My brain just made me taste it.
Interesting.
Yeah, yep, that's exactly what it tastes like.
I can taste it right now.
My brain had to go file a bunch of hard drive stuff
and find it, but I can taste it.
Weirdly enough, I can taste the slush version.
Right now I can taste the slush version
of a cotton candy slush.
That's gross.
Why are you still playing this?
I don't know, we're just hanging out.
All right, I messed this one up last time.
Oh, wait, I can't bump into it from here.
I thought I could.
Oops, got it.
I didn't want to do that.
There you go.
I believe his lies, don't forget.
What are you doing?
I will play, I will play it.
I'll play sorcery.
Okay, you want this chunky.
Little too much chocolate though.
I need something to break that up.
Way too much.
Get this out quick.
Play Mega Man Legends 2.
Is this done?
It's not, what's, okay, why isn't it?
It is done.
I wonder why I didn't answer the phone.
I have not seen the Mario movie,
although I very much anticipate seeing it.
Berry Blast, I watched it today, it was epic.
You could be a bug, which one would you be?
What bug lives the longest?
Because any bug you pick is like,
you're dead in like fucking four days.
A cockroach that lives for, how long do they live for?
They live forever.
I don't think that's true.
He's so bad at this.
I have not had a single bad order in maybe three,
in four and a half hours.
I've had three bad orders across 200 or 300 orders.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Termite queens live 25 to 50 years.
Beetle grubs live in the ground for like 16 years.
Splendor beetle, one of the longest living insects
in the world.
An impressive lifespan that averages 31 years.
With the longest recorded lifespan reaching 51 years,
I would want to be a Splendor beetle.
Isn't red velvet just a made up flavor?
It's not actually anything.
It's just chocolate right now.
All right, I gotta go place these.
It's just beets and chocolate.
It's supposed to be a cake.
Yeah, all right, this one's large.
This one's the medium.
Okay, so now you need medium.
This is strawberry banana.
They're all medium.
All right, let's go.
Hold this one off.
Okay, what is that little thing here?
A mango or something?
Oh, come on.
Shit.
Oh, that was sloppy.
Everybody here is ordering these like it's a subway.
All right, what do you want on it?
I guess I'll take a banana peppers,
fucking an oregano.
I'll give him some oil, maybe some vinegar.
And maybe, you know what?
Put like extra lettuce on it, a tomato.
These orders are all fucked up.
What kind of cheese do you got?
Oh, no, I don't care.
Just put all of them on.
Just do one slice of every cheese.
What do I got?
Cherries?
Yeah, put one on.
Cookies too?
Yeah, fucking.
What are those things?
Put it on.
Banana peppers and ice cream.
I love banana peppers.
They're so good.
You thinking of Quiznos?
Quiznos.
Man, I heard sad tale about Quiznos.
Just, it's just unfortunate.
That place was unbelievably good.
Unbelievably good.
What the hell happened?
They made the best sandwiches.
No one can even come close.
Every other chain sub shop that I've ever been to,
it was so far behind.
Literally D and Cs to Quiznos' S.
No one even comes close.
I don't wanna hear anybody else.
I don't wanna hear any of the other restaurants.
Nope, they don't even come close.
Honey Bacon Club is the single best chain sandwich
I've ever had in my life.
And it's S plus and nothing is even on A.
There's nothing is even on A.
Some stuff is on B.
There's a lot of Bs.
B pluses, maybe some A minuses, but no.
You are capping out of your mind.
It was just as bad as Subway.
No, no, it was not.
No way, no way.
Quiznos was so good.
I'm just guessing.
It was barely different.
You didn't, no, no, you didn't even eat it.
I don't think you ate it.
You probably saw it being,
you probably saw like somebody walking around with it,
eating it.
You know what I mean?
Like the big tube.
You probably saw somebody eating a tube
and you're like, I don't know about that.
You didn't eat it.
Did you eat it?
I don't think you did.
I'm serious.
I feel like I love Quiznos and I don't love Subway.
They're very, very distinct for me.
Corporate fucked over all the ingredient providers.
Come on.
Really?
Double points?
I promise you I ate it.
Okay, all right.
I believe you.
They jacked up prices and forced stores
to buy from the suppliers.
Can't we just have good yummy sandwiches?
Like, you know what I'm saying?
Why can't we just have just delicious sandwiches?
Just buy a toaster oven, make them at home.
It's different though.
I am gonna make a statement here
and I know a lot of people agree with this.
It does not matter what the food is.
It doesn't matter how much I spend on it
and how much time I spend, how quality the,
I could buy the highest quality ingredients in the world.
I could go and get, oh, like delicious Wagyu beef.
Make a Wagyu beef burger on the grill at your house.
It is never as good as if somebody else makes it for me.
Always.
It is never as good.
I could follow a recipe to a tea, take a bite out of it
and go, this sucks.
I did something wrong.
When somebody else does the same thing
and makes it for me, right?
Whether it's a restaurant, it's always better.
It just always is better than me, way better than me.
And I've come to accept that.
Like you're just doing this way.
You just, you're doing something way better than I am.
So yeah, let's get this out.
I think it's because you're afraid of ovens.
You still cook with an oven.
I bet you like unsalted butter.
And it's appropriate places to use it.
It should be used.
How's this?
This is a weird combo.
All right, I still haven't made this large.
None of these are, okay, this one's done.
Is this the right one?
Oh, shut up.
We ran out of pink whipped cream.
Sorry.
Is there something wrong with unsalted butter?
I don't know what the hell, what's the deal?
Uh-oh, I'm starting to lose control here.
This is this one, I'm losing control.
Oh my goodness, I've lost control.
Strawberries, okay, hurry up.
Okay, hurry up.
Really not even that bad for having the wrong whipped cream.
I love food though.
I could be having a really bad day
and just a nice delicious meal.
Just changes everything, it really does.
Are you a good cook?
No.
I know how to make a few things.
That's it.
I can make a good fish.
I can make a good salmon in the oven.
I can make a good cod in the pan.
I like fish.
Fish sandwiches, pretty easy.
Egg salad, egg salad's not necessarily cooking
as much as it's putting something together.
I mean, I guess technically you are cooking something.
You cook the eggs.
You know what, I'm gonna own that.
Yeah, it's good.
My recipe is phenomenal.
Yeah, I'm gonna own that because it's good, it's true.
What is this thing?
Okay, I need sprinkles.
There's not been one bad review of that recipe, by the way.
Coconut, and there's been zero reviews.
There's been at least five or 10.
Peanuts and then double stick curry.
What's wrong with this?
Blend it too much?
Oh my God, scared of it.
What is this one?
This one doesn't, I don't even know what that,
okay, let's make two more.
This is banana.
Please try.
Did you get permission to leak the family egg recipe
or was it a Prometheus?
What's that reference to?
I don't know what that means.
There we go.
The reference to the Bible.
Sorry, I have not kept up with my Bible studies.
What is, it's a Prometheus is stole fire from the gods
and gave it to man.
He got punished for it.
I think he had to have his liver eaten
by a raven every day.
Well, that didn't happen.
Do you mean am I getting a lot of flack
from my family for leaking the recipe?
I think that's where you're going with that, right?
Ooh, that's a good one.
Hey, you do know that a secret family recipe
can start at any generation.
Who's to say it didn't start with me?
You think there's some great dear old great grandma
or grandpa that I got that from?
Who'd be starting here?
I am the great grandpa.
I am the secret recipe, you understand?
Gotta leave something, right?
I'm gonna take a bunch of pictures of me in chef outfits
just to make sure that this, you know,
they can look back and be like,
oh, great, great, great, great grandpa Jerma.
I mean, there's a lot of pictures of him in chef hats.
He must have been a chef of some kind.
Why would he take photos like this?
That's hard.
That one was really, really hard.
There's a ton of green screen footage of you.
That's fine.
That was in my younger years.
I'm gonna take these photos when I'm like 60.
Oh my goodness, what a disaster.
That was a nice song.
If I walked in and this is all here,
don't you think that the people that were working here
were moving?
They're like, oh, it's like this because they're moving soon.
This is pretty good Kickstarter music.
What do you mean?
Mr. Elberson, this is Steve Jackson's
Sorcery Enjoyers High Council.
That thing got removed in a second.
You can't post that more than once.
Although that doesn't get posted more than once.
I'm only gonna read that once.
It was different?
No, oh well.
You've asked this question like 30 times.
Do I eat sludge?
Well, that depends on your definition.
Is oatmeal sludge?
Let's break this down and talk about this.
And the answer is yes, then.
All right, speed this one up.
What about slop?
If sludge is oatmeal,
we're considering that oatmeal is like thicker.
Sludge to me is a little thicker.
Slop is runny.
What would be runny?
Chili?
Chili might fall more into the sludge category, I think.
I need this one.
And then three cones.
At least cones are like waffle.
What is this?
Chowder is kind of slop.
I could see that.
I could see how that, you could see that.
Cannoli?
There we are.
The oatmeal depends on consistency, yeah.
You know what I haven't had in a long time?
It's a good fish chowder.
Clam chowder, F.
Fish chowder, A+.
Corn chowder, B.
Clam chowder is an F for me.
Fish chowder is an S.
It's an A+.
I don't like clams.
I never was a fan of clams or oysters.
Anything in the shell, really, besides maybe crab.
Clams are too rubbery.
Yeah, I feel like, I don't like it.
It's too weird.
Clams are rubbery.
I don't, no, I don't like squid either, or octopus.
No, thanks.
If you're one of those people that goes,
hey, let's get a calamari for the table.
I always kind of feel like, fuck,
I'm not gonna eat any of that.
And people are gonna be, you're gonna be looking over,
hey, you want those, you want any pieces?
There's like five or six pieces of calamari left.
Like, no, you can eat it.
Well, I already had like seven or eight pieces.
I'm not, I wanna leave room for my entree.
Like, oh, oops.
I have eaten calamari before.
That was very, very, very, very good.
It was perfect.
But I've also eaten calamari before.
That made me want to never eat it ever again
for the rest of my life.
So I'm sorry, that's too much of a range for me.
It's just too much of a range.
Hey, hold on.
Dude, your stream really is a food podcast.
I could talk about food all day.
Don't be surprised if I like fucking retire
and I have like an old man food podcast.
Today, where I go and I tried this restaurant today
and it was called Spaghetti for Two or whatever.
And it was delicious.
And let me tell you what I ordered.
Would you watch that?
Would you listen to it?
I will say I was not a huge fan
of the crust of the bread.
The crust of the bread to me needs to be brown
on the underneath, but soft on the top.
And it was fucking disgusting that they didn't do that.
And I will never go back to this place ever again.
The tomato sauce was high quality.
Server didn't remember my name.
So they are obviously, I'm gonna have to give minus
a full star for that one.
Wait, that's wrong.
It's done.
What, it wasn't mixed enough?
Angry grumpy spoiled old man rants about food
and dies of a heart attack in the middle of the podcast.
That's like sad.
I don't wanna think about that.
I don't wanna have that thought in my head.
And when I went there, you don't understand.
I dropped my napkin on the ground
and it wasn't replaced within one minute.
I don't think I wanna live that life, right?
No, I don't know.
This person's wanted this Calypso coconut thing.
Should I go out there and just say,
hey, listen, I'm sorry.
I don't know how to make that.
I know you saw some like TikTok video of the secret menu,
but I don't know what the fuck this is.
Okay, I think I do know what it is.
There we go.
Remember you use TikTok?
No, I just pretend to to fit in.
I have to be like aware of it.
Come on.
Anybody else in line?
No.
All right, so it's blue coconut, blue sprinkles.
This thing does look really good though.
I would eat this one.
I've been really too timid with that.
That was almost a perfect four.
This one looks really good.
That's my best one yet, I think.
What about deep dish pizza?
I like a thinner crust.
Deep dish pizza to me is a lasagna.
Lasagna is delicious.
Deep dish pizza is delicious,
but I prefer a thinner crust.
If you could preserve any existing food menu items
so that it would be available forever,
what would you pick?
Cheese agridita crunch from Taco Bell.
The aliens would have to eat that at some point.
You know how a lot of times I'm a little bit older
and maybe some of you are also in this after 30
or even if you're in your mid to late 20s.
You know there's that food item that you look back,
oh my God, all the nostalgia videos of,
imagine if this was still a thing.
I am so glad that the cheesy agridita crunch
from when I was like 13 to all the way to now,
it's been the exact same.
I'm so happy that I don't have to think
about where that went.
That is one of those items
that if it was gone 10 years ago,
I would be desperately talking
about how much I wish I could eat one,
but I don't have to think like that
because it's available and I'm gonna fail this one.
Good luck, excuse me.
I almost have it, come on man.
There's not enough fucking time to do this.
I got it, okay good.
Calm down with the come on mans.
Am I doing that a lot?
Do I say come on man a lot?
A and B button.
Oh, this is all the customers.
Who have I served the most?
I feel like I've served way more than this.
Maybe not, okay.
I wanna get this hat off.
Willy Wonka chocolate factory.
Willy Wonka wear purple.
The Willy Wonka stream is something else
I really wish I was able to do at some point.
It would have been so much fun.
There's still time.
Yeah, but I really, you know,
you're talking like you can't do it now.
No, but no.
Did I do this one right?
What a health and safety nightmare.
Well, all right, let me,
okay, let me be realistic.
A lot of times I'll come up with something that I wanna do
and then realize to do it right
will be hundreds of thousands of dollars.
So I go, oh, okay, that sounds fun.
How do I do that?
How do I be able to like afford that
and not lose everything?
Oh, and also stuff like that.
I think the reason why a lot of you like the kind of show
in quote streams or the event type streams
is because I'm doing those when I really want to.
And it's like, I am super excited.
I'm super passionate about it.
I wanna go for it as hard as I can.
I think that's probably why
is they don't have to happen all the time.
It's not something, oh, wow, I can't like every 30 days,
there's gotta be something fucking crazy.
I wanna steer away from that
because I feel like over the last year,
I've really tried to do that.
And you're watching right now,
I think part of the stream that I was maybe missing
for me at least.
Just make the smoothies, man, it's all right.
You should do whatever makes you happy.
This makes me happy right now.
And who knows, I don't know.
There are other things that are making me really happy.
Obviously the Grotto Beast project is a lot of work
and a lot of time went into that.
There's a lot of things to still show.
So that's really exciting.
But I gotta be all in, I have to be all in.
And I definitely think it's best to pull back.
This is correct, right?
No, it's not, throw it away.
I didn't even start that, wait, what is this one?
Oh shit, hold on, this one's easy.
Really like these no cam chill streams.
Yeah, so do I.
So do I.
We have elementary school dork taste in games.
This is, isn't this like half of everybody in this chat's
like favorite, one of like favorite Flash series?
I thought I was being a pleaser today.
Okay, is this one?
This is still Club Penguin, this is great.
This is very inoffensive music.
It just feels good to play it.
Just hanging out in the background.
All right, I need two mediums.
Strawberry and then strawberry lemonade.
This is Wii Sports music, it kind of is.
All right, it's cake, cake and blue.
You thought about doing some more small scale stuff?
Yes, you'll see.
The answer to that question is yes.
Cause I gotta be careful.
I can get really, really into stuff
and then be like, wow, I just only wanna do that.
And then I could get myself into a lot of trouble
if I don't be careful with that.
There we go.
But when I say trouble, I mean,
doing a bunch of streams that are big, big, big, bigger,
it's gotta be bigger, it's gotta be crazier,
it's gotta be even more ridiculous.
I mean, I'll just start blowing money left and right.
And sponsors can help, but it's never,
I obviously wanna make sure that,
is this the, did I do this wrong?
No, this is correct.
Have you lost passion over the years for streaming?
No, I don't think that's true.
I think, cause I've been doing it for long enough
that I can kind of cyclically go through different phases
and keep myself interested.
So that, I mean, that's really important.
What, oh, sprinkles, coconut, and then that.
This dude can't remember a color from more than two seconds.
No, I can't, it's true.
Level 13, yes.
What about Toontown?
I was gonna play Toontown a while ago, just never did.
There was a reason why it didn't, I forget what it was.
No, you would crash Toontown so bad.
Maybe the end, maybe that is what happened.
Do you ever get burnt out?
Um, yeah.
That's a hard one to answer because I,
I know the joke here is that I don't stream that often,
but that's very specifically to make sure
that does not happen.
What was that?
Like I, sometimes I might just disappear
for like four or five straight days.
That happens pretty frequently here.
Get out of the way.
How is this fair?
There's been no coins on the bottom or top
and they've been hogging the middle.
When are you gonna finally retire?
I will tell you, retirement on this channel
is gonna be soft.
It would be a soft retirement.
And what does that mean by soft retirement?
That means I'm not gonna stop.
I don't think I ever will be able to.
Cryptic Andy?
No, I'm just saying like,
it's not gonna be a case where it's like,
oh, by the way, I am retired.
Twitch is deleted, YouTube is deleted,
and my Twitter's gone and you never hear,
I literally never, you don't hear from me ever again.
You should transition to Battletoads.
Battletoads is sick.
That's not a bad idea.
No, I'm such a fucking clown.
It would be embarrassing
because I would be like, oh, I'm retired.
And then like a month later,
Durba is coming out of retirement to do this.
No, we'll call it a soft retirement whenever that is.
I gotta have my food podcast eventually.
Come on.
Did I do this one wrong?
Is it the wrong size?
No, that's good.
Will we know when the soft retirement has started?
Oh yeah, absolutely.
I wouldn't keep you guys completely in the dark over that.
That'd be weird.
We got a new ingredient.
Oh, Pog.
It's crispy dots, whatever they are.
Monthly retirement conversation?
That's not true.
We have not talked about this
in probably at least four to six months.
That's not true.
Thoughts on Dippin' Dots ice cream of the future.
S plus.
The first time I ate Dippin' Dots, I was a kid,
and I think my eyes were gonna bug out of my head.
It was one of the greatest experiences of my entire life.
If there was a video camera back then,
and like my mother took,
or like my parents took a video of me
eating Dippin' Dots for the first time,
it probably would be a meme right now.
A decade, two decades, three decades later.
It'd be one of those like,
look at this little kid does something really funny.
Okay, I need a large and medium.
Chocolate.
You lied about watching Mob Psycho 100.
Oh shit, somebody actually remembered that.
When's your birthday?
The Dippin' Dots kid finally plays Papa's Freezeria.
That's me.
The Dippin' Dots kid.
All of my merchandise would have to be like that picture
or that screenshot of my reaction to eating the Dippin' Dots
at all the conventions
that everyone would want me to do the face.
Like do the brain freeze face.
Dippin' Dots tier list.
I don't, can you even buy Dippin' Dots?
Do they even?
To me, Dippin' Dots are in a machine in a mall.
There's no story, where do you get them?
All right, what do I gotta say?
What's this?
This one here.
Get them online and deliver them?
How do they, is it packaged in like a freezer?
How do they make sure it gets there?
It's still being perfect.
But yeah, this is not just something you get
on an amusement park or at a mall.
They ship with dry ice.
Really?
They have a system.
You think they're amateurs or something?
I mean, you don't create ice cream like that
and not know kind of what's going on.
The Dippin' Dots CEO could run for president.
And I'd be like, all right.
All right, I think he understands.
I think he understands.
This guy can lead us or whoever they are.
Dippin' Dots C, weekly Dippin' Dots rant.
This is the first time I've ever spoke about this.
You're delusional, dude.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
When you tell him to use the gumball machine?
Oh, fuck, I have to play.
The best thing about Dippin' Dots
was being at an amusement park, it was.
And you could just see the air coming off of it.
Whatever it was, CO2, nitrogen.
I don't even know what it is.
But when they take that shit out of the container,
they do the big scoop, big scoop,
and they hand it to you.
And this thing is smoking.
Ah, you can't replace that.
Join me for another amazing afternoon
called Grandpa Jeremy's Sweets and Treats.
This episode, we're gonna be talking about ice cream
and how delicious it is.
And when I was younger, different experiences I had.
One time I wanted.
Yeah, it's gonna happen eventually.
This is fun.
You got two orders.
I know, I'm going.
And make sure to get my cookbook.
Eggs and such.
It's four pages long.
It's my secret recipe for,
I don't fucking remember.
And then there's a big forward by me telling you
that they're really happy that you downloaded their book.
And then my favorite songs are on the last one.
Only two recipes in the book.
We're gonna try egg flavored Dippin' Dots today.
And they are fucking disgusting.
Oh no, I better be careful.
Then that channel turns into like,
like cinnamon challenges and stuff.
Uh oh.
Today on Food Sweet Treats with Grandpa.
I'm gonna eat the one chip hot fucking chip challenge today.
Oh, oh no.
Somebody said, bro, why are people tipping you
this much for ice cream?
I don't know, they're being like generous.
I don't know.
How much are they tipping?
It's like a few bucks, five bucks.
You're doing body language with the camera off, aren't you?
I mean, yeah, cause I'm talking
and people talk and they move their arms.
$13 tip, that's a pretty, that's a pretty good tip.
$13 bucks.
How much are you, what are we selling these for?
That guy loves ice cream.
Nice.
Have you played this for five hours?
This game's a classic.
And I don't know, we've just been talking,
chilling out, talking.
Well, I've been talking.
You've been listening.
Don't ever mistake that.
Why did I do that?
I was like aiming over there.
There's way too much stuff in this restaurant.
All right, let's do one more night, one more day.
And then I'll probably call it there.
I wanna get some food.
Ooh, new topping.
I'll be back tomorrow, don't worry.
We're starting earlier tomorrow anyways.
It's good.
What are we doing tomorrow?
We are watching old 90s commercials.
And then on Sunday,
we're gonna play the House Flipper DLC, Farm DLC.
Very interested.
Yeah, we got some fun stuff to do.
Chocolate and cherry.
Can you see how tall the whipped cream can go?
Yeah, before I, I'll go and mess around in the other boat.
I have plenty more ingredients now.
This is, ready?
Oh, almost.
What is this stuff here?
Cherry sauce or something?
Blood.
There's a five-star customer now.
I've got at least three or four five-star customers.
Can you do a doy doy doy?
We've been good, yep.
Doy, doy, doy, doy, doy, doy.
I can't do it anymore.
I can do it a little bit.
I used to be disgusting at the doy doy doy.
Other people have tried to match me doing it,
but it's just, no one could even come close back in the day.
That's probably what I'm most known for.
Oh no, I'm definitely most known for burp puking
and swallowing it.
That was like my claim to fame from like five years ago.
Okay, this shit is not even right.
Oh, I remember when I got called out so bad.
There was a point a few years ago where somebody said,
hey dude, you know you keep doing the like,
I'm gonna puke and then swallow it thing?
And I was like, no way.
I've done it once.
And I think they came with receipts
and they were like five different times that I did it
over the course of like six months.
It was a thing that I did all the time, apparently.
Hey, I was pretty good at it.
Coconut, still another order.
I was mixed for way too long.
Hey, how often do you actually puke?
I haven't, I mean, this is kind of a gross conversation,
throw that away.
It's been a pretty long time.
I actually don't remember.
Well, that's not true.
I remember Holly and I went out one night
and we ate a bunch of pizza.
This is recent and we got an Uber home.
It was like, I feel like it was the way
that the pizza was settled
and the way the car was being driven.
And I was like, I don't feel good.
And I puked.
Yeah, no, that happened.
No, no, not in, no, no, no.
This is like well after like,
this is well after being out of the car.
Not in the car, no, well after,
at least I'd say at least 15 to 20 minutes later.
It was like the pizza just was sitting so strangely
and I don't know, something about being,
maybe I got like a little car sick or something.
Is that, that can happen to me sometimes
depending on where I am in the car.
No, I didn't puke in an Uber.
Guys, what are you talking about?
I puked like an hour later after being out of the car.
Before that, it was probably like 10 to 15 years.
Dude, what the, I'm not gonna let you tell me.
Didn't you say 20 minutes?
I don't know how fucking long it was.
It was at least 20 minutes.
Where are the customers?
Wait, hold on, whose order do I have?
Whose order is this?
There ain't nobody here.
Who am I making this for, me?
I gotta hurry this up, they've been gone.
No one wants to eat your moldy ice cream.
I don't know, I don't know how many times I've puked, okay?
Hey, probably a few in the last 10 years.
Maybe like three.
Hey, how about this, how many times have you puked?
What was the last time you puked, huh?
How many times have you puked in the last year?
Two years, five years.
I'm gonna flip it on you now.
Sometimes you just kind of feel like shit,
and sometimes you puke, whatever.
Hey, maybe every few years or something.
Something like that happens that often.
Couple of months ago I did, I ate a full pizza.
That's what I'm saying, I had like pizza
and it was like settling wrong with me.
Settled wrong.
Oh shit, well that's 75 points.
I actually like this comment a lot.
Imagine throwing up, wait, I gotta read it.
It was like about like being adult or something,
hold on, it was funny.
Where is it?
Where is it, it was funny.
Come on, I can't find it.
I don't know what the message was.
It was like, oh, imagine you throwing up,
like being an adult.
Yeah, imagine throwing up, you're an adult.
All right, if that's a true statement,
this is coming from somebody that's probably never had
one of those 24 hour bugs,
where you are puking and shitting every 15 minutes.
And I'm sorry, but I'm actually really happy
that you've never had to experience that before.
I'm actually really glad
that you've never had to deal with that.
That's actually great.
I hope you never have to.
I have had to deal with that before and it is not fun.
You're an adult, I love that.
I don't eat poisonous food.
You don't know what you, what?
It's not, they're jealous, dude.
I don't know if you'd be jealous of somebody throwing up
and like shitting their pants.
I didn't shit my pants.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
So you shit your pants in an Uber.
You guys, I swear to God.
Imagine walking into a restaurant
and the cashier is just straight up rambling
about all the times he puked.
I'm gonna shit your pants.
All right, I feel like we should,
all right, I feel like you should time that person
out for five minutes.
Right, that's like five minutes, right?
I guess you should be timed up for two minutes.
You're gonna puke in your Uber.
Oh my God.
Hey, how about, don't be an asshole to Uber drivers.
They gotta deal with enough bullshit as it is.
Am I the asshole?
Please don't shit in my pants.
All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
This is fun.
I like this.
This is a good time.
I'm gonna watch some ads tomorrow.
That's the plan.
Starting somewhere around 4 p.m. Pacific,
a couple hours earlier.
Tomorrow, probably not gonna be a long one tomorrow.
Maybe a few hours.
I feel like there's only a certain amount
of those videos that we can handle.
But Sunday we will do a big meaty one
because of House Flipper.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
Club Penguin Sound Effects has been going for two hours
and I'm not even upset about it.
Is this saved?
I think so, right?
Yep.
Thanks for sticking around.
See you tomorrow.
If you're gonna show up tomorrow,
I would highly suggest you do if you have time.
I feel like tomorrow will be a really fun stream.
Those ad streams are really actually some of my favorites.
What time tomorrow?
4 p.m. Pacific is when I'm gonna start.
We'll get some decent compilations going.
See you soon.
Can you do a sober stream tomorrow?
Yes.
But yeah, take care.
Call your mother.
Have a great evening.
It's really late for a lot of you.
Late night, Andy.
See you soon.
Ta ta.