I'm gonna play actual spy and like try to be spy.
Okay. And I'm gonna bake-stab this guy. What?
Oh, what was that? You wanna get bake-stabbed? Bake-stabbed?
You wanna get bake-stabbed? Is that what you want? What about you, Heavy? I don't want that.
You wanna get friggin' bake-stabbed? I don't. I don't.
Got him. Got him. 80. 80, 80. Got him. Okay, jump.
80, 80, 80, 80. Bake-stabbed that guy. I'm a soldier on your team.
Just come out. Yeah, heal me. Let's go. Vaccinate an uber charge, baby. Let's do it.
Oh, what a mistake.
I got him both. What a blunder.
I feel so bad. I hate when stuff like that happens to me.
You're in there. I'm helping the team. I picked medic. Yeah, you just feel like so awful.
Let's get on this cot, guys. Come on. Get on. Somebody get on this cot.
Anybody. Anybody come on the cot with me. I'm a soldier. They're not doing so
peachy keen. Oh, is it? Hey, you got out. Heavy got out.
I got out. Man, a sniper. Anybody else? Oh, the same medic.
Heal me, dude. Come on. Oh, dude, get the mini sentry. I need your love. Oh, Mike.
Oh. Oh, that was not fun. Oh, I don't have enough. Come on,
cloak. Hey. You're like, you're not a spy.
Guys are standing on the inside of their spawn, disguised as somebody on our team.
I am your friend. Yeah, for instance, this guy is a spy.
For instance, you want to get backstabbed? What do you want?
Oh, that guy didn't want to get backstabbed. Come on, get out of my way, soldier.
I don't want to let you to hear me. And no, no, no.
Don't kill me. I'm just like somebody on your team spy.
What the hell was that? What was he doing?
I'll just stand really still. What the hell?
All right, well. Oh, God.
That was unfair. If I've ever seen a crit rocket, that was unfair.
That was up there. Come on, we got to, like, snipe them.
I'm going to let them crouching. I'm sniping. I'll lure them out here.
I'll just, like, they'll come see me. And there's so many snipers in there.
Yeah, I'm one of them. I'm almost out of ammo.
Come on. Am I trying to? Yeah.
Don't kill me. Get up.
Well, that guy knew.
Um, now what? Sap Mini Sentry, please.
What is this guy? What are these guys doing?
I don't know. What is going on right now?
What the hell is going on? Should we switch teams?
I don't think we can. Dude.
All right, let's just go. Can we go on the other team?
I wish. I would. I'm just going to stand out here as the spy.
I'm not even going to disguise. Oh, turn around.
There's so many people out here now. Oh, OK.
I think they got killed, though. Never mind. Never mind.
Is that a spy? No.
Oh, my goodness gracious. I spent way too long taunting that guy.
I should have just shot him. He had no help.
Do you think this is a game? Oh, I'm joining blue.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it. Can we go?
One minute left. I want to join, too.
Got to turn the tide. You see me? Show me mercy.
Or don't. I want to join the other team. I want to get to the first point.
All right, get to the first point. I dare you.
What on earth? I want to extend this like horrible, horrible match.
Good one. I mean, if there wasn't three snipers in a line in our spawn,
I think we'd be in a pretty good spot. I want to switch.
I want to play, too. I want to go on the other team and try and win.
You can't. I know. I really can't.
Oh, my God. Where'd that heavy come from? He had to have been invisible.
Invisible. Hey, it's like half invisible and half invulnerable
and half free to be an American. Screw you.
I knew that was you. It was like, who else would do this?
Oh, I still can't switch. Oh, I can't do it.
There's just so many people walking at me and you hopping around on rooftops.
I was playing Fiddler on the roof. I don't know why I had to kill you,
but I had to kill you. I think we might get the point.
I'm going to make sure that doesn't happen. Here we go.
Not going to happen. No, no, you ruined.
You really did. You were the only person behind.
It's the only person I had to turn around for. It's like right there.
Oh, who's this living room sad asshole? Who the hell is that guy?
I was like, I was on blue. Suck. We lost.