Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Huntsman Sniper with the Huntsman, the Jurati, and the Bushwhacker.
So before the video gets started, I want to make this pretty clear. My backpack giveaway is officially over. I have all the people selected, all the people have been picked.
And if you have not responded to my YouTube PM yet, please go and check right now. Your YouTube PM is your inbox, and it's private message or personal message I think actually is what it is under.
But if you have not responded to me, I'm gonna have to re-roll you again. So just keep your eyes, all of you guys, on your YouTube private messages within the next day or two, because I might have to re-roll another one, maybe two people.
Also, I want to bring up something about YouTube and how things are changing around here on the site, and it can be pretty frustrating. I know guys, a lot of us are in the experimental phase with this new homepage and channel designs and all that stuff.
And I want to ask you guys first off the bat, have you guys been even seeing a lot of my videos in your subscription feed? And if you have not, then I do apologize about that, but there is really nothing I can do about that at this point.
And the only thing you can really do to make sure you do not miss any of my videos is really just go to my channel page. And the same thing can be said if you have other subscriptions that you enjoy, just head to their channel page.
Because until we get through this YouTube experimental phase like they do sometimes, it's really the only way to see new content if you're not getting videos in your feed.
Also, another way to do it is if you just check the description of this video, there's going to be two links there to my last two recent uploads.
So that is another way. That's going to be there for every single video. So that's another way you can check and see if you've missed an upload.
But we will get off of that topic now. I just wanted to throw that out there and tell you guys that we're all in this together with YouTube's crazy changes that they do, and we will see how it goes from here.
But now let's talk about the video, talk about the topic at hand, and it's going to have to do with the Huntsman Sniper.
It's going to have to do with how to go against a Huntsman Sniper and how to avoid getting hit in the face by a Huntsman Sniper.
And it's being unpredictable. It's unpredictability. That's not even a word, but I'm going to make it up right now. Unpredictability is the topic of this video.
And more so a general tip for Team Fortress 2, it's never stand still or never move in a straight line.
Those are the two most important things to not get your head blown off by any of the projectile classes in this game.
I'm talking about Soldier, I'm talking about Demoman, Huntsman Sniper, Medic with the Syringe Gun.
Anybody that has a projectile, a living, breathing projectile in the server is banking on the fact that they can predict where you are going to go.
And if they are correct, you're dead. And that's the way it goes.
So trying to fight other classes that have projectiles, especially the Huntsman, is really the whole fight you're going to have in this game.
Especially going up against people that know what you're doing.
So number one, most important, this is the most important thing, do not stand still.
I mentioned it earlier, we're going to talk about specifics here.
If you stand still in this game, in a fight, let's say you're in the middle of bad water and the carts turn in the corner and there's a bunch of crap going on.
If you stand still for more than three seconds, you're probably going to die.
You're going to get headshot from a sniper, you're going to get backstabbed by a spy, you're just free meat for a spy.
You're going to get a projectile coming over the corner, you're going to get a Demoman hitting you in the face.
If you stand still, you're dead. So make sure, unless you're answering a phone call from somebody or you're typing to somebody, try not to stand still.
It's going to be detrimental to your health if you stand still.
So secondly, let's talk about something else that's very, very important, and that is being unpredictable.
And going from point A to point B, how do you fool somebody so you don't just walk right into a rocket?
Because guys, something you've got to remember, this game's been out for a very, very long time.
So if you are new to the game or you're not good at the game or you're trying to get better at it,
there are people that have been playing since 2007 that know every calculation of how fast you're going and how fast their weapon moves to be able to destroy you.
So how you go about doing this is actually quite simple, and it has to do with the A and the D key.
Your A, D key, not W, not S, A and D.
So what happens here is let's say you're up in a fight against a soldier and you're looking straight at him and he's shooting at you.
If you walk straight at him, you're dead.
If you hold down A, he's going to try and shoot over where you're moving.
Right when you think he's going to shoot, hold down D instead and he's going to completely miss you.
That's the one thing about projectiles, you can miss by a lot and potentially do no damage to your target,
especially with something like the syringe gun or something like the huntsman, especially the huntsman.
Because it takes a few seconds for a huntsman sniper to get another shot ready.
So when they cock back their arms like that and they slow down, you need to be ready to move.
You can't be moving in the same spot because they will predict where you're going.
And just kind of slightly hitting the A, D, D, A, D, try to make them think that you're going one direction.
When you really are not going to go that way, you're going to go the other direction.
Now this does not mean that every single encounter you get into, you should be mashing A and D as hard as you can, as fast as you can.
You probably shouldn't do that. You look pretty weird if you did.
It would look like your computer is glitching out, so don't do that.
But the purpose of this video is to get you into the thought process of playing mind tricks on people.
And it doesn't happen overnight. These are things that take a while to learn.
I mentioned earlier that a lot of people have been playing Team Fortress 2 for almost five or six years.
I still learn stuff about this game and I've been playing since the beta.
So every day when I play Team Fortress, I figure something else out that I didn't know before.
And it's all about trial and error and just learning, guys.
So that's going to wrap up the video.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.