I've returned. Let's see if this'll stay on and if it'll work. Meme incoming. Where's
Otto? He's lying down. Downstairs. Just hanging out. I said hello to him. I said hi to him
for you guys. As well. Said hey, chat says hi. Wagged his tail a little bit. Gave him
a pat. So I just tried to load up into a online just random deathmatch mission to
see what happened. Well, if it's having problems for people now, what the hell is gonna happen
when they open it up tomorrow or the next day to potentially 100 to 200 percent more people?
I don't know. Is the GTA 5 launch all over again? Only 25 percent of those people
we actually be able to play. Yeah, I don't think, I mean, unless it's a regional thing.
Those of you guys that are having problems, what region are you in? If you're seeing the
same disconnect every 10 minutes, every 20 minutes thing, are you West Coast? Or does
it, does it even matter? West Elizabeth. All right. Well, I'm in. I'm currently in
and there are players here, right? There are. There are players. So this is, if the hat fits,
it's right here. Let's see if I can get it to work. Let's see if I can play a mission.
Just send me a shitty horse. That's fine. Never do it for free. Level eight stamina.
What's the highest stamina you can have? Go fast, go fast, go fast. The faster I've gone,
the actually the more I've been able to connect. Hyenas, watch out. This, yes,
this is online. We are now in online. How long we will be here is the real question.
Howdy. Start matchmaking. Get us in the game. If this horse goes under 45 miles per hour,
we're all dead. When do you get the ability to sell pelts? Look at that character.
Okay, game details. Oh, horribly directed towards the Blackwater police chief in
Pike's Basin. Con man and outlaws on the loose. Where the justice is done will depend
on your honor. Let's go. So we, we're gonna try to take this guy alive as a crew here.
You're an ambassador. A what? An idiot. I'm sorry. He said he wouldn't run away. Shut up.
But please. But just shut up. I don't think you can. They're gonna fire me.
Oh, you, you get to keep your job, but they'll fire me and they've got every right to fire me
because I'm the idiot who employed you. Oh, look, guests. Skip 103.
You can't be any worse than us because this idiot, this idiot right here, just let the
most notorious con man in the whole goddamn state walk clean out of a cell, clean out
and not a shot fired. Now you get him back for us. We'll happily pay you.
Are you with the same players earlier? I don't think so. How about that? That'd be very odd.
Good, good. Now see what I figure is I figure he's headed on down to Pike's Basin.
So you go down the canyon and you get it almost over and I'm gonna beat this poor dumb
bastard with a stick. I just didn't skip into the very beginning, but
if you're gonna sit through the movie, you're gonna get up right before the big reveal happens.
All right, go to camp. Oh, I took, we're taking all the wrong horses.
Nice musical chairs. All right, we're good. We get two lives. Track this guy down.
Watch it. Easy, easy. The gang is protecting the outlaw. Take them out. Sorry, sorry. Explosion.
Watch this. Ready? I'm the cool one. Okay, a couple more left. Okay. Have I been shooting
the rock the whole time? Someone's coming up. Hold them there. Just shoot the fucking rock.
I'm gonna get low score. No, I'm not. Go get the outlaw. No, don't stop. Don't, no.
Lose all of our lives. Okay. Well, it's gonna, we'll leave this up to you.
You just go get the outlaw. What are you doing? Where's the outlaw?
Okay, we're so stupid. This is not how this is supposed to be done.
Hog tie the outlaw. How are we gonna get him back up? Anybody have a horse?
Okay, let's go. Deliver the outlaw in one piece. What just happened? Oh no. Oh, this is not good.
All right, you guys gotta protect me. Protect me. Protect me. I'm the guy with the outlaw on my
back. We can't die. Dying is bad. Up there. On the cliff too. I think we have to just,
we have to get out of here. We have to leave. That's it, right? No, I need a horse.
All right, I'll take care of the outlaw. You guys just keep me,
you're on my horse. That's my horse. I love this how all over the place this happens every time.
All right, let's go. Just have to deliver him and he's gonna be alive. We're gonna get a good
bounty for it. Just watch. Yep, I knew it was gonna happen. What just happened? You can't
whistle for your horse right now. Guy to your left. Horse, get over here. Oh no, no, no,
he's gonna die. Get him up. Revive him before we lose. Okay, there we go. Epic teamwork.
Are we good? Good guy, Jerma. Oh, what you mean to say is team lives one. More explosions.
Explosions. Now, this mission's been fun. This is a cool one. I can totally see me doing
with, with like star, you know what I mean? Italic, Vinny. Yeah, once this is more stable,
this would be fun to have like three or four people. I would definitely do this again.
Instead of being like a QA tester, I'd like to get into it. Who are the current teammates?
Uh, yeah, just a couple of other YouTubers. You know, I gotta hit the explosion. See off
the gang. See off. That's it. All right, we need a horse. Drop the outlaw by the camp.
Why are we doing it like this? Let me go. Let me go. I've got money. I've got a lot of money
and I'll pay. I'll pay a lot. Hey, here's an idea. Take my hat. Put it on the dead guy
over there. You take him in as me. I go free and you get rich. Oh, and I won't kill
anybody else. I swear I'm reformed. I'm a changed man. I'm reformed. I'm better. Please,
please. I'm begging you. Set me free. Have a heart. Do we have to vote on this?
Refuse offer. Oh my god. Take offer or let the timer expire. Refu- I got it. I got majority.
I got majority. I really would like his hat. Sean's back. It's a pretty ugly hat
anyways. It kind of, yeah, it is. It is a really ugly hat, but is the material it's made out of
expensive? It could very well be. I probably shouldn't do that again. Don't stop in front
of me. Did she just fall off? Grandma got DC'd.
Excuse me. Feed the ho- yeah, this guy does look really good. It is a gorgeous guy. Cried
into a rock. Not after how long that took. Take him in. I could have just jumped to horse.
So you got him? Seven dollars. Real good. Look. Put him up on my horse there. I didn't do nothing.
There's the money I promised you. It's nice seeing you again, buddy. Seven dollars. That's enough for me to
take a ride to Blackwater. Just name your price and I'll make you rich.
See you later. I made the money back that I wasted on the horse, yeah? I did.
Free hat? No, we didn't get the hat. You get the hat if you let him live.
No, you don't turn him in. Hey, I got to play Red Dead Online for 30 minutes.
And we're still here? Yeah, don't jinx it. We'll see. No, we're still here.
Alright. What was that? Snake? Whoa, that's a perfect rattlesnake. How do I
not destroy the meat here? Once was good. I was scared. It costs money to just be alive in this
game. Does this person hide in the cactuses? Don't remind me. Just existing. Can I interact
with them? I just disconnected him. Oh no, I just made that guy DC.
Right now he's probably sitting in his room. What the fuck? I just DC'd again.
Why? What happened? God damn it. He's back. No, it's not. It's a different guy. How long do
they stay like this for? Hold on. This guy is just... I just have this guy. I fucking DC'd him
too. Oh, just the fucking serial disconnector. There's somebody else over here now. There he is.
What? Hold on a second. Why could I not hogtie him? I died instantly.
He wasn't even looking. He just swung in a circle and hit me right in the head and hit me in the
temple. So what's over here? Where are they? I think they got DC'd. He used all the power of
his internet to hit me and then disconnected. So what am I chasing over here? There they are.
Oh no, that's very far away. No, that person's not even here. See? Let's head to town. Let's
try to make some friends. I want to lasso somebody in the bar and then throw them over
the balcony and then run away. Making new death train. Make friends in a rock star game. Good
luck. Yo, that's what I mean. Another few days or so. I feel like maybe like a week
and they get all the bugs ironed out. Come in with like a group of like three or four people
and just have some fun. I think that's gonna be the plan. What the hell was that? What? Why
did I let it come? Was I just not close enough? Oh, they can break free. So you gotta be real
close to even attempt it. Come here! It takes so long to get over to them. Press the melee
button? Well, I have to be close enough to do it.
Come here! I'm gonna get you with this. Oh! Can't break out of that. This is so odd. Wait, what?
Oh shit! Oh shit! Oh shit! Oh shit!
Oh, the disconnect.
I just ran into a stop sign. Imagine being on his end and watching that. Oh, I would be dead.
I would kill me. I would be dead. You'd have to resurrect me.
It reminds me of once when I kicked sand at somebody in elementary school
and turned to run and smacked into a pole.
I love that shit. It's so stupid. So okay, so you can break out if you're actually hogtied
and stowed. So what's the point of being hogtied and stowed if it lasts like 10 seconds? I would
love if that lasted like at least five minutes. I would so I would love to be hogtied and just
brought around and just... Yeah, I hear you. It'd be so funny.
All right, a rival gang is doing something. Imagine just being part of somebody else's
video game where you're just an NPC but you're not. I'm just having a conversation,
just hanging out. I'm just like, okay, I'm still here. All right, which one of these
rival gangs? Apparently, this is the rival gang I'm about to stop. I have to stop this
person here. Who? Who needs to be stopped? I don't see anybody. Maybe I wasn't fast enough.
Let's see if I can do it this time. No missions right now. Really? Because
you got nothing to do? You have nothing going on? Doesn't have any missions. Okay.
I guess that is a response. Yeah. So who we got? I can do another one of those story
missions. There seems to be a lot of people down here. Somebody right behind me.
Somebody overlooking the view down there. What does that marker mean? Index. What does it mean?
I don't understand what that means. Well, I'm gonna take the stagecoach to Saint Denis.
There's a lot of people down there. Let me spend all of my money to do that.
It's only three bucks. Never mind. We're good. There's a free revolver?
Well, I'll get it. I'll get it later. Can you rob people? I don't think you can just rob another
player. Unless it's a specific mission where you're trying to stop them. All right, here we
are. Saint Denis. Somebody this way. Somebody that way. This person's trying to go do this
mission, I think. So let's see if I can... No, maybe not. You got a mission?
All right, so I'm gonna be the target here.
Pick up the mail bag. Deliver the mail to a series of recipients within the time limit
to earn the full reward. Where's the mail? Where's the mail bag? Mail bag? Where's the mail bag?
I'm stuck in here now. I locked myself in with this fucking guy. What? How is that even possible?
The door is locked. Oh, I can't pick up the mail bag because I can't get out of the mail room.
I can't do it. I'm stuck here forever. Somebody help me. Somebody come help me.
How do I get someone to know that I'm in here? It makes me put it away immediately.
How do you whistle? Whistle? What's a whistle? What's a whistle? I can't punch him.
How do I whistle? I'm gonna... How do I invite everybody?
Somebody let the bird out. Respawn. I feel like I want to be in here though.
I feel like somebody could... This is gonna be fun. How do I invite people to my location?
Invites. Okay, this person here. Where's the nearest person? This person getting their
haircut right here. Damn it. How do I report myself? I can't. I'm stuck. Whatever.
Would have been kind of fun to be in here and be the guy that is locked in here.
How do I just respawn myself? Do I just go in and out? I'm just an NPC now. Quick join.
Just quick join again. Just wait out the 10 minutes and see what happens.
That's not a bad idea. That really isn't a bad idea.
Oh, I figured out what to do. Somebody help me. I'm stuck in here. Help me. Help.
Somebody just drove by. Somebody stop. I'm stuck in here. Somebody help me.
Help me. Help. Get in here and do something. Please. Help me. Open the door. See I...
I can't get out of here. See? Look. I tried everything. Help. Go get it. Go get some friend.
Go get some dynamite. Do anything. Blow this up. Help. No, don't go do a mission. Help me.
I'm in here. I tried the same thing. It doesn't work. There's a spot where I can shoot right
here. Got it. Where is it? Right here? Right there. This guy doesn't even care that I'm
just smashing the place up. Have them shoot through the window. Maybe they can shoot me
through the window. I got to get in the right place though. Time's counting down. I want to
see what happens. Okay. It needs to be perfect in the right position. No. A little bit more
to the right and right there. I was really hoping that I could shoot somebody from out
of there. If I knew that I could aim out the window like that and that guy stood there,
just put it between his eyes. And then his cause. Have him get angry to the point where
he needs to figure out a way to get him to get to me. At that point, he's going to throw a
dynamite into the window. Are Avans paying attention to what the players are doing? No.
It's just a problem with, for some reason. I don't know what it is with my west coast
connection to the Rockstar servers, but they don't want me on here. Rockstar's servers
for me just keep dropping. It's not my internet. My internet's fine. It's somehow
wherever I'm going doesn't like me there. Kill all the players to rise up the leaderboard the
higher you get, the more points you're worth. See if I can just play it. Rockstar, I hate your rat videos.
Well, I got to hear the... I got to at least hear it. Well, we're going on about six hours
here. It might be time to throw the towel in after like another couple attempts. Don't you
fucking... Well, the end of the stream voice. How good does it feel to say it's not my internet?
It actually feels pretty great. Do I have an opinion on online yet? No, I don't. I really don't.
It looks very fun. And from the random snippets of time that I get to be in it,
oh, it's great. It seems very cool once it's actually stable. He's doing the concerned
professional voice. Well, you know, you can give my opinion on the video game.
I'm going to sound at least somewhat professional so when somebody links this
to rockstar.com. All right, where are we right now? Is somebody over here?
Okay, I'm going to just go visit that person or try to do this mission. Hopefully I don't
get locked into the room, whatever the hell it is. I went around every inch of your
house except the one place to go in. Don't go inside, I'm gonna get trapped in here.
Why am I made out of plastic? My character is made out of plastic.
Android person.
I had them. I went away for a couple of days on a killing of a bastard.
Melting wax figurine.
I'll find them again. I've lost them before. You know, once was for three months it was.
That's how it goes, I guess. Anyway, where was it? Oh, yeah, yeah. Murder and mayhem.
Now to kill innocent folk myself gives me a real nasty feeling inside, but these bastards.
Where does this take place during the story? These bastards are. There's a stage. I'm actually
not sure. I heard a fella say it's laden with silver. I can't rob it. I can't guarantee
someone else hasn't gone before, but it'd be a rotten shame to let it pass, boy. Anyways,
armatures. All right, matchmaking time. Ambush and rob the stagecoach. Not matchmaking.
Stop the stagecoach and steal the loot bag within the time limit. I'm assuming there's
other people that are also doing this or trying to stop me from doing this. That would
be interesting. How far away is it? No, it's right there. That's convenient. Right in front
of me. Driver. Yeah, I'll try. There's so many people in there. There's a lot of people in here.
Full party in this wagon. Okay, target the passengers and take the loot. What?
They're going anywhere. Give me that loot bag. All right, get out of here.
Bag. All right, deliver the loot bag. Get out of the road. I can't stop. Get out of the road. I
can't stop. Rival players can steal the loot bag. They won't be doing that. That's damn, damn sure
about that. Well, he's dead. No, I'm too far away. I'm kind of in the middle of fucking nowhere.
Can you eat the bag? I don't think you can eat it. The horse is getting too tired.
Yeah, if I get disconnected here before turning this in, then I think that's a
throw the towel up in the air situation. That's what I think.
I got a bag and it's full of loot. Stuck in the loot bag. So what do I get for doing that?
One cent and two dollars. And you're telling me people can fight over that bag?
Why would you fight over that bag? This is my horse? Yeah, I can do a two bird.
Okay, let me go into the city center. Well, that would have been cool if somebody tried
to stop me. I think we're here alone. I don't think there's anybody in this session. God damn
it. That's why. Well, whoops. I think that's gonna be it. I think it's time to throw the
towel in. It's just not ready yet. At least for me to play it. Maybe you can stay connected
if you're from a part of the world or the country where you're able to stay connected.
A rock star does not want me to be connected to their game for some reason. I don't know why.
Sure is beautiful out here. I haven't dced all day. Yeah, I think it's just depending on what
region you're connecting to or where you're connecting from. King of the castle. All right,
a free roam event. Yes, I'll do it. Take me there. That's how I feel right now. Well,
thanks for coming to the stream. That's Red Dead Redemption 2 Online. You've been disconnected
from Red Dead Online due to a fault on Rockstar game services. Red Dead Offline. Yeah. Well,
it wasn't a total loss because there was some stuff to see there and hopefully over the next
day or two the service is brought up to the task of a higher standard to be able to be
allowed to connect to it. Stay connected to it. But that's going to be the end of the stream.
So again, let me make this very clear. Tomorrow night is the last day and night for you to do
a green screen submission from the green screen stream a couple weeks ago. If you want to put
something in, it's got to be at least 10 seconds. Can't be more than two minutes.
There are rules to read that are pinned in that Discord's channel.
Got to be a YouTube link because it's going to be going on a giant playlist
and that deadline is tomorrow. Tomorrow night. Submissions will not be considered
if they come in after tomorrow night. And with that, I will see you guys on Friday.
Friday, we're going to do Jackbox, which will lead us into Sunday, which will be the
green screen movie night. This should be the thumbnail and I may even stream on Saturday
as well. We might go Friday, Saturday, Sunday, depending on what's available because if Red Dead
works by Saturday, then maybe we'll do a thing where it's Friday is Jackbox, Saturday is
Red Dead Online. Maybe get a few friends, get a few people to join into a squad
and then Sunday will be movie night. So we'll give it a try. Do I have a schedule yet? I
don't. I don't. And I know it's been about three or four straight weeks here of streaming
in Vegas on Pacific time. And I'm like, yeah, I got a schedule. I don't know. Maybe I just won't.
Maybe I'll just stream because I look, here's the long and short of that. I've been streaming
more often since being here, right? Let me put the outro on so people don't think I'm
sticking around. I've been streaming more often. So I think that having the opportunity
to just kind of plan each week, because then it's like, oh, okay, so here's what's
gonna happen. I'm gonna do this on Monday, Tuesday, and then like Thursday, Friday.
Maybe I'll just stay with it for a while. I think the start time will always be the same.
It'll always be somewhere around 3 p.m. Pacific, between like 2 to 3 p.m., 3-ish p.m. Pacific.
But I'm not sure. I think when I have a schedule, I've talked about schedules before
and it's great and it helps, but I feel like I've been streaming more often because
when I have a schedule, oh, Tuesday, Thursday, and Friday, that's it. That's when I stream.
Just Tuesday, Thursday, and Friday. That's when I'm live. I'm not live. I don't do anything else.
Having no schedule allows me to kind of just do what I want and sometimes that
even means streaming four or five days a week. I don't know. I haven't come to
a conclusion yet, but for now I'm still going to be schedule-less for now.
But let's do the bits. Thanks for sticking around. I'll see you hopefully on
Friday for Jackbox 5 and then hope to see you again this weekend.
I'm going to take the offline screen down, but I got to change it before I do that because
I don't want it to just be like a default thing. I got to have that ready. It's going
to go and just edit it. But let's start back six plus hours ago here. Shrapnel or Shcrapnel,
thanks for the $1. Thanks also to Mostly Lost for the $1. Jerma, if all you did for the
rest of your career was just stream character creation sequences, I'd be perfectly happy.
I do love creating characters. It is a lot of fun. It is one of my favorite things,
but thank you. Thank you to Divus P for the three bucks coming in with a three spot.
Seems like Divus comes in every single stream with $3. Thank you for the $3. Thank you for
consistent $3 pretty much every stream and more than that. You've given way more than
that on some streams. Thank you. That's my go-to number. Thanks. Extra Cheesy, thanks
for the $1. Congrats. You made a Neanderthal cowboy. No, it's the Muppet from the taxicab,
but thanks a lot. Extra Cheesy for the $1. Lightning Rider had five community subs.
Thank you Lightning Rider. Lots of subscriptions and congratulations to the people that got those
subscriptions. Yen Wen, thank you Yen Wen. Yen Wenlin for the $1. I've been enjoying your red
dead streams, especially the two and a half hour death train bit you did. I decided to
draw a picture of you and Francis the Fox. You technically owe me like $200 now, but I'll
let it slide. Wait, what? This image is for you only. You can show chat, but please don't
share the link. Okay, this is for me only. The death train was a lot of fun. This image
is for you only. Private image. I'm going to screen cap it. He said you can show chat.
Here. No, that's, oh my God. That is, that is so detailed. All right. I'm going to have to,
I have to show this on stream. That's absolutely amazing. Let me pull it out here.
You got to look at this shit guys. Oh my God. I feel like I need to hang this in my
living room. That has to go over a mantle. Wow. Nice fucking job hanging in the living room.
I'm going to like just have a, I'm going to have a copy of that. It's going to be sitting
right here on my desk. But thank you. That's Yen Wen Lin. Yen Wen Lin for your incredibly
amazing piece of artwork. Thank you. That's for me only. That's for me only though.
Nobody else. Right onto the fridge. In every room. Hey, Dr. Clay, thanks for the one dollar.
Just keep it up. Yeah, let's go. I'm just going to keep it like over here. It's my new wallpaper.
Thank you, Dr. Clay for the one dollar. The guy who helped you with the muppet taxi thing
was Dragon Breath. Here's proof. We got time stamp. We got proof. Thank you. Thank
you for the help. Oh, that's me. Thank you, Dr. Clay. Thank you extra cheesy for the one
dollar. I don't need to understand. I just need to do. Jerma the Philosopher 2018. That's
accurate. Thank you extra cheesy again for the one dollar. You should make another character
that looks like a hipster and roleplay him as a time traveler. Why would I do that? Thank you
to Mulu Mulum for the one dollar. I love you, Jerma boy. You're the best fluffy Garfield
kitty. Thanks for the one dollar Mulum or Mullium. Renegade Panther. Thanks for the 15 dollars.
15 bucks from Renegade Panther. They say hey hey Jerma. 69. That's it. Thanks for the 15 dollars
Renegade. Appreciate it. 15 bucks. Got him. Hey WildFox. Thanks for the one dollar WildFox 73.
WildFox 173. Jerma currently watching my way through the VODs again and I'm super thankful
for your regular streaming. Since I can't work in winter as a landscaper, I have tons of
free time. I've been playing Fallout straight for longer than is probably good for me. What
are some good games you got obsessed with and fell in love with? There are a couple of very obvious
answers here. There's Diablo 2 is one of my favorite games. I have thousands of hours in
that game. Binding of Isaac is another one. If you just want to just fall into a video game
and just keep doing run after run and it's just something you always play, Binding of Isaac
is probably the best one I would say in this current kind of generation. I'd also tell you
to play Team Fortress 2. Maybe if you asked this two or three years ago, maybe I'd say that.
I just don't know what the state of the game is really at all. But if you've never played TF2
before, it's kind of just opening up an entire world of fun shit to do. Diablo 2,
he's a boomer. Diablo 2 is so good. It is so much fun. It's just the best, but it's just